<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>合作基金</title><description>Collab Fund 是企业家推动世界前进的主要资金来源。</description><link/> https://collabfund.com<atom:link href="https://collabfund.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><pubDate> Sun, 27 Aug 2023 07:39:08 -0400</pubDate><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 8 月 27 日星期日 07:39:08 -0400</lastbuilddate><generator>站点叶</generator><item><title>智能与智能</title><description>&lt;p>;这是生活中需要做出的重要区分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有些人很聪明，但没有一点聪明才智。他们在世界上取得成功的能力可能会在负面方面让你感到惊讶。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他人缺乏智力，但却才华横溢。他们的潜力会让你大吃一惊。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在极少数情况下，你会遇到既聪明又聪明的人。他们绕着每个人跑圈。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我对智力和聪明的定义是这样的：聪明的人理解技术细节，聪明的人理解情感细节。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;或者也许：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;智力&lt;/strong>;：良好的记忆力、逻辑性、数学能力、应试能力、遵守规则。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;聪明&lt;/strong>;：高度同理心，废话检测、组织、沟通技巧、说服力、社会意识、理解你的行为的后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两者都很重要。但两者的评估方式存在重大差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;学校擅长教授和测量智力，因此人们往往重视和渴望这一点。但几乎在任何领域，聪明才智才是获得长期回报的因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你无法像衡量 SAT 分数那样衡量同理心，因此简历受到更多重视也就不足为奇了。但谁更有可能在生活中取得成功——主要技能是记住公式的人，还是能够立即理解同事、客户、配偶和朋友的情绪的人？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是显而易见的。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;这就是为什么世界上充满了无处可去的聪明混蛋，以及努力学习微积分但继续过着成功、幸福生活的中等学生。大多数人会做出的最重要的决定是是否结婚、何时结婚以及与谁结婚。但学校里从来没有教过这一点——怎么可能呢？你无法将其提炼为一个公式，或者一个放之四海而皆准的答案。这是一个需要大量智慧和很少智慧的决定。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这里的核心是认识到人不是电子表格。他们是情绪化、荷尔蒙旺盛、信息误导、追求地位、缺乏安全感的生物，竭尽全力度过这一天。因此，如果您必须在理解世界在理论上应该如何运作与它在实践中实际上如何运作之间做出选择，那么倾向于后者。就像历史学家威尔·杜兰特曾经说过的那样：“逻辑是人类的发明，可能会被宇宙忽视。”太聪明了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个极端的例子。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;乔治·索罗斯说，只要他看到泡沫，他就会冲进去买。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你是一个聪明人，这可能看起来很疯狂。为什么你会故意购买一项被高估的投资？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但如果你是个聪明人，也许这是有道理的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你知道泡沫可能会变得更大并持续下去。比大多数人想象的要长。你了解人们的想法，你知道投资者会在一段时间内继续疯狂买入，不是因为数字有意义，而是因为他们的邻居变得富有，他们会陷入嫉妒和错误决策的黑洞。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;“这并非非理性，”索罗斯说。 （但是请不要尝试这个；你可能不像索罗斯那么聪明）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这里还有一些其他难以衡量的“聪明”特征。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;接受那些与你过着不同生活的人想要不同的东西并且会以不同的方式看待世界。看起来像是辩论的事情往往只是具有不同生活经历的人互相交谈。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;亨利·福特说：“如果有任何一个成功的秘诀，那就在于能够获得另一个的能力”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;纯粹聪明的人会发现这一点很难理解，因为如果你认为每个问题都有一个正确的答案，你就会坚持进行更多的辩论，直到对方同意你的观点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于世界上大多数问题，“正确”的答案就是最能促进你个人福祉的答案，这需要聪明才智&lt;em>;并且符合您对世界运作方式的体验。由于每个人都有不同的需求和经历，因此前进并完成工作的唯一方法就是容忍并与某些观点合作，即使您不同意它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你能做到这一点，结果就是，是与你不同意的人相处的技巧。这是不可或缺的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;认识到友善并不意味着软弱 - 这实际上是一种随着时间的推移获得合作的自私策略。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对冲长期资本管理基金 (Long Term Capital Management) 在 1998 年崩溃，威胁要摧毁整个华尔街。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为回应，14 家华尔街银行介入，集体救助该基金并平息恐慌。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;每家大银行都参与了救助——贝尔斯登除外，据说贝尔斯登的首席执行官吉米·凯恩对这一请求回应说：“他妈的没办法”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;十年后，贝尔斯登本身也摇摇欲坠。在边缘。猜猜还有多少华尔街银行愿意向吉米·凯恩伸出援助之手？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;查理·芒格曾经指出，本杰明·富兰克林并没有说诚实是最好的道德 - 他说这是最好的道德&lt;em>;政策。从长远来看，它会&lt;em>;帮助&lt;/em>;您，并让您处于最佳位置，为您赚到最多的钱&lt;/em>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有一个推论善待每个人有两个原因。一是道德，二是自私。从道德上讲，你应该这样做，因为你有同理心。自私地说，你应该这样做，因为你很容易低估你最终可以依靠多少人来帮助你，而且只有保持他们的好感，你才会获得他们的合作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;多-纪律思维&lt;/strong>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我在 Markel 董事会任职。最近有人问我从 Markel 的首席执行官汤姆·盖纳 (Tom Gayner) 那里学到了什么——他确实是近几十年来最有成就的投资者之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的回答是，无论我们谈论什么，汤姆都有一个完美的解决方案。完全不相关的事物的类比。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果我们谈论保险准备金，汤姆会说，“你知道，这让我想起了音乐之声中的场景&lt;/em>; ……”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果我们谈论市场估值，汤姆可能会说，“这有点像温斯顿·丘吉尔过去常说的……”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在每种情况下，这个类比都适用于这是当前主题的核心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这不仅仅是有趣的聊天。我认为汤姆是一位优秀的投资者，因为他了解世界是如何运作的——将各个领域之间的点联系起来——这比仅仅了解金融要广泛得多。了解金融的人可能很聪明，但了解世界如何运作需要智慧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;太多聪明人在自己的领域陷入孤立，忘记了世界是如何相互联系的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;强>;真正的独立思考。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;凯文·凯利有一个伟大的想法，即只有当你对某些主题的看法无法从你对其他主题的看法中预测出来时，你才能独立思考。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;许多观点是可以预测的，因为真正的独立思考是如此罕见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;告诉我你对移民的看法，我大概可以猜到你对堕胎的看法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;告诉我我是你投票选总统的人，我大概可以猜出你认为今天的经济是强还是弱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你对某些话题的看法可以从不相关的陈述中预测出来时，你很有可能已经外包了部分内容真正的独立思考很少见，因为大多数人宁愿舒服，也不愿正确，而且知道自己是部落中信誉良好的成员会让人感到安慰。独立思考并不意味着你是对的，因为大众通常非常接近准确。反对部落也可以被解释为傲慢——突然间你可能看起来像吉米·凯恩。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是诗人拉迪亚德·吉卜林写道，“如果你能与人群交谈并保持你的美德，或者与国王同行，也不会失去平庸”，你就走上了通往伟大的道路。测试这一点的一种方法是，是否有人在某些话题上你同意，但在其他话题上你不同意。如果有人在每个话题上你都同意他的观点，那么要小心了。如果有人在每个话题上你的观点都不同意，那就要更加小心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为我自己的狗 - 她是一个很好的女孩 - 一半的时间都很疯狂，所以当人们可以时我会关闭不要在他们最喜欢的政治家或投资大师身上找出任何错误。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;认识到最好的故事会获胜。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不是最好的答案。不是准确的答案。这不是人们需要听到的答案。谁能引起人们的注意并点头同意，谁就是胜利者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你只是聪明，你可能会集中精力寻找精确的真相。如果你很聪明，你就会集中精力围绕这一真理传递有效的信息，并意识到如果你不能让人们关注它，那么最有力的真理也没有任何好处。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;一位医生曾经告诉我，医学专家和医疗保健专家之间是有区别的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;医学专家知道教科书上的所有正确答案。他们可以进行精确的诊断，并了解所有最新的治疗方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;医疗保健专家明白，从患者的角度来看，药物是令人生畏的、令人困惑的、昂贵且耗时的。在您向患者解决这一现实之前，您诊断或开出的任何处方都不重要，因为即使是完美的解决方案对于不遵循它的患者来说也没有什么区别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这与投资类似。对冲基金经理凯尔·巴斯对此进行了很好的总结，他说：“保持信念很容易。留住投资者更加困难。”最成功的投资者往往是沟通专家，因为在不可避免的业绩不佳时期，你必须迫使投资者坚持你。巴菲特。红杉。甚至先锋；他们非常熟练（故意如此），能够传递超出数字的有效信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;沃伦·巴菲特 - 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;查理·芒格 - 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; Seth Klarman – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;John Bogle – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Joel Greenblatt – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Howard Marks – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;我不认为这是巧合。这些投资者的写作能力让他们能够有效地讲述自己的故事、设定期望并让投资者放心。这使得他们的投资者更有可能在困难时期留下来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这一点很难教。讲故事是一种软性的情感技能。在情报中找不到它。它存在于智能中。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:49:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/intelligent-vs-smart/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/intelligent-vs-smart/</guid></item><item><title>关于重大决策的一些故事</title><description>&lt;p>;1964 年，沃伦·巴菲特拥有一家前景黯淡的老牌工业公司的股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该公司首席执行官认为巴菲特的收购对其工作保障构成威胁，并提出以溢价回购股票。巴菲特急于出售，厌倦了看着企业陷入困境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两人达成协议：公司将以每股 11 1/2 美元的价格购买巴菲特的全部股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;巴菲特交易正式确定后不久就收到一封信。该公司仍会购买他的全部股票，但价格为每股 11 3/8 美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“这真的让我很兴奋，”巴菲特回忆道。 “你知道，这家伙实际上是想从握着我的手说这就是交易中获得八分之一的分数。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;巴菲特质问首席执行官，后者辩称从来没有达成协议。首先。这让他更加愤怒。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，巴菲特没有出售股票，而是开始尽可能多地购买股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他最终购买了该公司三分之一以上的股份。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;传记作家爱丽丝·施罗德 (Alice Schroeder) 写道，最重要的是，巴菲特购买更多公司股票的动机是为了将其粘在试图从他每股 12 美分身上榨取的首席执行官身上。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这家公司——伯克希尔哈撒韦公司——成为巴菲特的杰作。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;类似的故事：1955 年，刚毕业的大学毕业生张忠谋 (Morris Chang) 获得了两份工作：一份在福特，月薪 479 美元，另一份在福特工作，月薪 479 美元。在电气公司 Sylvania 工作，每月 480 美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;福特似乎是更好的机会，但 Chang 要求招聘人员与他的 Sylvania 报价相匹配 - 仅仅&lt;em>;每月 1 美元&lt;/em>;多。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;福特拒绝了。因此，张在 Sylvania 接受了这份工作，在那里他了解了不断发展的晶体管和微芯片领域，并成为了专家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;张最终创立了台湾半导体，如今该公司的价值近 5000 亿美元，生产世界上 60% 的芯片。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;亨利·福特知道汽车将改变世界。世界其他地方则不太确定。在 1900 年代初期，汽车对于富人来说就像是吵闹的玩具。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但玩具很有趣，所以公众疯狂的一件事就是赛车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;福特没有兴趣在赛车领域——他的愿景是为大众制造一辆廉价、优质的汽车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但他知道自己需要赢得投资者和公众的支持，因此他制造了世界上最好的赛车，并且1902 年，它击败了卫冕冠军。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“那是我的第一场比赛，它带来了人们唯一愿意阅读的广告，”福特写道。他在全国闻名。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关注度足以从投资者那里筹集资金，八个月后福特汽车公司成立。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一切都是销售。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr / >; &lt;p>;女演员格洛丽亚·斯旺森 (Gloria Swanson) 于 1927 年拒绝了一份价值 100 万美元的电影合同。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;制片厂感到震惊，并询问她为何犹豫不决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“我会是第二个或第二个“电影史上第三位签下百万美元合同的人，但我是第一个拒绝的人，”她说。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这句话成为头条新闻，并帮助她变得更加出名，这，我假设，这就是重点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是职业建议中最极端的例子，“不要试图成为最好的。成为唯一的一个。”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;当已故作家克里斯托弗·希钦斯 (Christopher Hitchens) 与食道癌作斗争时，正如彼得·阿蒂亚 (Peter Attia) 博士所写，化疗的残酷副作用似乎“再持续几年的公平贸易” ”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但当希钦斯接近尾声时，他写道：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我连续躺了好几天，徒劳地试图推迟我本来可以拥有的那一刻。吞下。每次我吞咽口水时，一股地狱般的疼痛就会顺着喉咙涌上来，最终感觉就像是骡子踢在我后腰上一样。 ……然后我突然产生了一个流氓想法：如果我事先被告知这一切，我会选择接受治疗吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;肯尼迪和杰奎琳·肯尼迪没有&#39;关系很好。 1955 年，他们结婚两年后，杰克告诉他的父亲乔·肯尼迪，他想要离婚。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;乔回答道：“你疯了。有一天你会成为总统。这会毁了一切。离婚是不可能的。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;杰克重申他和杰基并不幸福。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他的父亲反驳道：“你就不能明白这并不重要吗？你真的是？唯一重要的是人们认为你是什么样的人！”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;婚姻得以维持。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;一切都是销售。&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;二战期间，糖、牛奶和鸡蛋都是配给的。许多食品公司适应使用不同的、通常质量较低的原料来度过难关。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;See&#39;s Candy 非常注重质量，拒绝降低标准。在一个假期期间，该公司关门歇业，并在店内贴出标语，上面写着：“已售完。购买战争债券作为圣诞节礼物。”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;美国 1942 年 11 月入侵北非的决定极不受欢迎，甚至在罗斯福总统最亲密的顾问中也是如此。几乎所有方面都认为，部队还没有准备好，计划仓促，任务过于雄心勃勃。高级将领们认为再等几个月并没有什么坏处。当时的将军德怀特·艾森豪威尔预测，罗斯福仓促的入侵命令将成为“历史上最黑暗的一天”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;入侵奏效了。但战后回顾，总统的顾问们想知道他为何如此着急。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一种解释是，美国人民对珍珠港事件和德国宣战后发生的任何事情感到焦躁不安。 。罗斯福自己的儿子给他写了一封信，说他和他的战友们只是坐着，“没有任何乐趣……只是在等待轮到我们。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;抓紧这些痒痒可能已经取代了军事战略。&lt;/p>; &lt;时任陆军参谋长乔治·马歇尔在战后表示：“民主国家的领导人必须让人民开心。这听起来可能是一个错误的词，但它传达了想法。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大多数决策不是在电子表格上做出的，您只需将数字相加，就会弹出一个合理的答案。其中有一个难以量化、难以解释的人为因素，看似脱离了最初的目标，但影响力却最大。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:15:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-stories-about-big-decisions/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-stories-about-big-decisions/</guid></item><item><title>白炽灯泡的终结：技术和市场的失败</title><description>&lt;p>;拜登政府最近实施了禁止销售传统白炽灯泡的禁令，完成了 2007 年立法中长达数年的逐步淘汰计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然更节能的 LED 灯泡将为消费者节省电费账单并减少碳排放，在某种程度上，这种转变代表了技术和市场的失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从可持续发展的角度来看，白炽灯泡具有邪恶的品质，会浪费大量能源作为热量。然而，它们提供更温暖、更有吸引力的光线，对眼睛更舒适。荧光灯和早期 LED 灯泡在质量和对消费者的吸引力方面从未达到预期。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;市场未能刺激解决这一困境的创新——一种更好的兼顾可持续性和需求的灯泡。因此，现在政府监管成为强制变革的杠杆，剥夺了消费者的选择权。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://collabfund.com/uploads/unnamed-fd7d8f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;unnamed-fd7d8f .jpg&quot; />;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;批评者会认为这是政府对个人自由和决策的无理越权。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在大型清洁能源项目等领域，考虑到资本，政府的参与是有道理的要求。但企业无法创造出具有普遍吸引力的节能灯泡，代表了技术和自由市场的失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;需要的不是严厉的监管，而是更好地将商业激励与可持续发展结合起来的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许碳定价或节能灯泡的回扣会有机地刺激所需的创新。自由市场成功地推动了创新，使其他领域的商业激励和消费者需求保持一致，例如拼车和拼车。 Uber、Lyft 和 Waze 等公司创建了可以减少交通、污染和停车需求的平台，同时允许公司从通过应用程序产生的费用和广告收入中获利。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过技术改进的结合（即GPS）和精明的营销，拼车和拼车并不被视为对消费者的牺牲，也不是政府的强制要求，而是一种让生活更轻松的优质产品。类似的双赢解决方案应该在不需要政府禁令的情况下有机地出现在灯泡领域。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这次错失的机会凸显了对创造性解决方案的需求，而这些解决方案不能仅仅依靠政府的大棒来推动变革。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;向更可持续的产品过渡应该让消费者感觉是一种升级，而不是一种牺牲。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;需要做更多的工作来更好地协调消费者的愿望、商业利益和社会需求。真正的创新将这三者结合在一起。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:20:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/the-end-of-the-incandescent-light-bulb-a-failure-of-technology-and-markets/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/the-end-of-the-incandescent-light-bulb-a-failure-of-technology-and-markets/</guid></item><item><title>如何阅读：大量输入和强大的过滤器</title><description>&lt;p>;我的阅读策略是开始阅读尽可能多的书，但读完其中的几本书。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;几年前，我听查理·芒格说过“大多数书我读完第一章就不会读完。我不会被坏书所困扰，”这句话一直困扰着我。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你坚持读完你开始读的每一本书，那么阅读就是一件苦差事，因为大多数书要么 a) 在简介，b) 不适合你，或 c) 不适合任何人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;费力地读完这些书的最后一页（这可能是在学校早期养成的习惯）可以将阅读变成相当于 10-一个小时的工作会议什么也没做，每个人都很无聊。一旦你从这个角度看待阅读，你拿起另一本书的意愿就会减弱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这当然是悲剧性的。马克·吐温说：“不读好书的人比不会读好书的人没有优势。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认识的每个聪明人都是贪婪的读者，他们也说“每个聪明人都喜欢阅读”。我认识的一个人是一位贪婪的读者。”这条规则几乎没有例外，这令人震惊。大学学费为每年 25,000 美元，每堂课大约为 100 美元。好书——有时是同一位教授写的——可以花十五美元购买，并且可以提供数倍的改变生活的见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这两者之间的冲突——大多数书不需要阅读直到最后，但有些书可以改变你的生活 - 意味着你需要两件事才能从阅读中获得很多收获：&lt;strong>;大量输入和强大的过滤器&lt;/strong>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你只挑选你确信你会喜欢的书，你会限制自己阅读相同主题的相同作者的书。它为确认偏见提供了新鲜的氧气，并限制了你将不同领域和不同文化之间的点联系起来的能力。最好对你愿意尝试的书设定一个较低的标准，即使是最微弱的兴趣也足以让你成功。 Kindle 样品是免费的，所以借口很少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦你的办公桌上充满了输入，你就必须拿出过滤器。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;它应该是无情的，不留任何俘虏并且毫不留情。与约会类似，一本你在关注了 10 分钟后就不喜欢的书几乎不可能有幸福的结局。猛地关上它并继续前进。如果你读了三页书就退出了，就像你拒绝与刚认识的令你烦恼的人进行 10 小时的约会一样，你也不算失败。海里有很多鱼。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这不仅仅适用于读书。对于所有类型的数据、研究、对话和学习都是如此。如果你的大脑不被大量的输入淹没，你就会陷入你个人经历过的狭小世界中。但是，如果没有强大的过滤器，您会因选择而不知所措，并因无所作为而陷入瘫痪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;良好的阅读过滤器更多的是艺术而不是科学。您必须找到一个适合您的。更重要的一点是，找到正确信息的最高几率来自于让自己被信息淹没，但很快就能说，“不是这样的。”&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:57:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/how-to-read-lots-of-inputs-and-a-strong-filter/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/how-to-read-lots-of-inputs-and-a-strong-filter/</guid></item><item><title>一切都是周期性的</title><description>&lt;p>;法国地质学家最近发现喜马拉雅山脉在800年前曾遭受过大规模山体滑坡。规模可能是轻描淡写的：滑坡移动的泥土足以掩埋曼哈顿，高度与帝国大厦一样高。安纳普尔纳四号峰曾经是世界五座最高的山峰之一。今天，在滑坡从顶部削去三分之一英里后，它只是很大。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;令人惊奇的是，滑坡并不是由冰川侵蚀山体造成的，而冰川通常是侵蚀山体的原因。山的高度受到检查。安纳普尔纳四号峰太大了。正如任何建造过沙堡的人都知道的那样，总有一天，整个沙堡会自行崩溃，被自身垂直贪婪的重量压垮。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一切都是周期性的，而且是容易的事情忽略周期性的是，它不需要任何外力将其推向另一个方向。变大的行为足以让你变得更小，而无需受到任何人或任何事的推动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你认为风险是由外力引起的，而实际上风险是由外力造成的时，生活中就会犯很多错误。在没有任何外部帮助的情况下，你自己的成功就足以让你失望。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这适用于很多事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在他 1944 年出版的书中&lt;em>;我们为什么不从历史中学习？&lt;/em>;，BH Liddell Hart 写道，为什么每次战争结束后，人们都会说：“那太可怕了，我们再也不会这样做了”，但几年后却发现自己又上了战场：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我们从历史中得知，完全的胜利从来不是通过胜利者一直期待的结果——良好而持久的和平来完成的。因为胜利总是播下新战争的种子，因为胜利在战败者中滋生了平反和复仇的渴望，因为胜利催生了新的对手。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;胜利总是播下新的种子。新战争的种子&lt;/em>;。这是一个很奇怪的概念，但它显然是正确的。罗伊·鲍迈斯特在他的《邪恶》一书中写道：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;第一次世界大战比欧洲人记忆中甚至想象中的任何事情都要可怕得多，它产生了持久而持久的影响。深刻的心理影响。胜利者得出的结论是，不能再有战争了。失败者得出的结论是，必须有另一场战争来扭转局面：不能让如此多的牺牲白费。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;这几乎就像胜利越大，胜算就越高。未来的战争。第一次世界大战导致了第二次世界大战，导致了冷战，导致了俄罗斯入侵乌克兰，等等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;风险较低，但我认为类似的事情也会发生在公司身上。你变得越大、越成功，就越难保持成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;上个世纪的大赢家是什么？通用汽车、通用电气、IBM、诺基亚、花旗集团、柯达、美国钢铁公司……不难列出一系列在自身压力下崩溃的先前巨头。公平地说，对于每个人来说，过去的成功通过权利、竞争对手之间的嫉妒和官僚主义膨胀直接导致了未来的失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在阅读这篇关于当今不可触及的巨人的最新文章，&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.businessinsider.com/amazon-leaders-aws-day-two-mindset-2023-7&quot;>;亚马逊&lt;/a>;：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;在亚马逊，它总是应该是“第一天，“新时代的黎明，客户至上，大胆的赌注得到支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;毫不奇怪，现在它是一个科技和零售巨头，维持这一点变得更加困难。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; >;员工抱怨繁文缛节、臃肿和官僚主义。面对新的财务现实，首席执行官安迪·贾西 (Andy Jassy) 在对待亚马逊的赌注时表现得非常严格。该公司面临着巨大的外部压力，包括最近联邦贸易委员会的诉讼……成为价值 1 万亿美元的革命者很难。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Slack 前首席执行官 &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter .com/volodarik/status/1665854827224498177?s=20&quot;>;最近解释了&lt;/a>;成功公司膨胀的一个令人着迷的原因。争夺注意力的管理者经常根据一个简单的指标对自己进行排名：有多少员工向他们报告。那么，激励就是雇佣大量的人——即使他们几乎没有什么工作要做——这样经理就可以说，“400 个人向我汇报”，这表明了他们所谓的价值和重要性。你只能在一家拥有如此多的资金和如此成功的公司来实现这一目标，以至于令人讨厌的预算都得到批准。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这有什么教训？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;小心你的愿望吗？ &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;保持警惕？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在背后小心？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;是的，但最重要的是一切都是周期性的。平静孕育着疯狂的种子，成长孕育着衰落的种子，成功孕育着失落的种子。一切都是周期性的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在个人层面上也是如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作者罗伯特·格林写道：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;永远不要愚蠢到相信你通过炫耀使您超越他人的品质来激起钦佩。让别人意识到自己的劣势，只会激起不愉快的钦佩或嫉妒……&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有什么比胜利更令人陶醉的了，也没有什么比胜利更危险的了。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p >;确实如此——你认为自己在强调自己的成就，但你所做的往往是在强调别人相对缺乏的成就，这会滋生嫉妒而不是钦佩。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一件棘手的事情。你越成功，人们就越容易怨恨你的成功。即使有人说：“我为你感到高兴！”，而且他们是真心实意的，你的成功——也许是升职或加薪——也会让他们自己的职业生涯变得更加清晰，从而提高他们的期望，并有可能离开他们对自己的感觉更糟。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当那些曾经渴望帮助你的人将来不再热情时，支持的减少可能会反过来产生影响。说唱歌手德雷克说：“当你为某件事而努力时，人们更喜欢你，而不是当你拥有它时。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后是金钱和野心之间的联系。威廉·范德比尔特（William Vanderbilt）曾经说过，拥有很多钱“就像可卡因对道德的毁灭一样，对野心的毁灭。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幸福可能是另一个周期性的东西。我喜欢轮胎大王哈维·费尔斯通的这个细节，想知道他在变得富有和成名之前过着简单的生活：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;有时似乎回到那些简单的日子可能会更好，人们可能会从不太复杂的生活中获得更多。但这是不可能的。人随着繁荣而改变。我们都认为我们应该过简单的生活，然后我们发现我们已经养成了一千个我们完全没有意识到的小习惯，因为它们是我们存在的一部分——而这些习惯并不存在于简单的生活中。 。 There is no going back-except as a broken man.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Maybe that&#39;s the cycle: Start with a dream, accomplish that dream, then what was previously considered a dream becomes a new baseline, and the gaze of your ambition moves to the next dream. Inadequacy, hard work, elation. Inadequacy, hard work, elation. Everything is cyclical.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;—&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To some extent these cycles are inescapable. That&#39;s especially true for the economy, the stock market, and other social trends. So much of long-term success relies on accepting and preparing for cyclicality versus assuming it can be prevented.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the individual level, I think cyclicality can be managed around the edges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Shane Parrish &lt;a href=&quot;https://fs.blog/entropy/&quot;>;once described&lt;/a>; the difference between passive and active stability. A rock is passively stable – it&#39;ll keep its form without any intervention. Marriage is not. It can be stable over time, but it requires constant work, compromise, and maintenance to keep it intact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most things in your life are, at best, actively stable. Left alone they&#39;ll follow the natural path of cyclicality. But if there&#39;s constant intervention and management – managing your expectations, managing your reputation, managing how you advertise yourself and who you surround yourself with – you have at least a shot at keeping something good going for the longest period of time.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:19:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/everything-is-cyclical/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/everything-is-cyclical/</guid></item><item><title> Rich and Anonymous</title><description> &lt;p>;I think there&#39;s an “ideal” net worth for everyone, when money not only stops bringing pleasure but becomes a social liability. And that number is probably lower than most people think.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Business Insider recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/lottery-winners-lost-everything-2017-8#gerald-muswagon-ended-up-feeling-sorry-for-partying-8&quot;>;did a story&lt;/a>; of lottery winners who lost it all (people love the schadenfreude of these tales).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A common denominator of the stories is that lottery winnings have a high degree of, let&#39;s call it, social debt – friends, family, and strangers who feel entitled to ask, beg, and steal in a way that leaves the winners not only broke, but socially exploited.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the winners explained:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;After winning $3.9 million in October 1985 and $1.4 million four months later, Ms. Adams found that she no longer had the privilege of privacy. “I was known,” she said, “and I couldn&#39;t go anywhere without being recognized.”&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;A subtle problem with money is that assets are easy to measure but liabilities can be hidden. Measuring lottery winnings is simple: $3.9 million, down to the penny. But how do you measure losing your privacy? Or the nagging doubt that some friends only like you for your money? That&#39;s way harder.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I once spoke to a group of NBA rookies. The topic was how to avoid the tragedy of athletes who make a fortune in their 20s and are bankrupt by age 30.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One player mentioned something I thought was so important. He said most outsiders think athletes go broke because they spent their money on jewelry and cars. Sometimes that&#39;s true, but the most common cause is social debt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“When you grow up in poverty and then you&#39;re making $10 million when you&#39;re 22, that&#39;s not your money,” he said. “That&#39;s mom&#39;s money, dad&#39;s money, grandma&#39;s money, cousin&#39;s money, friends&#39; money. You can&#39;t just tell them &#39;I got mine, good luck to you all.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Buying themselves a mansion wasn&#39;t the problem; it was buying a modest house for their fifth cousin who they&#39;d never met but felt obligated to help that pushed athletes to bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These might seem like rich-people problems. But social debt creeps up everywhere for normal people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I used to ride the Amtrak train from DC to New York. The train has a “quiet car” – a section where everyone is supposed to be quiet so you can sleep or get some work done. People use the quiet car because they want serenity, but it was astounding how often it backfired. When you expect quiet, you become ultra-sensitive to the slightest noise. If someone in the quiet car speaks in more than a whisper, the entire car plunges into a state of deep irritation. I&#39;d bet that sitting in the “peaceful” quiet car actually leaves people with higher blood pressure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A similar thing often happens when people buy nice stuff.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You didn&#39;t mind when your old car was dirty or dinged – but now that you bought a nicer car you can&#39;t stand it when it gets muddy, and you lose your mind when someone scratches it in the parking lot.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you bought a new, bigger, house, you thought you&#39;d be happier. But then you realize that the reason you wanted a nicer house was to socially compete with other people who had nice houses. So once you got a nice house, you just started dreaming about even nicer homes. Once you accept that having the nicest home in your social group is your goal, it becomes not only an obsession but a game that cannot be won, since the group you compare yourself to shifts with each salary increase you receive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My theory is that the more money people have, the more social debt they tend to be burdened with.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The point is not to say you should avoid nice cars and nice homes – I like both. It&#39;s a realization that once money goes from being a tool you can use to make yourself happy to a symbol of what other people measure you by, you are buried in a kind of social debt that&#39;s hard to measure but has a real impact on your happiness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thoreau once explained: “The cost of a thing is the amount of what I will call life which is required to be exchanged for it, immediately or in the long run.”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;I once did some consulting for a family that&#39;s worth $8 billion. If you Googled their name, nothing came up. No Forbes list, no gala photos, no profiles, no Wikipedia pages … nothing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was intentional.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;They figured out what so many other people fail to recognize: The way you maximize enjoying your money is by eliminating social debt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;They had total freedom, privacy, and independence. They chose their friends carefully and gave money away anonymously. It may have been their most valuable asset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It reminded me of what Naval once said: The best position to be in is rich &lt;em>;and anonymous&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:01:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/rich-and-anonymous/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/rich-and-anonymous/</guid></item><item><title> Our Investment in Verse</title><description> &lt;p>;Electricity makes the world go round.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Generating all that electricity also drives 25% of the world&#39;s emissions, largely because we burn fossil fuels to get electricity. So to avoid catastrophic climate change, organizations must transition to clean power as quickly as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies, aware that energy market volatility and increasingly evident climate change leave their operations highly exposed, are ready for the switch. A few corporations have helped catalyze the clean energy market by creating Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs), but it is very difficult for most companies today to secure clean power.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If procuring and managing clean energy remains highly complex, time-consuming, and expensive, most organizations will struggle to make the transition. Even those that can afford to procure clean power today still rely on manual processes and outdated spreadsheets that are ill-suited for delivering robust, data-driven analysis. Carbon-free energy purchases won&#39;t scale on Excel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But what if it was possible to purchase hundreds of megawatts on an intuitive software platform that helped manage everything for you?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Enter &lt;a href=&quot;https://verse.inc/&quot;>;Verse&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Verse is building a SaaS platform called Aria that leverages generative AI to provide an end-to-end solution for organizations to buy, manage, and report on clean power at a fraction of the time and cost required today.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the first time, companies can define their clean power goals, design and procure a portfolio of clean energy assets, manage and optimize those assets, and report on portfolio performance — all from one platform. Overall, we expect that this can reduce the cost of buying clean power by up to 70%, democratizing carbon-free energy for all companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the Aria platform, organizations can set parameters that target specific goals (eg, cost, emissions, or hourly matching), hedge exposure to fossil fuel price fluctuations, optimize clean power asset management, and deliver verifiable reports on portfolio performance. The platform can help companies at all stages of their emissions reduction journey, from transacting power purchase agreements (PPAs) to optimizing for 100% renewable energy, emissionality, or 24/7 CFE (carbon-free energy).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At &lt;a href=&quot;https://collabfund.com/&quot;>;Collab Fund&lt;/a>;, we are proud to work alongside &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/seyed-h-madaeni-ph-d-5697a749/&quot;>;Seyed Madaeni&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/matt-penfold/&quot;>;Matt Penfold&lt;/a>;, and the entire Verse team. We are particularly excited to support them in this seed round along with Coatue, Twine Ventures, My Climate Journey, First Minute Capital, Future Positive, and Incite.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By enabling organizations to reduce their energy costs with clean power and dramatically simplifying the clean power procurement process, Verse&#39;s Aria platform will help scale decarbonization across industries.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 08:58:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/our-investment-in-verse/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/our-investment-in-verse/</guid></item><item><title> Smart Things Smart People Said</title><description> &lt;p>;A few lines I came across recently that I liked:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The appetite for applause counts amongst the lowest of human character traits.” – Jan-Willem van der Rijt&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“A great way to understand yourself is to seriously reflect on everything you find irritating in others.” – Kevin Kelly&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People in their 30s know where the world is going because they&#39;re going to do it. I&#39;m in my 80s so I have no idea.” – Daniel Kahneman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I&#39;m at the stage in life where I stay out of arguments. Even if you say 1+1=5, you&#39;re right. Have fun.” – Keanu Reeves&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If you find the right balance between desperation and fear you can make people do anything.” – Trevor Noah&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The happiness of most people is not ruined by great catastrophes or fatal errors, but by the repetition of slowly destructive little things.” – Ernest Dimnet&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Happiness is that feeling you get right before you need more happiness” – Don Draper&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Jokes of the proper kind, properly told, can do more to enlighten questions of politics, philosophy, and literature than any number of dull arguments.” – Isaac Asimov&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Inherited wealth is as certain a death to ambition as cocaine is to morality.” – William Vanderbilt&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“It doesn&#39;t take much to convince us that we are smart and healthy, but it takes a lot of facts to convince us of the opposite.” – Dan Gilbert&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Insecurity is the mother of greed.” – Will Durant&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The greater the ignorance, the greater the dogmatism.” – William Osler&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Don&#39;t try to fix people. Just set boundaries.” – Shibetoshi Nakamoto (pseudonymous)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Better to get your dopamine from improving your ideas than having them validated. “ – Nat Friedman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“It&#39;s good to have people in your life who you don&#39;t want to disappoint.” – Warren Buffett&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“More information is just a form of procrastination.” – Russ Roberts&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Injuries done to us by others tend to be acute; the self-inflicted ones tend to be chronic.” – Nassim Taleb&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The thing that is least perceived about wealth is that all pleasure in money ends at the point where economy becomes unnecessary. The man who can buy anything he covets, without any consultation with his banker, values nothing that he buys.” – William Dawson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The most accurate metric for your love of someone is how you feel about their flaws.” – Mark Manson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Assuming you rise to the top, please remember: what made you great may not be appropriate for the next generation.” – Richard Hamming&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Nobody gives a shit about anything except how they feel.” – Will Smith&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“In the soil of every satisfaction sprout the seeds of discontent.” – Dee Hock&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Thousands of people don&#39;t like what I do. Fortunately, millions do.” – James Patterson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Recognize what you like about somebody. Admire it as a quality separate from that particular person, rather than confusing it with him or her. What you admire about them are qualities that exist separately from the particular (and therefore flawed) example that they constitute.” – Darren Brown&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People might refuse to believe something even if it can help them live a little longer, if believing it will make them live a lot sadder.” – Cass Sunstein&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I believe pretty strongly that your overarching aim in life and work is to always be making yourself obsolete.” – Tim Hanson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Your capacity for gratitude is inversely proportional to your sense of entitlement.” – Mark Brooks&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Your calendar is a better measure of success than your bank account.” – James Clear&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If people want happiness so badly, why don&#39;t they attempt to understand their false beliefs? First, because it never occurs to them to see them as false or even as beliefs. They see them as facts and reality, so deeply have they been programmed.” – Anthony DiMello&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The purpose of life is to experience things for which you will later experience nostalgia.” – FedSpeak&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Nothing in life is as important as you think it is when you are thinking about it.” – Kahneman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The way to be safe is to never be secure.” – Ben Franklin&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If we can&#39;t laugh at something, we can&#39;t think rationally about it.” – Clay Johnson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“There are two types of stability: active and passive … People get in trouble when they confuse the two types of stability. Relationships, for example, require attention and care. If you assume that your relationship is passively stable, you&#39;ll wake up one day to divorce papers.” – Shane Parrish&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Write your obituary, then work backwards to live it.” – Buffett&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:54:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/smart-things-smart-people-said/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/smart-things-smart-people-said/</guid></item><item><title> A Few Questions</title><description> &lt;p>;Whose life do I admire that is secretly miserable?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What do I believe is true only because believing it puts me in good standing with my tribe?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Which of my current values would be different if I were raised by different parents?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What do I believe the most with the least amount of evidence of it being true?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Who has the right answer but I ignore because they&#39;re a bad communicator?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Who is full of it but I pay attention to because they&#39;re a good communicator?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What do I think is ambition (a good trait) but is actually envy (a terrible one)?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What annoys me about other people that I sometimes do myself?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How much of my nostalgia is a false or incomplete memory of the past?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What in your profession is impossible to know no matter how smart you become? David Deutsch said, “Beware of the difference between prediction and prophecy. Prophecy purports to know things which cannot be known.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Is this thing I&#39;m worried about actually a problem, or am I looking for problems to worry about because they make me feel in control?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What in my field do I think is a law (works all the time) but is actually just a rule (works some of the time)?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What do I think is a universal truth but is actually just a norm unique to my own culture?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What was true a generation ago that no longer is, and who is clinging to that old truth?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What is partially true but I believe in it so absolutely, and take it so seriously, that I&#39;ve turned it into a dangerous belief?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Are there things going well in my life today that I will look back on and wish I had quit while I was ahead?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Is there something in my life I think I&#39;m “passionate” about or “focused” on but I&#39;m actually just addicted to it?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Do I spend more time defending what I already know instead of trying to learn something new?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Are there people in my life who I consider kind and compassionate but they&#39;re actually just too shy to tell me hard truths?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What would Instagram look like if it were an honest reflection of people&#39;s life, instead of a curated highlight reel?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Am I being as nice as I could be, rather than just as nice as I need to be?&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:24:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-questions/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-questions/</guid></item><item><title> Why You Believe The Things You Do</title><description> &lt;p>;I remember reading an article years ago about a father in Yemen who lost a son to starvation, only to have another child fall dangerously ill. Desperate, he turned to tribal elders who recommended a folk remedy: Shove a burning stick through the sick child&#39;s chest to drain the illness. The father agreed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Asked about the horrific procedure, the father &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/10/26/world/middleeast/saudi-arabia-war-yemen.html&quot;>;said:&lt;/a>; “People said burn him in the body and it will be OK When you have no money, and your son is sick, you&#39;ll believe anything.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;When you have no money, and your son is sick, you&#39;ll believe anything.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That is such a powerful statement, and some version of it applies to everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s a universal reality: What you believe to be true is influenced by how much you want it to be true. The more something helps you deal with uncertainty, the lower the bar is for you to believe it&#39;s true.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s been like that forever. Describing the Great Plague of London, Daniel Defoe wrote in 1722: “The people were more addicted to prophecies and astrological conjurations, dreams, and old wives&#39; tales than ever they were before or since.” You&#39;ll believe just about anything that offers hope when a plague is killing a quarter of your neighbors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Visa Founder Dee Hock once said, “We are built with an almost infinite capacity to believe things because the beliefs are advantageous for us to hold, rather than because they are even remotely related to the truth.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Think about the investor whose strategy is so tied to their identity they can&#39;t let it go when it stops working.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Or the business that so desperately wants to be good it overlooks all the ways it&#39;s bad.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Charlie Munger &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamesclear.com/great-speeches/psychology-of-human-misjudgment-by-charlie-munger&quot;>;once said&lt;/a>;:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;If you turn on the television, you find the mothers of the most obvious criminals that man could ever diagnose, and they all think their sons are innocent. The reality is too painful to bear, so you just distort it until it&#39;s bearable.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Even things that appear to be hard science fall into this category. There&#39;s a thing in the legal world called Gibson&#39;s Law, which states that, “For every PhD there is an equal and opposite PhD.” No matter what argument you&#39;re trying to make, you can find a qualified expert witness who&#39;s willing to make it, under oath, for $500 an hour.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;People can be led to believe and defend almost anything, because the goal of a belief is often not to discover what&#39;s true – it&#39;s to justify past actions, or protect your reputation, or provide hope when it&#39;s lacking, or to maximize your income, or to signal to others that you belong to the tribe.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So there&#39;s one reason you believe the things you do: A belief&#39;s allure can eclipse its truth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A couple other reasons beliefs tend to form:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Memories of past events are filtered. You keep what makes sense and throw out the confusing details.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the late 1940s, two psychologists – Gordon Allport and Leo Postman – came up with what they called leveling and sharpening effects in memory.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It goes something like this: In any big event – a car accident, or a terrorist attack, or a recession, pandemic, etc. – there can be literally millions of variables that you experience and observe. You see people&#39;s emotions, you hear different opinions, you read about different perspectives. There&#39;s no way you can remember all the details; there are just too many. So in your recollection you emphasize some memories (sharpening) and discard others (leveling).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;People tend to sharpen details that make a good story and fit their existing views, and level the ones that are confusing, painful, or contradict pre-existing beliefs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So here we have a belief-generating system: What you think is true is heavily based on what you&#39;ve experienced, and you remember the parts of your experiences that make good stories, confirm stereotypes, and connect dots between other experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Think of how complex the 2008 financial crisis was. There were billions of people making complex, emotional decisions at the same time. No one could keep track of everything. So in hindsight people tend to believe what makes sense to them, in simple narratives – the Fed ruined the economy, bailouts were unfair, wealth was destroyed. All of those could be true and believed by one person, but argued against by another person who experienced the same economy but remembers different details. Maybe the Fed saved the economy, bailouts were the best option, and it was the buying opportunity of a lifetime. Depends what you remember.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The dangerous thing is that beliefs based on experience seem evidence-based. But when we&#39;re overwhelmed with observations in a complex world, we cherry-pick the most attractive evidence to appease our simple, story-loving minds.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;It is far easier to fool yourself into believing a falsehood than admit a mistake. Changing your mind is rarer than it should be, leading us to cling to false beliefs.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Physicist Max Tegmark writes in the book &lt;em>;This Will Make You Smarter&lt;/em>;:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;The core of a scientific lifestyle is to change your mind when faced with information that disagrees with your views, avoiding intellectual inertia, yet many of us praise leaders who stubbornly stick to their views as “strong.” The great physicist Richard Feynman hailed “distrust of experts” as a cornerstone of science, yet herd mentality and blind faith in authority figures is widespread. Logic forms the basis of scientific reasoning, yet wishful thinking, irrational fears, and other cognitive biases often dominate decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;You can agree with every word written there and still struggle to change your mind – or take seriously those who do – for two reasons.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One, when you change your mind you can feel like all the hard-fought effort you put into establishing your previous beliefs was wasted. Even a little pain from that reality can be enough to persuade you to stick to the original belief.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Two, when you change your mind, moving from one belief to another, it can be hard to take the new belief seriously – changing beliefs offers proof that the new belief may be short-lived, especially in the eyes of others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Both recognize an important truth: Beliefs are not just about what we know; They are social signals that offer clues about how we established our beliefs, our confidence in our intelligence, and our ability to pass reliable truth to other people. The quirk is that those signals can be counterintuitive: We should want an expert who is willing to change their mind, but what we actually want is someone who&#39;s confident enough to never have to.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lot of times we&#39;re not interested in truth – we&#39;re interested in the elimination of uncertainty, and that fact alone causes us to believe things that have little relation to reality.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:58:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/why-you-believe-the-things-you-do/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/why-you-believe-the-things-you-do/</guid></item></channel></rss>