<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>合作基金</title><description>Collab Fund 是企业家推动世界前进的主要资金来源。</description><link/> https://collabfund.com<atom:link href="https://collabfund.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 12:47:47 -0400</pubDate><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 9 月 12 日，星期二 12:47:47 -0400</lastbuilddate><generator>站点叶</generator><item><title>问 Netflix 联合创始人马克·兰道夫的三个问题</title><description>&lt;p>;马克·兰道夫 (Marc Randolph) 是 Netflix 的联合创始人兼首任首席执行官。我们最近问了他三个关于商业和生活的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;人们谈论的还不够多吗？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关于工作场所心理健康的讨论，包括倦怠、压力以及对更健康的工作与生活平衡的需求仍然没有应有的普遍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们需要开始，因为情况正在变得更糟。 Slack 不断地引起我们的关注。手机让我们可以随时联系并做出响应。最近（并且明显）转向在家工作进一步模糊了工作和个人时间之间的界限。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们都开玩笑说 Z 世代坚持“拥有自己的生活”，但我必须承认，他们已经对的。我不应该感到惊讶的是，我最受欢迎的社交媒体帖子（按数量级计算）不是关于创业策略的帖子，而是关于寻找更好的工作生活平衡、数字安息日、建立办公室和家庭之间界限的帖子以及类似的主题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些主题很重要。无休无止的产品冲刺、海量的短信和充满生产力指标的仪表板都在不断地推动我们以不可持续的方式行事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;必须做出一些改变，作为企业领导者，这一切都在我们的肩上。仅仅口头上承认平衡很重要的想法是不够的。由于文化是观察性的，而不是渴望性的，因此我们需要对我们希望看到的行为进行建模。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我经常写到这样一个事实：多年来（包括我创建 Netflix 的那些年），我很快就离开了家。每周二 5:00 与我的妻子约会之夜。如果出现危机，我们将在 5:00 之前结束。如果你迫切需要和我说话，我们可以在上车的路上说话。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这种行为可能挽救了我的理智（和我的婚姻），但真正的好处是，其余的事情当我告诉他们我希望他们为自己腾出时间时，公司可以看出我是认真的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这容易吗？不，但这有必要吗？是的。因为归根结底，唯一能记住你在办公室度过的那些夜晚和周末的人就是你的孩子。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;你最近改变了主意吗？&lt; /strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;别让我开始。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;几年前，我决定每月至少尝试一次改变对某件事的想法 - 结果证明太容易了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我从政治开始——我们是一个两极分化的国家，对于为什么对方的政策如此糟糕，我有很多看法。但如果美国在大多数问题上的分歧接近 50/50，我就不可能相信 1.6 亿人是完全错误的。或者愚蠢。或者被误导了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我需要像高中辩论时那样对待我的信仰。我必须做好准备，以便能够阐明并捍卫论点的某一方面，但我必须这样做，直到辩论之前我才知道我需要为哪一方辩护。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我这样做了，我越意识到我的许多观点是多么肤浅，而且这种思维方式不仅可以应用于教育改革、无家可归、枪支管制、移民、环境政策、刑事司法和种族等大话题。平等，但也涉及较小且同样热门的话题，例如最近的一个话题——Netflix 上的密码共享。 （我不是在开玩笑关于密码共享的事情——它已经发生了，所以我害怕涉足我的 TikTok 评论）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;它是一种解放，因为我不再花时间去解释为什么我是对的。我现在花了大部分时间试图弄清楚为什么他们认为他们是这样的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;它改变了我对几乎所有我看过的主题的看法。但这个练习最让我惊讶的是，几乎在所有情况下，改变主意并不意味着从一侧翻转到另一侧，而只是意味着靠近中心。这意味着承认这些都是复杂而微妙的答案，没有&lt;em>;任何&lt;/em>;正确答案。或者更常见的是，需要部分不令人满意的结果，双方才能达成一致、接受并继续前进。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我还有很长的路要走。我仍在努力弄清楚为什么人们如此强烈反对密码共享打击。 。 。但我保证我正在努力解决这个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;您认为错误的一条普遍接受的建议是什么？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“不存在所谓的馊主意。”这一定是有史以来最糟糕的建议。因为我了解到事实恰恰相反。 &lt;em>;所有&lt;/em>;想法都是糟糕的。事实上，不存在所谓的&lt;em>;好&lt;/em>;想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;而且它不仅仅是错误的。 。 。这很危险。因为假设所有想法都是好的，就会导致人们浪费数百个小时的精力来研究问题、编写计划、组建工作组等，而所有这些都没有来自现实世界的任何反馈来判断它是否真的是一个好想法。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为企业家，我们的工作就是接受那些（糟糕的）想法，并找出一种快速、廉价且简单的方法来找出它们为何糟糕。这是开始测试和迭代过程的唯一方法，如果我们幸运的话，我们最终会得到一些可行的东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想不出有哪家公司能够取得成功。做他们最初的想法。相反，这个想法只是一个起点。他们采纳了最初的想法；找到了一些便宜、快速、简单的方法来尝试；观察发生的事情；然后尝试了别的东西。可能已经这样做了很多年。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在 Netflix，我们花了 18 个多月的时间，进行了数百次失败的实验，才最终形成了一个好主意的商业模式。他们仍在尝试。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 12:21:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/ Three-questions-for-netflix-co-Founder-marc-randolph/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/ Three-questions-for-netflix-co-Founder-marc-randolph/</guid></item><item><title>尊重和钦佩</title><description>&lt;p>;我喜欢&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.berkshirehathaway.com/letters/2022ltr.pdf&quot;>;反向讣告&lt;/a>;的想法：写下你希望讣告说的内容，然后计算知道如何不辜负它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;每个人的情况都会有所不同，但我怀疑大多数人都希望他们的讣告上写着：你受到了尊重。你被钦佩了。你很有帮助。您是一位好父母、好配偶、贴心朋友。您是社区的财富。您为您的行业做出了贡献。你很聪明，有趣，聪明。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在意识到里面没有什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个练习中几乎没有人会想到他们的讣告提到他们的汽车有多少马力，如何他们的家有多少平方英尺，或者他们在珠宝和衣服上花了多少钱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我喜欢漂亮的东西。我有一些奇特的东西。但我总是对人们想要的与他们渴望的之间的对比感到震惊。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我儿子出生后，我&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/ investing/general/2015/10/13/financial-advice-for-my-new-son.aspx&quot;>;写了一些东西&lt;/a>;我认为他作为一个成年人会有所帮助。其中之一是：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;你可能认为你想要一辆昂贵的汽车、一块漂亮的手表和一栋大房子。但我告诉你，你不知道。你想要的是别人的尊重和钦佩，你认为拥有昂贵的东西就能带来这些。几乎从来没有——尤其是那些你想要尊重和钦佩的人。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;八年后我仍然相信这是真的，我什至可能会加倍努力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先让我区分好东西和花哨的东西。有人曾经说过，高端丰田比入门级宝马更好，因为好的丰田充满了让驾驶更愉快的东西，而入门级宝马大多只是地位和炫耀的资本。用钱买好东西真是太好了。花哨的东西是另一种动物。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这并不普遍，但在某些情况下，人们渴望炫耀花哨的东西，因为这是他们获得尊重和钦佩的唯一、绝望的方式。他们没有任何智慧、智慧、幽默、同理心或爱的能力来赢得人们的尊重。因此，他们依靠唯一剩下的、最不有效的杠杆：看看我的车，嘟嘟嘟，呜呜呜。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;前足球运动员查德·约翰逊 &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ ShannonSharpe/status/1620223077702586370?s=20&amp;amp;t=iqXe7T24ijApj57thXkneA&quot;>;曾经解释过&lt;/a>;为什么有些人认为他很便宜：当你的名气大到人们已经尊重和钦佩你时，没有必要炫耀你的物质财富仅凭你的才华：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;如果你能在职业生涯中达到你的名字比你能购买的任何东西都重要的程度，这就是你的价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有什么我可以买比我一个人的名字还大的东西。所以[购买珠宝]毫无意义。 &lt;em>;我就是我&lt;/em>;。这是毫无意义的。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;我的猜测是，如果你最喜欢的喜剧演员、演员或运动员最终破产了，你也不会在意。这不会影响你对他们的钦佩程度，因为你钦佩他们的才华是金钱买不到的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;即使在亚马逊规模庞大且成功的时候，杰夫·贝索斯 &lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.youtube.com/watch?v=tc0a28KrWKo&amp;amp;ab_channel=Way&quot;>;曾经驾驶过&lt;/a>;本田雅阁。如今他拥有一艘价值5亿美元的游艇。他是否因此而受到更多的尊重和钦佩？一点也不。他可以骑一辆赫菲自行车，人们会认为他是我们这个时代最伟大的企业家，因为他就是。史蒂夫·乔布斯 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultofmac.com/125861/steve-jobss-quest-for-perfection-could-make-even-buying-a-sofa-into-a-decade-long-ordeal /&quot;>;没有任何家具&lt;/a>;。没关系。他是个天才。他是史蒂夫·乔布斯。当你因内在特质而受到尊重和钦佩时，物质上的东西并没有什么区别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于你最钦佩的人来说可能也是如此。我爱并钦佩我的父母，让我告诉你这不是因为他们的衣服。难道没有太多值得学习的地方吗？难道不应该通过你所做的事情而不是你所拥有的东西来获得尊重和钦佩作为目标吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦你看到人们因为与他们所拥有的东西无关的原因而受到尊重和钦佩，你就会开始想知道为什么你对这些财产有如此强烈的渴望。我倾向于将物质欲望视为一个松散的代表，与你必须为世界提供的其他东西相反。我对奇特事物的渴望越高，我提供的实际价值就越少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为，如果你牢记这一点，就会看到许多更高的优先事项。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 12:02:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/respect-and-admiration/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/respect-and-admiration/</guid></item><item><title>智能与智能</title><description>&lt;p>;这是生活中需要做出的重要区分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有些人很聪明，但没有一点聪明才智。他们在世界上取得成功的能力可能会在负面方面让你感到惊讶。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他人缺乏智力，但却才华横溢。他们的潜力会让你大吃一惊。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在极少数情况下，你会遇到既聪明又聪明的人。他们绕着每个人跑圈。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我对智力和聪明的定义是这样的：聪明的人理解技术细节，聪明的人理解情感细节。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;或者也许：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;智力&lt;/strong>;：良好的记忆力、逻辑性、数学能力、应试能力、遵守规则。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;聪明&lt;/strong>;：高度同理心，废话检测、组织、沟通技巧、说服力、社会意识、理解你的行为的后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两者都很重要。但两者的评估方式存在重大差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;学校擅长教授和测量智力，因此人们往往重视和渴望这一点。但几乎在任何领域，聪明才智才是获得长期回报的因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你无法像衡量 SAT 分数那样衡量同理心，因此简历受到更多重视也就不足为奇了。但谁更有可能在生活中取得成功——主要技能是记住公式的人，还是能够立即理解同事、客户、配偶和朋友的情绪的人？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是显而易见的。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;这就是为什么世界上充满了无处可去的聪明混蛋，以及努力学习微积分但继续过着成功、幸福生活的中等学生。大多数人会做出的最重要的决定是是否结婚、何时结婚以及与谁结婚。但学校里从来没有教过这一点——怎么可能呢？你无法将其提炼为一个公式，或者一个放之四海而皆准的答案。这是一个需要大量智慧和很少智慧的决定。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这里的核心是认识到人不是电子表格。他们是情绪化、荷尔蒙旺盛、信息误导、追求地位、缺乏安全感的生物，竭尽全力度过这一天。因此，如果您必须在理解世界在理论上应该如何运作与它在实践中实际上如何运作之间做出选择，那么倾向于后者。就像历史学家威尔·杜兰特曾经说过的那样：“逻辑是人类的发明，可能会被宇宙忽视。”太聪明了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个极端的例子。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;乔治·索罗斯说，只要他看到泡沫，他就会冲进去买。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你是一个聪明人，这可能看起来很疯狂。为什么你会故意购买一项被高估的投资？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但如果你是个聪明人，也许这是有道理的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你知道泡沫可能会变得更大并持续下去。比大多数人想象的要长。你了解人们的想法，你知道投资者会在一段时间内继续疯狂买入，不是因为数字有意义，而是因为他们的邻居变得富有，他们会陷入嫉妒和错误决策的黑洞。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;“这并非非理性，”索罗斯说。 （但是请不要尝试这个；你可能不像索罗斯那么聪明）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;《大西洋月刊》的德里克·汤普森提出了一个绝妙的观点：棒球在过去 20 年里变得越来越无聊。为什么？因为每个团队都变得聪明起来：他们通过挖掘数据来确定如何获得最多的三振，从而制定策略。如果你想赢得比赛，那就是明智之举！但这让比赛变得无趣。它带走了一部分灵魂，一部分乐趣。现在这项比赛正面临着兴趣和上座率下降的危机。需要聪明人才能看到这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这里还有一些其他难以衡量的“聪明”特征。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;接受那些过着与你不同生活的人想要不同的东西，就会以不同的方式看待世界。看起来像是辩论的事情往往只是具有不同生活经历的人互相交谈。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;亨利·福特说：“如果有任何一个成功的秘诀，那就在于能够获得另一个的能力”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;纯粹聪明的人会发现这一点很难理解，因为如果你认为每个问题都有一个正确的答案，你就会坚持进行更多的辩论，直到对方同意你的观点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于世界上大多数问题，“正确”的答案就是最能促进你个人福祉的答案，这需要聪明才智&lt;em>;并且符合您对世界运作方式的体验。由于每个人都有不同的需求和经历，因此前进并完成工作的唯一方法就是容忍并与某些观点合作，即使您不同意它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你能做到这一点，结果就是，是与你不同意的人相处的技巧。这是不可或缺的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;认识到友善并不意味着软弱 - 这实际上是一种随着时间的推移获得合作的自私策略。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对冲长期资本管理基金 (Long Term Capital Management) 在 1998 年崩溃，威胁要摧毁整个华尔街。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为回应，14 家华尔街银行介入，集体救助该基金并平息恐慌。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;每家大银行都参与了救助——贝尔斯登除外，据说贝尔斯登的首席执行官吉米·凯恩对这一请求回应说：“他妈的没办法”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;十年后，贝尔斯登本身也摇摇欲坠。在边缘。猜猜还有多少华尔街银行愿意向吉米·凯恩伸出援助之手？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;查理·芒格曾经指出，本杰明·富兰克林并没有说诚实是最好的道德 - 他说这是最好的道德&lt;em>;政策。从长远来看，它会&lt;em>;帮助&lt;/em>;您，并让您处于最佳位置，为您赚到最多的钱&lt;/em>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有一个推论善待每个人有两个原因。一是道德，二是自私。从道德上讲，你应该这样做，因为你有同理心。自私地说，你应该这样做，因为你很容易低估你最终可以依靠多少人来帮助你，而且只有保持他们的好感，你才会获得他们的合作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;多-纪律思维&lt;/strong>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我在 Markel 董事会任职。最近有人问我从 Markel 的首席执行官汤姆·盖纳 (Tom Gayner) 那里学到了什么——他确实是近几十年来最有成就的投资者之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的回答是，无论我们谈论什么，汤姆都有一个完美的解决方案。完全不相关的事物的类比。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果我们谈论保险准备金，汤姆会说，“你知道，这让我想起了音乐之声中的场景&lt;/em>; ……”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果我们谈论市场估值，汤姆可能会说，“这有点像温斯顿·丘吉尔过去常说的……”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在每种情况下，这个类比都适用于这是当前主题的核心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这不仅仅是有趣的聊天。我认为汤姆是一位优秀的投资者，因为他了解世界是如何运作的——将各个领域之间的点联系起来——这比仅仅了解金融要广泛得多。了解金融的人可能很聪明，但了解世界如何运作需要智慧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;太多聪明人在自己的领域陷入孤立，忘记了世界是如何相互联系的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;强>;真正的独立思考。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;凯文·凯利有一个伟大的想法，即只有当你对某些主题的看法无法从你对其他主题的看法中预测出来时，你才能独立思考。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;许多观点是可以预测的，因为真正的独立思考是如此罕见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;告诉我你对移民的看法，我大概可以猜到你对堕胎的看法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;告诉我我是你投票选总统的人，我大概可以猜出你认为今天的经济是强还是弱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你对某些话题的看法可以从不相关的陈述中预测出来时，你很有可能已经外包了部分内容真正的独立思考很少见，因为大多数人宁愿舒服，也不愿正确，而且知道自己是部落中信誉良好的成员会让人感到安慰。独立思考并不意味着你是对的，因为大众通常非常接近准确。反对部落也可以被解释为傲慢——突然间你可能看起来像吉米·凯恩。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是诗人拉迪亚德·吉卜林写道，“如果你能与人群交谈并保持你的美德，或者与国王同行，也不会失去平庸”，你就走上了通往伟大的道路。测试这一点的一种方法是，是否有人在某些话题上你同意，但在其他话题上你不同意。如果有人在每个话题上你都同意他的观点，那么要小心了。如果有人在每个话题上你的观点都不同意，那就要更加小心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为我自己的狗——她是一个非常好的女孩——有一半的时间是疯狂的，所以当人们可以这样做时，我感到不寒而栗。不要在他们最喜欢的政治家或投资大师身上找出任何错误。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;认识到最好的故事会获胜。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不是最好的答案。不是准确的答案。这不是人们需要听到的答案。谁能引起人们的注意并点头同意，谁就是胜利者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你只是聪明，你可能会集中精力寻找精确的真相。如果你很聪明，你就会集中精力围绕这一真理传递有效的信息，并意识到如果你不能让人们关注它，那么最有力的真理也没有任何好处。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;一位医生曾经告诉我，医学专家和医疗保健专家之间是有区别的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;医学专家知道教科书上的所有正确答案。他们可以进行精确的诊断，并了解所有最新的治疗方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;医疗保健专家明白，从患者的角度来看，药物是令人生畏的、令人困惑的、昂贵且耗时的。在您向患者解决这一现实之前，您诊断或开出的任何处方都不重要，因为即使是完美的解决方案对于不遵循它的患者来说也没有什么区别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这与投资类似。对冲基金经理凯尔·巴斯对此进行了很好的总结，他说：“保持信念很容易。留住投资者更加困难。”最成功的投资者往往是沟通专家，因为在不可避免的业绩不佳时期，你必须迫使投资者坚持你。巴菲特。红杉。甚至先锋；他们非常熟练（故意如此），能够传递超出数字的有效信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;沃伦·巴菲特 - 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;查理·芒格 - 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; Seth Klarman – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;John Bogle – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Joel Greenblatt – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Howard Marks – 出色的作家。&lt;/p>; &lt;我不认为这是巧合。这些投资者的写作能力让他们能够有效地讲述自己的故事、设定期望并让投资者放心。这使得他们的投资者更有可能在困难时期留下来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这一点很难教。讲故事是一种软性的情感技能。在情报中找不到它。它存在于智能中。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:49:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/intelligent-vs-smart/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/intelligent-vs-smart/</guid></item><item><title>关于重大决策的一些故事</title><description>&lt;p>;1964 年，沃伦·巴菲特拥有一家前景黯淡的老牌工业公司的股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该公司首席执行官认为巴菲特的收购对其工作保障构成威胁，并提出以溢价回购股票。巴菲特急于出售，厌倦了看着企业陷入困境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两人达成协议：公司将以每股 11 1/2 美元的价格购买巴菲特的全部股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;巴菲特交易正式确定后不久就收到一封信。该公司仍会购买他的全部股票，但价格为每股 11 3/8 美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“这真的让我很兴奋，”巴菲特回忆道。 “你知道，这家伙实际上是想从握着我的手说这就是交易中获得八分之一的分数。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;巴菲特质问首席执行官，后者辩称从来没有达成协议。首先。这让他更加愤怒。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，巴菲特没有出售股票，而是开始尽可能多地购买股票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他最终购买了该公司三分之一以上的股份。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;传记作家爱丽丝·施罗德 (Alice Schroeder) 写道，最重要的是，巴菲特购买更多公司股票的动机是为了将其粘在试图从他每股 12 美分身上榨取的首席执行官身上。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这家公司——伯克希尔哈撒韦公司——成为巴菲特的杰作。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;类似的故事：1955 年，刚毕业的大学毕业生张忠谋 (Morris Chang) 获得了两份工作：一份在福特，月薪 479 美元，另一份在福特工作，月薪 479 美元。在电气公司 Sylvania 工作，每月 480 美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;福特似乎是更好的机会，但 Chang 要求招聘人员与他的 Sylvania 报价相匹配 - 仅仅&lt;em>;每月 1 美元&lt;/em>;多。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;福特拒绝了。因此，张在 Sylvania 接受了这份工作，在那里他了解了不断发展的晶体管和微芯片领域，并成为了专家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;张最终创立了台湾半导体，如今该公司的价值近 5000 亿美元，生产世界上 60% 的芯片。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;亨利·福特知道汽车将改变世界。世界其他地方则不太确定。在 1900 年代初期，汽车对于富人来说就像是吵闹的玩具。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但玩具很有趣，所以公众疯狂的一件事就是赛车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;福特没有兴趣在赛车领域——他的愿景是为大众制造一辆廉价、优质的汽车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但他知道自己需要赢得投资者和公众的支持，因此他制造了世界上最好的赛车，并且1902 年，它击败了卫冕冠军。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“那是我的第一场比赛，它带来了人们唯一愿意阅读的广告，”福特写道。他在全国闻名。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关注度足以从投资者那里筹集资金，八个月后福特汽车公司成立。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一切都是销售。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr / >; &lt;p>;女演员格洛丽亚·斯旺森 (Gloria Swanson) 于 1927 年拒绝了一份价值 100 万美元的电影合同。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;制片厂感到震惊，并询问她为何犹豫不决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“我会是第二个或第二个“电影史上第三位签下百万美元合同的人，但我是第一个拒绝的人，”她说。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这句话成为头条新闻，并帮助她变得更加出名，这，我假设，这就是重点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是职业建议中最极端的例子，“不要试图成为最好的。成为唯一的一个。”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;当已故作家克里斯托弗·希钦斯 (Christopher Hitchens) 与食道癌作斗争时，正如彼得·阿蒂亚 (Peter Attia) 博士所写，化疗的残酷副作用似乎“再持续几年的公平贸易” ”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但当希钦斯接近尾声时，他写道：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我连续躺了好几天，徒劳地试图推迟我本来可以拥有的那一刻。吞下。每次我吞咽口水时，一股地狱般的疼痛就会顺着喉咙涌上来，最终感觉就像是骡子踢在我后腰上一样。 ……然后我突然产生了一个流氓想法：如果我事先被告知这一切，我会选择接受治疗吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;肯尼迪和杰奎琳·肯尼迪没有&#39;关系很好。 1955 年，他们结婚两年后，杰克告诉他的父亲乔·肯尼迪，他想要离婚。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;乔回答道：“你疯了。有一天你会成为总统。这会毁了一切。离婚是不可能的。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;杰克重申他和杰基并不幸福。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他的父亲反驳道：“你就不能明白这并不重要吗？你真的是？唯一重要的是人们认为你是什么样的人！”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;婚姻得以维持。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;一切都是销售。&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;二战期间，糖、牛奶和鸡蛋都是配给的。许多食品公司适应使用不同的、通常质量较低的原料来度过难关。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;See&#39;s Candy 非常注重质量，拒绝降低标准。在一个假期期间，该公司关门歇业，并在店内贴出标语，上面写着：“已售完。购买战争债券作为圣诞节礼物。”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;美国 1942 年 11 月入侵北非的决定极不受欢迎，甚至在罗斯福总统最亲密的顾问中也是如此。几乎所有方面都认为，部队还没有准备好，计划仓促，任务过于雄心勃勃。高级将领们认为再等几个月并没有什么坏处。当时的将军德怀特·艾森豪威尔预测，罗斯福仓促的入侵命令将成为“历史上最黑暗的一天”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;入侵奏效了。但战后回顾，总统的顾问们想知道他为何如此着急。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一种解释是，美国人民对珍珠港事件和德国宣战后发生的任何事情感到焦躁不安。 。罗斯福自己的儿子给他写了一封信，说他和他的战友们只是坐着，“没有任何乐趣……只是在等待轮到我们。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;抓紧这些痒痒可能已经取代了军事战略。&lt;/p>; &lt;时任陆军参谋长乔治·马歇尔在战后表示：“民主国家的领导人必须让人民开心。这听起来可能是一个错误的词，但它传达了想法。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大多数决策不是在电子表格上做出的，您只需将数字相加，就会弹出一个合理的答案。其中有一个难以量化、难以解释的人为因素，看似脱离了最初的目标，但影响力却最大。&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:15:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-stories-about-big-decisions/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/a-few-stories-about-big-decisions/</guid></item><item><title>白炽灯泡的终结：技术和市场的失败</title><description>&lt;p>;拜登政府最近实施了禁止销售传统白炽灯泡的禁令，完成了 2007 年立法中长达数年的逐步淘汰计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然更节能的 LED 灯泡将为消费者节省电费账单并减少碳排放，在某种程度上，这种转变代表了技术和市场的失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从可持续发展的角度来看，白炽灯泡具有邪恶的品质，会浪费大量能源作为热量。然而，它们提供更温暖、更有吸引力的光线，对眼睛更舒适。荧光灯和早期 LED 灯泡在质量和对消费者的吸引力方面从未达到预期。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;市场未能刺激解决这一困境的创新——一种更好的兼顾可持续性和需求的灯泡。因此，现在政府监管成为强制变革的杠杆，剥夺了消费者的选择权。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;img src=&quot;https://collabfund.com/uploads/unnamed-fd7d8f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;unnamed-fd7d8f .jpg&quot; />;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;批评者会认为这是政府对个人自由和决策的无理越权。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在大型清洁能源项目等领域，考虑到资本，政府的参与是有道理的要求。但企业无法创造出具有普遍吸引力的节能灯泡，代表了技术和自由市场的失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;需要的不是严厉的监管，而是更好地将商业激励与可持续发展结合起来的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许碳定价或节能灯泡的回扣会有机地刺激所需的创新。自由市场成功地推动了创新，使其他领域的商业激励和消费者需求保持一致，例如拼车和拼车。 Companies like Uber, Lyft and Waze have created platforms that reduce traffic, pollution and parking demand while allowing the companies to profit from fees and advertising revenue generated through the apps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Through a combination of technology improvements (ie. GPS) and savvy marketing, carpooling and ride-sharing is not seen as a sacrifice for consumers, or mandated by the government, but rather a superior product that makes life easier. Similar win-win solutions should have emerged organically for lightbulbs without needing a government ban.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This missed opportunity highlights the need for creative solutions that don&#39;t rely solely on government sticks to drive change.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The transition to more sustainable products should feel like an upgrade for consumers, not a sacrifice.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More work is required to better align consumer desires, business interests and societal needs. True innovations marry all three.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:20:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/the-end-of-the-incandescent-light-bulb-a-failure-of-technology-and-markets/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/the-end-of-the-incandescent-light-bulb-a-failure-of-technology-and-markets/</guid></item><item><title> How to Read: Lots of Inputs and a Strong Filter</title><description> &lt;p>;My reading strategy is to start as many books as I can but finish few of them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Years ago I heard Charlie Munger say “Most books I don&#39;t read past the first chapter. I&#39;m not burdened by bad books,” and it stuck with me.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Reading is a chore if you insist on finishing every book you begin, because the majority of books are either a) adequately summarized in the introduction, b) not for you, or c) not for anyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slogging through to the last page of these books – a habit likely formed early in school – can turn reading into the equivalent of a 10-hour work meeting where nothing gets done and everyone is bored. And once you see reading through that lens, your willingness to pick up another book wanes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Which, of course, is tragic. “The man who doesn&#39;t read good books has no advantage over the man who can&#39;t read them,” said Mark Twain.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Every smart person I know is a voracious reader who also says “every smart person I know is a voracious reader.” There are so few exceptions to this rule it&#39;s astounding. College tuition at $25,000 a year comes out to roughly $100 per lecture. Good books – sometimes written by the same professor – can be purchased for fifteen bucks and can offer multiple times as much life-changing insight.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The conflict between these two – most books don&#39;t need to be read to the end, but some books can change your life – means you need two things to get a lot out of reading: &lt;strong>;Lots of inputs and a strong filter&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you only pick up books you know with certainty you&#39;re going to like you&#39;ll confine yourself to reading the same authors on the same topics. It gives fresh oxygen to confirmation bias and limits your ability to connect the dots between different fields and different cultures. It&#39;s better to have a low bar in what books you&#39;re willing to try, and even the faintest tickle of interest should be enough to make the cut. Kindle samples are free, so excuses are minimal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you&#39;ve flooded your desk with inputs, you have to bring out the filter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It should be ruthless, taking no prisoners and offering no mercy. Similar to dating, a book you&#39;re not into after 10 minutes of attention has little chance of a happy ending. Slam it shut and move on. You&#39;re not a failure if you quit a book after three pages anymore than if you reject the proposition of a 10-hour date with someone you just met who annoys you. Lots of fish in the sea.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This applies to more than reading books. It&#39;s true for all kinds of data, research, conversation, and learning. Without flooding your brain with inputs you&#39;ll be stuck in the tiny world of what you&#39;ve personally experienced. But without a strong filter you&#39;ll be overwhelmed with choice and paralyzed by inaction.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A good reading filter is more art than science. You&#39;ll have to find one that works for you. The bigger point is that the highest odds of finding the right piece of information comes from inundating yourself with information but very quickly being able to say, “that ain&#39;t it.”&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:57:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/how-to-read-lots-of-inputs-and-a-strong-filter/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/how-to-read-lots-of-inputs-and-a-strong-filter/</guid></item><item><title> Everything Is Cyclical</title><description> &lt;p>;French geologists recently discovered that a Himalayan mountain suffered a massive landslide 800 years ago. Massive may be an understatement: the slide moved enough earth to bury Manhattan as high as the Empire State Building. Annapurna IV used to be one of the top-five tallest mountains in the world. Today, after the slide shaved a third of a mile off its top, it&#39;s merely big.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The amazing thing is that the slide wasn&#39;t caused by a glacier gnawing at the mountain, which is usually what keeps mountain height in check. Annapurna IV just got too big. As anyone who&#39;s built a sandcastle knows, there comes a point when the whole thing comes crashing down on its own accord, crushed by the weight of its own vertical greed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Everything is cyclical, and the thing that&#39;s easy to miss about cyclicality is that it doesn&#39;t require any outside force to push it in the other direction. The act of getting big is enough to make you smaller without being pushed by anyone or anything.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lot of mistakes in life come when you think risk is something caused by external forces, when in fact the weight of your own success is enough to pull you down without any outside help.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That applies to so many things.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In his 1944 book &lt;em>;Why Don&#39;t We Learn From History?&lt;/em>;, BH Liddell Hart writes about why after every war people say, “That was so awful we will never do it again,” only to find themselves on the battlefield a few years later:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;We learn from history that complete victory has never been completed by the result that the victors always anticipate—a good and lasting peace. For victory has always sown the seeds of a fresh war, because victory breeds among the vanquished a desire for vindication and vengeance and because victory raises fresh rivals.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Victory has always sown the seeds of a fresh war&lt;/em>;. That is such a strange concept, but it&#39;s so obviously true. In his book &lt;em>;Evil,&lt;/em>; Roy Baumeister writes:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;The First World War had been so much more horrible than anything Europeans had remembered or even imagined that it produced a lasting and profound psychological impact. The winners concluded that there must be no more wars. The losers concluded that there had to be another war to set things right: So much sacrifice could not be allowed to be in vain.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s almost like the larger the victory, the higher the odds of a future war. World War I led to World War II, which led to the Cold War, which led to Russia invading Ukraine, and so on forever.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The stakes are lower, but I think a similar thing happens at companies. The bigger and more successful you become, the harder it is to maintain your success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What were the big winners of the last century? General Motors, General Electric, IBM, Nokia, Citigroup, Kodak, US Steel … it&#39;s not hard to come up with a list of previous giants that crumpled under their own weight. And for each it&#39;s fair to say that past success directly led to future failure through entitlement, jealousy among competitors, and bureaucratic bloat.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now read this recent piece about today&#39;s untouchable giant, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/amazon-leaders-aws-day-two-mindset-2023-7&quot;>;Amazon&lt;/a>;:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;At Amazon, it&#39;s always supposed to be “Day 1,” the dawn of a new era where the customer comes first and bold bets are backed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not surprisingly, that&#39;s gotten harder to maintain now it&#39;s a tech and retail goliath.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employees have complained about red tape, bloat, and bureaucracy. Facing a new financial reality, CEO Andy Jassy is exercising discipline when it comes to Amazon&#39;s bets. The company&#39;s facing intense external pressure, including a recent Federal Trade Commission suit … it&#39;s tough to be a $1 trillion revolutionary.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;The former CEO of Slack &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/volodarik/status/1665854827224498177?s=20&quot;>;recently explained&lt;/a>; a fascinating reason bloat seeps into successful companies. Managers vying for attention often rank themselves off a simple metric: How many employees report to them. The incentive, then, is to hire tons of people – even if they have little work to do – so a manager can say, “400 people report to me,” which signals their alleged value and importance. And you can only pull that off at a company with so much money and so much success that obnoxious budgets are approved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What&#39;s the lesson there?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be careful what you wish for?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Stay on your toes?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Watch behind your back?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yes, but the biggest is simply that everything is cyclical. Calm plants the seeds of crazy, growth plants the seeds of decline, success plants the seeds of loss. Everything is cyclical.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s the same at the individual level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Author Robert Greene writes:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Never be so foolish as to believe that you are stirring up admiration by flaunting the qualities that raise you above others. By making others aware of their inferior position, you are only stirring up unhappy admiration, or envy …&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There is nothing more intoxicating than victory, and nothing more dangerous.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;This is so true – you think you&#39;re highlighting your accomplishments, but often what you&#39;re doing is highlighting others&#39; relative lack of accomplishments, which breeds envy instead of admiration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s a tricky thing. The more successful you become, the easier it is for people to resent your success. Even when someone says, “I&#39;m so happy for you!,” and they&#39;re genuine about it, your success – maybe it&#39;s a work promotion or a raise – puts their own career into sharper context, inflating their expectations and potentially leaving them feeling worse about themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That dwindling support can come back to bite when those who were eager to help you at one point are less enthusiastic in the future. The rapper Drake says, “People like you more when you are working towards something, not when you have it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Then there&#39;s the connection between money and ambition. William Vanderbilt once said having a lot of money “is as a death to ambition as cocaine is to morality.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Happiness can be another cyclical thing. I love this detail from tire king Harvey Firestone, wondering about the simple life he had before becoming rich and famous:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Sometimes it seems that it might be better to go back to those simpler days, that one might get more out of a less complex life. But it cannot be done. One changes with prosperity. We all think we should like to lead the simple life, and then we find that we have picked up a thousand little habits which we are quite unconscious of because they are a part of our very being-and these habits are not in the simple life. There is no going back-except as a broken man.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Maybe that&#39;s the cycle: Start with a dream, accomplish that dream, then what was previously considered a dream becomes a new baseline, and the gaze of your ambition moves to the next dream. Inadequacy, hard work, elation. Inadequacy, hard work, elation. Everything is cyclical.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;—&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To some extent these cycles are inescapable. That&#39;s especially true for the economy, the stock market, and other social trends. So much of long-term success relies on accepting and preparing for cyclicality versus assuming it can be prevented.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the individual level, I think cyclicality can be managed around the edges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Shane Parrish &lt;a href=&quot;https://fs.blog/entropy/&quot;>;once described&lt;/a>; the difference between passive and active stability. A rock is passively stable – it&#39;ll keep its form without any intervention. Marriage is not. It can be stable over time, but it requires constant work, compromise, and maintenance to keep it intact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most things in your life are, at best, actively stable. Left alone they&#39;ll follow the natural path of cyclicality. But if there&#39;s constant intervention and management – managing your expectations, managing your reputation, managing how you advertise yourself and who you surround yourself with – you have at least a shot at keeping something good going for the longest period of time.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:19:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/everything-is-cyclical/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/everything-is-cyclical/</guid></item><item><title> Rich and Anonymous</title><description> &lt;p>;I think there&#39;s an “ideal” net worth for everyone, when money not only stops bringing pleasure but becomes a social liability. And that number is probably lower than most people think.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Business Insider recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/lottery-winners-lost-everything-2017-8#gerald-muswagon-ended-up-feeling-sorry-for-partying-8&quot;>;did a story&lt;/a>; of lottery winners who lost it all (people love the schadenfreude of these tales).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A common denominator of the stories is that lottery winnings have a high degree of, let&#39;s call it, social debt – friends, family, and strangers who feel entitled to ask, beg, and steal in a way that leaves the winners not only broke, but socially exploited.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the winners explained:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;After winning $3.9 million in October 1985 and $1.4 million four months later, Ms. Adams found that she no longer had the privilege of privacy. “I was known,” she said, “and I couldn&#39;t go anywhere without being recognized.”&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;A subtle problem with money is that assets are easy to measure but liabilities can be hidden. Measuring lottery winnings is simple: $3.9 million, down to the penny. But how do you measure losing your privacy? Or the nagging doubt that some friends only like you for your money? That&#39;s way harder.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I once spoke to a group of NBA rookies. The topic was how to avoid the tragedy of athletes who make a fortune in their 20s and are bankrupt by age 30.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One player mentioned something I thought was so important. He said most outsiders think athletes go broke because they spent their money on jewelry and cars. Sometimes that&#39;s true, but the most common cause is social debt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“When you grow up in poverty and then you&#39;re making $10 million when you&#39;re 22, that&#39;s not your money,” he said. “That&#39;s mom&#39;s money, dad&#39;s money, grandma&#39;s money, cousin&#39;s money, friends&#39; money. You can&#39;t just tell them &#39;I got mine, good luck to you all.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Buying themselves a mansion wasn&#39;t the problem; it was buying a modest house for their fifth cousin who they&#39;d never met but felt obligated to help that pushed athletes to bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These might seem like rich-people problems. But social debt creeps up everywhere for normal people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I used to ride the Amtrak train from DC to New York. The train has a “quiet car” – a section where everyone is supposed to be quiet so you can sleep or get some work done. People use the quiet car because they want serenity, but it was astounding how often it backfired. When you expect quiet, you become ultra-sensitive to the slightest noise. If someone in the quiet car speaks in more than a whisper, the entire car plunges into a state of deep irritation. I&#39;d bet that sitting in the “peaceful” quiet car actually leaves people with higher blood pressure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A similar thing often happens when people buy nice stuff.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You didn&#39;t mind when your old car was dirty or dinged – but now that you bought a nicer car you can&#39;t stand it when it gets muddy, and you lose your mind when someone scratches it in the parking lot.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you bought a new, bigger, house, you thought you&#39;d be happier. But then you realize that the reason you wanted a nicer house was to socially compete with other people who had nice houses. So once you got a nice house, you just started dreaming about even nicer homes. Once you accept that having the nicest home in your social group is your goal, it becomes not only an obsession but a game that cannot be won, since the group you compare yourself to shifts with each salary increase you receive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My theory is that the more money people have, the more social debt they tend to be burdened with.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The point is not to say you should avoid nice cars and nice homes – I like both. It&#39;s a realization that once money goes from being a tool you can use to make yourself happy to a symbol of what other people measure you by, you are buried in a kind of social debt that&#39;s hard to measure but has a real impact on your happiness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thoreau once explained: “The cost of a thing is the amount of what I will call life which is required to be exchanged for it, immediately or in the long run.”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr />; &lt;p>;I once did some consulting for a family that&#39;s worth $8 billion. If you Googled their name, nothing came up. No Forbes list, no gala photos, no profiles, no Wikipedia pages … nothing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was intentional.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;They figured out what so many other people fail to recognize: The way you maximize enjoying your money is by eliminating social debt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;They had total freedom, privacy, and independence. They chose their friends carefully and gave money away anonymously. It may have been their most valuable asset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It reminded me of what Naval once said: The best position to be in is rich &lt;em>;and anonymous&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:01:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/rich-and-anonymous/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/rich-and-anonymous/</guid></item><item><title> Our Investment in Verse</title><description> &lt;p>;Electricity makes the world go round.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Generating all that electricity also drives 25% of the world&#39;s emissions, largely because we burn fossil fuels to get electricity. So to avoid catastrophic climate change, organizations must transition to clean power as quickly as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies, aware that energy market volatility and increasingly evident climate change leave their operations highly exposed, are ready for the switch. A few corporations have helped catalyze the clean energy market by creating Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs), but it is very difficult for most companies today to secure clean power.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If procuring and managing clean energy remains highly complex, time-consuming, and expensive, most organizations will struggle to make the transition. Even those that can afford to procure clean power today still rely on manual processes and outdated spreadsheets that are ill-suited for delivering robust, data-driven analysis. Carbon-free energy purchases won&#39;t scale on Excel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But what if it was possible to purchase hundreds of megawatts on an intuitive software platform that helped manage everything for you?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Enter &lt;a href=&quot;https://verse.inc/&quot;>;Verse&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Verse is building a SaaS platform called Aria that leverages generative AI to provide an end-to-end solution for organizations to buy, manage, and report on clean power at a fraction of the time and cost required today.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the first time, companies can define their clean power goals, design and procure a portfolio of clean energy assets, manage and optimize those assets, and report on portfolio performance — all from one platform. Overall, we expect that this can reduce the cost of buying clean power by up to 70%, democratizing carbon-free energy for all companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the Aria platform, organizations can set parameters that target specific goals (eg, cost, emissions, or hourly matching), hedge exposure to fossil fuel price fluctuations, optimize clean power asset management, and deliver verifiable reports on portfolio performance. The platform can help companies at all stages of their emissions reduction journey, from transacting power purchase agreements (PPAs) to optimizing for 100% renewable energy, emissionality, or 24/7 CFE (carbon-free energy).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At &lt;a href=&quot;https://collabfund.com/&quot;>;Collab Fund&lt;/a>;, we are proud to work alongside &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/seyed-h-madaeni-ph-d-5697a749/&quot;>;Seyed Madaeni&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/matt-penfold/&quot;>;Matt Penfold&lt;/a>;, and the entire Verse team. We are particularly excited to support them in this seed round along with Coatue, Twine Ventures, My Climate Journey, First Minute Capital, Future Positive, and Incite.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By enabling organizations to reduce their energy costs with clean power and dramatically simplifying the clean power procurement process, Verse&#39;s Aria platform will help scale decarbonization across industries.&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 08:58:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/our-investment-in-verse/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/our-investment-in-verse/</guid></item><item><title> Smart Things Smart People Said</title><description> &lt;p>;A few lines I came across recently that I liked:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The appetite for applause counts amongst the lowest of human character traits.” – Jan-Willem van der Rijt&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“A great way to understand yourself is to seriously reflect on everything you find irritating in others.” – Kevin Kelly&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People in their 30s know where the world is going because they&#39;re going to do it. I&#39;m in my 80s so I have no idea.” – Daniel Kahneman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I&#39;m at the stage in life where I stay out of arguments. Even if you say 1+1=5, you&#39;re right. Have fun.” – Keanu Reeves&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If you find the right balance between desperation and fear you can make people do anything.” – Trevor Noah&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The happiness of most people is not ruined by great catastrophes or fatal errors, but by the repetition of slowly destructive little things.” – Ernest Dimnet&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Happiness is that feeling you get right before you need more happiness” – Don Draper&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Jokes of the proper kind, properly told, can do more to enlighten questions of politics, philosophy, and literature than any number of dull arguments.” – Isaac Asimov&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Inherited wealth is as certain a death to ambition as cocaine is to morality.” – William Vanderbilt&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“It doesn&#39;t take much to convince us that we are smart and healthy, but it takes a lot of facts to convince us of the opposite.” – Dan Gilbert&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Insecurity is the mother of greed.” – Will Durant&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The greater the ignorance, the greater the dogmatism.” – William Osler&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Don&#39;t try to fix people. Just set boundaries.” – Shibetoshi Nakamoto (pseudonymous)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Better to get your dopamine from improving your ideas than having them validated. “ – Nat Friedman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“It&#39;s good to have people in your life who you don&#39;t want to disappoint.” – Warren Buffett&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“More information is just a form of procrastination.” – Russ Roberts&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Injuries done to us by others tend to be acute; the self-inflicted ones tend to be chronic.” – Nassim Taleb&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The thing that is least perceived about wealth is that all pleasure in money ends at the point where economy becomes unnecessary. The man who can buy anything he covets, without any consultation with his banker, values nothing that he buys.” – William Dawson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The most accurate metric for your love of someone is how you feel about their flaws.” – Mark Manson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Assuming you rise to the top, please remember: what made you great may not be appropriate for the next generation.” – Richard Hamming&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Nobody gives a shit about anything except how they feel.” – Will Smith&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“In the soil of every satisfaction sprout the seeds of discontent.” – Dee Hock&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Thousands of people don&#39;t like what I do. Fortunately, millions do.” – James Patterson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Recognize what you like about somebody. Admire it as a quality separate from that particular person, rather than confusing it with him or her. What you admire about them are qualities that exist separately from the particular (and therefore flawed) example that they constitute.” – Darren Brown&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People might refuse to believe something even if it can help them live a little longer, if believing it will make them live a lot sadder.” – Cass Sunstein&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I believe pretty strongly that your overarching aim in life and work is to always be making yourself obsolete.” – Tim Hanson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Your capacity for gratitude is inversely proportional to your sense of entitlement.” – Mark Brooks&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Your calendar is a better measure of success than your bank account.” – James Clear&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If people want happiness so badly, why don&#39;t they attempt to understand their false beliefs? First, because it never occurs to them to see them as false or even as beliefs. They see them as facts and reality, so deeply have they been programmed.” – Anthony DiMello&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The purpose of life is to experience things for which you will later experience nostalgia.” – FedSpeak&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Nothing in life is as important as you think it is when you are thinking about it.” – Kahneman&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The way to be safe is to never be secure.” – Ben Franklin&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“If we can&#39;t laugh at something, we can&#39;t think rationally about it.” – Clay Johnson&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“There are two types of stability: active and passive … People get in trouble when they confuse the two types of stability. Relationships, for example, require attention and care. If you assume that your relationship is passively stable, you&#39;ll wake up one day to divorce papers.” – Shane Parrish&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Write your obituary, then work backwards to live it.” – Buffett&lt;/p>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:54:00 -0400</pubDate><link/> https://collabfund.com/blog/smart-things-smart-people-said/<guid ispermalink="true"> https://collabfund.com/blog/smart-things-smart-people-said/</guid></item></channel></rss>