<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 16 日星期四 01:39:22 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[America’s government isn’t shutting down just yet]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>据说疯狂就是</small><span>重复</span>做同样的事情却期待不同的结果。但在了解控制众议院的共和党人时，也许疯狂一点是健康的。 9月，时任众议院议长凯文·麦卡锡(Kevin McCarthy)无视极右翼共和党人的意见，严重依赖民主党选票来通过短期融资法案，从而达成了避免政府关门的协议。他被立即赶出窗外。六周后，他的继任者迈克·约翰逊(Mike Johnson)藐视强硬派，依靠民主党通过了一项临时拨款法案。然而，目前他的工作还算安全。是什么赋予了？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这一解释与麦卡锡先生在美国历史上首次以多数票被逐出议长职位后所引发的混乱有很大关系。他达成的协议使政府资金维持了大约六周。大约一半的时间被浪费在共和党人之间关于选择继任者的争论上。这使得他们几乎没有时间与同时控制参议院和白宫的民主党就长期解决方案进行讨价还价。约翰逊认识到他需要更多时间，而且他的政党将因政府关门而受到指责，因此他提出了一项类似于导致其前任下台的短期融资方案。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">九十三名共和党代表（约五分之二的军队）投票反对该法案。类似数量的人反对麦卡锡先生。但到目前为止，共和党人一直没有因为同样的罪孽而驱逐约翰逊。 “约翰逊将受到更大的束缚，”智库美国企业研究所研究员凯文·科萨尔说。 “他到底能做什么？在他们来抓他之前他能做到多久？这还不清楚。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">由数十名强硬派共和党人组成的众议院自由核心小组谴责该协议“因为它没有削减开支，没有边境安全，也没有给美国人民带来任何有意义的胜利”。然而该组织补充说，“我们仍然致力于与约翰逊议长合作。”即使他们也不愿再忍受另一场混乱和尴尬。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其中一些也与个性有关。约翰逊先生是一位来自路易斯安那州的绅士，但基本上不为人所知。多年来，他的杰出前任与许多民主党人和共和党人建立了不良关系。其中一些怨恨仍然存在。 11 月 14 日，即众议院通过最新支出法案的当天，一位帮助麦卡锡先生下台的共和党议员指责他在走廊上用肘部肘击他。麦卡锡先生辩称自己不知情：“如果我对某人进行肾击，他们就会倒在地上。”约翰逊先生的蜜月可能即将结束，但至少婚姻还没有沦为麦卡锡式的“扔盘子”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">约翰逊法案包括一些细小但有意义的区别。麦卡锡先生的缓刑使得资金在感恩节前不到一周到期，这对于喜欢家人的立法者来说并不是最理想的。本着节日精神，约翰逊先生不希望资金延期如此之短，以至于在圣诞节前设定了新的最后期限——用他的话说，“这是一种糟糕的铁路运营方式”。他的临时措施将资金延长至新的一年。它的到期不会立即让联邦政府完全关闭。 2024 年 1 月 19 日，资金将停止流向联邦政府部分部门；其余的将于2月2日被切断。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">民主党人已经做好了迎接更糟情况的准备。参议院多数党领袖查克·舒默表示，约翰逊的法案让他谨慎地“振奋”。国会进步核心小组主席普拉米拉·贾亚帕尔甚至称这项短期立法是“一次巨大的胜利”，因为它将资金保持在民主党完全控制政府时设定的（可以说是挥霍的）水平。这种赞扬无助于约翰逊先生与保守派的关系。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">真正的挑战在一月份到来，届时约翰逊将不得不召集喧闹的共和党核心小组，并与民主党达成一项长期支出协议。其后果不仅仅是政治尴尬，甚至是联邦政府关闭的烦恼。白宫为乌克兰、以色列、印太地区和边境安全提供 1060 亿美元军事资金的请求仍然停滞不前。参众两院绝大多数议员支持向最大受益国和最需要额外援助的国家乌克兰提供进一步援助。舒默希望在感恩节后提出该计划，但约翰逊表示他希望“分裂”以色列和乌克兰。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事实证明，约翰逊的当选并没有给美国的盟友带来好处。尽管新议长最近几周发表了一些亲乌克兰的言论，但他一直投票反对向该国提供援助。约翰逊先生暗示要加强对乌克兰支持的监督，这可能是一个不必要但可以接受的妥协。尽管他是以色列的坚定支持者，但他还建议将新的军事援助与削减国税局的开支结合起来，国税局是共和党长期困扰的问题。这种不严肃的提议——实际上会增加赤字——并不令人鼓舞。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不确定性令人担忧。 “我认识很多共和党人，他们的内心和思想都支持乌克兰。但他们如何对待特朗普和他的——我们可以说是相当热情的支持者呢？”众议院军事委员会民主党领袖亚当·史密斯说道。 “这里没有太多政策，但有很多政治。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:31:52 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/c0iahgmemktvh7oiq3mscmefkodj7e4q</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/11/15/americas-government-isnt-shutting-down-just-yet </item><item><title><![CDATA[Despite its sympathies, Egypt is unlikely to help Palestinian refugees]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1y6lujj e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text"><i>要阅读《经济学人》数据新闻的更多内容，请访问我们的<a href="/graphic-detail/">图形详细信息</a>页面。</i></p><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap">离开<span>加沙</span><small>只有</small>一种可行的方法：通过飞地南部的埃及边境口岸。自战争以来，埃及政府一直<a href="/1843/2023/11/15/fear-and-goading-in-the-west-bank">对难民关闭</a>，尽管它历来对巴勒斯坦事业表示同情。该国总统阿卜杜勒-法塔赫·塞西表示，开放边界可能会导致巴勒斯坦人失去加沙并无法返回。但埃及也有更多自私的动机。来自加沙的难民涌入可能会复兴穆斯林兄弟会，这些政治伊斯兰主义者长期以来一直是塞西先生最大的内部威胁。该国还受到该地区另一场冲突引起的大规模人口流动的严重影响（见地图）。这给埃及脆弱的经济带来了压力，并使其更加敌视巴勒斯坦人重返家园的想法。</p><div class="article__body-text-image"><figure> <span><meta><img src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/2308/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/361/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/541/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/721/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/1082/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/1154/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/1443/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/1803/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/2308/90/media-assets/image/20231118_WOF904.png 1280w" sizes="336px" alt></span></figure><p class="article__body-text">在加沙战争中，人们对苏丹<a href="/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/19/after-six-months-of-civil-war-little-remains-of-khartoum">残酷内战的</a>关注已经消失。 4 月，叛乱准军事组织领导人穆罕默德·哈姆丹·达加洛 (Muhammad Hamdan Dagalo) 试图从苏丹武装部队领导人阿卜杜勒·法塔赫·布尔汉 (Abdel Fattah al-Burhan) 将军手中夺取对该国的控制权，由此爆发了战斗。此后，数千人在两个组织之间的战斗中丧生，超过 600 万人流离失所，其中约 120 万人越境逃亡。</p><p class="article__body-text">在战斗的前三个月，埃及接收的逃离战争的人数最多。超过 25 万人在那里寻求庇护，但实际数字可能更高。据报道，在大开罗，人口涌入导致租金价格飙升。其他地方的资源也很稀缺。由于政府对经济处理不力，年通胀率徘徊在36%。许多埃及人正在努力购买食物。公立学校资金不足且人满为患，依赖联合国的支持。 </p></div><figure class="g-fallback"></figure><figure class="interactive-figure"></figure><p class="article__body-text">埃及政府 6 月份对来自苏丹的过境点进行了打击，使入境人数从危机开始时的每天 4,000 人减少到 9 月份的每周 400 人。到 7 月中旬，乍得接纳的苏丹难民数量已超过埃及（见图表）。南苏丹现在也有了。</p><p class="article__body-text">如果拉法过境点向巴勒斯坦人开放，新抵达的人数可能会使来自苏丹的人数相形见绌。这片居住着 220 万人口的飞地正在变得无法居住：12% 的建筑物遭到破坏，每 200 人中就有 1 人死亡。数千名巴勒斯坦人已经前往拉法边境寻找食物、电力、水和安全。 20 世纪 50 年代，埃及平等对待许多巴勒斯坦难民（尽管许多人仍然无法入籍）。埃及明确表示，那些日子早已一去不复返了。 <span>■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:18:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/vfhst5440rq1ofardebdp05dm0pl11gb</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2023/11/15/despite-its-sympathies-egypt-is-unlikely-to-help-palestinian-refugees </item><item><title><![CDATA[Taiwan’s opposition parties unite]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>台湾</span><small>将于</small>一月份举行<a href="https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/china-is-watching-closely-who-will-be-taiwans-next-president">总统选举</a>，这可能会导致这个岛国 <a href="https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/14/could-china-take-over-taiwan-without-force">对中国</a>的挑衅姿态显着放松。那将是一个重大的地缘政治事件。在台湾主要反对党于11月15日宣布达成选举协议后，这种可能性看起来更大了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">距离<small>候选人</small>登记截止日期不到十天，国民党侯裕一和台湾人民党<small>柯文哲</small>表示，他们将联合参选。他们尚未就谁将成为总统候选人达成一致。但由于两者对中国的友好程度远高于执政的<small>民进党</small>，因此任何一方的胜利都将带来巨大的变化。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>民进党</small>候选人、台湾副总统赖清德在 10 月底的竞选中以 33% 的支持率领先。相比之下，前台北市长柯先生的支持率为 24%，侯先生的支持率为 22%。 （富士康的亿万富翁创始人、独立候选人郭台铭的支持率为 8%。）如果反对派领导人能够成功地集中他们的选票份额，他们似乎会提前进入竞选活动。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">他们尚未发布联合政策平台。但两位候选人此前都承诺通过与中国重新开启对话来重置两岸关系。由于亲美的<small>民进党</small>拒绝承认台湾是中国的一部分，大陆中断了与台湾的正式谈判。<small>国民党</small>承诺通过回归“1992年共识”来结束这场争执，这是一个含糊的主张，即只有一个中国，有多种解释。柯先生表示，他不会回到1992年的共识，这在台湾不受欢迎。但他也提出过类似的提法，比如“两岸是一家人”。他和<small>国民党</small>都主张两岸交流和安抚而不是抵制（或者在他们看来是挑衅）共产党。这可能会缓解海峡两岸的紧张局势。它还可能让中国在台湾拥有更大的影响力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">反对党协议是在<small>国民党</small>和<small>跨太平洋党之间经过数月的争吵和讨价还价之后达成的。</small>柯先生在年轻选民中很受欢迎，他坚持在达成协议后成为总统候选人。但在台湾议会中拥有更多席位的德高望重的<small>国民党</small>不愿屈服于相对新贵的<small>TPP。</small>根据前<small>国民党</small>主席马英九斡旋的协议条款，此事将由公众舆论来解决。马英九、<small>国民党</small>和<small>跨太平洋党</small>将各自选出一名民意调查专家来审查民意调查，并确定哪位领导人是更有实力的候选人；该决定将于11月18日公布。这个过程似乎对柯先生有利。但侯先生发誓遵守结果：“无论结果如何，无论谁当总统，谁当副总统，我们都会共同努力，让中华民国的土地和人民安全，”他说。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">反对党还承诺建立台湾第一个联合政府。他们说，总统将任命国防部长、大陆事务部长和外交部长。其他部长将由各政党根据其在同期立法选举中的相对成功情况单独选出。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国高级官员毫不掩饰他们对赖智的厌恶，因为赖智致力于延续其党内同僚蔡英文总统的政策。其中包括加强与美国的关系、维护台湾的主权以及加强台湾的防御。北京官员最近称这位<small>民进党</small>候选人是“台独骗子”和“流氓到极点”。大陆没有对反对派协议立即发表评论。<small>民进党</small>发言人自然予以痛斥。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">台湾研究机构中央研究院的内森·巴托 (Nathan Batto) 表示，反对派候选人是否确实可以合并选票尚不清楚。柯先生的<small>Z</small>世代支持者可能会反对他与保守的<small>国民党合作。</small><small>国民党</small>的一些地方派系似乎不愿意接受柯先生。巴托表示，该联盟可能会“爆炸”。但如果它成立，反对派的票数将是强大的。这对共产党来说是个好消息。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:32:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/jqpkn9k6afg8jhri5qg42vlrap7m4o8m</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/11/15/taiwans-opposition-parties-unite</item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court’s code of conduct is a good first step]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>50 年来，</small><span>美国</span>大约 2,000 名联邦法官中除了 9 名外，其他所有法官都受到行为准则的约束，该准则为法学家在法官席内外的行为制定了道德准则。 11 月 13 日，例外人士——最高法院的法官——宣布他们决定加入下级法院同行的行列。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">新规则并非凭空而来。 <i>ProPublica</i>和其他出版物的调查报告揭露了几位法官的道德失误，要求法院整顿其行为的呼声随之而来。这些文章的主要目标克拉伦斯·托马斯（Clarence Thomas）法官未能宣布哈伦·克劳（Harlan Crow）数十年的豪华旅行是由保守派事业的慷慨捐助者承担的。克劳先生还购买了托马斯法官在佐治亚州拥有的一套房屋，并为他的侄孙的私立学校支付了学费。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">参议院委员会上个月发现，托马斯法官的另一位朋友显然免除了为法官普雷沃斯特马拉松大巴（他称之为“陆地游艇”）提供的 267,230 美元贷款中的“很大一部分”。这也没有宣布。尽管他的妻子弗吉尼亚游说唐纳德·特朗普总统的幕僚长帮助推翻 2020 年选举结果，但托马斯法官选择不回避质疑选举结果以及涉及特朗普在 2021 年 1 月 6 日国会大厦骚乱中所扮演角色的案件。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">没有提及任何这些——或者塞缪尔阿利托法官去阿拉斯加钓鱼的旅行，由一位右翼亿万富翁出资，他将生意带到法庭上，或者任何其他同事的明显冲突——法官们都签署了一项准则的行为。 （阿利托和托马斯法官声称他们没有做错任何事。）法院写道，该文件“实质上源自”适用于其他联邦法官的准则。法官应“维护司法机关的廉正和独立”并“避免不当行为和看似不当的行为”。他们将“公平、公正和勤勉地履行职责”，并且只能进行适当的“法外活动”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在该准则附带的五页评论中，法院承认，一些准则是“措辞宽泛的指导行为的一般原则”，而不是“具体规则”，并要求法官行使“判断”和“自由裁量权”。该文件还指出，由于最高法院是一个“独特的机构设置”，现有的法规不能不经过调整就被采用。例如，法官必须回避涉及经济利益或“个人偏见”的案件。但与容易被替换的法官不同的是，法官没有这样的替代者，并且只要有可能就有“出庭的责任”。该守则称，“即使一名法官不参与某一特定案件，也可能会造成很大损失。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">另一项修订可能是为了避免指责那些享受富有捐助者慷慨资助的法官。尽管其他联邦法官的守则禁止他们“传达”某人“处于影响法官的特殊地位”的印象，但最高法院的规则将这一短语限定为“故意”。只要法官没有意识到他的行为引起了人们的注意（例如，通过制造他受到意识形态捐助者的影响的印象），他或她就仍然遵守新的守则。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">还有一个更大的问题：除了法官本人之外，没有人可以决定何时违反准则或如何处理违规行为。相比之下，国会悬而未决的改革措施将允许公民抱怨法官的无赖行为，并让下级法院法官小组审查他们的主张。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，法官们的举动是朝着正确方向迈出的一步，并表明了对公众看法的一些反应，即第一街并非一切顺利。该准则以令人鼓舞的语气结束，如果法官希望检查和效仿“其他联邦和州法院的最佳实践”，这可能为进一步的自我完善铺平道路。但在那之前，美国最高法官将不得不密切关注自己。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:09:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b0lb6p4nq7tr55nq4k2u52lk88q7u2c7</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/11/15/the-supreme-courts-code-of-conduct-is-a-good-first-step</item><item><title><![CDATA[German judges toss a spanner into the government’s spending plans]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>敲打</span><small>指</small>关节很痛。当最高法院用木槌宣判时，伤害就更大了。对于德国执政联盟来说，联邦宪法法院 11 月 15 日发布的一项判决追溯性地阻止了最初专门用于 covid-19 的未动用资金转移到其他目的，这既是政治尴尬，也是预算噩梦。更微妙的是，这项裁决也是对整个德国的谴责，表明该国痴迷于对政府支出实施“债务刹车”是如何导致各种愚蠢行为的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">涉及的金额高达 600 亿欧元（650 亿美元）。德国前任政府于 2021 年初在常规预算之外借入这笔资金，用于支付应对新冠紧急情况的预期额外支出。由于德国宪法规定了对预算赤字的限制，因此需要特殊的豁免。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但到 2021 年底新当选的“红绿灯”联盟上任时，新冠紧急状态已经结束。因此，前财政部长、现任财政大臣奥拉夫·肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）将这笔钱转入另一个预算外盒子，即气候与转型基金（ <small>KTF</small> ），旨在支付与雄心勃勃的气候变化政策相关的成本。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种转变不仅意味着政府可以在不打扰纳税人的情况下增加支出。它有助于弥合与社会民主党总理的两位联盟伙伴的分歧。对于绿党来说，这意味着有更多的现金来支付他们自己的议程，包括鼓励采用节能热泵的巨额补贴。对于自由派自由民主党（ <small>FDP</small> ）来说，这意味着他们可以恪守对选民的主要承诺，即维护财政廉洁。财政部长兼<small>自民党</small>领袖克里斯蒂安·林德纳 (Christian Lindner) 一再坚称，在他的领导下，政府永远不会挑战债务制动。理论上，除紧急情况外，它将“结构性”预算赤字限制在<small>GDP</small>的 0.35%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">毫不奇怪，执政 16 年后下台的基督教民主党 ( <small>CDU</small> ) 提起诉讼，质疑将“紧急”资金从一个用途转移到另一个用途。政府的辩护——新冠危机间接导致了持续的经济紧急状态——得到了德国法院的一些同情。去年11月，当德国人普遍担心俄罗斯入侵乌克兰后将出现能源短缺时，一项临时裁决允许政府转移600亿欧元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">联盟似乎将这一缓刑视为支出的许可。 <small>KTF</small>作为一个整体，已在未来三年内投入约 2120 亿欧元用于一系列目的，从建设市政级供暖系统，到建立昂贵的氢电网，到升级磨损的国家铁路网络，再到抽水高达 200 亿欧元进军德国芯片制造业。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">法院的裁决不仅危及其中一些项目。它对使用各种“特殊”资金规避债务规则的行为提出了质疑。德国 16 个州中的许多州都与联邦政府一样富有想象力，除其他手段外，联邦政府还设立了 2000 亿欧元的基金，以使工业免受高能源成本的影响（实际上只花费了其中的一小部分）。用于补充国防预算的 1000 亿欧元特别基金在法律上是安全的，因为宪法经过了修改以允许这样做。但这需要议会三分之二的投票，这在其他情况下并不容易。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该判决的直接影响是，肖尔茨政府冻结了<small>KTf</small>的支出，直至另行通知。对于联盟来说，这是一个关键时刻，距离最终确定来年预算还有几天。一旦眼前的障碍过去，德国就需要讨论其过于严格的政府财政规则。法院裁决后，著名经济学家延斯·苏德库姆 (Jens Südekum) 在推特上写道：“债务减免正统观念取得了法律上的胜利。” “但今天的教训可能是，目前没有办法绕过债务制动的根本性改革。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:19:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b4ianl9s0402apa9945rb33lotfuia4r</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/15/german-judges-toss-a-spanner-into-the-governments-spending-plans </item><item><title><![CDATA[The battle of northern Gaza is almost over]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">六周<small>前</small>，<span>一座</span>拥有近百万人口的<small>城市</small>现在已成为空壳。 11 月 14 日，当<i>《经济学人》</i>受邀加入以色列军事补给车队前往加沙北部一度拥挤的沙蒂难民营时，里面的 9 万名居民无人在场。营地中许多密集的公寓楼已被摧毁；其他人则严重受损。以色列国防军（ <small>IDF</small> ）的装甲纵队撕毁了道路。电力、水和污水处理基础设施已不复存在。加沙市大部分地区和边远城镇的情况类似。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">经过六周的战争和三周的地面战斗，以色列现在有效控制了加沙干河以北的地区，这是一条将45公里长的地带一分为二的河床。这次破坏预示着以色列对哈马斯战争的一个阶段的结束，这场战争于 10 月 7 日开始，此前巴勒斯坦伊斯兰组织进行了一场大屠杀，最终导致约 1,400 名以色列人被杀或绑架。以色列数周的猛烈轰炸以及 10 月 27 日开始的地面攻势已导致加沙超过 11,000 名巴勒斯坦人死亡。他们实际上还推翻了哈马斯的权力，至少在飞地北部是这样：这个自 2007 年以来控制加沙的组织已经四分五裂，摇摇欲坠。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">阅读我们对以色列和哈马斯之间战争的所有报道。</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">所有这些都提出了两个重要问题。首先也是最紧迫的是如何缓解加沙南部的人道主义灾难。该领土 220 万人口现在几乎全部居住在南部。以色列的全面围困以及加沙与埃及边境的援助物资匮乏，导致加沙人民极度缺乏食物和水。燃料短缺使医院和援助机构陷入瘫痪。冬天已经到来，寒冷的气温和雨水只会加剧人们的痛苦。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其次是战场上接下来发生的事情。逃往加沙南部的不仅仅是平民：一些哈马斯武装分子无疑也做了同样的事情。以色列尚未找到该组织在加沙的领导人叶海亚·辛瓦尔(Yahya Sinwar)或其军事首领穆罕默德·德伊夫(Muhammad Deif)，据信两人都藏身于飞地下方迷宫般的隧道中。以色列军队将在未来几周内炸毁这些隧道的入口，并在北部搜寻武器和武装分子。不过，到了某个时候，以色列将不得不将注意力转向南部。它在那里能够做多少事情将取决于国内政治和外交压力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最近几天，人们的注意力集中在加沙最大的希法医院和其他此类设施上。以色列称哈马斯在希法地下设有地下总部。它还认为 239 名人质中的一些人藏在那里，至少是暂时的。 11月15日，以色列军队在包围医院六天后进入医院大院。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">截至<i>《经济学人》</i>付印时，情况仍在发展中，但初步报告显示，<small>以色列国防军</small>既没有找到哈马斯领导人，也没有找到任何人质。一直在医院避难的大约六万名巴勒斯坦人也消失了。当以色列军队进入时，只剩下约 1,500 人，其中包括医务人员、病人和流离失所者。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">大多数人逃往南方——其他人也一样。北部曾经居住着加沙一半以上的人口，现在却成了一片荒芜的荒地。据报道，驻扎在沙蒂的以色列军队只与小群平民发生过几次冲突。目前还没有准确的数字表明仍有多少人聚集在医院和救援中心周围，但以色列和外国消息来源一致认为，人数有数万人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但过去一个月，加沙南部的人口增加了一倍，即使没有几乎完全封锁该飞地，这一增长也会给基本服务带来压力。估计有 150 万人流离失所，其中大部分来自北方，但也有来自南方的人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自 10 月 21 日以色列同意通过埃及运送援助物资以来，约有 1,200 辆卡车通过拉法过境点运送食品、药品和其他必需品（战前，每天约有 500 辆卡车进入加沙）。南方的许多人不吃饭，努力寻找干净的水。由于以色列几乎完全禁止燃料运输，一些巴勒斯坦人开始焚烧家具作为做饭的柴火。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">燃料缺乏导致基本服务瘫痪。近三分之二的医疗机构已经停止工作。污水泵站已离线。国际救援委员会表示，霍乱和伤寒等水传播疾病将不可避免地开始传播。 11月14日，<small>联合国</small>表示将很快停止提供援助；它甚至缺乏足够的燃料来操作叉车。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第二天，一艘载有 23,000 升柴油的油轮从埃及进入加沙，这是以色列自战争开始以来允许的第一批此类货物。这总比什么都没有好——但也只是勉强。以色列的限制意味着这些燃料只能由<small>联合国</small>使用，不能由医院使用，因为医院的发电机已经耗尽。<small>联合国</small>驻加沙援助机构主任汤姆·怀特 (Tom White) 表示，这些物资只能满足该组织日常需求的 9%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">冬季大雨也来临了。 11月14日的一场倾盆大雨中，一些巴勒斯坦人发现他们的帐篷倒塌了；其他人则睡在泥里。加沙 12 月和 1 月确实寒冷潮湿，夜间气温降至 8°C。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">战争开始前，进入加沙的卡车约有三分之二经过凯雷姆沙洛姆（Kerem Shalom），这是与以色列接壤的过境点。自10月7日起一直关闭。在哈马斯的暴行之后，以色列几乎没有人支持帮助加沙人，本雅明·内塔尼亚胡政府中的极右翼政党也坚决反对。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，物资必须绕道埃及。他们抵达北西奈省。然后，他们被卡车运到以色列边境口岸，接受武器检查，然后返回拉法。绕道增加了 100 公里的路程，而且拉法每天只开放几个小时。以色列非政府组织 Gisha 的主任塔尼亚·哈里 (Tania Hari) 表示<small>：</small> “救援组织发现在埃及开展行动非常困难，这就是为什么他们通常在以色列开展行动，因为那里的距离更短，程序也更高效。”游说以增加进入加沙的机会。 “凯雷姆·沙洛姆必须重新开放，加沙人才能生存。”</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">下一步</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">是否这样做对以色列来说是一个问题，因为它决定如何继续战争。在坦克、嗅探犬和爆破队的陪同下，士兵们花了两个多星期的时间挨家挨户搜寻武器和通往哈马斯地道的竖井。一名官员解释了有条不紊的程序。可疑建筑物成为坦克或空袭的目标。然后，士兵们与警犬和工兵一起进行检查。他们不被允许冒险进入隧道。更多的竖井不断被发现。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">房屋内遗留的武器和爆炸物表明哈马斯武装分子匆忙离开。目前还不清楚他们去了哪里。有些人可能试图在剩下的隧道中生存。其他人可能已经逃往南方或撤退到城市的正中心。 “我们每天要处理大约 90 到 100 座建筑物，”营指挥官奥兹中尉说。数十个营在加沙城及其周边地区执行类似的任务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列将军们知道，他们无法像在北部那样在加沙南部采取同样凶猛的行动。相反，他们正在计划一场“更具机动性”的攻势。但任何行动都可能会阻碍救援工作，并引起国际社会的强烈抗议，而国际社会的抗议已经越来越强烈。本月在沙特阿拉伯举行的一次峰会上，阿拉伯和穆斯林国家要求结束战斗。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一些西方领导人已开始回应这一要求。法国总统马克龙在11月10日接受<small>BBC</small>采访时呼吁停火。乔·拜登仍然拒绝谈论永久休战，而他的声音迄今为止是最重要的。但他面临着民主党进步派推动停火的巨大压力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一场不那么残酷的战争可以缓解这种压力。在战争的头几周内，巴勒斯坦死亡人数每天激增数百人。不过，最近几天，伤亡率明显下降，北部地区几乎已无一人幸存。这可以为以色列赢得更多时间来继续其地面战役。大幅扩大的人道主义努力也将如此。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列还必须考虑加沙接下来会发生什么，而内塔尼亚胡先生迄今为止拒绝这样做。目前，哈马斯已经失去了统治能力。它也可能失去了曾经统治的人民的支持。 “（加沙人）指责哈马斯给他们带来了这场悲剧，”一名陪同部队进入加沙地带的以色列情报官员说。人们期望<small>以色列国防军</small>会这么说——但听起来确实如此。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">甚至在战前，就很难衡量加沙的民意：哈马斯是一个专制的一党国家，上一次巴勒斯坦议会选举是在 2006 年。现在更难了。不过，轶事证据表明，加沙的许多人对其表面上的统治者感到愤怒。最近几天，许多巴勒斯坦人在加沙南部接到电话，描述了针对哈马斯的愤怒场面。警察在试图插队领取食物和水时遭到咒骂和殴打。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这并不是说绝望的加沙人对以色列感到任何温暖。哈马斯诞生于加沙； its most influential leaders, Mr Sinwar and Mr Deif, grew up in the refugee camp near Khan Younis, the city that now hosts untold Gazans displaced from the north. Israel may have dealt the group a fatal blow. But a long period of miserable displacement would ensure that something else rises in its stead. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:58:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/4mt9sjhlgfiovp4kuvbsqoi6oqr6j2ua</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/15/the-battle-of-northern-gaza-is-almost-over </item><item><title><![CDATA[What is Iran’s axis of resistance?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>MERICA SAYS THAT</small> its troops in Syria and Iraq have been attacked at least 55 times since Hamas&#39;s assault on Israel on October 7th. Blaming Iran and its proxies across the Middle East, it has been hitting back: on November 12th America launched its third set of air strikes in eastern Syria since late October. Iran&#39;s proxies have so far stopped short of launching attacks that could drag America into full-scale war. But their firepower poses a clear threat to America as well as its allies. What is this self-proclaimed axis of resistance, and how powerful is it?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> After the Islamic revolution of 1979, Iran sought to export its ideology and build its political heft throughout the Middle East. One of its tools for doing so was a network of violent proxies and allies that spans Iraq, Lebanon, Syria, Yemen and elsewhere. Although not every member of this group shares Iran&#39;s religious fundamentalism—Sunni members do not even share its creed—they do have common goals: resisting Western influence and <a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/11/02/why-israel-must-fight-on">confronting Israel.</a></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The axis has long been co-ordinated by Iran&#39;s Quds Force, an arm of the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, the regime&#39;s praetorian guard. The force preys on weak states. In 1982 it began training young Shia militants in Lebanon to harass Israeli soldiers who were occupying the south of the country. Throughout the 1990s the Quds Force provided significant support to Palestinian Islamic groups, including <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-palestinian-islamic-jihad">Palestinian Islamic Jihad</a> and <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/10/how-powerful-is-hamas">Hamas</a> . It also backed the Northern Alliance, a loose grouping in Afghanistan that resisted the Taliban&#39;s takeover in 1996.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In 2002 George W Bush, America&#39;s president, warned of a new <a href="https://www.economist.com/international-relations-a-to-z">“axis of evil”</a> comprising North Korea, Iran and Iraq. After <i>Al-Zahf al-Akhdar</i> , a Libyan newspaper, wrote a widely read editorial condemning the phrase, some Arab and Iranian media began using the phrase “axis of resistance” to describe the growing network of anti-American militias in the region.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the late 1990s, after <a href="https://www.economist.com/obituary/2020/01/09/obituary-qassem-suleimani-was-assassinated-on-january-3rd">Qassem Suleimani</a> (pictured, on a poster), a prominent Iranian security official later <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2020/01/07/was-americas-assassination-of-qassem-suleimani-justified">assassinated by America</a> , took charge of the group, the Quds Force began to expand its network. It backed Shia opponents of Saddam Hussein&#39;s regime, including the Badr organisation, a powerful militia that was later to claim between 10,000 and 50,000 men under arms. After America&#39;s invasion of Iraq in 2003, the Quds Force established armed groups in the country to fight American and British troops.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In Syria&#39;s civil war, which began in 2011, the Quds Force trained and armed militias allied to <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2022/03/26/syrias-outcast-dictator-returns-to-the-arab-world">Bashar al-Assad</a> , the country&#39;s president. It also rallied around 70,000 armed men from Afghanistan, Pakistan, Lebanon and Iraq to fight in Syria in the decade to 2021, according to Iranian officials. In Yemen the Quds Force supported the Houthis, a Shia group that had rebelled against the Saudi-backed government and taken control of swathes of the country.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> America&#39;s State Department estimates that Iran spent $700ma year supporting militias before sanctions hit the country&#39;s revenues in 2019. A large portion of these funds were devoted to stocking the arsenals of Iran&#39;s long-term partners. <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">Hizbullah</a> , which has exchanged regular fire with Israel along the Lebanese border since Hamas&#39;s attack, is thought to sit on an arsenal of 150,000 rockets.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Since Suleimani&#39;s assassination in 2020 the more powerful members of Iran&#39;s axis, such as Hizbullah, have grown more autonomous. Iran says it did not have advance warning of <a href="https://www.economist.com/films/2023/10/13/what-is-hamas">Hamas&#39;s</a> attack on Israel. But it has nonetheless used the conflict to sew more chaos in the region. And it has benefitted in other ways: the fighting in Gaza has halted diplomatic efforts to normalise relations between Israel and Saudi Arabia, Iran&#39;s arch-rival.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Iran has more to gain from the turmoil. Anger across the Middle East over Western support for Israel may help some Iran-sponsored groups attract more disaffected recruits, and the prominence of Hamas, a Sunni group, in fighting Israel could ease sectarian tensions within the network. And should the fighting spread beyond Gaza, a surge in oil prices would fill Iran&#39;s coffers. A full-blown war that draws in America would be catastrophic for the entire region; on that, at least, Iran seems to see eye to eye with the Great Satan. But do not expect it to play peacemaker. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:38:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/b6k9jv0vmvlmr7l6db1jd1fim694panc</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/11/15/what-is-irans-axis-of-resistance </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court rules against Britain’s Rwanda policy. What next?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>T WOULD NEVER</small> have “stopped the boats”. But the Supreme Court&#39;s ruling on November 15th that the government&#39;s plan to fly <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/07/04/britains-tough-asylum-plans-are-held-up-in-court-and-by-the-lords">asylum-seekers to Rwanda</a> was unlawful is still a hefty blow to Rishi Sunak. The prime minister has pledged to tackle the problem of illegal migrants crossing the English Channel in small boats. The court&#39;s decision puts a big hole in the Illegal Migration Act, which allows for asylum-seekers who have entered Britain via another safe country to be detained and deported.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The prime minister is not giving up. Shortly after Britain&#39;s highest court ruled unanimously against the scheme on the ground that Rwanda was an unsafe destination for asylum-seekers, Mr Sunak said he would pass an “emergency” law asserting that it was in fact safe. He also said that he would not allow a “foreign court” to block the scheme. Tough talk may cheer hardliners, but it is hard to see how any planes will take off for Kigali soon.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The scheme always had an obvious logistical flaw. The British government claimed it was “uncapped”, but its counterpart in Rwanda said it could take only a few hundred people a year. Since security was stepped up on ferry and tunnel crossings, the number of small-boat migrants has surged. In 2022 it reached a record 46,000, up from 299 in 2018.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The bigger problem was legal. Many of those who enter Britain in this way are granted asylum: Afghans and Syrians have grant rates above 95%. In June the Court of Appeals said the risk of refoulement—sending asylum-seekers back to unsafe countries—meant the Rwanda plan breached the European Convention on Human Rights ( <small>ECHR</small> ). The European Court of Human Rights, which upholds that convention, had been the first court to block the government&#39;s scheme in 2022.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In its verdict this week the Supreme Court cited several cases, documented by the <small>UN</small> High Commissioner for Refugees, of asylum-seekers from decidedly unsafe countries, including Afghanistan and Syria, being sent home from Kigali. The rule against refoulement, it said, was contained in several laws ratified by Britain, not just the <small>ECHR</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That is a problem not just for Mr Sunak but also for his opponents on the right of the Tory party. In a furious letter to Mr Sunak shortly after she was sacked as home secretary on November 13th, Suella Braverman said the prime minister had betrayed his promise to “stop the boats” by rejecting calls to leave the <small>ECHR</small> . Claims that the convention prevents decisions that are Britain&#39;s to make are less persuasive when the Rwanda plan breaches other laws, too.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">现在怎么办？ Britain has already paid £140m ($175m) to the government in Kigali, though observers note the money has not been spent on improving its asylum processes. As well as legislation, Mr Sunak also said he would publish a new treaty with Rwanda giving “assurances” that when “we send someone to Rwanda they won&#39;t be incorrectly returned to their own country”. Mr Sunak is pushing for reforms to “rule 39 orders”, too—interim injunctions issued by the <small>echr</small> . Yet it is unclear whether any treaty would satisfy the courts, whether any emergency law would get through the Lords, or how the <small>echr</small> could be stopped from blocking things again.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Beyond such theatrics, the government will look for other safe third countries for asylum-seekers to be sent to. None of the court judgments that ruled against the Rwanda scheme found that the idea itself was illegal; only that Rwanda was an unsuitable destination. There was “clearly” an appetite for the concept in other European countries, said James Cleverly, the new home secretary.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Sunak can point to some progress elsewhere. So far this year the number of small-boat migrants is markedly down on last year&#39;s. That is largely because of a deal the government struck with Albania to return citizens who come to Britain illegally. Sunder Katwala of British Future, a think-tank, says it should seek to make similar deals with those countries whose citizens have asylum grant rates of, say, below 60%. Stopping the boats will not depend on one big policy, but a number of small ones. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:14:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/4n9jjca9e7c1apvlr3epj4rvqqak1qoj</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/15/the-supreme-court-rules-against-britains-rwanda-policy-what-next </item><item><title><![CDATA[Some scientists think newborn neurons could reverse Alzheimer’s]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>O</span> <small>NE OF THE</small> first signs of Alzheimer&#39;s disease is confusion. Most people can park their car in a different space every morning and find it again in the evening. Those with Alzheimer&#39;s find this type of problem much harder. Memories of things they do often, like eating or taking medication, become tangled in their minds.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The ability to distinguish between similar memories depends on a tiny strip of brain tissue called the dentate gyrus. Studies in mice have shown that the dentate gyrus is one of the few bits of the brain to generate new neurons even in adulthood. Those new neurons are thought to help keep similar memories distinct.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Whether something similar happens in humans is less clear. But a clutch of new results described this week at the Society for Neuroscience&#39;s conference in Washington, <small>DC</small> , suggest that it might. And if it does, then encouraging the process might offer a new treatment for Alzheimer&#39;s disease.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Until the 1960s scientists thought adult brains did not produce new neurons. Then evidence began to emerge of young neurons in the brains of adult rats and mice <sup>,</sup> —specifically in the olfactory bulb, which processes smell, and the dentate gyrus. These new neurons had developed from neural progenitor cells, a type of undifferentiated neuron akin to a stem cell, in a process scientists call neurogenesis.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And there seems to be a link, at least in mice, between these new neurons and Alzheimer&#39;s disease. Mice genetically engineered to have Alzheimer&#39;s-like symptoms also have fewer young neurons in their brains. Two studies published in 2021 and 2022 showed that encouraging neurogenesis could improve memory in such animals. And a paper published in April this year found that boosting neurogenesis also caused other cells known as microglia to begin cleaning up tangles of protein, called amyloid-beta plaques, that are characteristic of Alzheimer&#39;s disease.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> So far so promising—if you are a mouse. But studying neurogenesis in humans is tricky. <small>MRI</small> scanners cannot watch the growth of individual neurons. Scientists must take samples of brain tissue from cadavers and either stain them with chemicals that bind only to young neurons, or measure the genes that have been expressed within brain cells to look for the hallmarks of youth.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Dozens of such papers have been published. But for every one that has found evidence of neurogenesis, another has failed to do so. The pro-neurogenesis camp thinks the null results are down to poor-quality brain tissue or crude preservation techniques. The antis argue that either humans do not grow these neurons in the dentate gyrus, or if they do, there are too few of them to be useful.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The research presented in Washington strengthens the case for human neurogenesis. Maura Boldrini of Columbia University, María Llorens-Martín of the University of Madrid, Orly Lazarov at the University of Illinois at Chicago and Hongjun Song of the University of Pennsylvania presented evidence of young neurons in the dentate gyruses of humans—though most of their findings have not yet been peer reviewed.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Three of these researchers also studied the brains of healthy older people or people with Alzheimer&#39;s disease. Their results suggested that the production of the supposed new neurons slows with age, and falls precipitously in Alzheimer&#39;s disease. Previous studies by two of the groups also found that Alzheimer&#39;s patients with more of these neurons had better memories.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But while the new research strengthens the case for human neurogenesis, it is not yet definitive. One group of researchers from Yale University questioned whether the staining technique used in one of the studies was accidentally tagging other brain cells such as astrocytes. They are also concerned that the studies tend to find very few progenitor cells. “Where are all the mothers of these baby neurons?” asked Jon Arellano, one of the sceptics.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are other wrinkles. Dr Song found a different set of genes expressed in the supposedly young human neurons from those seen in neurons from other animals. And the few young neurons that both Dr Song and Dr Lazarov found in the brains of Alzheimer&#39;s patients looked very different from the same neurons in healthy brains. If the new cells are somehow defective, increasing their number may not help.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But although not all the scientists at the conference were convinced, some drug-makers appear to be. In April, Biomed Industries, a pharmaceutical firm based in California, said that results from an early clinical trial suggested that a new drug that the firm claims increases neurogenesis in mice improved memory in people with moderate Alzheimer&#39;s. If subsequent trials prove to be equally encouraging, that could be further evidence that the neurogenesis theory of Alzheimer&#39;s may indeed have something to it. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:58:27 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/l1aapet9lt2dpib0c9qfn9anuuks4lrs</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/some-scientists-think-newborn-neurons-could-reverse-alzheimers </item><item><title><![CDATA[New ways to pay for research could boost scientific progress]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>H</span> <small>ow might</small> science be done on an alien planet? Since the laws of nature are the same everywhere, the aliens would make the same discoveries as humans have—that matter is made of atoms, say, or that life develops via evolution. But while the results might be the same, aliens would be unlikely to have come up with the same methods for arriving at them. It would be remarkable if the little green men had invented universities, funding committees, a tenure system and all the other accoutrements of modern academic life.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This thought experiment, dreamed up by Michael Nielsen, a physicist, and Kanjin Qiu, an entrepreneur, was not merely a flight of fancy. It was part of an essay published last year pointing out that the way modern science is organised is not the only way it could be done, and perhaps not even the best way. Experimenting with different sorts of institutions, or novel ways to hand out research money, might help fix what the authors say is a “discovery ecosystem in a state of near stasis”. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"> <span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">image: The Economist</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Dr Nielsen and Ms Qiu are among a band of researchers concerned that scientific progress is slowing. A paper published in 2020 by economists from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology ( <small>MIT</small> ) and Stanford University concluded that American research productivity was falling, with more effort required to produce smaller gains in knowledge. A second paper, published in January this year, argued that the “disruptiveness” of both scientific papers and patents, as measured by citation patterns, fell by over 90% for papers, and more than 80% for patents, between 1945 and 2010 (see chart 1).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “The main thing I&#39;d like to see is far more diversity in how we fund and organise research,” says Dr Nielsen. There are plenty of ideas around. Some researchers advocate giving out research grants via lotteries, or expanding the system of competitive scientific or technological prizes. Others prefer to found entirely new types of institutions, displacing the universities that dominate scientific research today. And many see a chance to run a grand scientific experiment, turning science&#39;s methods inwards to work out how science itself might be improved.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Following the Benjamin Franklins</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The modern system of science funding—at least in America, the world&#39;s leading scientific power—is relatively recent. The Royal Society in Britain, the world&#39;s oldest national scientific academy, was founded in 1660 but limited its funding to an elite group of fellows. Before the second world war a good deal of American science was paid for by rich industrialists and corporate laboratories. The modern system in America owes much to the Rockefeller Foundation, a charity, in particular. It disbursed its money as grants for specific, well-defined projects, such as investigating the cause of yellow fever. As government funding rose after the second world war (see chart 2), America&#39;s government adopted a similar system. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"> <span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">image: The Economist</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These days, over half the funding given to universities by the National Institutes of Health ( <small>NIH</small> )—which, with its budget of nearly $50bn, is the world&#39;s biggest funder of medical science—is given out as fixed-term grants. Around 70% of the $8.6bn distributed in 2022 by the National Science Foundation ( <small>NSF</small> ) was structured the same way. A scientist applying for this money must write a grant proposal, perhaps 15 pages long, and ideally including some early results to prove his project&#39;s worthiness. The proposal is given a score by other researchers; this, in turn, helps a committee decide whether to fund it. Some 80% of <small>NIH</small> funding, and 90% of <small>NSF</small> grants, go through such peer review.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Silvana Konermann, a biochemist at Stanford University, notes that, with its mix of short timelines and small grants, the system leaves researchers “constantly thinking” about where their next cheque is coming from. But skill at raising money is not necessarily correlated with the usefulness of one&#39;s research. In October Katalin Karikó won <a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/10/02/a-nobel-prize-in-physiology-for-mrna-vaccines">a Nobel prize</a> for discoveries that led to m <small>RNA</small> vaccines. She had been demoted early in her career by the University of Pennsylvania because of her failure to bring in sufficient money.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And grants are becoming harder to win. Between 2003 and 2015 the likelihood that a researcher would be funded by the <small>NIH</small> at least once over a five-year window fell from 43% to 31%. One study estimated that researchers applying for grants from the National Health and Medical Research Council in Australia cumulatively spent 614 years writing them in 2014. One prominent biologist quips that if success rates keep falling, more money will be lost in wasted researcher time than the value of the grants themselves.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One common criticism of having committees decide where money should go is that the need for consensus will suppress unorthodox ideas. Sethuraman Panchanathan, the director of the <small>NSF</small> , is keen to try a proposal called the “golden ticket”. Each reviewer would be able to back a limited number of risky ideas in the face of disagreement from their colleagues.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A more radical solution is to abandon committees altogether and hand out money by lottery. Some organisations are already experimenting along such lines. In 2013 the Health Research Council of New Zealand began giving out around 2% of its annual funding at random—though proposals had to first clear a minimum quality bar. The Volkswagen Foundation in Germany, the British Academy and the National Science Foundation in Switzerland are all running similar trials. The Novo Nordisk foundation, in Denmark, is testing a hybrid system that rejects projects assessed as being of poor quality, gives money to good ones, and randomly hands cash to some of those judged middling.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Rather than reforming existing institutions, another idea is to create new ones. In his essay Dr Nielsen suggested an “Institute for Travelling Scientists”. Inspired by Craig Venter, a biologist and entrepreneur who has done much good science from the <a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2011/03/24/plenty-more-bugs-in-the-sea">deck of his yacht</a> , the institute would be based on a boat that would travel around the world, picking up and dropping off scientists with the aim of offering a relaxing atmosphere in which to master a new discipline or meet unusual collaborators.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A more hard-headed, if less relaxing, source of inspiration is the Defence Advanced Research Agency ( <small>DARPA</small> ), an American military funding agency originally founded in 1958 that has had a hand in developing everything from the internet to <small>GPS</small> and voice interfaces for computers. <small>DARPA</small> &#39;s $4bn budget sits outside the rest of America&#39;s military-research bureaucracy. Around 100 programme managers—described by Adam Russell, formerly one of their number, as “aliens” on account of their often unconventional backgrounds—can fund ambitious research problems however they see fit. At its best, it acts as a “force multiplier” on entirely new fields of research, says Dr Russell.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In America, the idea has given birth to organisations such as <small>IARPA</small> , which applies the same model to America&#39;s spy agencies rather than its armies, and <small>ARPA E</small> , which pays for research into novel energy technologies. <i>The Economist</i> calculates that the total amount of cash handed out by such entities rose from about $4bn in 2021 to nearly $6bn in 2022. The most recent addition to the family, founded in 2022, is <small>ARPA</small> - <small>H</small> , which covers health care. Britain, Germany and Japan have all tried to copy the model outside America in recent years, setting up <small>ARIA</small> , <small>SPRIN</small> - <small>D</small> and Moonshot <small>R</small> &amp; <small>D,</small> respectively.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But how well the <small>ARPA</small> model can be replicated is unclear. One former employee notes that <small>DARPA</small> “no longer attracts the same talent as it used to” and says there is “little interest” in studying cases of failure to figure out how to improve. The model may be less successful outside military research, suggests a chapter in a book by Pierre Azoulay and Danielle Li, a pair of economists at <small>MIT</small> , published in 2022. America&#39;s armed forces are the end-users of the technologies <small>DARPA</small> develops, and have a good understanding of what they need. End-users in other fields, such as energy or health care, are less single-minded.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Prizes, which offer a jackpot to anyone who can meet a scientific or engineering goal, can also push research in new directions. The Clay Mathematics Institute&#39;s $1m Millennium Prize Problems exist to focus attention on unsolved problems in mathematics. So-called XPrizes have boosted research into everything from rainforest preservation to space flight. The biggest, for removing carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, has a total pot of $100m, paid for by Elon Musk, an entrepreneur. A study in 2021 found that research topics that were associated with prizes gained 40% more papers and 37% more new scientists than fields that were not.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Prizes also have the advantage of being tightly focused. Adam Marblestone and Sam Rodriques, a physicist and a biologist respectively, have been thinking along similar lines. They have proposed setting up a series of “focused-research organisations” ( <small>FRO</small> s). Each <small>FRO</small> would have well-specified goals and limited lifetimes, a bit like the Human Genome Project, which began in 1990 and then shut down in 2003 after the first draft of a human genome had been published. The hope is that this would prevent them from sliding into bureaucratic complacency over time. Money could come from governments or philanthropists, for whom the prospect of bold, time-limited funding may prove attractive.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Marblestone&#39;s organisation, Convergent Research, has helped launch six <small>FRO</small> s. One is trying to map neural circuits in mammalian brains. On November 1st Mr Rodriques launched a <small>FRO</small> -like non-profit called Future House that aims to create a semi-autonomous “ <small>AI</small> scientist” within ten years. It is backed by Eric Schmidt, a former boss of Google. Mr Rodriques expects it to spend $20m next year. In March Rishi Sunak, Britain&#39;s prime minister, announced his intention to set up several such organisations—though exactly what they will study remains unclear.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And then there is the idea of funding people rather than projects. In theory, that would give researchers freedom to follow their noses, pursue ideas that may not have an obvious pay-off, and change course when something doesn&#39;t work. The idea is not new: the most famous example is the Howard Hughes Medical Institute ( <small>HHMI</small> ), founded in 1953 in Maryland. Researchers are generously funded for seven or more years, compared with four for the typical <small>NIH</small> grant. Between them they have won over 30 Nobel prizes, as many as Russia and the Soviet Union combined.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is other evidence to suggest the approach works well. Dr Azoulay has compared the <small>HHMI</small> with the <small>NIH</small> ’s standard funding programme. <small>HHMI</small> researchers produced nearly twice as much highly cited work, as well as a third more flops, suggesting a willingness to take more risks. Inspired, in 2021 Dr Konermann of Stanford (an <small>HHMI</small> fellow herself) started the Arc Institute, which is run on similar lines.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> The science of science</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> No one knows how fruitful any of these ideas will prove. Dr Russell argues it is vital to try many things, “collect data” and build “feedback loops” to improve the system. Kyle Myers, an economist at Harvard Business School, thinks funders should appoint chief economists to keep track of how each approach is working.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This turning of science&#39;s methods back on itself has been dubbed “meta-science”. It is a growing field of study, says Ilan Gur, <small>ARIA</small> ’s boss. Dr Myers calculates that since 2015 there have been an average of nearly 60 randomised experiments studying the scientific process. Two decades ago that number would have been in the single digits. More are coming: on September 28th the <small>NSF</small> announced a partnership with the Institute for Progress, a science-and-technology think-tank, to conduct meta-scientific experiments.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Using science to decide how best to do science is an idea with a pleasing symmetry. Yet Dr Nielsen cautions that finding out which funding method gives the best bang for each buck may take a long time. In the meantime, says James Wilsdon, who runs the Research on Research Institute at University College London, a diverse ecosystem of funders would bring its own benefits. “If you can&#39;t get funded one way, you have another,” he says. That might help prevent others falling through the cracks in the way Dr Karikó did. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:55:18 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/n7fvgkjclp8fujh4oeevjrmv7aos7dda</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/new-ways-to-pay-for-research-could-boost-scientific-progress </item><item><title><![CDATA[Was an ancient bacterium awakened by an industrial accident?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>N</span> <small>ew species</small> are generally found rather than awakened. And they are typically discovered in remote places like rainforests or Antarctic plateaus. But not so a species of bacterium described in a paper just published in <i>Extremophiles</i> . As Russell Vreeland and Heng-Lin Chui, the paper&#39;s authors, point out, the bug is new to science. But it is not new to Earth. In fact the microbe may have been slumbering for millions of years before being awakened by an industrial disaster.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The bacterium in question lives below Lake Peignur in southern Louisiana. The ground beneath the lake is rich in natural resources. In 1980 it boasted a mine producing rock salt, while a drilling rig run by Texaco was moving about on the surface looking for oil. But on November 20th, the two operations came together accidentally—and spectacularly. The oil rig&#39;s drill penetrated the third level of the salt mine, creating a drain in the lake&#39;s floor.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Over the next few days the resulting man-made sinkhole swallowed up the oil rig, 11 barges, a tugboat, 35 hectares of land and part of a house. A canal that drained the lake into the Gulf of Mexico began flowing backwards as the water level fell, briefly creating the tallest waterfall in Louisiana, while muddy geysers erupted from mine shafts. Somehow, all 50 people working in the mine managed to get out ahead of the rising floodwaters.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> An official report could not determine whether the oil rig had been drilling in the wrong place, or whether the maps of the mine were inaccurate. Either way, the disaster created an entirely new environment. The water that flowed into the mine contained less than 2% salt. But rock salt dissolves readily in water. When Dr Vreeland, then at the University of New Orleans, was granted access to part of the flooded mine in 1987, he found the water within contained 32% salt, about nine times more than seawater.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For most creatures, that much salt would be lethal. But Dr Vreeland found a species of bacteria, one of a salt-loving group called <i>Halobacteriales</i> , in his samples. The bug grew best in water containing 18% salt—and died when concentrations fell below 10%. Since the bacterium could not have survived in the lake, how did it get into the water in the mine?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Having access to only a small lab, and with comparatively few resources, Dr Vreeland decided to shelve the mystery and move on to other projects. During a visit to China in 2016, though, he met Dr Chui, another expert in salt-loving microbes, and decided to return to his cold case.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the intervening years, scientists have found that some bacteria possess exceptional powers of self-preservation. When times are hard they can enter a form of stasis, shutting down all biological activity until things improve. The salt beneath Lake Peignur was formed by the evaporation of a previous body of salty water. Some of the salt is 125m years old, meaning it was laid down during the heyday of the dinosaurs. The new species, the researchers suggest, is therefore antediluvian both literally and metaphorically. It was there before the mine was flooded, trapped in water pockets within the salt crystals—and it may have been there for millions of years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Exactly how long bacteria can remain in suspended animation is difficult to test, because experiments cannot reasonably run for more than a few decades. But Dr Vreeland claimed in <i>Nature</i> in 2000 that he and his colleagues had succeeded in reviving another salt-loving bacterium that was 250m years old. A study published last year argued that, in some circumstances, a particularly resilient species called <i>Deinococcus radiodurans</i> might be able to manage 300m years in stasis.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And Dr Vreeland points out that the conditions in the salt mine might have helped this latest species while away the aeons in relative safety. One problem faced by a somnolent organism is the gradual accumulation of damage to its <small>DNA</small> . Oxygen is one source of such damage. But the element does not exist inside rock-salt crystals, and is only very slightly soluble in brine. Ultraviolet light is another danger, but none penetrates below the ground.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Background radiation can also damage genomes. But the only radioactive atom found in brine is potassium-40. With a half-life of over a billion years, it is only mildly radioactive. And bacteria that live in harsh environments, including <i>Halobacteriales</i> , contain plenty of <small>DNA</small> -protecting proteins to prevent damage. Now, thanks to a human mistake, Dr Vreeland&#39;s bacterium has been given an entire mine in which to live, where it can finally reap the rewards of its prodigious patience. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:55:03 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ke7g2tcu5skf4oc9l3bqgkfe8sbbjbig</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/was-an-ancient-bacterium-awakened-by-an-industrial-accident</item></channel></rss>