<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 17 日，星期二 11:55:44 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Naftali Bennett argues that Israel’s future depends on striking fear into its enemies’ hearts]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1y6lujj e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> 10 月 7 日安息日早晨，<span>以色列</span><small>发生了</small>永远的变化，黎明时分，来自加沙的数千名恐怖分子冲破边境，袭击并屠杀了以色列社区。在那之前，我们以色列人大多认为我们是一个西方社会，人们从事科技工作，计划滑雪假期并进行健康疗养，几乎没有什么担忧。</p><p class="article__body-text">这一切都在那天早上结束了，我们意识到我们生活在一个烧死婴儿、强奸女孩、把整个家庭从地球上抹去的敌人旁边，这令人心寒。我曾担任特种部队的士兵和军官，以及以色列的国防部长和总理。我见过很多东西。没有什么比这更接近的了。我们被迫目睹自大屠杀以来从未见过的景象。</p><p class="article__body-text">以色列公众受伤了。没有一个以色列人没有失去过朋友或亲戚。我一些最亲密朋友的孩子在与恐怖分子的战斗中被谋杀或英勇牺牲。但与此同时，我们重新发现了一种强烈的以色列精神——体现在基布兹尼克徒手擒拿恐怖分子，为其他人争取生还机会，以及母亲们将自己的家变成急救诊所，拯救生命。这不应该是平民的工作，但当我们被召唤时，我们就在那里。</p><p class="article__body-text">这是一个鲜明的提醒，犹太国家已于 75 年前建立，因此犹太人将不再无力面对凶手。这就是为什么现在的反应必须确保我们的敌人永远不会再考虑进行此类攻击。</p><p class="article__body-text">但这不仅仅是以色列的战斗。以色列的斗争是世界上正直国家反对兽性恐怖主义的斗争。以色列实际上位于伊朗领导的战线的断层线上。哈马斯并不是唯一的敌人。它只是德黑兰恐怖主义章鱼伸出的一根触手。其他触角正在抓住叙利亚和黎巴嫩，并试图抓住海湾阿拉伯国家。我们需要从整体上看待这个敌人，并明白必须以新的、复杂的和令人惊讶的方式来面对它。</p><p class="article__body-text">规则已经改变。</p><p class="article__body-text">我们不会允许哈马斯躲在巴勒斯坦平民背后杀害我们的平民。我们永远不会针对平民，因为他们不是我们的敌人，但如果加沙平民在被用作人体盾牌时被杀害，哈马斯也会谋杀他们。</p><p class="article__body-text">以色列现在得到了世界的同情和支持，但作为总理我很清楚：以色列的未来不取决于世界的怜悯，而是取决于我们敌人心中的恐惧。</p><p class="article__body-text">在未来几天、几周甚至几个月内，我们将别无选择，只能发动一场规模空前的战争。所有以色列人，无论左派还是右派，无论是宗教还是世俗，都抛开了过去九个月来分散他们注意力的政治争论——尤其是关于政府司法改革的争论，并参加了这场战争。过去一周我访问的每个预备役部队都超员入伍。</p><p class="article__body-text">虽然我们感谢美国力量的支持，以及乔·拜登总统自哈马斯袭击和本周访问以色列以来所发表的支持性言论，但必须清楚的是，我们将进行自己的战斗。只要需要就可以。</p><p class="article__body-text">以色列目前的首要任务是加沙的去哈马斯化。我们决不能允许这种威胁再次出现在边境地区。该地区必须非军事化。这样做需要时间。以色列没有人对军事行动会是短暂或容易的抱有任何幻想。</p><p class="article__body-text">我们充分意识到这将对加沙平民产生的影响。以色列不针对平民，随着行动的展开也不会这样做。这就是为什么以色列国防军警告他们，并给他们时间离开加沙城并向南前往相对安全的地方。虽然以色列肯定不会向我们的敌人提供援助，但我们不会阻止其他国家向平民提供水、食物和药品，当然前提是红十字会能够探视哈马斯关押的所有以色列人质。</p><p class="article__body-text">这场战争不仅是对以色列的考验，也是对世界的考验。那些向以色列鼓吹“相称性”的人必须认识到，没有什么能够与哈马斯所犯下的暴行相称。以色列不会派遣数千名男子进入加沙强奸、掠夺和肆意谋杀家庭并在家中焚烧婴儿。这些从来都不是也永远不会成为我们的价值观。</p><p class="article__body-text">几千年来，犹太人一直是大屠杀、无节制谋杀和掠夺的受害者。我们建立了令人惊叹的犹太国家，并明确承诺“不再发生”。现在我们要兑现这一承诺。 <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"><i>纳夫塔利·贝内特于 2021 年 6 月至 2022 年 6 月期间担任以色列总理。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:22:48 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/rmvkt2k3fgsr2alos811gqadgcrj6ev3</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/10/17/naftali-bennett-argues-that-israels-future-depends-on-striking-fear-into-its-enemies-hearts </item><item><title><![CDATA[Higher bond yields are proving costly for governments. How should they respond?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>美国</span>上个月<small>可能</small>避免了政府关门，但其财政担忧还远未结束。 <a href="/leaders/2023/09/28/forget-the-shutdown-americas-real-fiscal-worry-is-rising-bond-yields">债券市场</a>的不安情绪将蔓延到世界其他地区。政府可以采取什么措施来避免财务打击？<a href="/china/2023/10/02/communist-rappers-are-luring-chinas-disgruntled-youth">中国共产党的青年派</a>正在利用说唱来吸引新成员，而且它正在发挥作用 (10:10)。 <a href="/culture/2023/09/29/bluey-captures-the-joys-of-childhood-and-parenting">《Bluey》</a>为何如此受欢迎（19:16）？时长：25分钟</p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theintelligencepodcast/e/652e5621bfc0890012264a25/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6ImZHeExMd3dDIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&sig=yZJUHYUd6RWldPYEpJ8VgDlDueZ-dUUtz4R-kpF6_jA"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text">收听： <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-intelligence-from-the-economist/id1449631195">Apple 播客</a>| <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN">Spotify</a></p><p class="article__body-text">立即注册<a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Dthe-intelligence">《经济学人播客+》</a> ，即可通过我们的限时优惠获得 50% 的订阅折扣。在《经济学人播客+》推出之前，您无需付费。</p><p class="article__body-text">如果您已经是《经济学人》的订阅者，作为订阅的一部分，您将可以完全访问我们的所有节目。</p><p class="article__body-text">有关《经济学人播客+》的更多信息，包括如何访问，请访问我们的<a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">常见问题解答页面</a>。</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:02:41 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/on634jeih6h1sb2ioqjd4e7cvbe0hi63</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/17/higher-bond-yields-are-proving-costly-for-governments-how-should-they-respond </item><item><title><![CDATA[How China’s Belt and Road Initiative is changing]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>10月17日，</small><span>至少</span>有90个国家的官员预计将抵达北京，参加为期两天的外交节日。这次峰会是由中国国家主席习近平组织的，旨在庆祝他最雄心勃勃的外交政策计划“<small>一带</small><a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/09/07/chinas-belt-and-road-initiative-will-keep-testing-the-west">一路</a>”倡议十周年。其中涉及中国为欧亚大陆和非洲的公路、铁路和其他基础设施投资提供数十亿美元的融资。中国声称<small>“一带一路”</small>创造了42万个就业岗位，让4000万人摆脱了贫困。但许多西方人认为，其<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/09/07/chinas-belt-and-road-initiative-will-keep-testing-the-west">真正目的</a>是构建一个中国领导的世界秩序，让令人厌恶的政权得以蓬勃发展。本周峰会的嘉宾名单就像一个无赖画廊。俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京将扮演主角。其他多位强者也已确认出席。甚至塔利班也派出了代表团。中国的<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议是为国际发展提供资金还是巩固独裁统治？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 2013年提出的“一带一路”<small>倡议</small>很快就明确表达了习近平决心打破邓小平“韬光养晦、韬光养晦”的决心。永远不要试图带头”。它寻求使欧亚大陆（以中国为主）成为一个与跨大西洋经济和贸易地区（以美国为主）相媲美的经济和贸易地区。习近平希望通过投资基础设施，为高铁公司等中国企业创造新市场，并出口中国水泥、钢铁和其他金属方面大量过剩产能。通过投资中亚动荡的国家，他试图为中国动荡的西部地区新疆和西藏建立一个更加稳定的邻里关系。通过鼓励中国在南海周边开展更多项目，该倡议旨在增强中国在该地区的主张（“一带一路”中的“道路”指的是海上通道）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从很多方面来说， <small>“一带一路”</small>倡议的第一个十年取得了惊人的成功。已有 150 多个国家签署了该计划，其中包括<small>欧盟</small>27 个成员国中的 18 个。这帮助中国成为发展中国家最大的债权人，增强了其外交和地缘政治影响力。它还给许多发展中国家带来了实实在在的好处，否则这些国家的公路和铁路就无法修建。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而<small>“一带一路</small>”的进展已经放缓。在该计划的最初几年，中国在没有适当评估风险的情况下，不顾一切地向贫穷国家提供贷款。其中许多贷款现已成为坏账，迫使北京方面变得更加谨慎。自2016年以来，中国的对外贷款一直在下降。习近平表示，现在将把重点放在“小而美”的投资上——这对于他曾经被誉为“世纪工程”的计划来说是一个明显的基调变化。<a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/07/the-belt-and-road-as-seen-from-china">国内的幻灭</a>在一定程度上解释了这一转变：中国经济步履蹒跚，导致普通公民在国外的奢侈消费不再那么受欢迎。随着中国与美国的全球竞争加剧，其他国家也对讨好中国变得更加谨慎。出于国家安全考虑，<small>欧盟</small>收紧了对关键基础设施的外国投资的规定。意大利是唯一加入<small>“一带一路”的七国集团</small>成员，预计将退出。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>可能会放慢步伐并调整其目标。但它仍然是习近平长期目标的重要组成部分，即团结全球南方国家支持中国的非民主发展模式。十年前，西方国家迟迟没有意识到该项目的重要性。他们现在正在争先恐后地提供替代方案。上个月在德里举行的<small>二十国</small>集团峰会上公布了连接印度、中东和欧洲的运输走廊计划。美国承诺通过世界银行增加对发展中国家的贷款。中国的<small>“一带</small>一路”建设也遇到了一些坎坷。然而它已经改变了世界的前进方向。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 08:51:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/rkig0rtea36095ogd1kc7bb4heju0m3r</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/17/how-chinas-belt-and-road-initiative-is-chang </item><item><title><![CDATA[David Petraeus and Andrew Roberts on Ukraine and the future of warfare]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>乌克兰战争</small><span>包含</span>了过去冲突的许多特征。它在多大程度上也提供了关于未来战争性质的线索——特别是涉及美国、<small>北约</small>和其他大国的战争可能是什么样子？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/ukraine-crisis">俄乌冲突</a>的某些方面似乎更让人想起上个世纪的冲突，而不是本世纪的冲突。乌克兰东部的顿巴斯地区有广阔的战壕、无人区和铁丝网，让人想起第一次世界大战； <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/04/12/why-so-many-russian-tanks-fall-prey-to-ukrainian-mines">雷区</a>让人想起第二个；装甲、火炮和火箭系统让人想起冷战时代。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">可以肯定的是，这场战争确实配备了许多最先进的武器，从复杂的反坦克和防空系统到无人机和海上系统以及现代导弹。鉴于商业卫星图像的可用性、新的地理定位功能以及智能手机、互联网接入、社交媒体网站和数据聚合服务的普及，这场战斗也是在战场透明度空前的背景下进行的。然而，它还没有包括太多复杂的远程无人系统，无论是远程还是算法驾驶，这种类型无疑会在未来大国之间的冲突中占据重要地位。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">乌克兰没有预示战争的未来，部分原因是很少有战争能预示战争的未来。例如，2003 年的伊拉克战争与 1990-91 年的海湾战争截然不同，尽管这场战争是在十多年后的同一地区进行的，而且由许多相同的战斗人员进行。同样，美国在越南的战争与几年前美国在朝鲜战争中看似具有影响力的经历截然不同，尽管这并没有阻止美国顾问寻求塑造南越军队，以应对类似朝鲜的冲突，而不是为了平叛运动。应该是努力的重点。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">战争的发展从来都不是线性的。它断断续续地发展，部分是由将军和政治领导人学习经验教训并将其应用于未来的热情（或缺乏热情）驱动的，部分是由背景、能力、局限性和其他品质（包括战斗人员承受伤亡的意愿）。自火药发明以来，技术的发展推动了战争方式的变化，特别是十九世纪机枪、第一次世界大战中坦克的出现以及结束第二次世界大战的核弹的出现，深刻地改变了战争的面貌。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">例如，五角大楼对 20 世纪 70 年代和 1980 年代的冷战以及后来的海湾战争的大部分思考都是受到对 1973 年以色列和阿拉伯国家之间赎罪日战争的深入研究的启发。美国军方对其越南经历的反应很大程度上是将非常规战争扔进了历史的灰堆——迫使9/11后时代的美国武装部队吸取本应从美国当时持续时间最长的战争中吸取的教训。时间。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">乌克兰战争已经让我们了解了很多关于遗留武器和极高的弹药消耗率的知识。在技​​术层面上，这场冲突揭示了很多关于哪些套件有效、哪些无效的信息，但还没有它可能发挥的作用那么多，因为战争尚未体现出大国拥有的许多尖端能力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，乌克兰远不是世界上最先进武装部队之间更全面战争的完美路标。事实上，美国和<small>北约</small>尚未向乌克兰提供最先进的系统，例如第五代战斗机和尖端无人机，一旦俄罗斯发动侵略，他们的部队将立即部署这些系统。引发了<small>北约</small>条约第5条中的集体自卫承诺。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>北约</small>与俄罗斯在波罗的海国家或加里宁格勒附近的苏瓦乌基缺口发生的任何直接冲突无疑都将涉及比乌克兰使用的能力更强的情报、监视和侦察套件和系统（事实上，开源空中跟踪显示有大量此类平台）沿着该国西部边境飞行）；射程更远、体积更大、速度更快的弹药；以及更先进的空中、海上、地面、海底、太空和网络空间武器系统。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">冷战时期有一句格言说：“看得见的东西可以被击中，而能被击中的东西则可以被杀死。”这句话经常被重复，尽管它从未被遵循，因为观察和深度打击的能力有限，特别是针对移动目标。然而，鉴于过去三十年的进步，特别是在通过强大的通信网络与武器系统连接的监视系统的复杂性方面，这句格言需要复活并认真对待。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如今，几乎任何重要的军事平台，从船只和飞机到后勤站点和部队集结，都越来越多地出现在任何战区（尽管海底系统仍然更难以探测）。因此，它也可能被击中，包括被先进的导弹和集群弹药击中，这些导弹和集群弹药可以压倒防御并且非常精确。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">鉴于这一新现实，政治和军事领导人必须使用人工智能和机器人等尖端技术来改变其军队的各个方面。而且，如果这无法阻止潜在的对手，则必须保护武器系统免受相对廉价的无人机舰队、传感器制导导弹以及网络和外太空的影响。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在战争中，需要是发明之母。但是，与其说俄罗斯展示了所谓的格拉西莫夫主义所倡导的混合战争的掌握，不如说是乌克兰，尽管其资源有限，却最令人印象深刻地展示了对所有战争领域的掌握（尽管乌克兰境内有数英里深的雷区）。乌克兰南部目前正在那里阻止进展）。特别是，事实证明乌克兰在网络空间中的恢复能力比预期要强得多，从而损害了俄罗斯作为网络攻击高手的声誉。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于俄罗斯领导人弗拉基米尔·普京来说，乌克兰事件是一次发人深省的经历。他和他的高级指挥部确信，在他们针对<small>北约</small>挑起的任何更广泛的战争中，实现他们的目标将会困难得多。尽管乌克兰人具有创新精神、决心和勇气，但他们的斗争并不能准确代表战争的未来，尽管它无疑提供了过去的教训，并为未来提供了线索。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>美国陆军将军戴维·彼得雷乌斯（退役）指挥了伊拉克增援、美国中央司令部和驻阿富汗的<small>北约</small>/美军部队，后来担任中央情报局局长。安德鲁·罗伯茨是上议院议员，着有 20 多本书，其中包括《丘吉尔：与命运同行》。他们的新书是《冲突：从 1945 年到乌克兰的战争演变》。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 08:07:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/qpat1p7l7j2apc9su1o2utvvqesbghng</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/10/17/david-petraeus-and-andrew-roberts-on-ukraine-and-the-future-of-warfare </item><item><title><![CDATA[2023 looks set to be a watershed year for the climate]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1y6lujj e1ey6m750"><figure> <span><meta><img src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/2998/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/468/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/703/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/937/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/1405/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/1499/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/1874/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/2342/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/2998/90/sites/default/files/images/2021/12/articles/body/20231014_wof043.png 1280w" sizes="(min-width: 720px) 640px, 95vw" alt></span></figure><p class="article__body-text"><span>美国宇航局和欧盟运行的地球观测计划哥白尼每个月都会发布上个月全球气温的分析结果。从来没有像九月份那样具有戏剧性。这不仅是有记录以来最热的九月，也是有史以来最热的月份。 NASA 于 10 月 13 日发布的数据显示，在 1951 年至 1980 年的基期中，月平均地表温度（陆地和海洋）比 9 月的正常温度高出 1.47°C。哥白尼将 9 月的平均绝对气温定为 16.38°C ，比之前的记录高出惊人的 0.5°C。</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> 9 月份的峰值虽然非常大，但这也不是气候分析师近几个月来第一次被迫扩大 y 轴。六月、七月、八月天气炎热。 2023年平均气温将首次比工业化前水平高出1.5°C以上的可能性超过90%。 2015 年谈判达成的《巴黎协定》，195 个签署国承诺到 2100 年将全球气温上升控制在 1.5°C 以下。这么快就突破这一神圣门槛是一个可怕的迹象。</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/phkkqjq2j455o4qf1e279gv5v2r91fj5</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/espressochart/2023<category>不确定</category><category>联合国</category><category>刚果民主共和国</category><category>埃塞俄比亚</category><category>印度</category><category>尼日利亚</category><category>巴基斯坦</category><category>中国</category><category>人口增长</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel’s tank commanders are studying Russia’s mistakes]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>像</span><small>每支</small>现代军队一样， <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/11/netanyahu-wages-war-and-fights-for-his-own-survival">以色列将军们</a>在过去一年半的时间里一直在密切关注乌克兰的战斗并做笔记。 10 月 7 日，以色列社区遭受<a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">恐怖袭击</a>，造成 1,400 多人被杀，现在以色列国防军 ( <small>IDF</small> ) 的坦克营已准备好大举进入加沙，这些教训尤其重要。尽管坦克越来越容易受到无人机、徘徊弹药和从顶部攻击的现代反坦克导弹的攻击，但坦克仍然是战场上唯一集机动性、防护性和强大火力于一体的平台。他们将成为以色列地面入侵加沙的先锋队，为身后的步兵部队扫清道路。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “我们看到了俄罗斯人如何在乌克兰作战以及他们犯下的错误，”<small>以色列国防军</small>装甲部队指挥官希沙姆·易卜拉欣准将说，他的职责是让以色列坦克及其人员做好战争准备。 “他们在那里以单军方式作战，而不是使用联合兵种战术，”他解释道。换句话说，俄罗斯的装甲团作为独立的坦克部队作战，而不是与步兵、作战工程和炮兵部队组成一体化编队，并且没有与情报和空中力量的协调。在某些情况下，坦克纵队在没有任何支援的情况下沿着道路排成一列，让乌克兰人将其击落。俄罗斯坦克乘员训练不足，几乎没有表现出遵循自己的条令的迹象。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列装甲部队的形状与以前不同，”易卜拉欣将军说。 “多年来，我们一直在各个级别进行联合训练。我们不再认为坦克能够做所有事情。战场已变；这里更加拥挤和拥挤。这些大平台面临很多挑战，我希望步兵和工兵能够弥补我的劣势。我们参加所有课程和演习的士兵现在已经习惯了在联合兵种环境中作战。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其中许多想法最初是从以色列50年前赎罪日战争期间的大规模坦克战中学到的。在那场冲突中，<small>以色列国防军</small>的装甲营（有时单独行动）因苏联提供的埃及当时新颖的赛格反坦克导弹以及敌方坦克而遭受重大损失。以色列国防军迅速适应，其战术在 20 世纪 70 年代和 80 年代被美国陆军广泛研究和采用。如今，以色列坦克兵被广泛认为是世界上训练有素、准备最充分的坦克兵之一。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但<small>以色列国防军</small>并不是唯一向乌克兰学习的国家。在哈马斯袭击以色列边境之初，袭击者使用携带大型手榴弹的无人机摧毁了观察哨。至少在一个案例中，有这样的手榴弹击中以色列梅卡瓦坦克的镜头。乌克兰人也曾对俄罗斯坦克使用过类似的战术。易卜拉欣将军坚称，虽然边境上的一些坦克被击中“两三次”，但没有一辆被摧毁，所有坦克很快就会恢复使用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，在一些集结区域，人们看到梅卡瓦坦克配备了“顶笼”，即固定在炮塔（车辆最暴露的部分）上方的板条金属屏障，以阻止来自上方的此类攻击。俄罗斯去年使用这种简易装置引起了嘲笑，但以色列的采用表明装甲专业人士越来越严肃地对待无人机的威胁。<small>以色列国防军</small>常规装甲旅使用的梅卡瓦坦克的更先进版本（与预备役人员所使用的梅卡瓦坦克不同）配备了<small>TROPHY</small> ，这是一种极其先进的以色列设计的“主动防护系统”系统，事实证明，它可以有效地击败来袭的敌方坦克。带有向外爆炸的爆炸板的反坦克导弹。然而，并非所有坦克单位都配备该系统。以色列储存库中的每辆坦克，包括早期版本的梅卡瓦坦克，现在都在部署中，这表明即将开展的大规模行动以及保卫以色列与黎巴嫩北部边境的必要性。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">哈马斯袭击开始后两小时内，易卜拉欣将军就通知<small>以色列国防军</small>所有装甲旅指挥官，他们应该开始动员，甚至在军队高层发出正式命令之前。现在，自 1982 年以色列入侵黎巴嫩以来，四十多年来第一次，整个装甲部队都被征召入伍。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这是一支庞大的部队，尽管以色列国防军热衷于保护其作战安全，并未透露具体数字，但据了解其中包括 1000 多辆主战坦克。其中许多并不是为了对加沙进行地面进攻，而是部署在以色列北部，以防与伊朗支持的黎巴嫩运动真主党爆发战争，真主党每天都用火箭弹和迫击炮弹挑衅以色列的回应自 10 月 7 日哈马斯袭击以来的炮击。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果第二条战线确实爆发，以色列坦克兵将进行两种类型的战争。虽然哈马斯和真主党在之前与以色列坦克的交锋中都使用了类似的战术和武器——小型伏击队发射俄罗斯制造（和伊朗提供）的反坦克导弹——但地形将产生很大的不同。在加利利和黎巴嫩南部的丘陵林地地区面对真主党的前景与在加沙城建筑密集的城市地区的战斗截然不同，在加沙城，袭击可能来自近距离。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">多年来，军事专家们一致认为，在狭窄的城市街道上驾驶笨重的坦克作战是一种负担。但更明智的观点是，如果使用得当，并与其他地面部队配合，在全副武装的对手保卫的城市环境中作战时，没有什么可以取代坦克的火力和突破能力。美国指挥官表示，坦克在伊拉克战争的关键城市战斗中发挥着至关重要的作用，包括轻型装甲车无法胜任的情况。在巴格达充满敌意的郊区萨德尔城，美国坦克和其他装甲车组成了一项研究所称的“流动装甲箱”，它们可以缓慢、稳定和安全地移动，而不会使徒步部队面临危险。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与许多其他坦克作战人员相比，以色列坦克军至少有两个优势。一是哈马斯不被认为拥有“顶部攻击”反坦克导弹，如供应给乌克兰的美国“标枪”和英瑞<small>“NLAW”</small>反坦克导弹，这些导弹可以攻击坦克装甲最薄弱的部分——车体顶部。另一个原因是，以色列坦克的设计目的是在该国边境作战，而不是远离家乡，并提供高水平的保护。这使得它们相对笨重，移动性可能较差，但能够承受严重的撞击。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">除了“主动”防护之外，更先进的以色列坦克和步兵战车还拥有先进的通信系统。这些设备将它们连接到一个网络，该网络在坦克的屏幕上为部队提供服务，所有信息都是由其他以色列平台上的传感器收集的，包括盘旋在头顶上的无人机的镜头。 “今天的坦克可以利用从其他来源收集的信息向目标开火，并自行收集信息，这些信息将被其他火源使用，”易卜拉欣将军说。这克服了城市战的传统问题：视线短，其中一个坦克排可能不知道下一个街区周围发生了什么。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与世界各地的坦克将军一样，他非常不同意那些根据俄罗斯的失败推断坦克时代已经结束的人，并引用了 10 月 7 日的事件作为证据。当数千名武装分子沿着边境围栏通过 29 个突破口冲入以色列时，他认为，在某些时候，当天早上驻扎在边境的少量坦克“是唯一剩下的保护层，他们使用了所有武器” 、大炮、机枪，然后跑过去，试图阻止周围数百名试图进入社区的恐怖分子。”由于边境上的大部分观察和摄像头都被摧毁，坦克上往往携带着唯一仍在运行以传递重要信息的监视系统。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最终，<small>以色列国防军</small>那天早上的失败是情报评估和缺乏能够快速到达边境的部队的原因之一。但易卜拉欣将军坚称，在当时抵达基布兹的少数坦克中，“它们是恢复对这些社区的控制和结束流血事件的关键因素。没有什么能像坦克那样做到这一点。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 20:50:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/sku0h3v760nqt55rpagu63lr9drbglll</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/16/israels-tank-commanders-are-stuying- Russias-mistakes </item><item><title><![CDATA[To save Palestinian lives in Gaza, open the crossing into Egypt]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>地面</span>战争尚未开始，伤亡已经在不断增加<small>。</small>加沙的 200 万人口<a href="https://www.economist.com/is-israel-acting-within-the-laws-of-war-in-gaza">挤在一个比伦敦人口还要稠密的空间里</a>。截至我们撰写本文时，飞地内已有超过 2,500 人死亡、近 10,000 人受伤。由于加沙的平均年龄仅为 18 岁，因此许多死者都是儿童。以色列决心<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/15/ehud-barak-blames-binyamin-netanyahu-for-the-greatest-failure-in-israels-history">摧毁哈马斯</a>。城市战是<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/11/brutal-urban-warfare-awaits-israels-army-in-gaza">血腥而激烈的</a>。可怕的事情即将展开。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这就是为什么从<small>联合国</small>秘书长开始，我们正在寻找拯救生命的方法——既在加沙内部，又防止战斗蔓延到以色列与黎巴嫩的北部边境。美国国务卿安东尼·布林肯正在不知疲倦地穿越该地区。他的老板乔·拜登可能很快就会访问耶路撒冷。在这场疯狂的外交活动中，各国政府、援助机构和巴勒斯坦同情者迫切请求以色列克制。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这一目标是崇高而公正的。不幸的是，善意的天真和双重标准正在削弱呼吁以色列停止干涉的呼吁。正如布林肯所表明的那样，保护无辜者的唯一现实途径在于进行冷静的谈判，而最重要的莫过于开放加沙和埃及之间过境点的计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">布林肯先生的首要工作是为好心人设定期望。他们常常认为杀害平民必定违反国际法。然而，哈马斯恐怖分子刚刚通过谋杀 1,400 名以色列人证明了他们所构成的威胁的严重性。作为回应，以色列国防军（ <small>IDF</small> ）可以通过摧毁哈马斯的武器、防御工事和战士来合法地保证国家安全。由于加沙城下方的土地被哈马斯的隧道密布，因此需要地面进攻。即使以色列试图保护许多平民，他们也会死亡，这一可怕的事实并不是对巴勒斯坦人的集体惩罚，而是城市战争的丑陋面目。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">外界有权要求以色列允许医疗用品、食物和水进入加沙。关于什么才算是适当的武力以及以色列对平民的警告是否充分，还有争论的余地。过去，以色列的行动有时有些过分，因为<small>以色列国防军</small>想要证明暴力是没有好处的；最近几天，国防部长竟然开始称哈马斯恐怖分子为“人畜”。然而，当人们对以色列的行为提出要求时，他们常常表现出双重标准，因为他们没有考虑到哈马斯让巴勒斯坦人陷入危险的策略。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在统治加沙的 16 年里，该组织并没有寻求帮助人民繁荣，而是加强对权力的控制，并招募和武装武装分子。它不是在战争中保护加沙人，而是用他们的身体作为活铠甲。过去，它利用清真寺、学校和医院藏匿武器并隐藏指挥所。 10 月 13 日，以色列警告加沙北部居民在入侵之前逃离。哈马斯没有帮助他们撤离，也没有试图通过释放其扣押的 199 名人质来为他们赢得安全前往南部的通道。相反，它试图操纵他们，使他们留在火线中。它知道巴勒斯坦妇女和儿童的死亡将引起国际社会的强烈抗议。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">那么，如何拯救无辜生命呢？部分答案是诉诸以色列的自身利益。摧毁哈马斯符合战争法，但如果消灭它的代价是许多无辜平民的死亡，那么对以色列声誉的损害将迅速攀升。 In addition, the bloodier the fighting in Gaza, the more likely Hizbullah will attack in earnest from its bases in Lebanon. Israel does not want a second front.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Another part of the answer is to appeal to Israel&#39;s values. Mr Blinken put it well when he echoed the sentiments of his president in Israel at the end of last week. “How Israel does this matters,” he said, standing beside Israel&#39;s prime minister, Binyamin Netanyahu. “We democracies distinguish ourselves from terrorists by striving for a different standard.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The immediate task is to save lives by persuading Israel to allow Egypt to open the Rafah crossing between Gaza with the Sinai peninsula. The hundreds of thousands of people moving south of the Wadi Gaza, a boundary set by Israel, will need food, shelter and medical aid on a huge scale. Supplies are being stockpiled on the Egyptian side, waiting to be allowed across into Gaza. Talks are focused on letting dual passport holders and aid workers out of Gaza as the aid goes in. A deal here is urgently needed.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That is unlikely to be enough. To save as many lives as possible, Egypt should also open the Rafah crossing to Palestinians wanting to flee temporarily from Gaza. It is easy to find reasons to object to such a plan. Palestinians understandably fear that they may never be allowed home. The precedent for that is on display in decades-old “temporary” refugee camps in Jordan and Lebanon. For its part, Egypt would not like to be seen to connive in emptying Gaza. It also fears that permanent camps could breed Islamist terrorism that aggravate instability in the Sinai, or blow back into the rest of the country. If, years from now, camps become bases for attacking Israel, they might even poison relations between Egypt and Israel, a cornerstone of Middle East security.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To guard against all of those things, Israel, America, Egypt and well-meaning Arab states, including those who have signed up to the Abraham accords—and Saudi Arabia, which may one day do so—should make a formal guarantee, underwritten by the United States, that the flight into the Sinai would be temporary. Egypt, which is in economic difficulties, may be more amenable if Arab states were to offer it relief on its debts. America could grease the wheels.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> We do not underestimate how hard such an initiative would be to pull off. In the old Middle East the very idea would have been unthinkable. But when Hamas started to massacre Israelis, that world was lost. A new Middle East is up for grabs and Iran, Hizbullah, Hamas and the forces of disorder intend to claim it. What better way to deny them than by a joint plan to save Palestinian lives? <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 20:18:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/p78ei95of50su6vut3gdn7lnv22m8emv</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/16/to-save-palestinian-lives-in-gaza-open-the-crossing-into-egypt</item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel needs to resist irrational retaliation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>“W</span> <small>E WILL OBLITERATE</small> Hamas. We will triumph. It might take time, but we will end this war stronger than ever.” The words of Binyamin Netanyahu, Israel&#39;s prime minister, are intended not only to convey resolve, but also to signal that <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/11/netanyahu-wages-war-and-fights-for-his-own-survival">his war in Gaza</a> is different. No longer is Israel aiming to punish and deter <a href="https://www.economist.com/films/2023/10/13/what-is-hamas">Hamas</a> . Now it wants to destroy it altogether.</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Read more on the war between Israel and Hamas</p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That is a tall order. Hamas is at the same time a religious idea, a social movement, a political party, a government and a hybrid militia wedded to terrorism. Whatever happens in Gaza, Hamas remains a powerful political force in the West Bank. In private conversations, Israeli military officials are defining the objective more narrowly: to seize the main urban centre, Gaza City; wipe out Hamas&#39;s top political and military leadership in the territory; and destroy as much of its military capacity as possible.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That might take weeks or even months of house-to-house fighting, given the extensive tunnel network beneath Gaza. In Iraq and Syria local forces backed by Western air power and thousands of Western troops spent 277 days in the streets of Mosul, and 90 in Raqqa, fighting the jihadists of Islamic State in 2017.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/15/ehud-barak-blames-binyamin-netanyahu-for-the-greatest-failure-in-israels-history">Ehud Barak</a> , a former Israeli prime minister, argues that Israel faces four constraints. Three are about the war: how to fight despite the presence of hostages, how to avoid a two-front war that draws in Lebanon&#39;s Hizbullah militia, and how to manage time given the inevitable erosion of international support as Palestinian suffering grows. A fourth concern is about the day after the fighting: “To whom can we pass the torch?” asks Mr Barak.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The last question is a fiendish problem to which Mr Netanyahu offers no answer. Hamas&#39;s onslaught on October 7th shows that Israel&#39;s policy of controlling the territory from the outside, by sealing its perimeter on land and at sea, is perilous. Yet in the past the occupation of Gaza, which is home to more than 2m people, proved too costly to maintain. Under pressure of violence from Hamas and other militias, Israel withdrew the last of its military forces and Jewish settlers from the territory in 2005.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Without a workable security and political strategy for the “day after”, any military victory may unravel. “Remember Afghanistan. Remember Iraq. Remember Lebanon,” warned Mr Barak on a recent webinar by the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, an American think-tank. He was referring to Israel&#39;s invasion of Lebanon in 1982, and America&#39;s invasion of Afghanistan in 2001 and of Iraq in 2003. All three were provoked by acts of terrorism. All three were marked by great initial military successes. And all three turned into grave political debacles.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “The Israelis are in the same state that we Americans were in right after 9/11,” argues Kenneth Pollack of the American Enterprise Institute, a think-tank in Washington, DC. “We were so angry and so frightened. All we really focused on was destroying anyone who threatened us, and there wasn&#39;t nearly enough attention paid to what comes next.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>What wars on terror wrought</b></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> America&#39;s “global war on terror” started triumphantly. Just two months after al-Qaeda&#39;s attacks on America in September 2001, American-led forces were in control of Kabul, the capital of Afghanistan. The Taliban government was gone. Al-Qaeda was hounded. Its leader, Osama bin Laden, was tracked to Pakistan and killed in 2011. But the Taliban fought a growing insurgency. Having lost more than 2,400 military personnel, America left in 2021. The Afghan government collapsed almost immediately and the Taliban returned to power. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_EPC052.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"> <span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">image: The Economist</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The war in Iraq was inglorious, too, and far bloodier. Once again, American forces quickly took the capital, Baghdad, in April 2003. President George W. Bush strutted on the flight deck of the <i>USS Abraham Lincoln</i> , an aircraft-carrier, under the sign: “Mission Accomplished”. In fact, the country was about to slip into civil war. American forces captured Saddam Hussein, Iraq&#39;s dictator, but soon faced bloody insurgencies by both Sunni and Shia militias. American forces withdrew in 2011 but returned in smaller numbers in 2014 to help beat back Islamic State after it captured swathes of Iraq and Syria (see chart). All told, America lost some 4,500 service members, not to mention some 300,000 Iraqis who died, most of them civilians.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For Hussein Ibish of the Arab Gulf States Institute in Washington, an American think-tank, the lessons are clear. Terrorist and insurgent groups, he argues, resort to spectacular violence to provoke an irrational response: “They know that the harm that they can do to the dominant power is limited. They understand that the harm that the dominant power can do to itself is infinitely greater.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Israel&#39;s own history offers similar warnings. In June 1982, amid artillery exchanges across Israel&#39;s northern border with the Palestine Liberation Organisation ( <small>PLO</small> ), the Palestinian umbrella group, gunmen shot and wounded Israel&#39;s ambassador in London. The Israeli government took the attack as a <i>casus belli</i> to invade Lebanon and dismantle the <small>PLO</small> , even though the hit was attributed to its rival, the Abu Nidal group. Israeli forces besieged the <small>PLO</small> in west Beirut, forcing its leader, Yasser Arafat, and thousands of fighters, to sail away into exile. Israel&#39;s Christian ally, Bachir Gemayel, was elected Lebanon&#39;s president.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Then it all fell apart. Gemayel was blown up. In sight of Israeli forces, his Phalangist fighters exacted revenge by killing Palestinians in the Sabra and Chatila refugee camps. An Israeli commission of inquiry found that Ariel Sharon, Israel&#39;s defence minister, was indirectly responsible, and he was demoted. Within a year, under pressure from anti-war protests, Menachem Begin, the prime minister, announced his resignation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One effect of the Lebanese imbroglio was that the <small>PLO</small> was replaced by Hizbullah, a more formidable Shia militia, which succeeded in pushing Israel out of Lebanon in 2000. Another impact was on Palestinians within the Israeli-occupied West Bank and Gaza Strip. Their first intifada, or “shaking off”, a stone-throwing uprising that started in 1987, set the stage for the Oslo accords between Israel and the <small>PLO</small> of 1993. Arafat made a triumphant return to Gaza the following year.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Hamas emerged as the main force of violent rejectionism. Copying Hizbullah&#39;s suicide tactics, it did much to destroy the Oslo accords. It forced Israel out of Gaza in 2005 and won the Palestinian legislative elections in 2006. The following year it pushed out the Palestinian Authority ( <small>PA</small> ), the administration created by the <small>PLO</small> . Bereft of Arafat, who died in 2004; stuck in parcels of autonomous territory in the West Bank; and unable to make progress towards statehood by negotiation, the <small>PA</small> was rapidly discredited as it sank into autocracy and corruption.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Deterrence theory</b></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Since 2006 Israel&#39;s wars have been based on punishment and deterrence, seeking not to destroy its enemies but to inflict such a heavy price as to dissuade the likes of Hamas and Hizbullah from attacking Israel.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Deterrence, though, is hard to measure. In the case of Hizbullah, it has generally held since the last big war in Lebanon in 2006, sparked by a cross-border Hizbullah raid that captured two Israeli soldiers. The fighting led to widespread destruction, notably in Dahieh, a Shia neighbourhood of Beirut. Hizbullah&#39;s leader, Hassan Nasrallah, later admitted he would not have ordered the raid had he known Israel&#39;s reaction would be so severe.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In Gaza, though, periods of calm have been shorter. Israel has engaged in what some call “mowing the grass”, ie, periodically beating down Hamas to weaken it. In response to Hamas rocket fire, Israeli forces have relied mostly on retaliatory bombardment, and the protection of its Iron Dome air-defence system. Ground units have entered Gaza only reluctantly.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Deterrence holds until suddenly it doesn&#39;t. Hamas&#39;s bloodlust on October 7th was “perhaps the most cruel action in 100 years of conflict between Israel and Palestinians”, notes Mr Ibish. Yet Israel is falling into Hamas&#39;s “trap” in the ferocity of its retribution. The fighting will turn international sympathy from Israel to the Palestinians, allow Hamas to claim leadership of the Palestinian cause and wreck prospects for rapprochement between Israel and Saudi Arabia, contends Mr Ibish.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Israel is in no mood for restraint. Forget mowing the grass; it wants extirpation. But such uprooting creates a new problem. “If you are going to eliminate Hamas it&#39;s a political issue, not a military one,” says Lawrence Freedman of King&#39;s College London. “You have to establish something, or else Hamas is going to come back.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The Israelis in Lebanon in 1982, and the Americans in Afghanistan and Iraq after 2001, had allies on the ground and day-after plans of sorts, flawed as they turned out to be. In Gaza today, Israel is acting alone. The <small>PA</small> is weak and cannot be seen to return to Gaza on Israeli tanks. Most Arab governments have little love for Hamas, but little courage to be seen conspiring with Israel against it.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “I don&#39;t care what happens next,” says Eitan Shamir, director of the Begin-Sadat Center for Strategic Studies, an Israeli think-tank. “Whatever it is, it starts with destroying Hamas.” The Allies went to war against the Nazis and only later developed a plan to run post-war Germany, he notes. In his view, America&#39;s and Israel&#39;s misadventures began when they started to meddle in local politics instead of leaving promptly. Moreover, America&#39;s experience has little relevance to Israel, says Mr Shamir. It was involved in expeditionary wars, and could bring troops home: “Israel is completely different. We are fighting for our homes. We have no other choice.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For the many Israelis who, like Mr Shamir, think peace is out of reach for the foreseeable future, the only option is to keep hitting foes hard, until they disappear or change. If the current war brings Israel some years of quiet, they say, that is good enough.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Israel, though, does not have a free hand. International law and sometimes domestic opinion limit how harsh its response can be. It relies on the West, especially America, to fend off international pressure, but its support is not unlimited. The promise that America “has Israel&#39;s back” risks making it complicit in Israel&#39;s actions, to the detriment of its interests in the region and elsewhere. To take one example: Arab commentators are already drawing comparisons between America&#39;s denunciations of Russia&#39;s atrocities in Ukraine and its forbearance of Israel&#39;s bombardment of Gaza.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such concerns explain why Antony Blinken, the secretary of state, has been shuttling across the Middle East seeking to open a humanitarian corridor, allowing vital supplies into Gaza and at least some people out to Egypt. For now, though, Mr Blinken&#39;s thinking about a post-Hamas world is mostly one of platitudes: “a region that comes together, integrated, normalised relations among its countries, people working in common purpose to common benefit.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A solution will not be easy. That is all the more reason to think about it now. Jay Garner, the American general charged with setting the new administration in Iraq in 2003, complained that George Marshall, the American army chief during the second world war, had enjoyed more than two years to plan for post-Hitler Germany, whereas he was being given just a few months to prepare for post-Saddam Iraq. Israel and the world may have even less time to prepare for what comes after Hamas in Gaza. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 19:52:41 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/sdbm3j34bgsjiqq7jdmt62bfbqgiddag</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/international/2023/10/16/israel-needs-to-resist-irrational-retaliation </item><item><title><![CDATA[Wartime leaders usually get a popularity bump. Israel’s hasn’t]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>T THE START</small> of wars or national-security crises, democratic leaders usually enjoy a surge in popular support. In the two weeks after the attacks of September 11th 2001 George W. Bush&#39;s approval rating rose from 51% to 90%. Binyamin Netanyahu, Israel&#39;s prime minister, has seen no such bump. The first polls taken since Hamas, a Palestinian militant group, killed over 1,400 people on <a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">October 7th</a> suggest that rather than rallying around the flag, <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/15/ehud-barak-blames-binyamin-netanyahu-for-the-greatest-failure-in-israels-history">Israelis</a> are turning on their government.</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Read more on the war between Israel and Hamas</p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On October 11th Camil Fuchs, a statistician at Tel Aviv University, released a survey of 620 Jewish Israelis, in which 95% of respondents expressing an opinion said that Hamas&#39;s raid represented a failure by Mr Netanyahu&#39;s government. Even among those who had voted for parties in his right-wing coalition, this share was 93%. By nearly as large a margin respondents said that the authorities&#39; lapse was even more serious than that at the start of the Yom Kippur war of 1973, when Israel failed to anticipate simultaneous surprise attacks by Egypt and Syria. The poll did not ask whether Mr Netanyahu should resign immediately but three-quarters of those with opinions said that the prime minister should step down once hostilities end.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Two days later <i>Maariv</i> , an Israeli newspaper, released its first poll of voting intentions since the Hamas attack. It found that if elections were held today, a centrist alliance of opposition parties led by Benny Gantz, a former defence minister who recently agreed to join an emergency war cabinet, would secure a majority with 78 seats while the governing coalition would win just 42. Respondents also said they would prefer Mr Gantz as prime minister to Mr Netanyahu by a margin of 48% to 29%.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Facing such grim numbers at home, Mr Netanyahu might find some solace abroad. In an online survey in France conducted in May by YouGov, respondents who were asked if they sympathised more with the Israeli or Palestinian side of the conflict preferred the Palestinians by 22% to 13%. Last week that ratio had reversed, as 29% of French participants leaned towards the Israelis, compared with 14% for the Palestinians. YouGov&#39;s polls in America show a similar pattern. From July 2014 to this March, Israel&#39;s lead over the Palestinians in support from Americans shrank from 27 percentage points to 18. Last week it bounced back to 33 points: 42% of respondents backed Israel, and just 9% supported the Palestinians. A survey by <small>CNN</small> on October 12th and 13th found that 90% of Americans expressing an opinion thought that Israel&#39;s military response to the attacks was at least partially justified.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As Israel&#39;s assault on Gaza gathers pace, however, things may change yet again. In YouGov&#39;s poll both sides gained around seven percentage points of support, compared with March among American participants aged 18-29—already the age group least friendly to Israel. In contrast, the share of respondents who were unsure or felt equal sympathy for both sides fell sharply. In other words, Hamas&#39;s attack has pushed undecided young Americans to pick a side; for each former waverer who chose the Israelis, another opted for the Palestinians. As international attention turns from Hamas&#39;s atrocities to the human cost of Israel&#39;s retaliatory air strikes in the Gaza Strip, support for Israel may once again ebb away. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 19:04:17 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/eueh4i1ket6i0emdadt62ls1k0qb8t4n</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/16/wartime-leaders-usually-get-a-popularity-bump-israels-hasnt </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are America’s allies the holes in its export-control fence?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>MERICA MAKES no</small> bones about wanting to stop China, its autocratic rival for geopolitical supremacy, from getting hold of advanced technology. Any day now the White House is expected to extend restrictions on sales to the country of advanced microchips used in training artificial-intelligence ( <small>AI</small> ) models. This is the latest set of export controls designed to prevent cutting-edge tech that America helped create, meaning most of it these days, from making its way to the Chinese mainland. It is also meant to close a loophole, which allowed Chinese firms&#39; foreign subsidiaries to procure chips that their parents were barred from purchasing.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The loophole is almost certainly not the last one that will need closing. Just this month America itself created room for a few more. Last year it imposed sweeping restrictions that cut off people and firms in China from many advanced technologies of American origin, including types of cutting-edge<small> </small>chips, software to design them and tools to manufacture them. On October 9th it granted two South Korean chipmakers, Samsung and <small>SK</small> Hynix, indefinite waivers to install chipmaking equipment that falls under these restrictions in their factories in China. Four days later <small>TSMC</small> , Taiwan&#39;s chipmaking champion, also received a dispensation. The carve-outs were secured (and announced) by governments in Seoul and Taipei, which are keen to protect their domestic firms&#39; vast commercial interests in China. They also shine a light on the knotty nature of the American-led global <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/03/30/americas-commercial-sanctions-on-china-could-get-much-worse">export-control regime</a> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> American sanctions&#39; global pretensions depend on the co-operation of allies. In principle, democratic governments in Asia and Europe are <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2023/09/14/chinese-carmakers-are-under-scrutiny-in-europe">similarly wary</a> of China, and devising their own export controls. In practice, their policies are not always aligned with Uncle Sam&#39;s. The result could be a mesh of rules that, once in place, would impose costs on technology companies without doing much to bolster national security in the way that the regimes&#39; architects envisioned.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This is not the first time that the democratic world has attempted to stem the flow of technology to undemocratic adversaries. After the second world war 17 countries, led by America, established the Co-ordinating Committee for Multilateral Export Controls to limit exports of strategic resources and technologies to the Communist bloc. The body was disbanded in 1994, once the Soviet threat was no more.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> America&#39;s efforts to co-ordinate some of its anti-Chinese restrictions have so far been much more piecemeal. The closest President Joe Biden&#39;s administration has come to co-ordination is an opaque agreement sealed in January with Japan and the Netherlands. This was important to America because Dutch and Japanese firms such as <small>ASML</small> and Tokyo Electron, respectively, are the sole manufacturers of sophisticated chipmaking tools without which it is almost impossible to make the most advanced semiconductors. In July Japan&#39;s government introduced rules limiting the exports of advanced chip technology. The Dutch followed suit in September.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Look closer, though, and the nuts and bolts of the three countries&#39; export controls vary considerably. The Bureau of Industry and Security ( <small>BIS</small> ), America&#39;s export-control agency, publishes an “entity list” of thousands of companies, including plenty of Chinese ones, that are barred from being sold certain types of technology. Japan has no such public entity list. Instead, it has announced a list of 23 specific types of product which require an export licence. The Japanese government has assiduously avoided mentioning China specifically, for fear of sparking the ire of a big trading partner. The Netherlands&#39; controls, too, are “country-neutral” and applied to a handful of products.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Various national regimes diverge in other meaningful ways. American allies in Europe and Asia have not tried to copy the long, extraterritorial reach of American sanctions. As a result, Asian and European companies that wish to continue selling technology to Chinese customers can in theory establish subsidiaries in places without strict export controls (at least as long as the firms do not rely on American inputs).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The situation in Europe is complicated further by the division of responsibilities between national governments and the European Union. For now individual <small>EU</small> members retain discretion over export controls related to their national security. But given the bloc&#39;s single market in goods, which lets technology flow across borders unimpeded, Eurocrats in Brussels want a greater say. On October 3rd the European Commission presented a list of areas deemed critical to the bloc&#39;s economic security. It would like the ability to impose <small>EU</small> -wide export controls in these areas, which include advanced chips, quantum computing and artificial intelligence. It is unclear how long it will take the 27 <small>EU</small> members to reach the consensus required to grant the commission such powers—if it can be reached at all.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Things get blurrier still when it comes to enforcing the rules. In most countries the bureaucratic capacity to police export-control regimes is limited. America&#39;s <small>BIS</small> , widely considered to be better endowed than similar agencies in other countries, has fewer than 600 employees and an annual budget of just over $200m—a modest figure given the outfit&#39;s global remit. Its Asian and European counterparts must make do with far less.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The relevant agencies often lack the expertise to assess exporters&#39; requests for a licence to sell products abroad. That requires an understanding of how a particular piece of equipment could be used. It is almost impossible to tell how such equipment will actually be used once it arrives in China. This year the <small>BIS</small> set aside a relatively piddling sum of $6m for inspections to be conducted abroad—and little if any is likely to be spent in China, which does not exactly welcome American inspectors with open arms. Many of the <small>BIS</small> ’s poorer cousins in other countries rely entirely on the exporting companies themselves to determine the actual end-use of their products—something the firms cannot know for sure either.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The result is a mishmash of opaque rules and fitful enforcement actions. Manufacturers of sensitive technologies are left guessing about what business they can and cannot do with Chinese firms. Four Taiwanese firms—Cica-Huntek Chemical Technology Taiwan, <small>L</small> &amp; <small>K</small> Engineering, Topco Scientific and United Integrated Services—recently found themselves under investigation by Taiwan&#39;s government after reports surfaced that they were involved in building a new network of chip factories in China. The four companies all deny that they have broken any sanctions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Lack of co-ordination may also explain why the system is not keeping high tech out of China as intended. In South Korea, <small>SK</small> Hynix is looking into how some of its older memory chips ended up in the latest smartphone made by Huawei. <small>SK</small> Hynix denies doing business with the Chinese telecoms giant. The Huawei smartphone in question, the Mate 60 Pro, also sported advanced microprocessors furnished by <small>SMIC</small> , China&#39;s biggest chip-manufacturer. Both Huawei and <small>SMIC</small> feature on <small>BIS</small> ’s entity list and were thought incapable of such chipmaking feats. Export comptrollers in America and its allies are still trying to work out how exactly the two companies pulled them off. This is unlikely to be the last China-related surprise they have to deal with. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:35:06 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/sa1am1ptsutss82am020dobpn9ij6rno</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/10/16/are-americas-allies-the-holes-in-its-export-control-fence </item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel’s agony, the backlash against greenery and a two-day workweek: misery or bliss?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>A</span> <small>selection of</small> three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of <i>The Economist</i> . This week, will <a href="/leaders/2023/10/12/will-israels-agony-and-retribution-end-in-chaos-or-stability">Israel&#39;s agony</a> and retribution end in chaos or stability? Also, the backlash against <a href="/leaders/2023/10/12/how-to-deal-with-the-global-anti-climate-backlash">green policies</a> (09:58) and a disastrous <a href="/business/2023/10/12/trialling-the-two-day-workweek">workplace experiment</a> (16:15). Runtime: 24 min </p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomisteditorspicks/e/652d5ea108a248001253a136/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6IjdKQnY5d0VUIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&sig=_WJzVVeksKNwmFm7P9_yJwbGyx-MQwmbLFS6mm3xh6A"><p> Your browser does not support the<audio> element.</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text"> Sign up for Economist Podcasts+ now and get 50% off your subscription with our <a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Deditors-picks">limited time offer</a> . You will not be charged until Economist Podcasts+ launches.</p><p class="article__body-text"> If you&#39;re already a subscriber to <i>The Economist</i> , you&#39;ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.</p><p class="article__body-text"> For more information about Economist Podcasts+, including how to get access, please visit our <a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">FAQs page</a> .</p><p class="article__body-text"> Listen on: <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/id313848583">Apple Podcasts</a> | <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/3a5n4DoT1xrV5rgBWBPxnR">Spotify</a></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:00:59 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/vovf5l2h0eqtcrddqs5dkb6njbj0q1p1</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/16/israels-agony-the-backlash-against-greenery-and-a-two-day-workweek-misery-or-bliss</item></channel></rss>