<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[China]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/china?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[China - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 2 日星期四 05:27:30 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Why China and India are watching the Dalai Lama closely]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20China_%20India%20and%20the%20Dalai%20Lama-737858a6b455ca1e8481968a749e4c5a.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>不久前</span><small>，</small>达赖喇嘛的行程排得很满。这位西藏精神领袖于 1959 年逃亡印度后的 60 年里，访问了数十个国家，沿途会见了皇室成员、宗教领袖和四位在任美国总统。最近，他的脚步放慢了。原因之一是他的年龄（他今年 88 岁）。 Covid-19也让旅行变得复杂，中国对他的东道主施加的处罚也使旅行变得复杂，中国认为他是分裂分子。不过，尽管他自 2018 年以来就没有出过国，但他承诺继续在印度境内旅行。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，当达赖喇嘛十月份取消四次印度之行时，流亡藏人及其同情者的担忧是可以理解的。其中包括东北部的阿鲁纳恰尔邦，该邦特别敏感。中国声称该邦是其领土，并在 1962 年与印度长达一个月的战争中短暂占领了该邦的大部分地区。自 2017 年达赖喇嘛上次访问阿鲁纳恰尔邦以来，该邦和其他边境地区的争端重新燃起，这引起了中国的愤怒。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_CNM948.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达赖喇嘛的代表将取消活动归咎于最近爆发的流感。但他们很快补充说，他的健康没有受到严重威胁，并指出他已在印度北部达兰萨拉的第二故乡恢复了正常活动。他们对印度政府是否要求他推迟阿鲁纳恰尔邦之行守口如瓶，他们通常在任何此类旅行之前都会咨询印度政府。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">印度官员没有回应就此问题发表评论的请求。他们过去曾表示，达赖喇嘛可以自由地前往印度任何地方。去年，他们帮助安排他访问印度拉达克地区，该地区最近与中国军队发生了边境冲突。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不管怎样，取消活动都暗示着达赖喇嘛晚年面临的令人担忧的地缘政治。他的活动，尤其是在边境地区的活动，不仅可能在不稳定的印中关系中引发新的危机。他的健康状况也越来越受到印度和中国官员的关注，更不用说藏传佛教徒了。所有人都在为达赖喇嘛去世后的一个潜在的混乱时期做好准备，届时中国预计将任命一位与藏传佛教传统相竞争的继任者，后者很可能被其助手<a href="https://www.economist.com/1843/2023/07/27/china-wants-to-choose-the-next-dalai-lama-he-has-other-plans">认定为达赖喇嘛的转世</a>灵童。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达赖喇嘛计划改变的第一个迹象是，他的办公室宣布，原定于 10 月 16 日至 22 日访问东北部锡金邦和邻近的西孟加拉邦的访问因洪水而推迟。随后当地媒体于 10 月 10 日报道称，他取消了阿鲁纳恰尔邦首席部长原定于 10 月或 11 月访问阿鲁纳恰尔邦的行程（并于 9 月召开了一次筹备会议）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达赖喇嘛办公室10月20日发表声明称，由于最近感染流感，他也不会在11月访问锡金，并将取消未来几周前往印度南部的计划。声明称，达赖喇嘛的医生“强烈建议任何旅行都会产生负担”。声明补充说，他将于12月前往印度东部的菩提伽耶，但没有提及前任达赖喇嘛的出生地阿鲁纳恰尔邦。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">西藏流亡政府发言人丹增列克谢(Tenzin Lekshay)表示，达赖喇嘛办公室从未正式证实阿鲁纳恰尔邦之行，有几个因素可能影响了有关此行的讨论，包括达赖喇嘛的健康状况、阿鲁纳恰尔邦的恶劣地形以及外交影响。莱克谢表示，无论达赖喇嘛前往何处，他“都不希望给东道国带来任何不便”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这个时机对中国和印度来说都很敏感，两国的领土争端还涉及中国控制的阿克赛钦地区，印度声称对该地区拥有主权。近年来，争端再次爆发，事实上的边界沿线发生了几起冲突。 2020 年发生的一起事件造成 20 名印度士兵和 4 名中国士兵死亡，这是该地区自 1967 年以来最严重的暴力事件。去年 12 月在阿鲁纳恰尔邦边境发生的另一起事件造成双方轻伤。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国最近还重申了对阿鲁纳恰尔邦的主权要求，称该地区为藏南，意思是藏南。该国已经为那里的村庄发布了自己的名称，并发布了一张显示阿鲁纳恰尔邦在其境内的官方地图。对此，印度提出抗议，并于10月24日派国防部长拉杰纳特·辛格前往阿鲁纳恰尔邦。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">后退一步</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管有这些争吵，但双方似乎都不希望发生冲突。事实上，自 2020 年 6 月以来军事指挥官会谈的结果是，中国和印度已从大部分边境热点地区撤军，建立了没有任何巡逻的缓冲区。局势的逐步缓和表明，中国领导人习近平比近年来更加渴望稳定与印度的关系，或许是为了阻止印度与美国建立更紧密的军事关系。中国官员还希望在达赖喇嘛去世后削弱国际社会对西藏的支持，特别是印度的支持。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">稳定边境似乎也是印度总理纳伦德拉·莫迪的首要任务。他需要从中国进口来实现他的经济目标。由于大选将于 2024 年举行，他可能还担心，鉴于中国的军事优势，进一步的冲突可能会损害他的声望。但他不想被视为屈服于中国的要求。政治对手指责他太轻易放弃领土。达赖喇嘛在印度广受欢迎。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与此同时，西藏流亡政府必须平衡对达赖喇嘛健康状况的担忧和促进其事业的需要，包括在印度的藏人中间（过去十年左右，有数万名藏人离开印度）。但它也必须维持印度的支持，它希望这将有助于使达赖喇嘛的追随者选择的转世灵童合法化并提供庇护。 “我们相信印度也会向下一任达赖喇嘛提供同样的协议，”西藏流亡政府领导人边巴次仁 (Penpa Tsering) 9 月表示。至于现任达赖喇嘛，他表示，一旦“90岁左右”，他将制定转世细节。他经常预言自己会活到 113 岁以上<span class="ufinish">。 ■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:35:33 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/ofsba1ovppvguj4g4pjabm0t3d52mpns</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/26/why-china-and-india-are-watching-the-dalai-lama-closely </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rumours swirl after China’s defence minister, Li Shangfu, is sacked]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/033%20China%20-%20High-level%20purges-d3e818496efeeebd9e2f8d1ec45704fe.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国国家情报总局局长陈一新上个月表示，网络谣言是中国面临的<small>最大</small>网络威胁<span>之一</span>。正如他所说：“一件小事，可能会酿成舆论漩涡。”然而，共产党对保密的偏好却让谣言四起。经过几周的猜测，他陷入了政治麻烦，政府于 10 月 24 日宣布，国防部长李尚福已被免职。它没有给出任何理由，但正如许多网友正确猜测的那样，这远非例行公事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">李将军的麻烦与有关秦刚的丑闻不谋而合，秦刚于7月失去了外交部长的职位。根据该公告，两人还被剥夺了国务委员的额外头衔：中国内阁中的高级职位目前仅由三人担任。自8月29日以来，李将军就没有在公开场合露面，他也被赶出了国家中央军事委员会，这是一个名义上的机构，复制了另一个由党控制的实权机构。此次清洗的最后一步预计将在党中央委员会的年度会议上完成。这次约 370 名显要人物的聚会几乎肯定会剥夺这两个人的委员会成员资格，就李将军而言，他在党的军事委员会的职务也将被剥夺。会议日期尚未确定，但可能即将举行。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">两位如此显赫的官员在升任后不久就如此迅速地继任而失宠（两人都担任部长不到一年），这已经足够引人注目了。更引人注目的是，两人的离开都被视为中国领导人习近平的得意门生。没有迹象表明习近平本人陷入了严重的政治麻烦。秦先生的继任者外交部长王毅（也是秦先生的前任）将于 10 月 26 日至 28 日访问美国。预计他将讨论习近平和总统乔·拜登之间可能于 11 月举行的会面。有关习近平活动的新闻仍然充斥着官方媒体。在国家电视台的晚间新闻中，在有关李将军和秦先生的简短报道之前，有一个较长的报道，内容是习近平向商界人士传达的信息。服从党的重要性是一个中心主题。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最新消息传出后，微博平台微博的一些用户暗示了在国外和中国的线下对话中流传的未经证实的故事：秦先生在担任驻华盛顿大使期间有婚外情，李将军是此前担任军事采购负责人期间涉嫌腐败。有网友询问，两人的垮台是否还有其他隐秘原因。 “从这个层面来说，这已经不能简单地归结为腐败案件了，”一位微博用户表示。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">他们的疑问是正确的。同样在10月24日，广东省前公安局长李春生被正式指控。他被指控腐败，但北京的<i>财</i>新杂志表示，他的职业生涯与前公安部副部长孙立军“有过交集”，孙立军去年因多项罪行被判处死刑缓期执行，其中包括收受超过 9000 万美元的贿赂。官方媒体称，孙先生还结成“政治集团”，对党的政策进行“无端批评”，并散布政治谣言。通过清洗和审查制度，该党正在传播更多此类内容。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:35:33 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/bs2j2f3etruhnr99tsu48e68mv1ervua</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/26/rumours-swirl-after-chinas-defence-minister-is-dismissed </item><item><title><![CDATA[How China sees Gaza]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/034%20China%20-%20Chaguan-838b3a4540700b8a7567a938bac78c6d.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">就在哈马斯袭击以色列<small>前</small><span>一个多月</span>，中国外交政策负责人王毅对席卷中东的“和解浪潮”表示欢迎，并将功劳归功于自己的国家。作为证据，王先生列举了今年早些时候在中国斡旋下达成的一项协议，旨在恢复该地区两大宗派竞争对手伊朗和沙特阿拉伯之间的外交关系。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 8月20日，王毅在致电伊朗外长时解释了为什么中国的务实主义使其成为理想的和平缔造者。王毅承诺，为了帮助该地区实现“睦邻友好”，中国将继续奉行不带偏见、以贸易为主导的国际关系方针。或者，正如他所说，中国将帮助中东国家找到“适合自身国情的发展道路”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种自信已经建立了一段时间。外交官们表示，伊朗-沙特协议在三月份签署后，自豪的中国官员就通知中东各国政府，他们已准备好解决以色列-巴勒斯坦冲突——尽管该计划缺乏细节。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">两位与中国情报部门有机构联系的学者七月下旬与一家政府智库发表了一篇论文，认为外国干预的倾向导致美国、英国、法国和苏联在中东都失败了。教授们写道，令人高兴的是，中国能够通过强调“对话”和“相互尊重”来发挥调解人的作用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">八月份，北京大学阿拉伯与伊斯兰文化研究所所长吴冰冰在<i>《北京文化评论》</i>上发表的一篇文章中，采取了更为有力的措辞。他的文章被时事通讯<i>《汉化》</i>发现并翻译后，在北京的外国使馆被广泛阅读。它赞扬中国注重发展和安全，拒绝选边站队。吴先生写道，这种“积极平衡”可以克服据称难以解决的敌意，因为伊朗和沙特阿拉伯等竞争对手正在争夺中国的商业利益。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果指责中国未能发现十月迫在眉睫的恐怖事件，那是不公平的。就在哈马斯袭击前八天，美国国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文称中东比二十年来“更加平静”。但我们可以公平地问，中国在入侵前的狂妄有多少能够在这个黑暗、血腥的中东时刻幸存下来。查官的初步回答是，中国人的信心比想象中的要强，尽管并不总是出于令人振奋的原因。这是基于中国对危机的公开反应以及与外国外交官的私下对话。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国对地区冲突不感兴趣是有建设性的理由的。它是许多中东国家最大的贸易伙伴，并被认为是伊朗和沙特石油的最大单一买家（伊朗石油销售是一项不透明的业务）。它与富裕的海湾国家的经济联系最为紧密，但它也渴望帮助重建饱受战争蹂躏的国家，例如在伊拉克投资数十亿美元。西方和中东许多国家的政府都要求中国敦促伊朗避免煽动冲突。外交官认为，中国愿意与伊朗讲道理。中国也有影响力。但他们补充说，归根结底，伊朗最想要的不是中国，而是美国：达成一项结束核相关制裁和伊朗孤立的协议。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不太令人高兴的是，加沙战争并没有削弱中国独裁世界观对许多中东统治者的吸引力。他们感谢中国没有对他们进行人权教育。王先生于 2022 年宣布，海湾合作委员会六个国家反过来支持中国在其偏远西部地区新疆的“合法”行动。这些政策包括拆除清真寺、监禁阿訇以及将多达 100 万穆斯林从新疆遣送回国。以铲除伊斯兰极端主义为名，将维吾尔族少数民族关进再教育营。许多阿拉伯政府害怕并厌恶草根“政治伊斯兰教”——这种虔诚会导致在后街清真寺里进行反政府布道——并相信这正是中国在新疆所进行的斗争。此外，维吾尔人是突厥人，阿拉伯人和土耳其人之间的竞争根深蒂固。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">美国和以色列的政客对中国拒绝称哈马斯为恐怖组织以及在官方媒体上淡化哈马斯暴行的做法提出了质疑，尽管中国的主要新闻节目每天晚上都会报道以色列空袭加沙的图片。在某种程度上，中国对哈马斯的立场反映了其长期以来的观点，即巴勒斯坦暴力的根源是缺乏国家。它还反映出人们对世界秩序的偏好，这种秩序旨在通过平衡民族国家的利益来解决危机，而不是通过抽象地诉诸普世价值，中国称之为西方的发明。据称，实际上，中国将哈马斯视为其希望的政治实体。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">拜登受到指责</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最不高兴的是，加沙冲突为将美国描绘成一个恃强凌弱的战争贩子提供了一个新的机会。乔·拜登总统没有将以色列紧紧拥抱以遏制以色列的功绩归功于他，而是将自私的动机归咎于他。中国前中东特使吴思科是无数坚持要求拜登支持以色列的中国声音之一，因为他面临2024年的大选，并担心犹太裔美国人的“影响”。在思考加沙溢出效应时，中国学者称赞美国斡旋的以色列与沙特谈判脱轨是对拜登连任的“沉重打击”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">打击美国不会给中东带来和解浪潮。但中国正在打一场持久战。民意调查已经显示，许多阿拉伯国家的公众对中国的支持超过对美国的支持。整个发展中国家对美国的不信任因战争而加深。美国重返中东并不是中国不久前所希望看到的。但如果这场危机分散了其强大竞争对手的注意力并削弱了其实力，中国就会采取行动。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><b>阅读我们的中国专栏作家查官的更多内容：<br></b><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article73394-prod.ece">习近平希望得到南半球国家的喜爱</a>（10月19日）<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article72643-prod.ece">中美关系略有回暖</a>（10月12日）<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article70369-prod.ece">中国希望成为南半球的领导者</a>（9月21日）</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>另：茶馆柱如何<a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">得名</a></i></p></div>]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:35:33 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/o8cjra860mcaas9l2cic8soq9hf6v3am</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/26/how-china-sees-gaza </item><item><title><![CDATA[Chinese feminists are rebuilding their movement abroad]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/036%20China%20-%20Chinese%20feminism-69533567303b645ee5b82c73cd83f1fa.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>两名</span><small>中国</small>女性坐在曼哈顿一家地下室喜剧俱乐部的舞台上。他们穿着配套的西装外套，说着非常正式的普通话，就像中国国家电视台的主持人一样。但他们的“新闻评论”却很尖刻。一位新闻播音员坚称，最近不断向日本拨打骚扰电话，抗议福岛核电站失事排放废水的中国年轻人，在哄堂大笑的人群中表现出了“值得赞扬的精神”。尽管“没有工作或收入”，这些民族主义年轻人“把自己的钱花在长途电话上”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">两人是中国女权主义脱口秀“女字珠艺”（一种文字游戏，可以解读为“女性的想法”或“好想法”）的表演者。这是由中国年轻女性领导的一种新的、不敬的侨民激进主义形式的一部分。每个月，“女字主义”都会邀请中国公民，其中大部分是女性，登上纽约的舞台，说出她们在国内永远不会在公共场合说的话。他们的日常生活包括向保守的父母出柜的故事；关于性骚扰或移民困难的投诉；甚至还有关于中国警方拘留和虐待的报道。他们的故事大部分都很有趣。很多都是苦乐参半。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于自认为女权主义者的中国人来说，现在不是好时机。 2010年代初，女权活动人士在中国发起了频繁的公众抗议活动。他们占领男厕所，穿着染成红色的婚纱在街上游行，抗议性别不平等和家庭暴力。此类活动在 2015 年突然结束。那一年，五名著名女权主义者在国际妇女节前夕因策划一场反对公共交通性骚扰的运动而被拘留。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在这些逮捕事件发生后，中国女权主义在很大程度上转移到了网上。 2018年，中国的#MeToo运动正是在互联网上兴起。女性指控著名教授、商人和电视名人性侵犯，在某些情况下还提起诉讼。但大多数都失败了，原告有时会因诽谤而被起诉。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最引人注目的#MeToo 案件之一是由一位名叫周晓轩的女士提起的，她指控电视节目主持人朱军在她还是实习生时强行亲吻她。朱先生否认这一指控；中国法院于 2021 年驳回了此案。周女士及其支持者在网上受到审查，而民族主义者则被允许传播称#MeToo 是破坏中国稳定的阴谋的视频。同年，首批报道#MeToo 案件的中国记者之一黄雪芹被捕，并被指控“煽动颠覆国家政权”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在打击女权主义者的同时，共产党也加大了对传统性别角色的宣传力度。中国领导人习近平呼吁复兴儒家思想，鼓励妇女成为贤妻良母，教导家人爱国。自他上台以来，中国通过实施30天的强制性“冷静期”来限制离婚，禁止女性化男性出现在电视上，并鼓励地方政府尝试可能促进人们生育的计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">所有这些都让许多女权活动人士噤声或迫使她们逃往海外。一些参与纽约喜剧之夜的人已经看到了派对偏执的尖锐结局。该活动的组织者之一梁晓雯于 2016 年离开中国，但一直活跃在女权团体中，直到 2021 年她的微信和微博账户被关闭。一家官方小报指责梁女士从国外收受款项，以帮助美国在中国煽动骚乱。 （中国的宣传者一直在加倍强调女权主义是“外国敌对势力”的工具；共青团称激进女权主义是挑起“性别对抗”的“网络毒瘤”。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">李麦子是2015年镇压行动中被拘留的“女权五人”之一，去年，警察进入她的公寓并逮捕了她因张贴抗议严厉的新冠封锁海报的室友后不久，她就决定离开中国。李女士受到严密监视，也失去了她的社交媒体账户；她感到无声无息、无能为力。 “这是我的底线：如果我在中国大陆不能做任何有用的活动，那就是时候离开了。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于进入纽约的女权主义者来说，喜剧是重建她们运动的一种方式。十月初的“女字主一”开放麦克风之夜的舞台上装饰着标语，其中包括称习近平为“独裁者”和“#notmypresident”的标语。梁女士表示，这次活动有两个目的。她认为，多年来选择在网上和公共场合审查自己（许多中国人被迫这样做）最终会导致自我审查的思维。参加脱口秀可以说是一种解药。梁女士说，用中文举办活动很重要，因为这是他们受到审查的语言。她补充说，谈论政治时很容易变得有趣，因为中国版本的政治已经变得如此荒谬。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该节目还旨在鼓励更多人参与女权主义活动。二十多岁的莫莫说，当她还生活在中国时，她就寻找过有关新疆和香港镇压的独立报道，并在许多网络女权组织受到审查之前对其进行了关注。但直到2021年作为研究生来到美国后，她才终于见到了志同道合的中国女性。去年，当莫莫第一次参加开放式麦克风时，她听到舞台上有人说：“我喜欢做爱。”她感到很震惊。当演讲者开始拿政治开玩笑时，她感到一阵担忧，但同时也感到兴奋。几个月之内，她就可以在舞台上讲自己的笑话了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管组织空间不断缩小，中国的妇女权利仍取得了一些进展。 2022年，政府修订了妇女保护法，增加了反对工作场所性骚扰和歧视的更强硬措辞。针对该修正案的精心管理的咨询在网上吸引了超过 70 万条评论，使其成为近年来讨论最广泛的法律变更之一。生育权也引起了公众的关注。一名妇女起诉一家医院，要求其冷冻卵子的权利——在中国，对未婚女性来说这是非法的——最近引发了一场关于扩大体外受精机会的争论。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">李女士表示，中国女性将继续要求更好的待遇，即使她们无法团结起来行动起来。她认为，女权运动将变得越来越“去中心化和个性化”。 “政府对此感到非常无奈：他们认为必须有一个组织者。但在这个时代，没有组织者。只是有些人不同意你的观点。”反对习近平大力推动家庭价值观的中国女性通过选择退出来表达她们的不满。许多人推迟或拒绝结婚和生育。 2022 年，中国将有 680 万对新婚夫妇，大约是 2013 年的一半。去年，中国人口出现六十年来的首次萎缩。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">经营“女字注一”的人并不妄想他们可以从远处改变中国的政治。 “如果你幻想一夜之间发生翻天覆地的变化，那是不可能的，”梁女士说。她说，相反，他们的目标是在他们在国外创造的空间内“悄悄地让一些种子保持活力”。有一天他们可能会把这些种子带回家。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/dpiup1g2tfuidqtidrsrhdjka6492g7h</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/19/chinese-feminists-are-rebuilding-their-movement-abroad</item><item><title><![CDATA[China is educating engineers around the world]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/037%20China%20-%20Global%20influence-ef44637c2a4dfa263fd7f8b92d17943a.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>中国</span><small>官员</small>经常用夸张的术语谈论“一带一路”倡议，这是一场全球基础设施建设热潮。 10 月 17 日至 18 日，中国领导人习近平在北京主办了一次大型峰会，庆祝政府所称的“ <a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/19/xi-jinping-wants-to-be-loved-by-the-global-south">世纪工程</a>”十周年。最近，这种炒作掩盖了一个尴尬的现实。自 2020 年以来，由于各国政府发现偿还中国基础设施贷款变得更加困难，中国缩减了该计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而近年来，该项目的一部分取得了悄然的成功。自2016年以来，中国已在二十几个国家设立了约27所职业学院，其中大部分是较贫穷的国家。这些“鲁班工坊”（以<small>公元前</small>五世纪一位传说中的木匠的名字命名）已经在人工智能、电动汽车、铁路运营和机器人等领域培训了数千名学生。最新的研讨会之一于 9 月 4 日在肯尼亚梅鲁科技大学开幕。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">目的不是慈善。鲁班工坊推广中国希望向发展中国家出口的技术和标准。肯尼亚新工厂的设备将来自华为，美国希望将这家中国电信巨头排除在其盟友的移动网络之外，因为担心其设备可能协助中国从事间谍活动。华为（否认美国的指控）帮助建设了肯尼亚的移动网络，目前正在与其最大的电信提供商合作推出<small>5G</small>服务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些研讨会还有助于缓解人们对“一带一路”的担忧。参与国政府有时会抱怨赢得基础设施项目的公司过于依赖中国的劳动力和供应。多个鲁班工坊现在提供与“一带一路”项目直接相关的培训。吉布提的一名员工培训了一条通往埃塞俄比亚的新铁路线的员工。这条耗资 40 亿美元的铁路由中国建造和资助，但在 2018 年通车后难以盈利。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">鲁班计划与中国早些时候通过开设500多所“孔子学院”在世界各地大学教授普通话来扩大影响力的举措相呼应。但到目前为止，它避免了困扰这些机构的争议，其中许多机构因被指控促进宣传和压制异议而关闭。部分原因是鲁班工坊注重技术技能，部分原因是中国在设立鲁班工坊之前花了更多时间咨询东道国政府。美国智库大西洋理事会的尼瓦·尤（Niva Yau）表示：“与孔子学院不同，鲁班工坊实际上在每个国家都有所不同，因为东道国对技能的要求不同。”她认为这些证据表明中国正在回应对“一带一路”的批评，但没有放弃出口技术等核心目标。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些讲习班与美国、日本和其他富裕国家向南半球国家提供的培训相竞争。例如，德国就如何复制其著名的职业教育体系向 100 多个国家提供了指导。不过，鲁班作坊的不同寻常之处在于，它不仅提供设备，还提供教学，并拥有自己的品牌。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">鲁班计划开始时是由天津当地政府领导的，天津是北京附近的一个大城市，以技术培训而闻名（地方当局被鼓励支持“一带一路”并从中受益）。第一个工作室（如图）于 2016 年在泰国开业；它使用的是天津一家化工公司送来的设备。一时间，富裕国家和贫穷国家都出现了鲁班作坊。 2018 年至 2020 年间，伦敦附近的克劳利学院举办了一个讲习班，教授中国烹饪；葡萄牙的一所仍然提供电气自动化和工业机器人方面的培训。该计划并不总是仅限于“一带一路”参与者：印度（持怀疑态度）在钦奈设有鲁班工坊。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而最近，该计划似乎已被中国中央政府采纳。它已发展到包括天津以外的培训机构和公司，并与习近平的外交政策更加明确地联系在一起。 2018年，习近平承诺在非洲开设十个讲习班；此后，那里又开了十几家。 5月，他向中亚国家领导人承诺，中国将在该地区设立更多研讨会（第一个研讨会于去年12月在塔吉克斯坦开设）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国将补贴鲁班工坊多久，以及他们将在多大程度上兑现承诺，还有待观察。有些是值得怀疑的，比如一位在饱受战争蹂躏的马里教授传统中医的人。但就目前而言，它们代表了中国政府倾听批评意见并从错误中吸取教训的令人耳目一新的例子。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/oein1b66fsq864g14hjh1d3baa194it7</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/19/china-is-eduating-engineers-around-the-world </item><item><title><![CDATA[A landslip in Hong Kong fuels resentment of the rich]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/038%20China%20-%20Property-46d008ab38f25e6fa0d33a52a8b899d8.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">香港<span>豪华</span>沿海社区红山半岛的<small>百万富翁们</small>比以前要穷一些。上个月，一场名为“萨乌拉”的超级台风给该市带来了本世纪以来最多的降雨。在红山，一大块湿土滑入海中。虽然山体滑坡大部分没有影响周围的房屋，但它暴露了未经许可挖掘的地下室，这可能是导致倒塌的原因。在记者的推动下，政府开始了调查，目前调查仍在进行中。截至 10 月 6 日，该地区已发现十几栋房屋在某种程度上违反了规定。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">香港的规划体系常常看起来功能失调。一种猜测是，该地区多达四分之一的房产在未经适当许可的情况下被改变或扩建。平屋顶上的檐篷为休闲创造了空间。外部阳台被围起来。房东们一直在将他们的建筑物切成越来越小的“细分”公寓。十年前，一份政府报告称，普遍忽视规划规则和建筑法规可能“导致伤亡”。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231021_CNC073.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">香港最富有的居民所采取的自由往往是最大的，而且考虑到大多数香港人所忍受的狭小住所，这些自由最常引起轰动。花园和游泳池有时会超出房产的注册边界。在没有适当许可的情况下扩建三层楼。非<small>政府组织</small>Liber Research Community 确定了 8 个富裕社区的约 170 套房屋，它认为这些房屋的面积超出了他们应得的范围。报告称，在某些情况下，溢出面积比官方指定的面积更大。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">红山的山体滑坡加剧了人们对监管松懈和片面监管的旧有抱怨。理论上，搭建未经授权的建筑或侵占公共空间可能会让房主入狱。但利伯认为，在某些情况下，当局允许他们开始为额外的土地支付政府租金。当业主被迫撤销改建或从政府拥有的土地上撤出时，上诉可能会拖延数年。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Hong Kong&#39;s government says it handles things as well as possible, given its resources. Last year it sent out more than 16,000 orders to rectify “illegal structures” and brought 3,600-plus prosecutions. Critics say it is meek when taking on the rich. Activists say the government enforces the laws selectively and sometimes uses them to hassle people it links with the pro-democracy movement. Mount Zero, an independent bookshop, was recently told by government inspectors that its front step was illegally occupying public land.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Things may be coming to a head. China&#39;s leaders worry about Hong Kong&#39;s cramped housing. They think property prices helped stir up big protests in 2019. Local media, though much cowed since the introduction in 2020 of a noxious national-security law, increasingly report on violations of planning. Climate change is increasing the severity of wet and wild weather; this raises the risk that shoddy extensions or overloaded hillsides will collapse. Right now Redhill is “under the spotlight”, says Brian Wong of Liber. But he thinks there are similar risks elsewhere. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ofajjg5tm7o1f1vvs5f6e46i3ne5kka3</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/19/a-landslip-in-hong-kong-fuels-resentment-of-the-rich </item><item><title><![CDATA[Xi Jinping wants to be loved by the global south]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/039%20China%20-%20Chaguan-ae7b5151707ab42329aab8dfa596c044.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>“V</span> <small>ery few</small> <small>Chinese</small> ” know about the ruthless side of Zheng He, the Ming-dynasty explorer and eunuch admiral, a scholar once observed to Chaguan, unexpectedly, over tea in a Beijing courtyard house. Pouring fresh cups, the scholar—a member of China&#39;s national-security establishment—warmed to his theme. In China, he explained, Zheng He is seen as a 15th-century “Santa Claus”, leading his fleet to Africa, Arabia and Asia to hand out porcelain and silks on behalf of his mighty, far-off emperor. But in such places as Sri Lanka, Zheng He is remembered as a terror, who punished local rulers for defying his imperial writ and shipped some of them back to China as captives. The Chinese public is “blissfully ignorant” about that history, sighed the scholar, blaming his country&#39;s desire “to be loved”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Much the same desire suffused the Third Belt and Road Forum, held in Beijing on October 17th and 18th. The forum commemorated the first ten years of the Belt and Road Initiative ( <small>BRI</small> ), a lending and infrastructure scheme that has seen China build dams, bridges, ports and more on four continents. In part, the opening speech by Xi Jinping, the Communist Party chief, was a guide to how the <small>BRI</small> is changing. With China&#39;s growth slowing, and many existing <small>BRI</small> projects mired in debt, there is less emphasis now on billion-dollar loans and on pouring concrete, and more on promoting Chinese standards and technologies, notably in green and digital infrastructure, and on “small yet smart” grassroots projects. In larger part, though, Mr Xi&#39;s speech was a call for China to be loved.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Addressing foreign dignitaries in the Great Hall of the People, Mr Xi made a case for Chinese exceptionalism. He presented his country as a peace-loving giant, guided by the centuries-old spirit of the Silk Road. In this telling, China&#39;s Silk Road spirit is not a charitable impulse, but something more dependable: namely, a pragmatic pursuit of prosperity via mutually profitable trade. Though Mr Xi did not mention Zheng He by name, his government&#39;s white paper on the <small>BRI</small> , published on the forum&#39;s eve, cites the navigator as an inspiration, hailing his seven maritime expeditions that “boosted trade along the maritime silk routes”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The admiral&#39;s ghost hung over the speech as Mr Xi repeated one of his favourite claims about China&#39;s past. “The pioneers of the ancient silk routes won their place in history not as conquerors with warships, guns, horses or swords,” he declared. “Rather, they are remembered as friendly emissaries leading camel caravans and sailing ships loaded with goods.” Without mentioning the conflicts raging in the Middle East and Ukraine, Mr Xi contrasted this Chinese focus on trade and development with the selfishness of world powers that are bent on “ideological confrontation”. He announced a Global Initiative for Artificial Intelligence Governance. Though global in name, this promotes a very Chinese worldview. It would defer to the laws (and censors) of sovereign states, and prohibit America&#39;s current export controls on chips that enable <small>AI</small> . In a volatile world, Mr Xi said, the <small>BRI</small> is “on the right side of history”. He added a rebuke for countries that practise “economic coercion”. Foreign leaders in the hall were polite enough not to snigger or gasp, though China routinely uses trade as a weapon.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As ever in China, much of this propaganda is aimed at domestic audiences. Chinese state media offered blanket coverage of the forum, asserting that over 140 countries sent representatives. They did not mention that just 21 heads of state and government turned up, fewer than attended the first and second forums, held in 2017 and 2019—not least because few Western governments wished to share a stage with President Vladimir Putin of Russia, Mr Xi&#39;s guest of honour. Only one leader from the European Union attended, the Kremlin-friendly Viktor Orban of Hungary.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Putin gave a speech directly after Mr Xi&#39;s. To a striking extent it reflected his growing dependence on China. As a result of Western sanctions imposed after his invasion of Ukraine, China is now the largest buyer of Russian energy, and Chinese exports to Russia have soared. Thanking his “dear friend” Mr Xi for the invitation to Beijing, Mr Putin played dutiful cheerleader for the <small>BRI</small> . Sounding at times like his own transport minister, Mr Putin reeled off lists of <small>BRI</small> -compatible railway lines and logistics corridors that Russia plans to build. He praised the opening last year of a bridge across the Amur river between China and Russia, not mentioning that Russian officials dragged their feet on that project for years before rushing to finish it once the Ukraine war broke out. Forgetting Russia&#39;s long-standing wariness of Chinese investment in the Arctic, he invited “interested states” to take part in the development of a Northern Sea Route opening up as sea ice retreats.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Putin as a character witness</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In interviews with Chinese state media, Mr Putin offered still more praise. When offering economic opportunities to other countries, Mr Xi&#39;s China never imposes or enforces its will, he said. This, he averred, makes the <small>BRI</small> different from policies pushed by countries with a heavy colonial legacy. Once more, that language echoes Chinese talking points. China&#39;s white paper casts the <small>BRI</small> ’s model of development as a challenge to “the exploitative colonialism of the past”. It is the spirit of the Belt and Road to advocate equality, it argues, in contrast to those who push “the superiority of Western civilisation”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Attacks on Western arrogance resonate with many developing countries. If the <small>BRI</small> offers useful technologies, skills or investments, many governments will take that deal. Some countries support China&#39;s proposals for global governance, especially if that means fewer questions about their political systems, or human rights. But those leaders in the Great Hall of the People are not dupes. For one thing, many remember their history, and how Chinese naval fleets and armies brought their countries much more than trade over the centuries. Mr Xi&#39;s China is taken seriously, especially by its neighbours. Love has nothing to do with it. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read more from Chaguan, our columnist on China:<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article72643-prod.ece">China&#39;s ties with America are warming, a bit</a> (Oct 12th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article70369-prod.ece">China wants to be the leader of the global south</a> (Sep 21st)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article69628-prod.ece">Xi Jinping builds a 21st-century police state</a> (Sep 14th)</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Also: How the Chaguan column <a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">got its name</a></i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/o72e85khbc9jc1b5laor38grbmd2l4vq</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/19/xi-jinping-wants-to-be-loved-by-the-global-south </item><item><title><![CDATA[Amid turmoil in China’s property market, the public seethes]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20The%20property%20market-cb0e094feedb49a523bb5c9f31f02291.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>L</span> <small>ampooning Hui Ka Yan</small> has become something of a national pastime in China. Once one of the country&#39;s richest men, the tycoon was detained in September for unspecified crimes. His company, Evergrande, the world&#39;s most indebted property developer, is on the cusp of death; a debt-restructuring plan for it has collapsed. No sooner did news of Mr Hui&#39;s detention spread than a flood of jokes at his expense surged through China&#39;s social media, pillorying his extravagance and pomposity. The humour was bitter: tens of thousands of homebuyers feel cheated by his firm.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One accusation levelled by netizens against Mr Hui is that Evergrande took billions of dollars in prepayments from average people but never built the promised homes. In one short video posted to social media, a gleeful image of Mr Hui is superimposed over pictures of failed and uncompleted housing projects. A speech bubble reads “I&#39;ve received the money”. Another satirical clip records a purported conversation between a bank officer and a man wanting a loan. The banker asks if the man has collateral. In a jab at Evergrande&#39;s unsold and unfinished homes, the customer replies, “Yes, I am Hui Ka Yan&#39;s little brother; I have lots of buildings.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Many such videos being shared online are sombre. One, for example, shows panoramic shots of what appears to be an abandoned Evergrande construction site, accompanied by the sobs of a woman who meekly asks, “How much of the blood and sweat of average people is in this?” The video has been forwarded more than 100,000 times on WeChat, a messaging app. Another shows a vast holiday resort, with castles and hotels, that has fallen into disrepair in the southern province of Guizhou. The narrator tells viewers that Evergrande invested 170bn yuan in the region, but has left projects such as this to crumble. At the end of the video he asks: “Is there any hope of these projects restarting?”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The property market is the subject of endless discussion around dinner and boardroom tables. But tracking national sentiment on the sector is difficult. Direct criticism of state policies has been largely blocked from China&#39;s internet platforms. And yet a surge in scornful content directed at property moguls such as Mr Hui has been tolerated. So too have wide-ranging comments on the loss of family fortunes to real-estate mishaps. Homes remain the most important investment for most Chinese households. This means many homeowners are fearful of the possibility of falling prices (although their children may cheer: at last, that first house-purchase may become affordable).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The central government&#39;s failure to intervene more decisively to prop up the market has been fuelling despondency. Since 2021, developers such as Evergrande have struggled to build, and to pay their bills. Home sales have fallen or slowed in most major cities, and prices have come down. This was largely tolerated until late August, when officials in Beijing offered some salve by lowering mortgage rates and the size of downpayments on homes. Large cities have removed many of the restrictions on purchases that once helped control runaway speculative buying. Homes have become easier to resell in most places. Rules that favoured first-time homebuyers with no record of taking mortgages have been scrapped in order to enable people to buy second and third homes. Some cities have even given cash subsidies to homebuyers who have two or three children. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC002.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">The measures sparked optimism after months of gloom. But the excitement is ebbing. China&#39;s National Day holiday, which this year ran from September 29th to October 6th, is often a prime time for buying flats. Not so this time. Holiday sales based on gross floor area fell by 79% and 57% year on year in Shanghai and Shenzhen respectively, according to <small>CRIC</small> , a research firm. These are two of China&#39;s strongest property markets. At least seven other large cities experienced decreases of more than 30% during the week. Wuhan, where the covid-19 crisis began, and the tech hub of Hangzhou both notched up unexplained increases (see chart).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Only veiled criticisms of state policy appear on the Chinese internet. In one sarcastic social-media post in August, the official account of NetEase, an internet portal, advised Chinese people to stop getting married, stop having children, spend less, not buy homes or cars, and stay home instead of travelling. The message, which caused the account to be suspended, was a poke at the ineffectiveness of central measures aimed at reviving the economy: consumers were doing the opposite of what the government wanted. But such voices are rare. Netizens are sometimes wary even of serious debate about the property market. One piece of analysis, published online on October 9th, compared China&#39;s housing policy with America&#39;s. The author, a former banker, says that when she tried posting the article on some social-media platforms it was blocked.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Another source of gloom is the chaos at China&#39;s largest property firms. Netizens have chuckled at the detention of Mr Hui. But his plight, and the rounding up and arrests of a handful of his colleagues, indicate that Evergrande&#39;s troubles will long continue. The company abruptly cancelled its debt restructuring in September after nearly two years of negotiations. On October 9th a creditor group owed some $6bn by Evergrande said that the collapse of the restructuring had come as a “complete surprise”. On the same day, Country Garden once China&#39;s largest home builder, said it had defaulted on a $60m offshore debt and that it would probably fail to pay other dollar-denominated debts.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such news will not encourage buyers. As more large developers fail to pay debts, they also stop paying the contractors and materials suppliers that build homes. This inevitably leads to homes going unfinished despite already being paid for by ordinary people. Fears that more developers will succumb to these pressures have probably deterred many Chinese citizens from buying new homes this year. Listed developers owe Chinese people about 7trn yuan ($960bn) in unbuilt homes, according to analysts at Gavekal, a research firm. These concerns are echoed across the Chinese internet. In one short video posted online in October, a vlogger airs a growing concern among homebuyers that Country Garden will become the next Evergrande. If the prediction proves right, the impact could be huge: Country Garden is estimated to be building about 1m flats.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The market for second-hand homes is looking much healthier than it is for new ones, notes Goldman Sachs, a bank, in part because people do not want to risk paying for a home that may not be completed. Those buying new flats are more reticent about paying up front for them, too. After prepayments hit a peak of 89% of all new home transactions in mid-2021, that figure fell to 76% in August.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The prospect of tumbling home prices continues to worry ordinary people. But although prices have gradually declined in many large cities, they have not collapsed. This has differentiated China&#39;s property crisis from those in America in 2008 and in Japan in 1992. One reason is that China keeps a firm grip on the sales prices of new homes. Many places have banned price cuts. Between May and December last year, about 20 cities introduced policies that limited how much developers could lower prices. In a southern city a desperate developer slashed prices by 50% in an effort to attract buyers. This fire sale, however, was halted by local authorities. During the National Day holiday, officials in some places reportedly stepped in to cancel special deals offered by builders.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> They have good reason to do so. For one, price cuts can lead to protests when buyers discover they have paid more than those who bought later. They often demand government action and cash back from developers. More worrying is the prospect of price declines spiralling out of control. If property values were to drop by 30%, about 12% of China&#39;s total loan book, or 4.7trn yuan, would suffer from negative equity, according to an analysis by <small>ANZ</small> , a bank. A 50% price collapse would put half of the national mortgage book underwater, leading to a full-blown crisis.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China&#39;s leaders face a predicament. Price drops are bad for anyone who has already purchased a home. But the unaffordability of Chinese cities is a separate crisis for the have-nots. An average home in Beijing, for instance, costs 34 times the average annual salary, making it one of the least affordable places in the world. Young Chinese people are vocal about the pressures of everyday life. From their perspective the current catastrophe playing out in the property market does not sound all that bad. After the recent uptick in Hangzhou, one young netizen pleaded in a social media post: “All I&#39;m hoping for is that prices in Hangzhou don&#39;t start rising again”. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:04:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/kncrh45i20c0g5dqinl78a51m368cfuh</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/12/amid-turmoil-in-chinas-property-market-the-public-seethes </item><item><title><![CDATA[Xi Jinping bumps up the share prices of firms he visits]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/033%20China%20-%20Leaders_%20inspection%20tours-c6a8ac44c5946b7ee126628eaaca4fc1.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>n imperial times</small> , to gather unfiltered information and tap into the public mood, emperors slipped into civilian clothing and travelled around incognito.中国的共产党统治者也喜欢视察。 But unlike the emperors&#39; hugger-mugger trips, modern equivalents are highly publicised affairs, intended to show that the visitors are caring and down-to-earth. State media often show China&#39;s current leader, Xi Jinping, visiting schools, offices and factories, surrounded by onlookers beaming with adoration.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It might be expected that Mr Xi&#39;s inspections of firms would generate such a positive buzz that their business would benefit. But a paper by researchers in Japan, led by Ito Asei of the University of Tokyo, paints a more complex picture of the Xi effect. It is based on a study of leaders&#39; visits to companies listed on the Shanghai and Shenzhen stock exchanges during the rule of Mr Xi and his predecessor, Hu Jintao, who was the party&#39;s chief from 2002 to 2012. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_CNC004.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">The researchers measured profits on investments in shares of the visited firms and compared them with returns that would have been expected had a visit not occurred (“cumulative abnormal returns”, in stockmarket jargon). They focused on a 15-day period around each inspection. Between 2012 and 2022 Mr Xi visited 53 listed firms while his prime minister, Li Keqiang (who stepped down this year after holding the job for a decade), toured 43 of them.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The impact was clear. For Mr Xi, abnormal returns peaked on average at nearly 6% above the expected amount. For Mr Li, they were about 3.5% above. Both figures were much higher than the researchers calculated for Mr Hu (2.2%) and his prime minister, Wen Jiabao (1.3%). In Mr Xi&#39;s second five-year term as the party&#39;s leader, which began in 2017, the effect was even greater, reaching nearly 7%. Curiously, the influence of a visit by Mr Xi is often seen before the trip itself, suggesting that rumours of his plans may spread before he sets off.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Ito and his co-authors found that leaders were more likely to call on larger firms that are already doing well. Some speculators may reckon that the visits could portend government action that would give these companies an extra boost. But the researchers found that state firms, which are always politically favoured, do not reap any additional benefits from leaders&#39; visits. It is non-state-owned companies, which rank lower in the party&#39;s esteem, that revel more in the afterglow: they find it easier to get bank loans and experience a spike in sales.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The leader effect on company value is not confined to China. In a study published in 2020, researchers led by Jeffrey Brown of the University of Illinois found that when bosses of American companies met White House officials, their firms&#39; share prices also increased. But the abnormal returns, at about 0.4% on average, paled in comparison with those noticed in China.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The outsize impact of a Xi visit could be explained partly by his politics. Under his leadership the Chinese government has put much greater effort into directing investment towards what it considers to be strategically important industries. Mr Xi is a champion of this dirigiste approach. So when investors get wind that he will visit a firm, they may be all the more inclined to see the trip as a sign that he has picked a winner. Mr Xi would abhor the term state capitalism, but China&#39;s speculators feed on its abundant manifestations. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:04:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/0pd3fmj1jm5ugp9e7sgd7jiaors02nf5</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/12/xi-jinping-bumps-up-the-share-prices-of-firms-he-visits </item><item><title><![CDATA[Babysitting duties are stressing China’s grandparents]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/034%20China%20-%20Family%20life-5ffb4f337258928efd63ca8de03cc523.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>T</span> <small>raditionally, doting</small> Chinese grannies look after their grandchildren free. So when a grandmother in the south-western province of Sichuan sued her daughter and son-in-law for unpaid child-care fees, it caused a stir on social media. The grandmother, who is surnamed Duan, had looked after her grandson for five years while his parents worked in another city. She wanted compensation. In September, a local judge found in her favour. The boy&#39;s parents were ordered to pay her 82,500 yuan ($11,300).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Ms Duan is not the only Chinese grandparent to think they are getting a rough deal. In state media, reports of similar lawsuits have become more common in recent years. They suggest China&#39;s grandparents are growing sick of being treated as free childminders. In 2021 a grandfather in another part of Sichuan was given 100,000 yuan in child-care fees, with the judge scolding the child&#39;s mother and father for <i>kenlao</i> , or “gnawing on the elderly”. The term is used to describe taking advantage of one&#39;s parents.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China&#39;s grandparents have always helped out with child care. But there used to be an easy alternative. Under Mao Zedong, state-owned nurseries were set up, providing cheap care for many of China&#39;s children, to encourage mothers to work in farms and factories. Many were shut down during economic reforms that began in 1978, two years after Mao&#39;s death. Those that remain are few, often expensive, and usually open only to children over the age of three. Nannies, meanwhile, are often distrusted, after scandals involving mistreatment of their charges.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These days most Chinese families rely on grandparents to look after young children. A study published in 2017 found that nearly 80% of households did so in the biggest cities. Migrant labourers from rural areas ask grandparents back in the countryside to care for their children while the parents work far from home. In many Chinese villages, only the elderly and the young are left. The one-child policy, which led to many children having four grandparents all to themselves, made the burden of care more manageable. So did early retirement. Many Chinese quit work in their 50s.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Nevertheless, grandparents sacrifice a lot. Many will leave their homes to move in with their children after a baby is born. Millions of such “elderly drifters”, as they are known, live in China&#39;s big cities. This cuts them off from friends and can lead to loneliness and depression. It can also make it harder for them to get medical care, as big cities often exclude out-of-towners from public services. The end of the one-child policy in 2016 has meant that some grandparents have to look after more children. White-collar workers often have to work long hours, making it difficult for parents with such jobs to pitch in.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Children may not be getting the best of upbringings under grandparental care. Parents worry about their children getting spoiled. Some research suggests that Chinese children raised by their grandparents are more likely to be obese. Research by Scott Rozelle of the University of Stanford found that in rural areas toddlers are often cognitively delayed, partly because their grandparents may not realise that it is important to talk to them.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> An increasing number of China&#39;s grandparents are also resisting being used as carers. They want to have more fun in their retirement, such as by travelling. Some start looking for love again (a dating show for over 50s was a hit last year). Elderly social-media influencers urge viewers to live in the moment and spend more of their time and money on themselves.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On a warm autumn day at a park in east Beijing, plenty of grandparents are still pushing prams and chasing toddlers. Those your correspondent talked to seemed happy to be doing so, without payment. “We pressured his parents into having him,” says Guo Zhenhai, a 67-year-old man who is standing next to a carousel, holding a toddler. “Chinese people live together and help each other. We don&#39;t have this idea of making it about money.” Mr Guo&#39;s wife, though, seems less keen on the arrangement. “It&#39;s exhausting,” she says. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:04:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/tt44jfkcg086hrqsnorp0p186kmjai62</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/12/babysitting-duties-are-stressing-chinas-grandparents </item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s ties with America are warming, a bit]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/035%20China%20-%20Chaguan-aab889a97a46179d46832c8427bd51e8.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>n New York</small> politics, plain speaking is an asset. Fearless public candour is less useful when climbing to the top ranks of the Chinese Communist Party. Despite this daunting culture gap, Chuck Schumer—the acerbic, Brooklyn-born majority leader of America&#39;s Senate and co-chairman of the first congressional delegation to China since before the pandemic—held businesslike meetings with Xi Jinping and other party bosses on October 9th and 10th.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The encounters began with less-than-promising displays of party doublespeak. Earlier this year, Mr Xi accused America and allies of trying to contain and suppress his country on all fronts. Yet when the supreme leader welcomed the six senators to the Great Hall of the People, he dismissed bilateral tensions as mere “wind and rain”. Deploring the very notion of a great-power contest, Mr Xi declared that “competition and confrontation are not in line with the trend of the times.” For his part, the foreign minister, Wang Yi, suggested that ignorance explains Americans&#39; growing wariness of China. With luck, Mr Wang averred, the senators&#39; visit would give them a more “accurate” understanding of his country.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Schumer was having none of it. It is “natural” that the world&#39;s two greatest powers are competitors in trade, technology, diplomacy and more, he told his hosts, adding: “We welcome this competition. We do not seek conflict.” In his meeting with the foreign minister, the senator said he was “very disappointed” by China&#39;s initial response to terror attacks by Hamas, which “showed no sympathy” for Israelis murdered in their hundreds. Mr Schumer was correct. As with Russia&#39;s invasion of Ukraine, China&#39;s diplomats claimed to be neutral after Hamas attacked Israel. They called on both sides to lay down their arms. China&#39;s official media have played down mass killings and hostage-taking of civilians by Hamas, emphasised Israeli air strikes on Gaza and presented America as a warmonger fuelling the conflict for selfish ends. Mr Schumer asked for a clear condemnation of Hamas. Several senators asked China to use its influence and urge Iran to avoid escalating the war. For good measure Mr Schumer complained about unfair Chinese trade practices and China-based chemical factories that feed the deadly trade in fentanyl. He urged China not to support “Russia&#39;s immoral war against Ukraine”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> His hosts were pragmatic, not cross, in response. The commerce minister, Wang Wentao, said that China does not seek to avoid competition, as long as it is based on world trade rules. During the Americans&#39; visit, the foreign ministry somewhat toughened its line on Hamas, condemning acts that harm civilians.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It is not a love of Brooklyn-style bluntness that explains China&#39;s reaction. Party chiefs respect power, whether economic or political. China needs foreign investment and know-how, and wants to head off tighter, American-led controls on exports of semiconductors and other technologies. Leaders in Beijing notice that, at a time when members of Congress agree on very little, politicians in Washington can come together to pass tough-on-China bills and industrial subsidies for American firms. Congress demands stronger armed forces to counter the People&#39;s Liberation Army.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Party leaders understand diplomatic clout, too. They have watched, appalled, as America harnesses fears of China to broker a rapprochement between Japan and South Korea, and to deepen defence ties with regional countries from Australia and India to the Philippines. Diplomats report that China has heard from many governments that it should lower tensions and talk to America—and that countries have sent the same message to President Joe Biden&#39;s team. Mr Xi all but confirmed this in public, telling Mr Schumer&#39;s delegation that the international community expects their two countries to co-operate on such global tasks as fighting climate change and securing a post-pandemic economic recovery. American officials sound confident that Mr Xi will attend an Asia-Pacific leaders&#39; summit next month in San Francisco, and hold a side meeting with Mr Biden. For the past three months China has eased off from dangerous mid-air and maritime encounters with surveillance aircraft and warships from America and allies, such as Australia and Canada, says an American defence official.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> The party respects a united front</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This modest lowering of tensions cannot be separated from the tough-on-China mood that unites America&#39;s politicians. That bipartisan consensus is real, Chaguan heard on a recent trip to Washington. Both parties agree that China is “the pacing challenge of this century”, says Senator Chris Coons, a Democrat with close ties to Mr Biden. Still, divisions lurk. Not every member worries about the views of foreign allies and non-aligned countries. Most Republicans are far less fussed about competing with China for top jobs and influence at the <small>UN</small> , laments Mr Coons. Even as China expands its diplomatic footprint, the Senate has failed to confirm American ambassadors to vital countries.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Republicans complain that Mr Biden&#39;s focus on climate change and what they call his “war on fossil fuels” will leave Americans dependent on Chinese-made electric cars. Isolationism, on the hard right and far left, is a growing force. Mike Gallagher, the Republican chairman of the House Select Committee on the Chinese Communist Party, is a Reagan-admiring internationalist. Like Mr Coons, he sees a link between America&#39;s global credibility and the health of its democratic institutions at home.但就连加拉格尔也担心，如果成本太高，美国公众对台战的支持可能会“消失”。这让他渴望看到美国在台湾预先部署足够的武器，并在亚洲部署足够的威慑力量，以确保夺取台湾岛成为不可能。其他人则担心让中国失去所有希望会引发战争。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">简而言之，美国政界人士一致认为，他们正在与中国进行一场大国较量，但不知道如何竞争。对华政策制定并未屈服于党派失调或特朗普式的“美国优先”民族主义。但坦白说，确实可以。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read more from Chaguan, our columnist on China:<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article70369-prod.ece">China wants to be the leader of the global south</a> (Sep 21st)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article69628-prod.ece">Xi Jinping builds a 21st-century police state</a> (Sep 14th)<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/07/the-belt-and-road-as-seen-from-china">从中国看“一带一路”</a> （9月7日）</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Also: How the Chaguan column <a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">got its name</a></i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:04:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/1t69rof2hhqs1h9vgsm50dol77bciedc</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/12/chinas-ties-with-america-are-warming-a-bit</item></channel></rss>