<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 13 日星期一 23:00:43 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Can the Mediterranean become Europe’s energy powerhouse?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>马略卡岛的游客</small><span>现在</span>可能会对地中海岛屿上的一个新景点感到惊叹：完全由“绿色”氢驱动的微型经济。在其核心，两个太阳能发电厂为“电解槽”提供动力，电解槽将水分解为氧气和氢气，从而产生无碳燃料。氢气可以驱动公共汽车，注入岛上的天然气网络，并为酒店和港口的燃料电池提供动力。 “该项目展示了一切的可能性，”该项目投资者之一、可再生能源公司 Acciona Energía 的创新主管贝伦·利纳雷斯 (Belén Linares) 表示。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">有一个障碍：氢尚未实现。由于设计缺陷，美国康明斯公司生产的电解槽已被召回。进口来自可再生能源的绿色氢是不切实际的。公共汽车和燃料电池闲置。新当选的地方政府似乎也不太感兴趣。根据该岛首府帕尔马新市长在当地媒体上的引述，前任政府发表了“很多废话”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">无限的可能性，还是空谈？同样的问题也笼罩在更广泛的绿色氢经济上，欧洲各国政府希望看到这种经济在地中海盆地出现，将该地区变成一个以太阳能为燃料的地区，与北海周围已经形成的风力驱动的北方发电机相对应。奖品很大。如果欧洲南部发电站的计划进展顺利，将使欧洲大陆获得廉价的可再生能源，并使其能够清理排放碳的重工业。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">地中海一直是能源的通道。从罗马统治时期到 19 世纪，劳动力都是以被奴役的非洲人的形式存在的。如今，主要是天然气。六条管道将欧洲与非洲和中东连接起来。<small>欧盟</small>三分之一以上的天然气进口依赖该地区。在可再生能源时代，地中海沿岸国家拥有地球上获取自然力量的最佳条件。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">太阳能发电显示出巨大的潜力。西班牙平均每年每平方米的日照量为 4,575 千瓦时 ( <small>kWh</small> )，摩洛哥为 5,563 千瓦时 ( <small>kWh</small> )，是德国预期的两倍。人口稀少意味着西班牙和葡萄牙有充足的土地种植此类植物，北非和中东的沙漠也是如此。在摩洛哥和毛里塔尼亚的一些地区，阳光和风都充足，形成了氢电解槽几乎可以不间断运行的罕见最佳地点。 “全世界只有十个这样的地点，”负责德国能源和建筑公司 BayWa 太阳能业务的贝内迪克特·奥特曼 (Benedikt Ortmann) 解释道。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">开发这个可再生能源库并不是一个新想法。 2000 年代初期，一个由数十家公司（主要是德国公司）支持的协会提出了在撒哈拉沙漠修建巨型太阳能发电厂的想法。但对 2009 年成立的 Desertec 的支持很快就消失了，主要是因为该技术的成本。更好、更便宜的收集太阳光线的方法的开发是这一想法复兴的背后原因。根据国际可再生​​能源机构的数据，公用事业规模太阳能发电厂的平均电力成本已从 2010 年的每<small>千瓦时</small>0.45 美元下降到去年的 0.05 美元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">将能源向北输送到需要的地方现在也更加可行。 Desertec 的计划涉及海底电缆，但其容量有限。但现在更便宜、更高效的电解槽可以将电能直接转化为氢气。然后可以将其作为气体或衍生物（例如液氨）进行运输。分析师预计，几年后，来自北非的绿色氢的成本将低于每公斤 1.5 美元，可能比“蓝”氢便宜，“蓝”氢来自天然气，但需要捕获和储存由此产生的碳。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与沙漠技术时代相比，南方对能源的需求也更有可能实现。欧洲钢铁和化工行业迫切需要氢气及其衍生物作为无碳原料。<small>欧盟</small>设定的到 2030 年 2000 万吨的消费目标中，大部分将来自其南部边缘和北非。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，该地区作为欧洲南部强国的地位并不是既定的。欧洲必须启动新能源市场，并在一个有许多竞争者的放松管制的舞台上做到这一点。 “这是一个先有鸡还是先有蛋的问题，”游说团体德国能源和水工业协会的克尔斯滕·韦斯特法尔 (Kirsten Westphal) 说。同时增加需求和供应是一种微妙的平衡行为。如果公司不确定氢气的供应和定价，他们就会犹豫是否签订长期承购协议。这反过来又阻碍了生产商做出关键的投资决策。北非的政治不稳定增加了风险，从而增加了资本成本，这无济于事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，最大的问题是连接市场双方，这首先要建立物理连接。大部分氢气首先需要通过船舶运输，可能以氨的形式运输（液态氢必须保持在 -253°C，运输起来很困难）。但运输能力有限。佛罗伦萨管理学院的 James Kneebone 估计，即使在技术上可行，重新利用全球现有的能够运输液化天然气的整个船队每年也只能输送约 650 万吨。这就留下了对管道的依赖</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">专家们对于现有天然气网络是否可以升级为氢气以及建造新管道是否昂贵存在分歧。地缘政治动荡可能会阻碍管道投资和氢气生产。<small>欧盟</small>确定的氢气可以在地中海盆地流动的所有三个走廊都穿过麻烦的领土。从毛里塔尼亚通过管道输送的氢气最好通过西撒哈拉，但摩洛哥对该地区的控制存在争议。正在考虑的替代方案是通过加那利群岛的海上路线。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">管道一旦建成，就很容易受到政治干预。 2021 年 11 月，阿尔及利亚与摩洛哥的不稳定关系导致阿尔及利亚与摩洛哥断绝外交关系，并中断马格里布-欧洲管道的天然气流动，该管道通过邻国领土将摩洛哥的气田与西班牙连接起来。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">言归正传，事情也同样复杂。关于连接巴塞罗那和马赛的水下管道的协议，氢气可以从西班牙通过现有基础设施经法国输送到德国，但该协议仍可能陷入德国和法国之间关于核电是否应被视为“绿色”的争端中。此外，法国液化空气公司是全球最大的工业气体生产商，该公司正在大力游说反对一个会降低其自身氢气管道网络价值的项目。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果欧洲想要实现减少碳排放的雄心勃勃的目标，它就别无选择，只能面对这些问题。已经采取了一些步骤。其中包括欧盟委员会推出的六项举措，从扩大天然气使用的“氢加速器”，到启动贸易的“欧洲氢银行”。更重要的是，该委员会通过放宽国家援助规则允许补贴流动，因此成员国可以支持企业脱碳的努力。资金还专门用于建设氢气管道，例如从阿尔及利亚和突尼斯到奥地利和德国的 3,300 公里长的管道。北非的氢能项目将受益于欧洲复兴开发银行等机构的投资。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一些成员国希望行动更快。西班牙和葡萄牙已开始实施雄心勃勃的国家战略，旨在将伊比利亚半岛转变为绿色氢中心。但德国最希望看到其蓬勃发展，该国将不得不进口高达 70% 的氢气来实现其强大的重工业脱碳。德国已拨出超过 80 亿欧元（86 亿美元）来帮助其企业走向绿色。几年前，为了表现出热情，该国外交部开始了“氢外交”，并在主要国家设立了六个“氢大使馆”。最近，经济部催生了氢气交易平台H2Global。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最重要的是，德国似乎承认它需要付出才能获得。它似乎不仅高兴地看到非洲建立太阳能发电厂和电解槽农场，而且准备帮助创造当地就业机会、升级电网和建设海水淡化厂（电解槽需要大量纯净水）。随着时间的推移，德国甚至可能接受其部分重工业可以迁移到氢气生产地。 “工业地图总是遵循能源地图，”智库勃鲁盖尔的西蒙·塔利亚皮特拉（Simone Tagliapietra）评论道。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果德国想要避免像对待俄罗斯和天然气那样依赖不可预测的独裁政权获取能源的情况，那么这些计划就至关重要。 “为了避免氢能重蹈覆辙，德国需要建立真正的伙伴关系，”爱尔福特大学的安德烈亚斯·戈德索 (Andreas Goldthau) 说。如果一切按计划进行，欧洲南部的发电机加快步伐，像马略卡岛这样的地方不仅会因其海滩和夜生活而热闹，还会因氢电解槽产生的能量而热闹。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:58:18 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/mteukmtk6v72k6kri9vg7o3ndlj98pp6</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/11/13/can-the-mediterranean-become-europes-energy-powerhouse </item><item><title><![CDATA[Sweden is suffering a grim wave of gang violence]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>10</span><small>月 15 日，</small>瑞典说唱歌手 5iftyy 的数千名粉丝收看他的 Instagram 频道，观看他所说的重要直播。他们发现自己看到一名大胡子男子挥舞着镀金的<small>AK</small> -47，同时辱骂<a href="https://www.economist.com/europe/2020/11/28/why-sweden-struggles-to-curb-gang-violence">敌对帮派成员</a>，身后还有三名头戴巴拉克拉瓦、手持步枪的暴徒。拿着金枪的男子是穆斯塔法·“本泽马”·阿尔吉布里，他是 <a href="https://www.economist.com/europe/2021/06/12/europes-drug-habit-proves-immune-to-covid-19">瑞典毒品网络</a>狐步舞的主要成员。据信阿尔吉布里先生住在伊拉克。他出庭露面是为了消除有关他死亡的谣言，并威胁包括一名瑞典检察官在内的各种敌人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">直播看起来很荒唐，但威胁却很严重。多年来，瑞典与帮派相关的暴力事件发生率很高，但在过去两年里，这种情况一直持续不断。今年前十个月，瑞典发生了 324 起枪击事件，其中 48 人死亡。枪支犯罪率比邻国高出数倍。帮派开始用手榴弹和炸药袭击对手的房屋；今年已发生139起爆炸事件。政府正在疯狂加强法律并提高执法预算，但仍落后于形势。 “我们至少在十年前就应该预见到这一情况并采取这些措施，”瑞典司法部长顾问丹尼尔·伯格斯特罗姆 (Daniel Bergstrom) 表示。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">当前的暴力浪潮很大程度上是由涉及狐步舞的争斗引发的。该团伙的名字来源于其头目拉瓦·马吉德 (Rawa Majid)，他是一位 37 岁的库尔德瑞典人。 （“Rawa”听起来像<i>räv</i> ，瑞典语中“狐狸”的意思。）马吉德先生小时候随母亲从伊拉克移民，在斯德哥尔摩以北约 70 公里的乌普萨拉长大。警方称，在过去的几年里，他已经将狐步舞变成了该国最大的非法毒品经销商，拉拢竞争对手或夺取他们的地盘。他现在在土耳其负责这些工作，2018 年他因毒品指控在瑞典服完刑后移居土耳其。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">总体而言，瑞典仍然是一个相对安全的国家，发生冲突的地区看起来不像犯罪猖獗的贫民窟。斯卡普纳克是斯德哥尔摩南部的郊区，发生过多起枪击和爆炸事件，是一个整洁的街区，有低层公寓和花园。最近在舒适的<i>kulturhus</i> （社区中心）举行的镇议会会议上，社区活动人士向议会成员施压，要求他们考虑混合收入住房，并恳求保护当地公园的蝙蝠群。但谈话很快转向安全问题。 “2022 年初发生的几起枪击事件确实让我们警醒了，”市议会成员莫妮卡·洛夫斯特罗姆 (Monica Lovstrom) 说。今年该地区已发生三起爆炸事件； 8月19日，一处公寓楼的楼梯井被炸毁。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">犯罪团伙经常以爆炸事件作为警告，但斯卡普纳克的爆炸事件中没有人造成任何人死亡。 （瑞典今年唯一的爆炸死亡事件是一名 25 岁的旁观者。）但 9 月初，一名来自该地区较富裕和安全地区之一的 13 岁男孩在该市南部的森林中被发现，他被枪杀在头脑中。检察官尚未公布细节，但表示这起谋杀案与帮派有关。由于承担刑事责任的最低年龄为 16 岁，因此犯罪团伙正在招募越来越年轻的青少年作为毒品运送者，有时还招募刺客。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">警方表示，部分招募是通过聊天应用程序进行的。学龄儿童会关注发布任务和价格列表的帐户。通常，他们运送毒品；极少数情况下，他们可能会收到一把枪和目标的描述。如果没有经过训练，他们很可能会错过。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从政治上讲，犯罪浪潮对政府来说是困难的。中右翼总理乌尔夫·克里斯特森 (Ulf Kristersson) 在去年的选举中领导温和党上台，他将帮派暴力归咎于自 2014 年以来一直执政的中左翼社会民主党。保守派选民预计右翼内阁将打击犯罪尤其如此，因为这取决于极右翼反移民瑞典民主党的支持。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">政府确实延长了刑事刑期，尽管许多刑期仍比其他北欧国家短。克里斯特森表示，他希望采用“丹麦对瑞典罪行的惩罚”，这是对丹麦更严格规则的认可（例如，对团伙犯罪的刑罚加倍）。他还赋予警察更多权力。 10 月 1 日生效的一项法律允许他们根据目标参与有组织犯罪活动的证据请求电子监视；以前，它们必须与特定犯罪有关。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一些政党提出了不太实际的想法。瑞典民主党建议，年仅 13 岁的儿童应因严重犯罪而面临成人处罚，包括终身监禁，并且将非瑞典背景的帮派成员驱逐出境。这位社会民主党领导人提出了使用军队的想法——尽管军队对青少年加入帮派的作用尚不清楚。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其他人则认为，仅仅关注执法是短视的。 “我们必须集中精力对抗年轻人价值观的恶化，”斯德哥尔摩副市长、贫困社区的前校长简·琼森 (Jan Jonsson) 说。他希望在学校系统地教授公民道德，并增加对关押青少年罪犯的少年看守所的资助。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这似乎不太可能很快见效。但通过执法来减少帮派暴力也将是一项艰巨的任务。许多犯罪网络的头号人物，比如 Majid 先生，甚至不在瑞典：10 月底，五名与 Foxtrot 有关的人（据报道包括 5iftyy）在突尼斯被捕，10 月 31 日，据报道另一名男子是 Foxtrot 的成员在萨拉热窝被杀。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">警方众所周知，在反毒战争中，成功通常是暂时的。 2020 年，荷兰和法国警方破解了一个名为 Encrochat 的加密网络，毒品网络一直使用该网络进行通信。瑞典检察官利用这些证据将数十名来自当时占主导地位的帮派（如 Bandidos 和 Satudarah）的人物送入监狱。据侦探桑德先生说，这样做的效果是为新人打开了领域。几年后，狐步舞成为了主导。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:41:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/eg099u1q9qun1t2i6ikum11kh8ge4fc4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/13/sweden-is-suffering-a-grim-wave-of-gang-violence </item><item><title><![CDATA[What David Cameron’s return says about British politics]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>戴维</span><small>·卡梅伦</small>看上去总是那么符合这个角色。即使是地球上最有权势的人也对这位不穿夹克、不打领带的英国首相的轻松举止感到惊讶。美国前总统巴拉克·奥巴马 (Barack Obama) 指出，卡梅伦先生“对问题的掌控力令人印象深刻，语言流畅，并且拥有从未被生活压力过大的人所拥有的轻松自信”。卡梅伦先生具备成为一名优秀首相的品质：聪明、勤奋、机敏和圆滑的举止。相反，他却成为了<a href="https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2016/06/24/david-cameron-quits-downing-street-with-a-ruined-legacy">最糟糕的人之一</a>。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 2016 年卡梅伦卸任七年后，在英国脱欧公投失败后，这位前首相以外交大臣的身份重返政治前线。首相里希·苏纳克 (Rishi Sunak) 决定解雇强硬派内政大臣苏埃拉·布雷弗曼 (Suella Braverman)，这为他扫清了道路。詹姆斯·克莱弗利（James Cleverly）是一名胸肌发达的前预备役军人，他被调去接替布雷弗曼女士的职位，从而留下了该国最高外交官的空缺。于是，11月13日上午，卡梅伦熟悉的身影再次徘徊在唐宁街10号门口。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">考虑到卡梅伦的履历，他的回归显得有些特殊。一个搞砸了英国外交政策的人现在将再次帮助制定英国外交政策。一个正在努力解决如何修复公共服务的政府任命了这个人，他比其他任何人都对他们目前的困难造成了最大的影响。一个抛弃办公室的人现在被描绘成尽职尽责的典范。在英国政治中，能力的表现比能力的证据更重要。审美胜过成就。卡梅伦先生的复兴最能证明这一点。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">卡梅伦看似合理的态度掩盖了他的许多缺点。在外交政策上他的错误很多。五百年来，英国的目标是确保欧洲不会联合起来反对它。卡梅伦承诺在 2013 年举行公投，结果他在短短三年内就实现了这一目标。他对中国过于鸽派。中国企业被诱骗投资英国基础设施，从电信到核电站——这些投资现在基本上不得不像不需要的 Artex 天花板一样被取消。 2014 年弗拉基米尔·普京 (Vladimir Putin) 入侵克里米亚时，英国本应是乌克兰的安全保障者之一，但卡梅伦却允许法国和德国带头进行和平谈判。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自由主义者对卡梅伦的政治抱有扭曲的看法，称赞他是反对民粹主义的堡垒。中间派对布雷弗曼女士的离开感到高兴，但正是他第一个在移民问题上做出了不可能的承诺。他的政府承诺将每年新移民数量减少到10万以下，同时留在要求人员自由流动的<small>欧盟</small>。在政府承诺削减移民和英国加入欧盟之间，必须做出一些让步。那就是英国加入<small>欧盟</small>。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">卡梅伦的形象是一位成功的政治战略家，但由于英国脱欧公投这一错误而陷入低谷。事实上，卡梅伦先生的财政保守主义与社会自由主义相结合的哲学从来都不是一个受欢迎的愿景。 2010年，即使经历了严重的经济衰退，卡梅伦也未能赢得绝对多数席位。 2015年，当英格兰西南部抛弃了自由民主党、苏格兰抛弃了工党时，英国凯尔特人边缘地区爆发了一场骚乱，卡梅伦才勉强赢得了自1970年代以来最少的多数席位。卡梅伦赢得的选票远远少于特蕾莎·梅或鲍里斯·约翰逊。英国的喀麦隆人并不多。除了一些报纸的专栏版外，从来没有。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在利兹·特拉斯短暂的政府进行了混乱的实验之后，卡梅伦先生自己的经济政策可能会被描绘成谨慎的保守主义。但事实并非如此。紧缩政策是一项激进的实验，但基本上失败了。国家规模没有持续缩小；他的减税政策尚未实施；卡梅伦领导下开始的多年投资不足导致学校和医院破旧不堪。只有相比之下，卡梅伦先生才显得谨慎。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">老盟友称赞卡梅伦重返政府的责任感。但英国脱欧后，他不必从公共生活中消失。卡梅伦先生曾经斥责一位未来的<small>议员</small>厚颜无耻地询问他是否可以担任部长。卡梅伦先生说：“你会发现成为议会后座议员是你一生中最大的荣幸。” “当我不再担任总理时，我将非常自豪地以威特尼议会议员的身份回到后座议员，度过余生。”事实上，卡梅伦先生在离开之前在后座议员任职八周。 2016 年至 2019 年，卡梅伦在对英国脱欧大声疾呼的那些年里，在他最有用的时候，却辞去了职务。现在他厌倦了私人生活，他回来了。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">礼仪造就普通话</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在约翰逊担任首相期间的小丑表演结束后，威斯敏斯特的恶棍们向卡梅伦先生投射出一种庄重的气氛。然而，他在下台时却感到尴尬。实际上，每一位英国高级政治家在离开议会后都会试图填补自己的空缺，但大多数都是悄悄而有效地进行的。相比之下，卡梅伦代表格林希尔资本（Greensill Capital）（一家失败的供应链支付公司）进行游说，向已公开的内阁部长发送假笑短信（“我知道你们非常忙碌，顺便说一句，你们做得很好”） ）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这样的记录显然不构成担任高官的障碍。卡梅伦先生回归很大程度上是因为苏纳克先生感到绝望。他可能会安抚一些摇摆不定的南方保守党选民，这些选民为这位前首相提供了狭窄的基础。幸运的是，他作为外交大臣造成的损害将比作为首相造成的损害要小。但事实是，卡梅伦在某些方面保持着良好的声誉，这是因为他给人的印象而不是他实际做了什么。看起来还是有帮助的。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:26:59 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/13e95i7p0lrrs2dn894qvg8cbla7b7ih</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/13/what-david-camerons-return-says-about-british-politics </item><item><title><![CDATA[From Gaza to Ukraine, wars and crises are piling up]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>这</span><small>不是</small>快乐的时光。以色列和哈马斯在加沙的战争有可能蔓延到整个中东，而美国和伊朗则在幕后对峙。乌克兰战争是 1945 年以来欧洲最大规模的战争，目前还没有结束的迹象。现在，中国的飞机和军舰越来越多、越来越频繁地威胁台湾，而台湾即将举行的选举可能会带来更多的骚乱。马里、缅甸和苏丹的内战最近几周也恶化了。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>阅读我们对<a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">以色列-哈马斯战争</a>和<a href="https://www.economist.com/ukraine-crisis">乌克兰战争</a>的报道</i></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一系列危机并非史无前例。历史学家谢尔盖·拉琴科 (Sergey Radchenko) 列举了苏联入侵匈牙利和 1956 年苏伊士运河危机、1958 年黎巴嫩和台湾海峡危机以及 1978-79 年中国入侵越南、伊朗伊斯兰革命和苏联入侵阿富汗接连展开。 1999年，新装备了核导弹的印度和巴基斯坦就克什米尔发动了战争，而<small>北约则</small>轰炸了南斯拉夫境内的塞尔维亚军队。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但美国及其盟国无法像以前那样轻松或廉价地进行干预。中国和俄罗斯等对手更加自信，合作也越来越频繁。包括印度和土耳其在内的不结盟国家也是如此，它们在影响遥远事件方面的影响力越来越大，并相信一种新的、更有利的秩序正在出现。大国之间爆发直接战争的可能性笼罩着世界，迫使各国在今天奋战的同时也要密切关注未来。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">大型多人游戏</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">大国在曾经可能朝着同一方向推进的问题上变得更加两极分化。例如，在中东， <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/17/putins-plan-to-profit-from-the-israel-hamas-war">俄罗斯</a>与哈马斯走得更近，撕毁了与以色列多年的谨慎外交关系。<a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/26/how-china-sees-gaza">中国</a>在过去的战争中曾发表过温和的声明，敦促缓和局势，但现在却利用这场危机批评美国在该地区的作用。除了匈牙利领导人欧尔班维克托这样的强人之外，很少有西方国家再与俄罗斯对话。甚至与中国的对话也越来越以威胁和警告为主，而不是努力解决气候变化等共同问题。乔·拜登和习近平计划于 11 月 15 日在加利福尼亚州举行的会议可能就是一个很好的例子，尽管有传言称将就人工智能的军事应用达成协议。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">另一个转变是美国的对手之间日益趋同。 “俄罗斯、中国、朝鲜和伊朗之间确实正在出现一个轴心，它拒绝接受他们版本的美国领导的国际秩序，”斯蒂芬·哈德利说。他曾于 1970 年代在美国国家安全委员会任职，并于 1980 年代在五角大楼任职，随后于 2005 年成为乔治·W·布什的国家安全顾问。乌克兰战争巩固了俄罗斯与中国之间的伙伴关系。这不是一个正式的联盟，但两国今年六月在西太平洋进行了四年多来的第六次联合轰炸机巡逻。随后，他们于 8 月在该地区进行了 13,000 公里的联合海军巡逻。<a href="https://www.economist.com/international/2023/09/19/meet-the-worlds-new-arms-dealers">伊朗和朝鲜</a>都向俄罗斯提供武器，以换取军事技术。结果就是更大的纠缠。涉及一个敌人的危机越来越有可能卷入另一个敌人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">而且，每次危机不仅涉及更多的敌人，而且还涉及更多的玩家。澳大利亚、日本、新西兰和韩国领导人均出席了过去两届在欧洲举行的<small>北约</small>峰会。如果没有韩国炮弹的注入，乌克兰今年的反攻就不可能发生。土耳其已成为整个地区的主要武器供应国，凭借其军事技术和顾问重塑了利比亚、叙利亚和阿塞拜疆的冲突。欧洲国家正在更深入地计划如何应对台湾危机。因此，危机有更多的变化因素。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这反映了经济和政治权力分配的更广泛转变。 “多极化”这一概念曾经仅限于学术界，指的是这样一个世界：权力不是集中在两个地方（如冷战时期），也不是集中在一个地方（如美国主导的 20 世纪 90 年代），而是集中在一个地方。有几个——已进入外交主流。 9月，印度外交部长苏杰生指出，美国面临“伊拉克和阿富汗的长期后果”（这是对两场失败战争的认可）以及相对经济衰退，“正在适应多极世界”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这个论点是值得商榷的。美国国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文在最近的一篇文章中认为，与陷入这些战争时相比，美国现在的地位更加强大。 “如果美国仍在阿富汗作战，”他写道，“俄罗斯很可能会竭尽全力帮助塔利班将华盛顿控制在阿富汗，阻止其集中精力帮助乌克兰。”这是有道理的。但美国的形象无疑受到了损害。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">智库欧洲外交关系委员会2月份进行的一项民意调查发现，超过61%的俄罗斯人和中国人、51%的土耳其人和48%的印度人预计世界要么是多极化，要么是中国主导。在 2016 年 1 月的最后一次国情咨文演讲中，时任美国总统巴拉克·奥巴马 (Barack Obama) 坚称，“在每一个重要的国际问题上，世界人民不会指望北京或莫斯科来领导——他们在呼唤我们。”七年过去了，事情已经不再那么清晰了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这一切的结果就是一种混乱感。美国及其盟国面临越来越大的威胁。俄罗斯和中国看到了机遇。中等强国受到大国的追捧，但对世界贸易组织和联合国等机构日益功能失调感到担忧，他们看到了两者。 “一种无政府状态正在渗透到国际关系中，”曾任印度外交大臣兼国家安全顾问的希夫尚卡尔·梅农(Shivshankar Menon)在去年发表的一篇文章中写道。他解释说，这“不是严格意义上的无政府状态，而是缺乏中央组织原则或霸权”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其他几个趋势加剧了这种趋势。一是<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/04/19/in-sudan-and-beyond-the-trend-towards-global-peace-has-been-reversed">气候危机</a>，它增加了世界许多地区发生冲突的风险，并通过绿色转型创造了新的竞争来源，例如对风力涡轮机和电动汽车至关重要的关键材料的竞争。另一个是技术变革的步伐不断加快，人工智能以指数级的速度进步，并带来不可预测的后果。第三个是全球化，它以新的方式将危机交织在一起。例如，台湾战争将对半导体行业造成严重破坏，从而对世界经济造成严重破坏。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第四是民族主义和民粹主义的高涨，影响了解决所有这些全球性问题的努力。最近辞去五角大楼政策负责人职务的科林·卡尔 (Colin Kahl) 和拜登国家安全委员会高级官员托马斯·赖特 (Thomas Wright) 在 2021 年出版的一本书中指出，在新冠肺炎 (covid-19) 大流行期间，各国紧急采取行动，国际合作陷入停顿。关闭边界并保护自己。 “出于所有实际目的，七国集团已不复存在，”他们指出。 “流行病政治最终对旧的国际秩序造成了最后的打击。”</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">从黎明到黎明</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">新的世界秩序使美国及其盟国的机构能力面临压力，同时也使它们的军事能力捉襟见肘。首先考虑制度压力。哈德利先生认为，冷战是一个“有组织的世界”。他承认存在全球性挑战，但许多挑战都是更大的超级大国斗争的子集。 “对于冷战后的国家安全顾问来说，”他说，“这更像是在一个有八个燃烧器的炉子上做饭，每个燃烧器都有一个锅，每个锅都快要沸腾了。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一个更多危机同时发生的世界给负责管理危机的领导人和外交官带来了两种挑战。一是同时扑救多处火灾的战术问题。一位前英国高级外交官表示，危机往往会产生集中效应，首相或总统亲自负责处理原本可能分散在外交部和国防部的问题。即使在大国和强大的国家，官僚的带宽也可能非常有限。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">深陷危机的外交官常常认为自己的时代异常混乱。 Baroness Catherine Ashton, who was the European Union&#39;s de facto foreign minister from 2009 to 2014, points out that she was dealing with the Arab spring, Iran&#39;s nuclear programme and the Serbia-Kosovo dispute at the same time. “I can remember very clearly, when the Ukraine crisis began,” she says, referring to a revolution in Kyiv in 2014, “that I just didn&#39;t know if we would have the bandwidth for all of this.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One issue is that competition has turned to conflict. The war in Ukraine has been especially debilitating for diplomacy. Baroness Ashton recalls that when the Ukraine crisis began in 2014, her negotiating team for nuclear talks with Iran in Vienna included Russia&#39;s deputy foreign minister. She would travel to Kyiv to condemn Russia&#39;s meddling and he to Moscow to condemn the European Union. “Then we&#39;d fly back and all sit down and carry on with the Iran talks.” Such fleet-footed compartmentalisation would now be impossible.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> America&#39;s national security council is a bare-bones operation, in part because Congress is loth to fund White House staff. In an essay published in 2016, Julianne Smith, now America&#39;s envoy to <small>NATO</small> , recalled her time as deputy national security adviser to Mr Biden when he was vice-president. “A typical day would often involve four to six hours of back-to-back meetings on anything from Syria to cybersecurity to North Korea,” followed by 150 to 500 emails per day. “My ability to plan, think beyond the next day in the office, or significantly deepen my knowledge of any single issue was virtually non-existent.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The expectation that top officials represent their country in a crisis often puts enormous pressure on a handful of people. Antony Blinken, America&#39;s secretary of state, has spent almost every waking hour shuttling between Middle Eastern capitals over the past six weeks. He recently flew from the Middle East to Tokyo, for a meeting of <small>G</small> 7 foreign ministers, then to India, and on to San Francisco. Mr Sullivan is also spread thinly.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Of pens and swords</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Even if diplomats can successfully spin multiple plates, the concurrence of crises presents a larger, strategic problem when it comes to military power. The current crisis in the Middle East shows that military power is a scarce resource—like diplomatic bandwidth. Even in recent years, Pentagon officials would boast that they were finally rebalancing naval power from the Middle East to Asia, after two decades of counterinsurgency in Afghanistan and Iraq. Now, under pressure of events, the trend is reversing.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> When the <i>USS Dwight D. Eisenhower</i> and its escorts entered the Red Sea on November 4th it was the first time an American aircraft-carrier had operated in the Middle East for two years. The exercises it conducted earlier with the <i>USS Gerald R. Ford</i> marked an unusually large show of force. If the war in Gaza drags on or widens, American naval forces may need to choose between sticking around, creating gaps in other parts of the world, including Asia, or emboldening Iran.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Meanwhile, Western officials increasingly think the war in Ukraine could drag on for another five years, with neither Russia nor Ukraine prepared to give in, but neither capable of breaking the stalemate. As the 2020s roll on, the red lights begin to flash. Many American intelligence officials, and some Asian ones, believe that the risk of a Chinese attack on Taiwan is greatest in a window at the end of this decade. Too early, and China is not ready. Too late, and China faces the prospect of demographic decline and a new generation of Western military technology.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Even without a war, the West&#39;s military capacity will come under enormous pressure in the coming years. The war in Ukraine has been a reminder of both just how much ammunition is consumed in big wars, but also how meagre Western armouries—and their means of replenishment—really are. America is dramatically upping its production of 155mm artillery shells. Even then, its output in 2025 is likely to be lower than that of Russia in 2024.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The wars in Ukraine and Gaza illustrate these stresses. Israel and Ukraine are fighting two different sorts of war. Ukraine needs long-range missiles to strike Crimea, armoured vehicles to allow infantry to advance in the face of shrapnel, and demining gear to punch through vast minefields. Israel wants air-dropped smart bombs, including bunker busters, and interceptors for its Iron Dome air-defence system, which are being fired at a prodigious rate. But there is overlap, too.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Last year America dipped into its stockpile of shells in Israel to arm Ukraine. In October it had to divert some Ukraine-bound shells to Israel. Both countries also use the Patriot missile-defence system, which takes out planes and larger missiles. So too do other allies in the Middle East: on October 19th Saudi Arabia used a Patriot battery to intercept Israel-bound missiles launched from Yemen. Ukraine&#39;s consumption of interceptors is likely to rise sharply over the winter as Russia, having stockpiled missiles for months, unleashes sustained barrages against Ukraine&#39;s power grid.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> America can probably satisfy both of its friends for the moment. In recent weeks, France and Germany have both pledged to increase assistance to Ukraine. But if either war—or both—drags on, there will be a pinch. “As time goes on, there will be trade-offs as certain key systems are diverted to Israel,” writes Mark Cancian of the Centre for Strategic and International Studies, a think-tank in Washington. “A few systems that Ukraine needs for its counter-offensive may not be available in the numbers that Ukraine would like.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The bigger problem is that, realistically, America could not arm itself and its allies at the same time. “If <small>US</small> production lines are already struggling to keep pace with the exigencies of arming Ukraine,” notes Iskander Rehman of Johns Hopkins University in a recent paper on protracted wars, “they would be completely overwhelmed in the event of an actual protracted, peer-to-peer conflict with an adversary such as China.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These challenges point to deeper tensions in American defence strategy. From 1992 onward American military planners held to what was known as the “two-war” standard. America&#39;s armed forces had to be ready to fight two simultaneous medium-sized wars against regional powers—think Iraq or Iran—rather than simply a single big war. In 2018 the Trump administration changed this to a “one-war” standard: in practice, a commitment to be able to fight either a war in Europe or in Asia, but not both at the same time. Mr Biden&#39;s administration stuck with this approach.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The aim was to instil discipline in the Pentagon and to bring ends in line with means: America&#39;s defence budget is virtually flat in real terms, while Chinese defence spending has soared. But the risk, argued critics, was that the one-war standard would tempt enemies to open a second front—which could then force America to either back down or resort to unappealing options, like nuclear threats.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Too many plates</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> What risks do America and its allies run by being so stretched across diplomatic and military realms? If the war in Ukraine stays an open sore in Europe and the Middle East remains ablaze, the West will struggle gravely should another serious crisis erupt. One risk is that adversaries simply capitalise on chaos elsewhere for their own ends. If America were bogged down in a Pacific war, for instance, Iran would surely feel more confident of getting away with a dash for nuclear weapons.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Even more worrying is the prospect of active collusion. European military planners give weight to the possibility that Russia might conduct menacing manoeuvres during a crisis over Taiwan in order to divert American attention and tie down its allies, preventing them from lending a hand in Asia. As in the cold war, each crisis, no matter how parochial or trivial, might come to be seen as a test of American or Chinese power, drawing each country in.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Then there are the surprises. Western intelligence agencies have their hands full watching China and Russia. Few expected Hamas to throw the Middle East back into turmoil as it did on October 7th. Civil wars and insurgencies in the Democratic Republic of Congo, Mali, Myanmar, Somalia and Sudan have all been neglected, diplomatically, even as Russian influence in the Sahel continues to grow. Meanwhile on November 10th dozens of Chinese ships circled Philippine vessels, blasting one with water cannon, as the latter attempted to resupply an outpost on Second Thomas Shoal in the South China Sea, which China claims as its own. If the confrontations worsen, the terms of America&#39;s defence treaty with the Philippines may oblige it to intervene.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Amid disorder, strategists talk about the importance of “walking and chewing gum”. It is a uniquely American metaphor that once referred to performing two trivial activities at once, and now explains the importance of geopolitical multi-tasking. Others are available. In his forthcoming book, “To Run the World”, Mr Radchenko, the historian, quotes Zhou Enlai, China&#39;s premier, identifying America&#39;s predicament in 1964: “If there were just a few more Congos in Africa, a few more Vietnams in Asia, a few more Cubas in Latin America, then America would have to spread ten fingers to ten more places…we can chop them off one by one.”</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:38:58 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/11v2pq4psif4fpmblmaurnqmag4en119</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/international/2023/11/13/from-gaza-to-ukraine-wars-and-crises-are-piling-up </item><item><title><![CDATA[Inside a month of America’s school shootings]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="wrapper-black-bg svelte-1yz225c" id="article-core"><p class="wrapper"><svelte-scroller-outer class="svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background-container class="background-container svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background class="svelte-xdbafy"><div class="svelte-1t1wh6u"><div class="video-wrap svelte-1t1wh6u"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/guns_header_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/guns_header_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div><section class="svelte-1t1wh6u"><div class="svelte-1t1wh6u"> There has been an incident of gun violence<br> in or near an American school every day this year, on average. </div></section></div></svelte-scroller-background></svelte-scroller-background-container><svelte-scroller-foreground class="svelte-xdbafy"></svelte-scroller-foreground></svelte-scroller-outer></p><p class="wrapper"><svelte-scroller-outer class="svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background-container class="background-container svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background class="svelte-xdbafy"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="wrapper svelte-17bscwa"><svg height="537.5" width="700px" class="svelte-17bscwa"><g><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">中号</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">时间</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">瓦</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">时间</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">F</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa"> S</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa"> S</text><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 1</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 2</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 3</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 4</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 5</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 6</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 7</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 8</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 9</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 10</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 11</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 12</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 13</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 14</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 15</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 16</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 17 号</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend">18</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 19</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 20</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 21</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 22</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 23</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 24</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 25</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 26</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 27</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 28 </text></g></g></svg></div></div></svelte-scroller-background></svelte-scroller-background-container><svelte-scroller-foreground class="svelte-xdbafy"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> February 2023 was five years since the high-school massacre in Parkland, Florida, in which a gunman killed 17 students and staff. It was also representative of a typical month of school gun violence.</div></section><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> There were 23 incidents of gun crime on or near school property <span>over 13 days</span> , which ranged from a fourth-grader brandishing a gun in the toilets to a student&#39;s stepfather committing suicide in the school office.</div></section><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> In five shootings, <span>across four days</span> , a victim died.</div></section><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> In eight more someone was injured.</div></section><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> There were also <span>148 “ <small>SWAT</small> hoaxes”</span> , in which false threats of a school shooting were made to police, which can lead to an armed response.</div></section><section class="svelte-1m3vqzg"><div class="svelte-1m3vqzg"> What follows contains images and descriptions of violence some readers may find distressing. </div></section></div></svelte-scroller-foreground></svelte-scroller-outer></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/brooklyn_intro_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/brooklyn_intro_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> This shooting took place outside the school building, after school, which means it would not be counted as a <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/10/15/one-response-to-school-shootings-in-america-arm-the-teachers">school shooting</a> in most datasets. Although the government logs every time someone is killed or injured in a car crash in America, there is no federal record of when a gun is fired on school property, and the databases that do exist all define this type of violence differently. Some only include shootings that happen during the school day, while others only count incidents in which someone is killed or injured. </body-text></p><figure class="ai2html-chart svelte-1g0grgd text-col-image ds-container"><div class="container svelte-1ajxt9k"><div class><div id="g-schoolshooting_line-box" class="ai2html svelte-4oi5jr"><div id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy" class="g-artboard svelte-4oi5jr"><img id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy-img" class="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy-img g-aiImg svelte-4oi5jr" alt src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="><div id="g-ai0-1" class="g-KEY g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle0 svelte-4oi5jr"> Victims injured or killed in US school shootings </p></div><div id="legend-text" class="g-content-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle2 svelte-4oi5jr"> K-12 school shooting database </p></div><div id="source-string" class="g-background-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle5 svelte-4oi5jr"> Sources: Washington Post; Everytown for Gun Safety; K-12 School Shooting Database </p></div></div><div id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_2" class="g-artboard svelte-4oi5jr"><img id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_2-img" class="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_2-img g-aiImg svelte-4oi5jr" alt src="/interactive/united-states/2023/11/13/inside-a-month-of-americas-school-shootings/images/schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_2.png"><div id="g-ai1-1" class="g-KEY g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle0 svelte-4oi5jr"> Victims injured or killed in US school shootings </p></div><div id="legend-text" class="g-content-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle2 svelte-4oi5jr"> K-12 school shooting database </p></div><div id="source-string" class="g-background-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle5 svelte-4oi5jr"> Sources: <span class="g-cstyle0 svelte-4oi5jr">Washington Post</span> ; Everytown for Gun Safety; K-12 School Shooting Database </p></div></div><div id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_3" class="g-artboard svelte-4oi5jr"><img id="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_3-img" class="g-schoolshooting_line-Artboard_1_copy_3-img g-aiImg svelte-4oi5jr" alt src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="><div id="g-ai2-1" class="g-KEY g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle0 svelte-4oi5jr"> Victims injured or killed</p><p class="g-pstyle0 svelte-4oi5jr"> in US school shootings </p></div><div id="legend-text" class="g-content-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle2 svelte-4oi5jr"> K-12 school shooting database </p></div><div id="source-string" class="g-background-layer g-aiAbs g-aiPointText svelte-4oi5jr"><p class="g-pstyle5 svelte-4oi5jr"> Sources: Washington Post; Everytown for Gun Safety;</p><p class="g-pstyle5 svelte-4oi5jr"> K-12 School Shooting Database </p></div></div></div></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> The K-12 School Shooting database, compiled by David Riedman, a data scientist, includes every time a gun is brandished, fired on or hits school property—or areas outside the school, such as pavements—at any time and for any reason, as these incidents can all cause significant disruption. “Most people think that a school shooting is something where it&#39;s this deranged person who&#39;s coming into the school,” he says. “But really, the most common circumstance for a gun to be fired is a dispute between students, usually taking place in a hallway or parking lot at dismissal.”</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> The impacts can play out for years. Researchers from Stanford University studied gun violence in Texan schools between 1998 and 2006. They found absences and grade repetition increased after a shooting, while graduation rates decreased. Students whose schools had experienced a shooting earned less by their mid-20s than those from unaffected schools. Another Stanford study found that, nationwide, near schools that experienced a fatal shooting, youth antidepressant prescriptions increased by 21% for two to three years after.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> In Brooklyn, the school moved to remote learning for three weeks after the shooting. “There was the lingering question of will this happen again? Am I safe?” says Jahi Bashir, the head of school at the time of the shooting. “It&#39;s very difficult to focus on instruction when you have these thoughts.” Despite extensive mental-health support from the school, 49 students left in the months following—more than three times the drop-out rate of a year earlier. The 15-year-old who was shot did not come back to in-person lessons for the remainder of the school year. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/brooklyn_student_impact_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/brooklyn_student_impact_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> The school spent over $90,000 on metal detectors and new security cameras. Three other schools that experienced shootings in February also invested in added security, at a total cost of around $450,000, including bullet-resistant glass and entry systems. The school-security, or “ <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/06/28/can-school-design-help-prevent-school-shootings">hardening</a> ”, industry in America grew by 57% between 2016 and 2021, when adjusted for inflation, to $1.6bn. But as this spending has increased, so too have shootings. “We&#39;re going in the wrong direction,” says Mr Riedman.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Part of the reason is that, by Mr Riedman&#39;s calculations, more than 70% of shootings take place outside school buildings, which metal detectors and bullet-proof doors will do little to prevent. Ellen Eagen, legal counsel for Williamsburg Charter High School, says the school&#39;s Board of Trustees nevertheless had little choice: “We are desperate to make schools safer, and in the absence of sensible gun regulation, educators have to do whatever they can to improve safety.” But it is not just spending on hardening that appears misplaced. The ways in which schools prepare students for an active shooter can have harmful consequences too. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/drills_aspen_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/drills_aspen_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Lockdown drills are part of life in around 95% of public schools in America. They became widespread after the Columbine mass shooting in Colorado in 1999, as no one who had hidden in a locked room was killed. But there is now a debate about whether these drills are needlessly traumatic given how unlikely children are to be involved in a Columbine-style siege. </body-text></p><div class="wrapper svelte-1c21mp8"><div class="legend svelte-1c21mp8"><div class="legend-item svelte-1c21mp8"> <span>Required but number not specified</span> </div></div><p><svg height="509.09090909090907px" width="700px" class="svelte-1c21mp8"><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> ME </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> AK </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> WI </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> VT </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NH </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> WA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> ID </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MT </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> ND </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MN </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> IL </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MI </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NY </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8">或者</text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NV </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> WY </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> SD </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> IA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> IN </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> OH </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> PA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NJ </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> CT </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> RI </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> CA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> UT </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> CO </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NE </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MO </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> KY </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> WV </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> VA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MD </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> DE </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> AZ </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NM </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> KS </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> AR </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> TN </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> NC </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> SC </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> DC </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> HI </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8">好的</text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> LA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> MS </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> AL </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> GA </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> TX </text><rect width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363" class="svelte-1c21mp8"/><text class="svelte-1c21mp8"> FL</text></svg></p></div><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> There is little guidance about how schools should run drills, or how many are necessary. Massachusetts does not mandate a number of lockdown drills per year, while neighbouring New York requires four. It is down to school districts or even individual schools to determine what these should involve. This has led to reports of schools using role play and fake blood, and children messaging their parents during a drill to say goodbye because they thought they were going to die.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Some of the most comprehensive research into how best to run drills has been done by Jaclyn Schildkraut, who has been studying drills in Syracuse, New York, for five years. There, drills are unannounced, but it is made clear they are not real, and students are given a chance to debrief afterwards. “We don&#39;t set schools on fire to practise fire drills,” says Ms Schildkraut. “So it&#39;s really important that we&#39;re not simulating active-shooter events to practise a lockdown.” But even in a school in Syracuse, some children seemed unsettled by the drills when <i>The Economist</i> visited. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/drills_syracuse_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/drills_syracuse_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> There are now multiple bills going through state legislatures to reduce drills&#39; frequency and make them less upsetting, by doing things like announcing a drill before students lock down, and allowing parents the chance to opt their children out.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Ultimately, however, no amount of practice can prepare students, teachers and parents for the terror of a potential shooting. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/swatting_intro_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/swatting_intro_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> These calls prompted a huge police response. One of the first dispatch centres to receive a call was in Aspen. Just over a minute later officers were in Aspen Elementary School hunting for a gunman. At least 44 officers from five different forces, along with 27 medics, 26 firefighters and nine ambulances, attended the scene. Michael Buglione, the local sheriff, said it was the biggest unplanned emergency response he had seen in his 18-year career. Around 500 children locked down in their classrooms, just as they had practised the day before.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> But there was no shooter. This was a hoax call, one of 17 made across Colorado on February 22nd.</body-text></p><div class="wrapper svelte-zhhopx"><p class="svelte-zhhopx"> 0 </p><p><svg height="509.09090909090907px" width="700px" class="svelte-zhhopx"><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> ME </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> AK </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NH </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MT </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> WY </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> SD </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> IA </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> IN </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> OH </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NJ </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> CT </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> RI </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> UT </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NE </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MO </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> KY </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> WV </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> VA </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MD </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> DE </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> AZ </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> KS </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> AR </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> TN </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NC </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> SC </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> DC </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> HI </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx">好的</text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> LA </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MS </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> AL </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> GA </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> TX </text><rect class="state svelte-zhhopx" width="63.63636363636363" height="63.63636363636363"/><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> FL</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> CA</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MI</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> WI</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MA</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> VT</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> WA</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NV</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NM</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> IL</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx">或者</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx">CO</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> ID</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> PA</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> NY</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> MN</text><circle class="hoaxes svelte-zhhopx"/><text class="state svelte-zhhopx"> ND</text></svg></p></div><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> These “ <small>SWAT</small> hoaxes”, so called as they can require the response of a special weapons and tactics, or <small>SWAT</small> , team, capitalise on fear to cause chaos—and they are increasing. According to The Educator&#39;s School Safety Network, a think-tank, there were around 70 such hoaxes against schools in the 2018 school year, and 450 in 2022. Mr Riedman, who started tracking swatting in 2023, recorded 148 in February alone.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Some of the calls were made from a number with a Florida area code—but they may not have come from there. They were made using a voice over internet protocol service, which, if coupled with the use of a virtual private network ( <small>VPN</small> ), means they could have come from anywhere. Although the attack was a hoax, the fear felt by people who lived through it was very real. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/swatting_trauma_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/swatting_trauma_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Jennifer Doebler, a former <small>FBI</small> intelligence analyst, believes these calls are more than just pranks. “It was an intentional plot to create mass chaos,” she says. “I personally believe these are acts of domestic terrorism.” The caller behind the Colorado hoaxes said his name was Nelson, and referred to pipe bombs and an <a href="https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/10/05/the-ar-15-is-a-symbol-of-liberty-or-loss-depending-on-whom-you-ask">AR</a> <a href="https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/10/05/the-ar-15-is-a-symbol-of-liberty-or-loss-depending-on-whom-you-ask">-15 rifle</a> on several calls. Keven Hendricks, a cybercrime expert and investigator, says these details suggest these could be copycat attacks, as they are reminiscent of Kya Nelson, a serial swatter who is now in prison. The <small>FBI</small> started tracking <small>SWAT</small> hoaxes in May 2023, and is investigating the Colorado calls, but declined to comment on these cases when contacted by <i>The Economist</i> . (Watch a<a href="https://www.economist.com/films/2023/11/13/inside-americas-hoax-school-shootings-epidemic">longer investigation</a> into swatting.)</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> There is also a financial cost. The Aspen school district spent $6m improving its security following the call in February—$2m over budget—because the police response highlighted shortcomings.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> But the real thing can damage communities in ways that cannot so easily be repaired. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/denver_twins_march_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/denver_twins_march_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> The twins&#39; activism has had some impact: in the months after the shooting state legislators raised the legal age to purchase firearms in Colorado from 18 to 21. The state&#39;s red-flag laws, which allow people to petition for authorities to confiscate an individual&#39;s firearms, were expanded, and a three-day waiting period before firearms purchases can be delivered was introduced. But the shootings continued. On March 22nd a student at East High, Austin Lyle, shot and injured two staff members as they were checking him for weapons at the school&#39;s entrance. He killed himself later that day.</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> This prompted a dramatic shift within Denver&#39;s public-school system. The school board reintroduced <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2020/07/18/do-police-officers-in-schools-help-or-hinder-teachers">school resource officers</a> ( <small>SRO</small> s), in effect armed police, to several schools. <small>SRO</small> s had been removed in 2020 in the wake of George Floyd&#39;s murder over fears they were disproportionately targeting non-white students. In June the school board voted to make <small>SRO</small> s permanent, and as of August 2023 there were at least 14 armed officers in Denver schools paid for by the city. But for many parents this was not the answer they were hoping for, and the community remains deeply divided about the best way to protect its children. </body-text></p><figure class="svelte-16w2070"><div class="sticky-container svelte-16w2070"><div class="container"><video width="896" height="NaN" class="svelte-xfdpaj"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/denver_dad_896.webm" type="video/webm"><source src="https://cdn.economistdatateam.com/videos/2023-us-school-shootings/denver_dad_896.mp4" type="video/mp4"> Your browser does not support this video.</video></div></div></figure><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> The Denver Public School board issued a new safety plan in June in response to the shootings stating that individual schools could invest in metal detectors, but Mr Katsaros&#39;s remain in a storage unit. Like many parents in Denver, he now feels the problem goes much deeper than security checks. “I thought it was all about guns,” he says, “but I&#39;ve come to find out, it&#39;s the entire discipline structure. Having metal detectors as a deterrent is one solution [...] Having school resource officers is a solution, but there&#39;s no singular solution that can fix this.”</body-text></p><p class="article-text"><body-text class="svelte-1hsw51r"> Many parents, teachers and pupils would agree. But a lack of timely and comprehensive data on school shootings is also hindering America&#39;s response. Mr Riedman notes that it can take over a year for crime data to be published. “With trends like swatting or shootings at schools, these are things where we need to be adjusting policy in real time,” he says. A clearer understanding of the extent of gun crime in American schools, and the dire consequences, may galvanise authorities and politicians to provide better answers.</body-text></p><h4 class="svelte-pt7au7"> Explore every incident in February 2023 using the calendar below. </h4><div class="wrapper svelte-pt7au7"><div class="svelte-pt7au7"><p class="wrapper"><svg height="537.5" width="700px" class="svelte-17bscwa"><g><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">中号</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">时间</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">瓦</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">时间</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa">F</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa"> S</text><text class="day-label svelte-17bscwa"> S</text><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 1</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 2</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 3</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 4</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 5</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 6</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 7</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 8</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 9</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 10</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 11</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 12</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 13</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 14</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 15</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 16</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 17 号</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend">18</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 19</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 20</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 21</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 22</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 23</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 24</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 25</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa weekend"> 26</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa incident"> 27</text></g><g><text class="svelte-17bscwa"> 28</text></g></g></svg></p></div></div><div class="sources svelte-1yz225c"><p class="article-sources">Sources: K-12 School Shooting Database;<i>经济学家</i></p></div></div>]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:21:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/m7qahgmkeu3fgbko528jc8n32cu1l7ug</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/interactive/united-states/2023/11/13/inside-a-month-of-americas-school-shootings </item><item><title><![CDATA[5. The clown car]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听这个播客</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/open/s/64ee35bafc643000110d1607/e/6542d584df8cb80012c15340/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6IkxWSlA2Sk9kIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwcml2YXRlIn0=&sig=0VvOqmIBkL8NdgcdrTYRpJ648wEEATgVTgLEHU8nuHQ"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>hat if all</small> the meetings in your calendar disappeared overnight? Tia Silas, Chief HR Officer of Shopify, an e-commerce firm, tells Andrew Palmer what happened when they tried just that. Claire Hughes-Johnson, a former COO of Stripe, offers a practical guide to <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2023/11/13/the-curse-of-the-badly-run-meeting">running meetings</a> . And we eavesdrop on the weekly meeting at <i>The Economist</i> , with lessons from Zanny Minton Beddoes, our editor-in-chief, on how she encourages constructive debate. Runtime: 30 mins</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">收听： <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/boss-class-from-the-economist/id1705972518">Apple 播客</a>| <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5U9AVLBdcqysaLO8vOxlpM">Spotify.</a></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This is a subscriber-only episode. Sign up for a <a href="https://economist.com/podcastsplus-bossclass">free trial</a> of Economist Podcasts+ or if you&#39;re already a subscriber to <i>The Economist</i> , you have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.有关如何访问《经济学人播客+》的更多信息，请访问我们的<a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">常见问题解答页面</a>或观看我们解释如何链接您的帐户的<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">视频</a>。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">播客成绩单可通过<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__">[email protected]</a>索取。我们致力于进一步提高可访问性，并正在探索新的方法来扩展我们的播客转录内容。</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/97llr5im3mbld6htsn14jp4bl9oc32v7</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/13/5-the-clown-car </item><item><title><![CDATA[The curse of the badly run meeting]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>n January 1944</small> the Office of Strategic Services, an American wartime intelligence agency, issued a short document. The “Simple Sabotage Field Manual” offered advice on how ordinary citizens in occupied Europe could disrupt the German war machine.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To cause physical damage, the guide tells the “citizen-saboteur” to use everyday items like salt, nails, pebbles and candles as weapons. This bit of the guide is a window into historical derring-do: dried-up sponges that can expand to plug sewer systems, jammed locks on unguarded buildings, various references to emery dust.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But the guide also outlines a less direct sort of sabotage, which is alarmingly familiar to anyone who works in an office today. This form of obstruction involves behaviour that confuses, demoralises and delays. Manager-saboteurs should ensure that three people have to approve things when one would do. Employees should spread disturbing rumours. Everyone should “give lengthy and incomprehensible explanations when questioned”. At some point a wartime effort to hurt the Nazis appears to have been mistaken for a serious guide on how to run the modern workplace.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> No bit of the manual is more recognisable than its advice on how to turn meetings into weapons of mass distraction. Hold them when there is more important work to be done, it urges. Talk as often as possible and at immense length. Reopen questions that have already been decided. Bring up irrelevant issues whenever you can.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It&#39;s hard not to read all this and ponder if your own organisation is being targeted by an enemy. And once that thought enters your mind, you also start to wonder whether all sorts of behaviour reflect instructions in a revised edition.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • Call hybrid meetings whenever possible to maximise inefficiency. If you are in the room together, initiate side conversations to sow confusion among remote attendees.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • If you are on Zoom, unmute yourself slowly or not at all. Pretend not to be able to hear anything even when you can. Look baffled. Put on eight different pairs of headphones. Shrug theatrically. Entire geological eras can pass in this way.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • Alternatively, dial into the meeting on your phone, unmute yourself and put the phone in your pocket. Go for a long walk. If this is done right, a single person can force tens of others to abandon a meeting.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • Always turn up to meetings a few minutes late. This is especially important if you hold a senior role. Nothing will happen until you get there except for some awkward interchanges about weekend plans. If discussions have started, ask for a quick recap. If you have co-conspirators, stagger your arrival times so that you are constantly going back to the beginning.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • Don&#39;t have an agenda. Just turn up and look expectant. If there is pre-reading, don&#39;t do it. Never agree on action items or take minutes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • If there is an agenda, take advantage of “the law of triviality”, a rule of thumb coined in 1957 by Cyril Northcote Parkinson. This refers to an imaginary committee whose members are asked to decide on proposals for a nuclear power plant and a new bike shed. Lacking expertise in nuclear power, the committee nods the plant through. Where everyone is an authority, like the bike shed, endless debate ensues. Whatever your version of the bike shed is—coffee machines, Oxford commas—bring it up early.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • If you are giving a presentation after someone else, take an absolute age to find it. Faff around in the wrong folder. Act as if you can&#39;t see the slide-show button until someone else points it out.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> • Say things like “there are no bad ideas”, so that everyone offers up their own bad ideas. At the end ask “does anyone have anything else?” and wait for as long as it takes for someone to fill the silence. Hopefully, it will be about the coffee machine and everything will kick off again. Conclude by saying that you think it has been a very useful meeting but don&#39;t specify in what way.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> If you are behaving like this inadvertently, listen to the latest episode of <a href="https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/13/5-the-clown-car">Boss Class</a> , our management podcast, to find out how to run a meeting better. If you are trying to cause disruption, your cover is blown. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:58:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/gjr73dtm4a0ltegpuvd4o993urjuj418</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/11/13/the-curse-of-the-badly-run-meeting </item><item><title><![CDATA[Should lockdown drills be part of life for American students?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<main id="content"><article id="new-article-template"><div class="css-1bfdg3q e1pkqesp0"><div class="css-1qjp74c e8tkvfk0"><div class="css-1r2sn2n e1mdktgm0"><div class="css-17yzdrv euxoahl0"><section class="css-12k3cm0 e1ey6m751"><div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/97UHTAlEk5U?enablejsapi=1" class="css-wc7bct e1wp1ol0"></iframe><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>M</span> <small>ost children</small> in America will experience a lockdown drill. Introduced in the wake of the Columbine massacre, drills have become a mainstay in preparing pupils for the worst. But questions are being asked about whether drills do more harm than good.</p></div></section></div></div></div></div></article></main> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:49:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ts5v5cbecuqb9oo4uffice9cgi3rc9ko</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/films/2023/11/13/should-lockdown-drills-be-part-of-life-for-american-students </item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 is the biggest election year in history]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="script-microapp"><div class="scroller"><p class="wrapper"><svelte-scroller-outer class="svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background-container class="background-container svelte-xdbafy"><svelte-scroller-background class="svelte-xdbafy"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="bubble-chart svelte-16mje1o"><svg width="800" height="5592"><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="N. Korea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Chad" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Belarus" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Venezuela" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Russia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">俄罗斯</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">144m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Guinea-Bissau" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Burkina Faso" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Rwanda" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Jordan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Comoros" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mali" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mozambique" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Algeria" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mauritania" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Pakistan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">巴基斯坦</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">245m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Turkey" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">火鸡</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">86m</text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="El Salvador" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Georgia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mexico" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">墨西哥</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">129m</text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Ukraine" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Tunisia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Senegal" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bangladesh" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">孟加拉国</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">175m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="North Macedonia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Moldova" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mongolia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Dominican Republic" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Ghana" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Romania" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Sri Lanka" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Croatia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Namibia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bulgaria" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Hungary" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Indonesia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">印度尼西亚</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">280m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Panama" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="India" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">印度</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">1.4bn </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Poland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="S. Africa" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Slovakia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Lithuania" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Latvia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cyprus" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Belgium" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Italy" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Malta" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Botswana" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Slovenia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="United States" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">美国</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">342m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Portugal" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Estonia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Greece" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="S. Korea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="France" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Spain" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Mauritius" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Austria" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Britain" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">英国</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">68m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Taiwan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Germany" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Luxembourg" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Uruguay" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Netherlands" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Ireland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Denmark" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Finland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Sweden" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Iceland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="New Zealand" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Norway" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Australia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Canada" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Switzerland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Israel" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Chile" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Costa Rica" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Japan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Thailand" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Colombia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Philippines" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Brazil" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><text class="text svelte-3zvhw2">巴西</text><text class="text-value svelte-3zvhw2">218m </text></g></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Argentina" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Suriname" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Jamaica" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Trinidad and Tobago" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Malaysia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bhutan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Fiji" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Armenia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Ecuador" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Madagascar" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Zambia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Paraguay" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Malawi" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Papua New Guinea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Lesotho" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Singapore" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Serbia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Guyana" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Albania" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Montenegro" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bolivia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Uganda" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Guatemala" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Sierra Leone" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Morocco" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Kenya" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Tanzania" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Honduras" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Hong Kong" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Liberia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Lebanon" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Qatar" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Niger" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Kuwait" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Palestine" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Angola" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Nigeria" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Benin" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Gambia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Nepal" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bahrain" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cameroon" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Egypt" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cuba" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Vietnam" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Djibouti" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Haiti" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Azerbaijan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Zimbabwe" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Togo" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Swaziland" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Kazakhstan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Oman" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Iraq" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Ethiopia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Sudan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cambodia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Gabon" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Turkmenistan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Lao" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Equatorial Guinea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="China" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Tajikistan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Yemen" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Iran" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Eritrea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Libya" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Saudi Arabia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Uzbekistan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Burundi" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Guinea" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Nicaragua" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Peru" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="United Arab Emirates" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cape Verde" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Cote d'Ivoire" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Bosnia" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Timor-Leste" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Congo-Brazzaville" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Kyrgyzstan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Czech Republic" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Afghanistan" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Myanmar" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Central African Republic" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Syria" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g><g><g class="svelte-3zvhw2"><circle id="Congo" class="node svelte-3zvhw2"/></g></g></svg></div></div></svelte-scroller-background></svelte-scroller-background-container><svelte-scroller-foreground class="svelte-xdbafy"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> In 2024, countries with <span>more than half the world&#39;s population</span> —over four billion people—will send their citizens to the polls. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> But many elections are not fully free and fair. Some of these will have no meaningful influence on governments. </div></div></section><section class="section-four svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> Our sister organisation, <small>EIU</small> , grades countries out of ten according to the state of their democracy and categorises them from authoritarian regimes, to hybrid regimes and democracies. </div><div class="key svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="bomb-damage-spectrum-legend-labels"><div class="categories-wrapper-text svelte-1drkihi"><p class="svelte-1drkihi"> Authoritarian</p><p class="svelte-1drkihi">杂交种</p><p class="svelte-1drkihi">Democracies </p></div></div></div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> In the most democratic countries, such as <span>Britain</span> , elections will decide the next government or cause a substantial change in policy. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> In <span>Russia</span> , one of the least democratic, the vote is very unlikely to weaken Vladimir Putin&#39;s grip on power. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> For countries in between, such as <span>India</span> or the <span>United States</span> , elections still matter, and may even be free and fair. But other aspects of democracy, such as participation or governance, have weaknesses. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> Some places, such as <span>Brazil</span> and <span>Turkey</span> , will not hold general elections in 2024 but have local or municipal elections in which the whole country will participate. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> Similarly, the European Union&#39;s 27 member states will elect the bloc&#39;s next parliament. </div></div></section><section class=" svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="svelte-ulc3n9"><div class="step-container svelte-ulc3n9"> More people will vote in 2024 than in any previous year. But this great march to the ballot box does not necessarily mean an explosion of democracy. </div></div></section></div></svelte-scroller-foreground></svelte-scroller-outer></p></div><p class="article-text"> According to our calculations, 76 countries are scheduled to hold elections in which all voters have the chance to cast a ballot in 2024. Of the 71 covered by <small>EIU</small> ’s Democracy Index, 43 will enjoy fully free and fair votes (27 of which are <small>EU</small> members); the other 28 do not meet the essential conditions for a democratic vote. Eight of the ten most populous countries in the world—Bangladesh, Brazil, India, Indonesia, Mexico, Pakistan, Russia and the United States—will hold elections in 2024. In half of these, elections are neither free nor fair and many other prerequisites of democracy, such as freedom of speech and association, are absent. Elections in Bangladesh, Mexico, Pakistan (all hybrid regimes, which combine elements of democracy and authoritarianism) and Russia (an authoritarian one) are almost certain not to bring regime change.</p><p class="article-text"> Brazil, India, Indonesia and the United States, meanwhile, are classified by <small>EIU</small> as “flawed democracies”, meaning that elections are free, fair and allow for the possibility of change, but their political systems have weaknesses. In February in Indonesia, the most populous country in South-East Asia, the centre-left <small>PDI-P</small> is likely to win the legislative and presidential elections. In India in May, Narendra Modi&#39;s ruling <small>BJP</small> , the world&#39;s biggest political party with more than 180m members, is likely to win despite rising anti-incumbent sentiment. And in Brazil in October municipal elections will reveal whether the left-wing Workers&#39; Party of President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva can make gains at the expense of the right-leaning Liberal Party, which dominates congress and is backed by Lula&#39;s right-wing predecessor Jair Bolsonaro.</p><p class="article-text"> Then in November voters in the United States will elect their next president, as well as the entire House of Representatives and a third of the Senate. Of the five aspects of democracy that <small>EIU</small> measures—electoral process and pluralism; functioning of government; political participation; political culture; and civil liberties—America&#39;s lowest score is for political culture. President Joe Biden is likely to face Donald Trump, the Republican front-runner, in a repeat of 2020.</p><p class="article-text"> It is not only the biggest elections that will capture the world&#39;s attention: Taiwan&#39;s vote in January will shape the island&#39;s relations with China at a critical time for the would-be independent island, which is home to 24m people. The pro-independence Democratic Progressive Party is likely to retain control of the presidency and the legislature. </p><div><div class="container svelte-12zyglz"><div class="chartContainer svelte-12zyglz"><p class="chart"><svg width="700" height="450" class="svelte-12zyglz"><g><g class="axis svelte-1u2byv9 y"><line class="gridline svelte-52m8tk gridline-zero"/><line class="gridline svelte-52m8tk"/><line class="gridline svelte-52m8tk"/><line class="gridline svelte-52m8tk"/><line class="gridline svelte-52m8tk"/><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><text> 0</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><text> 1</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><text> 2</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><text> 3</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><text> 4 </text></g></g><g class="x_axis"><g class="axis svelte-1u2byv9 x"><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text>1800</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text> 50</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text> 50</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text> 1900</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text> 2000年</text></g><g class="tick svelte-1u2byv9"><line class="svelte-1u2byv9"/><text>24 </text></g><line class="domain svelte-1u2byv9"/></g></g><rect width="3" height="0.8216666666667152"/><rect width="3" height="1.0503976900000112"/><rect width="3" height="1.6639567799999782"/><rect width="3" height="0.625263296666617"/><rect width="3" height="0.19559185333332607"/><rect width="3" height="1.757603096666685"/><rect width="3" height="1.1203796199999942"/><rect width="3" height="0.6740588900000262"/><rect width="3" height="0.23259952666666095"/><rect width="3" height="2.13063434999998"/><rect width="3" height="0.07457320999998274"/><rect width="3" height="2.28397832666667"/><rect width="3" height="1.155388710000011"/><rect width="3" height="0.8853322033333484"/><rect width="3" height="3.2945664599999986"/><rect width="3" height="3.82546308000002"/><rect width="3" height="3.3219087233333084"/><rect width="3" height="5.7407715600000415"/><rect width="3" height="3.011199533333297"/><rect width="3" height="7.585199689999968"/><rect width="3" height="0.1214557700000114"/><rect width="3" height="2.7459661133332816"/><rect width="3" height="0.4350261966666835"/><rect width="3" height="4.725608289999968"/><rect width="3" height="0.19380970666668418"/><rect width="3" height="4.403266813333346"/><rect width="3" height="3.245628960000033"/><rect width="3" height="1.905341083333326"/><rect width="3" height="0.19821703000002344"/><rect width="3" height="7.699119616666678"/><rect width="3" height="6.721192636666672"/><rect width="3" height="3.846347526666648"/><rect width="3" height="0.5494003599999928"/><rect width="3" height="7.282480580000026"/><rect width="3" height="3.0675917733333335"/><rect width="3" height="3.98310727333336"/><rect width="3" height="7.646654266666644"/><rect width="3" height="2.6562982099999886"/><rect width="3" height="5.1109182399999895"/><rect width="3" height="3.9346104766666485"/><rect width="3" height="5.506158176666702"/><rect width="3" height="7.030382516666691"/><rect width="3" height="2.411495676666675"/><rect width="3" height="4.379624756666658"/><rect width="3" height="1.6958577466666611"/><rect width="3" height="7.931092840000019"/><rect width="3" height="4.202808663333315"/><rect width="3" height="12.09697676999997"/><rect width="3" height="4.510229446666699"/><rect width="3" height="5.2476067433333355"/><rect width="3" height="2.5441604300000336"/><rect width="3" height="10.166799506666678"/><rect width="3" height="3.8602378500000327"/><rect width="3" height="5.611140786666681"/><rect width="3" height="0.9919947833333254"/><rect width="3" height="5.315182059999984"/><rect width="3" height="9.651460226666643"/><rect width="3" height="6.322129630000006"/><rect width="3" height="5.724159780000036"/><rect width="3" height="5.561780756666678"/><rect width="3" height="6.788521356666649"/><rect width="3" height="4.718930266666632"/><rect width="3" height="6.702097200000026"/><rect width="3" height="8.919727296666622"/><rect width="3" height="9.075480593333339"/><rect width="3" height="6.801892966666685"/><rect width="3" height="10.254141319999974"/><rect width="3" height="12.705716156666654"/><rect width="3" height="9.963762676666647"/><rect width="3" height="9.47081526333335"/><rect width="3" height="11.94115145666666"/><rect width="3" height="10.241898100000014"/><rect width="3" height="3.716246083333317"/><rect width="3" height="16.53153477666666"/><rect width="3" height="3.3474858533332963"/><rect width="3" height="16.298767920000046"/><rect width="3" height="9.14834695999997"/><rect width="3" height="13.268210403333342"/><rect width="3" height="5.229080383333326"/><rect width="3" height="13.013042206666626"/><rect width="3" height="14.325829479999982"/><rect width="3" height="10.749873313333353"/><rect width="3" height="2.2009998533333146"/><rect width="3" height="16.69320948666666"/><rect width="3" height="10.439051699999993"/><rect width="3" height="17.462683983333307"/><rect width="3" height="8.817477066666697"/><rect width="3" height="9.21345012333336"/><rect width="3" height="4.844807956666671"/><rect width="3" height="22.48815894333336"/><rect width="3" height="6.866011579999963"/><rect width="3" height="23.275081676666673"/><rect width="3" height="12.355355266666663"/><rect width="3" height="15.892722776666687"/><rect width="3" height="9.805585753333332"/><rect width="3" height="14.675839566666696"/><rect width="3" height="6.25999664666665"/><rect width="3" height="26.30265509333333"/><rect width="3" height="7.7316841033332935"/><rect width="3" height="17.82378134999999"/><rect width="3" height="6.772887746666697"/><rect width="3" height="20.40982464333331"/><rect width="3" height="16.07916425999997"/><rect width="3" height="18.83826128333334"/><rect width="3" height="7.404055830000004"/><rect width="3" height="22.36608653666667"/><rect width="3" height="10.894457936666697"/><rect width="3" height="19.56896403666667"/><rect width="3" height="8.235523530000023"/><rect width="3" height="26.953193146666706"/><rect width="3" height="6.340196340000034"/><rect width="3" height="70.71930806999995"/><rect width="3" height="6.002709516666641"/><rect width="3" height="24.675813673333323"/><rect width="3" height="10.7996581933333"/><rect width="3" height="14.53596599333332"/><rect width="3" height="17.471273396666675"/><rect width="3" height="68.11322819333333"/><rect width="3" height="29.24730813333332"/><rect width="3" height="63.317695103333335"/><rect width="3" height="53.84656229000001"/><rect width="3" height="29.734227896666653"/><rect width="3" height="41.30765906333335"/><rect width="3" height="41.693999770000005"/><rect width="3" height="15.635736473333338"/><rect width="3" height="51.59324692000001"/><rect width="3" height="9.815585823333379"/><rect width="3" height="41.39973135666668"/><rect width="3" height="15.147325626666714"/><rect width="3" height="67.95467794333337"/><rect width="3" height="19.82858885666667"/><rect width="3" height="36.26112266000001"/><rect width="3" height="20.096455186666674"/><rect width="3" height="58.0301571"/><rect width="3" height="17.26954175999998"/><rect width="3" height="39.43341207000003"/><rect width="3" height="24.077690606666692"/><rect width="3" height="32.76430333666667"/><rect width="3" height="9.411209436666638"/><rect width="3" height="20.294170129999998"/><rect width="3" height="3.249673009999981"/><rect width="3" height="25.049955723333312"/><rect width="3" height="10.213359296666681"/><rect width="3" height="17.139847379999992"/><rect width="3" height="59.14901847333334"/><rect width="3" height="97.76587754333332"/><rect width="3" height="24.66965793999998"/><rect width="3" height="87.01568465000003"/><rect width="3" height="31.423031586666696"/><rect width="3" height="46.58599420666667"/><rect width="3" height="64.15979304333331"/><rect width="3" height="44.677625233333345"/><rect width="3" height="33.6843120966667"/><rect width="3" height="46.48609462000002"/><rect width="3" height="38.21367535666667"/><rect width="3" height="36.18345698666667"/><rect width="3" height="77.76274455000004"/><rect width="3" height="82.82506246333332"/><rect width="3" height="30.8337553566667"/><rect width="3" height="54.293060016666686"/><rect width="3" height="36.66713281"/><rect width="3" height="103.3078438566667"/><rect width="3" height="39.8475544966667"/><rect width="3" height="51.035968999999966"/><rect width="3" height="46.9470547433333"/><rect width="3" height="56.541382940000005"/><rect width="3" height="87.96389784333331"/><rect width="3" height="40.998263766666696"/><rect width="3" height="55.63602913666671"/><rect width="3" height="82.77738453"/><rect width="3" height="104.09202850666668"/><rect width="3" height="58.264751536666665"/><rect width="3" height="39.70445042"/><rect width="3" height="75.65845051333332"/><rect width="3" height="38.39059720333336"/><rect width="3" height="73.75953573333334"/><rect width="3" height="117.89452031333332"/><rect width="3" height="74.52448284666667"/><rect width="3" height="96.13478472333333"/><rect width="3" height="137.69753561666664"/><rect width="3" height="56.35505687666665"/><rect width="3" height="80.71739775666668"/><rect width="3" height="66.14440785"/><rect width="3" height="171.97824537666668"/><rect width="3" height="67.10098503"/><rect width="3" height="100.31933053999995"/><rect width="3" height="97.50527832333336"/><rect width="3" height="106.96428005000001"/><rect width="3" height="175.55063512333334"/><rect width="3" height="140.50138118666666"/><rect width="3" height="177.06875709000002"/><rect width="3" height="135.16678391666665"/><rect width="3" height="102.20192489333334"/><rect width="3" height="130.83651097333336"/><rect width="3" height="102.6775903366667"/><rect width="3" height="234.48089325666663"/><rect width="3" height="106.8379033666667"/><rect width="3" height="207.30894392666667"/><rect width="3" height="256.60360957"/><rect width="3" height="156.57674828333336"/><rect width="3" height="78.71596043666665"/><rect width="3" height="146.39398012000004"/><rect width="3" height="75.60213783"/><rect width="3" height="303.51968554666666"/><rect width="3" height="97.58062225666669"/><rect width="3" height="117.32922921"/><rect width="3" height="133.99873361333334"/><rect width="3" height="149.44908285000002"/><rect width="3" height="259.12961860999997"/><rect width="3" height="147.50950736333328"/><rect width="3" height="129.81880160000003"/><rect width="3" height="161.96362162999998"/><rect width="3" height="96.72409981333334"/><rect width="3" height="347.38707610666665"/><rect width="3" height="138.51486823333335"/><rect width="3" height="151.70478927000005"/><rect width="3" height="87.13346428333335"/><rect width="3" height="201.09629722333332"/><rect width="3" height="317.56298368666666"/><rect width="3" height="139.85044331999995"/><rect width="3" height="137.66838491333334"/><rect width="3" height="119.02365358333333"/><rect width="3" height="120.92882250333332"/><rect width="3" height="402.09141595999995"/></g><text class="text svelte-12zyglz"> 4.2bn</text></svg></p></div></div></div><p class="article-text"> The two continents with the largest number of countries voting in 2024 are Europe (37) and Africa (18), though they could hardly be further apart in the Democracy Index. The Middle East and North Africa is the region with the lowest overall score (3.3), while sub-Saharan Africa is not much better (4.1). African countries with a combined population of over 330m, including Algeria, Ghana and Mozambique, will hold elections. The biggest will be in South Africa, home to more than 60m people. A divided and weak opposition means that, despite a series of corruption scandals, the ruling African National Congress is almost certain to win again.</p><p class="article-text"> Western Europe, meanwhile, scores highly in the index with an average of 8.4. The European Parliament elections in June will bring the issue of migration to the fore. The <small>EU</small> is on track to receive over 1m asylum applications this year, the most since a rush of arrivals in 2015-16. Many European politicians and voters see the influx of migrants as a threat, despite a mounting shortage of workers. The elections may shift the Parliament to the right as voters opt for parties calling for stricter controls on immigration.</p><p class="article-text"> And there is one scheduled election in Europe that, if it takes place, will be as much an act of defiance as democracy. Ukraine is due to elect a president in 2024. Volodymyr Zelensky, the incumbent, has not ruled out holding the vote, despite the country being under martial law, which forbids it. Any election that takes place while swathes of the country are under foreign occupation, and millions of Ukrainians remain displaced from their homes, could never be truly free or fair. A successful vote, were it possible, would be a show of resistance to Russia&#39;s attempts to crush Ukrainian independence. But a botched one could undermine Ukraine&#39;s efforts to be recognised as a democracy. <span>■</span> </p><div class="container"><div class="wrapper svelte-1vqa632"><input type="text" class="svelte-56k8rw"></div></div><p class="article-sources"> Sources: EIU; UN; V-dem 4;<i>经济学家</i></p><div class="related-content"><div class="related-content svelte-vhanhg"><div class="wrapper svelte-vhanhg"><div class="tiles svelte-vhanhg"><div class="tile main svelte-vhanhg"> <a href="https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2023/11/09/is-ukraines-counter-offensive-over" class="svelte-vhanhg"><img src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/image/20231111_WOT394.png" class="svelte-vhanhg"></a><p class="svelte-vhanhg"> Evidence from The Economist&#39;s war tracker </p></div><div><div class="tile other svelte-vhanhg"><div class="image svelte-vhanhg"><img src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/image/20231111_WOT317.png" class="svelte-vhanhg"></div></div><div class="tile other svelte-vhanhg"><div class="image svelte-vhanhg"><img src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/image/20231111_WOT971.png" class="svelte-vhanhg"></div></div><div class="tile other svelte-vhanhg"><div class="image svelte-vhanhg"><img src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/image/20231104_WOT296.png" class="svelte-vhanhg"></div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:49:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/vbl2p08p94or1gadmv6bju8c5ps479r5</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/interactive/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/2024-is-the-biggest-election-year-in-history </item><item><title><![CDATA[Teachers in Utah are learning to shoot. That may not be such a bad idea]]></title><description><![CDATA[<main id="content"><article id="new-article-template"><div class="css-1bfdg3q e1pkqesp0"><div class="css-1qjp74c e8tkvfk0"><div class="css-1r2sn2n e1mdktgm0"><section class="css-qm1vln e1m3q8rc0"><div class="css-b4a1pi elvs37n0"> <span class="css-1te5c83 e11l78dl0"><a href="/films/"><span>Films</span></a></span> <span class="css-1mdqtqm e11bnqe00">| Correspondent&#39;s Take</span> </div></section></div><div class="css-1r2sn2n e1mdktgm0"><div class="css-17yzdrv euxoahl0"><section class="css-12k3cm0 e1ey6m751"><div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xY1tuzs_xzI?enablejsapi=1" class="css-wc7bct e1wp1ol0"></iframe><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>T</span> <small>eachers in</small> 33 American states are legally allowed to carry a concealed weapon into a classroom. Now there are courses to teach them how to use these firearms. Tamara Gilkes Borr, <i>The Economist</i> ’s US policy correspondent and a former teacher, went to Utah to see how one such course is preparing teachers for the worst.</p></div></section></div></div></div></div></article></main> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:44:09 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/cvt20ic0e44sm7lgikrjhgq7dj4l53c1</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/films/2023/11/13/teachers-in-utah-are-learning-to-shoot-that-may-not-be-such-a-bad-idea </item><item><title><![CDATA[Inside America’s hoax school shootings epidemic]]></title><description><![CDATA[<main id="content"><article id="new-article-template"><div class="css-1bfdg3q e1pkqesp0"><div class="css-1qjp74c e8tkvfk0"><div class="css-1r2sn2n e1mdktgm0"><div class="css-17yzdrv euxoahl0"><section class="css-12k3cm0 e1ey6m751"><div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/q182URSXLv8?enablejsapi=1" class="css-wc7bct e1wp1ol0"></iframe><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>O</span> <small>ver the</small> past six months, <i>The Economist</i> has been <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/10/15/one-response-to-school-shootings-in-america-arm-the-teachers">investigating gun violence in American schools</a> . The impacts of firearms are devastating, even when no gun is fired. The fear of school shootings is being weaponised by hoax callers claiming they are about to attack a school.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the 2022-23 school year there were 450 such hoax calls, over six times more than in 2018-19. On February 22nd 2023 there were 17 in Colorado alone. In this film, <i>The Economist</i> investigates what happened that day.</p></div></section></div></div></div></div></article></main> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:41:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/6b7j465cpnog0kb6euh70r9ta73hftti</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/films/2023/11/13/inside-americas-hoax-school-shootings-epidemic</item></channel></rss>