<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 8 日星期三 09:22:45 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[The fall of WeWork shows the deepening cracks in real estate]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>自</span>2010年<small>成立以来</small>，WeWork从未实现过盈利。多年来，由于其浮夸的创始人亚当·诺依曼(Adam Neumann)扭曲现实的权力，它的现金火炬方式从未受到挑战，他成功地让投资者，尤其是软银，相信它不是一家办公室租赁公司，而是一家充满活力的科技公司。 “提升世界意识”的使命。 2019 年初，在首次公开募股 ( <small>IPO</small> ) 前夕，该公司的估值达到了 470 亿美元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事情很快就开始瓦解，外部投资者对其泡沫般的估值犹豫不决，并对诺伊曼对公司实行铁腕控制的非正统治理安排提出质疑。<small>首次公开募股</small>被搁置，诺伊曼先生被提供 17 亿美元的离职条件。桑迪普·马特拉尼 (Sandeep Mathrani) 是一名房地产资深人士，被任命来管理该公司，他尽最大努力通过削减成本和重新谈判租赁来扭转局面。 2021年，他通过一家特殊目的收购公司成功将公司上市，估值为90亿美元。然而，由于疫情导致办公市场低迷以及向远程工作的持久转变，他的努力化为泡影。 11 月 6 日，WeWork 申请破产，该公司在 39 个国家的 777 个地点租赁办公空间。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这并不是唯一一家陷入动荡的房地产企业。几天前，在大西洋的另一边，曾经著名的奥地利房地产巨头雷内·本科(René Benko)被逐出了他一手打造的价值230亿欧元（合250亿美元）的房地产帝国西尼亚。其投资组合包括纽约克莱斯勒大厦； <small>K</small> a <small>D</small> e <small>W</small> e，西柏林的一家豪华百货商店；以及伦敦另一家豪华消费殿堂塞尔福里奇百货公司的股份；以及豪华酒店、高端开发项目和其他零售业务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这两个案例并不完全相同。与 WeWork 不同的是，Signa 并未宣布破产，尽管它面临着流动性紧缩，并聘请了著名的德国破产专家阿恩特·盖维茨 (Arndt Geiwitz) 来接管。与诺伊曼先生不同的是，本科先生是一位白手起家的高中辍学生，他的职业生涯始于将家乡因斯布鲁克的阁楼改造成顶层公寓，直到周末被赶下台之前，他一直参与西尼亚的事务。 2012 年因行贿罪被定罪后，他退出了日常运营职责，但继续担任公司顾问委员会成员。他对盖维茨先生的任命表示祝贺，盖维茨先生帮助德国国家航空公司汉莎航空度过了破产危机。 （与此同时，诺伊曼则只能在一旁对 WeWork 的倒闭进行冷嘲热讽，抱怨该公司“未能充分利用当今比以往任何时候都更重要的产品”。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，这两个帝国的兴衰却有相似之处。其一，两者都依赖于高风险的赌注，但在利率上升和房地产市场低迷的世界中，这些赌注都失败了。在建立自己的帝国的过程中，本科先生积累了大量债务，以便在维持丰厚股息的同时购买新资产。这种模式只有在利率较低且优质房产价值持续上涨的情况下才有效。在WeWork的案例中，风险源于一种模式，即对房产进行长期租约，有时长达20年，斥巨资进行时髦的翻新，然后租用空间一次短至一个月。当写字楼市场转向时，该公司被迫支付远远超出其向租户收取的租金的租金，因为有更便宜的替代方案可供选择。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，两个帝国都可能变得更加强大。因斯布鲁克大学的莱昂哈德·多布施 (Leonhard Dobusch) 认为，盖维茨将拆分西格纳庞大的投资组合，出售资产以获取现金并偿还债务。私营企业由数百家控股公司组成，需要进行一些简化。 WeWork 则已获得大多数债权人的支持，将其 30 亿美元的债务转换为股权，使其资产负债表近乎全新。它还将利用破产的机会终止在美国的 60 多项租约，并重新谈判其他租约。诺伊曼和本科可能会离开，但他们创建的公司很可能会持续下去。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:41:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/5g4lhmpmdtni0kh2lvknfluk39j61dlo</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/11/07/the-fall-of-wework-shows-the-deepening-cracks-in-real-estate </item><item><title><![CDATA[Portugal’s prime minister resigns over a corruption scandal]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">欧洲的中<span>左翼</span><small>政党</small>近年来处境艰难，但葡萄牙是个例外。社会党总理安东尼奥·科斯塔自 2015 年以来一直执政，首先领导一个包括极左翼政党在内的联盟，后来领导一个少数派政府。葡萄牙经济是欧洲表现最好的国家之一，预计今年将实现 2% 的稳健增长。在 2022 年的选举中，科斯塔先生出人意料地为他的政党赢得了议会的绝对多数席位。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但11月7日，他的好运戛然而止。他在警方突袭其住所后辞职，这是对锂矿和绿色氢项目腐败丑闻调查的一部分。科斯塔的幕僚长和一名亲密顾问被拘留，里斯本南部港口城市锡尼什的社会党市长以及一家数据中心公司的两名高管也被拘留。检察官宣布，环境和气候部长以及基础设施部长已被列为被告，科斯塔先生也正在接受调查。总理否认有任何违法行为，并表示他“问心无愧”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">腐败调查正在调查政府授予两个大型锂矿项目的合同，葡萄牙试图在欧洲不断增长的电池制造生产链中赢得一席之地。该国声称拥有西欧最大的锂矿石储量，五月份其环境监管机构批准在巴罗佐地区建造一座大型露天矿。另一个矿场位于西班牙边境附近的蒙塔莱格里地区，于 9 月获得批准。两者都因其环境影响而面临当地人的抗议。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但葡萄牙检察官的腐败调查可以追溯到 2019 年，当时一名举报人声称，在授予在锡尼什建造绿色氢能源工厂和相关数据中心的合同时，葡萄牙公司受到偏袒。此后，它已发展到包括锂矿。正在调查的潜在犯罪包括“公职人员主动和被动腐败”和“政治影响力”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">科斯塔表示，无论调查结果如何，他都不会再次竞选总理。原则上，社会党可以组建一个由不同领导人领导的新政府。但葡萄牙总统马塞洛·雷贝洛·德索萨在接受科斯塔的辞职后表示，他已召集该国国务院开始解散议会的程序。新选举的时间表尚未公布。雷贝洛先生表示，他将在 11 月 9 日的演讲中提供更多细节。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在科斯塔先生的领导下，葡萄牙已成为欧洲的成功典范。该国强劲的经济增长以及蓬勃发展的旅游业和科技行业使其从欧洲的一潭死水变成了吸引投资者的磁石，并因其先进的健康和社会福利政策而赢得赞誉。腐败丑闻可能会给这一遗产蒙上阴影（并结束人们对科斯塔先生可能在明年该职位空缺时成为下一任欧洲理事会主席的猜测）。里斯本大学法学教授保罗·奥特罗称，这是自 1976 年该国成为民主国家以来制度信誉最严重的时刻。现任部长，”他告诉葡萄牙报纸<i>Público</i> 。无论谁接替科斯塔先生，都将面临恢复公众对政府信任的艰巨任务。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 20:42:43 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/3da9eoervta20qr9dbqi3ocl50cu94jd</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/07/portugals-prime-minister-resigns-over-a-corruption-scandal </item><item><title><![CDATA[The deadly missile race in the Middle East]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 10 月 31 日从也门飞向<span>以色列</span><small>的弹道导弹</small>创下了多项记录。它们的飞行距离可能比任何其他作为侵略行为发射的弹道导弹都要远，至少跨越了 1,600 公里。他们在内盖夫沙漠上空被以色列的“箭”导弹防御系统拦截。这是“箭”部署23年来首次发射地对地导弹。据两名以色列官员称，这也是有史以来第一次在太空进行战斗拦截。这一事件是射程和精度不断提高的导弹扩散如何改变中东军事格局的一个小例子。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">五十多年来，导弹一直是该地区战争的一部分。苏联飞毛腿导弹是火箭世界的主力，在 1973 年针对以色列的赎罪日战争的最后阶段首次发射。在 20 世纪 80 年代的所谓城市战争中，伊朗和伊拉克发射了大量飞毛腿导弹。据估计，1945 年至 2017 年间，在战斗中发射的 5,000 枚导弹中，90% 是在中东发射的。现在威胁正以两种方式转移。更多的人可以获得更多的导弹。而且导弹本身的质量也在变得更好。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">阅读我们对以色列和哈马斯之间战争的所有报道</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从扩散开始。 20 世纪 50 年代，埃及在纳粹科学家的帮助下开始制造弹道导弹。以色列在法国的帮助下紧随其后。 20世纪60年代到80年代，苏联导弹大量涌入埃及、伊拉克、利比亚、叙利亚等国家。中国向沙特阿拉伯和土耳其供货。朝鲜帮助了伊朗、也门和阿拉伯联合酋长国。随后，美国、英国和法国也相继发射了自己的先进导弹。国王大学的哈桑·埃尔巴蒂米 (Hassan Elbahtimy) 估计，该地区 11 个国家现在拥有射程超过 250 公里的弹道导弹（以抛物线弧线飞行的导弹）或巡航导弹（使用类似飞机的发动机在平坦的轨道上飞行）伦敦学院。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">同样重要的是，国家不再垄断该技术。在过去的20年里，伊朗向加沙的哈马斯、也门的胡塞武装、伊拉克和叙利亚的各种民兵组织，尤其是黎巴嫩的真主党提供了无人机、火箭和导弹以及制造它们的技术。据以色列估计，2007 年哈马斯拥有数百枚火箭弹。 2014 年这一数字跃升至 10,000 枚，然后在 2021 年增加了两倍，达到 30,000 枚。真主党更先进的武器库从 2006 年（与以色列开战的那一年）的约 15,000 枚导弹增加到如今的约 150,000 枚。其中大约 400 枚是远程导弹，可以击中以色列任何地方。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">结果是，武装团体现在构成的常规军事威胁达到了 20 年前只有国家才能做到的程度。美国外交关系委员会的布鲁斯·霍夫曼（Bruce Hoffman）认为，“以色列的两线战争的危险开始呈现出生存的维度”。更大的库存可以实现更大规模、更持久的齐射。在第一次海湾战争中，萨达姆侯赛因领导的伊拉克在短短一个多月的时间里平均每天向以色列发射约一枚飞毛腿。哈马斯虽然装备了较弱的火箭，但从 2014 年战争期间每天发射 192 次的峰值，增加到 2021 年重大冲突第一天的 470 次（不包括小型迫击炮）。仅 10 月 7 日这一天，它就至少发射了 2,200 发子弹。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_MAC363.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，数字并不是主要问题。哈马斯对建筑区的直接打击相对较少。这表明“铁穹”仍能拦截大约 90% 的目标，就像它在之前与加沙的战争中所做的那样。据一位接受<i>《经济学人》</i>采访的以色列国防军 ( <small>IDF</small> ) 高级军官透露，自 10 月 7 日以来，已有 1,400 名以色列人丧生，其中只有 4 人死于火箭弹袭击。以色列的导弹防御系统是世界一流的。其中两人是在冲向防空洞时突发心脏病。问题是导弹正在变得越来越好。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">想想萨达姆的飞毛腿。 “你的系统非常昂贵，操作起来非常复杂，而且非常不准确，”智囊团国际战略研究所的法比安·欣茨（Fabian Hinz）说。这些飞毛腿导弹的圆概率误差 ( <small>CEP</small> ) 超过两公里，这意味着发射的导弹中只有一半预计会落在距弹着点的这一距离内。欣茨表示，这使得它们可以做三件事：在游行中炫耀、恐吓城市或运送核武器。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">现任五角大楼高级官员迈克尔·霍洛维茨 (Michael Horowitz) 和乔治城大学的劳伦·卡恩 (Lauren Kahn) 在 2021 年发表的一篇论文中指出，1990 年，只有 9 个国家拥有“智能”精确制导炸弹，这种炸弹结合使用惯性导航和卫星信号来寻找目标他们的目标。即使是中国、印度等大国以及大多数<small>北约</small>国家也缺乏这种能力。然后这项技术走向了全球：到 2000 年，已有 22 个国家拥有该技术，到 2017 年，已有 56 个国家拥有该技术。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其中包括伊朗。 Shahab-1 导弹是飞毛腿的仿制品，伊朗在 20 世纪 90 年代和 2000 年代初用来打击伊拉克武装分子，其<small>CEP</small>约为半公里。如今，伊朗设计的 Fateh-110 导弹系列被认为具有远低于 35 米的<small>CEP</small> ，在可靠的卫星信号下可能低至 5 米，足以击中大型车辆。它在 2020 年 1 月就证明了这一点，当时它对一名伊朗将军被暗杀进行了报复，袭击了驻伊拉克的美军，并对导弹机库进行了六次直接命中。去年，疑似伊朗无人机和巡航导弹对沙特石油设施发动的袭击也同样击中目标。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “那次罢工产生了巨大的地缘政治影响，”欣茨先生说。此前，大多数想要远距离打击敌人的国家都需要昂贵的空军；非制导导弹在1000公里之外就毫无用处。 “现在，演员们没有空军，或者拥有非常可怕的空军，比如伊朗，却能够打击对手的纵深，”他说。 “这改变了战略计算。” 2019 年和 2020 年的袭击表明，伊朗及其代理人对以色列、美国和其他国家具有严重的常规威慑力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">更大的射程还意味着能够从更广泛的国家攻击以色列。从以色列在黎凡特的家门口发射的短程导弹总是更便宜，因此可以负担得起更大的弹幕或更长的战争所需的大量导弹。但也门仍然是一个有用的发射台。目前尚不清楚到底是胡塞武装还是他们的伊朗支持者发动了 10 月 31 日的袭击。这是上诉的一部分。伊朗革命卫队可以将袭击归咎于胡塞武装分子。如果以色列在也门进行报复，升级和政治影响的风险将低于黎巴嫩或伊拉克战争。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最后，精确度也对导弹防御提出了深刻的挑战。铁穹和其他以色列防御系统的工作原理是计算导弹的航向，只有当导弹降落在人口稠密地区或军事基地等重要地点时才进行拦截。 2006年，真主党的武器库几乎完全没有制导，因此许多火箭弹可以被安全地忽略。但以色列官员表示，在过去十年中，伊朗已成功向黎巴嫩发送了数百枚制导套件，这些制导套件可将常规导弹转变为精确导弹，尽管以色列对叙利亚进行了零星空袭以拦截这些供应。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这意味着，在未来的战争中——以色列官员认为这场战争是不可避免的——更大比例的来袭导弹将拥有特定的预期目标，并且有很好的命中率。因此，以色列将不得不花费更多的拦截弹。每个铁穹拦截器的成本约为 10 万美元。大卫弹弓是一个独立的系统，可以处理更大的火箭，其成本是这个数字的几倍。以色列可能不得不把重点放在总部和空军基地等战略地点，而不是城市。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一种适应方法是通过改进预测火箭可能着陆地点的算法来节省拦截器。另一种方法是利用电子战来干扰导航信号，就像以色列已经在做的那样，这让依赖手机应用程序出行的司机感到困惑。第三是专注于更便宜的拦截手段。以色列对一种名为“铁束”的激光系统进行了多次测试。不过，在这场战争期间，它不会与现有的导弹防御系统集成，而且它也有缺点，例如机械笨重和在阴天条件下的有效性有限。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列还可以呼吁盟友。美国在以色列内盖夫沙漠设有大型X波段雷达，其军舰于10月19日击落了来自也门的密集炮火。来自该弹幕的一枚导弹甚至被沙特阿拉伯拦截，该国与以色列没有外交关系，但通过美国共享雷达。去年六月，以色列表示已加入中东防空联盟（ <small>MEAD</small> ），这是一个由美国主导、包括阿拉伯国家在内的计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “这项技术的成功之处在于，多年来它能够适应来自不同方向的一系列不同威胁，”以色列工程师、“箭”最初开发者之一、前导弹防御系统负责人亚伊尔·拉马蒂 (Yair Ramati) 说道。以色列国防部理事会。 “30多年来，军备竞赛一直在进行，以色列的敌人不断建立他们的武库，而我们一直在发展我们的防御系统。”这场竞赛没有任何放缓的迹象。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 20:39:27 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/m2l2t64g036nrjhnc0nmv75c2pu70edi</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/07/the-deadly-missile-race-in-the-middle-east</item><item><title><![CDATA[Will America pull the plug on Israel’s invasion of Gaza?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>这</span><small>算不上是</small>一种热烈的欢迎，尽管这无疑并不令人意外。美国国务卿安东尼·布林肯(Antony Blinken)过去几天穿梭于中东，这是他自10月7日加沙战争爆发以来第二次进行此类访问。在安曼，约旦同行艾曼·萨法迪告诉布林肯“停止这种疯狂行为”。他在整个地区私下听到的语言甚至更加强硬。他与巴勒斯坦总统马哈茂德·阿巴斯的会晤持续了不到一个小时，最终没有发表联合声明。土耳其的雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安根本懒得会见他。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">布林肯的冷遇表明人们对以色列在加沙的战争越来越愤怒。现在已进入第二个月，它已造成 10,000 多名巴勒斯坦人死亡，并损坏或摧毁了飞地 11% 以上的建筑物。它激怒了阿拉伯世界，激怒了西方国家的首都，并引起了许多世界领导人的谴责。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">阅读我们对以色列和哈马斯之间战争的所有报道</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列将军们仍在谈论发动一场长达一年的长期战役。 11 月 7 日，总理本雅明·内塔尼亚胡 (Binyamin Netanyahu) 告诉美国广播公司新闻<small>(ABC</small> News)，以色列将“无限期”负责加沙的安全。但实际上，以色列官员所说的“合法性之窗”可能要短得多。这个窗口关闭的速度在很大程度上取决于美国，美国向以色列提供军火、外交支持以及价值约 140 亿美元的一揽子援助计划。如果乔·拜登希望结束战争，以色列将很难忽视他。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">到目前为止，他还没有。尽管拜登现在支持“人道主义暂停”以允许更多援助进入加沙，但他拒绝了彻底停火的呼吁。但政府官员在一系列泄密事件中明确表示，他们怀疑以色列在加沙是否有连贯的退出战略。他们抱怨内塔尼亚胡先生几乎不愿意讨论这个话题，并表示他们想现在就将他们的担忧记录在案，以免战争结局糟糕。认为战争有可能陷入泥潭却又支持战争的立场是站不住脚的——尤其是在美国选民同意的情况下。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>《经济学人》</i>和 YouGov 的一项民意调查发现，大多数美国人 (41%) 认为拜登处理战争的方式很糟糕。昆尼皮亚克大学对登记选民的一项调查发现，51% 的独立人士和 66% 18 至 34 岁之间的人不赞成他的政策。他在阿拉伯裔美国选民中的支持率大幅下降，这可能会损害他明年在密歇根州等关键摇摆州的表现。华盛顿的消息人士认为，拜登还需要几周时间才能转向谈论休战，但不要怀疑他会做出这样的转变。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">阿拉伯国家当然希望如此。在哈马斯大屠杀后的几天里，人们对多线战争的担忧已经有所缓解。黎巴嫩什叶派民兵真主党继续每天向以色列发射火箭，但该组织领导人哈桑·纳斯鲁拉在 11 月 3 日的一次讲话中表示，他对全面战争不感兴趣。也门什叶派武装组织胡塞武装向以色列发射了无人机和导弹，但距离太远，无法构成战略威胁。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中东地区的许多独裁者会很高兴看到以色列粉碎哈马斯。但他们也担心战争会动员他们的臣民，其中许多人已经对糟糕的经济状况感到不安。这增加了美国和以色列的压力，美国和以色列已经听到了他们的担忧，而以色列则热衷于维护其最近在阿拉伯世界的外交成果。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">到目前为止，大多数国家都对以色列进行了象征性的谴责。 11月2日，巴林议会下院宣布，巴林将召回驻以色列大使。商会的权力很少；召回大使不是其中之一。两国特使已于几周前回国。议会在民粹主义政治中表现得好像立法者已经下令他们回归。巴林和以色列官员均表示，外交关系保持完好。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">四天后，约旦国王阿卜杜拉宣布，他的空军已向加沙空投了一批医疗援助物资。如果没有征求以色列的批准，约旦不会采取这样的行动，以色列军队后来证实它确实已经批准了。不过，通过在声明中省略这一细节，国王可能会表现得好像他挑战了以色列对加沙的封锁。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，这样的举动在国内并没有赢得多少好感。即使是以色列最亲密的阿拉伯盟友阿拉伯联合酋长国（ <small>UAE</small> ）也变得越来越挑剔（至少在公开场合）。<small>阿联酋</small>总统外交政策顾问安瓦尔·加尔加什 (Anwar Gargash) 在 11 月 4 日的一次会议上表示，美国应该推动停火，“越快越好”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然后是以色列本身。军队士气高涨，以色列人似乎愿意接受比平常多得多的伤亡（迄今为止，已有 34 名以色列士兵阵亡）。但公众对一位更关心政治生存而非战场战略的首相感到愤怒。 11 月 4 日，抗议者聚集在内塔尼亚胡先生的家中，要求他辞职。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">另一个问题是经济。 2006 年长达一个月的黎巴嫩战争造成约 95 亿谢克尔（当时为 20 亿美元）的损失，而 2014 年上一次大规模加沙冲突造成了 70 亿谢克尔的损失。这个可能更贵。以色列央行认为明年政府赤字将攀升至<small>GDP</small>的3%，而2022年盈余为0.6%；一些外部分析师的估计高于 5%。动员 36 万名预备役军人也导致以色列部分经济领域出现工人短缺，尽管其中一些人现已被遣送回国。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列官员希望，战争第一个月的猛烈轰炸现在正在进入一个新阶段。加沙城被<small>以色列国防军</small>包围，地面部队和装甲部队正在接近<small>以色列国防军</small>所说的哈马斯总部所在地以及其核心战士和领导层藏身的地区。如果<small>以色列国防军</small>能够很快摧毁这些设施并杀死大量武装分子，一些官员认为，它将部分完成其削弱哈马斯管理加沙能力的使命。随后，战争将转向更为有限的地面袭击活动。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这可以缓解每次以色列飞机轰炸面包店或难民营时都会加剧的国际压力，并通过允许军队释放一些预备役人员来缓解经济压力。以色列人还认识到，缓解加沙的人道主义危机可以赢得更多时间。 11月6日，<small>阿联酋</small>宣布将与以色列协调，在加沙建立一座拥有150个床位的野战医院。内塔尼亚胡先生现在表示，他愿意“战术性的小停顿，这里一个小时，那里一个小时”，以允许更多援助进入。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，可以说，以色列国际合法性面临的最大挑战是内塔尼亚胡本人。他的政府充满了激进分子。遗产部长阿米猜·埃利亚胡最近建议向加沙投放核弹。监督被占领约旦河西岸的议会委员会新任主席兹维·苏科特 (Zvi Sukkot) 是一位极右翼理论家，因涉嫌极端主义活动而受到以色列辛贝特 (Shin Bet) 的调查。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">当他们在拉马拉会面时，阿巴斯告诉布林肯，控制西岸部分地区的巴勒斯坦权力机构可以在战后返回加沙来管理这片飞地。这样的结果会让以色列军队和美国人都满意。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但阿巴斯先生补充说，这只会在“全面政治解决方案的框架内”发生——换句话说，作为迈向两国解决方案的一步，内塔尼亚胡先生在整个政治生涯中都在反对这一解决方案。如果他继续留任，就不会有关于加沙结局的严肃讨论。美国的耐心将会耗尽，而以色列的回旋余地将会越来越有限。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:45:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/19stthmb3tjmrte1vcd3hlnj7dbs6vak</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/07/will-america-pull-the-plug-on-israels-invasion-of-gaza </item><item><title><![CDATA[Australia and China patch things up]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 11月6日，<span>安东尼</span><small>·阿尔巴尼斯</small>在北京与习近平握手，这是澳大利亚总理七年来首次前往中国会见领导人。在此期间的大部分时间里，两国的经济和政治关系严重破裂。然而，习近平在人民大会堂宣称，中国和澳大利亚已经“走上了改进的正确道路”。阿尔巴内塞先生则表示，澳大利亚支持中国的增长和“与世界的持续接触”。他的访问是在澳大利亚与中国建交50周年之际进行的，双方都希望这象征着关系正常化迈出了重要一步。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">造成破裂的原因有很多，但根本原因是中国想让澳大利亚屈服于其意愿。澳大利亚与其长期盟友美国深化安全合作，此举激怒了澳大利亚统治者，以应对中国对台湾、周边海域及其他地区日益增强的自信。澳大利亚禁止中国电信巨头华为的决定加剧了摩擦。当时的澳大利亚保守党政府对中国“锐利”实力的迹象感到愤怒，包括通过中国驻堪培拉大使馆、澳大利亚大学和大量华人侨民精心策划的干预和监视。随着澳大利亚对中国的态度日益强硬，中国大使馆在 2020 年底向澳大利亚媒体提交了一份充满不满的清单。中国还冻结了两国之间的部长级交往，并对澳大利亚的一些出口产品实施禁运，包括大麦、木材、煤炭、糖、葡萄酒和龙虾。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管中国是澳大利亚最大的市场，但这种惩罚并没有成功。受骗的澳大利亚企业非但没有反抗政府，反而支持了政府。他们中的许多人为他们的产品找到了新的市场。与此同时，澳大利亚向<small>世贸组织提起诉讼，令中国难堪。</small>中国自己的企业也受到了禁运的影响，尽管中国经济因疫情、房地产崩盘和外国投资疲软而开始衰退。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">去年澳大利亚政府的更迭为中国尝试采取更温和的做法提供了机会。预计将恢复定期部长级对话。中国的大部分禁运正在解除，其余的预计很快就会解除。出生于中国的澳大利亚记者成雷于 2020 年在中国因莫须有的间谍罪名被国家暴徒逮捕，现已被释放。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">许多澳大利亚人认为，这直接表明反抗中国的欺凌行为是有回报的。然而，其他人警告说，中国的胁迫本质上是阴险的，这种胁迫不会结束，即使对澳大利亚可能采取不同的形式。成女士获释几天后，澳大利亚政府续签了中国对战略港口达尔文的租约（阿尔巴尼斯先生表示反对，称该租约是“严重的判断错误”）。政府否认这是交换条件。然而，堪培拉澳大利亚战略政策研究所的尤安·格雷厄姆认为政府在处理中国问题上“失去了纪律”。他表示，现在存在着放弃太多的风险。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">指控可能还为时过早。阿尔巴尼斯先生的口头禅是，澳大利亚和中国必须“在可以合作的地方合作，在必须分歧的地方分歧”。到目前为止，这似乎有效。但像一些人那样希望中国将与澳大利亚建立平等关系是错误的。正如堪培拉澳大利亚国立大学的本杰明·赫斯科维奇（Benjamin Herscovitch）指出的那样，中国近几个月的和解举措似乎是为了“让澳大利亚更多地支持自己的目标”。其中包括中国继续获取澳大利亚的稀土和其他矿产资源；澳大利亚支持中国加入 12 国贸易组织<small>CPTPP</small> 。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">美国在这两方面都会不满意，这也是澳大利亚与中国的关系不会轻松的另一个原因。赫斯科维奇先生预测，美国将对澳大利亚与中国深厚且正在恢复的经济关系感到更加不安。澳大利亚的困境——在安全方面依赖美国，而在贸易方面，有如此多的道路通向中国——只会加剧。澳大利亚刚刚通过了一次重大的外交考验。但考虑到中国的胁迫、澳大利亚的抵抗决心以及美国的刺激，关系正常化的时刻可能相当短暂。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><b>阅读我们亚洲专栏作家 Banyan 的更多内容：<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/11/02/narendra-modi-has-shifted-india-from-the-palestinians-to-israel">纳伦德拉·莫迪 (Narendra Modi) 将印度从巴勒斯坦转向以色列</a>（11 月 4 日）<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/10/26/south-korean-politics-is-one-big-row-about-history">韩国政治是一场关于历史的大争论</a>(10月26日)<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/asia/article73544-prod.ece">印巴关系变得更加边缘化和恶化</a>（10月19日）</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:39:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/qbod99l8g1oml​​36nu2hc6oanvd5d5as</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/11/07/australia-and-china-patch-things-up </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lawmaking in Britain is becoming worse]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>当</span>英国<small>公务员</small>第一次了解法律是如何制定时，他们会得到一个棋盘游戏。 “立法？！”由负责起草政府立法的议会法律顾问办公室制定。玩家们一边掷骰子、移动筹码，一边引导白厅和议会的立法。他们翻牌揭示了系统的障碍。 “忘记表示女王的同意。后退2格。” “需要新的计划动议。错过了一个转弯。”第一个将自己的政策变成国家法律的玩家获胜。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As with many family games, much of the procedure that governs Parliament is a product of custom rather than of iron laws.规则是可以改变的。可以切角。这就是现在正在发生的事情。 Parliament&#39;s most vital job is to scrutinise legislation, and it is neglecting it.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This is no rubber-stamp body. 11 月 7 日国王演讲中提出的法案不会在没有反对的情况下获得通过。首相的提问一如既往地喧闹。叛乱分子仍然在深夜投票中羞辱他们的领导人。 But the theatre of confrontation obscures the fact that <small>MP</small> s spend increasingly little time on fine-bore examination of proposed legislation.法律往往会被议会快速通过。一位趾高气扬的高管有时会将审查视为一种不便。这不仅在宪法上是令人反对的。它还具有实际成本。 This is a story of how the machinery of lawmaking can start to fail, almost unnoticed.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Some of the obstacles to thoughtful legislation are structural.政府必须将立法纳入紧迫的时间表。因此，他们习惯性地抵制接受法案修正案。 The Cabinet Office&#39;s legislative handbook warns ministers that changes must be “kept to a minimum” since each will delay progress, note <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/the-united-kingdoms-political-constitution-is-under-severe-strain">Jess Sargeant</a> and Jack Pannell of the Institute for Government, a think-tank, in a recent report.出于同样的原因，政府通常不愿在议会程序开始之前公布法案草案。 Since 1997 an average of only one in eight bills per session has undergone pre-legislative scrutiny, finds Ms Sargeant.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A second problem lies with bill committees, which are meant to hear evidence and undertake line-by-line scrutiny of bills as they make their way through Parliament. Many <small>MP</small> s regard them as a form of drudgery;对拟议法律真正感兴趣的独立思想者不太可能被党鞭挑选。由此产生的争论是党派之争，而且是草率的。按照惯例，主要宪法法案和其他一些法案都在主议院的“全体委员会”中听取。 That allows all <small>MP</small> s to have a say but is bad for close textual scrutiny. Across 177 bills between 2015 and 2021, 73% of them were subject to no oral evidence hearings at all. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC328.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">These long-standing problems have been compounded by other trends.议会制定的立法比以往任何时候都多：法案和法定文书的数量从 1911 年的 760 页增加到 2009 年数据系列结束时的 15,200 多页（也许打印机只是卡住了）。移民和福利的监管制度变得更加复杂。 Brexit landed Westminster with responsibility for dense <small>EU</small> rulebooks.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet the House of Commons is trying to do more in less time. It was in session for 173 days in 1988 but only 147 days in 2021. The average sitting day has shrunk from nine hours and four minutes to seven hours and 37 minutes over the same period, in part due to sensible reforms to make the place more family-friendly.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These shorter hours are also being used differently.众议院花在政府立法上的时间比例从 2005-06 年 41% 的近期峰值下降到 6 月最近一次会议的 20%。紧急问题——部长被立即传唤到议会的程序，几乎总是对当天的头条新闻发表评论——数量激增，从 2007-08 年的 4 个增加到 2021-22 年的 104 个。 The proportion of time spent on Westminster Hall debates, non-legislative sessions introduced in 1999 for <small>MP</small> s to air their pet causes, has grown.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> The fête of the nation</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>MP</small> s&#39; jobs have come to resemble those of “super councillors”, lobbying for their constituencies, rather than legislators with their mind on the national picture. In 2017 the Hansard Society, a research outfit focused on Parliament, polled the public to ask what they thought <small>MP</small> s should do with their time. “制定法律”排在第八位，低于“在下议院代表当地人民的观点”和“参加当地公共会议和活动”。 Between 2010 and 2019, the proportion of <small>MP</small> s representing a constituency in the region of their birth rose from 45% to 52%, including 60% of those newly elected in 2019.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Changes in the media landscape mean that ambitious <small>MP</small> s get less recognition for scrutinising legislation than their predecessors did.直到二十年前，许多大报都有由全职“画廊”记者撰写的“议会的昨天”页面。现在注意力集中在其他地方。 “The incentive structure is misaligned: [ <small>MP</small> s] don&#39;t get any credit or benefit for being a good scrutineer of legislation in the constituency,” says Ruth Fox of the Hansard Society.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Politicians also lack expert support. <small>MP</small> s&#39; staffing budgets are intended to support four full-time assistants, with pay for the most senior capped at £56,312 ($69,000).许多人都很年轻；营业额高。相比之下，一名美国国会议员最多可以雇用 18 名全职工作人员，其中通常包括立法专家。 Members of the House of Lords have no paid personal researchers at all.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This weakening system of scrutiny has been hit by two great shocks. Brexit meant that the British government needed to race against time to rewrite its statute book to get ready for separation from the <small>EU</small> . Covid-19 forced lawmakers to move <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/01/the-covid-19-inquiry-exposes-chaos-in-boris-johnsons-government">even faster</a> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Few dispute that speed was necessary.但英国脱欧公投引入了尖锐而激进的政治，议会的审查不是为选民服务，而是对选民的背叛。人们越来越担心，尤其是上议院的高级成员，危机时期的立法方式已成为一种新的运作方式。公务员表示，covid-19 和英国脱欧改变了部长们对正确起草法案所需时间的预期。 A generation of <small>MP</small> s elected since 2015 knows little different.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “For three years at least ministers seem to have regarded legislation as a series of party political broadcasts,” says Lord Lisvane, formerly the most senior clerk in the House of Commons.由下议院领袖担任主席的内阁部长委员会的任务是在法律草案进入系统之前对其进行审查。 “但如今，这种感觉似乎非常柔和。 Ministers simply aren&#39;t put in the dock about their legislative aspirations,” he says. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC975.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">In recent years a growing number of bills have completed their main Commons stages (the second and third readings) in a single day, almost eliminating the chance for meaningful scrutiny. Some instances of haste were justifiable: to pass covid-19 legislation or to change the royal household after the death of the Queen.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Others were less excusable.莉兹·特拉斯 (Liz Truss) 政府于 2022 年推出的《能源价格法案》支撑了一项 780 亿英镑的全民家庭和企业补贴计划。 Analysts and <small>MP</small> s had proposed much cheaper targeted designs, but the Tory leadership contest that summer crowded out proper policy work. 2020 年 12 月 30 日，实施鲍里斯·约翰逊脱欧贸易协议的法案在一天之内就获得了下议院和上议院的批准； in contrast, ratification of the Maastricht Treaty of 1992 was considered over a period of more than 400 days.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As a result of this haste, the details of laws are being worked out later in the process.特别是，部长们今天要求获得更广泛的权力，以便他们在明天制定政策。二级立法是部长们通过称为“法定文书”的法规制定的法律，并根据议会法案赋予他们的权力制定。传统上，主要立法用于制定政策（例如新的刑事犯罪），次要立法则用于确定其实施（例如设定罚款水平）。 But the boundaries have never been precisely defined and their growing use prompted the House of Lords in 2021 to warn that “government by diktat” was leaching power from Parliament.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “Skeleton bills”, which provide ministers with the framework powers to make a policy, but few clues as to what it will be in practice, were essential in the Brexit years as ministers prepared to take on old <small>EU</small> powers in areas such as fishing and chemicals.但它们的使用已经成为一种模式的一部分。 The Strikes (Minimum Service Levels) Act, a law intended to keep trains and schools running during industrial disputes, was “almost so skeletal that we wonder if bits of the bones were stolen away by wild animals and buried somewhere”, declared Sir Jacob Rees-Mogg, a Tory <small>MP</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Skeleton bills often depend on “Henry VIII” powers, named for the Tudor king&#39;s habit of governing by proclamation.这些条款规定部长们可以通过发布二级立法来修改过去甚至未来的议会法案。 Lord Judge, a former head of the judiciary, declared in a recent speech that they have become so common that “when an act of Parliament omits a Henry VIII clause it is only because someone in the department has failed to press the relevant button on the computer.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Lord Blencathra, a former Tory minister, complains that since Brexit departmental lawyers have been “tacking them on to tiddly little bills” on the basis of “just in case”.目前议会正在审议一项旨在防止公共机构参与抵制英国盟友的法案，其中包含五个单独的亨利八世条款。 《网络安全法》包含20多个条款。单独来看，这些条款都是合理的； collectively, they point to a government seeking shortcuts in the legislative process.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Statutory instruments get even less scrutiny than primary legislation.它们被提交给议会并由立法者委员会进行筛选，但关于它们的辩论可能只持续几分钟或几秒钟。它们不能被修改，只能被否决，这种情况很少见。下议院上次阻止一项法定文书是在 1979 年。上议院上次这样做是在 2015 年。2019 年做出的到 2050 年实现净零排放的法律承诺可能是英国本世纪做出的最昂贵的政策决定。 It was set by a statutory instrument after a 90-minute debate in the Commons and without a vote there, using a mechanism created in the Climate Change Act of 2008.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Under a procedure called “made affirmative”, some statutory instruments become law as soon as a minister signs it;立法者稍后对此进行投票。 <i>The Economist</i> ’s review of parliamentary data shows that this technique has been used far more liberally recently—from 1.8% of the statutory instruments in 1997-2019 to 8.1% in 2019-22. Covid-19 is mostly to blame.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> All this haste is leading to less informed decisions. <small>MP</small> s often pass legislation with no idea as to its costs or benefits.上议院最近的一份报告总结道，许多旨在量化拟议法定文书预期效果的影响评估“似乎是在最后一刻才拼凑在一起，以证明已经做出的决定是合理的”。英国内政部对《非法移民法案》的影响评估显示，将一个人驱逐到卢旺达将花费 169,000 英镑，而且只有阻止成千上万的人才具有成本效益。 But it was not published until June 26th, two months after it had cleared the Commons.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Errors are also rising. 2022-23 年议会会议制定的法定文书中约有 11% 是为了纠正之前的起草错误，是上议院二级立法审查委员会认为人为错误可接受的 5% 阈值的两倍多。 “真正的问题是，这是一种非常方便的做事方式，”委员会成员、前首席大法官 Cwmgiedd 的托马斯勋爵 (Lord Thomas) 说道。 “And when you do something because it&#39;s convenient, that is what really ought to cause you to worry.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Good scrutiny has historically depended on the interplay between the House of Commons, which takes the lead on setting policy, and the unelected House of Lords, which has focused on revising and fine-tuning legislation.上议院的许多议员认为，他们被迫进行下议院逃避的基本审查，而政府对此的关注也较少。传统上，上议院会诱骗政府对有缺陷的立法进行修改。这一过程已经崩溃，导致上议院更频繁地直接投票反对政府。 It has inflicted 370 defeats since December 2019, compared with 268 in 2010-19.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “When you see a larger number of defeats, a significant amount of it is down to greater government intransigence, rather than greater Lords&#39; aggressiveness,” says Professor Meg Russell of University College London.有时他们会成功地迫使事情发生逆转。 But more often the amendments are simply thrown out when a bill returns to the Commons, and have no impact.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Strikingly few Conservative <small>MP</small> s are animated by how the rules of the parliamentary board game have been forgotten.但如果选举迫使他们反对，议会被削弱的代价对他们来说将更加明显。工党官员坚称他们将恢复起草纪律。但工党政府将继承一本充满权力的法规，这些权力可能对部长们来说非常有用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Take the Retained <small>EU</small> Law (Revocation and Reform) Act, passed earlier this year, which creates wide-ranging powers for ministers to rewrite the regulations that predated Brexit. Its neo-Thatcherite architects hoped it would ignite a deregulatory Big Bang. But it might just as easily be used to strengthen trade-union rights or realign policies with those of the <small>EU</small> . “These powers could sit there for decades, being used by governments who may take an entirely different approach,” says Dr Fox of the Hansard Society. “That does not seem to compute at all with ministers.” The rules of the legislative game exist for the benefit of all the players. When they are bent, everyone ends up losing. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:21:15 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/2sc2uaae5v7vsv66hltlaljvk7rvk9tq</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/07/lawmaking-in-britain-is-becoming-worse </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Taiwan ready for war?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/open/s/633ebf6dfc7f5a0012acdc97/e/654a77cd660a120012dc1658/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6IlFQRW5LbjZqIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwcml2YXRlIn0=&sig=R25ztg9QKgJjM8JAh52uVDsnyFJoMCoPPJCDHW3uh_c"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text"> What if China were to invade? For the third episode of <a href="/podcasts/2023/10/24/what-does-taiwan-want">our four-part series</a> , we look at the worst-case scenario for Taiwan—armed conflict with its neighbour.</p><p class="article__body-text"> David Rennie, <i>The Economist</i> ’s Beijing bureau chief, and Alice Su, our senior China correspondent, meet Jack Yao.他是一位在乌克兰做志愿者的台湾咖啡师。现在他正在为可能需要保卫自己祖国的那一天做好准备。但他在台湾年轻人中很少见，因为他认真对待战争威胁。</p><p class="article__body-text"> Our hosts also speak with Jeremy Page, our Asia diplomatic editor, about how an invasion of Taiwan by China could start and end. His <a href="/special-report/2023/11/06/invading-taiwan-would-be-a-logistical-minefield-for-china">special report</a> this week examines China&#39;s armed forces and true military capabilities. Runtime: 50 min</p><p class="article__body-text"> <i>This is a subscriber-only episode. To listen, sign up for <a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus">a free trial</a> of Economist Podcasts+</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <i>If you&#39;re already a subscriber to The Economist, you have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <i>For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit <a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">our FAQs page</a> or watch <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">our video</a> explaining how to link your account.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:59:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/tcr0kmd69vrf7vea7ivcubnth7sl2iq5</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/07/is-taiwan-ready-for-war </item><item><title><![CDATA[Who is Herzi Halevi, the chief of staff of the Israel Defence Forces?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>E</span> <small>VEN BEFORE</small> Hamas, the militant group that runs Gaza, attacked Israel on October 7th, Lieutenant General Herzi Halevi was in a difficult position. In January 2023, when he became chief of general staff of the Israel Defence Forces ( <small>IDF</small> ), the most senior position in Israel&#39;s army, the officer and reserve corps were rent by <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/07/24/a-blow-against-israels-supreme-court-plunges-the-country-into-crisis">divisions</a> over proposed reforms to the country&#39;s <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/01/16/binyamin-netanyahu-rushes-to-take-on-israels-supreme-court">Supreme Court</a> . Some reservists threatened not to serve if the divisive prime minister, Binyamin Netanyahu, and his far-right coalition passed laws weakening the powers of the court. It was one of the army&#39;s most turbulent periods in recent times.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Hamas&#39;s murder of 1,400 Israelis, and capture of more than 200 hostages, eclipsed all that. General Halevi is now commanding an aerial and <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/06/israeli-soldiers-fight-to-reach-hamass-headquarters">ground offensive</a> against the militant group in Gaza, in which more than 10,000 Palestinians have died, according to the enclave&#39;s health ministry. <a href="https://www.economist.com/international/2023/10/28/the-culture-war-over-the-gaza-war">Popular rage</a> at the way Israel is conducting the war has inspired protests in many countries. The <small>UN</small> human-rights office says that Israel may have committed a <a href="https://www.economist.com/is-israel-acting-within-the-laws-of-war-in-gaza">war crime</a> when it struck the <a href="https://www.economist.com/interactive/the-economist-explains/2023/11/02/why-gazas-refugee-camps-vulnerable-jabalia">Jabalia refugee camp</a> . A minister in the Netanyahu government raised the possibility of using nuclear weapons against Gaza (he was suspended for his remarks).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But in General Halevi Israel has a commander with a strong reputation for upholding legal and ethical standards in the conduct of warfare. What is his background and how might it influence how he prosecutes the war? He was born in 1967 in Jerusalem and named after his uncle, who had been killed in action a few months earlier in the <a href="https://www.economist.com/special-report/2017/05/18/how-the-1967-war-changed-the-shape-of-israel">Six Day War</a> . His mother&#39;s family had lived in the city for 14 generations; his paternal grandparents emigrated from Russia. His father&#39;s father was a member of Irgun, a Zionist paramilitary group active in the years leading up to the establishment of Israel.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The general began his regular army service at the age of 18, as a paratrooper, and started training to be an officer two years later. During the early years of his career he skirmished with <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">Hizbullah</a> , a Shia militant group in southern Lebanon that is now exchanging shellfire with Israel, and joined Sayeret Matkal, a special-forces unit that conducts secret operations deep in Arab countries, which he eventually commanded. He next headed a brigade in the occupied <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-war-in-gaza-may-mark-a-watershed-for-the-palestinian-authority">West Bank</a> . In 2009, he led paratroopers in Gaza, in a ground offensive in the towns north of Gaza city where the <small>IDF</small> is fighting once again.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As commander of the Galilee Division from 2011 General Halevi led the <small>IDF</small> on the border with Lebanon. He became head of military intelligence in 2014 and of the Southern Command from 2018, with responsibility for deterring Hamas.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It was after his experience in the <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2008/12/27/strikes-on-gaza">Gaza war</a> of 2008-09, in which hundreds of Palestinian civilians died, that he became an outspoken advocate of the legal and ethical conduct of warfare. In a lecture in 2009 he criticised other Israeli field commanders for failing to set “moral standards” for soldiers fighting in urban areas with many civilians present. “A soldier cannot go into battle with a law book,” he said, but commanders have a responsibility to ensure that moral and legal standards are upheld.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> General Halevi&#39;s views belong to an Israeli military tradition. Yitzhak Sadeh, a leader of the Haganah, a Zionist militia that was the forerunner of the I <small>DF</small> , coined the term “purity of arms” and warned fighters against acts of wanton retribution. But the <small>IDF</small> also had commanders who ignored such principles. As a young commando officer in 1953 <a href="https://www.economist.com/obituary/2014/01/16/ariel-sharon">Ariel Sharon</a> , who was prime minister between 2001 and 2006, led a reprisal in Qibya, a village in the West Bank, then controlled by Jordan, that killed 69 Palestinians. Three decades later an Israeli commission found that Sharon, then defence minister, had not acted to prevent the massacre by Israel&#39;s allies of Palestinians in refugee camps in Lebanon.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> General Halevi is leading the <small>IDF</small> at a time when the ethics of Sadeh are under challenge from the vengeful spirit of Sharon. The <small>IDF</small> has gone deeper into Gaza city than it did in 2009 and 2014 and Hamas is better prepared with more <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/06/israeli-soldiers-fight-to-reach-hamass-headquarters">fortifications</a> and tunnels. With civilian casualties spiralling, intense bombardments and close-quarters fighting under way, the concept of an ethical and legal war is being tested to the brink.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> After the current fighting in Gaza is over, General Halevi&#39;s roles as head of the Southern Command and of the <small>IDF</small> overall will come under scrutiny. Hamas&#39;s surprise attack in October showed an extraordinary lapse in intelligence gathering. General Halevi was the first senior official to accept responsibility, saying on October 12th that “the I <small>DF</small> is responsible for the security of the state and its citizens” and that on the morning of the attack “we failed”. People close to him believe that he intends to resign in the not-too-distant future. But first he has his last war to fight. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:07:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/1jdcoju7j0stmh1qevmdkrhm2moohfhl</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/11/07/who-is-herzi-halevi-the-chief-of-staff-of-the-israel-defence-forces </item><item><title><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s political constitution is under severe strain]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>P</span> <small>OLITICAL INSTABILITY</small> and constitutional uncertainty have framed the past eight years of British politics. Parliament, government and the courts were the scenes of seemingly endless battles over Brexit. A wave of scandals over the conduct of individual <small>MP</small> s and law-breaking at the top of government have eroded public trust in politicians and political institutions. A year of three prime ministers—2022—damaged the country&#39;s reputation as a stable democracy. Big questions hang over the future of the United Kingdom, with the continuing absence of a functioning government in Northern Ireland and the Scottish government&#39;s unceasing efforts to secure independence. The boundaries of the constitution have been tested to—and sometimes beyond—their limits.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The United Kingdom is unusual in having no single written constitutional document that can be enforced by the courts. Instead it has a political constitution, which relies heavily on norms and conventions. When challenges arise, it rests on a shared understanding of the rules and the principal actors being willing, for the most part, to abide by them—the “good chaps” theory of government. When actors step out of line, or even contemplate doing so, the system of political checks and balances—involving <small>MP</small> s, members of the House of Lords, ministers, civil servants, the devolved institutions, the media and ultimately the public—is meant to ensure that they are either unable to or are punished for their behaviour.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Over the past eight years, however, politicians have been increasingly willing to test the boundaries of the constitution. The convention that the <small>UK</small> Parliament will not normally pass legislation on matters devolved to Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland without the consent of their respective legislatures—a convention which had held up for decades—was set aside as the government in Westminster sought to implement Brexit. Disputes with the <small>EU</small> over the terms of exit also led to the government twice introducing legislation that, if passed, would have broken international law by overriding elements of the Northern Ireland protocol, a part of the Brexit deal that, in effect, drew a border in the Irish Sea. And Boris Johnson&#39;s failed attempt to prorogue Parliament—force it into recess—in order to stymie opposition to his government&#39;s Brexit deal, showed a willingness to shut down democratic debate in a way that had once been unthinkable.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Politicians are increasingly willing to set aside key constitutional principles for the purpose of achieving specific policy aims. In most countries the constitution is a form of higher law, sitting above the cut and thrust of day-to-day politics. In Britain the two have become increasingly intertwined, with leading politicians seeking to interpret the constitution in a way that suits their agenda. Consider the Scottish National Party&#39;s insistence that securing a majority of Scottish seats in a <small>UK</small> general election would hand it a mandate for independence, or the claims of Mr Johnson and his allies that his victory in the general election of 2019—his “personal” mandate—made removing him from the Conservative leadership an affront to democracy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such bold constitutional claims demand close, authoritative scrutiny. Unfortunately, the British system has failed to provide an independent source of challenge. A recent <a href="https://www.instituteforgovernment.org.uk/constitution-review">review of the constitution</a> by the Institute for Government, where we work, and the Bennett Institute for Public Policy, concludes that there is a pressing need for enhanced checks on power to shore up our political constitution.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This could be achieved in a number of ways. One would be to set up a powerful cross-party committee to provide an authoritative view on the constitution, separate from the government of the day. This body could remedy the paucity of information and analysis available to parliamentarians, strengthening their ability to fulfil their constitutional-safeguarding role.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Legislation that affects the constitution should, moreover, be put into a category of its own. There is currently little meaningful distinction in the <small>UK</small> between major constitutional legislation such as the Human Rights Act and minor laws such as the Wild Animals in Circuses Act. As a result, lawmakers pay little additional care or attention to bills that amend the foundations of our political system, which can easily be rushed through Parliament. Creating a new category of constitutional acts could help strengthen the processes around constitutional change, while also underlining the importance of laws on constitutionally weighty matters such as devolution.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> More can also be done to help ministers understand and undertake their obligations in relation to the constitution. Establishing a new centre for constitutional expertise in government could ensure they receive high-quality advice on the most complex issues. Creating mechanisms through which officials could raise concerns about constitutional propriety would help ensure that ministers were held accountable if they chose to deviate from established constitutional practice. Clearer guidance on the unwritten rules governing political institutions and a simple list of high-level constitutional principles—akin to the Nolan principles on standards in public life, drawn up under John Major&#39;s government in the 1990s—could provide a common basis on which to judge such decisions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The past decade has underlined the need to strengthen the guardrails of Britain&#39;s political constitution. And calls for more radical reform will grow louder if the constitutional instability of recent years is allowed to continue. The British constitution is often described as a product of evolution. It urgently needs to evolve once again. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Jess Sargeant led the Institute for Government&#39;s review of the <small>UK</small> constitution and is an associate director at the think-tank. Hannah White is its director.</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>This article is part of a series on the British political system, examining the forces shaping the country&#39;s future. Read our guest commentaries on <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/think-twice-before-shaking-up-the-house-of-lords-says-its-speaker">House of Lords reform</a> and <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/ed-balls-and-dan-turner-on-the-long-shadow-cast-by-political-centralisation">devolution</a> .</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:52:53 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/0dpk1qn90qthbahfjncqpkkhnqmqjki7</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/the-united-kingdoms-political-constitution-is-under-severe-strain </item><item><title><![CDATA[Think twice before shaking up the House of Lords, says its speaker]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>T IS THE</small> peculiar fate of the House of Lords, the upper house of the Parliament of the United Kingdom, to be rarely in the headlines except when there are calls for its reform or abolition. Now is one of those times.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In my non-political role as Lord Speaker, which includes chairing the chamber&#39;s daily business, it is not for me to promote a favoured blueprint for a future upper house. However, it is my duty to ensure that any debate is conducted with proper understanding both of the work that the Lords performs and the pros and cons of current arrangements.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> We live in a democratic system. It is easy to assume that this simple fact renders an unelected House of Lords “indefensible”, as asserted in a recent report recommending its replacement with an Assembly of the Nations and Regions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> However, of the 78 second chambers globally, just 20 are wholly directly elected. Many of these—not least the United States Senate—are the subject of domestic controversy. Others have a mix of direct or indirect election and appointment, with 15 wholly appointed.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The composition of the House of Lords is indeed unique: a mixture of lifetime appointees, hereditary peers and Church of England bishops. But this does not in itself make it anachronistic or unacceptable. More important is the quality of its work and the impact this has on the governance of our nation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In his recent book, “How Westminster Works…and Why it Doesn&#39;t”, Ian Dunt described the Lords as being “one of the only aspects of our constitutional arrangements that actually works”, pointing to its record of diligence, expertise, independence and consensus.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> During the passage of legislation through Parliament, it is in the Lords that a bill receives detailed line-by-line scrutiny. With no guillotine on debate and no restrictions on which amendments can be debated, unlike in the House of Commons, the lower chamber, discussions continue for as long as it takes. With no overall party majority, ministers must proceed by persuasion rather than force of numbers, often seeking support from the 25% of peers who have no political affiliation. Without the need to secure re-election, peers can focus on the substance of issues, rather than chasing headlines or indulging in partisan point-scoring.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Government defeats occur more frequently in the Lords than in the Commons—around 100 in a typical session. But when they are overturned by <small>MP</small> s, peers most often back down, accepting that the elected Commons must have the final say.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> More significant are the 1,000-plus amendments passed in the Lords annually with government backing. These often represent ministers revising plans in response to concerns raised by peers. University College London&#39;s Constitution Unit estimated that 55% of changes to legislation made during passage through Parliament occur this way.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> However awkward this may be for ministers, many acknowledge that it helps highlight difficulties and prevent unintended consequences. This is the case, in no small part, because of the expertise and experience on offer in the second chamber.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The appointments system means that the Lords&#39; red benches are home to eminent figures from all corners of public life: scientists, doctors, diplomats and judges; business leaders and trade unionists; campaigners for civil liberties and disability rights; environmentalists, academics and engineers. Their presence reflects the fact that the life of the nation resides not only in political parties, but is expressed through organisations of many kinds. It makes the second chamber a forum for the discourse of civil society.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That expertise is to the fore in Lords committees, whose reports are recognised for their astute analysis of crucial long-term issues. For example, as long ago as 2021 the Economic Affairs Committee was raising the alarm over looming inflation. And critical reports on the <small>HS</small> 2 project dating back as far as 2015 warned of the very outcome which we have just seen: the scrapping of the high-speed-rail project&#39;s northern leg.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Advocates of an elected House of Lords must explain whether it would deliver similar levels of expertise and independence. Would former judges, generals and secretaries of state stand for election? If not, would their contribution be missed?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Would an elected second chamber accept the primacy of the Commons, and if not how would disputes be resolved? If both houses were elected on the same voting system and timetable, how could the second chamber avoid being a redundant carbon copy of the first? If election systems were different, how would this affect perceptions of legitimacy?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Anyone doubting the importance of this final point need only consider what would have happened in 2019 if the large Commons majority to “get Brexit done” produced by Britain&#39;s first-past-the-post voting system had been confronted by a proportionally elected second chamber where most members belonged to parties promising a second referendum.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> I am not arguing that the Lords as currently constituted is perfect. Reform is needed. I have myself raised questions over the balance between independent recommendations of crossbench (non-party-political) peers by the Lords Appointments Commission and prime ministerial nominations. Baroness Stowell of Beeston, a Conservative former Leader of the House, has proposed barring the award of peerages in “resignation honours lists” drawn up by outgoing prime ministers. There are proposals within the Lords to reduce the number of peers and to end by-elections for hereditary peerages.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These follow the tradition of incremental reforms which have improved the Lords, such as the creation of life peerages, the removal of most hereditary peerages and the introduction of retirement. More radical plans—under Harold Wilson in the 1960s, Tony Blair in the 1990s and the Conservative-Liberal Democrat coalition government in 2012—stalled because they had no answer to the questions listed here.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Edmund Burke famously said: “A state without the means of some change is without the means of its conservation.” But when reform is being considered, my watchword is: “First seek to understand.” Understand the work of the Lords and understand the potential consequences of radical change. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Lord McFall of Alcluith is Lord Speaker of the House of Lords.</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>This article is part of a series on the British political system, examining the forces shaping the country&#39;s future. Read our guest commentaries on the <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/the-united-kingdoms-political-constitution-is-under-severe-strain">political constitution</a> and <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/ed-balls-and-dan-turner-on-the-long-shadow-cast-by-political-centralisation">devolution</a> .</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:48:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ktl4h30ur4odr8bm9ti75q0erhst52cu</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/think-twice-before-shaking-up-the-house-of-lords-says-its-speaker </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ed Balls and Dan Turner on the long shadow cast by political centralisation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>F</span> <small>IFTY YEARS</small> ago the world economy reeled from a quadrupling of oil prices and the collapse of the Bretton Woods system of fixed exchange rates.英国对 20 世纪 70 年代动荡的反应在两个方面与其他发达国家不同。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The embrace of free markets, high interest rates and a soaring exchange rate by Margaret Thatcher&#39;s Conservative government meant that large parts of the UK outside London deindustrialised at the fastest rate in western Europe. A paper we co-wrote with Anna Stansbury of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and published earlier this year found that only the experience of eastern Europe during its post-communist transition is comparable to the economic shift that gripped Britain&#39;s regions in the 1980s.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The counterpart to the rapid decline of the north and Midlands of England, Scotland and Wales was the ascent of London and the south-east.英国的这个角落在 20 世纪 70 年代末就已经是欧洲知识密集型服务业的领跑者，也是世界上最适合起飞的地区之一。 As a result, regional economic inequality has grown faster in the <small>UK</small> since then than in any other large member of the <small>OECD</small> club of rich and middle-income countries. The gap between London and the south-east and the rest of the country is now greater than that between western and eastern Germany or the north and south of Italy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But there is a second, less well known part to the <small>UK</small> ’s story.随着中央政府退出其指导经济的角色，它开始将其角色集中在英国政治中。 Unlike in most other countries, economic decentralisation was not married to political decentralisation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Ronald Reagan, America&#39;s president in the 1980s, moved power from Washington, <small>DC</small> to the state capitols.他的法国总统弗朗索瓦·密特朗从巴黎到其他地区也做了同样的事情。相比之下，在英国，撒切尔夫人废除了可以为其左翼竞争对手提供基础的大城市政府，并大幅削减了地区政策支出。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This centralisation of governance in the 1980s has left British policymakers struggling to find either the political energy or the policy levers to counter this rising regional inequality. Politics over the past decade has responded: with a rise in separatism in the non-English nations, and a “geography of discontent”—places facing relative economic decline—large enough to swing the referendum on <small>EU</small> membership in 2016.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Drawing on close to a hundred interviews, including with three former prime ministers and six former chancellors of the exchequer, our new paper, “Why hasn&#39;t <small>UK</small> regional policy worked?”, identifies a broad consensus on how the country has found itself in its current mess.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The centralising politics of the 1980s cast a long shadow.地方政府也被掏空，并与注重交付的新工党政府争夺合法性。 National spending on transport and innovation remained skewed to “safer bets” in the south-east.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> With Whitehall lacking the confidence to release money and powers to the English regions, we instead saw a succession of short-lived regional initiatives, each uprooted before it had time to bed in: development corporations in the 1990s; 2000 年代的区域发展机构； 2010 年代的地方经济伙伴关系。 All the policymakers we spoke to lamented this policy churn and lack of consistency.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Sustained backing from senior politicians and cross-party support are essential to creating lasting reform. They helped ensure that the national minimum wage, Bank of England independence and increased funding for the National Health Service have all moved from being hotly contested to being subjects of broad political consensus in recent decades.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Both ingredients have been absent when it comes to regional policy. Since 1979, when Thatcher took office, prime ministers and their chancellors have never been fully unified in their view of what is needed to support England&#39;s regions and empower the <small>UK</small> ’s other nations. Instead, “levelling up” has too often reverted to centrally administered pots of cash, allocated by national civil servants, and responding to party-political need rather than economic necessity.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The good news is that this may be changing.自2000年代末以来，从工党领导层开始并由保守党加速，一种新的改革方法悄然改变了英国地方政府：地方政府和中央政府之间的联盟进行交易，通过分散支出和权力来推动地方改革。 Powerful “metro mayors” in Greater Manchester and the West Midlands now command the same credibility as the devolved governments in Cardiff and Edinburgh, having built up their power bases incrementally and by consensus.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Difficult decisions remain on spending and taxation, as well as on mandating reform where local politics cannot deliver. Devolution in the <small>UK</small> —an unusually densely populated country with wide income disparities between places—is necessarily difficult.将征税工作转移给地方政府可能会加剧不平等。 But our interviewees are cautiously optimistic that the country may have stumbled upon a formula that works: high-status political jobs in the English regions and non-English nations, finally creating the conditions for a virtuous circle of decentralisation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As political parties gear up for a general election, they should heed the conclusion of the leaders we spoke to across all major parties: now is the time for political bravery, to broker a cross-party, long-term consensus on the future of the nations and regions of the <small>UK</small> .这将意味着承担风险并尝试不同的治理国家的方式。但如果不做出改变，就意味着过去50年的惨淡记录将继续下去。 Britain can do better than that. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Ed Balls is a former British cabinet minister. Dan Turner is policy adviser to the South Yorkshire Mayor. The papers and interviews referenced in this article can be found <a href="https://sites.harvard.edu/uk-regional-growth/">here</a> .</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>This article is part of a series on the British political system, examining the forces shaping the country&#39;s future. Read our guest commentaries on the <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/the-united-kingdoms-political-constitution-is-under-severe-strain">political constitution</a> and <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/think-twice-before-shaking-up-the-house-of-lords-says-its-speaker">House of Lords reform</a> .</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/a244f1qnumgoe7d26kc9j12q1f227vsv</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/07/ed-balls-and-dan-turner-on-the-long-shadow-cast-by-political-centralisation</item></channel></rss>