<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 15 日星期三 21:36:11 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court’s code of conduct is a good first step]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>50 年来，</small><span>美国</span>大约 2,000 名联邦法官中除了 9 名外，其他所有法官都受到行为准则的约束，该准则为法学家在法官席内外的行为制定了道德准则。 11 月 13 日，例外人士——最高法院的法官——宣布他们决定加入下级法院同行的行列。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">新规则并非凭空而来。 <i>ProPublica</i>和其他出版物的调查报告揭露了几位法官的道德失误，要求法院整顿其行为的呼声随之而来。这些文章的主要目标克拉伦斯·托马斯（Clarence Thomas）法官未能宣布哈伦·克劳（Harlan Crow）数十年的豪华旅行是由保守派事业的慷慨捐助者承担的。克劳先生还购买了托马斯法官在佐治亚州拥有的一套房屋，并为他的侄孙的私立学校支付了学费。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">参议院委员会上个月发现，托马斯法官的另一位朋友显然免除了为法官普雷沃斯特马拉松大巴（他称之为“陆地游艇”）提供的 267,230 美元贷款中的“很大一部分”。这也没有宣布。尽管他的妻子弗吉尼亚游说唐纳德·特朗普总统的幕僚长帮助推翻 2020 年选举结果，但托马斯法官选择不回避质疑选举结果以及涉及特朗普在 2021 年 1 月 6 日国会大厦骚乱中所扮演角色的案件。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">没有提及任何这些（或者塞缪尔·阿利托法官去阿拉斯加钓鱼的旅行，由一位右翼亿万富翁支付，他将生意带到法庭上，或者任何其他同事的明显冲突），法官们都签署了一项协议。行为守则。法院写道，该文件“实质上源自”适用于其他联邦法官的准则。法官应“维护司法机关的廉正和独立”并“避免不当行为和看似不当的行为”。他们将“公平、公正和勤勉地履行职责”，并且只能进行适当的“法外活动”。大法官“应该避免政治活动”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在该准则附带的五页评论中，法院承认，一些准则是“措辞宽泛的指导行为的一般原则”，而不是“具体规则”，并要求法官行使“判断”和“自由裁量权”。该文件还指出，由于最高法院是一个“独特的机构设置”，现有的法规不能不经过调整就被采用。例如，法官必须回避涉及经济利益或“个人偏见”的案件。但与容易被替换的法官不同的是，法官没有这样的替代者，并且只要有可能就有“出庭的责任”。该守则称，“即使一名法官不参与某一特定案件，也可能会造成很大损失。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">另一项修订可能是为了避免指责那些享受富有捐助者慷慨资助的法官。尽管其他联邦法官的守则禁止他们“传达”某人“处于影响法官的特殊地位”的印象，但最高法院的规则将这一短语限定为“故意”。只要法官没有意识到他的行为引起了人们的注意（例如，通过制造他受到意识形态捐助者的影响的印象），他或她就仍然遵守新的守则。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">还有一个更大的问题：除了法官本人之外，没有人可以决定何时违反准则或如何处理违规行为。相比之下，国会悬而未决的改革措施将允许公民抱怨法官的无赖行为，并让下级法院法官小组审查他们的主张。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，法官们的举动是朝着正确方向迈出的一步，并表明了对公众看法的一些反应，即第一街并非一切顺利。该准则以令人鼓舞的语气结束，如果法官希望检查和效仿“其他联邦和州法院的最佳实践”，这可能为进一步的自我完善铺平道路。但在那之前，美国最高法官将不得不密切关注自己。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:09:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b0lb6p4nq7tr55nq4k2u52lk88q7u2c7</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/11/15/the-supreme-courts-code-of-conduct-is-a-good-first-step</item><item><title><![CDATA[German judges toss a spanner into the government’s spending plans]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>敲打</span><small>指</small>关节很痛。当最高法院用木槌宣判时，伤害就更大了。对于德国执政联盟来说，联邦宪法法院 11 月 15 日发布的一项判决追溯性地阻止了最初专门用于 covid-19 的未动用资金转移到其他目的，这既是政治尴尬，也是预算噩梦。更微妙的是，这项裁决也是对整个德国的谴责，表明该国痴迷于对政府支出实施“债务刹车”是如何导致各种愚蠢行为的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">涉及的金额高达 600 亿欧元（650 亿美元）。德国前任政府于 2021 年初在常规预算之外借入这笔资金，用于支付应对新冠紧急情况的预期额外支出。由于德国宪法规定了对预算赤字的限制，因此需要特殊的豁免。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但到 2021 年底新当选的“红绿灯”联盟上任时，新冠紧急情况已经结束。因此，前财政部长、现任财政大臣奥拉夫·肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）将这笔钱转入另一个预算外盒子，即气候与转型基金（ <small>KTF</small> ），旨在支付与雄心勃勃的气候变化政策相关的成本。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种转变不仅意味着政府可以在不打扰纳税人的情况下增加支出。它有助于弥合与社会民主党总理的两位联盟伙伴的分歧。对于绿党来说，这意味着有更多的现金来支付他们自己的议程，包括鼓励采用节能热泵的巨额补贴。对于自由派自由民主党（ <small>FDP</small> ）来说，这意味着他们可以恪守对选民的主要承诺，即维护财政廉洁。财政部长兼<small>自民党</small>领袖克里斯蒂安·林德纳 (Christian Lindner) 一再坚称，在他的领导下，政府永远不会挑战债务制动。理论上，除紧急情况外，它将“结构性”预算赤字限制在<small>GDP</small>的 0.35%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">毫不奇怪，执政 16 年后下台的基督教民主党 ( <small>CDU</small> ) 提起诉讼，质疑将“紧急”资金从一个用途转移到另一个用途。政府的辩护——新冠危机间接导致了持续的经济紧急状态——得到了德国法院的一些同情。去年11月，当德国人普遍担心俄罗斯入侵乌克兰后将出现能源短缺时，一项临时裁决允许政府转移600亿欧元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">联盟似乎将这一缓刑视为支出的许可。 <small>KTF</small>作为一个整体，已在未来三年内投入约 2120 亿欧元用于一系列目的，从建设市政级供暖系统，到建立昂贵的氢电网，到升级磨损的国家铁路网络，再到抽水高达 200 亿欧元进军德国芯片制造业。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">法院的裁决不仅危及其中一些项目。它对使用各种“特殊”资金规避债务规则的行为提出了质疑。德国 16 个州中的许多州都与联邦政府一样富有想象力，除其他手段外，联邦政府还设立了 2000 亿欧元的基金，以使工业免受高能源成本的影响（实际上只花费了其中的一小部分）。用于补充国防预算的 1000 亿欧元特别基金在法律上是安全的，因为宪法经过了修改以允许这样做。但这需要议会三分之二的投票，这在其他情况下并不容易。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该判决的直接影响是，肖尔茨政府冻结了<small>KFT</small>的支出，直至另行通知。对于联盟来说，这是一个关键时刻，距离最终确定来年预算还有几天。一旦眼前的障碍过去，德国就需要讨论其过于严格的政府财政规则。法院裁决后，著名经济学家延斯·苏德库姆 (Jens Südekum) 在推特上写道：“债务减免正统观念取得了法律上的胜利。” “但今天的教训可能是，目前没有办法绕过债务制动的根本性改革。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:19:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b4ianl9s0402apa9945rb33lotfuia4r</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/15/german-judges-toss-a-spanner-into-the-governments-spending-plans </item><item><title><![CDATA[The battle of northern Gaza is almost over]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">六周<small>前</small>，<span>一座</span>拥有近百万人口的<small>城市</small>现在已成为空壳。 11 月 14 日，当<i>《经济学人》</i>受邀加入以色列军事补给车队前往加沙北部一度拥挤的沙蒂难民营时，里面的 9 万名居民无人在场。营地中许多密集的公寓楼已被摧毁；其他人则严重受损。以色列国防军（ <small>IDF</small> ）的装甲纵队撕毁了道路。电力、水和污水处理基础设施已不复存在。加沙市大部分地区和边远城镇的情况类似。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">经过六周的战争和三周的地面战斗，以色列现在有效控制了加沙干河以北的地区，这是一条将45公里长的地带一分为二的河床。这次破坏预示着以色列对哈马斯战争的一个阶段的结束，这场战争于 10 月 7 日开始，此前巴勒斯坦伊斯兰组织进行了一场大屠杀，最终导致约 1,400 名以色列人被杀或绑架。以色列数周的猛烈轰炸以及 10 月 27 日开始的地面攻势已导致加沙超过 11,000 名巴勒斯坦人死亡。他们实际上还推翻了哈马斯的权力，至少在飞地北部是这样：这个自 2007 年以来控制加沙的组织已经四分五裂，摇摇欲坠。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">阅读我们对以色列和哈马斯之间战争的所有报道。</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">所有这些都提出了两个重要问题。首先也是最紧迫的是如何缓解加沙南部的人道主义灾难。该领土 220 万人口现在几乎全部居住在南部。以色列的全面围困以及加沙与埃及边境的援助物资匮乏，导致加沙人民极度缺乏食物和水。燃料短缺使医院和援助机构陷入瘫痪。冬天已经到来，寒冷的气温和雨水只会加剧人们的痛苦。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其次是战场上接下来发生的事情。逃往加沙南部的不仅仅是平民：一些哈马斯武装分子无疑也做了同样的事情。以色列尚未找到该组织在加沙的领导人叶海亚·辛瓦尔(Yahya Sinwar)或其军事首领穆罕默德·德伊夫(Muhammad Deif)，据信两人都藏身于飞地下方迷宫般的隧道中。以色列军队将在未来几周内炸毁这些隧道的入口，并在北部搜寻武器和武装分子。不过，到了某个时候，以色列将不得不将注意力转向南部。它在那里能够做多少事情将取决于国内政治和外交压力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最近几天，人们的注意力集中在加沙最大的希法医院和其他此类设施上。以色列称哈马斯在希法地下设有地下总部。它还认为 239 名人质中的一些人藏在那里，至少是暂时的。 11月15日，以色列军队在包围医院六天后进入医院大院。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_MAM903.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">截至<i>《经济学人》</i>付印时，情况仍在发展中，但初步报告显示，<small>以色列国防军</small>既没有找到哈马斯领导人，也没有找到任何人质。一直在医院避难的大约六万名巴勒斯坦人也消失了。当以色列军队进入时，只剩下约 1,500 人，其中包括医务人员、病人和流离失所者。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">大多数人逃往南方——其他人也一样。北部曾经居住着加沙一半以上的人口，现在却成了一片荒芜的荒地。据报道，驻扎在沙蒂的以色列军队只与小群平民发生过几次冲突。目前还没有准确的数字表明仍有多少人聚集在医院和救援中心周围，但以色列和外国消息来源一致认为，人数有数万人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但过去一个月，加沙南部的人口增加了一倍，即使没有几乎完全封锁该飞地，这一增长也会给基本服务带来压力。估计有 150 万人流离失所，其中大部分来自北方，但也有来自南方的人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自 10 月 21 日以色列同意通过埃及运送援助物资以来，约有 1,200 辆卡车通过拉法过境点运送食品、药品和其他必需品（战前，每天约有 500 辆卡车进入加沙）。南方的许多人不吃饭，努力寻找干净的水。由于以色列几乎完全禁止燃料运输，一些巴勒斯坦人开始焚烧家具作为做饭的柴火。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">燃料缺乏导致基本服务瘫痪。近三分之二的医疗机构已经停止工作。污水泵站已离线。国际救援委员会表示，霍乱和伤寒等水传播疾病将不可避免地开始传播。 11月14日，<small>联合国</small>表示将很快停止提供援助；它甚至缺乏足够的燃料来操作叉车。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第二天，一艘载有 23,000 升柴油的油轮从埃及进入加沙，这是以色列自战争开始以来允许的第一批此类货物。这总比什么都没有好——但也只是勉强。以色列的限制意味着这些燃料只能由<small>联合国</small>使用，不能由医院使用，因为医院的发电机已经耗尽。<small>联合国</small>驻加沙援助机构主任汤姆·怀特 (Tom White) 表示，这些物资只能满足该组织日常需求的 9%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">冬季大雨也来临了。 11月14日的一场倾盆大雨中，一些巴勒斯坦人发现他们的帐篷倒塌了；其他人则睡在泥里。加沙 12 月和 1 月确实寒冷潮湿，夜间气温降至 8°C。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">战争开始前，进入加沙的卡车约有三分之二经过凯雷姆沙洛姆（Kerem Shalom），这是与以色列接壤的过境点。自10月7日起一直关闭。在哈马斯的暴行之后，以色列几乎没有人支持帮助加沙人，本雅明·内塔尼亚胡政府中的极右翼政党也坚决反对。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，物资必须绕道埃及。他们抵达北西奈省。然后，他们被卡车运到以色列边境口岸，接受武器检查，然后返回拉法。绕道增加了 100 公里的路程，而且拉法每天只开放几个小时。以色列非政府组织 Gisha 的主任塔尼亚·哈里 (Tania Hari) 表示：“救援组织发现在埃及开展行动非常困难，这就是为什么他们通常在以色列开展行动，因为那里的距离更短，<small>程序</small>也更高效。”游说以增加进入加沙的机会。 “凯雷姆·沙洛姆必须重新开放，加沙人才能生存。”</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">下一步</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">是否这样做对以色列来说是一个问题，因为它决定如何继续战争。在坦克、嗅探犬和爆破队的陪同下，士兵们花了两个多星期的时间挨家挨户搜寻武器和通往哈马斯地道的竖井。一名官员解释了有条不紊的程序。可疑建筑物成为坦克或空袭的目标。然后，士兵们与警犬和工兵一起进行检查。他们不被允许冒险进入隧道。更多的竖井不断被发现。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">房屋内遗留的武器和爆炸物表明哈马斯武装分子匆忙离开。目前还不清楚他们去了哪里。有些人可能试图在剩下的隧道中生存。其他人可能已经逃往南方或撤退到城市的正中心。 “我们每天要处理大约 90 到 100 座建筑物，”营指挥官奥兹中尉说。数十个营在加沙城及其周边地区执行类似的任务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列将军们知道，他们无法像在北部那样在加沙南部采取同样凶猛的行动。相反，他们正在计划一场“更具机动性”的攻势。但任何行动都可能会阻碍救援工作，并引起国际社会的强烈抗议，而国际社会的抗议已经越来越强烈。本月在沙特阿拉伯举行的一次峰会上，阿拉伯和穆斯林国家要求结束战斗。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一些西方领导人已开始回应这一要求。法国总统马克龙在11月10日接受<small>BBC</small>采访时呼吁停火。乔·拜登仍然拒绝谈论永久休战，而他的声音迄今为止是最重要的。但他面临着民主党进步派推动停火的巨大压力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一场不那么残酷的战争可以缓解这种压力。在战争的头几周内，巴勒斯坦死亡人数每天激增数百人。不过，最近几天，伤亡率明显下降，北部地区几乎已无一人幸存。这可以为以色列赢得更多时间来继续其地面战役。大幅扩大的人道主义努力也将如此。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列还必须考虑加沙接下来会发生什么，而内塔尼亚胡先生迄今为止拒绝这样做。目前，哈马斯已经失去了统治能力。它也可能失去了曾经统治的人民的支持。 “（加沙人）指责哈马斯给他们带来了这场悲剧，”一名陪同部队进入加沙地带的以色列情报官员说。人们期望<small>以色列国防军</small>会这么说——但听起来确实如此。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">甚至在战前，就很难衡量加沙的民意：哈马斯是一个专制的一党国家，上一次巴勒斯坦议会选举是在 2006 年。现在更难了。不过，轶事证据表明，加沙的许多人对其表面上的统治者感到愤怒。最近几天，许多巴勒斯坦人在加沙南部接到电话，描述了针对哈马斯的愤怒场面。警察在试图插队领取食物和水时遭到咒骂和殴打。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这并不是说绝望的加沙人对以色列感到任何温暖。哈马斯诞生于加沙；其最有影响力的领导人辛瓦尔先生和德伊夫先生在汗尤尼斯附近的难民营长大，这座城市现在收容着无数从北部流离失所的加沙人。以色列可能对该组织造成了致命打击。但长期的悲惨流离失所将确保其他事物取代它。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:58:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/4mt9sjhlgfiovp4kuvbsqoi6oqr6j2ua</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/15/the-battle-of-northern-gaza-is-almost-over </item><item><title><![CDATA[What is Iran’s axis of resistance?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>美国</span><small>称，</small>自10月7日哈马斯袭击以色列以来，其在叙利亚和伊拉克的军队已遭受至少55次袭击。美国指责伊朗及其在中东的代理人，并进行了反击：11月12日，美国对叙利亚东部发动了自10月底以来的第三次空袭。迄今为止，伊朗代理人尚未发动可能将美国拖入全面战争的袭击。但他们的火力对美国及其盟友构成了明显的威胁。这个自称的抵抗轴心是什么？它的力量有多大？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 1979 年伊斯兰革命后，伊朗寻求在整个中东输出其意识形态并建立其政治影响力。其实现这一目标的工具之一是遍布伊拉克、黎巴嫩、叙利亚、也门和其他地方的暴力代理人和盟友网络。尽管该组织的每个成员并非都认同伊朗的宗教原教旨主义——逊尼派成员甚至不认同其信条——但他们确实有共同的目标：抵制西方影响并<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/11/02/why-israel-must-fight-on">对抗以色列。</a></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该轴心国长期以来一直由伊朗圣城军协调，该部队是伊朗伊斯兰革命卫队的一支部队，也是该政权的禁卫军。这股力量对弱国进行掠夺。 1982年，它开始在黎巴嫩训练年轻的什叶派武装分子，以骚扰占领该国南部的以色列士兵。整个 90 年代，圣城军为包括<a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-palestinian-islamic-jihad">巴勒斯坦伊斯兰圣战组织</a>和<a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/10/how-powerful-is-hamas">哈马斯</a>在内的巴勒斯坦伊斯兰团体提供了重要支持。它还支持北方联盟，这是阿富汗的一个松散组织，1996年抵抗塔利班的接管。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 2002年，美国总统乔治·W·布什警告称，存在一个由朝鲜、伊朗和伊拉克组成的新<a href="https://www.economist.com/international-relations-a-to-z">“邪恶轴心”</a> 。在利比亚报纸<i>《Al-Zahf al-Akhdar》</i>发表了一篇广为流传的社论谴责该短语后，一些阿拉伯和伊朗媒体开始使用“抵抗轴心”一词来形容该地区日益壮大的反美民兵网络。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 20 世纪 90 年代末，后来<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2020/01/07/was-americas-assassination-of-qassem-suleimani-justified">被美国暗杀的</a>伊朗著名安全官员<a href="https://www.economist.com/obituary/2020/01/09/obituary-qassem-suleimani-was-assassinated-on-january-3rd">卡西姆·苏莱马尼（Qassem Suleimani</a> ）（如图所示，海报）接管该组织后，圣城军开始扩大其网络。它支持萨达姆侯赛因政权的什叶派反对者，包括巴德尔组织，这是一个强大的民兵组织，后来声称拥有 10,000 至 50,000 名武装人员。 2003年美国入侵伊拉克后，圣城军在该国建立了武装团体，与美国和英国军队作战。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在2011年开始的叙利亚内战中，圣城军训练并武装了与该国总统<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2022/03/26/syrias-outcast-dictator-returns-to-the-arab-world">巴沙尔·阿萨德</a>结盟的民兵。据伊朗官员称，它还集结了来自阿富汗、巴基斯坦、黎巴嫩和伊拉克的约 7 万名武装人员，在截至 2021 年的十年间在叙利亚作战。在也门，圣城军支持胡塞武装，这是一个什叶派组织，反抗沙特支持的政府并控制了该国的大片地区。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">美国国务院估计，在 2019 年制裁影响该国收入之前，伊朗每年花费 700 美元支持民兵。其中很大一部分资金用于储备伊朗长期合作伙伴的军火库。自哈马斯袭击以来，<a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">真主党</a>经常与以色列在黎巴嫩边境交火，据信该组织拥有 15 万枚火箭弹。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自 2020 年苏莱曼尼被暗杀以来，真主党等伊朗轴心中实力较强的成员变得更加自治。伊朗表示，它没有收到<a href="https://www.economist.com/films/2023/10/13/what-is-hamas">哈马斯袭击以色列的</a>预先警告。但它仍然利用冲突在该地区制造更多混乱。它还在其他方面受益：加沙的战斗使以色列和伊朗的主要竞争对手沙特阿拉伯之间关系正常化的外交努力停止了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">伊朗可以从这场动荡中获得更多好处。整个中东地区对西方支持以色列的愤怒可能会帮助一些伊朗支持的组织吸引更多心怀不满的新成员，而逊尼派组织哈马斯在与以色列的战斗中的突出地位可能会缓解网络内部的宗派紧张局势。如果战斗蔓延到加沙以外的地区，石油价格的飙升将填满伊朗的国库。一场涉及美国的全面战争对整个地区来说将是灾难性的。至少在这一点上，伊朗似乎与大撒旦意见一致。但不要指望它会扮演和事佬的角色。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:38:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b6k9jv0vmvlmr7l6db1jd1fim694panc</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/11/15/what-is-irans-axis-of-resistance </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court rules against Britain’s Rwanda policy. What next?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>它</span><small>永远不会</small>“停船”。但最高法院11月15日裁定政府将<a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/07/04/britains-tough-asylum-plans-are-held-up-in-court-and-by-the-lords">寻求庇护者空运到卢旺达</a>的计划非法，这对里希·苏纳克来说仍然是沉重的打击。首相承诺解决乘坐小船穿越英吉利海峡的非法移民问题。法院的裁决在《非法移民法》中留下了一个大漏洞，该法允许通过另一个安全国家进入英国的寻求庇护者被拘留和驱逐出境。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">首相并没有放弃。英国最高法院以卢旺达对寻求庇护者来说是一个不安全的目的地为由一致裁定反对该计划后不久，苏纳克表示，他将通过一项“紧急”法律，声称卢旺达实际上是安全的。他还表示，他不会允许“外国法院”阻止该计划。强硬的言论可能会让强硬派感到高兴，但很难看出飞机很快会如何起飞飞往基加利。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该计划始终存在明显的后勤缺陷。英国政府声称其“不设上限”，但卢旺达政府表示，每年只能接纳数百人。自从加强渡轮和隧道过境点的安全以来，小船移民的数量激增。 2022 年，这一数字达到创纪录的 46,000 人，高于 2018 年的 299 人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">更大的问题是合法的。许多通过这种方式进入英国的人都获得了庇护：阿富汗人和叙利亚人的庇护率超过 95%。六月，上诉法院表示，驱回风险——将寻求庇护者送回不安全的国家——意味着卢旺达计划违反了《欧洲人权公约》( <small>ECHR</small> )。维护该公约的欧洲人权法院是第一个在 2022 年阻止政府计划的法院。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最高法院在本周的判决中引用了<small>联合国难民事务高级专员</small>记录的几起案件，这些案件涉及来自阿富汗和叙利亚等绝对不安全国家的寻求庇护者被从基加利遣送回国的案件。报告称，禁止驱回的规则包含在英国批准的几部法律中，而不仅仅是<small>《欧洲人权法院》</small> 。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这不仅是苏纳克先生的问题，也是他的保守党右翼对手的问题。 11 月 13 日，苏纳克被解除内政大臣职务后不久，苏纳克在一封愤怒的信中表示，苏纳克总理拒绝退出<small>欧洲人权法院</small>的呼吁，违背了他“阻止船只”的承诺。当卢旺达计划也违反其他法律时，声称该公约阻止英国做出决定的说法就不那么有说服力了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">现在怎么办？英国已经向基加利政府支付了 1.4 亿英镑（1.75 亿美元），不过观察人士指出，这笔钱并没有用于改善其庇护程序。除了立法外，苏纳克还表示，他将与卢旺达发布一项新条约，“保证”当“我们派人去卢旺达时，他们不会被错误地遣返回自己的国家”。苏纳克先生也在推动对“第 39 条命令”的改革——<small>欧洲人权法院</small>发布的临时禁令。然而，目前还不清楚是否有任何条约能让法院满意，是否有任何紧急状态法会在上议院获得通过，或者如何阻止<small>欧洲人权法院</small>再次阻止事情发生。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">除了这样的表演之外，政府还将寻找其他安全的第三国来将寻求庇护者送往目的地。法院对卢旺达计划作出的判决中没有一项判决认为该想法本身是非法的；只是卢旺达不是一个合适的目的地。新任内政大臣詹姆斯·克莱弗利表示，其他欧洲国家“显然”对这一概念有兴趣。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">苏纳克先生可以指出其他地方取得的一些进展。今年到目前为止，小船移民的数量明显低于去年。这主要是因为政府与阿尔巴尼亚达成了一项协议，遣返非法来到英国的公民。智囊团“英国未来”的桑德·卡特瓦拉表示，英国应该寻求与那些公民庇护批准率低于（比如）60%的国家达成类似的协议。停船靠的不是一项大政策，而是一系列小政策。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:14:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/4n9jjca9e7c1apvlr3epj4rvqqak1qoj</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/15/the-supreme-court-rules-against-britains-rwanda-policy-what-next </item><item><title><![CDATA[Some scientists think newborn neurons could reverse Alzheimer’s]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">阿尔茨海默病的<small>最初症状之一</small><span>就是</span>精神错乱。大多数人每天早上都可以把车停在不同的地方，晚上再找到它。患有阿尔茨海默氏症的人发现这类问题更难解决。他们经常做的事情的记忆，比如吃饭或服药，在他们的脑海中纠缠不清。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">区分相似记忆的能力取决于称为齿状回的一小块脑组织。对小鼠的研究表明，齿状回是大脑中为数不多的即使在成年期也能产生新神经元的部分之一。这些新的神经元被认为有助于保持相似的记忆不同。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">类似的事情是否会发生在人类身上还不太清楚。但本周在华盛顿<small>特区</small>举行的神经科学学会会议上描述的一系列新结果表明，情况可能如此。如果确实如此，那么鼓励这一过程可能会为阿尔茨海默病提供新的治疗方法。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">直到 20 世纪 60 年代，科学家们还认为成人大脑不会产生新的神经元。然后，证据开始出现，表明成年大鼠和小鼠大脑中存在年轻神经元<sup>，</sup>特别是处理气味的嗅球和齿状回。这些新的神经元是从神经祖细胞（一种类似于干细胞的未分化神经元）发育而来的，这一过程被科学家称为神经发生。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">至少在老鼠身上，这些新神经元和阿尔茨海默病之间似乎存在联系。经过基因改造而具有类似阿尔茨海默病症状的小鼠大脑中的年轻神经元也较少。 2021 年和 2022 年发表的两项研究表明，鼓励神经发生可以改善此类动物的记忆力。今年四月发表的一篇论文发现，促进神经发生还导致其他称为小胶质细胞的细胞开始清理蛋白质缠结，称为淀粉样蛋白斑块，这是阿尔茨海默病的特征。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">到目前为止，一切都很有希望——如果你是一只老鼠的话。但研究人类的神经发生是很棘手的。<small>核磁共振</small>扫描仪无法观察单个神经元的生长。科学家必须从尸体上采集脑组织样本，然后用只与年轻神经元结合的化学物质对其进行染色，或者测量脑细胞内表达的基因以寻找年轻的标志。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">此类论文已发表数十篇。但对于每一个发现神经发生证据的人来说，都有另一个人未能做到这一点。支持神经发生的阵营认为无效结果是由于脑组织质量差或保存技术粗糙造成的。反对者认为，要么人类不会在齿状回中生长这些神经元，要么即使生长，它们的数量也太少而无用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在华盛顿发表的这项研究强化了人类神经发生的论据。哥伦比亚大学的 Maura Boldrini、马德里大学的 María Llorens-Martín、伊利诺伊大学芝加哥分校的 Orly Lazarov 和宾夕法尼亚大学的 Hongjun Song 提出了人类齿状回中存在年轻神经元的证据，尽管他们的大部分发现尚未经过同行评审。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其中三名研究人员还研究了健康老年人或阿尔茨海默病患者的大脑。他们的结果表明，所谓的新神经元的产生随着年龄的增长而减慢，并且在阿尔茨海默病中急剧下降。其中两个小组之前的研究还发现，拥有更多此类神经元的阿尔茨海默病患者记忆力更好。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管这项新研究强化了人类神经发生的论据，但目前还不确定。 One group of researchers from Yale University questioned whether the staining technique used in one of the studies was accidentally tagging other brain cells such as astrocytes. They are also concerned that the studies tend to find very few progenitor cells. “Where are all the mothers of these baby neurons?” asked Jon Arellano, one of the sceptics.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are other wrinkles. Dr Song found a different set of genes expressed in the supposedly young human neurons from those seen in neurons from other animals. And the few young neurons that both Dr Song and Dr Lazarov found in the brains of Alzheimer&#39;s patients looked very different from the same neurons in healthy brains. If the new cells are somehow defective, increasing their number may not help.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But although not all the scientists at the conference were convinced, some drug-makers appear to be. In April, Biomed Industries, a pharmaceutical firm based in California, announced results from an early clinical trial suggesting that a new drug that had been shown to increase neurogenesis in mice improved memory in people with moderate Alzheimer&#39;s. If subsequent trials are equally encouraging, that could be further evidence that the neurogenesis theory of Alzheimer&#39;s does indeed have something to it. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:58:27 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/l1aapet9lt2dpib0c9qfn9anuuks4lrs</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/some-scientists-think-newborn-neurons-could-reverse-alzheimers </item><item><title><![CDATA[New ways to pay for research could boost scientific progress]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>H</span> <small>ow might</small> science be done on an alien planet? Since the laws of nature are the same everywhere, the aliens would make the same discoveries as humans have—that matter is made of atoms, say, or that life develops via evolution. But while the results might be the same, aliens would be unlikely to have come up with the same methods for arriving at them. It would be remarkable if the little green men had invented universities, funding committees, a tenure system and all the other accoutrements of modern academic life.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This thought experiment, dreamed up by Michael Nielsen, a physicist, and Kanjin Qiu, an entrepreneur, was not merely a flight of fancy. It was part of an essay published last year pointing out that the way modern science is organised is not the only way it could be done, and perhaps not even the best way. Experimenting with different sorts of institutions, or novel ways to hand out research money, might help fix what the authors say is a “discovery ecosystem in a state of near stasis”. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC445.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"> <span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">image: The Economist</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Dr Nielsen and Ms Qiu are among a band of researchers concerned that scientific progress is slowing. A paper published in 2020 by economists from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology ( <small>MIT</small> ) and Stanford University concluded that American research productivity was falling, with more effort required to produce smaller gains in knowledge. A second paper, published in January this year, argued that the “disruptiveness” of both scientific papers and patents, as measured by citation patterns, fell by over 90% for papers, and more than 80% for patents, between 1945 and 2010 (see chart 1).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “The main thing I&#39;d like to see is far more diversity in how we fund and organise research,” says Dr Nielsen. There are plenty of ideas around. Some researchers advocate giving out research grants via lotteries, or expanding the system of competitive scientific or technological prizes. Others prefer to found entirely new types of institutions, displacing the universities that dominate scientific research today. And many see a chance to run a grand scientific experiment, turning science&#39;s methods inwards to work out how science itself might be improved.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Following the Benjamin Franklins</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The modern system of science funding—at least in America, the world&#39;s leading scientific power—is relatively recent. The Royal Society in Britain, the world&#39;s oldest national scientific academy, was founded in 1660 but limited its funding to an elite group of fellows. Before the second world war a good deal of American science was paid for by rich industrialists and corporate laboratories. The modern system in America owes much to the Rockefeller Foundation, a charity, in particular. It disbursed its money as grants for specific, well-defined projects, such as investigating the cause of yellow fever. As government funding rose after the second world war (see chart 2), America&#39;s government adopted a similar system. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231118_STC446.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"> <span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">image: The Economist</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These days, over half the funding given to universities by the National Institutes of Health ( <small>NIH</small> )—which, with its budget of nearly $50bn, is the world&#39;s biggest funder of medical science—is given out as fixed-term grants. Around 70% of the $8.6bn distributed in 2022 by the National Science Foundation ( <small>NSF</small> ) was structured the same way. A scientist applying for this money must write a grant proposal, perhaps 15 pages long, and ideally including some early results to prove his project&#39;s worthiness. The proposal is given a score by other researchers; this, in turn, helps a committee decide whether to fund it. Some 80% of <small>NIH</small> funding, and 90% of <small>NSF</small> grants, go through such peer review.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Silvana Konermann, a biochemist at Stanford University, notes that, with its mix of short timelines and small grants, the system leaves researchers “constantly thinking” about where their next cheque is coming from. But skill at raising money is not necessarily correlated with the usefulness of one&#39;s research. In October Katalin Karikó won <a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/10/02/a-nobel-prize-in-physiology-for-mrna-vaccines">a Nobel prize</a> for discoveries that led to m <small>RNA</small> vaccines. She had been demoted early in her career by the University of Pennsylvania because of her failure to bring in sufficient money.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And grants are becoming harder to win. Between 2003 and 2015 the likelihood that a researcher would be funded by the <small>NIH</small> at least once over a five-year window fell from 43% to 31%. One study estimated that researchers applying for grants from the National Health and Medical Research Council in Australia cumulatively spent 614 years writing them in 2014. One prominent biologist quips that if success rates keep falling, more money will be lost in wasted researcher time than the value of the grants themselves.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One common criticism of having committees decide where money should go is that the need for consensus will suppress unorthodox ideas. Sethuraman Panchanathan, the director of the <small>NSF</small> , is keen to try a proposal called the “golden ticket”. Each reviewer would be able to back a limited number of risky ideas in the face of disagreement from their colleagues.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A more radical solution is to abandon committees altogether and hand out money by lottery. Some organisations are already experimenting along such lines. In 2013 the Health Research Council of New Zealand began giving out around 2% of its annual funding at random—though proposals had to first clear a minimum quality bar. The Volkswagen Foundation in Germany, the British Academy and the National Science Foundation in Switzerland are all running similar trials. The Novo Nordisk foundation, in Denmark, is testing a hybrid system that rejects projects assessed as being of poor quality, gives money to good ones, and randomly hands cash to some of those judged middling.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Rather than reforming existing institutions, another idea is to create new ones. In his essay Dr Nielsen suggested an “Institute for Travelling Scientists”. Inspired by Craig Venter, a biologist and entrepreneur who has done much good science from the <a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2011/03/24/plenty-more-bugs-in-the-sea">deck of his yacht</a> , the institute would be based on a boat that would travel around the world, picking up and dropping off scientists with the aim of offering a relaxing atmosphere in which to master a new discipline or meet unusual collaborators.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A more hard-headed, if less relaxing, source of inspiration is the Defence Advanced Research Agency ( <small>DARPA</small> ), an American military funding agency originally founded in 1958 that has had a hand in developing everything from the internet to <small>GPS</small> and voice interfaces for computers. <small>DARPA</small> &#39;s $4bn budget sits outside the rest of America&#39;s military-research bureaucracy. Around 100 programme managers—described by Adam Russell, formerly one of their number, as “aliens” on account of their often unconventional backgrounds—can fund ambitious research problems however they see fit. At its best, it acts as a “force multiplier” on entirely new fields of research, says Dr Russell.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In America, the idea has given birth to organisations such as <small>IARPA</small> , which applies the same model to America&#39;s spy agencies rather than its armies, and <small>ARPA E</small> , which pays for research into novel energy technologies. <i>The Economist</i> calculates that the total amount of cash handed out by such entities rose from about $4bn in 2021 to nearly $6bn in 2022. The most recent addition to the family, founded in 2022, is <small>ARPA</small> - <small>H</small> , which covers health care. Britain, Germany and Japan have all tried to copy the model outside America in recent years, setting up <small>ARIA</small> , <small>SPRIN</small> - <small>D</small> and Moonshot <small>R</small> &amp; <small>D,</small> respectively.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But how well the <small>ARPA</small> model can be replicated is unclear. One former employee notes that <small>DARPA</small> “no longer attracts the same talent as it used to” and says there is “little interest” in studying cases of failure to figure out how to improve. The model may be less successful outside military research, suggests a chapter in a book by Pierre Azoulay and Danielle Li, a pair of economists at <small>MIT</small> , published in 2022. America&#39;s armed forces are the end-users of the technologies <small>DARPA</small> develops, and have a good understanding of what they need. End-users in other fields, such as energy or health care, are less single-minded.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Prizes, which offer a jackpot to anyone who can meet a scientific or engineering goal, can also push research in new directions. The Clay Mathematics Institute&#39;s $1m Millennium Prize Problems exist to focus attention on unsolved problems in mathematics. So-called XPrizes have boosted research into everything from rainforest preservation to space flight. The biggest, for removing carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, has a total pot of $100m, paid for by Elon Musk, an entrepreneur. A study in 2021 found that research topics that were associated with prizes gained 40% more papers and 37% more new scientists than fields that were not.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Prizes also have the advantage of being tightly focused. Adam Marblestone and Sam Rodriques, a physicist and a biologist respectively, have been thinking along similar lines. They have proposed setting up a series of “focused-research organisations” ( <small>FRO</small> s). Each <small>FRO</small> would have well-specified goals and limited lifetimes, a bit like the Human Genome Project, which began in 1990 and then shut down in 2003 after the first draft of a human genome had been published. The hope is that this would prevent them from sliding into bureaucratic complacency over time. Money could come from governments or philanthropists, for whom the prospect of bold, time-limited funding may prove attractive.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Marblestone&#39;s organisation, Convergent Research, has helped launch six <small>FRO</small> s. One is trying to map neural circuits in mammalian brains. On November 1st Mr Rodriques launched a <small>FRO</small> -like non-profit called Future House that aims to create a semi-autonomous “ <small>AI</small> scientist” within ten years. It is backed by Eric Schmidt, a former boss of Google. Mr Rodriques expects it to spend $20m next year. In March Rishi Sunak, Britain&#39;s prime minister, announced his intention to set up several such organisations—though exactly what they will study remains unclear.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And then there is the idea of funding people rather than projects. In theory, that would give researchers freedom to follow their noses, pursue ideas that may not have an obvious pay-off, and change course when something doesn&#39;t work. The idea is not new: the most famous example is the Howard Hughes Medical Institute ( <small>HHMI</small> ), founded in 1953 in Maryland. Researchers are generously funded for seven or more years, compared with four for the typical <small>NIH</small> grant. Between them they have won over 30 Nobel prizes, as many as Russia and the Soviet Union combined.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is other evidence to suggest the approach works well. Dr Azoulay has compared the <small>HHMI</small> with the <small>NIH</small> ’s standard funding programme. <small>HHMI</small> researchers produced nearly twice as much highly cited work, as well as a third more flops, suggesting a willingness to take more risks. Inspired, in 2021 Dr Konermann of Stanford (an <small>HHMI</small> fellow herself) started the Arc Institute, which is run on similar lines.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> The science of science</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> No one knows how fruitful any of these ideas will prove. Dr Russell argues it is vital to try many things, “collect data” and build “feedback loops” to improve the system. Kyle Myers, an economist at Harvard Business School, thinks funders should appoint chief economists to keep track of how each approach is working.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This turning of science&#39;s methods back on itself has been dubbed “meta-science”. It is a growing field of study, says Ilan Gur, <small>ARIA</small> ’s boss. Dr Myers calculates that since 2015 there have been an average of nearly 60 randomised experiments studying the scientific process. Two decades ago that number would have been in the single digits. More are coming: on September 28th the <small>NSF</small> announced a partnership with the Institute for Progress, a science-and-technology think-tank, to conduct meta-scientific experiments.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Using science to decide how best to do science is an idea with a pleasing symmetry. Yet Dr Nielsen cautions that finding out which funding method gives the best bang for each buck may take a long time. In the meantime, says James Wilsdon, who runs the Research on Research Institute at University College London, a diverse ecosystem of funders would bring its own benefits. “If you can&#39;t get funded one way, you have another,” he says. That might help prevent others falling through the cracks in the way Dr Karikó did. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:55:18 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/n7fvgkjclp8fujh4oeevjrmv7aos7dda</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/new-ways-to-pay-for-research-could-boost-scientific-progress </item><item><title><![CDATA[Was an ancient bacterium awakened by an industrial accident?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>N</span> <small>ew species</small> are generally found rather than awakened. And they are typically discovered in remote places like rainforests or Antarctic plateaus. But not so a species of bacterium described in a paper just published in <i>Extremophiles</i> . As Russell Vreeland and Heng-Lin Chui, the paper&#39;s authors, point out, the bug is new to science. But it is not new to Earth. In fact the microbe may have been slumbering for millions of years before being awakened by an industrial disaster.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The bacterium in question lives below Lake Peignur in southern Louisiana. The ground beneath the lake is rich in natural resources. In 1980 it boasted a mine producing rock salt, while a drilling rig run by Texaco was moving about on the surface looking for oil. But on November 20th, the two operations came together accidentally—and spectacularly. The oil rig&#39;s drill penetrated the third level of the salt mine, creating a drain in the lake&#39;s floor.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Over the next few days the resulting man-made sinkhole swallowed up the oil rig, 11 barges, a tugboat, 35 hectares of land and part of a house. A canal that drained the lake into the Gulf of Mexico began flowing backwards as the water level fell, briefly creating the tallest waterfall in Louisiana, while muddy geysers erupted from mine shafts. Somehow, all 50 people working in the mine managed to get out ahead of the rising floodwaters.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> An official report could not determine whether the oil rig had been drilling in the wrong place, or whether the maps of the mine were inaccurate. Either way, the disaster created an entirely new environment. The water that flowed into the mine contained less than 2% salt. But rock salt dissolves readily in water. When Dr Vreeland, then at the University of New Orleans, was granted access to part of the flooded mine in 1987, he found the water within contained 32% salt, about nine times more than seawater.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For most creatures, that much salt would be lethal. But Dr Vreeland found a species of bacteria, one of a salt-loving group called <i>Halobacteriales</i> , in his samples. The bug grew best in water containing 18% salt—and died when concentrations fell below 10%. Since the bacterium could not have survived in the lake, how did it get into the water in the mine?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Having access to only a small lab, and with comparatively few resources, Dr Vreeland decided to shelve the mystery and move on to other projects. During a visit to China in 2016, though, he met Dr Chui, another expert in salt-loving microbes, and decided to return to his cold case.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the intervening years, scientists have found that some bacteria possess exceptional powers of self-preservation. When times are hard they can enter a form of stasis, shutting down all biological activity until things improve. The salt beneath Lake Peignur was formed by the evaporation of a previous body of salty water. Some of the salt is 125m years old, meaning it was laid down during the heyday of the dinosaurs. The new species, the researchers suggest, is therefore antediluvian both literally and metaphorically. It was there before the mine was flooded, trapped in water pockets within the salt crystals—and it may have been there for millions of years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Exactly how long bacteria can remain in suspended animation is difficult to test, because experiments cannot reasonably run for more than a few decades. But Dr Vreeland claimed in <i>Nature</i> in 2000 that he and his colleagues had succeeded in reviving another salt-loving bacterium that was 250m years old. A study published last year argued that, in some circumstances, a particularly resilient species called <i>Deinococcus radiodurans</i> might be able to manage 300m years in stasis.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And Dr Vreeland points out that the conditions in the salt mine might have helped this latest species while away the aeons in relative safety. One problem faced by a somnolent organism is the gradual accumulation of damage to its <small>DNA</small> . Oxygen is one source of such damage. But the element does not exist inside rock-salt crystals, and is only very slightly soluble in brine. Ultraviolet light is another danger, but none penetrates below the ground.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Background radiation can also damage genomes. But the only radioactive atom found in brine is potassium-40. With a half-life of over a billion years, it is only mildly radioactive. And bacteria that live in harsh environments, including <i>Halobacteriales</i> , contain plenty of <small>DNA</small> -protecting proteins to prevent damage. Now, thanks to a human mistake, Dr Vreeland&#39;s bacterium has been given an entire mine in which to live, where it can finally reap the rewards of its prodigious patience. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:55:03 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ke7g2tcu5skf4oc9l3bqgkfe8sbbjbig</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/15/was-an-ancient-bacterium-awakened-by-an-industrial-accident </item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel sets its sights on Gaza’s tunnels]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption> Listen to this podcast</figcaption> <span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">Enjoy more audio and podcasts on <a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a> or <a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a> .</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistbabbage/e/655508ea076466001274b32a/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6ImpwNDdzenVqIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwcml2YXRlIn0=&sig=u-TwBERJ0-2SqUjf_oZM45xNjBTZZdAzl8mUN42Hnbw"><p> Your browser does not support the<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This week, <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/12/as-israel-fights-on-in-gaza-its-dilemma-gets-worse">Israeli soldiers</a> entered the al-Shifa hospital in Gaza, claiming that Hamas runs a command centre in tunnels underneath the building. Hamas has denied this claim. Under the ground in Gaza, though, Hamas does run a <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/17/hamas-tunnels-under-gaza-will-be-a-key-battlefield-for-israel">sophisticated network of secret tunnels</a> . Israel has vowed to destroy them and their forces will call on every <a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/08/israel-hopes-technology-will-help-it-fight-in-hamass-tunnels">technological trick</a> they can have in their arsenal. But finding and eliminating tunnels is no easy task, and will no doubt make the war more deadly to civilians. How does war work, when it moves underground? Runtime: 42 min</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Host: Alok Jha, <i>The Economist</i> ’s science and technology editor, with Shashank Joshi, <i>The Economist</i> ’s defence editor. Contributors: Daphné Richemond-Barak, author of “Underground Warfare” and a researcher at Reichman University, Israel; Eyal Weizman, an architect at Goldsmiths, University of London and boss of Forensic Architecture, which investigates violence committed by states, police forces, militaries, and corporations.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Listen on: <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/babbage-from-the-economist/id508376907">Apple Podcasts</a> | <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH?si=nJxIwIpZSp6Yfx6ObmnfhA&dl_branch=1&nd=1">Spotify</a></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>播客成绩单可通过<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__">[email protected]</a>索取。我们致力于进一步提高可访问性，并正在探索新的方法来扩展我们的播客转录产品。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:52:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/0klpnodh93bh03hkpboug5slv0cu4i43</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/15/israel-sets-its-sights-on-gazas-tunnels </item><item><title><![CDATA[How maths can help you win your favourite games]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-14046qw e1xfd4x10"> <b>Around the World in 80 Games.</b><br> By Marcus du Sautoy.<i>基础书籍； 384 pages; 30 美元。 Fourth Estate; £16.99</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>HICH ARE</small> the best properties to buy when playing Monopoly, and how many houses should you build on them? Which continent should you aim to take over first in Risk? And what is the best strategy when using the doubling cube in <a href="https://www.economist.com/obituary/2020/03/19/falafel-died-on-february-14th">backgammon</a> ? These are some of the questions considered and answered by Marcus du Sautoy, a British mathematician and Oxford professor, in his sprightly, light-hearted history of <a href="https://www.economist.com/1843/2017/12/13/table-top-generals">games and gaming</a> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The narrative is organised geographically as a trip around the world, starting with ancient games from the Middle East—backgammon, the Royal Game of Ur, the Egyptian game of senet—and ending up in Europe with modern games such as Pandemic and Dobble. Along the way the author considers many old favourites (Cluedo, Scrabble, Risk), recent arrivals ( <a href="https://www.economist.com/1843/2022/04/19/the-wordle-hurdle-the-pitfalls-of-setting-puzzles">Wordle</a> , Settlers of Catan) and less familiar games from a wide range of cultures and historical periods, such as the African game of mancala and the Indian card game of ganjifa, whose rules change at night.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The list is not exhaustive or comprehensive but reflects his own collection. It includes a handful of <a href="https://www.economist.com/special-report/2023/03/20/ready-player-four-billion-the-rise-of-video-games">video games</a> (Prince of Persia, Game of Life) and one sport (the Mayan ball game of pitz).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> All this is, of course, really an opportunity for Mr du Sautoy to sprinkle in plenty of mathematical explanations, to provide what he calls “a <a href="https://www.economist.com/1843/2015/09/22/whats-the-best-number">celebration of the mathematics</a> that swims seductively just below the surface of many of the games I love”. Playing games, he writes, “overlaps with what I enjoy about mathematics”: the challenge of solving a problem within a set of rules, the need to overcome obstacles and the victorious “aha” moment when a solution is found.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As well as forays into probability and game theory, he explains dice rolls in Monopoly using Markov chains; the torus-shaped playing field of video games like Spacewar!; and how the geometries of finite projective planes underpin the deceptively simple game of Dobble. And in many cases these explanations provide concrete advice to players.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In Monopoly, says Mr du Sautoy, the best properties to buy are the orange ones, followed by the red ones (and build three houses on them). In Risk, control of North America has the best risk-reward ratio, generating a good supply of bonus armies while being easy to defend. In backgammon, accept a double if you think you have more than a 20% chance of winning; offer one if you think you have more than an 80% chance of winning. Oh, and “ <small>TALES</small> ” is the best starting word in Wordle.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The hybrid history-travelogue approach is clunky at times, and some of the entries are not games at all, but mini-essays on game-related topics, from biography to psychology. And despite its high-concept framing, the book can be read in pretty much any order; indeed, the author suggests a game to randomise the order of the chapters. (In an appendix, he then works out how many possible options there are, which doubles as an illustration of the technique of proof by induction.)</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Fun, unexpected, operating within fixed but arbitrary rules, producing a range of complex outcomes and offering insights that can be applied to everyday life—a good game combines all these elements. The same can also be said of this book. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:14:14 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/72tmfe7pe9u1csd7bltjnaivophtp21o</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/11/15/how-maths-can-help-you-win-your-favourite-games </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vivian Silver knew no good could ever come of war]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-aasbfu e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>S</span> <small>ometimes truth</small> could come from the mouths of babes. This time it came from Vivian Silver&#39;s two small sons. They had made a friend of Nassar, a Palestinian labourer who worked at their kibbutz, and wondered why, after the second intifada, he wasn&#39;t working for them any more. She explained that he had no permit to come over now. “Why not?” one son wondered. “Because there is a big conflict between the Palestinians and the Israelis.” “What is it over?” “Land,” she told him.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In Hebrew the words for “earth” and land” were the same. So her son went off, fetched a bucket, filled it with earth, and returned. “Here,” he said. “Give it to Nassar, so he can come back.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> How simple peace could be, she thought. How uncomplicated, if it were only a matter of talking, sharing and helping. She spent 50 years with that thought in her head, trying all the ways she could think of to bring neighbours together. For neighbours they were, with only four and a half kilometres separating her kibbutz, Be&#39;eri, from the Gaza Strip. What was home to her was also home to them. No one intended to move anywhere. It made no sense to fight, only to live in mutual respect and freedom. On the other side were women like herself, mothers with children, who wanted nothing more than to bring them up happy, healthy and in peace.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> She would tell friends from Tel Aviv how quiet it was in the kibbutz. Yet she endured four wars. In the conflict of 2009 she was walking in the fields when bombs began falling round her. She knew at once this was not a stray raid; a war had started. With no safe place near, she simply had to run, in terror, the several kilometres home. In 2018 Palestinian kite-bombs torched other green places she loved, the Tel Gama archeological site and her local nature reserves. They were all turned to ash. Israel&#39;s retaliation, as usual, was fierce. But what good did that do?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> At the kibbutz they tried to live normally. There was no guard on the gate, and most people did not bother to lock their doors. They got shelters later, which made them feel safer; but they were not safe. The war with Gaza in 2014 was the worst. It lasted 50 days, the killing and maiming, the destruction and deep psychological damage on both sides. Yet the idea that war would bring peace had been proved false time and time again. When were the two parties going to come to their senses, and stop this?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> She had never expected to become a peace activist, though she knew some cause would consume her. When she was younger, growing up in Canada and, for a while, in New York, women&#39;s rights were her chief passion. But a stint at Hebrew University in Jerusalem convinced her in 1974 to move to Israel, where her interests began to expand. She became one of the few female secretaries, or chief decision-makers, at her first kibbutz, Gezer, and took charge of building both there and at Be&#39;eri, not usually a woman&#39;s job. She also began to help the Bedouin she found camped almost in her front yard at Be&#39;eri, as poor as if they were in some pocket of India or Africa. And she started to work with Palestinians in any way she could, because that gave peace more of a chance.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Her work burgeoned. She gave Palestinians jobs on the kibbutz, and founded a group called “Creating Peace” which encouraged cross-border links between traders and artisans. In 1998 she became executive director of the Negev Institute for Strategies of Peace and Development, later in partnership with Amal Elsana Alh&#39;jooj, a Palestinian; in 2011 they won an international award. She spent a lot of time in Gaza in the late 1990s, making friends there; it infuriated her when people said that Israel had “no partner on the other side”. But when Hamas took over the strip in 2007, everything became hard. The Friday night phone calls she had organised, gathering her neighbours in a field to chat to Gazan friends, had to stop. To make sure her Palestinian workers, who now could not cross, were not destitute, she had to take their money to the checkpoint. She had to go there, too, to pick up the sick Palestinians she would then drive to hospitals in Jerusalem.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> By 2014 she felt that nothing was working. It was a momentous year for her. She turned 65, retired, and became a grandmother: a good time for soul-searching. For 40 years now she had been a peace activist, and a proud member of the Left for just as long. But the Left had not managed to end the seemingly eternal conflict between Israelis and Palestinians. What was the answer? As her feminist brain eagerly suggested, it was to turn to woman-power. She would help build up a movement of Israeli and Palestinian women who would work together if they could, and would also keep in the public eye by marching and appealing (including every Monday outside the Knesset), for negotiated agreement rather than war.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Her branch, the Israeli side, now with around 45,000 Jewish and Arab-Israeli women, was called Women Wage Peace. From the moment she joined, she lived and breathed it. The Palestinian branch was called Women of the Sun. In a mass rally on October 4th this year they gathered at the “separation wall” in Bethlehem, walked hand in hand to the Haas Promenade in Jerusalem and mustered on the shore of the Dead Sea, the <small>WWP</small> members in white shirts with turquoise ribbons and the slogan “Peace is possible”. At the Dead Sea beach, against a fence hung with peace quilts, sympathetic female diplomats and representatives of Israel, Palestine, the United States and several European countries sat at a round table to talk. It was a symbolic, triumphant moment. The peace-wagers dispersed with hugs and laughter.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Three days later, Hamas broke into the Be&#39;eri kibbutz. Her son Yonatan, now in his 30s and in Tel Aviv, had called his mother to check she was safe. Even as the terrorists rampaged through, shooting from house to house, she made light of it. Then, wary of making any sound, she switched to WhatsApp. She was typing in a cupboard in her safe room; the terrorists had now barged in.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> What, an interviewer asked Yonatan later, would she have said about this new war, and the atrocities that had launched it? He knew the answer at once, without equivocation. “That this is the outcome...of not striving for peace.” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:27:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/i4osg559lp52t0s7240lnqfudo9nn78h</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/obituary/2023/11/15/vivian-silver-knew-no-good-could-ever-come-of-war</item></channel></rss>