<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 13 日星期一 08:45:01 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[The scourge of “stealthflation”]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>正如</span>经济学家常说的<small>那样</small>，天下没有免费的午餐。然而，如果你在麦当劳的分店购买午餐，你可能会发现也没有免费的美味。一些国家的商店现在对番茄酱和其他调味品收费。然而，麦当劳并不是唯一一家以意外收费来打击顾客的公司。在通货膨胀加剧的情况下，企业找到了几种秘密的方法来提高价格。 2024 年会成为这一令人反感的趋势的转折点吗？</p><p class="article__body-text">一个典型的例子是“分拆”技术，这是低成本航空公司首创的策略。很久以前，他们开始对过去包含的东西收取额外费用，例如机上食品和托运行李。然后是选座费用，或者任何比装满备用内衣的袜子大的随身行李包的费用。</p><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>宝马每月收取 18 美元的费用来激活其部分汽车的座椅加热器</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">最近事情确实已经失控了。一些航空公司现在对在线预订的特权收取“技术开发费”，奇怪的是，这取决于旅行的距离——你看，这些网络服务器必须更加努力地工作才能提供长途机票。其他人则对打印登机牌、机场办理登机手续或机上毯子收费。航空公司开始出售前往飞机的班车票、对每件穿着的衣服收取费用或对使用厕所收费只是时间问题。 （瑞安航空的老板迈克尔·奥利里（Michael O&#39;Leary）实际上曾经建议过最后一项。）</p><p class="article__body-text">这种做法已经流传开来。酒店和度假村通常收取“入住费”，外卖店收取“包装费”，叫车应用收取“安全费”。短租平台Airbnb因收取过高的服务费和清洁费而受到批评。</p><p class="article__body-text">但额外费用不仅限于服务：它们也适用于实体产品。<small>宝马</small>在其部分汽车上推出了每月 18 美元的费用来激活座椅加热器，一次性费用为 415 美元，即可“无限制”使用。梅赛德斯-奔驰每月收取 60 美元，或每年 600 美元，用于提高部分电动汽车的加速能力。想象一下这是否流行起来。想要使用智能手机相机的变焦功能吗？付清。需要在最高温度下使用烤箱吗？抱歉，这仅适用于高级订阅者。</p><p class="article__body-text">企业偷偷增加收入的第二种方式是“峰时”定价。航空公司和酒店长期以来一直根据季节性需求调整价格。但实时跟踪需求的能力意味着价格可以每分钟进行调整：当需求高时，优步和其他乘车共享应用程序会收取更高的费用。</p><p class="article__body-text">峰时定价现在正在影响其他行业。九月份，一家英国连锁酒吧宣布，晚上、周末或大型体育赛事期间，品脱啤酒的价格会更高。音乐会、体育赛事和主题公园的门票价格也在不断调整。从理论上讲，这是市场看不见的手的胜利：如果你想花更少的钱，就在需求低迷时购买。但心怀不满的消费者抱怨说，收取市场可以承受的费用与牟取暴利之间的界限很窄。</p><p class="article__body-text">此外，小费的流行似乎势不可挡。多年来，到美国旅游的外国人一直被这个国家普遍存在的小费文化和令人眼花缭乱的期望所困扰。美国的平均小费率为20%，是世界上最高的。理由是，服务人员的合法工资可以低至每小时 2.13 美元，因此顾客有责任做体面的事情，以确保服务员、调酒师等人能够赚取生活工资。基于触摸屏的结账意味着顾客被要求更频繁地支付小费，而且是在不太可能的地方。他们可能会发现自己在便利店、自助服务机甚至网站上被要求提供小费。</p><p class="article__body-text">有些酒店会自动将员工小费添加到账单中，从而将小费视为隐藏费用。但这不仅仅是美国。由于应用程序和非接触式支付系统的普遍存在，索要小费已经蔓延到其他国家。澳大利亚人抱怨送餐应用程序现在添加了自动提示。印度人常常对给出租车司机小费的提示感到困惑。</p><p class="article__body-text"> 2024 年，价格隐性上涨的热潮是否最终会结束？也许。通胀下降可能会抑制使用奇怪的方法来维持利润。各国政府正在就监管问题发出声音：在美国，总统乔·拜登希望打击“垃圾”费用。消费者正在反击。美国人抱怨“倾翻疲劳”。为了回应顾客的愤怒，<small>宝马</small>最近取消了座椅加热费。 Airbnb 改进了其平台，使额外费用更加明显。当然，对于准备提供简单、“无隐藏额外费用”定价的公司来说，这是一个机会。</p><p class="article__body-text">然而，在发现了无数抬高价格的方法后，公司更有可能会继续这样做。航空公司正在尝试将商务舱机票的福利分拆。<small>宝马</small>和梅赛德斯-奔驰计划继续提供其他收费“额外服务”。对小费的要求仍然很多。事实上，一家美国航空公司现在允许乘客给机组人员小费。隐形通货膨胀技术的交叉授粉显然还有很长的路要走。预计 2024 年将会遭遇更多愤怒<span>。 ■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Leo Mirani，</small> <i>《经济学人》亚洲记者，</i>孟买</p><p class="article__body-text"><em>本文发表在<a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">《2024 年世界展望》</a>印刷版的领导者部分，标题为““隐形通货膨胀”的祸害”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:42:34 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/8evlq1tcvq0krov655nvcl03s9t3s545</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/the-scourge-of-stealthflation </item><item><title><![CDATA[The green transition will transform the global economic order]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap">至少在理论上，<span>向</span>碳中和世界的<small>过渡</small>应该会让所有国家变得更好。许多国家将减少对燃料进口的依赖，从而节省大量资金，并使经济免受碳氢化合物价格波动的影响。那些出口新特斯拉、涡轮机和太瓦时电网容量所需金属的企业将赚取丰厚的租金。即使是前石油国家，如果能够利用改造后的炼油厂和管道以及风能和太阳能来生产氢气，也可能会蓬勃发展。每个人都会欢迎一个不再每年变得更热、更危险的星球。</p><p class="article__body-text">实际上，向净零的过渡将是动荡的。能源消费格局的变化和贸易流向的重新洗牌，既会产生新的赢家，也会产生新的输家。到 2024 年，这种迄今为止被 covid-19、全球经济疲软和中国经济减速的影响所掩盖的差异将开始变得更加明显，但并不总是以你可能期望的方式。情况不仅仅是化石燃料资源的提供者会输而绿色资源的提供者会赢。两个阵营都会有赢家和输家。</p><p class="article__body-text">在转型期间，世界将继续消耗碳氢化合物。国际能源署预测石油需求将在 2030 年之前达到顶峰，但 2023 年出现的绿色反弹表明石油需求可能不会这么快消退。与此同时，投资者的压力和对长期需求的疑虑意味着，只有海湾和拉丁美洲的国有企业才会在新供应上投入巨资。这将使仍然丰厚的石油租金集中在少数出口商手中。最终，石油输出国组织（ <small>OPEC</small> ）这个其成员在如何最好地处理转型问题上存在分歧的卡特尔可能会崩溃，让低成本的石油国家攫取更多的市场份额。</p><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>只有最精明的人才能靠绿色资源致富</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">对天然气的需求将持续更长时间，这使得以液体形式出口大部分天然气的三个国家——美国、澳大利亚和卡塔尔——能够获利。即使是煤炭也将在 2040 年代保持其吸引力。只要能源匮乏的亚洲吞噬它，最适合为该地区服务的澳大利亚和印度尼西亚就不会介意肮脏的美元。</p><p class="article__body-text">但随着石油财富继续流动，许多石油国家将无法保证其经济的未来发展，并最终将遭受损失。非洲、欧洲和亚洲的能源进口商将不得不为碳氢化合物支付高价。在 2023 年底地缘政治担忧再次出现波动之后，这些石油的价格可能会在 2024 年再次波动。正如亚洲和欧洲争夺天然气一样，全球经济的反弹将需要更多的石油。除非出现全球性崩盘，从德国到日本的进口国可能面临十年或更长时间的高价格。</p><p class="article__body-text">电气化的影响也将是微妙的。急于实现脱碳目标将对钴、铜、锂和镍等金属产生巨大需求，这些金属是绿色发电站、电网和电动汽车的重要成分。到 2024 年，这一前景可能会超越对经济的近期担忧，导致金属价格再次上涨。然而，由于清洁技术仍在不断变化、需求适应价格上涨以及新供应大量涌入，许多此类矿物的市场可能会经历快速的繁荣与萧条周期，使出口商措手不及。许多此类国家刚涉足采矿业，缺乏管理波动所需的运作良好的主权基金、对冲机制和财政审慎措施。开矿和停矿的难度和成本，以及矿藏的​​地理分散性，使得金属<small>欧佩克</small>不太可能出现。这表明，只有最精明的少数人才能通过利用绿色资源而致富。</p><p class="article__body-text">而且繁荣不会永远持续下去：一旦有足够多的风车转动和道路上的电动汽车，对绿色金属的需求将稳定在较低水平。更持久的租金将流向那些能够利用强烈的阳光、风和河流来产生他们不需要的大量绿色电力的国家。在某些情况下，资源禀赋的不平等会加剧地区差异：预计多风的北海和阳光明媚的地中海表现良好，而多云的欧洲大陆则表现不佳。最幸运的是能够结合多种资源来保证可再生能源持续供应的国家。那些人口较少的国家可以利用他们生产的任何剩余来吸引高耗能行业，例如炼钢或数据存储，到他们的海岸。其他国家将寻求以电子或液体燃料的形式出口过剩的电力。</p><p class="article__body-text">转型期的能源超级大国将是那些无视批评、无所不用其极的国家：消耗化石燃料、开采金属和涡轮增压可再生能源。目前还没有哪个国家能做到这一切。海湾国家经常谈论太阳能和氢能，但尚未大规模实现。智利开采大量的铜和锂，但并未利用其 6,500 公里的海岸线、南部风暴和阳光明媚的沙漠来大量发电。美国拥有页岩石油和天然气以及越来越多的可再生能源，但在自家后院开采绿色金属时面临反对。转型的最大收获仍有待争夺。 <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Matthieu Favas，</small> <i>《经济学人》</i>商品编辑</p><p class="article__body-text"><em>本文发表在<a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">《2024 年世界展望</a>》印刷版的领导者部分，标题为“转会窗口”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:41:52 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/nmflots8v8eg9lh5cbg4j4t0pv0nng4i</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/the-green-transition-will-transform-the-global-economic-order </item><item><title><![CDATA[Generative AI holds much promise for businesses]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>当</span><small>Chatgpt</small>于 2022 年底首次推出时，它很快就引起了轰动。两个月内，一亿用户提出了各种有趣的问题（“用海绵宝宝的参考资料给我写一首说唱歌曲”）。谷歌搜索“人工智能”的人数激增，引发了投资者对各类<small>人工智能</small>项目的热情。然而，这些投资者和企业家认为，真正的希望在于它在商业中的应用。在这里，它也可以比过去的创新更快地被采用。但这并不意味着这会在一夜之间发生。</p><p class="article__body-text">潜力令人兴奋。咨询公司麦肯锡表示，生成式<small>人工智能</small>四分之三的业务用途将分为四个领域：客户运营、营销和销售、软件工程以及研发。浏览复杂的税法或总结法律文件可能变得轻而易举。输入正确的提示，营销文案的初稿就会神奇地出现。已经有许多程序员依赖 Microsoft 的编码工具 Copilot 来帮助他们编写软件。研究表明，绩效低于平均水平的专业工人往往从使用生成式<small>人工智能</small>中获得最大收益，有望大幅增加公司的产出。</p><div class="article__body-text-image"><figure> <span><meta><img src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/608/723/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/238/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/357/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/476/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/713/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/761/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/951/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/1189/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/1522/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC008.png 1280w" sizes="336px" alt></span></figure><p class="article__body-text">同样有益的是，许多生成式<small>人工智能</small>工具将比以前的技术更容易使用。这不像个人电脑或智能手机的出现，雇主需要购买大量硬件，甚至不像电子商务，零售商需要建立物理基础设施才能开设在线店面。许多企业可能会发现他们可以与<small>人工智能</small>专家合作设计定制工具。微软和谷歌等公司正在将生成式<small>人工智能</small>嵌入到他们的办公软件中，这意味着任何打开文档或电子表格的人很快就能使用这些工具。</p><p class="article__body-text">许多最大的公司已经在进行试验。摩根士丹利银行正在利用<small>人工智能</small>构建一种工具来帮助财富管理者。制药公司礼来公司 (Eli Lilly) 与一家初创公司达成了一项协议，该公司运营“自主实验室”来识别有前景的分子，然后制药商将对其进行开发、测试和商业化。 2020 年至 2023 年 6 月期间，美国大型银行发布的职位空缺中约有 5% 在职位描述中提到了<small>人工智能</small>，大型科技公司在 2020-22 年注册的专利中约有 8% 与<small>人工智能</small>相关。</p></div><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>另外两个阵营正在出现：谨慎的和不情愿的</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">然而，并非所有企业都会热心采用。在科技界之外，只有三分之一的全球经理告诉麦肯锡，他们经常在工作中使用生成式<small>人工智能</small>；大约一半的人尝试过这项技术，但决定不使用它，大约五分之一的人没有接触过这一切。简而言之，谨慎的和不情愿的<small>人工智能</small>采用者的数量是二比一。</p><p class="article__body-text">从谨慎开始。一些企业正在采取谨慎的态度，因为该技术的许多方面仍需要解决。聊天机器人很容易产生“幻觉”，或者编造一些听起来危险的可信的东西。作家、艺术家、摄影师和出版商正在法庭上质疑<small>人工智能</small>模型对他们数据的使用。一些企业担心因使用这些模型而面临法律风险，或者认真对待幻觉而面临声誉风险。摩根大通银行已禁止使用 Chat <small>GPT</small> ，尽管它正在其他领域试验<small>人工智能</small>。</p><p class="article__body-text">其他企业根本不愿意尝试。处于生产率前沿的企业和生产率较低的企业之间的行为差​​异并不罕见。技术采用的滞后期可能会很长。例如，尽管互联网在 20 世纪 90 年代初就开始被企业使用，但直到 2000 年代末，美国甚至三分之二的企业才拥有网站。许多公司都有过时的系统（想想仍在使用<small>COBOL 的</small>日本银行），这使得采用尖端技术成为一项艰巨的任务。公共部门或公用事业等受到严格监管的行业的管理者可能感觉不到创新的动力。这些部门构成了经济体的很大一部分：在美国，它们总共占<small>国内生产总值</small>的四分之一。</p><p class="article__body-text">不情愿也可能源于工人。尽管这项技术有望消除苦差事，但一些人担心它最终可能会取代它们。咨询公司<small>BCG</small>的一项调查发现，与管理者或领导者相比，一线员工更有可能对生成<small>人工智能</small>感到担忧，但不太可能持乐观态度。在某些情况下，工会可能会采取行动减缓该技术的采用；有些人甚至可能会走到好莱坞编剧协会，该协会在 2023 年的大部分时间里都在罢工，部分原因是担心<small>人工智能</small>对就业的影响。</p><p class="article__body-text">那么，对<small>人工智能</small>感兴趣的老板应该如何看待这项技术呢？在决定是否成为热情的采用者，还是谨慎或不情愿的采用者之前，它有助于对所获得的收益以及使用仍然新颖且有风险的技术的成本进行清晰的评估。最重要的是，您的员工需要参与其中。因此，请关注他们的恐惧，并让他们相信实验的乐趣。 <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Rachana Shanbhogue，</small> <i>《经济学人》</i>商业事务编辑</p><p class="article__body-text"><em>本文发表在<a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">《2024 年未来世界》</a>印刷版的领导者部分，标题为“采用决定”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:41:18 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/b3o9ofs5j6i2j7ogc53n9g3m20lr7hmm</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/generative-ai-holds-much-promise-for-businesses </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don’t count on a soft landing for the world economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><small>一段</small>时间<span>以来，</span>世界经济似乎违反了地心引力。尽管实行了自 20 世纪 80 年代以来最快的货币政策紧缩，但美国的经济增长可能会在 2023 年加速。欧洲基本上已经摆脱了对俄罗斯天然气的依赖，没有发生经济灾难。全球通胀率有所下降，但失业率并未大幅上升，部分原因是迄今为止劳动力市场的降温主要是由于职位空缺的减少，而不是工作岗位本身。随着年底的到来，预测“软着陆”的乐观主义者正在取得胜利。</p><p class="article__body-text">然而，到2024年，世界经济仍将脆弱。尽管通胀率会较低，但仍将过高。经济政策仍然面临着令人痛苦的平衡问题。即使美国继续避免经济衰退，世界其他地区看起来也很脆弱。</p><div class="article__body-text-image"><figure> <span><meta><img src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/608/651/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/214/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/321/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/428/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/642/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/685/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/857/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/1071/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/1371/90/media-assets/image/20231118_TWLDC774.png 1280w" sizes="336px" alt></span></figure><p class="article__body-text">通货膨胀最近的下降让各国央行官员松了口气。但在富裕的大型经济体中，除非出现经济衰退，否则不太可能继续一路下滑至 2% 的目标。一方面，劳动力市场看起来仍然太热，名义工资增长太高。另一方面，经济将不得不应对石油价格上涨的影响。正当大流行时代和俄罗斯入侵乌克兰的供应冲击似乎已经消散、供应链畅通、经济重新平衡时，由于乌克兰减产，自夏季以来每桶石油的价格已上涨约三分之一。沙特阿拉伯和其他地方。哈马斯对以色列的袭击阻止了价格下跌。由此产生的汽油价格上涨可能会引发人们对“第二波”通胀的担忧。</p><p class="article__body-text">主要央行可能不会进一步加息，而是将石油驱动的通胀反弹视为暂时的。但由于担心过早宣布胜利，他们也不会热衷于降息。最近的证据表明，美国经济能够承受紧缩的货币，即使大公司为债务再融资，以及在大流行期间耗尽储蓄的家庭开始感到受到挤压。但高利率可能会让本已摇摇欲坠的欧元区经济陷入衰退，而对通胀的担忧可能会阻止其政策制定者降息。</p><p class="article__body-text">就连美国经济的强劲也带有一个大星号：它得到了高额政府借贷的支持。截至撰写本文时，联邦政府的赤字年增长率已超过<small>GDP</small>的 7%。关于利率是否已进入“长期较高”状态的争论十分激烈。答案取决于借贷热潮是否继续。它可能会：国会不会在总统选举年面对它。下一任白宫主人的首要任务将是延续唐纳德·特朗普 (Donald Trump) 2018 年的减税政策，其中许多减税政策将于 2025 年到期，甚至连民主党人也不愿让其完全失效。</p></div><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>主要央行可能不会进一步加息</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">没有政府自由借贷的经济体看起来更加脆弱。除了欧洲可能出现的衰退之外，世界经济也受到中国增长放缓的影响。中国能否反弹并摆脱“日本化”将取决于政府继续打开刺激水龙头的程度。但最近中国经济政策制定的恶化——从结束零新冠疫情到科技打击——表明期望出台精心调整的刺激措施是不明智的。由于地方政府负债累累，中国面临着财政紧缩。</p><p class="article__body-text">与此同时，中美地缘政治紧张局势逐渐恶化，全球保护主义浪潮不断涌现，给贸易带来了阻碍。根据慈善机构“全球贸易警报”的数据，已实施的保护主义措施数量从十年前的约 9,000 项增加到如今的约 35,000 项。尽管亚洲一些经济体受益于供应链转移到中国以外的地区，但重复投资和专业化收益的损失正在影响全球经济的潜在增长。即使是像快速增长的印度这样的赢家，也表现出了令人担忧的本土经济倾向。</p><p class="article__body-text">无法从投资再分配中受益的贫穷国家正遭受高负债、低增长和强势美元的困扰。 2024年，<small>国际货币基金组织</small>将继续努力研究如何向对中国和其他不遵守传统债务重组原则的债权人负债累累的国家提供债务减免。如果美国的赤字继续推动其经济发展，而全球经济增长令人失望，那么预计美元将进一步升值，从而加剧他们的困境。</p><p class="article__body-text">特朗普连任白宫的可能性使所有这些趋势都有可能被放大。特朗普的第二个任期可能意味着更大幅度的减税——从而导致更大的赤字——以及贸易战的进一步升级。与 2016 年一样，如果特朗普在 11 月获胜，股市可能会上涨，但这并不是什么好消息。到 2024 年底，全球经济可能不再像软着陆，而更像是另一场疯狂之旅的开始。 <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Henry Curr，</small> <i>《经济学人》</i>经济学编辑</p><p class="article__body-text"><em>本文发表在<a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">《2024 年世界展望</a>》印刷版的领导者部分，标题为“软着陆？别指望它”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:40:39 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/3dm5p2u1e5i7tqbb05j4335ne9q8o29r</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/dont-count-on-a-soft-landing-for-the-world-economy </item><item><title><![CDATA[America will need a new vocabulary to discuss its presidential election]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>如果</span><small>没有不可预见的</small>疾病或死亡，2024 年总统选举将是乔·拜登和唐纳德·特朗普之间的重赛。这将在 2024 年的政党初选中得到证实，该初选将比平常早得多完成。通常情况下，现任总统会在不经过太多斗争的情况下被选为本党的提名人。在民主党方面，这种情况将会再次发生。但共和党方面的情况会奇怪得多，其中一位候选人已经遥遥领先，以至于他能够跳过早期的辩论。</p><p class="article__body-text">在典型的初选周期中，美国人必须等到三月底或更长时间才能知道挑战者可能是谁。这次共和党初选实际上可能会在二月底结束。随后，美国将面临两位不受欢迎的候选人之间长达八个月的大选竞选，而美国在全球的盟友则屏住呼吸。</p><p class="article__body-text">如果初选的相关性不如平时，那么参与政治的美国人（特别是那些不希望看到特朗普第二次担任总统的人）的注意力将从候选人特朗普转移到被告特朗普。这位前总统因试图推翻 2020 年选举而受到的联邦审判将于 3 月 4 日开始，即“超级星期二”的前一天，届时 13 个州将在共和党初选中投票。</p><p class="article__body-text">他的竞选团队将利用这个时机，将针对特朗普的案件描绘成左翼阴谋，以阻止他赢得连任，并邀请他的支持者投票给他（并向他的法律基金捐款），以此作为一种反抗行为。特朗普最喜欢的政治技巧之一就是对他所受到的任何指控进行反驳。因此，虽然他实际上因破坏美国民主而在联邦法院受审，但他会声称对民主自由的真正威胁是联邦法院。</p><p class="article__body-text">候选人的加冕仪式将在密尔沃基举行，共和党将在 7 月举行全国代表大会，而民主党将在 8 月在芝加哥举行大会，为拜登先生的四年任期加冕（届时他们的候选人将年满 85 岁）。岁）。地点的选择再次提醒人们，中西部在选举年的重要性，以及总统竞选在某种程度上并不是真正的全国选举。</p><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>对于美国和世界来说，这一结果的重要性怎么强调都不为过</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">如果投票结果很接近，就像现在大多数总统选举一样，那么结果将取决于六个州的情况：亚利桑那州、佐治亚州、密歇根州、内华达州、宾夕法尼亚州和威斯康星州。这意味着总人口为 5000 万（略多于西班牙，但少于意大利）的国家将选出下一任总统。任何一个方向的更大摇摆都可能会让更多的州参与其中：明尼苏达州、新罕布什尔州、北卡罗来纳州，甚至佛罗里达州。</p><p class="article__body-text">针对特朗普的联邦案件不太可能在 11 月 5 日（选举日）之前提起诉讼，因为特朗普的法律策略将是推迟，然后上诉。因此，美国将首次出现一位被指控犯有联邦和州罪行的总统候选人。特朗普第一任期结束时，“未知”和“史无前例”等词已经过时了。美国这次选举将需要新的。</p><p class="article__body-text">很难夸大这一结果对美国和世界其他国家的重要性。美国的下一任总统将面临一些可预见的问题。支付社会保障和医疗保险（养老金领取者的医疗保健）费用的信托基金已经快没钱了。伊朗和朝鲜的核扩散问题将再次成为焦点。还有迫在眉睫的台湾问题。西方的中国观察人士认为，在下届总统任期内，有一个狭窄的窗口期，在此期间，人民解放军将在岛屿冲突中占据优势。因此，2024 年选出的总统将在最危险的时刻掌权。</p><p class="article__body-text">然而，大多数危机都是出乎意料的。 2016年，特朗普在竞选时主张结束美国在中东的纠葛。不到一年后，他下令向叙利亚境内的目标发射59枚“战斧”巡航导弹。他总统任期的最后一年因对新病毒传播处理不当而度过。拜登的总统任期更加稳定、更加成功，但最需要他关注的主题——阿富汗撤军失败、乌克兰入侵俄罗斯以及以色列和哈马斯之间的战争——却是不可预见的。</p><p class="article__body-text">然而，特朗普第二次获胜，可以预见的是，情况将会很糟糕。将在未来 12 个月内制定计划，为他的政府配备真正的信徒。完整的效果是难以想象的。这对外交政策或应对气候变化的行动意味着什么？其他国家会效仿巴西2018年的做法，再次选举民族主义民粹主义者吗？</p><p class="article__body-text">对于美国来说，问题更大。如果特朗普再次当选一位像特朗普那样执政、曾两次被众议院弹劾、并试图推翻上次选举结果的人，这对国家的民主意味着什么？ <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"><small>约翰·普里多 (John Prideaux)，</small> <i>《经济学人》</i>美国编辑</p><p class="article__body-text"><em>本文发表在<a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">《2024 年未来世界》</a>印刷版的领导者部分，标题为“史无前例、未知、并非不可想象”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:39:56 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/a44n116rvt3kqsukr8ndpaqpicdi05rd</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/america-will-need-a-new-vocabulary-to-discuss-its-presidential-election </item><item><title><![CDATA[Europe needs to step up support for Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>显而易见</span><small>的</small>是，除非最后一刻出现奇迹，否则乌克兰的反攻——曾经不仅在基辅而且在整个西方带来如此多乐观情绪的源泉——在 2023 年失败了——而且惨重。经过五个月的血腥和昂贵的努力，到 11 月初，结果却微乎其微。没有占领任何主要城镇，仅解放了约 400 平方公里（154 平方英里）的领土，不到乌克兰总土地面积的 0.1%。俄罗斯仍占据乌克兰约18%的领土，其中约一半是在2014年吞并克里米亚并占领顿巴斯东部时占领的；其余的是 2022 年 2 月入侵后所占领领土的剩余部分。</p><p class="article__body-text">所有这一切都预示着一场漫长而艰苦的消耗战，乌克兰的支持者必须为此做好准备。俄罗斯当然是。弗拉基米尔·普京的战略依赖于等待西方厌倦了日益看似无限期的承诺。长期的战争可以发挥他的优势。作为一个逐渐压制异见的残暴独裁者，他不太担心公众舆论。尽管伤亡惨重，俄罗斯人却没有表现出任何反对战争的迹象，部分原因是高油价削弱了西方制裁的效果。俄罗斯将血腥地坚持下去。但在欧洲，尤其是在美国，选民和政策制定者将厌倦这一负担的危险迫在眉睫。</p><p class="article__body-text">现在看来，反攻的承诺太多了，而对长期战争的准备却太少。这种情况必须改变。乌克兰和俄罗斯都没有兴趣实现让当地局势看起来像现在这样的和平。对于乌克兰来说，允许俄罗斯保住其占领的领土是不可接受的，尤其是因为失去大部分南部海岸的经济影响。但对俄罗斯来说，这次入侵看起来仍然是失败的，因为它没有完全控制 2022 年 9 月吞并的四个省份中的任何一个。因此，不要指望任何一方会在 2024 年试图解决问题。</p><p class="article__body-cite"><cite>欧洲也可以通过加快乌克兰与欧盟的一体化来提供帮助</cite></p><p class="article__body-text">这一新的现实需要新的政策，尤其是欧洲领导人的政策，他们必须明白，支持乌克兰的任务正在迅速交给他们。尽管美国一开始是乌克兰的主要武器供应国，但欧洲在2023年加大了支持力度，到7月31日已微弱超过美国，成为乌克兰最大的累计军事援助供应国。然而，它是通过消耗自己的坦克、弹药和导弹储备来做到这一点的。如果不对国防采购进行进一步的大规模投资，欧洲将无法保持这一步伐。尽管承包商可以提高现有设施的产量，但这还不够。为了让他们投资新设施，他们需要政府做出重大的、多年的承诺。</p><p class="article__body-text">这个故事更好地讲的是非军事承诺，特别是为帮助乌克兰弥补因军费开支增加和饱受战争蹂躏的税收收入造成的巨额预算赤字而提供的资金。 6 月，<small>欧盟</small>承诺在 2024-27 年向乌克兰额外提供 500 亿欧元（合 530 亿美元）的财政援助。这使得欧洲承诺的援助总额远远高于美国。 According to the Kiel Institute for the World Economy, America&#39;s commitments by the end of July amounted to $69bn, against $155bn for the Europeans (the <small>EU</small> plus Britain, Norway and Switzerland). But Ukraine&#39;s budget deficit, of roughly 20% of <small>GDP</small> , means that it needs something like $42bn every year to stay afloat. Then there is reconstruction on top of that. Accordingly, €50bn over four years is not enough. European governments can easily afford to do better. But will they want to?</p><p class="article__body-text"> The fact is that America can no longer be depended upon to lead this fight. The new speaker of the House of Representatives, Mike Johnson, began his term by blocking President Joe Biden&#39;s attempt to get authorisation for a fresh package of $61bn in military support for Ukraine (though Mr Johnson has also said that he does not want to see Mr Putin prevail). Donald Trump is an even bigger mystery, having often contradicted himself over Ukraine, as with so much else. Mr Biden, who has done an excellent job of backing Ukraine so far, may find the politics of fighting the Republicans over it too difficult as the election in November nears. All <small>G</small> 7 countries agreed to produce bilateral security guarantees for Ukraine, but none has yet done so.<br></p><p class="article__body-text"> So Europe will, like it or not, have to step up and take on more responsibility for supporting Ukraine. That means providing more cash as direct financial assistance, but also investing much more heavily in military kit so that Europe can arm Ukraine without leaving itself defenceless. It can also help by speeding up Ukraine&#39;s integration with the <small>EU</small> itself. It was formally accepted as a candidate in June 2022, but formal accession talks have still not started. At their summit in December 2023, the <small>EU</small> ’s leaders should give the green light to the start of detailed negotiations, while also making it clear that these must not be allowed to drag on for years. Bound into the huge European economy, Ukraine has a far better chance of holding the line against Russia—and outlasting Mr Putin. <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>CHRISTOPHER LOCKWOOD,</small> Europe editor, <i>The Economist</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <em>This article appeared in the Leaders section of the print edition of <a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">The World Ahead 2024</a> under the headline “Time for Europe to step up”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:39:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/3opekhdk5ojfdj7h9gq8pf7qvena9h64</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/europe-needs-to-step-up-support-for-ukraine </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don’t give up on peace in the Middle East]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>I</span> <small>F 2023 was</small> the year when the Palestinian conflict shook the Middle East, 2024 will be the year when it starts to become clear whether the Middle East can shake the Palestinian conflict. Terrible as it is to write after so much death, the region has not had a better chance of peace in two decades. Unfortunately, neither has the Palestinian conflict had a greater chance of spiralling out of control. Which will it be?</p><p class="article__body-text"> Hamas&#39;s murder of 1,400 Israelis will bring change in 2024 because it destroyed the strategic concept that had allowed Israel and much of the Arab world to ignore the Palestinians&#39; plight. No longer can anyone pretend that a mix of financial incentives and Israeli air strikes can control Hamas. If Israel is to honour its founding promise to be a homeland where Jews are safe, it needs a new approach.</p><p class="article__body-text"> The attack will also produce new leaders on both sides. Israel&#39;s military and intelligence chiefs will resign when the war is over. And its prime minister, Binyamin Netanyahu, will be forced from office. Not only did this catastrophe take place when he was in charge, but his political brand as Israel&#39;s staunch defender lies in ruins. Meanwhile, Hamas&#39;s leaders are likely to be killed by Israeli forces, and their counterparts in the Palestinian Authority ( <small>PA</small> ) in the West Bank could end up being driven from power. New leaders bring change, too.</p><p class="article__body-text"> A number of things could conspire to make this a change for the worse. One is the war itself. Israeli forces are killing thousands upon thousands of Palestinians, including many women and children. Hamas cannot defeat Israel, but it does not need to. Amid the understandable fury this is causing in the Arab world and beyond, just surviving would mean that Hamas emerges stronger in the eyes of Palestinians. If Israel loses international support, it may be forced to stop fighting sooner than it is ready. If Palestinians are radicalised, Hamas could rise from the ashes to become a symbol of resistance.</p><p class="article__body-cite"> <cite>Hamas&#39;s attack destroyed the notion that the Palestinians&#39; plight could be ignored</cite></p><p class="article__body-text"> Another danger is that the violence spreads. Hizbullah, an Iranian-backed militia, could open a second front in the north, across the border with Lebanon. More likely is popular unrest in the West Bank, where Hamas has recently been working to increase its influence, and where young Palestinians have lost faith in the <small>PA</small> and its do-nothing, election-avoiding president, Mahmoud Abbas.</p><p class="article__body-text"> If Hamas retains control of Gaza, and the West Bank is in flames, Israel will not be safe. It will strike Gaza repeatedly, whenever Hamas seems a threat, lest another attack take place. No Palestinian leader will be in a position to talk to it, even if they wished to. The Arab world, whose backing is vital for peace, will want to keep its distance. The Holy Land will be in a state of permanent semi-war.</p><p class="article__body-text"> However, that does not have to be the outcome. The operation to destroy Hamas and its tunnels could last several months. Imagine that at the end of it, Israel is satisfied that Hamas&#39;s rule over Gaza has been broken. Imagine that ordinary Palestinians will contemplate the idea of living beside Israel in peace. And imagine that even as the presidential campaign in America enters its final months, the Biden administration still has the drive and focus to undertake active diplomacy. There is a slender chance of all these things falling into place, but if they do, a delicate transition may begin.</p><p class="article__body-text"> It starts in the Palestinian territories, with leaders who can combine legitimacy at the ballot box with an acceptance of Israel&#39;s right to exist. Only that combination will produce a partner with whom Israel can cautiously begin to build trust. At the moment, while Palestinians are seething with anger at Israel&#39;s assault in Gaza, no such leader is available. But although Mr Abbas has engineered it so that he has no rivals today, successors may appear once he has gone.</p><p class="article__body-text"> New leaders in Israel will have almost as daunting a task. Not only must they win over traumatised Israelis to the idea of making peace, but they must also confront the settler movement which was never so powerful as under Mr Netanyahu&#39;s last government. For as long as settlers are killing Palestinians in the West Bank, peace will remain out of reach.</p><p class="article__body-text"> It will be just as hard to create the security needed in Israel and the Palestinian territories to allow peace to take root. In the past those who wished to destroy peace were able to use violence to discredit moderate voices within their respective camps.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Nowhere is this problem harder than in Gaza. An Israeli occupation would only radicalise the Palestinians there. Some imagine an Arab peacekeeping force, perhaps of armed police rather than troops. The Arab countries that now have closer relations with Israel than they did in the past, through the Abraham accords, may help. But they will take a lot of persuading.</p><p class="article__body-text"> The Middle East is the graveyard of plans for peace. It is a harsh and violent part of the world. But in 2024 you should cling to one hope. After two decades of stagnation ended on October 7th with terrible violence, the pursuit of peace is the only fresh idea left. <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>EDWARD CARR</small> , Deputy editor, <i>The Economist</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <em>This article appeared in the Leaders section of the print edition of <a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">The World Ahead 2024</a> under the headline “Don&#39;t give up on peace in the Middle East”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:38:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/le7ob2473ops9lf5j6ad0svg57cbkfla</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/dont-give-up-on-peace-in-the-middle-east </item><item><title><![CDATA[The world must try to break a vicious cycle of insecurity]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>A</span> <small>S 2023 drew</small> to a close, wars were raging in Africa, Israel and Gaza, and Ukraine. These crises are explosive in their own right. Combine them with a presidential race in America and 2024 promises to be a make-or-break year for the post-1945 world order.</p><p class="article__body-text"> The 2020s were destined to be dangerous. The West&#39;s share of world <small>GDP</small> has fallen towards 50% for the first time since the 19th century. Countries such as India and Turkey believe the global institutions created after 1945 do not reflect their concerns. China and Russia want to go further and subvert this system. Though America&#39;s economy is still pre-eminent, its unipolar moment has ended. Allies in Europe and Japan are in relative economic decline. There is tepid support among the middle class for America&#39;s global role, and an isolationist tilt in the Republican Party.</p><p class="article__body-text"> At the start of 2023 America was busy adapting to this reality, implementing the Biden administration&#39;s foreign policy. The idea was to be a more selective, even selfish, superpower. Prioritisation had meant quitting Afghanistan and shifting resources to Asia to counter China. Alliances were rejuvenated in the Pacific and in Europe, where <small>NATO</small> was expanded and Ukraine kept afloat. Energy and tech embargoes were used to weaken adversaries, at little cost to the West. Domestic industrial subsidies, though inefficient, were potent: in mid-2023 American factory construction hit its highest rate since the 1950s.</p><p class="article__body-text"> By some yardsticks—oil and grain prices, Western combat casualties—geopolitical risk is tolerable. Yet the new dynamic is one of instability. In the 1990s many countries aspired to a self-reinforcing cycle of freedom, market economics and rules-based globalisation. Now there is an unpredictable cycle of populism, interventionist economics and transactional globalisation. As a result, three threats loom in 2024.</p><p class="article__body-cite"> <cite>The final threat is the fragility of the Western coalition</cite></p><p class="article__body-text"> First, there is a growing zone of impunity where neither global powers nor global institutions tread. You can walk 6,000km from the Red Sea to the Atlantic through six African countries that have faced coups in the past 36 months. Azerbaijan has just fought a war against Armenia involving ethnic cleansing, without much blowback. Iran&#39;s proxies thrive in failing states across the Middle East. In 2024 this zone of impunity could expand further across Africa and Russia&#39;s flanks.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Second, a trio of trouble is emerging featuring China, Iran and Russia. They have much less in common than Western allies do, and China is far larger and more integrated into the world economy than the others. But their interests intersect: all want to undermine American legitimacy and to evade actual or potential sanctions. China buys Russian and Iranian oil. None has condemned Hamas or the invasion of Ukraine. Their collaboration is likely to expand into tech. China is pioneering ways to bypass Western finance: half of its trade is now in yuan. Iran exports drones to Russia; China and Russia collaborate on nuclear-warning systems and patrols in the Pacific. In 2024 the world will learn how far this nascent club might go.</p><p class="article__body-text"> The final threat is the fragility of the Western coalition. The response to Ukraine&#39;s invasion was exhilarating: America and Europe united, public opinion was supportive and the principles of the 1945 order were defended, even if non-Western countries were not fully onboard. Now, with a military stalemate, cracks are showing. In America, Republicans are divided over funding for Ukraine. Israel&#39;s invasion of Gaza is even more divisive: it has split the <small>EU</small> and America, which has vetoed a <small>UN</small> ceasefire resolution, fuelling claims of double standards and Western illegitimacy. Other crises could expose more splits: would Europe join America in fighting to defend Taiwan?</p><p class="article__body-text"> How these threats play out in 2024 partly depends on the performance of the West&#39;s autocratic competitors. Just as the very different regimes of China, Iran and Russia share some interests, they have some similar vulnerabilities. All face economic difficulties and rely on intensifying repression. Vladimir Putin faced a mutiny in 2023; Ayatollah Ali Khamenei is 84 and has no clear successor; Xi Jinping relies on purges. All this could sap their vitality and their claim to have a rival model that others should emulate.</p><p class="article__body-text"> But America&#39;s election is key. An isolationist president would not drop treaties overnight but will be tested quickly: think of China “inspecting” Taiwanese ships or Russia “reinterpreting” borders. If America&#39;s commitment falters, Europe will soldier on in Ukraine but will struggle to provide funding or military muscle. Asian allies will placate China and bolster their defences. Middle powers such as South Korea and Saudi Arabia may seek nuclear weapons.</p><p class="article__body-text"> If America elects an internationalist at the end of 2024, much of the world will breathe a sigh of relief. But America faces a long slog to stabilise and then renew a system of international trade and security. The to-do list includes European enlargement; deepening co-operation with India; and a two-state solution between Israel and the Palestinians. Perhaps one day historians will talk of the post-2025 order. <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Patrick Foulis,</small> Foreign editor, <i>The Economist</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <em>This article appeared in the Leaders section of the print edition of <a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">The World Ahead 2024</a> under the headline “Multipolar disorder”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:37:41 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/1sjs0atb9a2eqe5imsku4ls79k7vmtq4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/the-world-must-try-to-break-a-vicious-cycle-of-insecurity </item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 will be stressful for those who care about liberal democracy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-hu1ce2 e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>M</span> <small>ore than</small> half the people on the planet live in countries that will hold nationwide elections in 2024, the first time this milestone has been reached. Based on recent patterns of voter turnout, close to 2bn people in more than 70 countries will head to the polls. Ballots will be cast from Britain to Bangladesh, from India to Indonesia. Yet what sounds like it should be a triumphant year for democracy will be the opposite.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Many elections will entrench illiberal rulers. Others will reward the corrupt and incompetent. By far the most important contest, America&#39;s presidential election, will be so poisonous and polarising that it will cast a pall over global politics. Against a backdrop of conflict, from Ukraine to the Middle East, America&#39;s future direction—and with it the world order American leadership has hitherto underwritten—will be on the line. It will be a nerve-racking and dangerous year.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Some elections will be obvious shams. In Belarus or Rwanda, for instance, the only question is how close to 100% the incumbent&#39;s vote-share will be. Having illegally changed the constitution to remove term limits in 2020, Vladimir Putin will doubtless win a third consecutive term (and fifth overall) as Russia&#39;s president.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Most ballots cast will be in Asia. Its biggest democracies—Bangladesh, India and Indonesia—will all go to the polls. Unfortunately, the danger is of growing illiberalism. Under Narendra Modi, India is enjoying remarkable economic and geopolitical success, even as the prime minister condones anti-Muslim chauvinism and a dismantling of institutional safeguards. Indonesia&#39;s president, Joko Widodo, seems focused on entrenching a political dynasty. Bangladesh has already taken an authoritarian turn, with opposition leaders jailed and no dissent brooked.</p><p class="article__body-cite"> <cite>America&#39;s poisonous and polarising election will cast a pall over global politics</cite></p><p class="article__body-text"> Africa will be the continent with the most elections, but its voters are increasingly disillusioned with how democracy works. Coups are becoming more common: nine regimes have seized power by force since 2020. Polls suggest that growing numbers of Africans might be willing to go along with a military government. South Africa&#39;s election will be a reminder of serial disappointment. Three decades after the <small>ANC</small> swept to power in the first post-apartheid election, it will limp to power again in a country ground down by corruption, crime and unemployment.</p><p class="article__body-text"> The news is not all bad. Mexico will elect its first female president: both leading contenders are women, and less populist than the incumbent. British voters will (at last) have a choice between two competent candidates. After 14 years of Tory rule a Labour win is likely, but few outside Britain will notice much change.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Some elections will have a disproportionate impact beyond their country&#39;s borders. Whether Taiwan&#39;s 18m voters plump for the incumbent Democratic Progressive Party or the Kuomintang ( <small>KMT</small> ), the more China-friendly opposition, will affect relations across the Taiwan Strait and, as a result, the level of <small>US</small> -China tensions. In the short term a <small>KMT</small> victory might reduce the odds of conflict. But in the medium term Taiwanese complacency might later increase the risk of Chinese adventurism and, potentially, a great-power clash.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Nothing, however, will compare to America&#39;s election, either for grim spectacle or potential consequences. It is hard to believe the most likely outcome is a rematch between two old men, both of whom the majority of voters wish were not candidates.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Donald Trump&#39;s very candidacy undermines American democracy. That the Republican Party would nominate a man who tried to overturn the results of the previous presidential election dims America as a democratic beacon. A second Trump term would transform America into a loose cannon with isolationist tendencies at a time of grave geopolitical peril. His fondness for strongmen, particularly Mr Putin, suggests that his boast to end the Russia-Ukraine conflict in 24 hours would be at Ukraine&#39;s expense.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Mr Trump may not become the nominee, and if he does, he may well lose. But the odds of a second Trump term are alarmingly high. The consequences could be catastrophic—for democracy and for the world. <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"> <small>Zanny Minton Beddoes,</small> Editor-in-chief, <i>The Economist</i></p><p class="article__body-text"> <em>This article appeared in the Leaders section of the print edition of <a href="/the-world-ahead-2024">The World Ahead 2024</a> under the headline “Democracy in danger”</em></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:37:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/csj95qmofjiduflma3og1hovqrjcbbjd</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-world-ahead/2023/11/13/2024-will-be-stressful-for-those-who-care-about-liberal-democracy </item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s power, America’s rise in STIs, AI and stardom, and spicy-chicken wars]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap">朗读最新一期<i>《经济学人》</i>中<span>精选</span><small>的</small>四篇重要文章。本周，我们在世界大部分地区的封面故事提出这样的问题：<a href="/leaders/2023/11/09/how-scary-is-china">中国</a>有多可怕？此外，我们还调查了<a href="/united-states/2023/11/09/why-sexually-transmitted-infections-are-rising-in-america">美国性传播感染为何呈上升趋势</a>(11:15)。我们在欧洲和英国的封面故事思考<a href="/leaders/2023/11/09/how-artificial-intelligence-will-transform-fame">人工智能将如何改变名誉</a>(15:35)。另外，南非的<a href="/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/09/the-battle-over-south-africas-spicy-chicken-market">辣鸡大战</a>(24:05)。片长：29分钟</p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomisteditorspicks/e/6550421e0d6c960012e3f71c/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJUaGVFY29ub21pc3QiLCJ0ayI6IlM4WlVYa3pEIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwcml2YXRlIn0=&sig=s79p7-p-u6SFF1s8zIKwhs218teMH1NaMb-6VbRDowo"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text"><i>这是仅限订阅者观看的一集。要收听，请注册<a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Deditors-picks">免费试用</a>《经济学人播客+》</i></p><p class="article__body-text"><i>如果您已经是《经济学人》的订阅者，作为订阅的一部分，您可以完全访问我们所有的节目。有关如何访问《经济学人播客+》的更多信息，请访问我们的<a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">常见问题解答页面</a>或观看我们解释如何链接您的帐户的<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">视频</a>。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:15:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/r5rq2ptd2u1oal8mop0mnbi7t4e3v1fh</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/13/chinas-power-americas-rise-in-stis-ai-and-stardom-and-spicy-chicken-wars </item><item><title><![CDATA[As Israel fights on in Gaza its dilemma gets worse]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">内盖夫沙漠军事基地边缘的一个帐篷上有<span>一个</span><small>大屏幕</small>。数十个蓝色方块代表以色列地面部队，距离加沙城东北20公里。在以色列国防军（ <small>IDF</small> ）一个步兵旅的总部内，作战官员从远处协调哈马斯隧道的搜索和摧毁任务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在加沙地带发动地面攻势两周后，以色列在该地区部署了大约 4 个师（约 10,000 名士兵）。一些石柱正在进入加沙市中心。其他人则在偏远城镇开展业务，这些城镇现在大多空无一人，他们挨家挨户寻找更多的隧道开口。 “这将是我们尽可能摧毁哈马斯地下网络的唯一机会，”一名军官说，他指的是该组织长达 500 公里的隧道系统。 “我们不知道我们还要运营多久，但我们需要尽可能地充分利用它。”</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">阅读我们对以色列和哈马斯之间战争的所有报道</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">西方对以色列行动的支持正在动摇。 11 月 10 日，法国总统埃马纽埃尔·马克龙 (Emmanuel Macron) 呼吁加沙停火，并表示，尽管他支持以色列对 10 月 7 日哈马斯恐怖袭击作出反应的权利，但“事实上，有婴儿、有女士、有老人被炸死” 。这没有任何理由，也没有合法性。”但以色列最亲密的盟友美国尚未<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/07/will-america-pull-the-plug-on-israels-invasion-of-gaza">要求停火</a>，因此<small>以色列国防军</small>正在抓紧时间。然而，以色列军队在其行动中已经达到了一个阶段，以色列政府的既定目标——摧毁哈马斯的军事基础设施并营救仍被扣押在加沙的239名人质——变得越来越紧张。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最近几天，人们的注意力集中在加沙中部的医院，尤其是最大的希法医院。这些地区不仅聚集了伤员，还聚集了留在城内、在他们周围避难的数千名平民。阿赫利医院的一名医生表示，该医院的血液供应已于 11 月 12 日耗尽，导致患者无法输血。以色列情报部门认为，这些医院也是哈马斯主要地下总部所在地。希法医院的工作人员指责以色列向他们开枪，并切断医院的电力，导致患者死亡。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 11 月 12 日，<small>以色列国防军</small>宣布，正在为平民开辟一条逃离 al-Shifa 和另外两家医院的逃生路线，这将使他们能够到达通往以色列边界以南的道路。以色列官员表示，对据称是哈马斯总部的医院发动最后攻击的命令尚未来自总理内塔尼亚胡领导的战时内阁。但就在同一天，美国国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文在承认“公开信息”指出哈马斯利用医院作为武器储藏处和指挥所的同时，对哥伦比亚广播公司新闻表示，美国“不希望看到医院发生交火”无辜的人和接受医疗的病人都陷入了交火之中。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">内阁不愿的主要原因是希望与哈马斯就释放大量人质达成协议；以色列至少坚持了一百年。作为回报，以色列将释放一些巴勒斯坦囚犯（其中监狱关押着 4,450 人），并允许更多物资（包括燃料）进入加沙。卡塔尔和埃及正在就任何类型的协议进行间接谈判，但最终的决定将由加沙哈马斯领导人叶海亚·辛瓦尔（Yahya Sinwar）做出，他是以色列的首要目标。目前尚不清楚任何协议是否会推迟<small>以色列国防军</small>摧毁医院附近或下方哈马斯设施的企图；似乎不太可能放弃它。随着紧张谈判的继续，以色列正试图敦促加沙城内剩余的平民（据信人数约为10万）尽可能多地前往南部。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但以色列政府拒绝承诺巴勒斯坦人在战后对加沙进行任何形式的控制，这也削弱了国际社会对其行动的支持。极右翼联盟成员一直呼吁以色列重新占领加沙并重建以色列于 2005 年拆除的定居点。内塔尼亚胡先生否认有任何这样做的计划，但也坚称以色列应保留、发布-战争，“整体安全控制，包括每当我们想要消灭可能再次出现的恐怖分子时就介入的能力”。他还排除了巴勒斯坦权力机构（ <small>PA</small> ）回归的可能性，该权力机构在 2007 年的政变中被哈马斯推翻，称该机构“教育其孩子仇恨以色列、杀害以色列人、消灭以色列国”，并且其总统马哈茂德·阿巴斯“30天后仍然没有谴责这场可怕的大屠杀”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登政府已经明确表示，希望巴勒斯坦<small>权力机构</small>在战斗结束后控制加沙，并正在努力实现这样的未来。内塔尼亚胡的公众支持率一直在直线下降，他似乎更担心的是继续缩小自己日益萎缩的民族主义基础，而不是为哈马斯被赶下台后飞地的命运做好准备。然而，以色列官员已经在悄悄制定巴勒斯坦<small>权力机构</small>控制下的加沙计划，这表明他可能不会永远执政。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Sun, 12 Nov 2023 20:29:58 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/qct5e6imo8k7unvoqtjspdmgcgsh6uth</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/12/as-israel-fights-on-in-gaza-its-dilemma-gets-worse</item></channel></rss>