<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 25 日星期三 00:21:44 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Netanyahu’s handling of the hostage crisis enrages Israelis]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>九个月</small><span>来</span>，耶路撒冷的总统官邸一直是愤怒而喧闹的集会场所，每周六晚上，以色列人都会抗议政府<a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/07/24/a-blow-against-israels-supreme-court-plunges-the-country-into-crisis">削减最高法院权力的</a>计划。然而，10 月 22 日，艾萨克·赫尔佐格总统会见了确认在加沙被扣为人质的 220 名以色列人的亲属时，聚集在那里的数百人在基本静默的守夜中站了几个小时。 10 月 7 日<a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamass-attack-was-the-bloodiest-in-israels-history">哈马斯袭击</a>中被绑架的人大部分是平民。其中有婴儿和老人。会议结束后，当家人出来时，人群中传来“现在把他们带回家！”的低声呼喊声。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">了解有关以色列和哈马斯之间战争的更多信息</p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从表面上看，这是一种非政治的团结表现。但守夜活动也让人回想起之前的抗议活动以及战争前几个月分裂以色列的政治不和。许多反对政府司法改革的人现在支持人质。聚会开始时，一些人质问了一位著名记者，这位记者以强烈支持陷入困境的以色列总理本雅明·内塔尼亚胡而闻名。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">人质的困境是以色列人最关心的问题，这主要是一个人道主义问题。全国各地也举行了类似的守夜活动。人质的亲属定期接受电视和广播采访。但这个问题也具有深刻的政治意义。许多居住在遭受袭击的基布兹的人都是世俗的左倾人士。这些以色列人最有可能积极参与反对内塔尼亚胡政府的抗议活动，他们觉得内塔尼亚胡政府在 10 月 7 日抛弃了他们，而且仍然让他们失望。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">来自家人的压力已经迫使政府改变计划。尽管政府原本倾向于不顾人质安全冲入加沙，但政府此后宣布营救人质是“首要任务”。以色列推迟入侵加沙的原因之一是希望与哈马斯达成协议，释放至少部分人质。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，对于许多家庭来说，政府在将亲人接回家方面做得还远远不够。在特拉维夫市中心的一座办公楼里，距离国防部和以色列国防军总部不远，这些家庭设立了自己的总部，并配备了数百名志愿者。一个大型私人组织的成立是为了填补政府留下的空白。该组织将人质家属收到的有关人质的信息传递给当局，并让他们随时了解情况。每个家庭都分配了一个团队，以确保他们获得所需的支持。媒体顾问安排了以色列和国际媒体的采访。莫兰·斯特拉·亚奈 (Moran Stella Yanai) 的妹妹莉亚 (Leah) 说，这是因为家人有责任确保人质不被遗忘。在社交媒体上发布的一段视频中，可以看到她蜷缩在田野里，一名枪手站在她身边。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">新组织还包括与外国政府联络的前外交官团队。在阿拉伯世界拥有广泛联系的前以色列间谍头子正在担任谈判代表。以色列科技公司联合起来，梳理社交媒体上数千小时的视频，寻找人质的任何迹象，并追踪他们手机的信号。这并不是以色列俘虏家属第一次发起自己的运动并向政府施加压力，要求其采取行动。但它发生的速度比以往任何时候都快得多，而且规模也大得多。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些家庭的总部是由大卫·扎尔莫诺维奇 (David Zalmonovich) 建立的，他是一名律师，他 21 岁的侄子奥马尔·谢姆·托夫 (Omer Shem Tov) 在一次音乐节上被绑架。学生谢姆·托夫 (Shem Tov) 是一名学生，他在一段视频中看到他的纹身，显示一辆卡车在加沙运载人质。 “我们不会取代政府，”扎尔莫诺维奇先生煞费苦心地说。 “我们正在补充他们。”但其他许多亲戚则不太外交，有些人已经等待了一个多星期才与政府联系或收到政府的正式通知。 “我们从第一天起就明白，政府里没有人为我们工作，”希拉·阿尔巴格 (Shira Albag) 说。视频中可以看到她 18 岁的女儿莉莉 (Liri) 穿着血迹斑斑的睡衣在加沙被从吉普车里拖出来。 “相反，以色列公众是。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这是一些相关专家的共同观点。 “我们正在为这些家庭做政府的工作，因为人们对政府不信任，”一位一直在协调亲属和外国大使之间会面的以色列前外交官说。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不信任的原因之一是内塔尼亚胡先生因腐败审判和政府削弱法院的努力而心烦意乱，在任命人质和战俘事务国家协调员问题上犹豫了九个月，尽管当时有两名平民被关押在加沙。直到哈马斯发动袭击后，他才任命了盖尔·赫希(Gal Hirsch)。这位颇受争议的将军因在黎巴嫩战争期间的指挥受到批评而于2006年被迫辞职。此前，这一职位是由以色列情报部门的高级官员担任的，他们拥有与恐怖组织进行秘密交易的丰富经验，而赫希则缺乏这些经验。许多人认为他的主要资格是对总理的忠诚。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些家庭最痛苦的事情之一是几乎完全不知道人质的健康状况和他们被关押的条件。许多家庭仍不确定他们的亲人是否被杀害或被绑架。根据遇难者家属和以色列当局编制的名单，除了已知的 220 名人质外，还有大约 80 人失踪。数十具尸体仍在通过 DNA 进行鉴定，其中许多尸体已被肢解或烧毁，无法辨认。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 10 月 7 日的视频显示，至少在某些情况下，尸体被带入加沙，哈马斯声称扣押的一些人质已经死亡。增加不确定性的是以色列的评估，即伊斯兰圣战组织甚至犯罪组织等其他组织冲过哈马斯在边境围栏上开的洞来抓捕自己的人质。现在它们都是讨价还价的筹码：每组捕获者都有其价格。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">哈马斯迄今已释放四名女囚犯：两名美国以色列公民和两名以色列老人。美国通过哈马斯的卡塔尔支持者谈判释放了他们。他们的家人感到如释重负，但同时也夹杂着对仍被扣为人质的其他亲属的担忧，以及对以色列政府没有更多地参与确保他们获释的愤怒。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">家人的沮丧是可以理解的。任何处于战争状态的政府在寻找数百名失踪的平民和士兵、辨认尸体并不断向每个家庭通报最新情况方面都面临着同样的困难。即使对于像以色列这样在此类问题上拥有丰富经验的国家来说也是如此。但人质家人的痛苦加剧了许多以色列人的愤怒，因为他们认为政府向被哈马斯摧毁的社区和成千上万被迫离开家园的人提供救援行动缓慢且无能。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自袭击事件发生以来，反对内塔尼亚胡政府的运动已暂停所有反对内塔尼亚胡政府的示威活动。但这种喘息可能不会持续太久。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 19:29:34 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/adcph7rrui49s4i4fumd42gt9sv5hu0v</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/24/netanyahus-handling-of-the-hostage-crisis-enrages-israelis </item><item><title><![CDATA[The world wants to regulate AI, but does not quite know how]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>场地</span>将风景如画：伦敦北部一座 19 世纪的建筑堆，在第二次世界大战期间是<a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/07/18/alan-turing-a-computing-pioneer-will-feature-on-britains-ps50-notes">阿兰·图灵</a><small>、</small>他的密码破译团队和第一台可编程数字计算机的故乡。与会者将是由 100 名世界领导人和<a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2023/05/25/why-tech-giants-want-to-strangle-ai-with-red-tape">技术高管</a>组成的精英群体。他们将努力回答的问题是划时代的：如何确保<a href="https://www.economist.com/films/2023/09/14/can-ai-be-controlled">人工智能</a>既不会成为不受控制的渎职工具，也不会反人类。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">英国政府将于 11 月 1 日至 2 日在布莱奇利公园举办的“<small>人工智能</small>安全峰会”似乎注定要载入史册。有一天，这确实可能被视为全球权力掮客第一次坐下来认真讨论如何对待一项可能改变世界的技术。正如组织者之一乔纳森·布莱克（Jonathan Black）所观察到的那样，与气候变化等其他重大政策辩论相比，“人们有很多做某事的政治意愿，但尚不清楚做什么。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">控制<small>人工智能的</small>努力比比皆是。 10 月 25 日，布鲁塞尔谈判进入关键阶段，官员们努力在年底前敲定欧盟雄心勃勃的<small>人工智能</small>法案。在英国峰会前几天或此后不久，白宫预计将发布一项有关<small>人工智能</small>的行政命令。由富裕民主国家组成的<small>七国集团</small>俱乐部将于今年秋天开始起草<small>人工智能</small>公司的行为准则。 10月18日，中国发布了“全球人工智能治理倡议”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这一势头源于不寻常的政治经济。采取行动以及共同行动的动力是强大的。首先，<small>人工智能</small>确实是一项全球技术。大型语言模型 ( <small>LLM</small> ) 为 Chat <small>GPT</small>等极其人性化的服务提供支持，并且可以轻松传播。有些可以在笔记本电脑上运行。如果在其他国家仍然松动<small>人工智能</small>的螺丝，那么在某些国家拧紧人工智能的螺丝是没有多大用处的。选民可能会赞成。皮尤研究中心的民意调查显示，超过一半的美国人对<small>人工智能</small>的使用“更担心而不是兴奋”。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">北京效应</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">监管竞争加剧了紧迫性。欧洲<small>人工智能</small>法案的部分目的是巩固欧盟作为全球数字标准制定者的角色。白宫希望阻止这种“布鲁塞尔效应”的发生。无论是<small>欧盟</small>还是<small> </small>美国希望被中国超越，中国已经通过了多项<small>人工智能</small>法律。他们对英国政府邀请中国参加峰会感到愤怒——更不用说如果没有中国，任何监管制度都不会真正具有全球性。 （中国实际上可能会出现，即使它的利益不如共产党那样保护人类。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>人工智能</small>规则制定外交的另一个驱动力更令人惊讶：模型制定者本身。过去，科技行业大多反对监管。现在，Alphabet 和微软等巨头，以及创建了 Chat <small>GPT</small>的 Anthropic 和 Open <small>AI</small>等<small>人工智能</small>宠儿，都在为它游说。公司担心，无节制的竞争会促使他们鲁莽行事，发布容易被滥用的模型或开始发展自己的想法。这确实会让他们陷入困境。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">换句话说，行动的意愿就在那里。约翰·霍普金斯大学的亨利·法雷尔表示，“对于我们需要治理的问题是什么，更不用说我们应该如何治理这些问题，目前还没有达成共识”。三个争论很突出。世界应该担心什么？任何规则应该针对什么？又该如何执行？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从监管目标入手。这些很难设定，因为<small>人工智能</small>正在迅速发展。几乎每天都有初创公司推出新产品。即使是<small>法学硕士</small>的开发者也不能确定这些将展示什么能力。这使得进行能够衡量其风险程度的测试变得至关重要——这更像是艺术而不是科学。如果没有这样的“evals”（评估的缩写），就很难检查模型是否符合任何规则。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">科技公司可能支持监管，但希望监管范围更窄，并且只针对极端风险。 7 月在华盛顿举行的参议院听证会上，Anthropic 首席执行官达里奥·阿莫迪 (Dario Amodei) 警告称，<small>人工智能</small>模型将在几年内提供制造生物武器所需的所有信息，从而使“更多参与者能够实施大规模生物攻击” 。关于网络武器也有类似的可怕预测。本月早些时候，美国证券交易委员会主席加里·詹斯勒 (Gary Gensler) 预测，如果不迅速干预，人工智能引发的金融危机“几乎不可避免”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其他人则认为，这些投机风险分散了人们对其他威胁的注意力，例如破坏民主进程。在早些时候的参议院听证会上，著名的<small>人工智能</small>怀疑论者加里·马库斯 (Gary Marcus) 用 Open <small>AI</small>顶级模型<small>GPT</small> -4 编写的突发新闻片段作为他的证词。它令人信服地声称国会的部分部门“受到外星实体的秘密操纵”。马库斯先生表示：“我们都应该对能够流畅交谈的系统深感担忧。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">关于具体监管内容的争论并不容易解决。科技公司大多建议限制对最强大的“前沿”模型的审查。微软等公司呼吁建立许可制度，要求公司注册超过特定性能阈值的模型。其他提议包括控制用于训练<small>法学硕士</small>的强大芯片的销售，并要求云计算公司在客户训练前沿模型时通知当局。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">大多数公司也同意应该监管的是模型的应用，而不是模型本身。办公软件？轻触。医疗保健<small>人工智能</small>？严格的规则。公共场所面部识别？大概是没办法了。这种基于使用的监管的优点是现有法律基本上就足够了。<small>人工智能</small>开发人员警告说，更广泛、更具侵入性的规则将减慢创新速度。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">直到去年，美国、英国和<small>欧盟</small>似乎都同意这种基于风险的方法。自一年前 Chat <small>GPT</small>推出以来，<small>法学</small>硕士的惊人崛起让他们重新考虑。毕竟，<small>欧盟</small>现在想知道这些模型本身是否需要受到监督。欧洲议会希望模型制作者测试<small>法学硕士</small>对从人类健康到人权等各个方面的潜在影响。它坚持获取有关模型训练数据的信息。加拿大的议会工作中有一项强硬的《人工智能和数据法案》。巴西正在讨论类似的事情。在美国，总统乔·拜登即将发布的行政命令预计也将包括一些更严格的规则。甚至英国也可能会重新审视其不干涉的做法。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些更严格的监管将是对非约束性行为准则的改变，而迄今为止，非约束性行为准则一直是首选方法。去年夏天，白宫谈判达成了一系列“自愿承诺”，现已有 15 家模型制造商签署。两家公司同意在发布之前对其模型进行内部和外部测试，并分享有关如何管理<small>人工智能</small>风险的信息。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">那么接下来的问题就是谁来监管。美国和英国认为现有的政府机构可以完成大部分工作。<small>欧盟</small>希望建立一个新的监管机构。在国际上，一些科技高管现在呼吁建立类似于政府间气候变化专门委员会（ <small>IPCC</small> ）的机构，<small>联合国</small>的任务是及时了解气候变化的最新研究，并制定衡量其影响的方法。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">考虑到所有这些悬而未决的问题，伦敦峰会的组织者听起来并没有那么雄心勃勃也就不足为奇了。组织者布莱克表示，它主要应该被视为“一次对话”。尽管如此，一个不那么秘密的希望是它会产生一些切实的成果，特别是在第二天，当时会议室里只剩下 20 名左右最重要的企业和世界领导人。他们还可以认可白宫的自愿承诺，并建议成立<small>人工智能政府</small>间气候变化专门<small>委员会（IPCC）</small> ，甚至将英国现有的“前沿<small>人工智能</small>工作组”全球化。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这样的结果将被视为英国政府的成功。它还将加速全球<small>人工智能</small>治理方面的更多官方努力，例如<small>七国集团</small>的行为准则。因此，这将是有用的第一步。这不会是最后一次。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 19:12:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/06caciib1lcun0uahnp17169q4gv3m4n</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/10/24/the-world-wants-to-regulate-ai-but-does-not-quite-know-how </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can America handle two wars, and maybe a third?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>哈马斯</span>武装<small>分子</small>冲过加沙地带的安全围栏，造成 1,400 多人死亡，绑架约 220 人，三天后，美国最现代化的航空母舰<i>杰拉尔德·福特号</i>抵达地中海东部，其舰队随行军舰。由<i>艾森豪威尔号航空母舰</i>率领的第二支航母打击群正在驶往中东，可能是为了靠近伊朗。飞机和防空系统正在被派遣到该地区，部队也正在做好准备。</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">了解<a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">有关以色列和哈马斯之间战争的更多信息。</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这是美国在远离家乡部署军事力量的速度和规模的惊人展示。武力展示传递出两个信息。对伊朗及其代理人：不要插手。对以色列：你并不孤单。有迹象表明战争可能蔓延，美国军队可能仍会被命令采取行动。以色列正在为地面行动做准备；西岸的暴力活动正在加剧；以色列和与伊朗结盟的黎巴嫩什叶派民兵真主党之间的导弹和炮火交火预示着第二条战线的出现。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 10 月 22 日，美国国防部长劳埃德·奥斯汀警告称，针对美军的“局势可能会大幅升级”。三天前，一艘美国军舰在红海击落了也门与伊朗结盟的胡塞民兵针对以色列的巡航导弹和无人机。美国在伊拉克和叙利亚的基地也遭到火箭弹和无人机的袭击，这些火箭弹和无人机可能是由其他伊朗代理人发射的。华盛顿<small>特区</small>智库大西洋理事会的马修·克罗尼格表示，“这是自冷战以来最危险的时刻”。 “如果伊朗和真主党介入，美国可能会觉得有必要做出回应。那么中国是否会看到一个机会来尝试针对台湾的行动？”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，乔·拜登总统不太可能成为一位战时总统。当他在最近的一次电视讲话中告诉美国人世界正处于一个转折点时，他并没有夸大其词：“我们今天做出的决定将决定未来几十年的未来”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">去年，当美国采取行动帮助乌克兰抵抗俄罗斯的入侵时，许多人问美国是否有足够的资金来阻止中国迫在眉睫的对台湾的攻击。由于美国也在寻求保卫以色列，这个问题变得更加尖锐。在拜登看来，帮助朋友不仅是可能的，而且是必要的。 “美国的领导力是让世界团结在一起的力量，”他宣称。 “美国的联盟是保证我们美国安全的力量。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">疑虑依然存在。学术界争论冷战后美国横扫全球的“单极”世界是否以及何时恢复为“两极”世界，美国面临中国而不是苏联的挑战；或者是否已经是一个拥有多个权力中心的“多极”世界。哈佛大学学者约瑟夫·奈（Joseph Nye）从三个维度定义了国家实力：军事、经济和“软实力”，即拉拢他人听从自己命令的能力等。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC151.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">从军事角度来看，美国仍然是一个巨人（见图表）。根据斯德哥尔摩和平研究所的数据，按市场汇率计算，它占全球国防开支的 39%。在经济上，世界是冷战时期从未有过的两极格局，按市场汇率计算，中国的经济产出略低于美国，但按购买力平价计算，则超过美国（尽管美国人仍然比中国富裕得多）。克罗尼格表示，软实力更难衡量，但在这方面，世界变得更加多极化。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，在中东，美国仍然是“不可或缺的国家”，这一概念是由已故前国务卿马德琳·奥尔布赖特推广的。它是唯一愿意并且能够在地区领导人之间进行调解并塑造事件的国家。这包括确保在加沙开放一条（仍然不足的）人道主义走廊。 “北京的电话没有响。莫斯科的电话没有响。但华盛顿的电话却一直响个不停，”美国前驻<small>北约</small>代表伊沃·达尔德 (Ivo Daalder) 指出。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，与这一核心作用相悖的是，三位阿拉伯领导人——约旦国王阿卜杜拉、埃及总统阿卜杜勒-法塔赫·塞西和巴勒斯坦总统马哈茂德·阿巴斯——已经挂断了拜登的电话。总统原定于 10 月 18 日在访问以色列后在安曼会见他们。但一天前，加沙一家医院发生爆炸，造成数十名甚至数百名巴勒斯坦人死亡。巴勒斯坦人称大屠杀是由以色列的袭击造成的；以色列称这是巴勒斯坦导弹失误造成的。拜登似乎认为以色列是无辜的（后来更坚定地表示以色列不承担责任）。阿拉伯领导人却没有这样做。阿巴斯宣布哀悼三天并回国后，他们取消了峰会。就在那时，美国看起来就像是一个可有可无的大国。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">不是他要开始的地方</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登在任期间的首要任务是重振美国经济。他借鉴了前任唐纳德·特朗普的保护主义思维，并增加了大量补贴和产业政策，以促进绿色技术和半导体制造等。令人欣慰的是，美国经济的表现优于富裕国家。他希望此类政策能够减少助长民粹主义的社会和政治两极分化。他还希望他们能够在美国与中国日益加深的竞争中增强美国的实力。拜登的国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文将这个时代描述为“相互依存的竞争时代”，他表示，外交和国内政策比以往任何时候都更加相互关联，例如在努力实现供应链多元化和限制中国获得先进技术方面。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在国外，拜登还寻求重振特朗普忽视或威胁要撤销的联盟。他与俄罗斯续签了《新<small>削减战略</small>武器条约》，限制远程核武器，这是他与俄罗斯领导人弗拉基米尔·普京建立“稳定、可预测关系”的努力的一部分。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">改变焦点</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最重要的是，拜登的外交政策意味着在中东的行动要少得多，这个地区曾消耗了许多美国总统的精力。他寻求结束伊拉克和阿富汗的“永远的战争”。他承诺恢复与伊朗的核协议，以遏制伊朗拥有核武器的危险。巴拉克·奥巴马于 2015 年签署了该协议，而唐纳德·特朗普于 2018 年放弃了该协议。他最初表示沙特阿拉伯应该被视为“贱民”。他恢复了美国长期以来对“两国解决方案”的支持，即与以色列一起建立巴勒斯坦国，尽管他对此没有付出什么努力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些都没有成功。普京远非稳定和可预测的，他入侵了乌克兰，“新<small>起点”</small>下的信息交流被暂停。美国从阿富汗的混乱撤离使得塔利班立即重新掌权。与此同时，在海湾地区，中国对伊朗和沙特阿拉伯恢复外交关系表示欢迎，似乎填补了美国冷漠留下的真空。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登去年7月飞往沙特城市吉达与王储穆罕默德·本·萨勒曼会面。总统无法说服世界最大石油出口国的事实上的统治者帮助调节油价；相反，沙特阿拉伯坚持与俄罗斯达成生产协议，以保持高油价。此外，他为拜登希望实现的与以色列关系正常化设定了很高的标准：在巴勒斯坦问题上做出让步；与美国签订共同防御协议；以及在国内进行铀浓缩，以制衡伊朗的核计划。拜登团队经常会陷入善意的忽视。 “今天的中东地区比二十年来更加安静，”沙利文先生在哈马斯发起猛攻前几天宣称。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">华盛顿另一家智库美国企业研究所的科里·沙克表示，美国在世界各地的盟友，特别是亚洲的盟友，提出了两个看似矛盾的问题。第一，美国的资源和注意力是否会转移到中东？第二，美国解决一场或另一场危机的决心会失败吗？ “如果我们允许欧洲的安全因俄罗斯的侵略而不稳定，或者允许以色列遭受可怕的恐怖袭击，他们就会认为我们不关心任何其他问题，”她辩称。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">美国作为盟友的可靠性取决于信誉和能力。鉴于美国有众多盟友，学术界长期以来一直在争论信誉的重要性：未能履行对一个盟友的义务是否会影响对其他盟友的承诺？例如，美国放弃越南战争并没有太大损害其保卫西欧的意志。西方继续赢得冷战。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如今的问题是，美国从阿富汗的混乱撤离是否损害了美国的信誉并鼓励俄罗斯入侵乌克兰。前<small>北约</small>部队军事指挥官托德·沃尔特斯去年表示，这是几个因素之一。但沙利文坚称，事实上，离开阿富汗“提高了我们应对乌克兰入侵和台湾威胁的战略能力”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">至于军事能力，美国必须向乌克兰、台湾以及现在的以色列提供武器。这让人怀疑其国防工业是否能够满足他们以及自身的需求。总的来说，美国向这三个国家发送了不同的武器，但有些要求是重叠的。例如，155毫米炮弹供应短缺，据报道美国已将一批原本运往乌克兰的炮弹转移到以色列。乌克兰战争表明，大规模的国与国冲突会消耗大量弹药。兵棋推演表明，在台湾战争中，美国将很快耗尽远程反舰导弹，而这些导弹对于击退中国对台湾的入侵最为有用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这些问题可以通过时间和金钱来解决，但由于美国的两极分化和国会瘫痪，这两个问题都供不应求。共和党人，尤其是特朗普“美国优先”倾向的共和党人，对乌克兰战争越来越持怀疑态度。更重要的是，自从众议院议长凯文·麦卡锡被罢免后，国会一直无法通过法案。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登希望跨党派对以色列的同情能够解除障碍。他已要求国会提供 1060 亿美元的巨额补充国家安全支出。他试图通过向乌克兰拨款 610 亿美元的军事和经济援助来预防未来针对乌克兰的分裂性选票，以帮助其渡过美国火热的 2024 年选举季。为了使其更容易接受，他将其纳入了共和党人认为更有吸引力的其他支出中，其中包括为以色列提供 140 亿美元； 20亿美元用于印度-太平洋地区（可能是台湾）的军事装备转让；近120亿美元用于加强南部边境移民处理的各种措施； 30亿美元用于潜艇国防工业基地。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登表示：“哈马斯和普京代表着不同的威胁，但他们有一个共同点：他们都想彻底摧毁邻国的民主国家。”然而，以色列的战争在几个方面与乌克兰的不同。其中之一涉及国际看法。美国以《<small>联合国宪章</small>》、主权边界不可侵犯和人权的名义帮助乌克兰。在捍卫以色列的过程中，美国支持的国家违反了国际法，在被占领土上建立犹太人定居点，拒绝巴勒斯坦人建国，并被指控在轰炸和围困加沙时对巴勒斯坦人实施集体惩罚，即使没有犯下战争罪。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管西方盟国在保卫乌克兰方面几乎团结一致，但在巴勒斯坦问题上却存在分歧。<small>联合国</small>安理会一项呼吁在加沙战斗中“人道主义暂停”的决议得到了法国和其他 11 个国家的支持，但英国（和俄罗斯）投了弃权票，并被美国彻底否决，理由是该决议不承认以色列有自卫权。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第二个因素是美国自身的角色。在欧洲，它与乌克兰保持一定距离，向乌克兰输送武器、情报和资金，但不向乌克兰输送军队。在中东，它正在部署自己的军队，以保护以色列免受伊朗及其盟友的攻击。拜登先生对以色列的拥抱是真诚的——拜登先生称自己是犹太复国主义者——但也是试图影响和限制以色列。英国智库国际战略研究所的埃米尔·霍卡耶姆表示：“如果拜登的拥抱策略能够让以色列做出更有针对性的回应，人们就会认为这是拜登的特殊才能。” “如果不起作用，美国将被视为交战方。”</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">中东规则</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">区域动态又增加了一个因素。阿拉伯国家的态度模棱两可。许多人憎恨哈马斯，因为哈马斯是穆斯林兄弟会的一个分支，挑战其统治，并与以色列实现了和平，或与其建立了默契关系。然而，当巴勒斯坦人打仗时，这些国家就被迫支持巴勒斯坦问题。在接收了一波又一波的巴勒斯坦难民后，他们不再想要更多。事实上，他们担心以色列暗中想通过驱逐更多巴勒斯坦人来解决其问题。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">霍卡耶姆先生指出，加沙危机已将人们的注意力重新转移到巴勒斯坦，此前美国多年来一直努力忽视这一问题，或者从“由外到内”解决问题，即实现以色列与阿拉伯国家关系正常化，然后再处理巴勒斯坦问题。巴勒斯坦人自己。然而加沙的最后阶段却被故意留作空白。以色列坚称哈马斯不得再次统治加沙；美国表示以色列不得再次占领该地区。两者都没有说替代方案可能是什么。此外，内塔尼亚胡先生还竭尽全力破坏巴勒斯坦建国。在哈马斯发动猛攻之后，他和许多以色列人将更加确信这构成了致命的危险。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">美国官员欣然承认他们没有“后天”的战略。霍卡耶姆先生表示，两国模式“是一种偏好，而不是一项政策”。如果解决方案看起来不可能，部分原因是在同一片神圣的土地上调和以色列和巴勒斯坦这两种民族主义的要求存在固有的困难。霍卡耶姆表示，这也是“美国紧缩开支的代价”。 “对于长期缺席比赛的美国来说，重新回到比赛中更加困难。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China and Russia may offer no substitute for America&#39;s diplomacy, but they will be more than happy to see American discomfiture and will play up the claims of American double standards. Ahead of his visit to Washington this week, Wang Yi, China&#39;s foreign minister, described Israel&#39;s actions as “beyond the scope of self-defence” and did not mention Hamas.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The impact of the crisis may be more tangible among some “swing states”, says Richard Fontaine of the Centre for a New American Security, a think-tank in Washington, <small>DC</small> . These are countries that are “multi-aligned”, and for whose allegiance America, China and Russia compete ever more intensely. Saudi Arabia may demand a higher price from Israel and America if it is ever to follow its Gulf neighbours, Bahrain and the United Arab Emirates, in establishing formal ties with Israel.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Turkey, an equivocal ally of the West&#39;s in the Ukraine crisis, could turn more hostile. Though he has tried to patch up relations with Israel, and condemned the killing of Israeli civilians, President Recep Tayyip Erdogan hosts Hamas leaders and has sharpened his denunciation of Israel&#39;s response as “amounting to genocide”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Indonesia, the world&#39;s most populous Muslim country, inevitably sympathises with Palestinians. Though India thinks of itself as non-aligned and a friend of anti-colonial movements, it has expressed solidarity with Israel, feeling sympathy for it as a fellow victim of Islamist terrorism.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> South Africa under the ruling African National Congress sees Israel&#39;s treatment of Palestinians as akin to apartheid. African countries, more broadly, feel America either ignores conflicts on their continent—such as the war in Sudan—or is hypocritical when it comes to human rights. They regard America not so much as indispensable as absent. Many fear Mr Biden will not keep his promise to visit Africa this year.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Countries of the global south have also been courted more avidly by big powers. Though critical of Russia&#39;s invasion they do not want to be trapped in a new cold war. America has been trying to woo them through such things as boosting the lending capacity of the <small>IMF</small> and World Bank, and creating a global infrastructure fund to compete with China&#39;s Belt and Road Initiative ( <small>BRI</small> ). But it has a long way to go. On the same day as Mr Biden was in Tel Aviv, 20-odd leaders were in Beijing for a <small>BRI</small> summit hosted by China&#39;s leader, Xi Jinping.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A day later, in a televised address, Mr Biden made the case for America as the world&#39;s “essential nation”. In Europe and the Indo-Pacific his administration has acted nimbly, knitting existing alliances more tightly and creating new partnerships, helped by the aggression of Russia and China. In the Middle East, though, America is more alone in its defence of Israel, and more liable to lose friends and partners than win over new ones.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In an age of great-power competition that makes a difference. The pay-off to Mr Biden&#39;s address—”May God protect our troops”—is a common refrain of his. But right now, with America supporting two friends at war, and perhaps Taiwan in years to come, his words carry an ominous new ring. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 18:46:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/dg1i1cbnd7sbe99rmdbvk4u4dqgr59gv</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/international/2023/10/24/can-america-handle-two-wars-and-maybe-a-third </item><item><title><![CDATA[Pity the modern manager—burnt-out, distracted and overloaded]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>M</span> <small>ANAGERS DO NOT</small> make for obvious objects of compassion. It is hard to feel sorry for the <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2023/10/23/is-being-a-leader-really-sexier-than-being-a-manager">bossy office lead</a> , let alone the big-shot chief executive, who pockets <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2023/10/17/are-americas-ceos-overpaid">millions of dollars</a> a year in compensation. Yet their lot deserves scrutiny and even some sympathy. From the corner office to the middle manager&#39;s cubicle, the many <a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/07/27/how-to-run-a-business-in-a-dangerous-and-disorderly-world">demands on their time</a> are intensifying.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A recent survey of workers in 23 countries by Adecco Group, a recruitment and outsourcing firm, found that 68% of the 16,000 managers in the sample suffered burnout in the past 12 months, compared with 60% for non-managers, and up from 43% the year before. “I feel like I jumped on a treadmill where someone controls both the incline and the speed,” says one big-tech executive with a sigh. Plenty of his peers echo the sentiment. Managers increasingly require literal stamina: recruiters report that companies often ask candidates for executive positions how often they exercise.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That is a problem not just for the haggard individuals, but also for their employers and, given the mushrooming of management jobs in recent decades, whole economies. Today America has 19m managers, 60% more than in 2000. One in five employees at American companies manages others.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As firms in knowledge industries automate routine tasks and rely on the same digital tools—Amazon Web Services, Gmail, Microsoft office software, Salesforce customer-relationship programs—it is increasingly better management, rather than investments in technology, that can give them a competitive edge. Poor management can blunt it, by dampening productivity and increasing staff turnover. According to a Gallup survey conducted in 2015 around half of Americans who left a previous job did so because of a bad manager. Last year McKinsey, a consultancy, found that a similar share of job-leavers said they did not feel valued by their managers.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The importance of good management, then, is rising. At the same time, the environment in which managers do their job is undergoing changes of its own. This new landscape rewards some skills more and some less than in the past. As a result, your manager tomorrow will not look the same as your parents&#39; did.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Until the early 2000s, remembers Christoph Schweizer, boss of <small>BCG</small> , a consultancy, “ <small>CEO</small> s were superheroes”: larger than life, seldom wrong, never in doubt. For all manner of executive, “the highest compliment was &#39;brilliant&#39;,” says Hubert Joly, who used to run Best Buy, an electronics retailer, and now teaches at Harvard Business School ( <small>HBS</small> ).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Intellect still matters, of course. A study of Swedish bosses found that the typical head of a large firm was in the top 17% of the population by <small>IQ</small> . But across all layers of management, the emphasis has gradually shifted towards softer social skills, such as clear communication, ability to build trust and willingness to show vulnerability. Executives, including <small>CEO</small> s, need to be comfortable with ambiguity, and happy to delegate even the strategic responsibilities that they would once have hogged, observes Nitin Nohria, a former dean of <small>HBS</small> . (Mr Nohria is also chairman of Exor, which part-owns <i>The Economist</i> ’s parent company.) </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC129.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">David Deming of Harvard University has found that the number of jobs that require social interaction is rising faster than average, as are wages for such roles. A study of executive job listings, by Raffaella Sadun of <small>HBS</small> and colleagues, found that between 2000 and 2017 descriptions mentioning social skills rose by nearly 30%. Those singling out an ability to manage financial and material resources declined by 40% (see chart 1). The most common goals requested by companies who employ management coaches for their managers on <small>EZRA</small> , Adecco&#39;s coaching platform, include communication, emotional intelligence, building trust and collaboration. One of the hottest courses at Stanford University&#39;s Graduate School of Business is “Touchy Feely”, which teaches students to assess how they come across to others.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Social skills are increasingly sought after because they enable better co-ordination of people, goals and resources. And 21st-century business requires more such co-ordination than ever. Managers once used to supervise individuals performing repetitive tasks. Today they increasingly oversee professionals, often working in teams and engaged in complicated projects with outcomes that are harder to measure with any precision. The world outside the firm is becoming more complex, too. All this means that, as Mr Deming remarks, “it takes more time to converge on a decision.” A good manager, whose main role boils down to that of co-ordinator, can cut this time. This ability to get disparate people and goals to coalesce smoothly is thus at a premium, especially relative to purely intellectual and technical skills.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One thing making co-ordination harder is an otherwise welcome development—greater workforce diversity. For much of the 20th century in America the manager and the managed were the same white men. “You used to run mini-mes,” says Nicholas Bloom of Stanford University. That, as Ms Sadun explains, meant managers could be assumed to possess an implicit “theory of mind” of their underlings—an intuitive understanding of how they thought and felt about the world. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC114.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">This is, thankfully, no longer a safe assumption. In America, women make up 42% of managers, up from 38.5% in 2010. Between 2013 and 2022 the share of non-whites in managerial posts has risen from 14% to more than 18% (see chart 2). Both women and non-whites are still underrepresented in such roles, relative to their share of America&#39;s population; non-white employees in particular are still likelier than their white colleagues to say that they left a job because they didn&#39;t feel they belonged at their companies. But progress is undeniable. Diversity has, says Mr Nohria, “caught up with us”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The problem for managers, be they women or men, white or not, is that putting yourself in your subordinates&#39; shoes is no longer automatic. Because you cannot assume you know what others are thinking, you need keen social “antennae”, Mr Nohria explains. Hybrid work, where managers in Mr Bloom&#39;s words, “adjudicate private lives” through decisions about work from home, makes this task even more delicate.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Like diversity, the post-pandemic spread of remote work brings benefits while raising co-ordination costs. Running a workforce virtually imposes what organisational scholars call “management overhead”. Even when the network connection is not patchy and people do not forget to unmute themselves, virtual meetings strip out lots of important signals, such as eye-contact and gestures. They are more tiring; one study found that people speak more loudly on Zoom than in face-to-face meetings.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And they are taking up more and more of managers&#39; time. A study by Microsoft of 31,000 corporate users of its 365 office software in 31 countries found that in March 2023 the average person participated in three times as many Teams video-conferencing meetings and calls than in February 2020. In roughly the same period the typical user sent 32% more chat messages.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The number of unscheduled calls rose by 8% between 2020 and 2022, to 64% of all Teams meetings. Some 60% of such encounters are now under 15 minutes. Shorter activities probably mean more interruptions, says Ms Sadun. Two in three workers in the Microsoft study complained that they did not have enough uninterrupted focus time during the workday. “Work has become more staccato,” sums up Jared Spataro, who oversaw the research at Microsoft. That, Ms Sadun adds, imposes a heavy cognitive cost—and may explain some of the troubling burnout numbers.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Focus is scarcer for executives, too, including <small>CEO</small> s. When Ms Sadun and her colleagues looked at how 1,100 bosses in six countries spent their time, they discovered that only a quarter of their working days involved being alone, and some of that me time was taken up by writing emails. A long-running study of 27 leading chief executives&#39; time use by Mr Nohria and Michael Porter found that bosses often used long-haul travel to think. The post-pandemic decline in business trips means there is less of this time to recoup. If the composition of executives&#39; working hours reflects the relative value of the things those hours consume, then co-ordination activities outweigh those that include thinking about strategy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A final thing that could further lift the premium for social skills relative to intellectual ones is technology. Ever since Chat <small>GPT</small> , an artificially intelligent chatbot developed by a startup called Open <small>AI</small> , took the world by storm a year ago, progress in <small>AI</small> appears to have kicked up a notch. <small>AI</small> boosters argue that machines can take on some of the tasks that would in the past have required “brilliance”, to echo Mr Joly. The comparative value of the sort of non-artificial intelligence required to perform them may decline. Open <small>AI</small> ’s boss, Sam Altman, went so far as to declare that the cost of intelligence is “going to be on a path towards near-zero”. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPC119.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">It is unclear when—if ever— <small>AI</small> will live up to such bold forecasts. But it is likely to have at least some effect on the practice of management and the competences required for it. Fully 70% of respondents told the Adecco survey that they are already using “generative” <small>AI</small> at work. Mr Spataro of Microsoft (which has a large stake in Open <small>AI</small> ) observes that managers are generative <small>AI</small> ’s most effective users. “They treat it as the newest member of the team, and delegate tasks to it.” The tasks they offload are not just routine administrative ones. Nearly 80% of respondents in Microsoft&#39;s study said they would be comfortable using <small>AI</small> for analytical work; three-quarters said the same of creative work.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> None of this is to say that managers are about to become clueless empaths. Indeed, many still seek old-school markers of good management. Managers on Adecco&#39;s <small>EZRA</small> coaching platform are much likelier than their employers to ask for advice on shaping strategy, individual development and articulating ambition, and much less likely to pick emotional intelligence, trust-building and collaboration (see chart 3). Possibly more popular still than Stanford&#39;s “Touchy Feely” course is another called “Paths to Power”, in essence a how-to guide for aspiring Machiavellian princes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These competing priorities may help explain why so many managers are feeling overwhelmed. The new model of management—which favours social aptitude and co-ordination skills—is taking hold before the old one—which rewarded expertise and intellect—has loosened its grip. Amid all this managers are, in the words of Denis Machuel, chief executive of Adecco Group, “lost in translation”. The quicker they find themselves, the better: for them and their employers alike. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 18:36:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/14erb0m7p8rr45tbikpovveupfsvpt77</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/10/24/pity-the-modern-manager-burnt-out-distracted-and-overloaded </item><item><title><![CDATA[What does Taiwan want?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>S</span> <small>ince Russia’s</small> invasion of Ukraine, many have worried: is Taiwan next ? China is giving Taiwan a terrifying choice: unify with China, or face war. People in Taiwan want neither of these. </p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/open/s/633ebf6dfc7f5a0012acdc97/e/6537f96df60f870012204db4/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6IlFQRW5LbjZqIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&sig=EGd_Vg4EtOR97HAb-ujbshwVf7mG8K-bvxKGPmcgNPI"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text"> For this special four-part series, David Rennie, <i>The Economist</i> ’s Beijing bureau chief, and Alice Su, our senior China correspondent, ask whether <a href="/special-report/2023-03-11">Taiwan can preserve its freedoms and decide its own future.</a></p><p class="article__body-text"> .In this first episode, they explore how <a href="/special-report/2023/03/06/how-taiwan-is-shaped-by-its-history-and-identity">Taiwan&#39;s divided and changing identity</a> impacts how close Taiwanese people want to be to China. They meet Chen Yao-chang, a doctor turned novelist, who&#39;s idea of what it means to be Taiwanese has changed in recent years. Runtime: 46 min</p><p class="article__body-text">立即注册《经济学人播客+》，即可通过<a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Ddrum-tower">我们的限时优惠获得 50% 的订阅折扣。</a> If you&#39;re already a subscriber to The Economist, you&#39;ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.</p><p class="article__body-text"> For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit <a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">our FAQs page</a> or watch <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">our video</a> explaining how to link your account.</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 17:15:35 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/761e3qv1for39jlu0l339dahelfvo3vd</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/24/what-does-taiwan-want </item><item><title><![CDATA[Liz Truss and Jeremy Corbyn still haunt British politics]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>elcome to the</small> haunted house of Westminster. It is a year since Liz Truss left office, after serving as prime minister for 49 days. Britons are going to keep hearing about her for a lot longer than that. At the Labour Party&#39;s conference this month, few shadow-cabinet ministers missed a jibe at her expense—and, by extension, at that of her successor, Rishi Sunak. The message: that he is weak and she is still running the show. “We all know that he&#39;s just Ken in her Barbie-world,” said Angela Rayner, Labour&#39;s deputy leader.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The compliment is returned. At the Tory party conference, speeches were replete with references to Jeremy Corbyn. Never mind that he quit as Labour&#39;s leader more than three years ago, and that he is barred from running as a Labour <small>MP</small> . The message: that by having loyally served under him, his successor is an untrustworthy shape-shifter. “Rather like Jeremy Corbyn, Keir Starmer truly is a Marxist. Because as Groucho Marx put it, &#39;I have principles, but if you don&#39;t like them, well, I have others,” zinged Mel Stride, the welfare secretary.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Targeting such calamitous predecessors makes sense for both parties, notes Tom Hamilton, a former Labour adviser. Whatever their faults, Mr Sunak and Sir Keir “pass a basic test of looking as if they can more or less do the job”. Sir Keir has higher approval ratings now than Mr Corbyn did at the last election, at -22% to -50% respectively. Mr Sunak&#39;s wilting ratings outstrip Ms Truss&#39;s, at -40% to -70%.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In both cases the attacks contain some fragments of truth. Repudiating Mr Corbyn and his followers has been Sir Keir&#39;s defining project since he became party leader. The shadow cabinet has been remade. So have local Labour branches: votes at conference suggest the proportion run by the “hard left” has fallen from 80% in 2018 to 23% this year, according to Luke Akehurst, a Starmerite member of the party&#39;s governing body. Yet Sir Keir has never given a compelling explanation for why, unlike many colleagues, he served in his predecessor&#39;s shadow cabinet for over three years. The charge of opportunism lingers.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Sunak ran against Ms Truss in the Tory leadership contest in 2022, adhering to the “abacus economics” that she rejected. Although Ms Truss is an unpopular figure among Tory <small>MP</small> s, the prime minister has only criticised her disastrous term in office in mild terms (“some mistakes were made”). The charge of weakness sticks. “When is he going to say &#39;Liz Truss can&#39;t stand for the next election? That would be bold&#39;”, Sir Keir told an interviewer.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The parallels between the two leaders go well beyond their role as campaign fodder. Undeterred by their failures at home, both hanker to fix the world. Ms Truss is working on a book titled “Ten Years to Save the West”. The fact that Labour rejoices with every public appearance won&#39;t silence her as the election approaches. Mr Corbyn&#39;s “Peace &amp; Justice Project”, a sort of campaign group, has similarly vaulting objectives—among them ending conflict and achieving “climate justice”. Quite how is left unsaid. It hosts a conference in London on November 18th; he toys with a run to become the city&#39;s mayor.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Both figures press on something neuralgic in their parties. Ms Truss is a reminder of a double Tory failure: the acute blunder of the mini-budget of September 2022, and the chronic inability to control the ballooning tax burden. Shortly before the Treasury&#39;s autumn fiscal statement on November 22nd, Ms Truss&#39;s supporters will lay out a rival tax-cutting manifesto. Mr Sunak can hardly discipline her for preaching lower taxes, since he and the rest of the party agree with that goal in principle.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As for Mr Corbyn, it has been easy to see his leadership victory in 2015 as an aberration. But he did not come from the moon. His vague homilies on peace appealed to Labour members who had grown sceptical of British foreign policy, especially in the Middle East, since the Iraq war of 2003. Before him came Ed Miliband, who had opposed air strikes against the Syrian regime in 2013 in light of “the lessons of Iraq”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That all seemed like ancient history, until now. Sir Keir has been determined to show Labour&#39;s support for Israel after the attacks by Hamas, and to stamp out a reputation for anti-Semitism that grew during Mr Corbyn&#39;s tenure. But his suggestion, later clarified, that it would be legitimate to cut off water and electricity to Gaza caused a ripple of anger among Labour&#39;s rank and file, Muslims in particular. Mr Corbyn, meanwhile, could be found at the head of large pro-Palestinian demonstrations in London. Neither ghost is fully exorcised <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 16:45:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/j7eavu86c3rreuc2u5ln6tr7kkluoc6p</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/10/24/liz-truss-and-jeremy-corbyn-still-haunt-british-politics </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine’s allies are scrambling to bolster its air defences]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>M</span> <small>UD AND EXHAUSTION</small> are pushing the Ukrainian <a href="https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/10/14/now-russia-is-fighting-to-gain-territory-in-the-east-of-ukraine">counter-offensive</a> towards its close. The focus is thus shifting to protecting the country&#39;s cities, infrastructure and vital production facilities from a renewed Russian missile and drone campaign, aimed at eroding Ukraine&#39;s will and capacity to fight.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On October 11th the Ukraine Defence Contact Group, an alliance of 54 countries providing military support to Ukraine, convened in Brussels for its 16th meeting. President Volodymyr Zelensky left the group in no doubt that his country&#39;s most urgent needs are air defence and artillery munitions. But earlier this month, Admiral Rob Bauer, <small>NATO</small> ’s most senior military official, said of the West&#39;s ammunition stockpile that “the bottom of the barrel is now visible.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Last winter, after some difficult months when Ukraine&#39;s power grid came under frequent assault by salvoes of Russian cruise missiles and Iranian-supplied Shahed drones, the country&#39;s <a href="https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/06/13/how-kyiv-fended-off-a-russian-missile-blitz-in-may">air defence slowly gained the upper hand</a> . The vast majority of Russian missiles were shot down before reaching their targets. Western ground-based air-defence systems, such as Patriot and <small>IRIS-T</small> missile batteries, arrived in the nick of time, and Ukraine showed considerable skill in integrating a wide mix of platforms and radars. Its repair teams confounded expectations by managing to restore energy supplies rapidly, even after multiple attacks—and despite becoming targets themselves.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But this winter Ukraine is braced for more of the same, or worse, from an enemy that has learned from last year&#39;s campaign. Ukraine has built concrete defences around important parts of its electricity grid, and has acquired emergency generators to prevent total blackouts. But just as the ground war is essentially attritional in nature, so is the air war.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Douglas Barrie, an air-power specialist at the International Institute for Strategic Studies, a think-tank, says the question for both the defenders and the attackers is, “What have you got left?” In other words, will Ukraine run out of anti-missile munitions before Russia runs out of cruise and ballistic missiles and attack drones? And will Ukraine have enough batteries to cover the targets that the Russians are able to hit?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Nico Lange, a Ukraine expert at the Munich Security Conference, worries that Ukraine has neither enough platforms nor sufficient munitions for those that it does have. The country is now almost entirely dependent on Western systems, having used up nearly all of the mostly Soviet-era <small>S-300</small> and Buk missiles it was able to get its hands on. The deficiency is especially acute for short-to-medium range systems, such as the Kongsberg/Raytheon National Advanced Surface-to-Air Missile System ( <small>NASAMS</small> ), made in Norway and America.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Lloyd Austin, America&#39;s defence secretary, has hinted that more <small>NASAMS</small> , and the <small>AIM-7</small> missiles it can fire, will be sent to Ukraine from existing stocks. However, Mr Lange says that production rates are not increasing quickly enough to meet Ukraine&#39;s needs this winter. Defence companies in Europe are willing to crank up production on existing lines, but, says Mr Lange, still appear reluctant to invest in new lines to increase longer-term capacity.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> So even when Ukraine has been promised the kit it needs, there is no guarantee it will arrive in a timely way. Take the IRIS-T batteries, two of which have already shown their effectiveness. Germany has promised to send more to Ukraine, but it is not clear when they will arrive. After the Brussels meeting Germany issued a list of everything it has sent, or is about to send, to Ukraine. The list included two more <small>IRIS-T</small> batteries. The system&#39;s manufacturer, Diehl Defence, has committed to doubling production from four systems a year to eight, but not until 2025.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Six <small>IRIS-T</small> systems are due to be delivered this month, but to Germany&#39;s own air force rather than to Ukraine. Other European air forces are also scrambling to place orders for <small>IRIS-T</small> , impressed by its near 100% hit rate in defending Kyiv.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One short-term answer to the shortage of cutting-edge air-defence systems is to send older systems that the West and its allies no longer want but are held in storage. An example is Patriot&#39;s predecessor, the Hawk medium-range surface-to-air missile that entered service in the 1960s, but which remains effective if fitted with updated radar. Spain has sent some Hawks to Ukraine, and America may provide many more, some via Taiwan.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Similarly, the <small>RIM-7</small> Sea Sparrow, an equally whiskery short-range anti-ship missile, has turned out to work well with Ukraine&#39;s Soviet-era Buk launchers. More could be dusted off for service.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And Ukraine needs whatever it can get. The West once thought its sanctions might deny Russia the components it needs to make more missiles. But those hopes have dimmed. In May Ukrainian intelligence sources estimated that each month Russia is able to manufacture around 60 land attack cruise missiles, five Iskander ballistic missiles and two Kinzhal hypersonic glide weapons. Mr Barrie says that debris recovered from recent strikes by <small>KH101</small> cruise missiles confirms that they were recently produced.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Russia is repurposing surface-to-air and anti-ship missiles for land attack roles. It can also call on innumerable cheap loitering munitions and Shahed drones, which are now being built in Russian factories.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> An emerging threat is air-launched “glide bombs” guided by <small>GLONASS</small> , the Russian equivalent of <small>GPS</small> . They have a range of 50km, are accurate to within ten metres and are far cheaper than missiles. Mr Lange says that Ukraine has a desperate need for more and better electronic-warfare equipment that can counter both guided bombs and drones. But he fears that donor countries may be reluctant to share it.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> By stockpiling missiles during the summer, Russia should be able to resume attacks at a similar level of intensity to last year&#39;s, and maintain them for several months. There are also some indications from recent strikes that Russia will opt to hit targets less well defended than Kyiv, such as Odessa and other port cities. As Mr Barrie says: “Ukraine is a big country. There are lots of things the Russians can go after.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Russia, it appears, is not going to run out of missiles. The question is whether Ukraine will retain the means to keep shooting them down. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Read more of our recent coverage of the <a href="https://www.economist.com/ukraine-crisis">Ukraine crisis</a> .</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 15:45:38 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/4h5lp9b496nn8nfqpsiberm28gb4n789</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/10/24/ukraines-allies-are-scrambling-to-bolster-its-air-defences </item><item><title><![CDATA[How has Israel’s commercial airspace remained open?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>S</span> <small>INCE THE</small> <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamass-attack-was-the-bloodiest-in-israels-history">bloody attack on Israel</a> on October 7th, roughly 90% of airlines flying to Israel, including British Airways and Emirates, have suspended flights to the country. <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/10/how-powerful-is-hamas">Hamas</a> , the militant group that runs the <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/12/a-short-history-of-gaza">Gaza Strip</a> , has repeatedly fired rockets at Ben-Gurion airport, Israel&#39;s largest, near Tel Aviv. On October 9th one landed nearby, sending travellers scrambling for cover. Yet Israeli airports, including Ben-Gurion, continue to operate. Why and how have they stayed open?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Israel needs its airports, particularly now. In preparation for a <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/19/as-israels-invasion-of-gaza-nears-the-obstacles-get-more-daunting">ground offensive in Gaza</a> it has called up army reservists, some of whom were abroad. Airlines are also ferrying in diplomats and negotiators. A high proportion of Israel&#39;s cargo, from hospital equipment to supplies for the war effort, arrives by air. Stopping flights would dent morale and represent an apparent capitulation to Hamas. During a conflict in 2014 America&#39;s Federal Aviation Administration suspended flights to Ben-Gurion, a decision condemned by many politicians in America and Israel. The order was rescinded within 36 hours. Grounding civilian flights, says an Israeli aviation official, would be like “closing our only oxygen line”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet the threat of strikes on aircraft is real. Hamas recently unveiled its first locally produced anti-aircraft missile, Mutabar-1. It is not yet viable against commercial flights, given that its range is probably 8km or less. But the group&#39;s ground-attack rockets fly further. Since 2011, Israel has been protected from most of them by Iron Dome, its missile-interceptor system. But in that period, the range of Hamas rockets has increased from roughly 20km to 170km, says Yossi Kuperwasser, a retired brigadier-general and former director-general of Israel&#39;s Ministry of Strategic Affairs, putting airports in range. In the past, to conserve pricey interceptors, rockets that were expected to land in unpopulated areas were not usually shot down. Now, says Mr Kuperwasser, if an airport is nearby, interceptors are launched to limit panic among travellers. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="1280" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_WOM933.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">Before the recent conflict, civilian aircraft had already kept at least 80km from Gaza. Airlines have adjusted their routes further in recent days. Flights from America and Europe bound for Ben-Gurion now take a northerly route, entering Israeli airspace just south of Haifa before banking southwest to reach the airport from the north, says Gideon Mendelson of the Israeli Air Line Pilots Association. This reduces the number of planes over heavily populated areas where rockets are most likely to fly.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In recent years<b> </b>Israel has increased the integration of its civilian and military air-traffic control, with controllers in the same operations rooms using shared radar screens. Staff now have more warning before a potential strike on an airliner, usually at least 90 seconds. That is enough to give pilots “a calm, simple instruction” for an evasive manoeuvre, says the aviation official. The new flight routes also give pilots more time to direct their aircraft away from approaching rockets.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To increase safety, Israel&#39;s Civil Aviation Authority has told airlines to carry more fuel. Some Ben-Gurion-bound planes have been put in holding patterns for almost 50 minutes due to rocket fire. The extra fuel has prevented the need for emergency landings at other airports. The time airliners spend at Israeli airports has also been shortened, often from 90 minutes or so to less than an hour, by speeding up cleaning and refuelling. All flights to and from Ben-Gurion have been moved to the airport&#39;s newest terminal, which has more bomb shelters and was built to better withstand rocket strikes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The weeks ahead will be trying. Israeli airlines and some foreign carriers, including Etihad, the United Arab Emirates&#39; flag carrier, and Air Serbia are still operating flights to the country. But most airlines that suspended flights after October 7th are yet to resume them. In recent days some flights to Beirut, Lebanon&#39;s capital, have been cancelled due to shelling between Israel and <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">Hizbullah</a> , in southern Lebanon. If the Iran-backed militia is drawn into the fighting <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/13/israel-faces-the-danger-of-fighting-on-a-second-front">on a large scale</a> , the danger will increase. The group&#39;s leader, Hassan Nasrallah, has hundreds, if not thousands of rockets that can hit Ben-Gurion. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:47:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ub0etnodt66cip9tdtn4sf72sq0usj5q</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/24/how-has-israels-commercial-airspace-remained-open </item><item><title><![CDATA[Even Alexei Navalny’s lawyers are now at risk, as his privations deepen]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>P</span> <small>resident Vladimir Putin</small> has long had it in for Alexei Navalny, Russia&#39;s principal opposition figure. But now his <a href="/europe/2023/10/19/alexei-navalnys-lawyers-are-arrested">lawyers are in peril</a> , too, and Mr Navalny&#39;s privations in prison are ramping up. Gaza&#39;s need for aid may be urgent but is not new—Israel&#39;s <a href="/finance-and-economics/2023/10/19/israel-turns-to-financial-weapons-as-well-as-military-ones">economic stranglehold</a> goes back years (10:24). And, introducing <a href="/bartleby/2023/10/23/is-being-a-leader-really-sexier-than-being-a-manager">“Boss Class”</a> , our new, subscriber-only podcast series on being a better manager (19:50). Runtime: 27 min </p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theintelligencepodcast/e/653792c419b1f30012c20f57/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6ImZHeExMd3dDIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&sig=U0_Q3i0nAfjAfe5YbFyM_rM1DglFygp-E2BPAgXFlZo"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text">收听： <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-intelligence-from-the-economist/id1449631195">Apple 播客</a>| <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN">Spotify</a></p><p class="article__body-text">立即注册<a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Dthe-intelligence">《经济学人播客+》</a> ，即可通过我们的限时优惠获得 50% 的订阅折扣。在《经济学人播客+》推出之前，您无需付费。</p><p class="article__body-text"> If you&#39;re already a subscriber to <i>The Economist</i> , you&#39;ll have full access to all our shows as part of your subscription.</p><p class="article__body-text"> For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit our <a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">FAQs page</a> or watch our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">video that explains</a> how to link your account.</p><p class="article__body-text">播客成绩单可通过<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__">[email protected]</a>索取。我们致力于进一步提高可访问性，并正在探索新的方法来扩展我们的播客转录内容。</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:23:43 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/akjjoctb94llb3o3v3e7a7v4gipe60f9</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/24/even-alexei-navalnys-lawyers-are-now-at-risk-as-his-privations-deepen </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mikhail Khodorkovsky says that support for Israel should not come at the expense of Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>E LIVE IN</small> an era when the resolve of democratic states is being tested in the most extreme ways. The fighting in Ukraine continues unabated after that democratic country was invaded by Vladimir Putin&#39;s terrorist state. Now Israel has been forced into war following the barbaric massacre on October 7th of Israeli civilians by Hamas, a non-state terrorist actor backed by the terrorist state of Iran.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> People with any concept of morality were horrified by Hamas&#39;s cold-blooded murder of babies, women, young people at a music festival and the elderly, and by the group&#39;s kidnapping of over 200 people, mostly civilians. But for Mr Putin, not exactly renowned for his moral integrity, Hamas&#39;s attack and Israel&#39;s retaliation have been a welcome distraction from his own campaign of terror against Ukraine. With the world&#39;s media focused on the Middle East, spare a thought for the civilians in Zaporizhia and Kharkiv killed this week by indiscriminate Russian missiles.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is of course nothing that implicates the Russian leader in the Hamas attack, even if it serves his interests. It is, though, worth noting that his regime has in the past year held several meetings with Hamas leaders, including a delegation that visited Moscow to discuss Israeli-Palestinian tensions. Mr Putin has compared Israel&#39;s blockade of Gaza to the Axis powers&#39; siege of Leningrad in the second world war. And it is true that Mr Putin shares with Hamas a weapons supplier, dependent as he is on Iranian drones and missiles with which to menace the people of Ukraine.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It was also notable that his first comments about the attack in Israel were given as he sat alongside the prime minister of Iraq, himself dependent on Iranian support. It was, Mr Putin said, “a clear example of the failure of <small>US</small> policy in the Middle East”. His global interests are served by a perception of Western weakness that generates instability and emboldens autocrats and terrorists. Israel&#39;s war against Hamas is now the latest test of Western resolve, which was already straining following Russia&#39;s invasion of Ukraine last year, and in fact long before that.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The rise of rogue states, terror and lawlessness is something an expert might call the breakdown of the rules-based international order. I think of it as a situation in which criminals stop being afraid of the police in a multinational, multifaith city. The world is such a city, the criminals have been let loose and order has broken down.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Not long before the Hamas attack I bluntly told American politicians and experts that, outside the developed countries of the West, there was a widespread perception that their country was “not winning” yet another war. Observers had witnessed America leaving Afghanistan after the Taliban&#39;s reconquest, more than ten years of non-stop brutality in Syria, the Iraq debacle, Ukraine in 2014—and Ukraine since 2022, after a dictator rolled tanks into a democratic European country, fired missiles at homes and hospitals and sent death squads to slaughter civilians.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such criminality and barbarism demands a robust response. America, however, has shown restraint, backing Ukraine enough for it not to lose but not enough for it to win decisively. In the eyes of many people outside the democratic world, America appears weak. “They want to win but can&#39;t pull it off,” they think.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Many in America might no longer wish to be the world&#39;s policeman. But if the policeman is seen as weak, every lowlife out there will think they can get away with anything, and the number of challenges to the global order will only increase. Where next? Will China, having trampled the rights of Hong Kong, increase its aggression against Taiwan? There are plenty of other potential flashpoints around the world, from Kosovo to Iran.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> President Joe Biden, to his credit, appears to recognise the need for reinvigorated American leadership. “Hamas and Putin represent different threats, but they share this in common,” he told his public last week. “They both want to completely annihilate a neighbouring democracy.” He added: “We cannot and will not let terrorists like Hamas and tyrants like Putin win.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Americans often ask why they should foot the bill for maintaining global peace. Yet retreating from the world and permitting the bad guys to run riot has consequences. “It&#39;s a smart investment that&#39;s going to pay dividends for American security for generations,” Mr Biden said as he sought congressional backing for a new security package for two American allies under attack. Those who would stand in his way, or seek to play one democratic ally off against the other, risk going down in history as appeasers, however tough they might talk.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The European Union and its member states should welcome a revival of American engagement, and play their part. Whether through Mr Putin on their borders or other rogue states and bad actors beyond, malign forces are seeking to destabilise European societies. The sooner Ukraine can be helped to victory, the less serious the damage will be.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the face of a crisis, now is not the time for despair. But to ensure a brighter, more stable future, it is vital that America and Europe give Ukraine the tools it needs to secure victory. That goal does not contradict support for Israel against Hamas. It is part of the same struggle, because a win for terror anywhere would be a win for terror everywhere. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Mikhail Khodorkovsky, a former political prisoner and head of Yukos, an oil company, is the author of “How to Slay a Dragon: Building a New Russia After Putin”</i> .</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:52:35 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/sfbdv5609jqdcq2tli1gr47vvvfj1749</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/10/24/mikhail-khodorkovsky-says-that-support-for-israel-should-not-come-at-the-expense-of-ukraine </item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran’s ayatollahs play the Middle East’s most dangerous game]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>T</span> <small>HE WARNING SIGNS</small> that <a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">Israel&#39;s war with Hamas</a> may become a <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/13/israel-faces-the-danger-of-fighting-on-a-second-front">wider Middle East conflagration</a> are flashing ominously. America has sent a second carrier strike group led by the <i><small>USS</small> Eisenhower</i> to the Persian Gulf. “There&#39;s a likelihood of escalation,” said Antony Blinken, the American secretary of state, on October 22nd. The chances of further attacks by Iranian proxies on American forces are growing, he continued: “We don&#39;t want to see a second or third front develop.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Fears are also growing in Lebanon that Israel could use America&#39;s cover to launch a pre-emptive strike. Israel has evacuated its towns near the border with Lebanon and Binyamin Netanyahu, Israel&#39;s prime minister, has cautioned that if <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">Hizbullah</a> , an Iran-backed militia in Lebanon, enters the fighting, the consequences for Lebanon will be devastating. One reason Israel has delayed its offensive in Gaza may be to bolster its preparations for escalation on its northern front. Iran&#39;s foreign minister has said the region is like a “powder keg”.</p><aside class="css-13k2iu7 e1e9ys590"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Read more on the <a href="https://www.economist.com/israel-hamas">war between Israel and Hamas.</a></p></aside><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Iran&#39;s autocratic rulers hold one of the matches that could set it alight: an “axis of resistance”, or network of violent proxies across the region. They have spent two decades building this up in Iraq, Lebanon, Syria and Yemen. Iran preys on places where the local polity is weak, where it is easy to funnel in personnel and weapons and where no external actor can challenge it, according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies, a think-tank based in London. Iran&#39;s ability to cause mayhem at arm&#39;s length—through Hamas, Hizbullah, Iraq&#39;s plethora of Shia militias and Yemen&#39;s Houthis—may even give it more leverage than its conventional military capabilities, which are relatively weak.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Iran&#39;s goal right now, as it has been over the past decade, is not to provoke outright war with the West and its allies but to sow uncertainty and instability. Just as it has hovered on the threshold of becoming a nuclear power, so it maintains strategic ambiguity with the axis. It denies it is in charge while supplying armed groups like the Houthis with arms, giving them training and using them as fronts to conduct attacks, such as a missile strike on Saudi Aramco in 2019 which temporarily shuttered 5% of global oil production. The purpose is to intimidate while complicating the West&#39;s calculus. That strategy pleases Iran&#39;s ever-closer friend, Russia. Similarly isolated from the West, it engages in weapons trade and sanctions-busting with the Islamic republic: think of Iranian-designed Shahed-136 kamikaze drones killing Ukrainians.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The present crisis shows the opportunities and problems of Iran&#39;s approach. It has long sponsored Hamas but did not appear to know in advance about its attack on Israel on October 7th, according to Western officials familiar with the matter. Yet it has sought to capitalise on Hamas&#39;s atrocities and mobilise the axis of resistance. Hizbullah and Israel have exchanged fire, with the explicit support of Iran and America, respectively. As many as 19 of Hizbullah&#39;s fighters have been killed. The Houthis, who control Yemen&#39;s capital, have launched three medium-range cruise missiles, recently acquired from Iran, and a number of drones towards Eilat, Israel&#39;s port city (they were intercepted by an American destroyer). And Iranian-backed Shia militias in Syria and Iraq have broadened the struggle by repeatedly targeting bases housing American troops with rockets and drones (America has drawn down its diplomatic presence in Iraq as a result). </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231028_EPM935.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">For Iran, there are some obvious benefits. The conflagration in Gaza has halted—even if only temporarily—talks on normalising relations between Israel and Saudi Arabia. Any such agreement would mark a further step in the Abraham accords through which Bahrain, Morocco, Sudan and the United Arab Emirates have since 2020 established diplomatic ties with Israel. Iran&#39;s Shia ayatollahs cannot stand the idea of being isolated as Sunni-led Muslim states and Israel co-operate more. A push to delegitimise the Abraham accords continues: at a meeting of Muslim foreign ministers in Saudi Arabia on October 18th, Iran called on Muslim countries to impose an oil embargo on Israel. The Iranian regime is backing calls to push Egypt to take in Palestinians from Gaza, perhaps in the hope of aggravating tensions between Israel and its oldest Arab ally.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Regional turmoil also means more cash for Iran, at least for now. Oil prices have climbed by over $5 per barrel since October 7th. America is anxious to tamp down inflation in the run-up to its election next year and has been tacitly allowing Iran to export more oil, despite formally retaining sanctions. “Those Iranian barrels are very important” to Joe Biden, says Ahmed Mehdi, a London-based oil analyst. Production has topped 3m barrels per day, its highest levels since the Trump administration imposed sanctions in 2018. Year on year, Mr Mehdi says, exports are up by over a third.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet the escalating proxy war with America and its friends comes with big risks for Iran. At home officials crow that they have become “statesmen” again, with president Ebrahim Raisi—viewed by many in the West as a hardline pariah—speaking to the French president, Emmanuel Macron, in recent days. Ordinary Iranians are less impressed. A regional war could prompt a new cycle of protests at home. Armita Geravand, an Iranian schoolgirl who collapsed on October 1st after a beating from the morality police, according to local activists, has been declared brain-dead—news that could revive the outrage that brought Iranian protesters into the streets in 2022 after the death in custody of Mahsa Amini, detained for “improperly” wearing the mandatory veil. Iranians are exhausted by their regime&#39;s adventures abroad and reluctant to endure more suffering for Palestine. Government-organised protests have been sparsely attended. A minute&#39;s silence at a football match in Tehran for those killed in Gaza was interrupted by raucous guffaws. “Neither Gaza nor Lebanon,” protesters chanted from their windows. “We sacrifice our lives for Iran.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Iran&#39;s shadow war is a delicate game and it is not clear that the country can control its proxies. Since America&#39;s assassination of Qassem Suleimani, one of the masterminds behind the axis of resistance, three years ago, Iran&#39;s satellites have increased their autonomy. As they hurl threats of war along with their rockets, they may find it hard to step back from their rhetoric. Each has set “red lines” for intervention against Israel and the West. A failure to respond could puncture their credibility with local supporters. An Israeli ground invasion of Gaza could force their hand.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The proxies must also balance their military aspirations with the interests of their host countries. According to Iranian officials, Bashar al-Assad, the Syrian president, has told Hizbullah he has no desire to heed its calls to attack Israel from his territory. In his view, Hamas betrayed him by siding with the rebellion against him in 2011 after he gave them sanctuary. He does not want to fight for them now.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Lebanon fears being another sacrificial pawn. Its Shias are the country&#39;s largest sect, but its other 17 official denominations form a majority. Tellingly, Hassan Nasrallah, Hizbullah&#39;s leader famed for his belligerent speeches, has shied from addressing his public from his bunker in Beirut since the fighting began. The threat of war has kiboshed Lebanon&#39;s hopes of a tourism revival. Lloyd&#39;s, an insurance firm, has signalled it could withdraw cover, and Middle East Airlines, Lebanon&#39;s national carrier, is docking some of its fleet in Turkey. America has told its citizens to leave. The Lebanese prime minister has said “the decision regarding war and peace” is out of his hands.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> If Iran&#39;s proxies attack American interests, or possibly Israel, it is most likely that America retaliates against them, rather than their sponsor Iran, in the first instance. Still, that is a high-stakes gamble. And in the long run Iran&#39;s decision to mobilise the axis of resistance signals it is heading towards isolation and autocracy. Only a month ago, the regime was celebrating a prisoner exchange with America and the imminent transfer to Iran of $6bn of frozen oil revenues. Ayatollah Ali Khamenei had blessed direct talks for the first time since the Trump administration withdrew from a nuclear deal. Some spoke of a new detente. Now that lies in tatters—and the chances of a catastrophic wider war, while still low, are far too high for comfort. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 21:06:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/e2uvhu5oscs740irbuvmuk3g5cd6aqhf</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/23/irans-ayatollahs-play-the-middle-easts-most-dangerous-game</item></channel></rss>