<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 2 日星期四 04:39:09 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[A new gonorrhea drug was developed by a non-profit foundation]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>淋病</span><small>是</small><small>一种</small>古老的疾病。 《利未记》提到了一种传染性疾病，涉及持续射精和勃起疼痛。仅仅 2500 年后，也就是 20 世纪中叶，抗生素的发现才让人们的生活得到缓解。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但或许不会持续太久。几十年来接触抗生素导致导致这种疾病的细菌<i>淋病奈瑟</i>菌产生了耐药性。随着市场上几乎没有新的抗生素上市，这种细菌再次占据了上风。许多国家都有治疗失败的报告。它现在被世界卫生组织指定为“优先”病原体。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 11月1日，新抗生素佐利氟达星临床试验取得成功的消息令人欣喜。该药物抑制一种称为 II 型拓扑异构酶的酶，该酶对细菌繁殖至关重要。然而，比佐利氟达星如何发挥作用更有趣的是它是如何产生的。大多数药物是由私营公司开发的。 Zoliflodacin 是在美国政府和全球抗生素研究与发展伙伴关系 ( <small>GARDP</small> ) 的协助下创建的，该伙伴关系是一个非营利组织，由大型慈善机构 Wellcome Trust 和瑞士日内瓦州等多个组织资助。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>GARDP</small>与美国制药公司 Innoviva Specialty Therapeutics 合作。该公司负责早期开发，并正在引导该药物在美国食品和药物管理局注册。美国国家过敏和传染病研究所指导其完成第二阶段试验，检查新药是否有效。 <small>GARDP</small>支持该药物通过后续更大规模的 3 期试验，这是药物批准使用之前的最后阶段。它的支持使得这些试验能够根据公共卫生目标进行定制，例如将妇女、青少年和<small>艾滋病毒</small>感染者等高危患者纳入试验。 <small>GARDP</small>也在处理许可事宜，希望这将使佐利氟达星变得便宜且广泛使用。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>GARDP</small>发言人 Duncan Graham-Rowe 表示，这种合作关系可以增加新抗生素的供应。 （另一个非营利组织<small>CARB</small> - <small>X</small>也在做类似的工作。）近几十年来新药的缺乏主要反映了激励措施不力。为了延缓耐药性的产生，需要储备新的抗生素，直到真正需要它们为止。但搁置数年的药物在商业上没有吸引力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">各国政府试图通过保证价格和即使不使用药物也每年支付等想法来解决这个问题。国营制药公司也已被讨论。要证明<small>GARDP</small>已经找到了成功的配方，需要的不仅仅是唑利氟达星。但迹象是好的：它正在开发其他四种抗生素，其中一种用于复杂的尿路感染，而且更多的抗生素正在开发中。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:27:48 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/ndu7836sqpg32lslqnfbfn8s3el8qv4m</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/01/a-new-gonorrea-drug-was-development-by-a-non-profit-foundation</item><item><title><![CDATA[Could AI help find valuable mineral deposits?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>未来</span>是电动<small>的</small>。这意味着它将需要大量的电池、电机和电线。反过来，这意味着制造它们需要大量的钴、铜、锂和镍。那么，对于探矿者来说，尤其是对于那些认为自己可以提高职业效率的人来说，这是一个伟大的时代。一些公司正在将<a href="https://www.economist.com/artificial-intelligence">人工智能</a>（ <small>AI</small> ）应用到这一过程中，既可以提高地表开采的几率，也可以探测当前技术无法看到的地下矿体。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">加利福尼亚州伯克利的 KoBold Metals、旧金山的 Earth <small>AI</small>和波士顿的 Ver <small>AI</small>目前还处于起步阶段，墨尔本的 SensOre 和布里斯班的 OreFox 也是如此。但至少有一条更大的鱼——澳大利亚-英国公司——力拓集团——也很热衷。他们正在收集大量地质、地球化学和地球物理数据来输入软件模型。他们希望这些能够发现模式并推断出在何处埋设新地雷。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">有些数据是新的。但很多东西曾经在国家地质调查档案、地质期刊和其他历史资料库中腐烂，或者以力拓为例，该公司已经运营了 150 年，以岩芯的形式存放在世界各地的各个棚屋中。世界。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">狗头人是神秘的地下精灵，困扰着中世纪德国的矿工。 （他们也给钴起了自己的名字。）KoBold 的老板库尔特·豪斯 (Kurt House) 希望他们的一些魔力能够发挥作用。他的公司将来自世界各地的档案数据重新格式化为机器可用的形式，其中许多是纸质的，其中一些可以追溯到 19 世纪。这使得它能够绘制整个地球表面感兴趣区域的地图。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其中一些地图用于训练该公司的<small>人工智能</small>模型。另一些则用于测试该软件的有效性，方法是检查它在以前从未见过的地图上预测已知矿床的效果。如果它通过了，它就会被释放到尚未探索的感兴趣的地方，为 KoBold 的地质学家提供线索。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">由 Roman Teslyuk 领导的 Earth <small>AI</small> 、由 Richard Taylor 领导的 SensOre 和由 Warwick Anderson 领导的 OreFox 也采取了类似的方法，但都集中在拥有特别丰富的公共地质记录的澳大利亚。 Ver <small>AI</small>由 Yair Frastai 领导，专注于北美和南美西部地区，世界十大铜矿中的八个都位于该地区。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">豪斯博士对他的<small>人工智能</small>能够预测地下深成侵入体的形状和分布感到特别自豪。这些是火成岩体，通常含有矿石，它们作为液态岩浆从地球内部升起，但在到达地表之前就凝固了。它们可以通过磁异常从地表检测到，磁异常表明一组特定的岩石是在与其周围环境不同的时间形成的，这是行业的标准做法。但 KoBold 的<small>人工智能</small>能够更准确地预测这些入侵的形状，从而建议最有效的钻探位置。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">并取得成功。去年，KoBold 宣布在赞比亚发现了丰富的辉铜矿（一种铜的硫化物）矿藏。与此同时，地球<small>人工智能公司</small>在新南威尔士州发现了大量钼（特种钢的重要组成部分）。 Ver <small>AI</small>在智利和秘鲁发现了含有铜、金和银的矿石。 SensOre 在西澳大利亚发现了大量锂矿。 OreFox 的技术在维多利亚州发现了一个潜在的金矿，以及几个有前景的铜矿前景。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">力拓正在建造其勘探数据科学主管 Russell Eley 所说的“虚拟核心棚”。这将汇集该公司多年来收集的许多岩心样本的详细信息。然后，软件将在其中搜索有助于解释新岩心的模式，并告诉地质学家下一步钻探的最佳地点。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> House 博士观察到，99% 的勘探项目未能转化为实际的矿山。因此，<small>人工智能</small>还有很大的改进空间。它还可能有助于解决更微妙的问题。通过大幅扩大可搜寻的岩石数量，它将能够在熟悉的、治理良好的国家进行新的打击，从而减少未来供应对泰勒先生在外交上所称的“外国司法管辖区”的依赖。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:25:04 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/lf01uur1c8a3e123nerecqbo4hqbb0c9</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/01/could-ai-help-find-valuable-mineral-deposits </item><item><title><![CDATA[Lab-grown models of embryos increasingly resemble the real thing]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">制造胚胎的<span>传统</span><small>方法</small>是将精子细胞与卵子结合，通常是在晚餐和一瓶酒之后进行。但一种新的方式可能即将到来。近年来，科学家发现他们可以说服干细胞（那些能够转化为许多其他类型细胞的细胞）形成外观和行为都非常<a href="https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/01/how-stem-cell-embryo-models-could-advance-reproductive-science">类似于胚胎的</a>结构。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种创造物被称为“胚胎样体”，可以帮助研究胚胎学和怀孕，以及它们如何出错。有些传真看起来惊人的真实。 2022 年，两个团队（一个由加州理工学院和剑桥大学的 Magdalena Zernicka-Goetz 领导，另一个由以色列魏茨曼科学研究所的 Jacob Hanna 领导）发表了描述具有<a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2022/08/31/mouse-embryoids-can-now-be-grown-from-stem-cells">基本肠道的</a>小鼠胚胎的论文<a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2022/08/31/mouse-embryoids-can-now-be-grown-from-stem-cells">、大脑和跳动的心脏</a>。 6 月，Zernicka-Goetz 博士发表了一篇论文，描述了一种旨在模仿发育最早阶段的人类胚胎，即真正的胚胎植入母亲子宫后不久。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第二项研究引起了争议，其他一些科学家怀疑它是否像其作者声称的那样代表了进步。但最先进的技术发展得足够快，以至于一些人认为胚状体可能很快就会变得很难与它们要建模的胚胎区分开来。从很多方面来说，这将是一件好事：模型越准确，它就越有用。人类胚胎样体可以揭示发育性心脏缺陷或脊柱裂等疾病，并提高体外受精（ <small>IVF</small> ）的成功率。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但胚胎研究——毕竟胚胎有发育成人类的潜力——受到严格监管。许多国家禁止在研究中使用超过 14 天的人类胚胎，而没有此类法律的国家的研究人员通常会自愿遵守相同的标准。胚状体与真实事物越相似，就越难避免它们是否应该遵守类似规则的问题。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自然胚胎始于单个受精卵。为了制造胚状体，科学家们培养了来自胚胎或有时来自成体生物体的不同干细胞的混合物。他们可能会调整细胞之间的分子信号以及哪些基因处于活跃状态。几天之内，胚胎样结构就出现了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">胚胎之所以受欢迎，部分原因是真正的胚胎稀缺：主要来源是<small>体外受精</small>治疗的剩余物。它们也很难生长。这使得进行大规模实验变得棘手。胚胎提供了一种道德问题较少的替代方案。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">任何其他名称的玫瑰</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">它们的好处的一个例子是植入研究，即胚胎植入子宫的过程。大多数流产都是在这里发生的。但在胚状体出现之前，几乎不可能详细研究其原因。 “你无法通过母亲的身体来观察胚胎的发育，”泽尼卡-戈茨博士说。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">胚状体——具体来说，一种称为胚细胞的类型——提供了次佳的东西。它们首先由奥地利科学院的尼古拉斯·里夫龙 (Nicolas Rivron) 创建，类似于植入前的胚泡阶段的胚胎。在人类中，植入发生在第七天左右，而在小鼠中，植入发生在第四天左右。每个胚泡都由一个空心的细胞球组成，在真正的胚胎中，这些细胞球会继续成为胎盘的一部分。附着在内壁上的是一个较小的球，在其他情况下，它会发育成胎儿。通过将胚泡在培养皿中的子宫组织上滚动，里夫龙博士的团队发现，只有当它们定向以使内部物质最接近子宫组织时，它们才会粘住。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这意味着内部质量向外部细胞发送信号，指示它们粘附在子宫上。里夫龙博士认为他已经识别了这些信号，并计划很快公布他的结果。他希望帮助解释为什么这么多胚胎无法着床。反过来，这可能会提高<small>IVF</small>的成功率，而在美国，IVF 的成功率仅为 35% 左右。 Rivron 博士说，Blastoids 使此类发现变得更加容易。他创办了一家名为 Dawn Bio 的公司，该公司利用胚泡来筛选可能对生育治疗有用的候选药物。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">其他胚状体试图捕捉胚胎植入后的样子。最先进的是用小鼠干细胞制成的，例如上面描述的大脑和心脏模型，它代表小鼠发育的第八天。汉纳博士保持着人类胚胎的记录。在 9 月份发表的一篇论文中，他和他的同事描述了模仿人类胚胎在第 8 天到第 14 天发育的拟胚体。他热衷于尝试将事情推得更远，也许到第 35 天。那时，他的拟胚体就像老鼠一样那些，将开始发育器官。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">汉纳博士相信这可以使它们成为医学上有用的细胞的来源。例如，它们可能提供干细胞，这些干细胞又可以转化为骨髓，用于白血病患者的移植。如果用于产生胚状体的干细胞取自患者，那么骨髓在基因上将与患者自己的骨髓相同。这将消除免疫排斥的风险，以及对免疫抑制药物的需求。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">说服胚状体进一步发育可能会带来真正令人费解的可能性。从第 50 天左右开始，胚状体就会有性腺。这可能意味着，有一天，那些努力怀孕的女性可以得到一套全新的、新鲜出炉的自己的鸡蛋。 （汉纳博士的公司 Renewal Bio 正在追求这样的目标。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">没有人知道这些目标何时——甚至是否——能够实现。伦敦弗朗西斯·克里克研究所 (Francis Crick Institute) 的发育生物学家内奥米·莫里斯 (Naomi Moris) 也认为汉纳博士的 14 天大胚胎看起来很合适。但她认为他们还没有资格成为完全替代者。一方面，汉纳博士的胚胎从未经历过囊胚样阶段。这个缺失的环节阻止了它们附着在自然子宫上，并可能限制它们在培养皿中发育的时间。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，这些目标正在被追求的事实已经让一些科学家相信，现在是考虑监管的时候了。莫里斯博士提出了胚胎的新法律定义，该定义将基于胚胎发育成胎儿的潜力，胎儿的发育阶段从受精后八周开始一直持续到出生。在许多国家，人类胚胎的法律定义不明确。莫里斯博士希望她的提议能够明确表明，如果拟胚体具有相同的发育潜力，那么它就可以成为胚胎。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，要弄清楚它们是否确实存在，可能会很棘手。确定胚胎是否能发育成胎儿的唯一方法就是尝试一下——尽管如果成功的话，这样的实验可能会面临违法的风险。相反，莫里斯博士和她的同事，包括里夫龙博士，建议进行一个由两部分组成的测试，至少可以提出一个令人信服的论据，证明胚状体已经缩小了差距。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第一步是检查人类胚胎与真实胚胎发育轨迹的密切程度。第二个是尽可能地推动动物胚胎，理想情况下达到产生活的、可育后代的程度。这样的过程可能会从小鼠开始，然后再转移到猪或猴子身上。如果这种长期发育的胚状体在生化上看起来与人类最先进的技术相似，那么就需要谨慎对待。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">莫里斯博士估计，两到五年之内，就会有人制造出可以进入胎儿阶段的动物胚胎。 4月，中国研究人员将猴子胚芽移植到代孕动物体内，产生了持续长达20天的妊娠。而且总是有可能有人变得流氓。 2018年，中国研究人员贺建奎宣布他已经创造出基因编辑的人类婴儿。他被判入狱，并受到广泛谴责。但有人可能会尝试以类似的方式利用胚胎来突破界限，这并非不可想象。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">突破极限</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">国际干细胞研究学会主席阿曼德·克拉克（Amander Clark）强调了另一个可能使监管变得困难的讽刺。由于人类胚胎的培养时间不能超过 14 天，因此科学家们无法详细了解它们随后如何发育。这使得判断 14 天以上的胚状体是否表现出应有的行为变得非常困难。唯一的比较是动物胚胎和通过手术从孕妇身上取出的子宫解剖。换句话说，这条旨在保护胚胎的规则意味着研究人员可能很难判断他们的替代方案是否足够好，或者好到应该获得法律保护。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>澄清（2023 年 11 月 1 日）：这篇文章的早期版本给人的印象是 Zernicka-Goetz 博士是第一个发表有关高级小鼠胚胎的工作的人。事实上，汉纳博士的团队首先到达那里。我们对这个错误感到遗憾。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:21:57 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/7a3al2e9gb3sddp6q62dj2epkplq38t9</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/01/lab-grown-models-of-embryos-increasingly-resemble-the-real-thing </item><item><title><![CDATA[When can American officials block citizens on social media?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>唐纳德</span><small>·特朗普</small>在白宫的四年里多次测试美国宪法的界限。他的一次不幸遭遇—— <a href="https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/07/10/an-appeals-court-says-donald-trump-may-not-block-critics-on-twitter">阻止批评者</a>查看他在 Twitter 上的帖子或与其互动（该网站后来更名为<small>X</small> ）——导致联邦上诉法院裁定他的冷遇违反了第一修正案。但在<a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/09/28/the-new-supreme-court-term-takes-aim-at-the-administrative-state">最高法院</a>审查这一决定之前， <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/08/02/donald-trump-is-indicted-for-trying-to-steal-the-2020-election">特朗普在 2020 年大选中失败</a>，<i>奈特研究所诉唐纳德·特朗普案也</i>变得毫无意义。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 10 月 31 日，两起不涉及第 45 任总统的案件向法官提出了同样的问题：官员使用个人社交媒体账户何时会成为“国家行为”并受到宪法限制？三个小时的辩论揭示了区分 Facebook 的个人使用和按照 1982 年先例而言“相当可归因于国家”的帖子的难度。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在<i>奥康纳-拉特克利夫诉卡尼尔一案中，</i>一对来自圣地亚哥附近小镇波威的夫妇起诉学校董事会的两名受托人，因为他们在 Facebook 和 Twitter 上屏蔽了他们。卡尼尔夫妇将孩子送到该地区的学校，他们在虚拟页面上写下长篇重复的评论，惹恼了受托人。但他们声称，由于官员的平台是社区讨论学校董事会活动的论坛，当官员封锁他们时，他们的言论自由受到不公平的限制。 2022 年 7 月，第九巡回上诉法院的一个小组一致同意，认为受托人“以国家权威”“掩盖”了他们的账户。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但一个月前，在<i>林德克诉弗里德一案中，</i>密歇根州休伦港一位同样受到回避的选民未能说服第六巡回上诉法院的一个小组，让他相信将他从城市经理的 Facebook 页面上驱逐出去是违宪的。第六巡回法院裁定，城市经理詹姆斯·弗里德（James Freed）并未在其个人 Facebook 页面上处理公务，尽管他正在与居民讨论与流感大流行相关的政策。他对这个账户的使用——他在多年前还是一名大学生时就开设了这个账户，分享他的狗的照片、外卖的细节以及与浣熊的斗争——既不是“履行他实际或表面上的职责”，也不是直接行使“国家权力”。权威”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">当九名法官推动竞争测试时，他们努力想出一种方法，让公务员以个人身份表达自己的意见，同时保护选民获取信息和挑战从捕狗者到总统的官员的权利。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">学校董事会受托人的律师哈希姆·穆普潘 (Hashim Mooppan) 为第六巡回法院的狭隘测试辩护，他表示，如果特朗普先生在没有工作人员帮助的情况下自己发推文，他就会行使“在学校谈论政府”的权利。他的个人能力”。埃琳娜·卡根法官对此表示怀疑。她说，作为总统，特朗普先生不仅谈论他的工作，而且还“做……很多政府工作”并通过推特“宣布政策”。将公民逐出该论坛就是“将公民与政府运作的部分方式隔绝”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">司法部的两名律师与穆潘先生和维多利亚·费雷斯（弗里德先生的律师）一起辩论，捍卫官员的言论自由权。费雷斯女士和政府律师玛莎·汉斯福德表示，这起诉讼迫使弗里德先生停用了他的 Facebook 帐户。汉斯福德女士补充说，在个人页面中发现国家行动“会危及政府官员作为公众公民就公众关心的问题发表言论的自由”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">代表被封锁选民的律师承认，官员有言论自由的权利。密歇根州批评者的律师阿隆·凯德姆表示，城市经理和其他雇员应该有“足够的空间……以个人身份进行沟通”，但不应该能够“逃避宪法”。为卡尼尔家族辩护的帕姆·卡兰表示，学校董事会成员本可以提出免责声明，强调其账户的个人性质。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">法院的大多数成员似乎都围绕着布雷特·卡瓦诺法官提出的一项原则：仅在个人账户上转发官方事务并不算作国家行为。但凯德姆先生列举了弗里德先生爆料的例子，包括该市决定给予居民 30 天的缓刑，然后因欠费而停水。弗里德先生在回答询问时补充说，那些最近关闭水源的人将重新打开水源。凯德姆先生指出，即使在其他地方可以获得这样的信息，城市经理的 Facebook 页面也是了解这些信息的最自然的地方：“镇上基本上没有其他游戏。”如果这成为法院裁决的一部分，公职人员可以删除选民对其猫<small>GIF</small>的粗鲁评论，但不能阻止他们阅读（或辩论）有关宠物所有权的规则。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:14:10 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/1ja4n0uglp99h0jph6nn0qgbrp43plil</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/11/01/when-can-american-officials-block-citizens-on-social-media </item><item><title><![CDATA[“King Lear” and the purpose of tragedy in dark times]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">电视<small>上</small><span>有</span>谋杀，广播里有痛苦；互联网上的谎言和仇恨，还有你在意识到自己的错误之前点击的鼻烟视频。这个星球是一个沸腾的大锅，而你是其​​中一只自鸣得意的青蛙。当现实世界感觉就像停尸房时，为什么要花一个晚上和一大笔钱看着舞台上堆积如山的尸体呢？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在《李尔王》中， <a href="https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/04/19/shakespeares-first-folio-assembled-the-worlds-greatest-literature">莎士比亚</a>把它们堆得高高的。 “这在这里只是小事，”一个角色在谈到另一个人在最后的死亡时死亡时说道。<b> </b>但这部戏剧——以及肯尼思·布拉纳爵士在伦敦精心制作的新剧——为让自己屈服于<a href="https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2020/03/19/how-shakespeares-plays-reflect-americas-preoccupations">悲剧艺术</a>提供了强有力的理由，即使是在环绕声恐怖的时代。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如今，《李尔王》的演出次数不如《哈姆雷特》，其心理学极其敏锐，或者《奥赛罗》和<a href="https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/starry-new-productions-show-macbeth-is-the-tragedy-for-our-times/21806303">《麦克白》</a> ，其明显的现代主题是种族、厌女症和权力的腐败影响。评论家经常认为《李尔王》是哲学诗歌的胜利，但作为戏剧来说却是不切实际的。它包含了太多，太多了：太多的想法和情感，太多的故事，最重要的是，太多的荒凉和绝望。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">邪恶的人物互相毁灭，但他们也把善良的人带走了。爱会杀人；人不过是“可怜的、光秃秃的、分叉的动物”。在整个 18 世纪，这种凄凉似乎是如此令人震惊，甚至是不道德的，以至于《李尔王》的结局被修改为幸福的结局。观众仍然在与情绪超负荷作斗争。十年前，在伦敦另一场大肆宣传的演出中，人们在本该哭泣的时候却窃笑起来。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">英国<a href="https://www.economist.com/culture/2022/01/21/belfast-offers-a-jarringly-comfy-depiction-of-the-troubles">演员兼导演</a>肯尼思爵士主演并执导了该版本，该版本于 10 月 31 日在温德姆剧院上映。 （该剧将于 2024 年在纽约的 Shed 上演。）他对这部剧的规模做出的部分反应是删减了很多内容。这是两个小时的精彩悲剧，故事背景大胆地以新石器时代的英国为背景，中间没有冰淇淋和八卦的间隙。身穿兽皮、挥舞长矛的演员们围绕着一个让人想起巨石阵的荒凉布景，他们的脸间歇性地以非新石器时代的投影出现在石头上。它们上方悬挂着一个既像行星又像眼球的球体，有时看起来会流血。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在这里，李尔王分裂他的王国之后发生的权力斗争与其说是一场军队的冲突，不如说是一场泥里的小玩意的争斗。然而，没有盛况也让故事核心的家庭戏剧显得非常亲密和熟悉。肯尼思爵士饰演的李尔被敌人抓住，双手被绑在背后，他用胡子擦干心爱的女儿科迪莉亚（杰西卡·雷维尔饰）的眼泪。很快，他把她的尸体抬到了舞台上，悲伤地嚎叫着。这一次，没有人笑。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，在其他时刻，他们也会咯咯地笑，因为肯尼思爵士明智地保留并磨练了有趣的部分，以帮助这一哲学深入人心。这不仅仅是荒诞疯狂和闹剧折磨的幽默，徘徊在悲情和嘲笑之间，通常被称为“怪诞喜剧”。还有充满魅力的邪恶和轻信的喜剧，冠军的双关语和莎士比亚的一些最丰富多彩的侮辱。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">至于悲剧的目的：埃德加（道格·科林饰）拖着双目失明、有自杀倾向的父亲格洛斯特（约瑟夫·克洛斯卡饰）穿越古代英国，暗示了这一悲剧的目的。 “人们必须忍受/他们离开这里，就像他们来到这里一样，”他宣扬道。 “成熟就是一切。”换句话说，人生就是一场耐力考验。由此可见，对于观众来说，悲剧艺术是一种微笑和承受的实践。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">今天的投注者可能会认为，我们在这方面已经进行了足够多的练习；对斯多葛主义的说教会产生一种自以为是的道德观。然而，埃德加的结论并不是戏剧的结论。它为痛苦场面提供的理由不仅仅是耐心的教训，甚至比肯尼思爵士那样出色的行为所能提供的在苦难中的团结感更重要。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 《李尔王》里充满了观众：目睹愚蠢、痛苦或残酷的角色必须选择如何应对。有些人权衡自己的利益并加入进来。有些人则束手无策。一些人反抗，比如当康沃尔（险恶的休吉·奥唐纳饰演）在嗜血和不受惩罚的痉挛中撕掉格洛斯特的眼睛时，英勇的仆人表示反对。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">很难想象你自己是李尔王，即使是像肯尼思爵士那样赤裸裸的人。但也许你可以像那些默默无闻的小人物一样，选择行动而不是仅仅观看。 “哦，你们是石头人，”国王在结尾时哭喊着，要求幸存的角色和观众对不公正现象给予更大的同情。剧中呼吁，不要只是坐在那里。做一点事。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:19:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/9iun0e2knlmnodafoc7bn4jnthhh4l4r</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/11/01/king-lear-and-the- Purpose-of-tragedy-in-dark-times </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can America’s weapons-makers adapt to 21st-century warfare?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>RMING 山姆大叔</small><span>是</span>一项伟大的事业。美国最新的国防预算指定 1,700 亿美元用于采购，1,450 亿美元用于研发 ( <small>R</small> &amp; <small>D</small> )，其中大部分最终落到少数直接与国防部 ( <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> ) 打交道的“主要”承包商手中。美国向乌克兰提供的 440 亿美元军事援助中的一部分以及美国欧洲盟国 <a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/26/american-power-indispensable-or-ineffective">额外的国防支出</a>也将同样如此，这些支出占主要产品销售额的 5-10%。尽管这些资金的增长速度不及企业<small>IT</small>支出等，导致大幅增长的空间较小，但武器制造商也能通过长达数十年的巨额合同免受令人眼花缭乱的损失。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">由于冷战结束时的大变动，该行业也高度集中。在 1993 年一次被称为“最后的晚餐”的会议上，时任总统比尔·克林顿 (Bill Clinton) 的国防部副部长威廉·佩里 (William Perry) 对行业老板们表示，产能过剩不再合适，必须进行整合。结果，素数的排名从 20 世纪 50 年代美国的 50 多个减少到了 6 个。卫星供应商数量从 8 个减少到 4 个，固定翼飞机从 8 个减少到 3 个，战术导弹从 13 个减少到 3 个。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC229.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">过去 50 年来，有保障的定制和疲弱的竞争帮助美国军火制造商的股票跑赢了大盘。<small>国防部</small>今年<small>4</small>月发表的一篇论文发现，2000 年至 2019 年间，国防承包商在股东回报、资产回报率和股本回报率等财务指标方面比民用承包商表现更好。世界日益不稳定意味着更多的资金流向武装部队及其供应商。当俄罗斯于 2022 年 2 月入侵乌克兰以及哈马斯于 10 月 7 日袭击以色列时，通用动力、洛克希德·马丁和诺斯罗普·格鲁曼等主要公司的股东总回报（包括股息）有所上升（见图 1）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种舒适的寡头垄断现在正受到两个方面的挑战。一是技术性的。正如乌克兰平原和加沙街道上的坦克战所表明的那样，“地面上的金属”仍然很重要。导弹、炮弹和战斗机也是如此。但这两场冲突也表明，现代战斗越来越依赖于更小、更简单的战术装备以及通信、传感器、软件和数据。第二个挑战是五角大楼努力从军工联合体中获取更大的经济效益。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这两项发展都削弱了 Prime 的巨大竞争优势：他们构建庞大套件和驾驭令人难以置信的采购流程的能力。具有成本效益的创新，例如五角大楼最近宣布的“复制器”项目，旨在<small>尽快</small>让大量小型无人机飞上天空，需要敏捷的工程，而国防巨头“天生没有组织起来”，正如咨询公司科尔尼所言，微妙地说。如果他们想在新时代蓬勃发展，他们就必须重新发现一些在二战后几十年里帮助他们塑造硅谷的创新方式。但到目前为止，他们发现这很困难。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">很容易理解为什么主要投资者（及其投资者）喜欢当前的设置。<small>国防部</small>报销主要<small>研发</small><small>费用</small>，并在此<small>基础</small>上增加 10-15%。这种“成本加成”的方法使公司不必将大量自有资本投入到有风险的项目中，这提供了安全性，但降低了按时、按预算交付产品的动力。建造<small>F</small> -35战斗机的项目于20世纪90年代启动，该项目在过去三年中占洛克希德公司收入的四分之一以上。它的运行晚了大约十年，并且在飞机的整个使用寿命期间将花费美国纳税人高达 2 万美元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">新开发的大型套件一旦投入生产，就会以固定价格出售，通常持续数十年。诺斯罗普·格鲁曼公司目前正在研发的<small>B</small> -21<a href="https://www.economist.com/military-terms-a-to-z#stealth-technology">隐形轰炸机</a>将花费五角大楼超过2000亿美元，在30年内交付100架飞机。通用动力公司子公司制造的哥伦比亚级<a href="https://www.economist.com/military-terms-a-to-z#submarine">核潜艇</a>计划将从 2030 年代初开始航行，至少持续到 2085 年。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">过了巅峰期</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">五角大楼对这种历史悠久的商业模式的耐心正在消失。 Last year&#39;s national-defence strategy summed it up succinctly: “too slow and too focused on acquiring systems not designed to address the most critical challenges we now face.” Instead, it wants to “reward rapid experimentation, acquisition and fielding”. This is forcing the primes to think about how they could build fresh functionality atop their existing platforms, by adding new software, modules, payloads and the like, and to create production processes which can be modified to accommodate innovations.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As Lockheed Martin&#39;s chief executive, Jim Taiclet, recently acknowledged, soldiers expect seamless integration of sensors, weapons and systems for battle management such as joint all-domain command and control ( <small>JADC</small> 2), a new concept for sharing data between platforms, services and theatres. Contracting, building and continuously updating such systems will be a struggle for firms that have hitherto produced huge bits of hardware slowly and which, in the words of Steve Grundman of the Atlantic Council, a think-tank, are not “digital natives”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The primes face another problem. The technology the Pentagon has in mind is not inherently military, observes Mikhail Grinberg of Renaissance Strategic Advisors, a consultancy. Most of the defence giants do have civilian divisions—large ones in the case of Boeing, General Dynamics and Raytheon. But the Pentagon&#39;s growing appetite for dual-use technologies means more competition from civilian industry, which is constantly devising new equipment, materials, manufacturing processes and software that could be used for military as well as peaceful ends.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In 2020 General Motors won a contract to supply infantry vehicles. The carmaker has now teamed up with the American arm of Rheinmetall, a German weapons firm, in a deal to furnish military trucks. Other challengers are trying to muscle their way into the military-industrial complex, drawn by the <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> ’s appetite for more diverse systems. Palantir, founded in 2003 to help avert more attacks like that of September 11th 2001, makes civilian and military software that processes the vast amounts of data that modern life and warfare throws up. Elon Musk&#39;s Space <small>X</small> sends payloads, including military ones, into orbit and is being paid by the <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> to provide internet access to Ukrainian forces in their fight against Russian invaders. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_WBC224.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">Big tech is getting in on the action, too. Amazon, Google and Microsoft have targeted defence and security as promising markets, says Mr Grundman. Military procurement is a rare business large enough to make a difference to the tech titans&#39; top lines, which are counted in the hundreds of billions of dollars. The trio, along with Oracle, a smaller maker of business software, are already sharing a $9bn cloud-computing contract with the Pentagon. Microsoft also supplies the army with augmented-reality goggles in a deal that could eventually be worth $22bn.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The Pentagon&#39;s new approach is also attracting upstart rivals. Anduril, a startup founded in 2017 solely to serve military needs, has developed Lattice, a general-purpose software platform that can be swiftly updated and adapted to solve new problems. The company also makes a short-range drone called the Ghost, which can be operated by a couple of soldiers. Recognising that to win business quickly it needs to be vertically integrated, it has acquired a manufacturer of rocket engines and is developing an underwater autonomous vessel for the Australian navy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The wannabe primes and their financial backers still bemoan the barriers to new entrants. Brian Schimpf, Anduril&#39;s boss, says that when working with the <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> you get “punched in the face every day”. SpaceX and Palantir both had to fight court battles just to be able to contest military contracts. In June Palantir signed an open letter with 11 other companies, including Anduril, and investors, imploring the Pentagon to remove obstacles to smaller contractors. The letter, which drew on proposals from the Atlantic Council, condemned “antiquated methods” that “drastically limited” access to commercial innovation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As the national-security strategy shows, the <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> seems keen to move away from procurement antiquity, for example by shifting more risk onto contractors through fixed-price, rather than cost-plus, development contracts. Such developments are causing palpitations among the primes. Boeing&#39;s recent financial travails are partly a result of catastrophically underbidding in fixed-price contracts for the <small>KC</small> -46 tanker and Air Force One, which ferries around American presidents.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In contrast, Anduril has dispensed with the crutch of cost-plus of its own accord, and is investing its own capital to make what it thinks the <small>D</small> o <small>D</small> will need. By clinging on to the old model, the primes may be depriving America of the 21st-century defence industry it needs. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The Economist&#39;s <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/military-terms-a-to-z">A to Z of military terms</a> explains modern warfare in plain English</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:59:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/qighd6r7dnnntc0dckojandi723r10p9</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/business/2023/11/01/can-americas-weapons-makers-adapt-to-21st-century-warfare</item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine’s top general on the breakthrough he needs to beat Russia]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>F</span> <small>IVE MONTHS</small> into its counter-offensive, Ukraine has managed to advance by just 17 kilometres. Russia fought for ten months around Bakhmut in the east “to take a town six by six kilometres”. Sharing his first comprehensive assessment of the campaign with <i>The Economist</i> in an interview this week, Ukraine&#39;s commander-in-chief, General Valery Zaluzhny, says the battlefield reminds him of the great conflict of a century ago. “Just like in the first world war we have reached the level of technology that puts us into a stalemate,” he says. The general concludes that it would take a massive technological leap to break <a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/09/21/ukraine-faces-a-long-war-a-change-of-course-is-needed">the deadlock</a> . “There will most likely be no deep and beautiful breakthrough.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The course of the counter-offensive has undermined Western hopes that Ukraine could use it to demonstrate that the war is unwinnable–and thus change Vladimir Putin&#39;s calculations, forcing the Russian president to negotiate. It has also undercut General Zaluzhny&#39;s assumption that he could stop Russia by bleeding its troops. “That was my mistake. Russia has lost at least 150,000 dead. In any other country such casualties would have stopped the war.” But not in Russia, where life is cheap and where Mr Putin&#39;s reference points are in the first and second world wars in which Russia lost tens of millions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> An army of Ukraine&#39;s standard ought to have been able to move at a speed of 30km a day as it breached Russian defensive lines. “If you look at <small>NATO</small> ’s text books and at the maths which we did [in planning the counter-offensive], four months should have been enough time for us to have reached Crimea, to have fought in Crimea, to return from Crimea and to have gone back in and out again,” General Zaluzhny says sardonically. Instead he watched his troops and equipment get stuck in minefields on the approaches to Bakhmut in the east, his Western-supplied equipment getting pummelled by Russian artillery and drones. The same story unfolded on the offensive&#39;s main thrust, in the south, where newly formed and inexperienced brigades, despite being equipped with modern Western kit, immediately ran into trouble.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “First I thought there was something wrong with our commanders, so I changed some of them. Then I thought maybe our soldiers are not fit for purpose, so I moved soldiers in some brigades,” says General Zaluzhny. When those changes failed to make a difference, the commander told his staff to dig out a book he once saw as a student in a military academy in Ukraine. Its title was “Breaching Fortified Defence Lines”. It was published in 1941 by a Soviet major-general, PS Smirnov, who analysed the battles of the first world war. “And before I got even halfway through it, I realised that is exactly where we are because just like then, the level of our technological development today has put both us and our enemies in a stupor.” </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231104_EUM951.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">That thesis, he says, was borne out as he went to the front line in Avdiivka, also in the east, where Russia has recently advanced by a few hundred metres over several weeks by throwing in two of its armies. “On our monitor screens the day I was there we saw 140 Russian machines ablaze—destroyed within four hours of coming within firing range of our artillery.” Those fleeing were chased by “first-person-view” drones, remote-controlled and carrying explosive charges that their operators simply crash into the enemy. The same picture unfolds when Ukrainian troops try to advance. General Zaluzhny describes a battlefield in which modern sensors can identify any concentration of forces, and modern precision weapons can destroy it. “The simple fact is that we see everything the enemy is doing and they see everything we are doing. In order for us to break this deadlock we need something new, like the gunpowder which the Chinese invented and which we are still using to kill each other,” he says.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This time, however, the decisive factor will be not a single new invention, but by combining all the technical solutions that already exist, he says. In an article written for <i>The Economist</i> by General Zaluzhny ( <a href="https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/01/the-commander-in-chief-of-ukraines-armed-forces-on-how-to-win-the-war">see here</a> ), as well as in a full-length essay shared with the newspaper, he urges innovation in drones, electronic warfare, anti-artillery capabilities and de-mining equipment, including new robotic solutions. “We need to ride the power embedded in new technologies,” says the general.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Western allies have been overly cautious in supplying Ukraine with their latest technology and more powerful weapons. Joe Biden, America&#39;s president, set objectives at the start of Russia&#39;s invasion: to ensure that Ukraine was not defeated and that America was not dragged into confrontation with Russia. This means that arms supplied by the West have been sufficient in sustaining Ukraine in the war, but not enough to allow it to win. General Zaluzhny is not complaining: “They are not obliged to give us anything, and we are grateful for what we have got, but I am simply stating the facts.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But by holding back the supply of long-range missile systems and tanks, the West allowed Russia to regroup and build up its defences in the aftermath of a sudden breakthrough in Kharkiv region in the north and in Kherson in the south late in 2022. “These systems were most relevant to us last year, but they only arrived this year,” he says. Similarly, <small>F</small> -16 jets, due next year, are now less helpful, suggests the general, in part because Russia has improved its air defences: an experimental version of the <small>S</small> -400 missile system can reach beyond the city of Dnipro, he warns.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet the delay in arms deliveries, though frustrating, is not the main cause of Ukraine&#39;s predicament, according to General Zaluzhny. “It is important to understand that this war cannot be won with the weapons of the past generation and outdated methods,” he insists. “They will inevitably lead to delay and, as a consequence, defeat.” It is, instead, technology that will be decisive, he argues. The general is enthused by recent conversations with Eric Schmidt, the former chief executive of Google, and stressed the decisive role of drones, and of electronic warfare which can prevent them from flying.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> General Zaluzhny&#39;s assessment is sobering: there is no sign that a revolutionary technological breakthrough, whether in drones or in electronic warfare, is around the corner. And <a href="https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/10/29/trenches-and-tech-on-ukraines-southern-front">technology</a> has its limits. Even in the first world war, the arrival of tanks, in 1917, was not sufficient to break the deadlock on the battlefield: it took a suite of technologies, and more than a decade of tactical innovation, to produce the German blitzkrieg in May 1940. The implication is that Ukraine is stuck in a long war—one in which he acknowledges Russia has the advantage. Nevertheless, he insists that Ukraine has no choice but to keep the initiative by remaining on the offensive, even if it only moves by a few metres a day.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Crimea, he believes, remains Mr Putin&#39;s greatest vulnerability. It is the linchpin of his imperial restoration project, and his legitimacy rests on having brought it back to Russia. Over the past few months, Ukraine has taken the war into the peninsula Mr Putin annexed in 2014 and which remains critical to the logistics of his war. “It must know that it is part of Ukraine and that this war is happening there.” On October 30th Ukraine struck Crimea with American-supplied long-range <small>ATACMS</small> missiles for the first time.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> General Zaluzhny is desperately trying to prevent the war from settling into the trenches. “The biggest risk of an attritional trench war is that it can drag on for years and wear down the Ukrainian state,” he says. In the first world war, mutinies interfered before technology could make a difference. Four empires collapsed and a revolution broke out in Russia.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A collapse in Ukrainian morale and Western support is precisely what Mr Putin is counting on. There is no question in General Zaluzhny&#39;s mind that a long war favours Russia, a country with a population three times and an economy ten times the size of Ukraine&#39;s. “Let&#39;s be honest, it&#39;s a feudal state where the cheapest resource is human life. And for us…the most expensive thing we have is our people,” he says. For now, General Zaluzhny says, he has enough soldiers. But the longer the war goes on, the harder it will be to sustain. “We need to look for this solution, we need to find this gunpowder, quickly master it and use it for a speedy victory. Because sooner or later we are going to find that we simply don&#39;t have enough people to fight.” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read a more detailed <a href="https://infographics.economist.com/2023/ExternalContent/ZALUZHNYI_FULL_VERSION.pdf">new essay</a> by General Zaluzhny on this topic.</b></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:28:29 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/rno5q4jbi1qhlif7dbv8thfgmeei1qt8</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/01/ukraines-top-general-on-the-breakthrough-he-needs-to-beat-russia </item><item><title><![CDATA[How stem-cell embryo models could advance reproductive science]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>E</span> <small>xactly how</small> humans grow from a single cell in the womb is shrouded in mystery. To uncover the secrets, scientists need to watch human embryos as they develop, but these are hard to come by for research purposes and strict regulation restricts their use. So scientists have come up with an alternative tool: model embryos grown in the lab from stem cells. These “embryoids” have proven invaluable to medical researchers in recent years, but rapid advances in their technology mean that embryoids are becoming increasingly similar to real human embryos. Very soon, some embryoids could become indistinguishable from real embryos. How can scientists navigate this ethical grey area and work out—with public input—how these models should be used? Runtime: 40 min </p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theeconomistbabbage/e/65428e6bdf8cb80012a6f3dd/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6ImpwNDdzenVqIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwcml2YXRlIn0=&sig=E15Nlk3Zc26Yhf8jYibAUa_UvkTcBfsDH6eKVHtMR8Q"><p> Your browser does not support the<audio> element.</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text"> Host: Alok Jha, <i>The Economist</i> ’s science and technology editor. Contributors: <i>The Economist&#39;s</i> Emilie Steinmark; Berna Sozen, a reproductive scientist at Yale School of Medicine; Kirstin Matthews, a biologist and science policy researcher at Rice University.</p><p class="article__body-text"><i>这是仅限订阅者观看的一集。 To listen sign up for a <a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Dbabbage">free trial</a> of Economist Podcasts+</i></p><p class="article__body-text"><i>如果您已经是《经济学人》的订阅者，作为订阅的一部分，您可以完全访问我们所有的节目。 For more information about how to access Economist Podcasts+, please visit our <a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">FAQs page</a> or watch our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">video</a> explaining how to link your account.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:44:57 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/v5me01l70khi9sgkljf9f2nsmmung2e4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/01/how-stem-cell-embryo-models-could-advance-reproductive-science </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is a two-state solution possible after the Gaza war?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>n trying to</small> plan for the future, world leaders are looking to the past. “When this crisis is over, there has to be a vision of what comes next, and in our view it has to be a two-state solution,” said Joe Biden, <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/24/the-overstretched-superpower">America&#39;s</a> president, in one of his many public statements about the nearly month-long war in Gaza. Rishi Sunak, the British prime minister, has made similar comments; so has Emmanuel Macron, the French president. An emergency meeting of the Arab League last month ended with a call for “serious negotiations” towards a two-state solution.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> When Israel left <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/12/a-short-history-of-gaza">Gaza</a> in 2005, uprooting some 8,000 Jewish settlers from a territory it had controlled since 1967, no one knew quite what to make of the decision. Some hoped that Israel&#39;s willingness to cede occupied territory would be a trend, a step towards a final settlement with the Palestinians. Others saw a canny ploy: relinquishing control of Gaza might help Israel entrench its control of the West Bank. The latter view turned out to be correct.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Similar confusion has emerged since October 7th, when Israel began planning a <a href="https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/30/israels-ground-offensive-in-gaza-points-to-a-grinding-encirclement">ground invasion of Gaza</a> after Hamas, the militant Islamist group that controls the territory, massacred 1,400 Israelis. Palestinians fear the war will lead to a second <i>naqba</i> (“catastrophe”), referring to the mass displacement that accompanied Israel&#39;s birth in 1948. Far-right Israeli ministers hope it will offer a chance to reassert control over Gaza and rebuild the dismantled Jewish settlements. A few hopeful sorts, among them Mr Biden, hope it will provide a chance to revive the comatose Israeli-Palestinian peace process.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For now, that is a far-off dream: Israeli generals expect months of fighting. But both they and many foreign powers hope eventually to transfer control of Gaza to the Palestinian Authority ( <small>pa</small> ), which governs parts of the West Bank, probably with a peacekeeping force brought in to help the transition. And they doubt that Mahmoud Abbas, the Palestinian president, would return without a guarantee of meaningful talks about Palestinian statehood.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Any plan for the “day after” in Gaza, in other words, needs to consider the possibility of a two-state solution. The broad outline has not changed much for decades. A Palestinian state would be formed in Gaza and the West Bank; Israel would swap chunks of its territory for portions of the West Bank where it has built large settlements. Jerusalem would be divided, with some sort of joint control over the old city. A small number of Palestinian refugees could return to Israel, while the rest would settle in either Palestine or their present homes elsewhere. Israel would expect a Palestinian state to be demilitarised.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> After two decades of serious talks—from the hopeful era of the Oslo accords in the early 1990s, through a desultory attempt under Barack Obama—the peace process ground to a halt in 2014. There have been no serious negotiations since.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Negotiators cannot quite pick up where they left off. At the end of 2021 there were 465,400 Israeli settlers living in the West Bank, up from 116,300 when the Oslo accords were signed in 1993. They are a growing obstacle to peace. Most are concentrated in areas that would probably be ceded to Israel in an agreement, but their political clout (they would oppose surrendering even land that they do not live on) has increased along with their population.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Context is everything</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The regional picture is also more complicated. In 2002 the Arab League endorsed a Saudi proposal that promised Israel normal relations with Arab countries after a two-state solution: by ending its conflict with the Palestinians, Israel could end all its regional conflicts. The Arab Peace Initiative was meant as a powerful inducement. Israel might be more willing to take its boot off the Palestinians if it felt that other threats would then dissipate.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But the region has changed since 2002. Some militias, from <a href="https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/10/18/what-is-hizbullah">Hizbullah</a> in Lebanon to the Houthis in Yemen, are now more powerful than the states they call home. It would not suffice for Arab governments to end their conflicts with Israel: non-state actors would have to agree to do so as well.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Other things could be easier. A two-state solution would be costly. Even before the war, the Palestinians would have expected help to rehabilitate Gaza; the bill will be much higher now. At the failed Camp David summit in 2000 negotiators discussed a $30bn fund to compensate Palestinian refugees for lost property. Gulf states such as Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates ( <small>uae</small> ), which have boosted ties with Israel in recent years, might be more willing to stump up the cash to show they have not abandoned the Palestinians.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The biggest problem, however, remains not the details of a solution but the political will to negotiate and implement one. There will be no serious peace process with <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/31/bibi-netanyahu-is-the-wrong-man-in-the-wrong-place">Binyamin Netanyahu&#39;s</a> coalition of far-right and religious politicians. That coalition is unlikely to survive long after the Gaza war, and Mr Netanyahu&#39;s opponents hope that the next government will be more amenable to talks with the Palestinians. “We learned a lesson that we need to separate from them in a good way,” says one centrist Israeli lawmaker. “It&#39;s time to start that discussion.” But Israeli politicians from the centre and left have avoided the issue in public for more than a decade.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On the Palestinian side, Hamas has always been eager to play spoiler. Its first suicide-bombings in the 1990s helped to scuttle the Oslo process, and the carnage it wrought during the second <i>intifada</i> (“uprising”) from 2000 to 2005 turned a generation of Israelis against the idea of compromise. Perhaps Hamas will fade away after the war in Gaza—but another group could take its place.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Ordinary people on both sides have lost faith in the two-state solution. A poll in September 2022 by the Israel Democracy Institute, a non-partisan think-tank, found that only 32% of Israeli Jews would support one, down from 47% five years earlier. Israeli Arabs, who make up one-fifth of the population, still endorsed the idea, although their support has also dropped, from 87% in 2017 to 71% in 2022. A plurality of Israeli Jews preferred the status quo.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Support has plummeted even further among <a href="https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/05/11/the-palestinians-need-new-leaders">Palestinians</a> . A survey in June 2023 by the Palestinian Centre for Policy and Survey Research found that just 28% still support a two-state solution. Some 53% of them backed the idea ten years ago, though just 39% thought it feasible.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Optimists hope that these results are squishy: people are unlikely to support something they think impossible. A meaningful peace process could push the poll numbers back up. “I don&#39;t think our people would reject a chance to end the occupation,” says one former Palestinian minister. But the events of recent weeks could just as well harden both sides against the idea of compromise.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As ever in Israel, some of the strongest supporters of ending the occupation are the men tasked with running it. In the wake of the Hamas attack, few Israelis are talking publicly about the two-state solution—or any other solution for the conflict. But defence officials are discussing it in closed rooms. That is partly because the desired end state of the war will shape the war itself and because the Netanyahu government is incapable of holding a serious debate on Israel&#39;s long-term strategy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Then there is the question of who will play mediator. Though Russia and China both aspire to a role in Middle East peacemaking, neither has much leverage or credibility to assume it. The European Union could position itself as an honest broker but it is not taken seriously.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That leaves America. Mr Biden spent the first three years of his presidency trying to ignore the conflict. He will have other things on his mind in 2024—and neither Israelis nor Palestinians are likely to embark on a peace process with a president who could soon be turfed out. If Mr Biden wins in 2024, he could try to lead efforts.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Donald Trump would be another story. In January 2020, after years of trailing a supposedly serious peace plan devised by Jared Kushner, his son-in-law, he finally unveiled it. The plan, almost laughably biased in favour of Israel, was dead on arrival. It would have given the Palestinians just 75% of the occupied West Bank, in three cantons linked by highways. Israel would have kept the Jordan valley, the breadbasket of the territory, and compensated the Palestinians for their loss by ceding a few patches of barren desert in the Negev. Palestine&#39;s capital would have been limited to a few destitute suburbs of east Jerusalem. The Palestinians, unsurprisingly, refused even to discuss the proposal. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:36:15 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/jl5nvrr8n3jovtjirmatljr1ggl3mj81</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2023/11/01/is-a-two-state-solution-possible-after-the-gaza-war </item><item><title><![CDATA[The covid-19 inquiry exposes chaos in Boris Johnson’s government]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>T WAS EASY</small> to get distracted by the foul language. Did Dominic Cummings regret calling ministers “useless fuckpigs”, “morons” and “cunts” in WhatsApp messages, or describing the Cabinet Office as “terrifyingly shit”? Giving evidence to the covid-19 inquiry on October 31st, <a href="https://www.economist.com/1843/2020/11/20/how-dominic-cummings-wasted-the-greatest-opportunity-of-his-life">the one-time chief aide</a> to Boris Johnson was characteristically caustic. If anything he had “understated” the scale of the dysfunction within the government as it grappled with covid.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Many countries have completed short, sharp exercises to draw lessons from the pandemic. Britain&#39;s sprawling inquest will try to dissect the functioning of almost every part of the state. Witnesses will be questioned until at least 2026. Lawyers will pore over a vast trove of documents and try somehow to pin down a narrative.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In retrospect, <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/10/05/how-britain-lives-with-covid-19-today">Britain&#39;s handling</a> of the pandemic does not appear as bad as it once did. On a crude measure of excess deaths, the country ranks close to the middle of the pack, helped greatly by an impressively fast vaccine roll-out. But the inquiry will look at why Britain did so badly before the jabs arrived, probing government decisions over lockdowns, care homes and public-health guidance. This autumn&#39;s hearings, focused on 10 Downing Street and the Cabinet Office, will be among the juiciest sessions. Hovering over them is one question: was the British state badly prepared or were individuals in power spectacularly unsuited to the job?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It is already known, for example, that the country&#39;s national risk assessment failed to anticipate and plan for a novel pathogen, and that the state was slow to adapt the plans it did have for a flu pandemic. The Cabinet Office lacked basic data to track what was happening. In 2021 Mr Cummings told a parliamentary committee that departmental responsibilities for the crisis were horribly muddled. This week he reiterated that the core part of the state supposed to prepare for emergencies was glacially slow to respond.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet the big-name witnesses now appearing on the stand heighten the sense that the chaos was driven by individuals. The portrait of Mr Johnson as a prime minister who was unserious, indecisive and unable to grasp detail is hardly new. Memorable colour is being added, though. In one message Mr Johnson ponders whether older people should accept their fate (while demonstrating a sketchy grasp of the concepts of “median age” and “life expectancy”). As a former media adviser put it on the witness stand this week, covid did “not suit his skill set”. (Mr Johnson himself is expected to appear next month.)</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As for Mr Cummings, he styles himself as a truth-telling maverick interested in systems. Yet he appears to have been incapable of running a functioning office. At one point he moans that meetings in Number 10 did not function on a basic level, when he had been the prime minister&#39;s chief of staff for seven months. On November 1st Helen MacNamara, the deputy cabinet secretary, described a working environment that was toxic, macho and sexist.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> All of which raises difficult questions for Simon Case, the cabinet secretary, who is yet to give evidence. It also bodes ill for Rishi Sunak, who will also appear before the inquiry next month. It is not just that the prime minister will face tough questions about his time as chancellor. It is that Mr Sunak has spent the past year <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/10/05/a-glimpse-of-the-conservative-party-after-rishi-sunak">trying to banish</a> memories of his chaotic predecessors. Instead, the circus is back. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:26:41 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/6cjsjshq1nbf9u1b5i5sld6jj4gpcodj</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/01/the-covid-19-inquiry-exposes-chaos-in-boris-johnsons-government </item><item><title><![CDATA[The commander-in-chief of Ukraine’s armed forces on how to win the war]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>R</span> <small>USSIA&#39;S INVASION</small> of Ukraine in February 2022 provoked a global security crisis. The assault on democracy by a morally sick imperial power in the heart of Europe has tilted the balance of power in other parts of the world, including the Middle East and Asia-Pacific. The failure of multilateral bodies such as the <small>UN</small> and Organisation for Security and Cooperation in Europe to maintain order means that Ukraine can only restore its territorial integrity by military force.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Ukrainians have shown their willingness to lay down soul and body for their freedom. Ukraine not only halted an invasion by a far stronger enemy but liberated much of its territory. However, the war is now moving to a new stage: what we in the military call “positional” warfare of static and attritional fighting, as in the first world war, in contrast to the “manoeuvre” warfare of movement and speed. This will benefit Russia, allowing it to rebuild its military power, eventually threatening Ukraine&#39;s armed forces and the state itself. What is the way out?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Basic weapons, such as missiles and shells, remain essential.但乌克兰武装部队需要关键的军事能力和技术来摆脱这种战争。 The most important one is air power. Control of the skies is essential to large-scale ground operations. At the start of the war we had 120 warplanes. Of these, only one-third were usable.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Russia&#39;s air force has taken huge losses and we have destroyed over 550 of its air-defence systems, but it maintains a significant advantage over us and continues to build new attack squadrons. That advantage has made it harder for us to advance. Russia&#39;s air-defence systems increasingly prevent our planes from flying. Our defences do the same to Russia. So Russian drones have taken over a large part of the role of manned aviation in terms of reconnaissance and air strikes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Drones must be part of our answer, too. Ukraine needs to conduct massive strikes using decoy and attack drones to overload Russia&#39;s air-defence systems. We need to hunt down Russian drones using our own hunter drones equipped with nets. We must use signal-emitting decoys to attract Russian glide bombs. And we need to blind Russian drones&#39; thermal cameras at night using stroboscopes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> This points to our second priority: electronic warfare ( <small>EW</small> ), such as jamming communication and navigation signals. EW is the key to victory in the drone war. Russia modernised its <small>EW</small> forces over the past decade, creating a new branch of its army and building 60 new types of equipment. It outdoes us in this area: 65% of our jamming platforms at the start of the war were produced in Soviet times.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> We have already built many of our own electronic protection systems, which can prevent jamming. But we also need more access to electronic intelligence from our allies, including data from assets that collect signals intelligence, and expanded production lines for our anti-drone <small>EW</small> systems within Ukraine and abroad. We need to get better at conducting electronic warfare from our drones, across a wider range of the radio spectrum, while avoiding accidental suppression of our own drones.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The third task is counter-battery fire: defeating enemy artillery. In this war, as in most past wars, artillery, rocket and missile fire make up 60-80% of all the military tasks. When we first received Western guns last year, we were quite successful at locating and striking Russian artillery. But the effectiveness of weapons such as Excalibur, a <small>GPS</small> -guided American shell, has declined dramatically owing to improved Russian electronic warfare.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Meanwhile, Russia&#39;s own counter-battery fire has improved. This is largely thanks to its use of Lancet loitering munitions, which work alongside reconnaissance drones, and its increasing production of precision-guided shells that can be aimed by ground spotters. Despite the dismissive view of some military analysts, we cannot belittle the effectiveness of Russian weapons and intelligence in this regard.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For now, we have managed to achieve parity with Russia through a smaller quantity of more accurate firepower. But this may not last. We need to build up our local <small>GPS</small> fields—using ground-based antennas rather than just satellites—to make our precision-guided shells more accurate in the face of Russian jamming. We need to make greater use of kamikaze drones to strike Russian artillery. And we need our partners to send us better artillery-reconnaissance equipment that can locate Russian guns.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The fourth task is mine-breaching technology. We had limited and outdated equipment for this at the start of the war. But even Western supplies, such as Norwegian mine-clearing tanks and rocket-powered mine-clearing devices, have proved insufficient given the scale of Russian minefields, which stretch back 20km in places. When we do breach minefields, Russia quickly replenishes them by firing new mines from a distance.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Technology is the answer. We need radar-like sensors that use invisible pulses of light to detect mines in the ground and smoke-projection systems to conceal the activities of our de-mining units. We can use jet engines from decommissioned aircraft, water cannons or cluster munitions to breach mine barriers without digging into the ground. New types of tunnel excavators, such as a robot which uses plasma torches to bore tunnels, can also help.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> My fifth and final priority is to build up our reserves. Russia has failed to capitalise on its hefty manpower advantage because Vladimir Putin is worried that a general mobilisation might spark a political crisis, and because Russia cannot train and equip enough people. However, our capacity to train reserves on our own territory is also limited. We cannot easily spare soldiers who are deployed to the front. Moreover, Russia can strike training centres. And there are gaps in our legislation that allow citizens to evade their responsibilities.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> We are trying to fix these problems. We are introducing a unified register of draftees, and we must expand the category of citizens who can be called up for training or mobilisation. We are also introducing a “combat internship”, which involves placing newly mobilised and trained personnel in experienced front-line units to prepare them.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Russia should not be underestimated. It has suffered heavy losses and expended a lot of ammunition. But it will have superiority in weapons, equipment, missiles and ammunition for a considerable time. Its defence industry is increasing its output, despite unprecedented sanctions. Our <small>NATO</small> partners are dramatically increasing their production capacity, too. But it takes at least a year to do this and, in some cases, such as aircraft and command-and-control systems, two years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A positional war is a prolonged one that carries enormous risks to Ukraine&#39;s armed forces and to its state. If Ukraine is to escape from that trap, we will need all these things: air superiority, much-improved electronic-warfare and counter-battery capabilities, new mine-breaching technology and the ability to mobilise and train more reserves. We also need to focus on modern command and control—so we can visualise the battlefield more effectively than Russia and make decisions more quickly—and on rationalising our logistics while disrupting Russia&#39;s with longer-range missiles. New, innovative approaches can turn this war of position back into one of manoeuvre. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>General Valery Zaluzhny is commander-in-chief of Ukraine&#39;s armed forces. He has held the position since July 2021.</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read a more detailed <a href="https://infographics.economist.com/2023/ExternalContent/ZALUZHNYI_FULL_VERSION.pdf">new essay</a> by General Zaluzhny on this topic.</b></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:54:49 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/gmoi5jboqucq0vf72t4310njnqo58edc</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/01/the-commander-in-chief-of-ukraines-armed-forces-on-how-to-win-the-war</item></channel></rss>