<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[China]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/china?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[China - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 10 日，星期二 05:47:48 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[An unusual museum in China is dedicated to Vinegar Joe]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20America_%20China%20and%20history-a397d34997765a8edd28e3d23ace75eb.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>一个</span><small>奇特的旅游</small>景点坐落在重庆西南部的一个山坡上，俯瞰着嘉陵江。它具有美国武器和军事装备。部分客房装饰有美国国旗。庭院里的石头上刻着富兰克林·罗斯福总统的演讲。这是史迪威博物馆，专门纪念约瑟夫·史迪威的地方。这位令人愤怒的美国将军在第二次世界大战期间在中国服役。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管史迪威已经去世近80年了，但他的名字最近却频频出现在新闻中。八月，中国驻华盛顿大使馆宣布，中国国家主席习近平已回复史迪威孙子约翰·伊斯特布鲁克的一封信。几周后，有报道称习近平还与“飞虎队”的两名老兵进行了通信。“飞虎队”是一群在战争中为中国作战的雇佣美国飞行员。习近平在两封信中都呼吁改善与美国的关系。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">习近平为何要向这些人伸出援手？史迪威博物馆提供了一些线索。它将这位将军描述为中国的“伟大的朋友”。 1942年至1944年，他担任驻中国、缅甸和印度的美军司令，并担任中国<small>国民党</small>政府领导人蒋介石的参谋长。该博物馆建在史迪威在重庆的住所内，重庆是中国的战时首都（当时该城市的名字被罗马化为Chungking）。这位将军的主要任务是帮助中国人抗击日本侵略者，并监督美国向蒋介石军队提供军事援助。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">史迪威绰号“醋乔”，他对自己的盟友有强烈的看法，而且并不害怕表达出来。他经常与被他称为“花生”的蒋介石发生冲突。他在日记中记录了<small>国民党</small>的腐败、优柔寡断和无能。 1944年，根据史迪威的呼吁，罗斯福写信给蒋介石，威胁如果他不授予对所有中国军队的全面、不受限制的指挥权，就要切断援助。史迪威亲手将它交付，并在日记中写道：“鱼叉正好击中了这个小混蛋的太阳神经丛，并穿过了他。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">史迪威对蒋介石的蔑视可能有助于解释为什么允许这样一个博物馆存在。毕竟，<small>国民党</small>也一直在与毛泽东的共产党人作斗争。史迪威奉命促使各方合作对抗日本。博物馆表示，他为毛泽东的军队“做出了积极贡献”，并促进了人们对毛泽东事业的“更好、正确的理解”。这可能有点夸张，但史迪威确实支持派去与共产党建立关系的美国陆军观察团。他还向罗斯福抱怨说，蒋介石正在囤积物资，以便在日本战败后用它们来对抗毛泽东的军队。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国决定于 1991 年开放该博物馆的另一个原因（也是习近平写信的原因）可能是共产党对第二次世界大战的看法不断变化。 1949年控制大陆后，该党因支持<small>国民党</small>而拒绝承认美国在冲突期间提供的帮助。但其态度却慢慢发生了变化。今天，它承认美国在帮助中国抗击日本方面所发挥的作用。此外，习近平领导的共产党已经从把中国描绘成第二次世界大战的受害者，转变为胜利者。研究中国历史的英国学者拉纳·米特(Rana Mitter)在其著作《中国的好战》中写道，这种重新评估帮助塑造了中国在国外的自信和国内日益高涨的民族主义。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">有些人借用二战时期的中美合作来呼吁今天改善关系。习近平在给飞行员的信中表示，美国和中国“应该而且必须实现相互尊重”。但当时的领导人之间缺乏尊重。史迪威在日记中描述了在注意到蒋“坐在手上，高兴地看着那些真正走出去战斗的愚蠢的美国人”之后，他有一种想咬散热器的冲动。在他向<small>国民党</small>领导人递交罗斯福照会后不久，这位将军就被召回了。史迪威与蒋介石的关系已经到了临界点。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:47:55 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/f657r3rjb421158in55e7cikuksu6h8j</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/05/an-unusual-museum-in-china-is-dedicated-to-vinegar-joe </item><item><title><![CDATA[Many of the world’s new mpox cases are in China]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/033%20China%20-%20Public%20health-4ba7a32160cc9276d7e60abd5c0ca8de.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">去年，当mpox（一种以前称为猴痘的疾病）开始蔓延到其流行的非洲地区以外时，<span>全球</span><small>卫生</small>官员感到震惊。它的影响范围迅速扩展到欧洲和美洲，主要是通过性接触。 Mpox 可引起类似流感的症状、疼痛的水泡，在极少数情况下甚至会导致死亡。由于疫苗和健康教育，今年世界大部分地区的病例迅速下降。但在中国则不然。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 7 月和 8 月，该国表示发现了近 1,000 例新病例，占这几个月全球报告的新感染病例的一半以上。这标志着从年初的零感染人数急剧上升。麻疹病毒已在中国蔓延，大陆31个省份中有26个报告感染。卫生官员表示，约 80% 的病例缺乏明确的感染链，这意味着还有许多病例没有被记录。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国之所以成为异类，有几个原因。一是排外情绪。去年9月，中国首席流行病学家吴尊友在社交媒体上发布了无益的建议，称“避免与外国人直接皮肤接触”可以降低感染风险。官方尚未批准任何有效的外国 MPOX 疫苗（就像他们不允许普遍使用外国 Covid-19 疫苗一样）。尽管世界卫生组织建议高危人群和治疗MPO患者的卫生工作者应该接种疫苗，但情况仍然如此。一家中国公司研发的MPOX疫苗仍在试验中。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">保守主义也是一个问题。在中国和其他地方，几乎所有MPO病例都是男男性行为者。在其他国家，事实证明，同性恋者的支持团体在提高人们对病毒的认识和对人们进行检测方面发挥了无价的作用。但多年来，中国一直压制这些团体，认为它们对公共道德和政治稳定构成威胁。地方政府发布的指南称，mpox 对“普通民众”构成的风险很小。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在中国的社交媒体上，许多人在讨论MPOX时使用恐同诽谤。调查显示，中国很少有同性恋或双性恋男性愿意告诉医生他们的性取向，这使得他们更难获得所需的建议。八月份，官员们表示，五名女性被发现患有MPOX（中国此前宣布的感染者均为男性）。有网友表示，这些女性是被“卑鄙”的同性恋者骗结婚的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国对麻疹的反应让人回想起其最初对<small>艾滋病</small>病毒（一种导致<small>艾滋病的</small>病毒）的处理。 20 世纪 80 年代末，中国官员将<small>艾滋病毒</small>视为西方颓废生活方式造成的外国问题。但在 20 世纪 90 年代，许多人在出售血浆时感染了该病毒。直到丑闻曝光后，全国范围内的<small>艾滋病</small>防治运动才获得关注并成功减少感染。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于mpox，官方思维也出现了转变的迹象。 9 月 20 日，政府重新分类了该疾病，将其与<small>艾滋病毒置于同一级别。</small>这应该会释放更多资源来解决这个问题。同样是在上个月，流行病学家吴先生与人共同写了一封信给医学杂志《<i>柳叶刀》</i> ，警告说“如果不立即控制局部传播，MPOX的全球传播可能会加剧”。他建议中国应该开始使用疫苗，并努力减少人们对这种疾病的恐惧。迟到总比不到好。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:47:55 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/jt3666lfl4bc46l9s8ebfldkqbs02nir</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/05/many-of-the-worlds-new-mpox-cases-are-in-china </item><item><title><![CDATA[Communist rappers are luring young disgruntled Chinese]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/031%20China%20-%20The%20Communist%20Youth%20League-55807eb577be827144853392c33c7376.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>为</span><small>庆祝 10 月 1 日中国</small>国庆节，共青团在微博平台微博上向其近 1800 万粉丝发送了一条信息。 “今天，我们作为这个时代的主角，将在这片神圣的土地上书写新的传奇！”它宣称。随附的是一段音乐视频，歌词充满了爱国主义言论，并穿插着毛泽东和中国现任领导人习近平的讲话片段。到目前为止，一切都是可以预见的。令人惊讶的是这位歌手和他的风格：一位说唱歌手，他早期有关毒品和暴力的歌曲被认为不适合公开播放。众所周知， <small>gai</small>已经翻开了新的一页。他现在是联盟的<small>司仪</small>。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">共产党的青年团是一个庞大的组织。它拥有 7400 万党员，几乎与该党 (9800 万) 一样大，尽管它的一些成员同时隶属于这两种党派，但它与党是分开的。它在中国的政治生活中发挥着重要作用。该联盟向14岁至28岁之间的人灌输党的意识形态，培训潜在的党员，并帮助党识别可以培养担任高级职务的人才。它还有一项面向外部的任务：在没有政治关系的年轻人中传播党的信息。 2012年上台后，习近平担心联盟无法胜任这项工作。官员们承认，它已经与中国年轻人脱节了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对党来说，中国的青年人是一个日益严重的问题。经济停滞不前，年轻人失业普遍，住房成本高昂。去年年底，几个城市爆发了由青年领导的小规模抗议活动。它们的目标是习近平严厉的“零新冠”政权（后来被放弃）。上海的一些示威者甚至以非凡的勇气呼吁习近平下台。他会留意1989年的民主动乱，当时联盟的一些官员加入了抗议者行列。那段共产主义世界的动荡时期困扰着习近平。他经常回想起苏联的解体，并将其归咎于意识形态正统和纪律的崩溃。 “共青团犯一千个错误也没关系，”他在2015年引用邓小平的话说。 “但它不能犯的一个错误就是偏​​离党的轨道。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 6月，习近平宣布，自2012年以来，该组织已获得“全新形象”。但就在这个月，联盟主席阿东表示，在国内外“深刻复杂的变化”中，“整个组织的整体斗志和能力亟待提高”。这将涉及推进2016年开始的全面改革。这些改革包括削减臃肿的管理层、扩大联盟的基层影响力以及加强对会员的控制。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">磨练联盟的宣传技巧也是这项努力的一部分。像<small>gai</small> （真名周彦）这样的人正在帮忙。 2018年，中国网民猜测，在<small>gai</small>在真人秀<small>节目</small>中成名后，他在官方批准的平台上表演的日子可能屈指可数了：据报道，那一年政府命令广播公司不得使用代表“嘻哈文化”的艺术家，或者甚至还有运动纹身（ <small>gai</small>有很多：“Badkidz”用英语说）。热爱派对的小报<i>《环球时报》</i>的头条新闻称，“中国说唱歌手退出<small>电视</small>节目后，嘻哈在中国的前景似乎黯淡”。报道指出<small>盖伊</small>从电视广播中消失了。但该报的预测很快被证明是错误的。联盟开始转向包括<small>gai</small>在内的说唱歌手，以使自己看起来更适合该国的年轻人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">联盟通过大量社交媒体帐户推出了以这些歌手和其他歌手为主角的精美视频。据该联盟的报纸<i>《中国青年报》</i>报道，截至去年 8 月，该组织的中央管理机构已运营 26 个此类网站，粉丝总数超过 2 亿。报道称，联盟微信主账号拥有1.1亿粉丝，是社交平台上最大的账号之一。在网上，该组织开始将自己称为<i>团团</i>（“联盟”）。在中文中，双音节会让名字听起来更可爱——熊猫的名字通常都是这样组成的。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">攻击，攻击</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于西方人来说，这些叙述所使用的言辞往往并不讨人喜欢。习近平将新面貌的联盟推向了中国网络民族主义的前线，利用它在互联网上充斥着对西方和任何对共产党持负面看法的中国人的批评。 “为什么我们不能表达自己的意见？” 2013年，他问联盟领导人。“正义战胜邪恶。”当网上积极的声音强大起来时，负面舆论的影响就可以减少。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">联盟账户被用来对西方记者进行尖刻批评，散布虚假信息，并攻击涉嫌试图煽动“颜色革命”的持不同政见者。 2021年，该联盟宣扬了一种阴谋论，称引起covid-19的病毒<small>SARS</small> - <small>C</small> o <small>V</small> -2是由美国军事实验室开发的。联盟在微博上创建的用于传播这个故事的标签已被浏览约 15 亿次——中国人均浏览次数超过一次。最近几周，该联盟的报道激起了公众对日本排放福岛核电站处理后的废水的愤怒，该核电站在 12 年前的海啸中被摧毁，而无视其他地方许多科学家对该计划的支持。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">毫无疑问，民族主义言论让许多中国年轻人兴奋不已。然而，目前尚不清楚该联盟的在线存在在多大程度上帮助它招募了它所说的为该党本身创造“健康和充满活力的新血液”所需的人才。在14岁到28岁之间的中国人中，大约有三分之一是会员（联盟官员的年龄可能更大）。但官方统计数据显示，自习近平就任中国领导人以来，会员人数已减少近 20%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这可能并不能反映出年轻人加入愿望的任何变化。习近平的改革旨在让联盟更加精英化。老师们被告知不要像以前那样为整个班级报名（而且现在仍然是少先队的公认做法，少先队是一个由联盟控制的针对 6 至 14 岁儿童的组织）。学校已获得可招收学生的配额。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">联盟并没有试图提高目标年龄组中会员与非会员的比例。事实上，它已将 2025 年的上限设定为 30%，这表明它计划几乎没有改变。但它正在努力扩大私营企业和<small>非政府组织</small>的成员数量。在中国5000万家注册私营企业中，联盟的存在仍然很小。然而，2018 年至 2022 年 1 月期间，此类企业的联盟分支机构数量增加了两倍多，达到 30 万多个。今年在银川，联盟官员宣布计划到九月在西部城市工业园区的所有企业建立分支机构。在最近开发的名为“智能联盟建设”的数据库的帮助下，该组织可以更好地监控此类活动。所有联盟成员都必须在此系统上注册其个人详细信息。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">习近平急于提升共青团影响力的愿望似乎与人们普遍认为的不一致，即他执政十年中至少有一部分时间与曾在共青团担任高级职务的高层领导人发生过斗争。这些官员通常被称为“<i>团</i>派”成员。在习近平的领导下，他们在党的高层中变得更加边缘化。但几乎没有证据表明该联盟是作为派系堡垒运作的。更有可能的是，习近平更喜欢让自己周围都是以前的同事，而他从未在联盟中担任过职务。巴黎政治大学的杰罗姆·多永 (Jérôme Doyon) 指出，联盟管理部门仍然是各省领导职位招聘的重要来源。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在习近平看来，联盟可以发挥至关重要的作用。甚至十年前，他就警告中国官员，全球“意识形态冲突”涉及“国内外敌对势力”不断西化和分裂中国的努力。他说，这使得为中国年轻人的理想信念提供“强有力的引导”变得更加必要。这就是为什么，除了偶尔去革命遗址和在社区做好事之外，新兵们可以有充足的时间在课堂上学习习近平的思想。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 17:43:52 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/9eum7f9s5sm1sngn4m6nto74vvueetla</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/10/02/communist-rappers-are-luring-chinas-disgruntled-youth</item><item><title><![CDATA[Politics hamper China’s efforts to stimulate the economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/035%20China%20-%20The%20economy-1af8fe58d6eb8b2c5d73a0e873dc5a6b.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>十年</span><small>前，</small> 200多名中共中央委员会成员齐聚北京，召开“三中全会”，这是一次传统上专门讨论经济问题的五年一度的会议。全会承诺让市场而非国家“在资源配置中发挥决定性作用”。自2012年以来担任中国领导人的习近平未能兑现这一承诺，这在很大程度上解释了过去十年对<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/24/why-chinas-economy-wont-be-fixed">中国经济的</a>失望。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但经济当前的困境有所不同。今年的问题不在于国家发挥过于决定性的作用而牺牲了市场。最紧迫的困难是市场和国家在资源调动和配置方面的决定性不够。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">消费者<a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/08/17/chinas-consumers-officials-and-statisticians-all-lack-confidence">失去了信心</a>。他们不愿意挥霍或投资，而是宁愿将钱存入银行存款。他们尤其对购买曾经是经济支柱的房地产持谨慎态度。这使得恒大这样的房地产开发商无法摆脱破产困境。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">再加上出口低迷，消费者的犹豫不决已经影响了大流行后的经济复苏。 5月至8月公布的工业生产、零售销售和出口等数据均远低于预期。增长放缓与价格下降同时发生。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">过去，中国政府对此类经济衰退采取了强有力的应对措施。 2008年全球金融危机袭击该国时，政策制定者发起了贷款和支出热潮，迅速使经济增长重回正轨，尽管世界其他地区却步履蹒跚。但面对今年的经济放缓，政府和消费者一样犹豫不决、胆怯。它的犹豫暴露了目前阻碍中国刺激措施的一些政治和意识形态限制。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在大多数经济体中，对经济放缓的“第一响应者”是央行。中国货币当局确实在六月份降息，但幅度不大。它将 7 天利率降低了 0.1 个百分点，随后在 8 月份进行了第二次相同规模的降息。 （许多西方国家出于对通胀的担忧而加息，而中国不存在通胀问题。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与其他新兴经济体的政策制定者一样，中国的政策制定者担心大幅降息将削弱人们对人民币的信心并削弱银行的盈利能力。但这种限制还有另一个因素。中国的政治体系没有容纳激进、英勇的央行行长的空间。这个国家只有一位“大师”（曾经授予美国联邦储备委员会主席的术语）。那就是习先生。为了保留自主权，中国央行官员必须谨慎行事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">传统上，经济责任由中国的二号官员——总理承担。过去担任这一职位的人拥有抵御灾难和恢复增长的影响力和进取心。 1998年亚洲金融危机席卷中国时，朱镕基誓言将经济增长保持在8%，鼓舞了士气。相比之下，现任总理李强就显得较弱。他于三月上任，其职位完全归功于习近平。他的使命——维护繁荣——仍然很重要。但它常常在维护广义安全方面处于次要地位。李先生精力充沛，见多识广。斯坦福大学的吴国光表示，他仍然认为国务院（中国的内阁）仅仅是党的思想的实施者，而不是党的思想的来源。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">曾经泡沫十足的房地产市场或许是最大的担忧。自2021年年中以来，该公司一直处于低迷状态，当时对开发商过度借贷的监管限制开始发挥作用，导致恒大和其他公司违约。这些限制不仅仅是技术官僚措施。它们是一场激烈的、准意识形态运动的一部分，用习近平的口号来概括：“房子是用来住的，不是用来炒的”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这场运动非常成功。 8 月份的公寓销量比 2019 年 8 月的水平低 47%。在市场稳定之前，经济仍将脆弱。但重新调整意识形态运动是很困难的。监管机构放宽了首次购房者的定义，让更多人受益于更宽松的抵押贷款条款。他们降低了人们必须提供的现金首付。一些城市取消了对公寓的价格管制。负责制定政策的 24 人政治局在 7 月份的公报中删除了习近平的口号。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但习近平和他的下属都不能轻易承认他的竞选走得太远。他们也无法大声宣扬另一种口号，这种口号可能会在不引起人们注意的情况下提振市场。因此，对情绪的影响依然存在。 9月22日，恒大表示，令人失望的销售业绩迫使其推迟了债务重组计划。彭博社透露恒大集团董事长许家印受到警方监视后，恒大股份于 9 月 28 日停牌。人脉广泛的许先生既是该集团不幸的根源，也是其复苏的关键。所有这些都不会激发人们对其他陷入困境的开发商的生存能力的信心。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 2008年中国成功的经济刺激计划不是由北京官员而是由地方政府带头的。到习近平上台时，这种模式的成功已被过度行为所掩盖。此前，地方政府在中央政府实施的严格财政约束下相互竞争以促进增长。刺激措施打破了这种微妙的政治平衡。地方政府通过表外“融资工具”大量举债，使它们摆脱了财政束缚，并允许它们犯下更昂贵的错误。事实证明，他们的债务胃口很顽强。高盛银行表示，这些车辆目前欠债约 60 万亿人民币（超过 8 万亿美元）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">习近平决心对地方政府实施更严格的财政约束。这意味着他们没有能力领导另一轮刺激计划。相反，中央政府可以自己做更多的事情。一些经济学家敦促政府向穷人提供消费券或救济品。但国家似乎不愿意直接帮助家庭。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这可能反映了这样一种观点，即公共投资或减税等刺激经济的替代方法具有双重打击：它们有助于刺激需求，并通过建设基础设施或激发创业活力来改善经济的供给侧。对施舍缺乏热情也可能反映出习近平个人对“福利主义”的厌恶，他警告说，“福利主义”会导致懒惰。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最近几周，中国政府开始对经济放缓做出更有力的反应。它延长了对人们以旧房换取更好房子的税收减免。它谈到了改造所谓的“城中村”，这些曾经是乡村的土地在中国大城市向外扩张时被吞并了。仅 8 月份，地方和中央政府就发行了价值约 1.2 亿元人民币（1,650 亿美元）的债券，是今年前 7 个月平均水平的两倍多。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230930_CNC702.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">经济似乎也正在触底反弹。 8月份出口量高于一个月前。社会消费品零售总额和工业生产增速有所改善。消费者价格已停止下降。中国的经济数据最近开始超出预期（见图表）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">为了提升这些期望，习近平可能会在下一次全会上专门修改和阐明他的经济理念。他可以承诺更加优先考虑市场而不是国家、繁荣而不是安全、开放而不是强硬。与此同时，他的下属们还得继续应付过去。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:10:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/99pc6t2iom6t1acqlbhp9mbqu10p3eq0</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/28/politics-hamper-chinas-efforts-to-stimulate-the-economy </item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s persecution of Uyghurs extends to those it once favoured]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/036%20China%20-%20Rahile%20Dawut-a2d5965bf711d72764bb9f1ed504074e.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>拉希勒</span><small>·达吾提（Rahile Dawut）</small>曾经是中国的当权派人物。这位57岁的维吾尔族人类学家是一名共产党员。国家资助了她在新疆大学的一些工作，该大学是该地区最好的大学，她是该大学的教授和少数民族研究中心的创始人。她曾获得文化部颁发的奖项，2000年会见了国家主席江泽民，并登上了维吾尔族腹地新疆一家官方杂志的封面。但2017年12月，在告诉亲戚她要去北京后，达吾提女士（如图）失踪了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于达吾特女士的遭遇，目前还没有官方解释。但代表中国政治犯开展活动的对话基金会表示，他们已从政府消息来源获悉了她的命运。据该基金会称，达吾提女士因宣扬分裂主义和“危害国家安全”而被捕。 2018年，在新疆的一次秘密法庭审理中，她被定罪并被判处无期徒刑。她随后对判决提出上诉，但败诉。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达吾特女士的朋友和以前的学生表示，对她的指控是荒谬的。他们形容她是一位很少谈论政治的务实学者。多年来，她巧妙地应对了中国学术研究的严格限制。他们说，达吾提女士不是持不同政见者，而是国家迫害维吾尔少数民族的另一个受害者。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">自 2017 年以来，大约有 100 万维吾尔族和其他少数民族进入了新疆的“再教育营”，这是政府强制同化运动的一部分。该国以对恐怖主义和分裂主义的担忧为其行动辩护。批评者指责它是文化灭绝。对话基金会表示，达吾提女士是“自 2016 年以来被拘留、逮捕和监禁的一长串且不断增加的维吾尔知识分子名单（据统计超过 300 人）之一”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，达吾提女士的突然倒下还是有些奇怪，让观察人士感到困惑。挪威维吾尔人权组织创始人阿卜杜韦利·阿尤普 (Abduweli Ayup) 表示，她的高调可能使她成为目标。他表示，也许官员们想以她为榜样，让其他人遵守规矩。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达吾特女士的国际关系可能也引起了当局的担忧。她是剑桥大学、宾夕法尼亚大学等西方多所大学的访问学者。中国官员声称，外国势力试图破坏新疆的稳定，并对维吾尔人与外界的任何接触表示怀疑。该团体的成员有时很难获得护照。有些人仅仅因为出国旅行而被拘留。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">没有被遗忘</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">达吾提女士就读<small>于</small>北京师范大学，主修民俗学，是第一批获得<small>博士学位</small>的维吾尔族女性之一。她的早期作品绘制了分布在新疆各地的穆斯林圣地（称为<i>麻扎）</i>的地图，受到了学者的称赞。在接下来的几年里，她记录了维吾尔族民间传说和宗教传统，通常关注女性的角色。她还指导年轻学者。她在新疆大学的办公室和位于该地区首府乌鲁木齐的房子是当地和访问研究人员的中心。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但在她失踪前的几年里，达吾特女士的研究变得越来越敏感。她的作品记录了当地习俗被消灭之前的情况，这与官方创建以汉族为主体的单一中国身份的努力发生了冲突。在过去的十年里，许多<i>麻扎</i>因拆除朝圣者留下的祭品而被毁坏或亵渎。其他的则变成了主要吸引汉族游客的景点。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在最近的外交部新闻发布会上，发言人毛宁表示，她不了解达吾提的案件。官员们保持沉默。台湾历史学家约书亚·弗里曼 (Joshua Freeman) 认识达吾提女士二十年了，他认为自己知道原因。 “他们的沉默说明了一切，”他说。 “在国家眼中，她真正的罪行是出生为维吾尔族。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:10:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/hi1mh0rpqaoe7l4b8t4vnmq8oeujmks4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/28/chinas-persecution-of-uyghurs-extends-to-those-it-once-favored </item><item><title><![CDATA[After an unsuccessful boycott, women’s tennis is back in China]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/037%20China%20-%20Women_s%20tennis-35093781fcfe5cc8eac03f9e3bfc82a2.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 2021年，中国网球明星彭帅（如图）指控一名共产党要人性侵<small>后不久</small><span>，</span>她的运动管理机构女子网球协会（ <small>WTA</small> ）暂停了在中国的所有赛事。总部位于美国的<small>世界网球协会</small>呼吁对彭丽媛的指控进行“全面、公平、透明且不受审查”的调查。但那并没有发生。尽管如此， <small>WTA</small>又回来了。中国公开赛于9月下旬开始。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>WTA</small>的抵制并不是第一次中国政府未能给出结果的此类抵制。西方领导人以担心中国侵犯人权为由，拒绝参加 2022 年北京冬奥会。但火炬一旦点燃，他们的信息基本上就被观众遗忘了。许多中国人并不知道<small>WTA</small>的抵制，因为彭女士的指控遭到了审查。官方媒体称，由于疫情，比赛被暂停。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>WTA</small>也不是第一个发现对中国采取原则立场代价高昂的体育联盟。 2019年，美国国家篮球协会休斯敦火箭队总经理表示支持香港的民主抗议活动。中国的回应是暂时禁止<small>NBA</small>比赛的转播，导致联盟损失数亿美元。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">过去两年， <small>WTA</small>取消了中国大陆和香港的赛事，留下了数百万美元的损失。商业利益无疑在其屈服过程中发挥了重要作用。在抵制之前，中国帮助推动了<small>WTA的</small>发展，主办了包括<small>WTA</small>总决赛在内的大量赛事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该协会承认，远离祖国收效甚微。自从提出指控后，彭女士反驳了这些指控。 Observers believe she was under pressure from the authorities to do so. Chinese women who come forward with similar claims are often treated poorly. In 2018 a former intern at <small>CCTV</small> , the state broadcaster, went public with allegations that a prominent host had groped her, leading many women to speak up. Yet the former intern not only lost her legal case, but was sued for defamation. (The host withdrew the case on September 25th.)</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Gender equality is, theoretically, a central tenet of the Communist Party. But the government has muffled the country&#39;s #MeToo movement, lest it turn into political dissent. On September 22nd two well-known supporters of the cause went on trial in southern China for “inciting subversion of state power” (foreign diplomats and journalists were barred from the courthouse). The activists have already been held for two years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The <small>WTA</small> has been assured that Ms Peng is living safely with her family. She is rarely seen in public. When it announced its boycott, the association said it did not want to let powerful people suppress the voices of women. Yet that is exactly what has happened. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:10:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/n64rjqqcpvfollvo5bmqsnhobm52ghgj</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/28/after-an-unsuccessful-boycott-womens-tennis-is-back-in-china </item><item><title><![CDATA[How China uses UNESCO to rewrite history]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/031%20China%20-%20China_s%20heritage%20sites-60b94d31e0a4153d7b2145b4599de2e9.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>P</span> <small>U&#39;ER TEA</small> is an earthy brew beloved of dieters for its digestive qualities. Its leaves come from the forests of Jingmai mountain in south-west China, which was listed as a World Heritage site by <small>UNESCO</small> , the cultural arm of the United Nations, on September 17th. The designation, China hopes, will boost tea sales and lure tourists to the region, which is near the border with Myanmar, Laos and Vietnam. Chinese officials work hard to obtain the <small>UNESCO</small> stamp of approval. Only Italy has more such sites. No country comes close to China in terms of the number of cultural practices recognised by the organisation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But there is more to China&#39;s efforts than increasing tea sales and tourism. The Communist Party claims that present-day China, which has dozens (perhaps hundreds) of ethnic minorities, is a single nation with a continuous history stretching back thousands of years. National identity is conflated with that of the Han, the ethnic group accounting for more than 90% of the population. China&#39;s heritage laws aim to maintain “the unification of the country” and foster “social harmony”. In practice, this often means distorting history so that it aligns with the party&#39;s view of the past and reinforces its vision of nationhood.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> When <small>UNESCO</small> conceived its record of World Heritage sites in the 1970s, China was intent on crushing its cultural relics. Today, though, China donates more money and sends more delegates to the international body than any other country. Many of the sites ratified by <small>UNESCO</small> , such as the Great Wall, are well known. But others, along with certain cultural practices, are put forward in order to legitimise the party&#39;s rule over regions with large ethnic minorities, says Christina Maags of Sheffield University. Areas such as Xinjiang and Tibet have not always been part of China, nor dominated by the Han. Yet the party&#39;s version of history tells a different story.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the far-western region of Xinjiang, over 40% of the population are Uyghur, an ethnic minority. Their culture, language and Muslim faith set them apart from much of China. The Uyghur heartland began to fall under formal Chinese control in the mid-18th century—revealingly, the Manchu rulers of the Qing dynasty named it Xinjiang, meaning “new territory”. Over the past decade the party has forced Uyghurs and other ethnic minorities in the region to assimilate. After 2017 perhaps a million of them passed through “re-education camps”. Security remains intense, with the government citing concerns about terrorism and separatism. Activists say it is erasing the Uyghur culture.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> None of this is reflected in the government&#39;s nomination of the Tianshan mountains in Xinjiang as a World Heritage site. “Since ancient times, people of all Chinese nationalities have lived on this fertile land and have created a rich material culture and spiritual civilisation,” reads the application. It describes a Xinjiang of Han military towns and transportation centres and cites Han poets who lauded the Tianshan mountains. In nearly 1,000 pages of documentation the Uyghurs are mentioned only a handful of times, often as part of a list of ethnic groups who live in the area. A similar history of Xinjiang was put forward by the Chinese government when a portion of the Silk Road was up for <small>UNESCO</small> recognition. The region was described as a cultural belt that saw the “integration” and “continuous fusion” of Han people with “local residents”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> When Mao Zedong&#39;s guerrillas seized power in 1949, China&#39;s borders were not clearly defined, nor its population entirely submissive. In 1950, when Communist troops invaded Tibet, they were not welcomed by its residents as liberators, as the party claims. Promises of autonomy were broken, leading to an abortive Tibetan uprising against Chinese rule in 1959. The history approved by <small>UNESCO</small> , though, suggests a more harmonious past. In 2013 the organisation accepted the records of Tibet from China&#39;s Yuan dynasty (1279–1368) into its “memory of the world”. These were proof, said the government in Beijing, of an ancient period when imperial rulers were “highly tolerant of the religious, political system and culture of Tibet”—and also evidence that the integration of Tibet into China under the Yuan was lasting.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> All for one</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To bolster the idea of a Han-centric identity, the party seeks to dilute the contributions of minority groups in <small>UNESCO</small> claims. For example, documents filed with the organisation state that Tibet&#39;s Potala Palace, the winter home of Dalai Lamas from 1649 to 1959 (pictured), exhibits the skills of many ethnic groups, not just Tibetans. The government uses “radical selectivity” in choosing which places, people and practices to emphasise, says Rachel Harris of the School of Oriental and African Studies, part of the University of London.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The state is also selective about what cultural practices it ascribes to different groups. The Han are typically credited with “civilisation building”, says Juheon Lee of Midwestern State University in Texas. So the group is associated with applications involving high culture, such as the Peking opera, or technical expertise, such as bridges. In contrast, ethnic groups in border regions are nominated for folk practices like medicinal bathing (Tibetans) and throat singing (Mongols).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>UNESCO</small> tends not to dispute China&#39;s claims. Nor would it be safe for historians in China to do so. Ms Harris notes that Uyghur scholars are locked up for asserting a different version of history. But the party&#39;s effort to put forward its own interpretation has been slowed, at least. In 2018 <small>UNESCO</small> changed its rules so that a country could nominate just one new site a year. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 12:51:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/opiklvsf7cq8mi80k1kpd550v27rb5gd</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/21/how-china-uses-unesco-to-rewrite-history </item><item><title><![CDATA[China tells its citizens to be on the lookout for spies]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20Counter-espionage-350ab2360c3cc20b0c53cb1ba29b8b0c.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>sea-cucumber</small> farm is not an obvious target for spies. So when a group of foreigners turned up at one in north-east China last year, the owner, Mr Zhang, did not think much of it. According to state media, the guests received permission to install seawater-quality monitors. After they left, Mr Zhang noticed that the equipment was not working properly. It also had a mysterious, beeping antenna attached to it. So he called the authorities. They said it was transmitting strategic data on China&#39;s oceans to “hostile powers”. The foreigners were found and arrested.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Stories like this, true or not, serve the purpose of China&#39;s intelligence agency, the Ministry of State Security ( <small>MSS</small> ). It claims that the kind of espionage discovered by Mr Zhang is rampant—and ordinary Chinese must help to stop it. On August 1st the <small>MSS</small> joined WeChat, a popular messaging app, to implore “all of society” to look out for spies. This followed a comment by William Burns, the <small>CIA</small> director, that America had made progress in rebuilding its spy networks in China a decade after dozens of its sources were killed or disappeared.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The government is doing its part to increase public awareness. It has offered rewards of up to 500,000 yuan ($68,500) for reporting spies. In the city of Zhengzhou, warnings about foreign snoopers have been placed on the back of bus seats. Elsewhere officials are using leaflets, lectures and comic strips to get the message out. In the region of Xinjiang officials produced a short film depicting a spy disguised as an amateur photographer. The spy asks a taxi driver to take him to a military base. The alert driver takes him to the police.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A specific appeal has been directed at young people. The <small>MSS</small> says it wants “the seeds of national security to take root and sprout” in their minds. Local branches of the ministry have joined up with schools to put on classes and exercises. One of these, at Xiamen University earlier this year, saw students play spies and spy-hunters. Middle-schoolers in Shanghai are taught about national security on board a mock aircraft-carrier, while dressed in fatigues.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But things get tricky when students go abroad. Officials worry they will be lured into spying for foreign powers. The <small>MSS</small> has shared cautionary tales on WeChat. In one, a Chinese student in Italy is said to have been recruited by American spooks over fancy dinners and trips to the opera. Another is said to have got too friendly with an American embassy official in Japan. Both of the students returned to China and sold secrets to the <small>CIA</small> ; they have since been caught and punished, says the <small>MSS</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The ministry&#39;s campaign has gone down well with some members of the public. Netizens have warned government workers not to share too much about their jobs online, in case spies are reading. A video that claims the <small>CIA</small> was behind the recent deaths of several engineers and scientists has over half a million views.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Others, though, think the government is going too far. Hu Xijin, a well-known nationalist commentator, complained that people are growing increasingly scared to meet foreigners, lest they be reported. On Weibo, a social-media site, some users worried about a return to the days of the Cultural Revolution, a decade of Maoist madness when neighbours, friends and even family members informed on each other. “History is a circle,” said one person. “Tragedies like sons reporting on fathers seem to be getting close again.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The increased paranoia will make life even harder for foreigners in China. A photo circulating on social media shows an American teacher in Shanghai explaining to his class that he is not a spy. Your correspondent was recently intercepted by officials while on a reporting trip. A member of the public, the officials explained, had seen a foreigner asking questions. Being a good citizen, they had called it in. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 12:51:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/pp3libjck6a7bd94tbno0bu9jmh4ohmf</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/21/china-tells-its-citizens-to-be-on-the-lookout-for-spies </item><item><title><![CDATA[China wants to be the leader of the global south]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/033%20China%20-%20Chaguan-227a1c5abdcdc3a2e434b1d5590a45d8.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>t is not</small> every day that someone from Xi Jinping&#39;s inner circle drops a reference to Zhou Enlai, Mao Zedong&#39;s chief diplomat. Yet Zhou&#39;s dapper ghost hung over a recent speech given in Havana to developing-world leaders by Li Xi, boss of the feared Central Commission for Discipline Inspection. Indeed, the whole speech was filled with nods to the past. Mr Li recalled mid-20th-century struggles for “national independence and liberation”. He mentioned the “Bandung Spirit” and “Five Principles of Peaceful Coexistence”. That refers to the Bandung Conference of 1955, at which Zhou committed China to a path of non-aggression and non-interference in the affairs of other Asian and African countries.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The discipline-enforcement boss was sent to Cuba as Mr Xi&#39;s personal envoy to a summit involving China and emerging economies from the <small>G</small> 77 group. He promised that China will “always be part of the developing world and a member of the global south”, no matter how advanced it becomes. By way of explanation, Mr Li reached back into history. China is forever bound to other nations that fought colonial-era “exploitation and oppression”, he said.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Li, a member of the Politburo Standing Committee, the top leadership body, was not speaking off the cuff. Nor was his cold-war history lesson a one-off, inspired by the sight of shark-finned old Cadillacs chugging through Havana. China has launched a new, concerted campaign to present itself as a natural leader for the developing world, starting with countries that have painful memories of bullying by colonial powers or by America.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On September 13th the foreign ministry published a “Proposal of the People&#39;s Republic of China on the Reform and Development of Global Governance”. This urges sweeping changes to the rules and institutions that oversee international development, security and human rights. It finds many lessons in history. America (referred to as a “certain country”) is told to learn from past wrongdoing, including ignoring Russia&#39;s “legitimate security concerns”, making “wanton use” of sanctions and hampering scientific progress with “hegemonic” controls on technology sales.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the name of redressing “historical injustices”, China calls for developing countries to be given a much greater say at the United Nations, including seats for Africa on an expanded Security Council (the proposal makes no mention of China&#39;s rival, India, a developing giant that has long sought a seat on the council). Restating long-standing Chinese arguments, the proposal calls the rights to subsistence and development “the basic human rights of paramount importance.” All other rights must bow to “national realities”. To advance that worldview, China proposes that <small>UN</small> human-rights bodies should employ more citizens from developing countries as soon as possible. More clearly than ever before, the document weaves together Mr Xi&#39;s big foreign-policy proposals, from the Belt and Road Initiative to the Global Development Initiative, Global Security Initiative and Global Civilisation Initiative. It presents them as China&#39;s unified plan for tackling everything from climate change to the regulation of cyberspace. The stated goal: to create a “better future for humanity”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The proposal was followed days later by a joint statement issued by Mr Xi and Zambia&#39;s president, Hakainde Hichilema, who was on a state visit to China. The statement names and endorses Mr Xi&#39;s various global initiatives in turn. China&#39;s preferred foreign policies are presented as in the common interest of developing countries. Rich states are reminded of their “inescapable historical responsibilities over climate change”, and told to take the lead in reducing emissions. Zambia declares China a new model for countries seeking independent paths towards modernisation. Independence is relative, of course. Zambia owes China billions of dollars. After long resistance, Chinese lenders agreed to restructure much of this debt in June, but largely by extending maturities and offering to suspend interest payments for some years, rather than by writing off loans.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Towards a China-crafted, China-led order</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Chinese officials and scholars detect a turning-point in history. Many low- and middle-income countries resent Western arguments about right and wrong. They blame sanctions on Russia, imposed by Western countries over its invasion of Ukraine, for high food and energy prices. In response, China is presenting itself as leader of something resembling a new, non-aligned movement. China calls for “true multilateralism”, delivered by international bodies, from the <small>UN</small> to the World Bank and International Monetary Fund, that are no longer dominated by America and other rich liberal democracies. It talks of respecting the diversity of the world&#39;s civilisations: code for rejecting liberal values as a form of Western-centric racism.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China&#39;s non-aligned posture does not stand much scrutiny, though. In the original non-aligned movement, Egypt, India, Yugoslavia and others gained clout by forming an ideologically unpredictable and diverse group, says Richard Gowan of the International Crisis Group, a think-tank. This time, for all the “mood music about anti-colonialism”, what China is offering is “a coalition of states that China would lead”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> By declaring that a rich China would still be a developing country, Chinese leaders are manipulating language so that “developing” ceases to be an economic term and means “non-Western”, says a diplomat. The goal is to rally non-Western countries around Mr Xi&#39;s favoured vision for global governance. Some will be wary, adds the diplomat, for they wish “to diversify their strategic, economic and political interests”, not sign up to a China-led bloc.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Still, foreign leaders can expect pressure to endorse China&#39;s new proposal for global governance. It contains so many Xi-branded initiatives that Chinese diplomats must promote it, or risk seeming disloyal to their supreme leader. Chairman Mao&#39;s long-suffering envoy, Zhou Enlai, would understand. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read more from Chaguan, our columnist on China:<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article69628-prod.ece">Xi Jinping builds a 21st-century police state</a> (Sep 14th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/07/the-belt-and-road-as-seen-from-china">The Belt and Road, as seen from China</a> (Sep 7th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/when-china-thought-america-might-invade">When China thought America might invade</a> (Aug 31st)</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Also: How the Chaguan column <a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">got its name</a></i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 12:51:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/pv6kiqp2d5fogc20idp7ug9broerl810</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/21/china-wants-to-be-the-leader-of-the-global-south </item><item><title><![CDATA[The disappearance of China’s defence minister raises big questions]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/030%20China%20-%20Leadership%20purges-52fda46e33371e1abf928cf0eb5525f3.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>n ability to</small> groom talented officials, China&#39;s leader, Xi Jinping, once said, “largely determines the rise and fall, as well as the survival or demise” of political parties and countries. After a sweeping reshuffle of ministerial posts in March, the government&#39;s main news agency, Xinhua, recalled Mr Xi&#39;s words in an article aimed at showing how meticulous the selection process had been. Since late June, however, two of the most senior officials who were promoted in that shake-up have disappeared: first Qin Gang, the former foreign minister, and more recently General Li Shangfu, the defence minister. The swiftness of their apparent downfalls has been striking. The questions they raise about China&#39;s politics are big.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is no sign that this is an existential moment for the Communist Party, or Mr Xi&#39;s rule. Adulation of Mr Xi continues unabated in state media. He stayed away from the <small>G</small> 20 summit in Delhi on September 9th and 10th—an unprecedented absence. But on September 16th and 17th Wang Yi, who succeeded Mr Qin as foreign minister in late July, met America&#39;s national security adviser, Jake Sullivan, in Malta. According to Bloomberg, they discussed a possible meeting between Mr Xi and President Joe Biden at a gathering of Asia-Pacific leaders scheduled for November in San Francisco. China&#39;s military activities appear unaffected, too. On September 17th and 18th about 100 Chinese fighter jets flew around Taiwan, an unusually high number in such a space of time.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But the churn at the highest levels of the state and military apparatus has been unusually fast, even by the standards of Mr Xi&#39;s purge-filled tenure. General Li has not been seen in public since August 29th, when he appeared at a China-Africa security forum. He was supposed to attend an annual meeting with Vietnamese defence officials on September 7th and 8th. But that plan was scrapped, with Chinese officials citing the general&#39;s health. Unspecified illnesses seem to be a common problem for those in political trouble. Mr Qin was said to have a health condition, too. But according to the <i>Wall Street Journal</i> , senior Chinese officials were told in secret last month that he had “lifestyle issues”. They allegedly involved an extramarital affair, resulting in the birth of a child, while Mr Qin was ambassador in Washington before becoming foreign minister.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On official websites, no change has been indicated in General Li&#39;s duties. But American and other officials have told Western media that they believe he has been relieved of his post. Reuters reported that he was suspected of corruption related to the procurement of military equipment, which he oversaw from 2017 to 2022. The news agency said that eight senior officials from the procurement department were being investigated, too.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is also speculation that graft is a reason for the replacement in late July (announced in state media) of General Li Yuchao and General Xu Zhongbo. They were the two most senior commanders of the Rocket Force, which controls China&#39;s nuclear and conventional missiles. General Li Yuchao had been put in charge only last year. A less high-profile but equally unusual personnel change came to light on September 1st with the dismissal of Major General Cheng Dongfang as president of the People&#39;s Liberation Army military court after just eight months in the job. No reason was given. General Cheng had previously served as spokesman of China&#39;s military garrison in Hong Kong.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On Chinese social media, censors have stifled most discussion. Only one comment is visible on the post of a user with more than 670,000 followers who hinted at the defence minister&#39;s absence. “Aren&#39;t you afraid of having your account closed down?” it says. “Don&#39;t talk about him.” But given Mr Xi&#39;s efforts to portray China&#39;s political system as a more stable and effective alternative to liberal democracy, the purges have provided rich pickings for his foreign critics. On X (formerly Twitter) America&#39;s ambassador to Japan, Rahm Emanuel, compared the turnover to Agatha Christie&#39;s novel, “And Then There Were None”. He later offered another literary analogy: “As Shakespeare wrote in Hamlet, &#39;Something is rotten in the state of Denmark&#39;.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To be sure, the posts of defence minister and foreign minister are not as critical in China as they often are in other countries. Neither General Li nor Mr Qin are among the 24 members of the Politburo, the apex of political power. But the ministerial jobs involve defending the country&#39;s interests abroad. (In China&#39;s eyes, Mr Qin&#39;s alleged behaviour may have made him a security risk.) And the purges raise questions about Mr Xi&#39;s ability to select the right talent and his capacity to scare officials into avoiding corruption.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The moves have targeted people who were clearly Mr Xi&#39;s men. Mr Qin&#39;s elevation to the rank of foreign minister was unusually rapid, suggesting he may have impressed Mr Xi during a stint as the chief organiser of his foreign trips. He was promoted last year to the party&#39;s Central Committee and in March got the additional title of state councillor (a senior role in China&#39;s cabinet). Only four others hold that rank, including General Li. The defence minister is also a Central Committee member and one of the six officers who work under Mr Xi in the armed forces&#39; governing body, the Central Military Commission.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Team of no rivals</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> General Li and Mr Qin were among many people close to Mr Xi who benefited from the reshuffle in March as well as another one last October involving party jobs. The overhaul produced a ruling team more seemingly in lockstep with the paramount leader than any since the era of Mao Zedong. In China, questions will certainly be asked (in whispers) about how stable it is.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But Mr Xi must be used to muttering. His previous purges have affected hundreds of thousands of officials, high and low, including many in the services most vital to maintaining the party&#39;s grip on power: the armed forces, the police and the spy apparatus. Most of the fallen have been accused of corruption, but some, too, of political wrongdoing. Last September courts imposed lengthy prison sentences on several security chiefs accused of being corrupt, as well as members of a disloyal cabal. They included a former deputy minister of public security and a former justice minister. In 2015 Zhou Yongkang—a retired head of China&#39;s internal security services and former member of the Politburo&#39;s Standing Committee—was sentenced to life in prison for bribery and leaking state secrets. Mr Xi accused him and other jailed associates of attempting to “seize power”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> If General Li is replaced as defence minister, there could be an upside for America. Last August, in response to a visit to Taiwan by the then speaker of America&#39;s House of Representatives, Nancy Pelosi, China halted regular talks between the two countries&#39; defence establishments. America is keen to restart them, seeing them as useful for discussing ways of preventing unintended clashes.但在从事采购工作时，李将军于2018年因从俄罗斯购买战斗机和导弹而受到美国制裁。 China wants the sanctions to be lifted before talks resume. Removing the man himself may resolve an impasse. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 20 Sep 2023 19:13:43 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/qev86m9m987bll93sc86d74t1a92s2vt</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/20/the-disappearance-of-chinas-defence-minister-raises-big-questions</item><item><title><![CDATA[The mystery surrounding China’s missing defence minister]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>M</span> <small>AO ZEDONG</small> used to say that political power grows from the barrel of a gun. In other words, controlling the armed forces is key to any leader&#39;s success. Xi Jinping, China&#39;s current supremo (and a keen student of Mao), appears to believe the same, having built his authority to a large extent on his sweeping overhaul of the People&#39;s Liberation Army ( <small>PLA</small> ) in the past decade. Yet just as those changes were supposed to be bearing fruit, a broadening purge of the <small>PLA</small> ’s top ranks is calling into question its capacity to fight—and Mr Xi&#39;s to lead.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The latest blow came with reports on September 14th and 15th that General Li Shangfu, who was appointed defence minister and state councillor (a senior role in China&#39;s cabinet), in March, was recently detained for questioning. General Li, who is 65, has not been seen in public for more than two weeks, and was suddenly pulled out of an annual meeting with Vietnamese defence leaders that was scheduled for September 7th and 8th. Chinese authorities blamed a “health condition”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China&#39;s government has not confirmed any of the reports. A foreign-ministry spokeswoman said she wasn&#39;t aware of the situation when asked to comment at a routine briefing. But if the news is accurate, it will be the first time in about six years that such a fate has befallen a sitting member of the Communist Party&#39;s Central Military Commission, which controls the armed forces and is headed by Mr Xi.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这也表明，他的清洗远远超出了控制<small>解放军</small>常规导弹和核导弹的<a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/03/what-to-make-of-a-surprise-shake-up-in-chinas-nuclear-force">火箭军</a>。 In July the authorities announced the sudden dismissal of General Li Yuchao, the commander of the Rocket Force, and General Xu Zhongbo, its political commissar. No reason was given. But there has been speculation that they could be under investigation for corruption or leaking military secrets.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A less high-profile but equally unusual personnel change came to light on September 1st with the dismissal of Major General Cheng Dongfang as president of the <small>PLA</small> military court after just eight months in that post. No reason was given. A graduate of the prestigious Peking University, General Cheng had previously served as head of the legal department and spokesman of the <small>PLA</small> garrison in Hong Kong.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Since all four generals&#39; appointments would have been approved by Mr Xi, if not personally decided by him, their downfall also raises questions about his judgment—or his ability to vet personnel effectively. So too does the equally sudden removal as foreign minister of <a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/07/25/chinas-missing-foreign-minister-loses-his-job">Qin Gang</a> , who was given that post by Mr Xi in December. The Chinese authorities cited health reasons for that change as well.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One possible explanation is that the four generals&#39; problems are all connected to the Rocket Force. Its share of the military budget is thought to have expanded in recent years as it has been overseeing a major upgrade of China&#39;s nuclear arsenal. There has been no suggestion of corruption so far but big military-spending schemes have often enabled embezzlement, kickbacks and other misuse of funds.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Xi&#39;s new choices to lead the Rocket Force also suggest that he is trying to break up the kind of patronage networks within the service that have often led to corruption in the past. The force&#39;s new commander, General Wang Houbin, is a career naval officer. Its new political commissar, General Xu Xisheng, comes from the air force.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A second possibility surrounding General Li Shangfu&#39;s predicament is that it relates to his own long involvement in weapons development and procurement—another fertile ground for corruption. An engineer by training, he spent three decades working at China&#39;s main satellite-launch centre, eventually becoming its director.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> From 2017 to 2022 he headed the Central Military Commission&#39;s Equipment Development Department. America imposed sanctions on him in 2018 for his role in China&#39;s purchase of Russian combat aircraft and missile equipment. In July this year, the department announced a fresh crackdown on corruption, calling for tips about abuses dating back to 2017.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But there could be several other explanations, such as a failure to follow Mr Xi&#39;s orders or another breach of military discipline. As defence minister, General Li is principally responsible for military relations with other countries and does not oversee operations. In that sense, his dismissal might not have immediate effects on the <small>PLA</small> ’s capacity to fight.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Nonetheless, it would almost certainly be damaging to morale within the <small>PLA</small> and to the armed forces&#39; public image at home and abroad. The <small>PLA</small> ’s corruption and ineffectiveness before Mr Xi took power could be blamed on his predecessors. But its current problems suggest he has had less success than he hoped in turning it into a leaner—and cleaner—fighting force capable of taking on America in a war over Taiwan, the self-governing island that China claims.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are no signs of any organised challenge to Mr Xi&#39;s authority. However, the turmoil in the <small>PLA</small> is likely to amplify doubts about his ability to govern effectively as he confronts a wide range of challenges, including a slowing economy, crippling local-government debt and a rapidly ageing population.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The purges are also rich pickings for Mr Xi&#39;s foreign critics as he seeks to portray China&#39;s political system as a more stable and effective alternative to Western-style liberal democracy. Rahm Emanuel, the American ambassador to Japan, compared China&#39;s government to an Agatha Christie novel, “And Then There Were None”, in a post last week on X, a social-media platform. After the reports about General Li on September 15th, he offered another literary analogy: “As Shakespeare wrote in Hamlet, &#39;Something is rotten in the state of Denmark&#39;.” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 15 Sep 2023 16:59:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/fvkpds75ljfdlobte54edh02753u0pc4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/15/the-mystery-surrounding-chinas-missing-defence-minister</item></channel></rss>