<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[China]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/china?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[China - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 9 月 12 日，星期二 18:57:27 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[The Belt and Road, as seen from China]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/030%20China%20-%20Chaguan-902e6a7a59b0114d662c0c225cf14968.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>多年来</span><small>，</small>习近平一直邀请世界搭乘“中国发展的快车”。这句口号是习近平最喜欢的，是在习近平与外国领导人讨论经济合作时提出的，特别是通过“一带<small>一路</small>”倡议，这是十年前本月推出的一项全球基础设施计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于外国评论家来说，这种狂妄的言论是一个错误。是的，他们断言，贫穷国家的当地精英可能会欢迎中国特使为新机场、水坝和其他基础设施提供贷款。但普通民众越来越反对如此庞大的项目，谁能感到惊讶呢？对于那些乘坐头等舱的人来说，特快列车看起来与那些必须在铁轨上艰难生活的人截然不同。考虑到这一点，一些外国政界人士和分析人士怀疑中国是否可能将<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议视为一个价值数万亿美元、损害声誉的错误。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事实上，中国正在重新设计<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>——但是为了拯救它，而不是废除它。外国的不满是原因之一，因为中国在非洲、亚洲和其他地区最可靠的一些朋友正在为<small>“一带一路”</small>债务而苦苦挣扎。但西方的批评者可能忽视了重新设计的另一个重要原因。随着中国经济放缓，习近平自己的臣民对这一计划越来越持怀疑态度，特别是在当地人对<small>“一带一路</small>”倡议推动繁荣的希望已经破灭的地方。中国领导人意识到了这种不满。本月晚些时候，国务院新闻办公室将发布白皮书，纪念<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议十周年。该项目的一名顾问向宣传官员描述了他的建议：用具体例子强调该计划对国内普通中国人的好处。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">为了感受这种情绪，查官前往东川国际铁路中心，这是位于西北部甘肃省的一个物流园区。它坐落在省会兰州的边缘，位于干旱的棕色山脉之间的山谷中。兰州曾经希望通过开往中亚和欧洲的货运列车的铁路枢纽来赚钱。当地官员谈到要设立外国领事馆，这与过去作为丝绸之路骆驼商队的重要停靠站的情况相呼应。东川铁路站确实有开往欧洲的火车，官方媒体最近谈论了一条通往阿富汗的新铁路和公路货运路线。但工作日的早晨却出奇的安静，几辆中国制造的汽车开着，装上运输车。成都、郑州和西安等较为繁荣的省会城市作为<small>“一带一路”</small>交通枢纽的表现要好得多。事实上，甘肃这个贫困省份的每年进出口贸易总额自2013年以来实际上一直在下降。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">该党可以从舆论中得到一些安慰。当地人在铁路站场附近闲逛，谈论着中国的慷慨。罗女士是一位退休科技人员，她称<small>“一带一路”</small>是中国实力的标志。 “中国正在帮助其他国家，这是一件好事，”她说，并忠实地指出当地年轻人已经在附近建造仓库的物流公司找到了工作。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">东川仓库外就是河口，一个被修复为旅游胜地的丝绸之路古镇。说实话，它的清朝海关大厅和街市有点荒凉，附近的高速公路很吵。尽管如此，当地司机苏先生还是带了一些外地的中国游客到那里。苏先生认为中国异常仁慈，并对指责<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>推进“侵略性目标”的外国人表示不满。他断言，中国不同：“西方人考虑事情会对他们产生怎样的影响，但中国人有牺牲精神。”尽管如此，苏先生承认兰州并没有像他预期的那样从<small>“一带一路”倡议中获益，</small>而且官方媒体有时夸大中国的善行。 “国家领导人着眼大局，”他谨慎地说。但他承认：“从一个普通人的角度来看，我认为没有必要在非洲这样遥远的异国他乡花很多钱。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在兰州的白塔山公园，俯瞰黄河，一位养老金领取者在与朋友跳舞的间隙表示，普通人很难理解<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议。他表示，中国在较贫穷国家进行的十年大规模投资的回报不足。他的感觉是该计划现在正在缩小。那个精明的养老金领取者是对的。有很多迹象表明，人们正在放弃只提供长期回报的新的大型投资。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">较小的项目，较大的抱负</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">兰州大学“<small>一带一路</small>”研究中心主任朱永标表示，中国正在转向“小而美”的项目。较小的项目可以快速产生效益，并让当地人民有更大的“主人翁意识”。朱先生称这一转变是对受援国政治变化和中国人民需求的回应，其中一些人认为“<small>一带一路”</small>对外国人来说是“免费的钱”。他认为，只要“欧洲和美国愿意投入真金白银”，美国和欧盟提出的基础设施计划就是值得欢迎的竞争。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">北京人民大学国际事务研究所所长王义伟表示，由于自己的贷款资金减少，中国正在为<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议寻找全球资金，包括来自富裕穆斯林国家的资金。他说，这就是为什么沙特阿拉伯加入<small>金砖</small>四国并在中国的支持下与伊朗和解“非常重要”的原因之一。除此之外，中国不再关注资助和建设大型项目，而是越来越多地关注治理问题，因为中国领导人将规范、体系和标准视为可持续发展的关键。他认为， <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>的创建是为了解决中国的经济问题。现在它的使命是从民粹主义和那些呼吁分裂和脱钩的声音中拯救全球化。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">习近平将于十月在<small>“一带一路”</small>论坛上接待外国领导人。代表们可能会期待更多关于中国包容性模式的讨论，以及中国如何尊重不同国家的政治和法律传统，这与西方民主国家不同。未来几年，中国可能会减少对外国铁路的资助。在制定规范和标准方面，它的野心是走向全球。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><b>阅读我们的中国专栏作家查官的更多内容：<br></b><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/when-china-thought-america-might-invade">当中国认为美国可能入侵时</a>（8月31日）<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/the-world-should-study-chinas-crushing-of-hong-kongs-freedoms">世界应该研究中国对香港自由的压制</a>（8月24日）<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article66978-prod.ece">从地面看中国经济放缓</a>（8月17日）</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>另：茶馆柱如何<a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">得名</a></i></p></div>]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 14:20:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/s5bo6i3v8srkqio0q3p4rqq2db290ucq</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/07/the-belt-and-road-as-seen-from-china </item><item><title><![CDATA[The path ahead for China’s Belt and Road Initiative]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1y6lujj e1whazj10"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>习近平</span>2013 年 9 月 7 日在哈萨克斯坦发表的讲话中<small>几乎没有</small>暗示，他正在考虑在中国数千亿美元的贷款和投资的刺激下，在世界范围内掀起一场混凝土浇筑热潮。没有人预料到该项目将成为他外交政策的一个决定性特征以及中国崛起为全球大国的戏剧性象征。习近平谈到沿着古老的“丝绸之路”建设连接中国和欧洲的“经济带”。他呼吁改善基础设施并减少贸易壁垒。如果他有一个宏伟的计划，那么莱德就会被埋葬在对历史和哈萨克诗歌的沉思中。西方震惊了。</p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/029%20China%20-%20The%20Belt%20and%20Road%20Initiative-11dfccafdbba00236cf44625a2b627ae.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text">中国即将大张旗鼓地庆祝该项目十周年。它将宣传<small>“</small>一带一路”倡议（该计划的正式英文名称），作为给世界的礼物，创造了巨大的经济利益。中国声称，“一带一路”带来的经济增长已为<small>“一带一路”</small><small>沿线</small>国家创造了42万个就业岗位，4000万人摆脱了贫困。美国及其许多盟友认为， <small>“一带一路”</small>倡议远没有那么温和：它是一种政治工具，旨在压制外国对习近平铁腕统治的批评，并为那些让其他国家背负沉重债务的中国企业提供支持。</p><p class="article__body-text">在富裕国家中，中国的<small>“一带一路”</small>庆祝活动无助于缓解焦虑。其中的亮点将是定于 10 月在北京举行的“一带一路”论坛。世界领导人已被邀请，但预计西方国家不会出席。最重要的客人将是俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京。他与习近平一起出席，将突显西方许多人所看到的<small>“一带一路”</small>面纱背后的真相：中国试图兜售另一种发展模式，避开民主，为独裁者创造一个安全的世界。在该活动的筹备过程中，中国一直在努力留住已签署该计划的<small>七国集团</small>成员——意大利。其副总理安东尼奥·塔贾尼刚刚访问北京并传达了一个信息：他的国家可能会退出。</p><p class="article__body-text">预计 9 月 9 日至 10 日在德里举行的 20<small>国集团</small>会议上会遇到更多阻力。总统乔·拜登将提出另一种愿景，即通过加强世界银行和<small>国际货币基金组织</small>的作用来帮助较贫穷的国家。他的国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文表示，这些机构“建立在并继续体现<small>美国的</small>领导地位”。他补充说，这些将在对抗中国“强制性和不可持续的贷款”方面提供“最大的效益”。由于不明原因，习近平计划缺席这次聚会。</p><p class="article__body-text">当<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>启动时，人们几乎没有意识到中国和西方之间即将在公路、铁路、港口和管道建设等听起来很无辜的事情上展开斗争。习近平在哈萨克斯坦的讲话几乎没有引起人们的注意。近一个月后，他在印度尼西亚发表了另一篇演讲，他在演讲中呼吁建立“海上丝绸之路”。直到第二年，习近平才开始用“一带一路”来概括这两个想法。一些西方官员确实对此感到畏缩：对于一个涉及数十个国家的复杂计划来说，这个词听起来过于以中国为中心且过于简单化。所以中国调整了外国人的名字（不是中文）。 2015年，它成为<small>“一带一路”</small> 。 </p><figure class="g-fallback"></figure><figure class="interactive-figure"></figure><p class="article__body-text">那是在中国和西方之间本已紧张且不信任的关系开始急剧恶化之前。唐纳德·特朗普 (Donald Trump) 直到 2017 年才成为美国总统，对中国发动贸易战，这场贸易战将成为美国针对中国改变全球规范行为的更广泛行动的一部分。四年前，欧盟开始称中国为“系统性竞争对手”。对新疆穆斯林的大规模拘禁和香港对异见的全面镇压仍是未来的事情。即使在西方，中国也敞开了大门。<small>欧盟</small>27个成员国中有18个签署了<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议。</p><p class="article__body-text">其中之一是希腊，该国在2009年遭受了经济崩溃。中国已经就位。 2008年，中国国有航运巨头<small>中远</small>集团达成协议，租赁位于雅典南部的中国主要港口比雷埃夫斯港的两个集装箱码头。 2016年，希腊在<small>欧盟</small>和<small>国际货币基金组织</small>的金融救助者的压力下采取了进一步措施，要求其通过国有资产私有化来筹集资金。它同意将整个工厂51%的股份出售给<small>中远集团</small>。欧洲港口首次由中国公司控制。 2021 年，它又购买了 16% 的股份。</p><p class="article__body-text">中国取得了胜利。其官员称比雷埃夫斯为“<small>一带</small>一路”在欧洲的“龙头”。习近平在2019年访问后表示，该港口证明“<small>一带一路”</small> “不是口号、不是故事，而是成功的实践和光辉的现实”。这确实令人印象深刻。<small>中远集团</small>介入之初，比雷埃夫斯港在全球集装箱港口中排名第93位。现在它已跻身前 40 名。中国制造的巨型蓝色起重机从船上卸下集装箱，在<small>中远集团</small>成立之前，这些集装箱对于港口来说太大了，无法搬运。自从该公司抵达并开始大规模升级以来，比雷埃夫斯港的集装箱装卸能力已增长了四倍多。</p><p class="article__body-text">但如果中国希望获得一个重要港口的控制权将使其在<small>欧盟</small>和<small>北约</small>成员国中获得持久的政治影响力，那么它可能会失望。在授予<small>中远集团</small>控制权后，希腊阻止<small>欧盟</small>发表攻击中国在南海行为及其人权记录的声明。然而，一个更加亲美的政府在 2019 年上台。“希腊人不再将中国视为其经济的救世主。事实上，民意调查显示希腊公众越来越目中无人，”华盛顿智库卡内基国际和平基金会 2021 年的一份报告称。</p><p class="article__body-text">近年来，欧洲各地对中国的态度发生了很大变化。<small>欧盟</small>加强了对外国投资可能存在的安全风险的审查。欧洲只有少数大型<small>“一带一路”</small>项目。其中之一是由中国贷款资助的匈牙利和塞尔维亚之间正在建设的高速铁路线。中国最终希望将其与比雷埃夫斯港连接起来，但北马其顿和希腊仍在考虑如何推进其路段。</p><p class="article__body-text">中国在非洲的影响力要广泛得多，早在<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>提出之前，中国就已经是非洲的重要参与者。该计划促进了中国对从铁路线到港口等大型基础设施项目的参与。撒哈拉以南非洲吸收了<small>“一带一路”</small>贷款的很大一部分。但随着各国负债累累，许多贷款都变成了坏账。对于中国来说，非洲已经成为一个金融泥潭。</p><h2>为谁设下的陷阱？</h2><p class="article__body-text">中国的银行愿意放贷，但也很精明。大部分信贷是按照商业条款授予的。这些银行一直抵制西方通过注销部分贷款来帮助非洲国家的呼吁。但今年六月，中国与其他外国政府债权人一起与赞比亚就如何重组数十亿美元的债务达成协议，其中大部分欠中国。那是一个转变。中国通常更愿意通过秘密双边会谈来解决此类问题。尽管如此，它还是不同意理发。</p><p class="article__body-text">一些西方官员抱怨说，中国一直在设置“债务陷阱”，以诱骗粗心的<small>“一带</small>一路”贷款接受者：其想法是，当借款人违约时，中国可以获取让步，例如重要基础设施的所有权。一个据称的例子是，在斯里兰卡政府陷入债务困境后，一家中国公司于 2017 年收购了中国在斯里兰卡建造的港口汉班托塔 (Hambantota)。但几乎没有证据表明那里或其他地方有人故意设置陷阱。</p><p class="article__body-text">相反，中国的银行一直在没有对风险进行适当评估的情况下放贷，从而让自己陷入困境。现在，他们更愿意让借款人维持生计，而不是让他们陷入困境。根据美国研究组织 AidData 的一份报告，2016 年至 2021 年间，他们提供了 1850 亿美元的救助贷款。报告称，2010年，中国海外贷款中只有不到5%用于支持陷入困境的借款国。到 2022 年，这一数字已上升至 60%。中国的银行对此类贷款也持相对强硬的态度。 AidData 在 3 月份撰文表示，<small>国际货币基金组织</small>救援贷款的利息通常为 2%。中国人的平均税率是5%。</p><p class="article__body-text">中国可能正在吸取教训。另一家研究公司荣鼎集团(Rhodium Group)表示，在2016年达到峰值后，其对外贷款已经下降。 “在经历了备受瞩目的失误之后，中国的大型银行正在重新评估其贷款行为，”报告称。 2020年，中国向非洲政府新增贷款不到20亿美元。这是自 2004 年以来的最低金额。</p><p class="article__body-text">亲密盟友巴基斯坦也出现了类似的情况，该国的一家<small>“一带一路”</small>旗舰企业已谈及在道路升级和发电厂等大型项目上支出高达 600 亿美元（尽管只有约一半已落实）。它被称为中巴经济走廊 ( <small>CPEC</small> )，旨在刺激越过山区边境直至西南 1,500 多公里处的瓜达尔港的贸易。中国自2013年起开始管理瓜达尔港，但该港口的发展与比雷埃夫斯港的成功没有任何关系。它一直受到武装暴力和巴基斯坦政治冲突的困扰。该国与<small>中巴经济</small>走廊相关的大量借贷助长了债务危机。它一直在向<small>国际货币基金组织</small>和中国寻求帮助。</p><div class="article__body-text-image"><figure> <span><meta><img src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/608/739/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/243/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/365/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/486/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/729/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/778/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/972/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/1215/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/1556/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNC477.png 1280w" sizes="336px" alt></span></figure><p class="article__body-text">但中国仍然坚持<small>中巴经济走廊的</small>想法。对于周边国家来说， <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>具有更重要的意义。中国将其在基础设施建设方面的帮助视为安全保障和商业机会，在某些情况下为其能源进口提供替代陆路路线，绕过马六甲海峡，而马六甲海峡是美国可以扼杀的咽喉要道。就巴基斯坦而言，中国希望获得多重红利。它认为，繁荣的巴基斯坦可以制衡中国的竞争对手印度。它不太可能煽动可能蔓延到邻国新疆的暴力极端主义。西方安全专家推测瓜达尔可能成为中国海军基地（尽管有传言，但没有确凿证据表明中国正在那里建造海军基地）。</p><p class="article__body-text">在世界部分地区， <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>将变得不那么大胆和鲁莽。但出于安全和经济原因，中国将继续在自己的后院推行这一想法。伦敦智库国际战略研究所（ <small>IISS</small> ）表示，东南亚将成为特别关注的焦点。报告称，对中国来说，“没有一个地区比这更具战略重要性”。在与西方关系日益紧张的情况下，中国越来越关注其经济安全。国际战略<small>研究所</small>表示：“它希望利用<small>‘一带一路’</small>为其商品创造替代市场，并在供应链中创造替代环节，”特别是为中国的高科技产品。东南亚国家对这些连锁店至关重要。</p><p class="article__body-text">正在取得进展。 2021年，中国完成了一条耗资近60亿美元的新铁路线建设，将中国昆明市与亚洲最贫穷国家之一老挝的首都万象连接起来。老挝 422 公里的路段穿过山脉，这些山脉上仍散布着越南战争中未爆炸的美国炸弹。近一半的轨道位于隧道中。</p><p class="article__body-text">四月，乘客开始使用该线路过境。从万象到中国边境的旅程曾经是颠簸的一天，现在只需 3.5 小时即可顺利行驶。老挝农民已开始种植榴莲等高价值作物，通过火车销往中国。北京小报<i>《环球时报》</i>最近的头条新闻称，“<small>美国</small>在老挝投下炸弹，中国修建铁路”。这是<small>“一带一路</small>”信息中反复出现的一个特点：中国是仁慈的，美国是恶霸。这在老挝的一些人中引起了共鸣。老挝国立大学的普佩·基菲拉冯 (Phouphet Kyophilavong) 表示，中国是“我们可以学习的老大哥”。</p></div><p class="article__body-text">但民意调查显示，在中国附近的国家，公众对中国的影响力更加警惕，他们认为中国的影响力正在增长。在万象的谈话中，老挝分析人士经常批评政府未能从中国项目中获取更多利益。他们表示，老挝在偿债上花费太多，以至于忽视了教育等关键需求。</p><p class="article__body-text">老挝负债累累。截至 2022 年底，中国欠外国贷款人 105 亿美元，相当于其<small>GDP</small>的 84%。大约一半的钱是从中国借来的。去年，老挝的外汇储备大幅下降，以至于难以购买燃料。信用评级机构警告称，该公司已接近违约。中国允许老挝推迟偿还债务。</p><figure> <span><meta><img width="1280" src="https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/720/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg" srcset="https://www.economist.com/img/b/200/113/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 200w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/300/169/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 300w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/400/225/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 400w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/600/338/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 600w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/640/360/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 640w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/800/450/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 800w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1000/563/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 1000w, https://www.economist.com/img/b/1280/720/90/media-assets/image/20230909_CNP001.jpg 1280w" sizes="(min-width: 720px) 640px, 95vw" alt></span><figcaption>龙的头</figcaption></figure><p class="article__body-text">中国将中老铁路视为更长铁路网的其中一站，希望该铁路网最终将昆明与新加坡连接起来。对于中国来说，这条线路的成功并不取决于老挝750万人口如何使用它。更重要的是在更富裕的泰国铺设铁路，泰国的人口数量是泰国的十倍。这项工作正在进行中，尽管在整个地区完成该项目将受到泰国和马来西亚混乱的政治、项目条款的艰难谈判（老挝相对容易相处）以及一些当地立法者对与老挝走得太近的警惕的困扰。中国。</p><p class="article__body-text">辨别<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议的真正含义可能很困难。它经常被与马歇尔计划相比较，马歇尔计划是美国在第二次世界大战后为重建欧洲提供的资金。但事实并非如此。 <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>活动涉及援助的很少。事实上，许多<small>“一带一路”</small>国家都相对富裕。全球已有超过 150 家企业签署了该计划。其中约一半被世界银行标记为中上收入或高收入国家。丝绸之路语言具有误导性。加入没有地域限制。</p><p class="article__body-text">但它可能如何演变正变得越来越清楚。 2015年，中国表示，“<small>一带</small>一路”倡议还将打造一条“数字丝绸之路”，这是一种奇特的说法，用来形容中国企业（无论是国有企业还是私营企业）在电信和云计算等行业寻求海外业务。西方，尤其是美国担心，中国旨在利用低价尖端技术占领市场，从而威胁西方安全并侵犯个人自由。美国与中国的科技战在一定程度上是对这种担忧的回应。</p><p class="article__body-text">随着各国应对债务冲击以及中国国内经济增长疲软， <small>“一带一路”的</small>措辞变得更加谨慎。 2021年，习近平呼吁开启新阶段，强调“小而美”的工程。这些将有更高的标准和更好的回报，并涉及绿色能源和数字基础设施等行业。他表示，中国将停止在海外建设燃煤电厂。<small>国际战略研究院</small>表示，即使在疫情期间，中国对海外数字技术的绿地投资也在稳步增加。</p><p class="article__body-text">在官方媒体上，习近平提出的新想法已开始与<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>争夺关注度。全球发展倡议、全球安全倡议和全球文明倡议只是概念而非行动计划，但隐含着强烈的信息：中国的发展模式比强调人权的西方模式更适合贫穷国家、西方军事联盟威胁世界和平对中国共产主义的批评相当于对中国古代文化的种族主义攻击。</p><p class="article__body-text">但<small>“一带一路”倡议</small>远未被放弃。在下个月北京峰会的筹备过程中，中国官方媒体正在宣传一条信息。问题在于，该计划是习近平先生所珍视的项目。作为对他的明显致敬，共产党于 2017 年同意将推行<small>“一带一路”</small>倡议的任务写入党章，从而使怀疑它成为异端邪说。国家电视台的报道显示，习近平视察世界各地的项目，仿佛亲自传递了中国的财富。 8月的一篇文章称赞他“开辟了一条造福各国的‘幸福之路’”。换句话说， <small>“一带一路”倡议</small>还有充足的生命力。 <span>■</span></p><p class="article__body-text"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:45:53 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/9bnficufkfno9c9ls5a7ph1vbdc4dnkh</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/09/06/the-path-ahead-for-chinas-belt-and-road-initiative </item><item><title><![CDATA[China has embraced pets, but animal welfare is still a problem]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/028%20China%20-%20Animal%20welfare-16c71c4eac3bedfed0e2d44fd947cb78.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>毛泽东</span>可能认为它们是资产阶级<small>的</small>奢侈品，但宠物在中国正在兴起。中国城市中约有 1.16 亿只猫和狗与人类同住。并不总是清楚谁在掌控。最近在上海举办的宠物展上，出售的商品包括猫用水疗机和狗用舞会礼服。分析人士表示，年轻人越来越多地选择“毛宝宝”而不是儿童。去年中国宠物行业增长25%。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对这些四足朋友的关心也以其他方式表现出来。<small>非政府组织</small>在城市设立了救助收养中心。最近，在北京附近的洪水期间，人们使用皮划艇救出了数十只猫和狗，这是对动物生命的关注，这在大约一代人左右的时间里会让许多中国人感到困惑。活动人士敦促政府通过一项禁止虐待动物的法律，并禁止狗肉贸易，因为只有一小部分人吃狗肉。这些领域已经取得了一些进展。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但总体而言，中国的动物福利状况仍然严峻。这就提出了一个难题。中国城市的“宠物父母”听起来就像许多富裕社会的动物爱好者一样忧伤，并且同样坚信他们的毛茸茸的伙伴具有独特的个性。问问上海宠物展上的 25 岁刘凡就知道了，她带着她的猫去海滩看日出。但当谈到农场动物时——包括猪，这种比狗或猫聪明的物种——中国严峻的福利标准往往和贫穷得多的国家一样残酷，在这些国家，动物有感情或权利的想法是一种难以想象的奢侈。民意调查和消费者消费习惯表明，农场和屠宰场持续受到恶劣待遇的原因之一是公众对这种残忍行为普遍漠不关心，其中包括痴迷的宠物主人。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与往常一样，这会产生巨大的影响，因为中国幅员辽阔。虽然中国人的人均肉类和鱼类消费量远远落后于西方人，但中国是牲畜最多的国家之一。对食品安全的担忧导致大型农场的经营方式得到改善。但在改善动物福祉方面却几乎没有采取任何措施。伦敦的一个压力组织世界动物保护协会按照<small>A</small> （优秀）到<small>G</small> （差）的等级，给中国的农场动物福利评分为<small>G</small> （英国为<small>D</small> ，美国为<small>E</small> ）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">西方农场并不是避难所，但许多地方的情绪已经转向反对在中国仍然普遍存在的做法。中国农场的动物可以不经击晕就被宰杀。鸡通常被塞进狭窄的铁丝笼子里。猪越来越多地被饲养在大型设施内。批评者表示，这增加了疾病爆发和大规模扑杀的风险，而不良的标准会导致动物疾病传染给人类。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管在英国等国家，散养鸡蛋的销量已经超过了笼养鸡蛋，但这样的标签在中国却很少见。很少有公司愿意对动物福利做出任何声明。一些分析人士认为，存在一个尚未开发的食品市场，可以证明这些食品来自经过良好处理的牲畜。毕竟，中国不断壮大的中产阶级正在追求更高品质的有机食品。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，调查显示，许多中国人对他们所吃的动物的福利相对不感兴趣。 2018 年的一项调查发现，只有 37% 的人认为用作食物的动物能感受到与人类一样的疼痛。不到一半的人认为善待这些动物很重要。美国、巴西、印度和俄罗斯的受访者表现出更多的同情心。似乎很少有中国人基于对动物痛苦（而不是他们自己的健康）的担忧来做出饮食选择。不到5%的中国人是素食者。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">休斯敦市中心大学的彼得·李说，教育是问题的一部分。一些中国人认为，活动人士希望为动物提供许多人类仍然缺乏的舒适感。一名在上海展会上为孤独的狗出售机器人伙伴的男子认为，牲畜与宠物不同，不需要得到很好的对待。事实上，他说，“无痛宰杀的动物味道不如自然宰杀的动物”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国的一些人，包括许多民族主义者，认为动物福利的观念是西方引进的，与中国文化不一致。这一立场最著名的倡导者是于 2020 年去世的清华大学前教授赵南元。他称支持动物权利的论点是“洋垃圾”，并声称活动人士与“新帝国主义者”勾结（运行）也许是狗）。为撰写本文而联系的一位动物权利学者表示，这个话题变得过于敏感。他们要求匿名，以免被贴上外国特工的标签。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不过，中国有自己善待动物的传统，就像佛教徒所倡导的那样。活动人士还可以提到台湾，这是一个有着共同文化和历史的岛屿，而且那里的动物福利得到了更认真的对待。台湾约有14%的人口是素食者。李先生认为，真正从西方进口的是工厂化养殖——一种旨在最大限度提高产量的畜牧方式，但往往涉及不人道的待遇。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">目前，政府对改善动物福利兴趣不大。它更关心粮食安全和通过保持低价格来维护社会稳定。咨询公司 Trivium China 的 Even Pay 表示，在养殖动物方面，监管机构不会出台繁琐的规定，除非他们认为这对公共健康是必要的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “改革开放”以来的几十年里，中国的肉类和海鲜消费迅速增长。许多人，尤其是那些记得困难时期的人，认为这是进步的标志。但活动人士看到了一个日益严重的问题。尽管未来十年美国等地的肉类消费量预计将下降，但中国的肉类消费量预计将持续增长。因此，挑战在于让中国人相信动物福利的改善也是进步的标志。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>订阅者可以订阅我们新推出的每周通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">《鼓楼》</a> ，了解世界如何看待中国，以及中国如何看待世界。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:03:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/ck3eees8rmb0b0cg8ukk9er1ftvnch9n</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/china-has-embraced-pets-but-animal-welfare-is-still-a-problem </item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s Communist Party has co-opted ancient music]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/029%20China%20-%20Culture-245cbb905cff71a1161559e14c7b5441.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">伦敦市中心的<span>一座</span><small>教堂</small>里传来<i>古琴</i>轻柔的叮当声。伦敦国际中国音乐节的观众（如图）被告知，这种七弦乐器的声音将把他们带回到过去，给他们带来欢乐与平静。掌握<i>古琴</i>已有 3000 多年的历史，一度被认为是中国帝制精英的必备技能。连孔子也玩过。如今，共产党希望<i>古琴</i>和其他传统乐器也能为自己带来欢乐，弘​​扬中华文明和党自诩的中华文明的体现。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 20世纪90年代末，一位名叫郎朗的年轻中国钢琴家成为古典音乐明星，与世界顶级乐团合作演出。在2008年北京夏季奥运会开幕式上，他发挥了核心作用。但当北京在 2022 年再次举办奥运会（这次是冬季奥运会）时，开幕式以<i>古筝</i>和<i>琵琶</i>等中国民间乐器为特色。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于中国共产主义前的历史，共产党的创始人几乎没有什么好话可讲。但现任领导人习近平支持旧乐器的复兴。它们被列入中国<small>联合国教科文组织</small>“人类非物质文化遗产”提名名单。这是庆祝过去辉煌的更广泛努力的一部分。习近平表示，中国古代文化是民族的“根和魂”，他的目标是树立“文化自信”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">中国经常用自己的文明作为盾牌，抵御西方国家对人权和民主的批评。习近平建议，他们不应试图将自己的价值观强加于中国独特的文化之上。 At the same time, China is presenting a softer side to the West in the form of plucked strings and piped tunes. The party sponsors international festivals and concerts. Earlier this year Mr Xi and Emmanuel Macron, the president of France, enjoyed a <i>guqin</i> recital in the southern city of Guangzhou.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The party has a history of co-opting music for its own causes. Under Mao Zedong ostensibly old folk songs were rewritten with revolutionary lyrics and sometimes composed from scratch, says Kai Tang of the University of Music and Performing Arts Vienna. The solo repertory associated with the <i>dizi</i> , a traditional form of flute, was composed almost entirely after 1949 and, in the early days, made up mostly of revolutionary music.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Today, the effort to revive ancient instruments is showing some signs of success. Moyun, a Chinese musician who plays covers of pop songs on her <i>guzheng</i> , has 2.3m followers on Bilibili, China&#39;s equivalent of YouTube. Abigail Washburn, an American banjo player, released an album in 2020 with Wu Fei, a Chinese composer and <i>guzheng</i> player. But the plinks of ancient instruments are still drowned out by the piano, which 40m Chinese are learning to play. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:03:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/p1nr6r0as3ob6o0d7h399inn66frm5uq</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/chinas-communist-party-has-co-opted-ancient-music </item><item><title><![CDATA[An old health insurance scheme in China may have saved millions]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/031%20China%20-%20Health%20insurance-4fa94c78c0e22889f214db0bb88eb178.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>na country</small> of 1.4bn people, even small improvements in health care can have a big impact. That appears to have been the case with the New Co-operative Medical Scheme ( <small>NCMS</small> ), a health-insurance plan for rural Chinese that was launched in 2003 and folded into a more comprehensive programme in 2013. Though it is perhaps best known for being stingy, the <small>NCMS</small> saved millions of lives, according to a new working paper by Jonathan Gruber of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Junjian Yi of Peking University and Mengyun Lin of Xiamen University.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> At the time the <small>NCMS</small> was introduced, China&#39;s health-care system was ailing. The government had long neglected it. Many families had to pay for treatment out of their own pocket, even as the cost of care spiked. Under pressure to come up with a fix, the state introduced the <small>NCMS</small> . </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230902_CNC330.png"></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Within five years the scheme had enrolled over 800m people in the countryside. But it wasn&#39;t very generous. People had to pay large deductibles before the insurance kicked in. Once it did, the plan still only covered a portion of the cost of treatment (sometimes as little as 50%). And total compensation was capped. Because of all this, and the voluntary nature of the scheme, previous studies concluded that it wasn&#39;t all that effective.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But Mr Gruber and his team argue that the old research was flawed because it failed to account for different characteristics of counties, such as <small>GDP</small> , that may have influenced health outcomes. The new study used a complicated process to try and isolate the effects of the <small>NCMS</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The team&#39;s findings show that the scheme led to a 20% decline in mortality and a 4% increase in life expectancy in the counties where it was implemented. Between 2003 and 2010, the average life expectancy across China increased by 2.5 years. The <small>NCMS</small> may have been responsible for 78% of that, say the researchers. At its height, the scheme saved more than 1m lives per year. Participants were 13% less likely to be seriously ill than those not enrolled in the plan. They also spent considerably less on health care.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Millions of lives saved is a lot. But the <small>NCMS</small> ’s size, rather than the ingenuity of its design or the generosity of its benefits, may be the biggest reason for its success. On a per person basis, the researchers found that the programme saved one life per 900 people enrolled, making it much less effective than Medicaid, an insurance scheme for poor Americans which is thought to save over one in 600 enrolled.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The <small>NCMS</small> was merged with another scheme to become a programme called Urban and Rural Residents Basic Medical Insurance. Meanwhile, the Employee Basic Medical Insurance scheme provides insurance to people with formal job contracts. Together they cover 95% of the population.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Time for a follow-up</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Reimbursement rates are now higher, but people still complain that the plans are too parsimonious. The cost of treatment keeps growing. Drugs imported from the West, which are often more effective than those produced locally, are not covered. Graft is also a problem. In July the authorities launched a sweeping anti-corruption campaign in the health sector.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Big reforms are still needed. But even imperfect ones can save many lives, as the <small>NCMS</small> seems to show. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:03:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/llh08u7q2klrb0ji9v5ad1tlg5qvcs9v</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/an-old-health-insurance-scheme-in-china-may-have-saved-millions </item><item><title><![CDATA[When China thought America might invade]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20Chaguan-e94c2b8c52580a8833dd02f9fa34ddf3.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>hen foreign</small> foes threaten, an impregnable fortress is worth more than a comfortable home. Time and again, that doctrine guided China&#39;s Communist Party in its first decades of rule. Under Chairman Mao Zedong, talk of invasion was a constant. In those dark times, the usual priorities of peacetime government—feeding and clothing the masses, striving to raise living standards—were all too often neglected. In their stead came campaigns to ready China for war.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One such campaign built a complete military-industrial complex in China&#39;s inland mountains, known as the “Third Front”. Begun in 1964, it was a state secret for more than a decade, though it involved at least 15m workers and consumed resources at a fearsome rate. Chinese elsewhere paid an unwitting price in austerity and consumer shortages. Labourers were often recruited from coastal or border regions deemed at risk of attack by America, India, the Soviet Union and other hostile powers. Grouped into militarised brigades, they laid railways far into China&#39;s rugged western and south-western interior. They built steelworks and mines, armaments factories and nuclear sites in remote valleys and deserts, some of them underground. Though rail lines and other infrastructure helped to open up inland China, the costs, both human and financial, were staggering. When the campaign wound down in the late 1970s, most Third Front projects were deemed unviable and were scrapped, merged or moved.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Some tough but rational party bosses—among them Deng Xiaoping, the flinty survivor of several Maoist purges, and Mao&#39;s eventual successor—tried to slow or shrink the Third Front when it was first mooted. Their resistance is ably described by Covell Meyskens, a historian at the Naval Postgraduate School in California, in his book “Mao&#39;s Third Front: The Militarisation of Cold War China”. These relative pragmatists drafted a five-year plan that sought to restore orderly food production in rural areas and to develop modern factories, especially on the coast, to provide clothes and other necessities. Their plan was, in effect, a rebuke of Mao&#39;s Great Leap Forward, an earlier exercise in grassroots radicalism that killed 30m people in a man-made famine.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mao sensed opposition and counter-attacked. Party doctrine already described coastal development as a legacy of colonialism. Mao called coastal cities easy targets for foreign attack, too. He ordered key industries to move to remote mountain ranges, aping tactical retreats staged by early communist guerrillas. The country must build a rear base before war broke out, Mao insisted. Still, central planners and allies in the leadership played for time and called for more studies—right up to the moment in August 1964 that America accused North Vietnam of attacking one of its warships, bringing conflict and a superpower&#39;s armed forces to China&#39;s southern border. Mao used this security crisis to outflank other leaders, argues Mr Meyskens. Bowing to Mao as their supreme military strategist, top officials approved his most urgent priorities within days, including the building from scratch of Panzhihua, a steelmaking city in the mountains of the south-west, and a ban on new industrial projects in 15 coastal cities.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> History does not have to repeat perfectly to offer lessons in the present. Mao was a revolutionary who saw terror and anarchy as useful tools. By contrast, Xi Jinping, China&#39;s supreme leader, is an austere nationalist obsessed with order and party control. For his part, Mao seems to have relished China&#39;s break with the Soviet Union in the early 1960s and the turn to autarky that followed. Mr Xi&#39;s calls for self-reliance in food and in core technologies are more complicated. Even as his regime abhors dependency on America, its envoys tirelessly lobby Western allies in Asia and Europe to provide know-how that China needs to grow strong. For all those differences, the Third Front should be studied by blithe sorts who insist that Mr Xi&#39;s party must deliver growth and material prosperity to maintain its legitimacy, and so will never break with the rich West. Economic self-interest is a powerful force. But a lesson from 1964 is that once America seemed truly to threaten China, economic planners fell silent and security fanatics took charge.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Once, Panzhihua was too secret to appear on maps. Today, it is a sleepy city of 1.2m people in southern Sichuan, anchored by its still-active, state-owned steelworks, and by mines for iron ore, titanium and vanadium. Chaguan reached the city by high-speed train from Kunming, two and a half hours to the south. The Kunming-Chengdu rail line was also a Third Front project, cut through barren mountains at a cost of two deaths per kilometre of track. In the city centre high-arched bridges cross the Jinsha river, whose fast brown waters drowned pioneering workers crossing by boat. In the air, a faint oily tang is the only trace of the steelmaking that once poisoned local skies and water sources.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> In a dangerous age, old instincts stir</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The city&#39;s harsh beginnings are hard to imagine now: the lack of fresh food, the wolves that terrorised the first arrivals, the tents and huts of earth and straw that housed workers sent to terrace steep mountainsides. But several middle-aged residents are proud to recall fathers sent to the Third Front six decades ago, toiling alone for years before sending for wives and children to join them.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A phrase of Mao&#39;s, “Until Panzhihua is built, I won&#39;t sleep”, is carved on a boulder outside the city&#39;s Museum of the Third Front, near another old slogan: “Good People and Good Horses Go to the Third Front”. Inside, a father and his 12-year-old son from Guangxi, in China&#39;s far south, examine a life-size diorama of a mine entrance. Grumbling that today&#39;s young take comfort for granted, the man brought his son to discover how earlier generations endured hardship. He praises Mr Xi for updating Mao&#39;s calls for self-reliance, predicting that a global contest for resources is “definitely going to cause a war”. Not all Chinese feel such danger. For those that do, Panzhihua awaits their visit. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read more from Chaguan, our columnist on China:<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/the-world-should-study-chinas-crushing-of-hong-kongs-freedoms">The world should study China&#39;s crushing of Hong Kong&#39;s freedoms</a> (Aug 24th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article66978-prod.ece">China&#39;s slowing economy, seen from ground level</a> (Aug 17th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/10/why-chinese-women-are-denied-legal-land-rights">Why Chinese women are denied legal land rights</a> (Aug 10th)</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Also: How the Chaguan column <a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">got its name</a></i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:03:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/0qnvubgej06dfn81qo05o7g0kjuvhrat</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/31/when-china-thought-america-might-invade</item><item><title><![CDATA[China is stoking anger over Japan’s release of nuclear wastewater]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/030%20China%20-%20China%20and%20Japan-0ada91a0c4be8f49f75ced4febe881c8.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>O</span> <small>n August</small> 24th the government of Japan began releasing water into the ocean. This is not just any water, mind you, but treated wastewater from the Fukushima nuclear plant, which was destroyed 12 years ago by a tsunami. Japan has dealt with the situation carefully, putting the liquid through an advanced filtration and dilution process. It still contains a potentially harmful radionuclide called tritium. But experts say the levels are so low that this is not a concern. Japan wants to release more than a million tonnes of the water over the next 30 years. Many scientists back the plan, as does the <small>UN</small> ’s International Atomic Energy Agency.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China, though, has blasted Japan&#39;s actions, calling them reckless. The government has banned imports of Japanese seafood. State media has endlessly covered the story, with little mention of the scientists who support the plan. Nationalist netizens have taken it from there, promoting unfounded claims about contaminated fish and poisoned humans, and calling for a boycott of Japanese goods. A few Chinese cities have experienced a salt-buying frenzy, with people queuing for hours to purchase a bag. Some seem to think that salt may become tainted or that it is useful in treating radiation sickness (it is not).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are, to be sure, scientists and environmental activists who also oppose Japan&#39;s plan. Some claim that more studies are needed to assess the potential impact. Others say that the authorities in Japan are not to be trusted. The disaster in Fukushima exposed alarming levels of official corruption, incompetence and deception.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But China&#39;s response may have more to do with politics than anything else. Anti-Japanese sentiment in the country runs deep. Chinese nationalists often invoke Japan&#39;s invasion and occupation of China during the 1930s and 1940s. A dispute over five islets in the East China Sea a decade ago led to talk of war. More recently, officials in Beijing have watched with frustration as Japan draws closer to America and shows increasing support for Taiwan, a self-governing island that China claims. On the wastewater issue, Japan says China has rebuffed its offers to hold meetings where it would address any worries.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A different type of meeting has also complicated the situation. On August 18th President Joe Biden hosted Japan&#39;s prime minister, Kishida Fumio, and South Korea&#39;s president, Yoon Suk-yeol, for an unprecedented summit. A rancorous history has often divided Japan and South Korea. China&#39;s assertiveness has brought them closer. Now, though, China may spy an opportunity to drive a wedge between them. South Korea&#39;s government has supported Japan&#39;s wastewater plan, but the Korean opposition and much of the public are against it. (The Japanese public is also divided on the issue.)</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For China, the wastewater release has come at a convenient time. The country&#39;s economy is struggling. Each week seems to bring a new batch of disappointing data. Japan&#39;s actions have provided a distraction from the bad news. But concerns about the economy may undermine China&#39;s response. No country buys more seafood from Japan. The ban on imports risks hurting Chinese businesses nearly as much as Japanese fishermen. It may not last long. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:40:36 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/8hgc9ab3v0unti4uphasjqlt7rt8gs3l</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/30/china-is-stoking-anger-over-japans-release-of-nuclear-wastewater </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why fewer university students are studying Mandarin]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/029%20China%20-%20Learning%20Mandarin-c6eb910fcbf649edf834c921ed0a589c.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>T</span> <small>en years</small> ago Mandarin, the mother tongue of most Chinese, was being hyped as the language of the future. In 2015 the administration of Barack Obama called for 1m primary- and secondary-school students in America to learn it by 2020. In 2016 Britain followed suit, encouraging kids to study “one of the most important languages for the <small>UK</small> ’s future prosperity”. Elsewhere, too, there seemed to be a growing interest in Mandarin, as China&#39;s influence and economic heft increased. So why, a decade later, does Mandarin-learning appear to have declined in many places?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Good numbers are tough to come by in some countries, but the trend is clear among university students in the English-speaking world. In America, for example, the number taking Mandarin courses peaked around 2013. From 2016 to 2020 enrolment in such courses fell by 21%, according to the Modern Language Association, which promotes language study. In Britain the number of students admitted to Chinese-studies programmes dropped by 31% between 2012 and 2021, according to the Higher Education Statistics Association, which counts such things (though it does not count those who take Mandarin as part of other degrees).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China may be the top trade partner of Australia and New Zealand, but in those countries, too, local enthusiasm for learning Mandarin is flagging. Enrolment in university courses fell by a whopping 48% in New Zealand between 2013 and 2022. The dynamic looks similar in Germany, where the data show a decreasing appetite for Chinese studies among first-year university students. Scholars in Nordic countries report similar trends. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20230826_CNC252.png"></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To be sure, the study of modern languages is falling across the board in many rich countries. In general, students are drifting away from the humanities. Mandarin seemed like it would buck this trend. However, the study of it in American universities has fallen faster than enrolments in all foreign languages combined.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> According to an international survey taken in 2016 of education agents—consultants who help students to choose institutions—the most common reason people studied Mandarin back then was to improve their employment prospects. At the time, even a little Mandarin went a long way. From 2010 to 2015 the number of job postings in America that required skills in the language increased by 230%, according to the Language Connects Foundation, a lobby group. It reckons that American firms continue to desire Mandarin over any other foreign language, save Spanish. But that no longer seems to motivate students. Jennifer Liu, who runs Harvard University&#39;s Mandarin programme, says engagement by business students has fallen over the past decade, compared with those studying international affairs and security.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It could be that the market has changed. Tools like Google Translate and Chat <small>GPT</small> work so well that low-level Mandarin skills aren&#39;t really needed any more. The market may have also got more competitive. Bilingual Chinese graduates now fill many of the jobs that require Mandarin. In terms of language skills, they are often more qualified than their Western counterparts. All Chinese children start learning English by age eight, some even earlier. University-entrance exams in China require a high level of proficiency.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Students in the West may have also soured on the idea of doing business with China. Mandarin teachers point to the Beijing Olympics in 2008 as a seminal moment, when excitement for learning the language took off. Since then, though, China has grown more oppressive under Xi Jinping. Its human-rights abuses in Xinjiang and Hong Kong have been widely reported. In most rich countries negative views of China are at or near all-time highs.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> At the same time, tensions between China and the West have risen. American and European leaders now talk of “de-risking” their economic ties with China. Analysts fear that a broader decoupling is taking place. The shift in narratives about China, from a place to make money to America&#39;s main rival, has affected student choices, reckons James Gethyn Evans of Harvard. Many now see no point in studying Mandarin, says Chen Dongdong of Seton Hall University (in New Jersey), where the number of students taking Mandarin classes has nearly halved in ten years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are also fewer American university students studying in China. The number peaked in 2011, even as the total studying abroad continued to grow. One reason may be pollution. Around that time, Western media regularly reported on Beijing&#39;s “airpocalypse”. The capital&#39;s heavy smog made it difficult for foreign firms and embassies in China to recruit people, with or without Mandarin skills.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> In need of a BTS</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In many ways, the linguistic reach of a country is an expression of its soft power. Take South Korea, which can point to such cultural exports as <small>BTS</small> , a wildly popular boy band, “Parasite”, an Oscar-winning film, and “Squid Game”, a hit television show. Enrolment in Korean courses at American universities rose by 25% between 2016 and 2020. On Duolingo, a language-learning app, Korean is more popular than Mandarin.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China&#39;s soft power is weak by comparison, in part because its <a href="https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/08/18/the-monkey-king-is-one-of-chinas-most-successful-cultural-exports">entertainment industry</a> must please the Communist Party. Few of its cultural offerings have caught on in the West. China has more influence in poor countries, where its Belt and Road Initiative, a spree of global infrastructure building, is most active. In these places, Mandarin-learning appears to be ticking up. More than 81,000 students from Africa were studying in China in 2018, the last year for which data are available. (Many were on Chinese-government scholarships.) China&#39;s deployment of Confucius Institutes has also helped. These offer instruction in Mandarin, as well as other Chinese cultural pursuits.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Confucius Institutes were once prevalent on Western university campuses, too, providing them with cheap Mandarin teachers. But the outposts were accused of pushing a political agenda. Since 2017 more than 100 American universities have closed them. Universities elsewhere in the West have taken similar steps.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Western governments, though, say they need more people with advanced Mandarin skills. The <small>CIA</small> , for example, is looking to double the number of Mandarin-speakers that it employs. America&#39;s State Department deems it a “critical language”. Britain is underpowered when it comes to expertise on China and the ability to speak its main language, according to a recent official report. The German government has said much the same thing.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> As China and the West, especially America, struggle to get along, those who learn Mandarin seem more likely to be future spies and diplomats than businesspeople. Whether that will help ease a sense of mutual mistrust is an open question. For now, China and its rivals are doing a good job of misunderstanding each other. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:47:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ic87bon6l7e01so2mil1dnhvdbvbkvai</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/why-fewer-university-students-are-studying-mandarin </item><item><title><![CDATA[The clock is ticking on an old deal between America and China]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/030%20China%20-%20China%20and%20America-c3077527eb75dcc0801e86c188f2cf97.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>merica and</small> China established full diplomatic relations on January 1st 1979. By the end of that month they had also signed the Science and Technology Co-operation Agreement ( <small>STA</small> ). The deal didn&#39;t commit either side to much, but it laid out a shared desire for collaboration in these areas. Its terms call for renewal “by mutual agreement” every five years. For decades that happened with little fuss. Now, though, things are looking shaky. The deadline is August 27th.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China wants to stay in the deal. America is seeking a sixth-month extension so that it can negotiate changes to the pact. President Joe Biden is under pressure from Republicans to ditch the agreement. Some have written letters to Antony Blinken, the secretary of state. In one, ten congressmen claimed that China “has previously leveraged the <small>STA</small> to advance its military objectives and will continue to do so.” America, they added, must “stop fuelling its own destruction”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Backers of the <small>STA</small> say it has symbolic value, being among the first bilateral agreements signed by the countries after ties were established. And it has produced tangible benefits, too. They say that joint research enabled by the <small>STA</small> has helped prevent spinal birth defects and led to the regular monitoring of influenza strains, which is needed to formulate vaccines each year. They also cite achievements in seismology, agriculture, clean energy and other fields.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The <small>STA</small> does not fund or require any action. Rather, it is an umbrella agreement under which specific collaboration can be negotiated. Since it was signed, almost 100 protocols and annexes have brought American and Chinese scientists together. If any of those cause concern, they can be amended, abrogated or allowed to expire. In recent years, the level of activity occurring under the <small>STA</small> has decreased, partly because of the covid-19 pandemic and partly because of growing mistrust on both sides.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In 1979 America was already a scientific superpower, while China had relatively little expertise to offer. Now, though, China has caught up in many areas, so the potential benefits for America of staying in the <small>STA</small> are only increasing, say its proponents. The Biden administration says it wants to “strengthen” the deal. But it has already placed restrictions on the sale of certain technologies to China, such as advanced semiconductors, and prohibited American investment in some of the country&#39;s high-tech sectors. With elections coming next year, no one in Washington wants to appear soft on China. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:47:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/271nueonrha0qotdj23qbpqdk4449dke</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/the-clock-is-ticking-on-an-old-deal-between-america-and-china </item><item><title><![CDATA[How an amateur football league in China took off]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/031%20China%20-%20Village%20sports-23619650ecb918459abb54b0d886f8d8.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>R</span> <small>ongjiang County</small> , tucked away in the rainy hills of south-west China, has little going for it at first glance. The grey tiles covering houses in the county seat give it a rather drab feel. The area was one of the last in China to be declared free of extreme poverty. Locals often have to find work elsewhere, travelling to distant factories and construction sites. In 2019 a video went viral of three young children in Rongjiang begging their migrant-worker parents to stay with them.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet this summer it was Chinese from far-off cities who flocked to Rongjiang. They came to watch an amateur football league involving 20 of the county&#39;s villages. It started in May and quickly became a phenomenon. Weekend matches between teams made up of butchers and farmers drew crowds of nearly 50,000, straining the local stadium. Millions more watched on Weibo, a Twitter-like platform, and Douyin, the Chinese version of TikTok.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The league&#39;s group stage finished in mid-July. When your correspondent visited to watch the semi-finals of the knockout stage on July 28th, every hotel in town was fully booked. Some fans camped out by a river, their tents and rice-cookers sheltered by a rough concrete bridge.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There are many reasons behind the popularity of the Rongjiang league, which is men only. Start with the state of professional football. Despite decades of investment by China&#39;s leader and chief fan, Xi Jinping, the country&#39;s players are not very good. The men&#39;s national team, made up of players from China&#39;s top league, ranks 78th in the world (the women rank 14th). It has only qualified for the World Cup once, in 2002, when it failed to score a single goal. Lately China&#39;s football association, which oversees the sport, has been dogged by allegations of corruption.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The Rongjiang league, by contrast, has an authentic, even wholesome feel. Football in the county dates back to the 1940s, when it was introduced by university students who were fleeing China&#39;s cities during the invasion by Japan. Today the games are free to watch and feel enjoyably low pressure. Players brush off their missed shots with grins. After a penalty shoot-out in the semi-finals, fans swarmed the pitch waving China&#39;s national flag. The winners of this year&#39;s tournament, from a village in Chejiang township, walked away with a cow. The two runners-up won three pigs and three goats, respectively.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The league&#39;s cultural diversity is another draw. The players come from several minority ethnic groups, of which the biggest are the Dong and the Miao. During breaks in the matches, villagers in traditional silver headdresses often dance for the crowd. Others play <i>lusheng</i> , a musical instrument with multiple bamboo pipes. The performances are well received by locals and visiting Han Chinese, who make up more than 90% of China&#39;s population. Some of the latter are patronising, though. “The more backward people are, the more enthusiastic they are too,” says one. China&#39;s minorities are often presented by official media as fun-loving curiosities.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> A kick for business</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To the delight of officials at all levels, the league appears to have stimulated the local economy. During the Dragon Boat festival in June tourism spending shot up, much of it coming from football fans. Restaurants selling <i>niubie</i> , a kind of soup made from partially digested grass found in a cow&#39;s stomach, have been packed of late. (The grass is extracted early in the digestive process, says a local rather defensively.) Vendors at the hundreds of stalls set up by the local government outside the stadium report a brisk trade. Most sell food or traditional crafts. A man hawking barbecue skewers says he has doubled his income.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Officials are calling Rongjiang a successful case of “rural revitalisation”, which is a pet project of Mr Xi. He wants to boost development in the countryside. Following his lead, state media have raved about Rongjiang. Even China&#39;s foreign embassies boasted about the football matches. In June the central government called for over 100 new sporting events to be set up in rural areas by 2035.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But there are concerns that the success of Rongjiang may be fleeting. Attracting crowds to this part of China is not easy. Before the football league, officials tried to draw tourists by touting sports such as bullfighting and basketball. An effort was made to promote local customs, too. None of these really caught on.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The city of Zibo, in the northern province of Shandong, provides a cautionary tale. It became a social-media phenomenon when word of its delicious kebabs began making the rounds earlier this year. Tourists flocked to the city, where officials turned arenas into makeshift dining halls. But after a few months of this barbecue craze, interest in Zibo slumped.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Still, officials think they have found a winning strategy for the countryside. A new football league began this month and will run until October. This one is a little more contrived. It involves nearly 300 amateur teams from all around China. Each is named after a food. On August 13th a team called the Sour Soups from the nearby city of Kaili beat the Bamboo Shoots from the southern province of Guangdong. The stadium in Rongjiang was still packed. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Subscribers can sign up to <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/drum-tower">Drum Tower</a> , our new weekly newsletter, to understand what the world makes of China—and what China makes of the world.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:47:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/ktfo03edciurrgi1ngpm6ssdti700tqt</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/how-an-amateur-football-league-in-china-took-off</item><item><title><![CDATA[The world should study China’s crushing of Hong Kong’s freedoms]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-er00if e1whazj12"><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><div><figcaption>听听这个故事。</figcaption><span class="css-1fs0t47 ed4dtdz0">在<a id="audio-ios-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/bed1b25">iOS</a>或<a id="audio-android-cta" href="https://economist-app.onelink.me/d2eC/7f3c199">Android</a>上享受更多音频和播客。</span> </div><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://www.economist.com/media-assets/audio/032%20China%20-%20Chaguan-18d1834878f5db5d6491c17475649190.mp3"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>“H</span> <small>ONG KONG</small> is becoming less and less relevant,” says a Western diplomat in the city. On the face of it, that is an odd claim. Lots of foreign governments take Hong Kong seriously, noting each step of the financial centre&#39;s journey towards autocracy.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Only last month the governments of America, Australia and Britain formally protested when the authorities in Hong Kong announced bounties of HK$1m ($128,000) on eight democracy activists living as exiles in their respective countries. The territory&#39;s chief executive, John Lee, a former police officer, pledged that the eight will be “pursued for life” and “spend their days in fear”. This was not mere bluster. In recent times police have swooped on Hong Kong-based family members of those exiles, questioning them for hours about contacts with their relatives.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The European Union&#39;s latest annual report on Hong Kong, published on August 18th, is both grim and thorough. It describes the arrests of hundreds of opposition politicians, journalists and democracy activists, among them a retired Roman Catholic cardinal in his 90s, under a national-security law imposed on the city by the central government in Beijing. The report catalogues new pressures and controls on schools and universities, environmental groups, trade unions and professional associations. More broadly, diplomats posted to Hong Kong by dozens of countries have spent long hours observing national-security trials, held without juries before panels of hand-picked judges. Dutifully, foreign envoys write reports on stage-managed “elections”. Some of those contests involve a single, pre-screened candidate—the only one to meet the requirement, imposed from Beijing after anti-government protests in 2019, that “patriots administer Hong Kong”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For all those signs of external scrutiny, there are signs of policymakers in foreign capitals losing interest, or at least hope. The Western diplomat laments that, back home, the city&#39;s smothering is considered a done deal. “When I talk to colleagues at headquarters, they already consider Hong Kong to be part of China.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Actually, such fatalism is a mistake, for both principled and practical reasons. Start with the former. Democratic governments cannot change the Communist Party. But they can make China&#39;s rulers pay a price when they break their word. To shrug and turn away from China&#39;s actions in Hong Kong would break faith with the territory&#39;s 7.5m people, who were promised a high degree of autonomy and the preservation of many fundamental freedoms for 50 years after British colonial rule ended in 1997, under China&#39;s formulation of “one country, two systems”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Then there is the impact on the stand-off over Taiwan, the democratic, self-ruled island that China calls its own. China&#39;s preferred Taiwan scenario involves the island&#39;s peaceful submission, in return for limited autonomy under a version of “one country, two systems”. If foreign governments allow China to trample commitments to Hong Kong with impunity, they risk encouraging rulers in Beijing to imagine they can do the same to Taiwan. It is hard to see how that could be a consensual, bloodless process. Understandably, China&#39;s crushing of freedoms in Hong Kong has left the people of Taiwan warier than ever of a mainland takeover.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is a practical reason to keep tracking repression in Hong Kong, too. A good way to understand any edifice is to watch it being built. In the same way, the stifling of Hong Kong&#39;s pluralism is a work in progress, and as such is unusually revealing about the ambitions and terrors that drive China&#39;s secretive rulers, and about the controls they think are needed in an orderly society.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For now, the territory enjoys freedoms unknown in mainland China. The internet is not sealed behind China&#39;s “great firewall”. One of the biggest threats to debate is arguably self-censorship, induced by fear and by deliberately vague calls by Hong Kong&#39;s officials to eradicate “soft resistance”—their sinister description of dissent that does not explicitly challenge the law.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The trends are ominous, though. When Xi Jinping, China&#39;s supreme leader, visited Hong Kong last year he called on officials to heed central authorities in Beijing, to guard against foreign interference and to tackle what he called locals&#39; primary concerns, namely larger homes, more economic opportunities, better schools and quality care for the elderly. Hong Kong&#39;s leaders have made progress on Mr Xi&#39;s first two priorities, at least.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Their new political model has no time for the notion of loyal opposition. Officials praise the “efficiency” of the territory&#39;s Legislative Council since dissenting politicians were thrown out. School curriculums have shed classes that encourage critical thinking and added lessons about national security. The new model questions the legitimacy of even constructive criticism. When campaigners raise doubts about planned transport or housing schemes, state-backed news outlets denounce them for inciting “citizens&#39; negative emotions against the government”.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> A world city no more</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Hong Kong is being domesticated, in every sense of the word. To bring the city to heel, its leaders want to weaken the West&#39;s perceived influence. One of the exiles with a bounty on his head calls extraterritorial harassment a warning to Hong Kongers. “It is not as if they are going to extradite us,” he says. “The audience is domestic.” China is working to bind Hong Kong economically to nearby mainland cities. Reportedly, lucrative opportunities are increasingly steered to mainland firms in Hong Kong, or to “patriotic” locals. There is talk of admitting more mainland immigrants. Diplomats draw parallels with settler-colonialism practised elsewhere in China&#39;s restive periphery, from Tibet to Xinjiang.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Once, foreign governments and businesses predicted that Hong Kong&#39;s value as a global city would protect it from heavy-handed Chinese rule. Instead, party bosses prize control over openness: that is the ongoing lesson of Hong Kong. As a window on the party&#39;s bleak worldview, the city&#39;s fate is all too relevant. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <b>Read more from Chaguan, our columnist on China:<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article66978-prod.ece">China&#39;s slowing economy, seen from ground level</a> (Aug 17th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/10/why-chinese-women-are-denied-legal-land-rights">Why Chinese women are denied legal land rights</a> (Aug 10th)<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/china/article65928-prod.ece">Xi Jinping&#39;s revealing response to floods and heatwaves</a> (Aug 4th)</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Also: How the Chaguan column <a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">got its name</a></i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:47:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/rgt9hsmi12ctd7qmi444hnccbaovjfh6</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/china/2023/08/24/the-world-should-study-chinas-crushing-of-hong-kongs-freedoms</item></channel></rss>