<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 8 日星期三 19:30:04 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Are politicians brave enough for daredevil economics?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>乍一看</span>，阿根廷在11月19日的第二轮<small>总统</small>选举中面临着<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/23/argentinas-election-result-is-the-worst-of-all-possible-outcomes">严峻的选择</a>。现任财政部长塞尔吉奥·马萨 (Sergio Massa) 领导的政府正面临着 138% 的通货膨胀率和各种奇怪的官方汇率制度，他面临着<a href="https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2023/09/07/meet-javier-milei-the-frontrunner-to-be-argentinas-next-president">哈维尔·米雷 (Javier Milei)</a> 。米雷先生是一位自由主义者，他说他想借用弗里德里希·哈耶克、米尔顿·弗里德曼和其他自由市场经济学家的想法来摧毁这个体系。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，无论谁获胜，改革派阿根廷人都怀疑这个国家是否会真正改变。马萨很可能会加倍印钞。他对废除阻碍持续增长的赞助制度兴趣不大。相比之下，米莱先生在国会几乎没有支持。他没有执行政策的经验。许多同情米莱先生的市场导向经济学家，甚至那些为他提供建议的经济学家，对于阿根廷需要采取哪些措施来改善经济，都抱有令人惊讶的模糊想法。这个国家感觉陷入了困境。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231111_EPC351.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">阿根廷是更广泛趋势的一个极端例子。世界已经忘记了如何改革。我们分析了自由市场智库弗雷泽研究所的数据，该研究所以十个等级来衡量“经济自由”。我们将“大胆经济”定义为当一个国家在十年内进步 1.5 个百分点或以上（相当于瑞士和委内瑞拉之间的差距的四分之一），因此表明已经进行了自由化改革。在 20 世纪 80 年代和 90 年代，这种情况很常见，因为前苏联国家开始开放，加纳和秘鲁等许多被认为不可改革的国家证明它们实际上是可以改革的（见图 1）。政客们改变了对外贸易规则，加强了央行的实力，削减了预算赤字，并出售了国有企业。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">近年来，只有希腊和乌克兰等少数国家实施了改革。在截至 2020 年的十年里，只有缅甸和伊拉克两个国家的进步超过 1.5 个百分点。同年，乔治城大学、哈佛大学以及国际货币基金组织的经济学家发表了一篇论文<small>，</small>研究了结构改革，并发现了类似的结果。在 20 世纪 80 年代和 90 年代，世界各地的政治家都实施了抽签。到2010年代，改革已陷入停滞。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">夜魔经济学的受欢迎程度有所下降，部分原因是对其的需求减少了。尽管近年来经济自由度有所下降，但根据我们对弗雷泽研究所数据的分析，如今经济的自由度平均比 1980 年高出 30%。国有企业较少。关税较低。即使在阿根廷，电信和面向消费者的行业也比以前更好。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但大胆经济学的衰落也反映出人们普遍认为自由化失败了。在大众的想象中，“结构调整计划”或“休克疗法”等术语会让人想起非洲的贫困、俄罗斯和乌克兰黑手党国家的建立以及智利侵犯人权的景象。约瑟夫·斯蒂格利茨 (Joseph Stiglitz) 2002 年出版的《全球化及其不满》和娜奥米·克莱因 (Naomi Klein) 2007 年出版的《休克主义》等书籍煽动了对自由市场“华盛顿共识”的反对。在拉丁美洲，“新自由主义”现在是一个被滥用的术语。在其他地方，它很少被用作认可。许多阿根廷人认为，该国 20 世纪 90 年代经济自由化的尝试引发了 2001 年的巨大金融危机。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如今，<small>国际货币基金组织</small>和世界银行等国际组织对冒险经济学的兴趣已不如以前了。国际货币基金组织在1993年10月出版的《世界经济展望》中，139次提到“改革”<small>一词</small>。在 30 年后出版的最新版本中，这个词只出现了 35 次。如今，美国有了新的共识，即对全球化的好处持怀疑态度，将国内利益置于国际利益之上，并支持大规模补贴，以加快绿色转型，将制造业回流。由于西方国家的支持减少，其他国家的政府改革本国经济的压力也随之减小。 20 世纪 90 年代阿根廷的自由市场主义者利用了与美国的深厚联系。如今，这样的联系已经越来越少了。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">震惊</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，大胆经济学失败的观点经不起推敲，即使项目常常会带来短期痛苦。 20 世纪 90 年代，三个波罗的海国家开放了价格和劳动力市场。这使得它们能够在 25 年内从苏联成员国转变为欧元成员国（见图 2）。 2010年代，希腊实施了<small>国际货币基金组织</small>和欧洲当局要求的多项改革。目前，流入的外国直接投资正在飙升，今年希腊的<small>GDP</small>预计将增长 2.5% 左右——是欧洲增速最快的国家之一。不久前，许多人认为中国已经拒绝了冒险经济并取得了成功。最近的经济疲软，包括习近平主席领导下房地产市场的动荡，让人们对这一观点产生了怀疑。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事实上，越来越多的研究表明，大胆经济学已基本实现了其目标。乔治城美洲研究所的安东尼·埃斯特瓦德奥达尔 (Antoni Estevadeordal) 和加州大学戴维斯分校的艾伦·泰勒 (Alan Taylor) 发表的一篇论文研究了 20 世纪 70 年代至 2000 年代进口资本和中间产品关税自由化的影响，发现该政策使<small>GDP</small>增长率提高了约一个百分点观点。欧洲央行经济学家 2017 年发表的一篇论文分析了 22 个不同国家和地区，结果显示，“改革浪潮”开始十年后，人均<small>GDP</small>比合理预期高出约 6 个百分点。 1961年至2000年的收入水平</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与此同时，北卡罗来纳大学教堂山分校的 Anusha Chari 以及斯坦福大学的 Peter Blair Henry 和 Hector Reyes 在 2021 年发表的一篇论文发现，新兴市场的各种改革（从稳定高通胀到开放资本市场）产生了积极影响。例如，贸易自由化往往会使十年间<small>国内生产总值</small>的平均增长率每年提高2.5个百分点以上。在另一篇聚焦于拉丁美洲的论文中，美洲开发银行行长伊兰·戈德法恩 (Ilan Goldfajn) 及其同事承认，经济增长令人失望，但他们认为，“如果没有华盛顿共识政策的某些子集，如果在 20 世纪 80 年代末和 90 年代初实现宏观经济稳定并恢复获得外国融资的机会并非不可能。”其他研究发现，自 2000 年以来，非洲改革国家的增长速度更快。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在大多数改革似乎失败的地方，问题在于缺乏承诺。以乌克兰为例，在covid-19和俄罗斯入侵之前，乌克兰的人均国内<small>生产总值</small>就低于苏联解体时的水平。到了 20 世纪 90 年代初，很明显政府并没有认真对待冒险经济学。 1993 年，两位经济学家西蒙·约翰逊 (Simon Johnson) 和奥列格·乌斯坚科 (Oleg Ustenko) 为世界银行撰写的一份备忘录指出，“只有采取更严厉、更激进的政策才能避免恶性通货膨胀，但似乎没有政治领导人愿意采取这些措施。” 2001年阿根廷垮台的原因并不是人们普遍认为的大胆的经济政策。这是持续巨额的预算赤字。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">也许米雷先生会证明他的怀疑者是错误的。也许他会赢得选举，然后实施明智的经济改革。这将包括贸易自由化以及让阿根廷老板更容易雇用和解雇。这样做会对国家有很大帮助。它还将向世界其他地区展示前进的道路。大胆的经济学可能具有破坏性，但它会带来回报。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:52:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/tme50pge0ggmshdurtvqkoibbcces7md</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/11/08/are-politicians-brave-enough-for-daredevil-economics </item><item><title><![CDATA[Europe’s space ambitions might at last take it out of NASA’s shadow]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap">本周在西班牙举行的<span>塔</span><small>峰会上</small>，欧洲航天局（ <small>ESA</small> ）的官员提出了大胆的雄心：在新兴的太空竞赛中成为更加自主的参与者，并发展美国式的私人太空产业。但下一个 SpaceX 真的会是一家欧洲公司吗？显然，还有很多工作要做。</p><p class="article__body-text"> <i>《经济学人</i>》科技编辑阿洛克·贾 (Alok Jha) 前往<small>欧</small>空局巴黎总部会见其总干事约瑟夫·阿施巴赫 (Josef Aschbacher)。片长：39分钟</p><p class="article__body-text">基本聆听，来自我们的档案：</p><p class="article__body-text"> “ <a href="/podcasts/2023/08/16/why-the-lunar-south-pole-is-the-latest-focus-in-the-new-space-race">月球南极</a>竞赛”，2023 年 8 月 16 日</p><p class="article__body-text">“在别处寻找生命——第二部分， <a href="/juice-pod">JUICE</a> ”，2023 年 4 月 12 日</p><p class="article__body-text">“<a href="/privatemoon-pod">私人月球竞赛</a>”，2023 年 1 月 25 日</p><p class="article__body-text">“NASA 的新型<a href="/sls-pod">火箭</a>”，2022 年 8 月 23 日</p><p class="article__body-text">“一艘<a href="/starship-pod">星舰</a>诞生”，2022 年 2 月 15 日</p><p class="article__body-text"><i>这是仅限订阅者观看的一集。要收听，请注册<a href="https://subscribenow.economist.com/podcasts-plus?purchaseRedirect=economist.com%2Faudio%2Fpodcasts%2Fonboarding%3Fpodcast%3Dbabbage">免费试用</a>《经济学人播客+》</i></p><p class="article__body-text"><i>如果您已经是《经济学人》的订阅者，作为订阅的一部分，您可以完全访问我们所有的节目。有关如何访问《经济学人播客+》的更多信息，请访问我们的<a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">常见问题解答页面</a>或观看我们解释如何链接您的帐户的<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=48TlDbL-4vU">视频</a>。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:52:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/g59p6k7v1ben96g59ise2hh1pg4sipdg</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/11/08/europes-space-ambitions-might-at-last-take-it-out-of-nasas-shadow</item><item><title><![CDATA[How two teams plan to smash the world sailing-speed record]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>卡蒂萨克</i><span>号</span><small>于 1869 年下水</small>，是当时速度最快的帆船。如今，快艇已成为伦敦的旅游景点。在其全盛时期，当它载着来自中国的茶叶和来自澳大利亚的羊毛穿越世界时，它的时速可达令人兴奋的 17 节（31.5 公里/小时，或 19.6 英里/小时）。现代赛艇采用基于 150 年空气动力学和流体力学进步的激进设计，速度更快。甚至还有一些奇怪的船只也出现在人们的视野中，它们试图打破风帆驱动船只的速度记录，该记录于 2012 年创下了 65 节的纪录。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">多年来，速度一直在提高。 20 世纪 70 年代，随着船体变得更窄、更滑，赛艇开始以超过 30 节的速度在水中行驶。在 20 世纪 80 年代，勇敢的风帆冲浪者的速度达到了 40 节以上。 2000 年代，他们被风筝冲浪者以超过 55 节的速度超越。然而，以如此快的速度在小板上保持平衡所带来的体力要求和受伤风险，意味着帆船——某种意义上——又回到了比赛中。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">目前的纪录是由澳大利亚人保罗·拉森（Paul Larsen）创造的。他使用了一艘名为<i>Vestas Sailrocket 2</i>的看起来很奇怪的双体船<i> </i>依靠水翼升出水面并由翼帆推动。这些刚性结构类似于垂直安装的飞机机翼，比布帆更有效地利用风。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这一纪录是在 500 米单程赛跑中创下的。为了获得资格，一艘船必须能够漂浮，船上至少有一个人，仅由风推动并与水接触。新的竞争者遵守了这些规则，不过，就像拉森先生的船一样，它们看起来都不像普通的帆船。其中一种名为<i><small>SP</small> 80</i> ，起源于瑞士洛桑联邦理工学院。另一个来自 Syroco，这是一家位于法国马赛的海洋技术初创公司。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i><small>SP</small> 80</i> （如图）类似于未来派喷气式战斗机。该船不是由帆或翼帆驱动，而是由风筝推动。在高速行驶时，只有船的前部和两侧的两个吊舱与水接触，从而最大限度地减少阻力。飞行员坐在驾驶舱前部并驾驶。后座的副驾驶负责放风筝。 “在如此高的速度下，最好只专注于一项关键任务，”团队成员之一劳拉·曼农 (Laura Manon) 说。他们在法国南部海岸的勒卡特建立了一个基地，为明年的创纪录尝试做准备。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Syroco 还将推出一款两人座车型，尽管它的工艺更加不寻常。它也由风筝提供动力。船体是一个鱼雷形的舱室，船员们坐在里面。当风筝拉动舱室的速度更快时，它就会从海里升到空中，从而尽可能地减少阻力。水中只剩下一个小水翼，将飞船固定住，阻止它完全飞走。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Syroco 联合创始人之一（也是多项风筝冲浪记录的保持者）亚历山大·凯泽格斯 (Alexandre Caizergues) 将担任负责飞行员。 “我们有两只翅膀，一只在空中，一只在水中，”他说。在选择最终设计之前，仍在使用缩小的无线电控制原型来确定每个装置的具体控制方式。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">两个团队都面临的一个问题是一种被称为“空化”的现象。发生这种情况是因为快速移动的表面（例如水翼或螺旋桨叶片）在其后部产生低压区域。这使得气泡形成，引起湍流，使船减速，甚至损坏其结构。两家公司的秘密武器之一就是设计能够解决这一问题的水翼船。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果一切按计划进行，记录可能不仅会被打破，而且会被打破。两支队伍都将速度目标定为 80 节。这种速度更快的技术可能还有其他用途。一些实验性货船已经安装了翼帆以降低燃料成本，风筝拖曳也在尝试中。商业航运中风力发电的回归将标志着历史循环的一个令人愉快的结束。但翼帆和风筝不太可能像<i>卡蒂萨克号</i>曾经那样宏伟，因为所有 32 个帆都在翻滚。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:37:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/sk5ekqsjipftvrudbk4ob9pkjs690ije</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/08/how-two-teams-plan-to-smash-the-world-sailing-speed-record </item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel hopes technology will help it fight in Hamas’s tunnels]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <small>“加沙地铁”</small><span>即使</span>不强大，也算不上什么。哈马斯在飞地下方修建的隧道网络长达数百公里。它设有指挥中心、武器库以及食品和燃料仓库。它使哈马斯战士能够伏击以色列军队，并躲避炸弹和火炮。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列的既定目标是摧毁哈马斯。因此，10月27日进入加沙的以色列军队正试图攻击并摧毁这些隧道。 11 月 8 日，以色列表示已经摧毁了 130 座。但众所周知，地下战斗是<a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/17/hamas-tunnels-under-gaza-will-be-a-key-battlefield-for-israel">一项艰苦且致命的</a>工作。以色列国防军（ <small>IDF</small> ）将使用各种技术来帮助其士兵完成任务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第一项工作是寻找隧道。以色列<small>国防军</small>预备役上校迈克尔·米尔施泰因 (Michael Milshtein) 表示，自 2005 年撤军以来，以色列在加沙的间谍网络已经萎缩。监控无人机是一种替代方案。他们可以检测“生命模式”，从而提供入口在哪里的线索。美国国家地理空间情报局前局长罗伯特·卡迪罗 (Robert Cardillo) 表示，想象一下，如果 20 个人进入一个小建筑，24 小时内没有人出来。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">卫星也很有用。现代卫星雷达可以检测毫米级的表面高度变化。这足以发现隧道开挖造成的微妙地表扰动——尽管在<small>以色列国防军</small>期间分析过隧道网络的地貌学家乔尔·罗斯金指出，以色列轰炸加沙所产生的瓦砾将使这种分析变得更加困难。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">部队还可以使用探地雷达，在理想条件下可以探测地表以下 30 米的空隙。但加沙沿海的盐碱地远非理想。实际上，检测范围仅限于几米。罗斯金博士说，这项技术过去已被证明“不可靠”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">声学检测可以做得更好。<small>以色列国防军</small>加沙师前副指挥官阿米尔·阿维维表示，振动传感器可以检测新隧道的挖掘情况，尽管它们在寻找已经存在的隧道方面作用不大。这些可以通过地面声纳来发现。与海上对应物一样，这涉及发出声波（通常通过敲击金属板）并聆听回声。马萨诸塞州东北大学的计算机科学家凯里·拉帕波特 (Carey Rappaport) 表示，通过这种方式探测地下世界，可以揭示 100 米以下的隧道。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">甚至还有更高级的技术。埋地光纤网络可以通过穿过电缆的光子引起的“反向散射”来检测地下振动。此类技术的英国销售商 Sintela 对具体细节保持沉默，但其名为 Onyx 的系统已在美国南部边境使用。甚至可以通过检测隧道空隙引起的引力的微小减小来揭示隧道。英国初创公司 Silicon Microgravity 的目标是在明年年底之前开发出足够灵敏的重力计来完成这项任务。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一旦发现隧道，下一步就是禁用或摧毁它。隧道相对较浅，可以从空中进行，使用“地堡破坏”炸弹，在引爆前穿透地面。但哈马斯在民用基础设施下挖掘隧道的策略意味着此类袭击可能会杀死许多平民旁观者。例如，<small>以色列国防军</small>声称，哈马斯的一些领导人躲藏在加沙最大的希法医院下方的隧道网络中。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">控制加沙南部边境的埃及过去曾用污水淹没哈马斯使用的走私隧道。在早期的冲突中，以色列曾向隧道中浇筑混凝土。但一位美国军方官员认为，在当前的战争中，运送足够的物资可能是不切实际的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一名以色列安全官员表示，<small>以色列国防军</small>将使用“海绵炸弹”。这些化学物质混合后会膨胀成致密的硬质泡沫，堵塞隧道，为以后用炸药进行适当的拆除赢得时间。海绵炸弹也用于一种被称为“紫发”的战术。在海绵炸弹封锁入口之前，一枚烟雾弹被扔进隧道。如果被困的烟雾从附近的建筑物中飘出，则表明它隐藏了另一个入口。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但有时，士兵需要进入隧道。钻机可以开辟新的入口，以避免在现有入口处设置诱杀装置。以色列公司埃尔比特系统公司开发了一种武装四轴飞行器，利用计算机视觉在封闭空间内飞行。其他无人机可以穿过隧道和爬楼梯。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">双方正在进行一场残酷的战斗。哈马斯希望其隧道能够帮助其弥补<small>以色列国防军</small>在火力方面的压倒性优势。与此同时，以色列人希望他们的技术能够将这些隧道从避难所变成陷阱。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:36:14 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/apikfqpvirsmt1p0i2lfaj23bd0pt84h</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/08/israel-hopes-technology-will-help-it-fight-in-hamass-tunnels </item><item><title><![CDATA[Faecal transplants are just the start of a new sort of medicine]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">在伦敦盖伊圣托马斯医院的<small>一个小</small><span>实验室</span>里，德西雷·普罗索马里蒂正在处理捐款。每一种都经过称重、病原体测试、过滤、离心，然后冷冻干燥，然后制成粉末封装并给患者服用。这个过程需要强大的胃力，因为捐赠的是新鲜的粪便。 “我再也闻不到这种味道了，”普罗索马里蒂博士说。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">实验室工作人员对粪便本身并不感兴趣，而是对它们携带的微小生物体感兴趣。科学家们早就知道，包括人类在内的动物的肠道里充满了细菌、病毒和其他微生物。但直到最近，他们才开始了解它们的重要性。微生物群不仅仅是乘客的集合，它是健康身体的重要组成部分。它的成员帮助分解食物，产生调节它们所生活的身体的化学物质，并抑制其他有害细菌的生长。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Prossomariti 博士的药物旨在通过一种称为“粪便微生物群移植”（ <small>FMT</small> ）的过程来抑制有害细菌种类之一。五粒药丸（实验室工作人员喜欢称之为“crapsules”）可以克服<i>艰难梭菌</i>的反复感染，这种细菌已经对许多抗生素产生了耐药性。顾名思义，这个想法是复制健康人的肠道生态系统，并将其复制到微生物组失衡的人身上。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">它也有效。 <small>FMT</small>是英国治疗<i>艰难梭菌</i>感染的标准疗法，目前正在研究用于治疗从肠易激综合征到多发性硬化症等疾病。但<small>FMT</small>只是微生物医学革命的开始。研究人员认为，未来的方向不是采用相对生硬的复制微生物<i>组</i>的方法，而是调整微生物组以满足特定患者的需求。芝加哥大学微生物学家埃里克·帕默 (Eric Pamer) 表示， <small>FMT</small>是一种权宜之计。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">研究人员表示，除了“恶心”因素——当患者看到证据时，这种“厌恶”因素往往会消失<small>——FMT</small>还存在几个问题。那些捐赠粪便的人觉得这个过程令人不快。粪便本身不可能标准化，不同的捐赠者甚至不同的捐赠者都会有所不同。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这使得持续监管变得困难。美国和加拿大将<small>FMT</small>药丸视为研究药物。在意大利、荷兰和比利时， <small>FMT</small>被视为一种组织移植。与此同时，英国将其视为一种药品，因此可以进行更灵活的监管。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">我包容万千</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">所有这些都严重限制了供应。 Prossomariti 博士工作的实验室负责人西蒙·戈登伯格 (Simon Goldenberg) 估计，英国每年有 1000 名复发性<i>艰难梭菌</i>感染患者，其中只有几百人得到治疗。还有一个悬而未决的问题是，慢性病是否可以通过<small>FMT</small>可靠地治疗。加州大学圣地亚哥分校的胃肠病学家伯恩德·施纳布尔 (Bernd Schnabl) 表示，即使整个微生物群被替换，如果不治疗根本原因，好处也将是暂时的。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">因此，需要推动更精细的治疗。例如，施纳布尔博士并没有调整患者微生物组中个别细菌的数量，而是专注于它们产生的代谢物。以氨为例，它与肝硬化有关。限制其在肠道（以及随后的血液）中存在的一种方法是对邻近细菌进行基因改造，使其成为更好的食氨者。另一种方法是培养杀菌病毒，即噬菌体，它可以减少产氨微生物的数量。施纳布尔博士希望明年开始试验这种噬菌体治疗酒精相关性肝炎。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与此同时，由于缺乏符合足够高安全标准的细菌，细菌试验受到阻碍。因此，帕默博士正在开发符合严格法规（称为良好生产规范）的生产方法，这些法规适用于临床试验中使用的物质。帕默博士希望他的工厂能够在本月底之前获得认证，该工厂可以批量生产 50 升细菌。帕默博士说，如果它成功了，那么据他所知，这将使其成为第一个能够生产足够高质量细菌来提供试验的学术场所。他希望明年初开展微生物组治疗肝病的临床试验。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">工业界也很感兴趣。 Seres Therapeutics 是一家位于马萨诸塞州剑桥的生物技术公司。它的理念涉及设计细菌群落，当它们被空投到功能失调的肠道的恶劣环境中时，可以恢复秩序。该公司首席科学官 Matthew Henn 表示，这个想法是将细菌本身用作药物；它具有到达它需要去的地方的进化能力，并且其组成物种的多样性赋予它许多可能的同时影响。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 4 月，美国监管机构食品和药物管理局 ( <small>FDA</small> ) 批准了一种名为<small>SER</small> -109 的产品，这是第一种口腔微生物治疗药物，用于治疗复发性<i>艰难梭菌</i>感染。该公司目前正在接受同种异体造血干细胞移植的患者中测试一组被称为<small>SER</small> -155 的 16 种细菌，这是一种治疗白血病等疾病的方法，通过移植骨髓干细胞来增强患者的抵抗力。免疫系统。这个过程通常需要高剂量的抗生素，会严重损害微生物群，使危险的感染更难以抵抗。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 5 月份发布的早期结果显示，该治疗具有良好的耐受性，并且在 30 多天的时间里，接受<small>SER</small> -155 治疗的 9 名患者中仅发生 1 例新感染，而如果不接受治疗，预计会出现 6 例新感染。安慰剂对照试验的更多结果预计将于 2024 年末获得。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Seres 的团队已经确定了其他类型的易受细菌感染的免疫功能低下的患者，并希望很快开始其他试验。他们也有竞争。 Vedanta Biosciences 是另一家同样位于剑桥的生物技术公司。今年早些时候，该公司生产的产品<small>VE</small> 303 含有八种无害的<i>艰难梭菌</i>近缘菌株的混合物，在对 79 名反复感染该细菌的反复感染者进行的临床试验中表现良好。八周后，接受高剂量治疗的受试者比服用安慰剂的受试者复发<i>艰难梭菌</i>感染的可能性更低。该公司已获得<small>FDA</small>的“快速通道”指定，并希望很快开始更大规模的试验。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">换句话说，现在还处于早期阶段，但微生物组医学新时代的前景看起来很有希望，它比原始但有效的<small>FMT</small>更复杂。 “我们的药物就是这样，”Seres 的 Henn 博士说。 “他们是下一代。” <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:35:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/dlnh5u0sk72usheqls62lkjkjgc4nqki</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/11/08/faecal-transplants-are-just-the-start-of-a-new-sort-of-medicine </item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s home secretary uses a pro-Palestinian march to sow discord]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><span>停战</span><small>日</small>纪念几件事情，但这些事情并不意味着反对以色列轰炸加沙的抗议活动不应在这一天举行，而且其中一些建议应该举行。每年在 1918 年 11 月 11 日结束第一次世界大战的休战周年纪念日前后举行，停战日纪念自 1914 年以来在服役中牺牲的人们。它还庆祝战胜那些剥夺英国人重要自由的势力，包括抗议的权利。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，内政大臣苏埃拉·布雷弗曼 (Suella Braverman) 还是希望阻止定于 11 月 11 日在伦敦举行的亲巴勒斯坦游行。她将其描述为一场“仇恨游行”，展示了“暴徒恐吓和极端主义”。如果她的话是为了煽动分裂，那他们就成功了。最近几天，一些极右煽动者敦促支持者“保卫”和平纪念碑，这是伦敦市中心的一座战争死难者纪念碑。这可能促使伦敦警察厅敦促游行组织者取消游行。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而11月7日，大都会艺术博物馆专员马克·罗利爵士也明确表示，他不会屈服于政治压力。他说，这次游行并没有造成严重公共秩序混乱的威胁，不足以让他根据 1986 年《公共秩序法》寻求禁令。他还强调了“独立警察部门……只关注法律和我们面前的事实”的重要性。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">马克爵士指出，计划中的游行路线不会靠近和平纪念碑：将从大约一英里外的海德公园开始，结束于泰晤士河南部沃克斯豪尔的美国大使馆。停战日也发生在阵亡将士星期日的前一天，这是英国战争死难者的主要纪念活动，当天在纪念碑上举行仪式。游行的主要组织者之一巴勒斯坦团结运动组织 ( <small>psc</small> ) 成立于 1982 年，在过去的四个周六举行了基本上和平的游行，该组织计划将示威活动定于在全场默哀两分钟后两小时开始。停战日早晨。<small>公共安全委员会</small>还与大都会定期举行会议讨论安全问题。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">与其他地方一样，人们对英国反犹太主义的抬头感到真正的担忧。 10 月 7 日，哈马斯在伦敦杀害了以色列 1,400 人，哈马斯劫持人质的海报已被撕毁。抗议以色列轰炸加沙的人的一些口号是公然反犹太主义的。这些圣歌包括“从河到海”，这是在呼吁毁灭以色列，无论所有重复这句话的人是否明白这一点。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">警察确实有权处理仇恨煽动的抗议者。除了允许警方要求政府禁止游行外，《公共秩序法》还允许警方拘留任何造成“骚扰、警报或困扰”的人。大都会已经逮捕了几名明显的哈马斯支持者，哈马斯的政治派别于 2021 年被政府列为恐怖组织（军事派别于 2001 年被取缔）。但马克爵士此前曾表示，尽管法律对恐怖主义犯罪有明确规定，但对极端主义“还有更严厉的范围”。这就是“创造差距”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">看看法律是否需要收紧是合理的。但限制抗议权是一个错误。以色列在加沙的战争已造成一万多名巴勒斯坦人死亡。布雷弗曼女士的分裂言论并未得到政府其他人的响应。司法部长亚历克斯·乔克承认，抗议权“使我们成为一个公平和自由的国家”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而他和其他保守党人也表示游行不应该继续进行。 11 月 8 日，总理里希·苏纳克 (Rishi Sunak) 会见了马克爵士，强调他将为自己的决定负责。更多冲突还在后面。亲巴勒斯坦活动人士似乎不太可能放松抗议活动。内政大臣似乎有意加剧紧张局势。如果没有布雷弗曼女士搅局，警察的工作就已经够艰难的了。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:34:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/f9f0bpv8pktnid9jpliq0bqnl8tqger6</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/11/08/britains-home-secretary-uses-a-pro-palestinian-march-to-sow-discord </item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine inches closer to joining the EU]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">最近乌克兰的<span>好</span><small>消息</small>很少。美国驱逐俄罗斯军队的反攻行动已经陷入停滞，以色列和加沙的战斗抢走了它保持盟友资金和武器流动所需的一些风头，而特朗普主义在美国重启的前景也变得更加真实。因此，<small>欧盟</small>对乌克兰在加入该俱乐部的道路上走上正轨表示赞赏，这将是基辅的一个受欢迎的刺激——尽管距离它真正成为会员还需要数年时间。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 11 月 8 日，欧盟委员会在布鲁塞尔公布了对那些渴望成为<small>欧盟</small>成员国的国家如何进行所需改革的年度评估。包括乌克兰在内的八个国家正在积极争取加入欧盟，其中包括格鲁吉亚、摩尔多瓦和西巴尔干半岛的六个国家，这些国家几十年来一直寻求加入<small>欧盟</small>。 （土耳其名义上仍然是候选国，但其入盟谈判已被搁置。）乌克兰是迄今为止最大的活跃申请国。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">报告的结果是，一旦<small>欧盟</small>成员国领导人批准了委员会的建议，乌克兰和摩尔多瓦就应该获准在今年年底前开始正式加入谈判。 This would be an upgrade to their previous status as mere “candidate countries”, granted in June 2022. The report is not unambiguously positive: Ukraine is expected to deliver further reforms around the treatment of minorities, “de-oligarchisation” and combating corruption as a condition to keep making progress in talks.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> European officials helping their colleagues in Kyiv tick the required boxes have been impressed by the progress made. “They are moving forward fast, and not just in the circumstances of a country at war,” says one commission official. Nonetheless it will be some years before Ukraine&#39;s blue-and-yellow flag is flying outside Brussels buildings. A target date of 2030 floated by Charles Michel, who chairs meetings of <small>EU</small> leaders as president of the European Council, is seen as overly ambitious by many. Negotiations for Croatia, which in 2013 became the most recent country to join the <small>EU</small> , took six years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Part of the problem is that joining the <small>EU</small> requires the unanimous approval of all existing member states at every stage of the process. Plenty speak of a “merit-based” process, ie, one that does not offer short-cuts to aspiring member states—a phrase the commission used too as it unveiled its new report. Nobody wants to allow any new members to join, only for them to renege on commitments around the rule of law and democratic norms, as has happened notably in Hungary in recent years.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> So the road to accession will be long. One diplomat estimates that national capitals will have between 300 and 400 opportunities in effect to veto any new joiner, as progress on various metrics is gauged over the years. Nobody speaks critically of Ukraine publicly. But some diplomats privately express concern that it will be tricky to grant access to a country that does not fully control its territory, let alone to one at war. “Would Crimea be part of the single market?” asks one. A deal to provide Ukrainian agricultural products tariff-free access to the <small>EU</small> at the outset of the war later proved such a burden on neighbouring countries such as Poland that they in effect blockaded exports from their ally. Further similar problems would surely arise as actual membership neared.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such questions will not apply to the other aspiring members. The western Balkans have benefited hugely from Ukraine&#39;s efforts to join the <small>EU</small> , which have rekindled the entire idea of enlargement. Some, though, question the fairness of allowing Ukraine to potentially join ahead of countries that have been hoping to become <small>EU</small> members for years; Edi Rama, the Albanian prime minister, has quipped that Balkan countries should declare war on each other to accelerate their own membership talks.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> More broadly, war on the continent has pointed to the risks of having “grey zones”—countries that border the <small>EU</small> but are under the influence of rivals. Russia has plenty of sympathisers in the Balkans, notably in Bosnia-Herzegovina. That was once irritating; in these new geopolitical times it is intolerable. Turkey, China and Gulf states are also seen as encroaching on what the <small>EU</small> now thinks of as its backyard, with offers of aid and investment. The upshot is that vague promises of <small>EU</small> enlargement tomorrow are having to be replaced by concrete negotiating timelines today.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Such geopolitical imperatives will not cause the <small>EU</small> to close its eyes to shortcomings in applicants. Bosnia has been singled-out for criticism on matters concerning the rule of law, so although it is a candidate, its detailed accession negotiations have still not begun; Georgia is further behind in the joining process but now looks likely at least to gain candidate status in December. Tensions between Serbia and Kosovo, its former province, which five <small>EU</small> member states do not even recognise as an independent country, occasionally flare up into violence. The hope is that getting them closer to <small>EU</small> membership will give a boost to liberal forces that will improve governance.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A last thorny question is how the <small>EU</small> will have to reform to allow up to nine new members. A union of 27 is already tricky to manage, notably in areas where unanimity is required, as is the case in matters of foreign policy and setting the <small>EU</small> budget. Recasting the institutions for 36 members will prove tricky. But by giving a tentative green light to the aspiring members, the <small>EU</small> ’s existing countries are committing that they too will be ready when the time comes. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/f6b6283dolamo4aoddd1ma8jfd964fsf</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/europe/2023/11/08/ukraine-inches-closer-to-joining-the-eu </item><item><title><![CDATA[Rodeo plays a central role in Native American culture]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>F</span> <small>reshly washed</small> Wrangler <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2016/03/26/the-meaning-of-blue-jeans">jeans</a> and shiny silver belt buckles. Coors Light and Michelob Ultra for sale at the concession stands. It could have been any of the 650 professional rodeos sanctioned by the Professional Rodeo Cowboys Association ( <small>PRCA</small> ), the oldest and largest rodeo group, which 6m Americans attend each year. But instead, this was the Indian National Finals Rodeo ( <small>INFR</small> ), which recently took place in Las Vegas. Contestants were members of the 574 Native American tribes, and most of the 20,000 attendees were Native American, too. At one afternoon show, the national anthem was sung in Apache. “Where&#39;s the Navajos at?” the announcer boomed, as he warmed up the crowd.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Though historically sidelined, Indian rodeo is thriving, with more than 100 separate events across the country. The sport is remarkably popular among tribal members: though Native Americans account for only 3% of America&#39;s population, the <small>INFR</small> claims 3,500 cowboys and cowgirls, around half the members the <small>PRCA</small> has. Native competitors are becoming increasingly prominent in mainstream rodeo, too. Among the biggest stars are Dakota Louis, a bull-rider (pictured), and Derrick Begay, a roper, who will compete in the <small>PRCA</small> ’s National Finals Rodeo, held in December (also in Las Vegas).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For many on rural tribal lands, rodeo is not just a sport. It is “one of the few opportunities in Indian country to get out, to make a living, to get an education”, says Bo Vocu, a retired bull-rider and president of the <small>INFR</small> . Unemployment among Native Americans is more than double the national average and hovers around 50% on some reservations. With jobs scarce, bull-riding and roping can offer income and even bring college scholarships.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> But rodeo is not just a proverbial “ticket off the rez”, though its material rewards are real and attractive. (The <small>INFR</small> paid out more than $1m this year.) It is also a celebration of the fact that many Indians have long been cowboys and “rodeoed”.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The sport is often associated with white cowboys. But modern rodeo, which began in the 1880s and 1890s, was originally a “very multicultural, multilingual space”, says Rebecca Scofield, an associate professor of history at the University of Idaho. Rodeos brought together European immigrants, Mexican <i>vaqueros,</i> freed blacks and Native Americans.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Rodeo&#39;s name comes from the Spanish <i>rodear,</i> “to round up”. Regular round-ups to sort and brand cattle led to competitions to see who could rope and ride with the greatest skill. In 1888 a rodeo in Prescott, Arizona, was the first to charge admission and among the first to award prizes. By 1922, rodeo had even reached Madison Square Garden. As rodeo cowboys unionised in the first decades of the 20th century, some organisations explicitly excluded blacks and Native Americans, who were often relegated to <a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/01/25/restoring-black-americans-to-the-saddle">separate events</a> .<sup> </sup>By the late 1940s, the stereotypical rodeo cowboy had become “white, straight and hyper-masculine”, according to Ms Scofield.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The <small>INFR</small> provides a forum for Native Americans to connect and to be in a rare rodeo majority. “It definitely is a gathering of the nations for Indian cowboys,” says Megan Lunak, a roper from the Blackfeet tribe. With poverty and mental illness high on reservations, rodeo is a celebration of “resilience”. It is also a “a way to feel free,” since it facilitates travel, says Delphine Red Shirt, a lecturer in Native American Studies at Stanford.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Indian rodeos offer practice for competitors to be bucked off and beaten up as they develop the skills required to succeed on the higher-paying, mainstream rodeo circuit. The <small>INFR</small> is “pushing more Indian cowboys to get out there” rather than “just chase their local rodeos”, according to Bo Tyler Vocu, Mr Vocu&#39;s son, a talented bronc- and bull-rider.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Pro rodeo has begun to embrace Native American participants, in no small part because tribal riders come with a devoted following. Many Native Americans know someone who rodeos or have rodeoed themselves. As the sport seeks to shore up its audience (as white rural<a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/03/16/why-america-is-going-to-look-more-like-texas">populations</a> shrink), rodeo will only continue to get more diverse. The rodeo of the future may well look more like the rodeo of the past. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:25:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/uh8o61gib8p7hiisad8ucb4q28iah2gk</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/culture/2023/11/08/rodeo-plays-a-central-role-in-native-american-culture </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does America have enough weapons to support its allies?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1y6lujj e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text"><i>要阅读《经济学人》数据新闻的更多内容，请访问我们的<a href="/graphic-detail/">图形详细信息</a>页面。</i></p><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"> <span>W</span> <small>HEN AMERICA</small> provided Ukraine with weapons to resist Russia&#39;s invasion in 2022, many people asked whether it would also have the means to deter a Chinese assault on Taiwan. That question is all the more relevant now that Israel, another ally, is at war with Hamas. President Joe Biden <a href="/united-states/2023/10/20/biden-pleads-the-case-for-israel-ukraine-and-american-leadership">has insisted</a> that America will help its allies defend themselves, acting once again as the world&#39;s “arsenal of democracy”, as President Franklin Roosevelt promised the country would be in 1940. Does Mr Biden have the weapons he needs to keep his word? </p><figure class="g-fallback"></figure><figure class="interactive-figure"></figure><p class="article__body-text"> In general America sends different weapons to Israel, Taiwan and Ukraine, but when demands overlap they put pressure on the availability of some weapons (see table). Take air-defence missiles. All three allies have stocks of the Patriot, an expensive but effective missile system, for use against incoming missiles and aircraft. They also have the Stinger, a shoulder-fired missile capable of taking down low-flying aircraft. (The Avenger is a vehicle-mounted version of the Stinger.) All these battle-proven weapons are, however, in limited supply. In a recent assessment Mark Cancian of the Centre for Strategic and International Studies ( <small>CSIS</small> ), an American think-tank, deemed the Patriot to be “available but with some limits”, while stocks of Stingers and Avengers were “extremely limited”, because demand for them is high and spare parts are hard to find.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Javelins are also in short supply. These anti-tank missiles feature a fearsome combination of power and precision. Javelins in Ukraine, together with other anti-tank missiles, have taken out huge numbers of Russian tanks. Taiwan&#39;s arsenal of these American portable weapons systems may be helping to <a href="/special-report/2023/11/06/xi-jinping-worries-that-chinas-troops-are-not-ready-to-fight">deter China</a> . And although Israel has less need for anti-tank weapons, because Hamas does not have a serious fleet of armour, they could prove useful in urban warfare, for instance against fortified strongpoints, given their precision targeting, according to Mr Cancian. But getting hold of them will not be easy. An analysis by <a href="/graphic-detail/2022/05/03/why-weapons-crucial-to-the-war-in-ukraine-are-in-short-supply"><i>The Economist</i> last year</a> found that America may have given away more than a third of its stock of these weapons. <small>CSIS</small> now puts that share at 40%, making their supply extremely limited in a three-war scenario.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Stocks of other weapons not included in the <small>CSIS</small> tally are also depleted. For instance, 155mm artillery shells are in short supply; America has reportedly diverted to Israel a consignment intended for Ukraine. And war games suggest that, in a conflict over Taiwan, America would quickly run out of the long-range anti-ship missiles that would be most useful in repelling an invasion.</p><p class="article__body-text"> Many defence experts think that the shortages are a sign of America&#39;s inadequate investment in munitions in recent years. The reality of two wars—and the possibility of a third—is beginning to change that. America is increasing investment in the production of mortars, artillery, ammunition, rocket-propulsion systems and the microelectronics that increasingly go into modern munitions. These investments may give America&#39;s adversaries pause for thought.</p><p class="article__body-text"> America also has adequate stockpiles of many other weapons popular among its allies. Mr Cancian reckons that only a dozen of the 100 types of weapons sent to Ukraine since 2022 are in short supply. And the war between Israel and Hamas, for now, appears to be largely contained within Gaza, which should ease pressures on additional military aid. Still, should the world descend further into chaos, America would be at risk of becoming an <a href="/briefing/2023/10/24/the-overstretched-superpower">overstretched superpower</a> .■</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:25:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/qsv1t4lrn2sg8n4h3dgis10loqe5a6gq</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2023/11/08/does-america-have-enough-weapons-to-support-its-allies </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mathias Döpfner argues that the global trading system needs a shake-up]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>A</span> <small>DAM SMITH</small> is still the North Star for free-traders. But the 18th-century economist, who always placed national defence and security above wealth, would turn in his grave if he could see how free trade has been exploited in recent decades to the advantage of totalitarian systems and to the detriment of democracies. If we go on like this, we will get Marx instead of Smith.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Almost all democratic countries have fed this unfortunate trend, by naively strengthening bad actors through short-sighted and asymmetric trade policies. Now the West is paying the price.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Large parts of Europe, and to a lesser extent America, spent much of the past 30 years strengthening their business relations with undemocratic Middle Eastern countries from Saudi Arabia to Qatar, as well as with China and Russia. In doing so they bolstered Islamist and other autocratic regimes that have systematically undermined Western values. The war in Gaza is just the latest chapter. Through trade and other commercial ties, democracies helped to financially strengthen countries that have funded Hamas and other terrorist organisations that are escalating their war against the open-society model—in their eyes, the decadent Western lifestyle.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Ignoring these dangers was just as short-sighted as the policy errors that helped make the war in Ukraine possible. Under Angela Merkel, Germany turned away from nuclear energy and steadily increased its imports of Russian gas, from 36% of its total gas imports in 2011 to 65% in 2020. Mrs Merkel&#39;s trade policy helped finance Vladimir Putin&#39;s aggression. The current German government has tried to pivot away from Russia, but the damage will prove long-lasting.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Trade entanglements with China will have even more dangerous consequences for the West. Since joining the World Trade Organisation ( <small>WTO</small> ) in 2001, China&#39;s share of global <small>GDP</small> has grown almost five-fold, to over 18%, while those of both America and the <small>EU</small> have fallen significantly. It was a big mistake to expose market economies to a state-led capitalism that abuses existing terms of trade and competition—like agreeing to a football match where your team plays by <small>FIFA</small> rules and the other by its own.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> China continues to enjoy developing-country status within the <small>WTO</small> —allowing it to benefit from looser rules and privileges—even though it is the world&#39;s second-largest economy. It contributes almost a third of the world&#39;s carbon emissions (more than the next five largest polluters combined) and continues to expand its coal-based power generation. Any effort to combat climate change without China is pointless. Western countries have, in any case, contributed to the problem by outsourcing their climate sins to China—shifting production to an economy in which environmental protection is poor, child labour is accepted and human rights are flexibly defined.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The West&#39;s current approach to trade is rooted in dependency. A large portion of antibiotics prescribed in America are made with ingredients that come from China. Similar reliance abounds on the export side of the ledger: the three largest German carmakers sell more than a third of their vehicles to Chinese consumers. And then there is Taiwan. Businesses based on the island control 90% of the global market for the most advanced and sophisticated microprocessors. Were China to attack Taiwan, the chip industry would be at the mercy of the Chinese Communist Party.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The West has, in short, been led into a trade trap. To escape, it needs to reinvent truly free trade.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The <small>WTO</small> is not the answer. Dysfunctional and bureaucratic, it is part of the problem. It should cease operations and make way for a more stripped-down, efficient approach—something more like the General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, or <small>GATT</small> , that preceded the <small>WTO</small> . At its core should be a new alliance of democracies whose membership is based on three simple criteria: acceptance of the rule of law, respect for human rights and robust carbon-emissions targets. Any country that meets these criteria could trade tariff-free with other members. Those that don&#39;t would be subject to high tariffs. It would be a trade policy based on incentives rather than outright prohibitions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Every country would be free to join. For some it would involve a decision about whether to provide a little more freedom for a lot more prosperity and stability. The concept would stimulate and strengthen democratic economies. Like any good tax reform, the short-term losses would be far outweighed by the medium- and long-term gains. Over time, the price of sticking with the current, increasingly flawed model would be higher.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For 17 straight years Freedom House has recorded a decline in democracy around the world, and some 40% of the world&#39;s population now live in countries that the think-tank considers “not free”. But democracies still account for almost 70% of global economic output. Open societies still have the upper hand.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> If they are not to lose it, they must act now, led jointly by America and Europe. America cannot succeed alone; unilaterally decoupling from China would only further weaken the American economy. And a Europe that decoupled alone would achieve even less, ending up as a theme park for nostalgic tourists that created little value.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> For the sake of democracy, we need a new framework that is centred on truly free trade among free countries. Because we cannot trade freedom for profits. If we do, we will lose both. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Mathias Döpfner is the chief executive of Axel Springer and the author of “The Trade Trap: How to Stop Doing Business with Dictators” (2023).</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 15:32:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/iqgjrocnhvtudd8b6ldghkrjv0kfrr0v</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/by-invitation/2023/11/08/mathias-dopfner-argues-that-the-global-trading-system-needs-a-shake-up </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why covid-19 did not harm rich economies as badly as first thought]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>M</span> <small>ODERN ECONOMIC</small> statistics are best thought of as a work in progress. As new information becomes available to national statistics offices they update and revise previously published numbers. The picture of the economy comes into focus only slowly, more like an old-fashioned polaroid than a snap on a modern smartphone. Revisions of older data are part and parcel of the process and rarely make the headlines. But in the past two months revisions in Britain and Italy have come close to rewriting recent economic history.发生了什么？</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Data published in Britain during 2022 and early 2023 had depicted the country as the only <small>G</small> 7 economy that by the end of 2021 had still not <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/02/16/the-shape-of-the-post-pandemic-economy-in-britain">recovered</a> its pre-pandemic output levels. But after revisions to the 2020 and 2021 figures, in September <small>GDP</small> was found to be 0.6% <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/09/04/britains-statisticians-fix-a-blunder-and-find-a-bigger-economy">above</a> its pre-covid size rather than 1.2% below it. The Office for National Statistics added almost 2% to its estimate of national income and transformed Britain&#39;s economic performance from that of a global laggard to something more respectable. Also in September Italy&#39;s statistics office upgraded its estimate of growth in 2021, at current prices, from 7% to 8.3%. That was not enough to offer the government the room it hoped for to justify tax cuts, but was still a significant revision.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In both countries the absolute size of the revisions is partially explained by the magnitude of the <a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2021/01/09/what-is-the-economic-cost-of-covid-19">swings in <small>GDP</small></a> in nearly all economies in 2020 and 2021. The lockdowns of 2020 caused output to plummet at a pace not seen in decades and the unwinding of restrictions in 2021 prompted a strong <a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/which-economies-have-done-best-and-worst-during-the-pandemic/21806917">bounce-back</a> in most places. Proportionally normal revisions to large swings in <small>GDP</small> add up to big numbers.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> These revisions are driven by what the statisticians call input-output tables ( <small>IOT</small> ). The initial estimates are based on partial data and on headline revenue figures reported by companies. As more detailed data become available, statisticians are able to use <small>IOT</small> to measure the inputs and outputs of each sector more minutely. That allows them to get a better look at how profit margins evolved over time. Margins, it is now thought, held up better than once believed, leading to higher estimates of profits, income and hence total <small>GDP</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Over the coming months more rich countries will be able to update their data in light of better information. More revisions will follow. Changes of 1-2% in the estimated level of national output can grab the headlines, but the fundamental economic picture remains unchanged. The broad story is that 2020, though still dreadful, was not quite as economically disastrous as once thought and the recovery in 2021 was a touch stronger than it first seemed. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:21:38 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/j58erpsmvc286adc1emh7d2csb832et4</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2023/11/08/why-covid-19-did-not-harm-rich-economies-as-badly-as-first-thought</item></channel></rss>