<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[Latest Updates]]></title><link/> https://www.economist.com/latest/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/economist/latest?mode=fulltext" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[The most recent blogs and online articles from The Economist - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 12 日星期四 12:21:15 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[What will a successful ground invasion look like for Israel?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-9xqu6e e1ey6m750"><p class="article__body-text article__body-text--dropcap"><span>国防军</span>正准备<a href="/middle-east-and-africa/2023/10/11/brutal-urban-warfare-awaits-israels-army-in-gaza">派部队</a>跟进对加沙<small>的</small>空袭。入侵将是血腥的，如果真主党卷入冲突，情况可能会更加血腥。澳大利亚人将于本周末投票决定是否将<a href="/asia/2023/09/28/australians-looks-set-to-reject-new-provisions-for-aboriginal-people">土著议会之声</a>写入宪法（11:36）。而且，为什么 Birkenstock 的鞋子已有 249 年历史仍然很流行 (19:27)。 </p><div class="css-1lm38nn e50l3u40"><figure><audio class="react-audio-player " id="audio-player" src="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/acast/s/theintelligencepodcast/e/6527cbdbd40c970012554bfd/media.mp3?tk=eyJ1aWQiOiJ0b20iLCJ0ayI6ImZHeExMd3dDIiwiYWRzIjpmYWxzZSwic3BvbnMiOmZhbHNlLCJzdGF0dXMiOiJwdWJsaWMifQ==&sig=zyLcaZcVMLjrUIv_PaYdWZ0-ChazIlwL1wt5wE1vVhg"><p>您的浏览器不支持<audio>元素。</p></audio></figure></div><p class="article__body-text">立即注册<a href="https://www.economist.com/podcastsplus-intelligence">《经济学人播客+》</a> ，即可通过我们的限时优惠获得 50% 的订阅折扣。在《经济学人播客+》推出之前，您无需付费。</p><p class="article__body-text">如果您已经是《经济学人》的订阅者，作为订阅的一部分，您将可以完全访问我们的所有节目。</p><p>有关《经济学人播客+》的更多信息，包括如何访问，请访问我们的<a href="https://myaccount.economist.com/s/article/What-is-Economist-Podcasts">常见问题解答页面</a>。</p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:46:10 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/dte91cbim4o0cbbchf2pj4uk9na0fmtc</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2023/10/12/what-will-a-successful-ground-invasion-look-like-for-israel </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hamas’s atrocities and Israel’s retaliation will change both sides for ever]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><small>最初的几个</small><span>小时</span>很混乱。以色列南部靠近加沙边境的居民被火箭弹和迫击炮弹的声音吵醒。他们冲向避难所——在这个国家的这个地区，这是一个残酷的例行公事，但仍然是例行公事。几分钟后，他们听到枪声越来越近，并用阿拉伯语喊叫。这根本不是例行公事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">他们家外的难以想象的场景也开始在社交媒体上流传：巴勒斯坦武装分子坐在一辆皮卡车的床上，驶过以色列城镇，向路人开枪；公共汽车站有一堆尸体，军事哨所也有一堆尸体。早上的时间持续得很长，但没有任何救援到来。疯狂的以色列人在他们的安全室里打电话给电视新闻节目，并小声询问他们的军队在哪里。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然后，同样令人震惊的是关于绑架的报道。一位母亲说，她的两个儿子（其中一个只有 12 岁）被绑架并拖过边境。一段视频显示，一名老妇人开着高尔夫球车在加沙街道上游行，她僵硬的笑容掩盖了她的震惊，一名武装男子坐在她身后。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">死亡人数不断上升。近一周后，当局仍在清点尸体。在 Be&#39;eri 这个约有 1000 人的小基布兹，武装分子挨家挨户屠杀了大约 10% 的人口。在以北 8 公里的卡法阿扎 (Kfar Azza)，死亡人数可能更多。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于以色列人来说，10 月 7 日是史无前例的一天。在这个面积只有 1000 万的国家里，有超过 1,300 人被杀。死亡人数超过了过去20年以色列和巴勒斯坦之间所有暴力事件中丧生的以色列人人数。另有 3,300 人受伤。以色列人曾认为控制加沙的巴勒斯坦伊斯兰组织哈马斯是一个可以控制的威胁。现在它发动了该国历史上最致命的恐怖袭击。中东最强大的军队失去了对自己城镇的控制，需要几天时间才能重新控制。当局已找到至少 1,500 名巴勒斯坦武装分子的尸体，超过一个营的枪手数量，他们设法冲过据称防守严密的边界。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">随着震惊逐渐变成愤怒，迫在眉睫的问题是以色列将如何应对。它已经开始了报复性空袭，造成 1,200 多名巴勒斯坦人死亡，其中许多是平民，并使超过 30 万人流离失所。以色列不会就此止步，尽管其军事选择毫无吸引力。未来几周，以色列人和巴勒斯坦人必将遭受更多苦难。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但 10 月 7 日的后果将更为广泛。这场大屠杀不仅可能重塑以色列对巴勒斯坦人的态度，也可能重塑其国内政治。它<a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamas-has-failed-to-rally-the-middle-east-to-its-cause">威胁到哈马斯对加沙权力的控制</a>；它还可能引发地区战争。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">袭击以一连串火箭弹开始：几个小时内就发射了 2,200 枚火箭弹。这已经足够令人震惊了：哈马斯在 2014 年对以色列的战争中花了近一个月的时间才发射了这么多子弹。但以色列人很快发现这些发射是为更大规模的行动做掩护。推土机冲破了边境围栏，数百名武装分子涌了过去。其他人乘坐滑翔伞飞越它，或者乘坐小艇绕它航行。他们呈扇形散布到以色列城镇并开始杀戮。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列花了几个小时才组织防御。一些部队不得不从北部边境赶往南方。他们一抵达，就在集结地苦苦挣扎，而指挥官则试图制定作战计划。几位退役将军亲自动手，穿上旧军装，驱车前往被围困的村庄，进行临时反击。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">甚至在收复自己的领土之前，以色列就开始对加沙进行空袭。总理本雅明·内塔尼亚胡宣布以色列处于战争状态，他的政府开始为可能的地面进攻做准备。军队已动员了 36 万名预备役军人，并花了几天时间将坦克和其他装备运送到加沙边境。国防部长约夫·加兰特承诺全面包围加沙。 “没有电，没有食物，没有水，没有燃料，一切都关闭了。” 10 月 11 日，其唯一的发电厂燃料耗尽并关闭。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">埃雷兹是以色列和加沙之间的唯一过境点，已无限期关闭。以色列要求加沙平民通过与埃及接壤的拉法过境点逃离，但一再轰炸该过境点。无论如何，埃及严格限制允许过境的人数。即使在和平时期，巴勒斯坦人也很难离开加沙。现在这是不可能的了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">当以色列军队准备在加沙作战时，必须密切关注其北部边境。 10 月 8 日，黎巴嫩的什叶派激进组织和政党真主党炮击了有争议的一小片领土沙巴阿农场。根据不成文的交战规则，沙巴发生的事情就留在沙巴：真主党可以表达对巴勒斯坦人的支持，但也可以向以色列表明，它不希望发生更广泛的冲突。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而一天后，以色列军队击毙了一群从黎巴嫩越境的枪手。三名真主党武装分子随后在以色列的报复性轰炸中被打死，导致该组织向以色列军队哨所发射火箭弹。双方可能都不想爆发战争，但升级并不总是符合逻辑。黎巴嫩民众纷纷囤积食物和燃料。以色列已撤离北部边境附近的城镇。哈马斯大声呼吁其他国家加入对以色列的攻击。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列军队可能需要时间来准备，但对加沙地带的地面进攻似乎几乎是肯定的。以色列军队从 1967 年到 2005 年占领加沙，随后撤军，迫使约 8,000 名犹太定居者随之撤退。此后，以色列基本上封锁了该领土的空中、陆地和海上，同时允许一些巴勒斯坦人在以色列工作，并允许非威胁性的货物进入。 （埃及几乎也有同样的限制。）</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">以色列最近一次入侵加沙是在 2014 年，目的是摧毁哈马斯在边界围栏下挖掘的用于渗透以色列的隧道。以色列军队并没有渗透到该地区很远的地方，该地区只有约10公里宽、40公里长，但却居住着200万人口。即便如此，这次行动还是表明地面攻击可能会出错。哈马斯部队袭击了拉法附近的以色列巡逻队，并俘获了一名军官哈达尔·戈尔丁。以色列随后连续几天炮击拉法，造成数十名巴勒斯坦人死亡。戈尔丁后来被宣布死亡。以色列人将此事件称为“黑色星期五”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">即将到来的攻击将会更大。以色列可能部署两个装甲师和一个轻型空降师，每个师下辖五个旅。其中一些部队正在等待坦克和其他装备到达加沙周围的集结地。其他人在过去几天的战斗中遭受了损失。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">假设以色列领导人确实下令大规模入侵，一两个装备坦克的装甲旅可能会试图通过代尔巴拉附近最窄处（6公里）向西推进，将地带一分为二。其他两三个旅规模的部队（每个几千人）可能会集中在北部，包括加沙城周围，另外一两个部队则集中在南部的汗尤尼斯或拉法。 </p><div class="css-0 eitqf4z0"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt="摘自 Telegram 频道上发布的 UGC 视频的截图，展示哈马斯武装分子袭击超新星音乐节的后果" width="1280" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 834px, 95vw" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP003.jpg"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-nggv6j edweubf0">大屠杀纪念碑</span><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：Getty Images</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">他们的目标可能是针对哈马斯和伊斯兰圣战组织（一个独立的激进组织），重点关注空袭范围之外的领导人和基础设施。哈马斯声称其在加沙拥有数百公里的隧道。找到他们的入口并投放炸药将是首要任务。最大的挑战将是城市战，这是一项众所周知的艰巨任务。加沙的人口比伦敦或东京更稠密，为武装分子提供了很多藏身之处，而平民却没有多少地方可以避难。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">哈马斯可能指望进行相对谨慎的袭击。该组织认为，以色列无法承受地面入侵造成的巨大伤亡。 “我们知道他们是胆小鬼，”驻卡塔尔的哈马斯高级官员穆萨·阿布·马尔祖克说。 “我们知道他们无法在地面上作战。”它还预计加沙地带100多名以色列和外国人质的存在将限制以色列军队。哈马斯希望用这些囚犯来交换以色列监狱中关押的 5,200 名巴勒斯坦人中的许多人（如果不是全部的话）。它还威胁说，每次以色列“在没有事先警告的情况下”轰炸加沙平民住宅时，就会杀死一名平民。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，最近几天灾难性的死亡人数可能会改变以色列的盘算。华盛顿智库布鲁金斯学会的纳坦·萨克斯表示：“以色列承担成本的意愿——而且是确切的——成本比过去高得多。”至于人质，许多仍在埋葬亲人的以色列人表示，他们没有心情与杀害他们的组织讨价还价。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">忽视后果自负</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事实上，以色列不得不重新审视许多长期持有的假设，最引人注目的是认为加沙可以安全地任其恶化的信念。 2007年哈马斯从巴勒斯坦<small>临时</small>政府手中夺取了对加沙的控制权后，以色列和埃及大幅收紧了边境限制，窒息了加沙的经济。尽管此后暴力事件屡屡发生，但以色列官员开始认为哈马斯变得更加务实。 “最重要的是，他们希望保持对加沙的控制，”一名军官去年表示。 “要做到这一点，他们需要改善经济。”人们的想法是，如果以色列允许阿拉伯政府为加沙的基本社会服务提供资金，并为加沙人在以色列工作发放更多许可证，那么该领土将保持静止状态。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">这种观点不仅完全错误，而且以色列自诩的安全部门也未能发现一场精心策划的袭击正在酝酿之中。加沙的每一个电话都通过以色列网络进行，这简化了窃听。无人机经常飞越该地带。以色列在该领土上也有庞大的线人网络，但都无济于事。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">毫无疑问，部分问题在于概念上的失败：认为哈马斯已经对大规模冲突失去了兴趣。事实上，甚至一些哈马斯领导人似乎也感到惊讶。阿布·马尔祖克表示，他和卡塔尔其他高级领导人事先并未获悉此次袭击事件。自2017年叶海亚·辛瓦尔成为加沙哈马斯领导人以来，少数主要在加沙的强硬派巩固了权力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">第二个错误是本雅明·内塔尼亚胡(Binyamin Netanyahu)对巴勒斯坦人采取的分而治之的政策，内塔尼亚胡在过去14年中有12年担任以色列总理。长期以来，他一直试图削弱<small>巴勒斯坦权力机构</small>，该机构仍然管理着约旦河西岸的部分地区。自 2014 年半心半意的谈判破裂以来，他一直拒绝恢复和平谈判。他冻结了<small>以色列</small>代表巴勒斯坦权力机构征收的税收收入的转移。与此同时，他将哈马斯视为加沙的合法势力。例如，2011 年，他批准了一项协议，用 1,027 名巴勒斯坦囚犯交换武装分子 2006 年抓获的以色列士兵吉拉德·沙利特 (Gilad Shalit)。这次交换自然提高了哈马斯在巴勒斯坦人中的地位。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于内塔尼亚胡先生来说，逻辑很清楚。巴勒斯坦<small>权力机构</small>致力于与以色列谈判两国解决方案，这令总理的右翼支持者感到厌恶。削弱巴勒斯坦权力<small>机构</small>并支持其激进竞争对手将有助于他声称以色列没有“和平伙伴”。但巴勒斯坦人却得到了一个不同的、但也是可以预见的教训：从以色列获得让步的唯一方法是通过武力。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，哈马斯现在可能做得有些过头了。一些观察家认为，它没想到攻击会如此成功，并且不确定如何进行。它可能希望吓唬以色列让步，但实际上却让以色列做好了战争的准备。以色列军队10月10日告诉外国国防武官，其目标是“消灭”哈马斯的领导层。据参加会议的人士透露，军方的最终目标是摧毁哈马斯的能力，无论需要多长时间。然而，说起来容易做起来难，正如美国在阿富汗长期战争中或以色列在占领黎巴嫩南部 18 年期间所学到的那样。 </p><div class="css-0 eitqf4z0"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt="一名以色列士兵在以色列加沙边境附近的一辆装甲运兵车旁祈祷" width="1280" sizes="(min-width: 960px) 834px, 95vw" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBP002.jpg"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-nggv6j edweubf0">下一场战斗迫在眉睫</span><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：美联社</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">即使以色列能够铲除哈马斯，也没有人知道什么会取代它。巴勒斯坦权力<small>机构</small>太弱，无法在加沙维护权威；它甚至还不足以控制西岸，部分地区已经陷入无政府状态。大多数巴勒斯坦人和大多数加沙人都希望解散它。 87岁的总统马哈茂德·阿巴斯已经近20年没有踏足加沙了。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">有人闲谈派遣阿拉伯维和人员保卫加沙，但很少有阿拉伯政权愿意这样做。 1949年至1967年埃及占领加沙；双方都对那段时光有着痛苦的回忆。沙特阿拉伯和阿联酋等海湾国家无意统治超过200万巴勒斯坦人。大多数以色列人也不希望重新占领该领土。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">然而，入侵然后离开并不能改变现状。以色列人离开后，哈马斯的领导人和大部分武装人员可能会从他们的掩体中出来并恢复对巴勒斯坦领土的控制。这是一个令人难以接受的结果，但却是最有可能的结果。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于任何以色列政府来说，制定明确的前进道路都是困难的，尤其是现任政府。今年是政治严重动荡的一年。经过一年多的反对后，内塔尼亚胡在 11 月份的提前选举中赢得了多个席位。他领导的政府完全由右翼和宗教政党组成。他的国家安全部长伊塔马尔·本-格维尔因极端民族主义观点而被禁止在以色列军队服役。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">此后，内塔尼亚胡推行了一个分裂的议程，其中包括限制最高法院推翻政府政策的权力，以及赋予政客在法官任命方面更多的发言权。批评者称这是一场司法“政变”，并于今年每周六举行大规模抗议活动，直到 10 月 7 日被暂停。陆军预备役军人威胁要抵制他们的义务兵役（这一策略也已被搁置）。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">乐观者希望本月的大屠杀将有助于使以色列政治重新回到中间位置。纳夫塔利·贝内特 (Naftali Bennett) 的顾问希姆里特·梅厄 (Shimrit Meir) 写道：“在最黑暗的日子过后，如果能够达成和解，那就是以色列恢复理智、结束政治危机并组建联合政府。”贝内特于 2021 年接替内塔尼亚胡出任总理。短暂担任总理。内塔尼亚胡先生在 10 月 9 日的黄金时段讲话中敦促中间派政党“无条件”加入他的政府。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> 10月11日，经过几天的谈判，领导第二大中间派政党民族团结党的前陆军参谋长本尼·甘茨同意加入“紧急政府”。但最大反对党 Yesh Atid 的领导人 Yair Lapid 迄今拒绝参加。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">团结在怀疑之中</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">对于两党来说，困境在于加入一个他们的支持者在过去一年里一直抗议的政府。内塔尼亚胡承诺不会推行任何与战争无关的立法，但拒绝抛弃他最极端的联盟伙伴。对于一位一如既往地关心自己政治生存的首相来说，这是有道理的。只要战斗持续，联合政府就会持续下去。内塔尼亚胡先生不想疏远他随后需要组建另一个右翼联盟的政党。甘茨先生无论如何都捏着鼻子加入，向缺乏军事专业知识的政府提供军事专业知识。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管这将暂时稳定政府，但最近几天发生的事件可能会结束内塔尼亚胡先生漫长且充满卷土重来的职业生涯。他花了一年的时间进行一场不必要的政治斗争，而不是关注真正的威胁——而在此之前的许多年，他一直在努力让巴勒斯坦成为一个无法解决的问题。安全是他的口号，十多年来他一直负责监督以色列武装部队和情报部门，只曾短暂中断过一段时间。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">哈马斯则选择了凶残的虚无主义。与加沙领导人交谈就像进入了一个幻想世界，在那里加沙得到了“解放”，尽管其居民却被困在 365 平方公里的牢房里，陷入贫困。对以色列的胜利即将到来，在那之前，加沙人将欣然忍受他们的命运。自大屠杀发生以来，该组织明确表示，除了希望引发对以色列更广泛的攻击之外，除了持续暴力外，它没有任何计划。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">简而言之，正在发生的灾难似乎很可能暴露出双方思维的贫乏。唉，最近几天发生的令人震惊的流​​血事件，以及未来可能发生的更多恐怖事件，也将使采取更具建设性的方法来解决冲突变得更加困难。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:28:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/j3vtaf9f098u4n7jtcbvjrnrk61lurgg</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamass-atrocities-and-israels-retaliation-will-change-both-sides-for-ever </item><item><title><![CDATA[Hamas has failed to rally the Middle East to its cause]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>“噢，</span><small>我们所有阿拉伯和伊斯兰国家的人民</small>，”哈马斯军事部门领导人穆罕默德·戴伊夫在该组织袭击以色列南部之际发布的一份录音声明中吟诵道。 “……任何有枪的人都应该把它拿出来的一天已经到来。现在是时候了。如果你没有枪，请拿起你的菜刀、斧头、斧头、燃烧瓶、卡车、推土机或汽车。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">一些人响应了他的号召。在埃及第二大城市亚历山大，一名警察枪杀了两名以色列游客和他们的导游。在以色列与黎巴嫩紧张的边境地区，发生了零星的战斗。从巴林到摩洛哥，哈马斯的支持者纷纷走上街头。在叙利亚首都大马士革，巴勒斯坦国旗照亮了歌剧院。在黎巴嫩的巴勒斯坦难民营中，游客们报告了狂欢节的气氛。在阿拉伯世界颇受欢迎的半岛电视台的所在地卡塔尔，流亡的哈马斯领导人跪倒在办公室地板上致谢，该电视台一直以毫不掩饰的钦佩之情报道暴行。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">但哈马斯号召援助的阿拉伯和穆斯林军团还没有动静，至少现在还没有。一些阿拉伯政府已经或正在考虑与以色列正式实现和平。大多数其他人热衷于将敌意限制在纯粹的言辞层面。他们的秘密警察通常会压制任何抗议活动，担心示威者也可能反对他们自己的政府。此外，自2011年“阿拉伯之春”令人兴奋的抗议活动演变成混乱、分裂、暴力和镇压之后，阿拉伯“街道”仍处于疲惫不堪的状态。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，暴力和战争蔓延到其他战线，特别是黎巴嫩的危险依然严峻。以色列预计在加沙开始的地面行动可能是一个触发因素。一方面，美国正在认真对待这一威胁。它已在以色列附近海域部署了一艘航空母舰和其他军舰。中东的空军中队正在得到加强。紧急武器正在运往以色列。其目的既是为了表达对以色列的声援，也是为了阻止伊朗及其代理人参与其中。乔·拜登总统 10 月 10 日表示：“对于任何国家、任何组织、任何想利用这种情况的人，我都有一句话。” “不。不。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">由宿敌伊朗及其在伊拉克、黎巴嫩、叙利亚和也门的代理人组成的所谓以色列“抵抗轴心”的成员正在为哈马斯的“胜利行动”欢呼，并暗示他们可能会加入战斗。但目前还没有人这样做。真主党是黎巴嫩的什叶派民兵兼政党，可以说是以色列边境上最强大的敌人，它知道它在 2006 年发起的支持哈马斯的战争对黎巴嫩造成了巨大的破坏。到目前为止，它还没有再次加入。由于经济崩溃，黎巴嫩无力应对另一场灾难。即使像真主党这样的国中之国也可能会犹豫是否要造成进一步的损害。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">伊朗也保持着干燥状态。它向真主党提供的12万至15万枚导弹和火箭可能主要是为了阻止以色列轰炸伊朗核设施。尽管伊朗发表了各种反以色列言论，但它从未为巴勒斯坦人发动过战争。加沙的一名哈马斯官员表示：“我们知道我们是（伊朗）的工具。”他指出，哈马斯和伊朗在逊尼派和什叶派穆斯林之间的宗派分歧上处于对立面。 “归根结底，我们只有<i>zawaj muta</i> ，一段临时婚姻。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管如此，随着加沙战斗的加剧，轴心国采取更多行动的压力可能会增加。四个月前，真主党在黎巴嫩南部进行了一场大肆宣传的军事演习，练习占领以色列城镇。黎巴嫩安全专家希拉尔·卡尚表示，哈马斯现在这样做“让他们面临压力”。目前，跨境袭击的目的似乎是警告，而不是战争的开始。哈马斯发动袭击的第二天，真主党炮击了以色列在沙巴阿农场的阵地，这是一个有争议的边境地区，那里的战斗往往是自给自足的。其他地方也发生了更严重的交火，包括导弹和炮火。真主党报告称，其三名战士已被打死。以色列军队表示，还击毙了至少两名渗透者。问题是这些小冲突是否会升级为更大的事件。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">亚伯拉罕焦躁不安的孩子们</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">伊朗已经从哈马斯的屠杀中获益。它最大的担忧是其海湾邻国与以色列的和解。根据《亚伯拉罕协议》，以色列近年来与包括巴林和阿拉伯联合酋长国在内的几个阿拉伯国家实现了关系正常化。下一个获奖者是沙特阿拉伯，它是世界上最大的石油出口国，也是伊斯兰教两个圣地的所在地。上个月，沙特王储兼事实上的统治者穆罕默德·本·萨勒曼表示，与以色列的协议即将达成：“我们每天都在更接近。”以色列部长已开始公开访问沙特阿拉伯。就在哈马斯袭击前几天，伊朗最高领导人阿亚图拉阿里哈梅内伊警告说，与以色列建立关系的国家正在将自己置于“危险之中”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">考虑到沙特阿拉伯国内民众的敌意，以及王子要求与美国签订正式防御条约和浓缩铀手段等要求，以色列和沙特阿拉伯之间的协议永远不会轻易达成。如果以色列总理本雅明·内塔尼亚胡向巴勒斯坦人做出沙特希望的让步，他也将面临失去极右翼联盟盟友的风险。尽管如此，破坏这笔交易可能是哈马斯发动袭击的主要目标之一。 </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FBM944.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">如果是这样，它可能已经成功了，至少在一段时间内是这样。华盛顿智库卡内基国际和平基金会的亚伦·大卫·米勒表示，美国促成以色列与沙特达成协议的能力“已降至零”。鉴于流血事件，任何以色列领导人都不会向巴勒斯坦人做出让步。沙特阿拉伯也将受到类似的限制，无论如何，穆罕默德亲王可能不愿意仓促与可能很快失去权力的美国和以色列领导人达成协议。由于“持续占领”，沙特外交部实际上将暴力归咎于以色列。 10 月 11 日，穆罕默德王子和伊朗总统易卜拉欣·莱西通了电话——这是他们第一次这样做。伊朗表示，他们讨论了“结束针对巴勒斯坦的战争罪行的必要性”；沙特方面表示，王子正试图“阻止局势持续升级”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">尽管沙特阿拉伯对与以色列建立关系犹豫不决，但欧盟却因支持巴勒斯坦权力机构而陷入困境。巴勒斯坦权力机构管理着巴勒斯坦人控制的西岸部分地区，由巴勒斯坦竞争对手法塔赫领导。派别属于哈马斯。<small>欧盟</small>对<small>巴勒斯坦权力机构</small>的援助正在接受审查，因为有人声称它可能资助极端主义。 10 月 9 日，欧盟扩大事务专员奥利弗·瓦赫利 (Oliver Varhelyi) 表示，价值数亿美元的付款已被暂停。他立即遭到<small>欧盟</small>最高外交官何塞普·博雷尔的反驳，博雷尔表示“惩罚所有巴勒斯坦人民”会损害<small>欧盟</small>。</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0">拜登和比比的B计划</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">至于以色列的重要盟友美国，这场大屠杀使拜登和内塔尼亚胡之间和解了。拜登对以色列转向民族主义右翼以及针对遏制司法机构的大规模抗议活动感到担忧，此前曾试图限制与内塔尼亚胡的接触。现在，他给了总理很大的余地来采取军事反应。他在 10 月 10 日的电视讲话中宣称：“毫无疑问，美国是以色列的支持者。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登先生迫切关心的是确定有多少美国人被杀（已确认死亡 22 人）或被扣为人质（具体数字未知，但仍有 17 人下落不明）。第二个更广泛的目标是控制整个地区可能出现的冲击波。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登对以色列的拥抱可能在某个时候成为一种温和的克制形式。美国开始更加关注加沙平民的困境。拜登敦促以色列“在战争法范围内”行动，这是对以色列官员的一种含蓄的谴责，他们曾谈到“全面围困”并切断对该领土的食品、水和电力供应。美国敦促以色列和埃及开放某种人道主义走廊。细节尚不清楚，但有报道称，它正在倡导为美国公民和至少一些巴勒斯坦人提供离开加沙的安全方式。 “平民没有做错任何事。我们希望确保他们有出路，”白宫发言人表示。但埃及不希望出现人员外逃。其总统阿卜杜勒-法塔赫·塞西表示，巴勒斯坦问题的解决不应“以牺牲其他各方的利益为代价”。承认巴勒斯坦难民大量涌入将破坏埃及的稳定，并可能被视为为以色列对加沙的破坏性袭击铺平道路。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">动荡中的另一项克制努力涉及伊朗。也许是因为他们不想开辟另一条战线，美国和以色列官员表示，没有关于伊朗或真主党直接参与策划或指挥哈马斯袭击的硬情报。但拜登的国家安全顾问杰克·沙利文坚称，“从广义上讲，伊朗是这次袭击的同谋，因为他们向哈马斯提供了大部分资金”，更不用说多年的训练、武器和其他支持了。一些报道称伊朗对这次袭击感到惊讶。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">拜登上任时希望恢复一项限制伊朗核计划的协议，巴拉克·奥巴马(Barack Obama)不顾内塔尼亚胡的反对签署了该协议，但唐纳德·特朗普(Donald Trump)撕毁了该协议。目前还没有达成协议，伊朗现在距离制造核弹更近了。哈马斯现在的恐惧可能会让他看起来像个傻瓜，因为他甚至试图与一个高呼“以色列死亡”的政权进行谈判。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">事实上，共和党人正在将拜登的伊朗政策与哈马斯的屠杀划清界限。他们普遍批评他放松了特朗普对伊朗“极限施压”的政策。他们特别谴责他通过谈判达成一项协议，以确保五名被监禁的美国人于 9 月获释。这涉及解冻伊朗在韩国的 60 亿美元石油收入，这些收入目前由卡塔尔托管。政府表示，这笔钱尚未支付，将仅用于支付非伊朗承包商的食品和其他人道主义物资。一位高级官员坚称：“伊朗任何人都不会动用这些资金中的一分钱、一分钱或里亚尔。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">别管事实。对于可能成为共和党总统候选人的特朗普来说，“美国纳税人的钱为这些袭击提供了资金。”他后来感叹道：“我们被认为是软弱无能的，而我们的领导人也非常软弱。”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">也就是说，共和党人并没有给以色列提供太多帮助。他们的分歧，以及明年选举的临近，使国会比平时更加​​失能。参议院尚未确认拜登的驻以色列大使提名，也没有确认数百名高级军事任命。预算进程——包括对乌克兰和可能对以色列的新军事援助——处于停滞状态。 11 月政府再次关门迫在眉睫。在 10 月 11 日的一次集会上，特朗普本人称以色列国防部长是“混蛋”。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">出于真诚的信念，也为了化解共和党的攻击，拜登将拥抱以色列。 “像世界上每个国家一样，以色列有权——实际上也有义务——对这些恶意攻击做出回应，”他说。然后怎样呢？没有人能预测以色列报复后加沙或中东会是什么样子。鉴于哈马斯已经颠覆了拜登的大部分旧战略，拜登将需要针对该地区制定一项新战略。以色列与沙特关系正常化受挫。巴勒斯坦问题的“两国”解决方案几乎消失了。与伊朗建立不那么敌对的关系似乎是不可能的。总统将注意力从中东转向与俄罗斯、特别是中国的大国竞争的希望已经破灭。美国非常清楚，从9/11之后的阿富汗和伊拉克经历来看，如果没有可行的长期计划，对嗜血恐怖主义的过度反应可能会导致灾难。</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">不到两周前，在另一个时代，沙利文先生满意地宣称：“今天的中东地区比二十年来更加安静。”他认识到“一切都可能改变”，但吹嘘说，自 9/11 以来，他花在处理危机和冲突上的时间比任何前任都要少。现在他加入了他们的行列，试图以某种方式遏制中东的混乱和暴力政治。沙利文先生寻求“缓解中东地区压力、缓和局势并最终实现中东地区一体化”。但这一切都有逆转的风险：冲突、升级和混乱很容易再次开始相互助长。 <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:15:23 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /内容/qj8bss66cemnue1fg97t246smbc9ibms</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamas-has-failed-to-rally-the-middle-east-to-its-cause </item><item><title><![CDATA[The worst job in Washington is within Steve Scalise’s grasp]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>t is hard</small> to predict precisely when the vacancy for the worst job in Washington will be filled. Yet Steve Scalise, a congressman from Louisiana, appeared likely to replace Kevin McCarthy as speaker of America&#39;s House of Representatives at the time this issue went to press. It also remained unclear how much humiliation he might have to endure to secure the job, which will be a difficult one, whoever holds the speaker&#39;s gavel next.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> On October 11th Mr Scalise beat Jim Jordan, a Donald Trump-endorsed congressman from Ohio for the Republican nomination, 113-99. Mr Jordan then endorsed his rival, but enough spurned McCarthy allies and hard-right Republicans held out to prevent a speedy victory for Mr Scalise in the full House. His predecessor faced an embarrassing 15 rounds of voting, and no doubt Mr Scalise would like to avoid that. Should he become speaker, Mr Scalise certainly will have made concessions to various factions of his fractious party.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Scalise, aged 58, is a survivor—politically and physically. He has spent the past decade climbing the greasy pole of the House Republican leadership. In 2017 a left-wing activist shot and nearly killed Mr Scalise as he practised baseball with other Republicans. Now he is receiving chemotherapy for multiple myeloma, a blood cancer, though he returned to the Capitol last month and has been working.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Scalise remains generally well-liked in the Republican conference. He was the preferred choice of many moderates, and even Matt Gaetz, the Florida congressman who effected Mr McCarthy&#39;s defenestration on October 3rd, declared “long live speaker Scalise” after the intraparty vote. Perhaps Mr Scalise&#39;s greatest Republican foe was Mr McCarthy, who perceived a lack of support and loyalty when the former served underneath him as the second-ranked House Republican.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> If he has the job, the beef with Mr McCarthy will matter little compared with the legislative battles to come. Shortly after winning the Republican conference contest, Mr Scalise, wearing a <small>US</small> -Israel flag pin, said the first vote he would call as speaker would be a resolution expressing support for Israel. Passing that legislation, which already has more than 400 co-sponsors in the 435-seat House, is not the same as funding the government.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> “He&#39;s aware of the dynamics of legislating and the need for compromise. He is also a steadfast conservative,” says Matthew Green, a politics professor at the Catholic University of America. “I would expect him to be pushing hard for conservative legislative outcomes, but at the same time open to compromise if it avoids things like a government shutdown.”</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr McCarthy lost his job after he had cut a deal with Democrats to temporarily fund the government through November 17th. Mr Scalise will now have to find a way to pass a budget that covers more than a few weeks and is acceptable to the White House and Democrat-controlled Senate. Mr McCarthy had enough baggage for an early polar expedition, but even as a light packer Mr Scalise could find trouble pushing through fiscal legislation deemed insufficiently conservative.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Perhaps the legislative process will become a bit less rocky with a new speaker. But Dan Lipinski, a former eight-term Democratic congressman, says underlying House dysfunction is driven by an “identity crisis” among Republicans that hasn&#39;t gone away. Many want to legislate and pursue incremental conservative gains while others simply prefer nothing happen in Congress. Mr Lipinski also believes his own party, seeking political advantage from Republican chaos, has missed opportunities to change the tone on Capitol Hill.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> He noted that House Democrats joined forces with nihilist Republicans to oust Mr McCarthy after his dealmaking to avoid a shutdown. “They were punishing Kevin McCarthy for finally doing the right thing, for doing what they wanted him to do,” Mr Lipinski says. “I think that is bad for the institution.” If the next speaker works with Democrats to pass a responsible bill to fund the government and assist Ukraine, will they once again help dispose of the Republican leader? <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>Stay on top of American politics with <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/checks-and-balance">Checks and Balance</a> , our weekly subscriber-only newsletter, which examines the state of American democracy and the issues that matter to voters.</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:56:38 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/7q7s7gia8plshc0rq7i6e9jdcddj49fp</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/united-states/2023/10/12/the-worst-job-in-washington-is-within-steve-scalises-grasp </item><item><title><![CDATA[To beat populists, sensible policymakers must up their game]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>P</span> <small>oliticos, rejoice</small> . When it comes to elections, next year is a big one. In 2024 the Republicans and Democrats will battle it out in America, of course—but there will also be votes of one sort or another in Algeria, India, Mexico, Pakistan, Russia, South Africa, Taiwan, probably Britain, and many more countries besides. All told, as many as 3bn people, in countries producing around a third of global <small>gdp</small> , will have the chance to put an “X” in a box. And in many of these locations, populist politicians are polling well. What would their success mean for the global economy?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Economists have long suspected that populists do grave damage. Names such as Salvador Allende in Chile and Silvio Berlusconi in Italy are hardly synonymous with economic competence. By contrast, what you might call “sensible” leaders, including, say, Konrad Adenauer in Germany and Bill Clinton in America, are more often associated with strong growth. New research, forthcoming in the <i>American Economic Review</i> , perhaps the discipline&#39;s most prestigious journal, puts hard numbers on the hunch.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The authors, Manuel Funke and Christoph Trebesch of the Kiel Institute for the World Economy and Moritz Schularick of the University of Bonn, look at over a century of data. They classify administrations as “populist” or “non-populist” (or what you might call sensible), based on whether the administration&#39;s ideology has an “us-versus-them” flavour. This is inevitably an arbitrary exercise. People will disagree over whether this or that administration should really be classified as populist. Yet their methodology is transparent and backed up by other academic research.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Funke and colleagues then look at how various outcomes, including <small>gdp</small> growth and inflation, differ between the two types of regime. The trick is to identify the counterfactual—how a country under a populist government would have done under a more sensible regime. To do this, the authors create “doppelganger” administrations, using an algorithm to build an economy that tracks that country&#39;s performance pre-populist governance. During Berlusconi&#39;s tenure as prime minister for much of 2001 to 2011, for instance, the authors compare Italy&#39;s economy to a phantom Italy mostly comprised of Cyprus, Luxembourg and Peru. The three countries share characteristics with the world&#39;s eighth-largest economy, including a heavy reliance on international trade.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Having identified 51 populist presidents and prime ministers from 1900 to 2020, the authors find striking results. For two to three years there is little difference in the path of real <small>gdp</small> between countries under populist and sensible leadership. For a time, it may seem as though it is possible to demonise your opponents and run roughshod over property rights without all that much consequence. Yet a gap eventually appears, perhaps as foreign investors start to look elsewhere. Fifteen years after a populist government has entered office, the authors find that <small>gdp</small> per person is a painful 10% lower than in the sensible counterfactual. Ratios of public debt to <small>gdp</small> are also higher, as is inflation. Populism, the authors firmly establish, is bad for the pocketbook.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The results are comforting for those who believe in the importance of honourable politicians doing the right thing. But what if sensibles are not what they used to be? Although Mr Funke and his colleagues cannot judge the record of the most recent populist wave, some examples suggest the gap between sensibles and populists may not be as large as it was. Under President Donald Trump, the American economy largely beat expectations. Recep Tayyip Erdogan has stifled free speech in Turkey, but relative to comparable countries, real economic growth has been pretty strong. Under Narendra Modi, India&#39;s economy is roaring ahead: this year its <small>gdp</small> is likely to grow by 6% or so, compared with global growth of around 3%. Under populist leadership, Hungary and Poland are not obviously doing worse than their peers.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Given Mr Trump&#39;s tariffs and Mr Erdogan&#39;s unusual monetary policy, it is unlikely that these countries&#39; relative success is down to smart policymaking. Instead, their relatively strong performance may reflect the fact that countries with sensible leadership are finding growth harder to attain. In the 1960s Western countries, rebuilding from the second world war and with young populations, could hope to hit annual growth rates of 5% or more. The opportunity cost of poor economic management was therefore high. Today, in part because of older populations, potential growth is lower. As a result, the gap in <small>gdp</small> growth between a competent and an incompetent administration may be smaller.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Yet sensible politicians are also dropping the ball. In the past they promised voters higher incomes, said how they would deliver them and then implemented the necessary policies. These days, politicians across the <small>oecd</small> club of mostly rich countries pledge half as many pro-growth policies as they did in the 1990s, according to your columnist&#39;s analysis of data from the Manifesto Project, a research project. They also implement fewer: by the 2010s product- and labour-market reforms had practically ground to a halt. Meanwhile, politicians have put enormous blocks in the way of housing construction, helping raise costs and constraining productivity growth. Many focus their attention on pleasing elderly voters through generous pensions and funding for health care.</p><h2 class="css-8p8dhl e8f47sz0"> Shades of grey</h2><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Populists are themselves unlikely to solve any of these problems. But what are the sensibles offering as an alternative? Technocratic, moderate governments need to regain their growth advantage. After all, a belief that maverick politicians will damage the economy is one of the main things standing in the way of more people voting for them. If scepticism about the economic competence of sensible governments deepens, it may seem like less of a risk to vote for a headbanger. Although, over the long sweep of history, economists are right to mock the economic policies of populists, today the sensibles need to get their house in order, too. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><b>请阅读我们的经济学专栏《自由交换》了解更多内容：<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/article71753-prod.ece">To understand America&#39;s job market, look beyond unemployed workers</a> (Oct 5th)<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/article70920-prod.ece">为什么国家不应该提倡婚姻</a>（9月28日）<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/09/21/renewable-energy-has-hidden-costs">可再生能源具有隐性成本</a>（9 月 21 日）</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>如需对经济、金融和市场重大事件进行更多专家分析，请订阅我们的每周订阅时事通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/money-talks">Money Talks</a> 。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:47:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/dg634ses1riiph5dti8vijbqqa6c13on</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/10/12/to-beat-populists-sensible-policymakers-must-up-their-game </item><item><title><![CDATA[Investors should treat analysis of bond yields with caution]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>t was james</small> <small>carville</small> , an American political strategist, who said, in an oft-repeated turn of phrase, that if he was reincarnated he would like to return as the bond market, owing to its ability to intimidate everyone. Your columnist would be more specific: he would come back as the yield curve. If the bond market is a frightening force, the yield curve is the apex of the terror. Whichever way it shifts, it seems to cause disturbance.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> When the yield curve inverted last October, with yields on long-term bonds falling below those on short-term ones, analysts agonised about the signal being sent. After all, inverted curves are often followed by recessions. But now the curve seems to be disinverting rapidly. The widely watched 10-2 spread, which measures the difference between ten- and two-year bond yields, has narrowed markedly. In July two-year yields were as much as 1.1 percentage points above their ten-year equivalents, the biggest gap in 40 years. They have since drawn much closer together, with only 0.3 of a point between the two yields.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Since the inversion of the yield curve was taken as such a terrible omen, an investor would be forgiven for thinking that its disinversion would be a positive sign. In fact, a “bear steepener”, a period in which long-term bonds sell off more sharply than short-term bonds (as opposed to a “bull steepener”, in which short-term bonds rally more sharply than long ones), is taken to be another portent of doom in market zoology.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Driving the latest scare is the rising term premium, which is often described as the additional yield investors require to hold longer-dated securities, given the extra uncertainty over such extended periods. According to estimates by the New York branch of the Federal Reserve, the premium on ten-year bonds has risen by 1.2 percentage points from its lowest level this year, more than explaining the recent surge in long-term yields.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In truth, though, the term premium is a nebulous thing, and must be treated with caution. It cannot be measured directly. Instead, as with a surprising number of important economic phenomena, analysts have to tease it out by measuring more concrete parts of the financial system, and seeing what is left over. Estimating the premium for a ten-year bond requires forecasting predicted short-term interest rates for the next decade, and looking at how different they are from the ten-year yield. What remains—however large or small—is the term premium.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The difficulties do not stop there. John Cochrane of Stanford University&#39;s Hoover Institution points out that, although risk premiums might be more easily estimated at relatively short maturities, the calculations require more and more assumptions about the future of short-term interest rates as analysts move along the curve. When estimates of the term premium are published, they are not typically accompanied by a margin of error. If they were, the margins would get progressively wider the longer into the future the forecast was conducted.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> There is also surprisingly little history from which to draw when making assessments of changes in the yield curve or term premium. In the past 40 years, there have been perhaps eight meaningful periods of bear steepening, and only in three of them was the yield curve already inverted. The three instances—in 1990, 2000 and 2008—were followed by recessions, but with widely varying lags.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Movements in bond markets are therefore both easy and difficult to explain. They are easy to explain because any number of factors could be driving yields, including the Fed&#39;s quantitative-tightening programme, concerns about the sustainability of American debt and worries of institutional decay. Yet attributing bond yields to one factor in particular is fraught with difficulty. And without more clarity on the causes of a move, inferring the future from the shape of the yield curve becomes more like reading tea leaves than a scientific endeavour.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> One thing is certain, however. Whatever their cause, and regardless of their composition, rising long-term bond yields are terrible news for American companies that wish to borrow at long time horizons, and borrowers who take out new mortgages that will be linked to 30-year interest rates. The effect on the most sensitive borrowers will become only more painful if yields with long maturities remain at such high levels. For anyone concerned about whether a shifting yield curve or a rising term premium signals a looming recession or a nightmare for markets, these simple realities are a better place to start. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><b>阅读我们金融市场专栏作家 Buttonwood 的更多内容：<br></b> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/article71761-prod.ece">Why investors cannot escape China exposure</a> (Oct 5th)<br></i><i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/article70919-prod.ece">投资者对日本股市的热情过度</a>（9月28日）<br></i> <i><a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/09/21/how-to-avoid-a-common-investment-mistake">如何避免常见的投资错误</a>（9 月 21 日）</i></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>另：梧桐柱如何<a href="https://www.economist.com/column-names">得名</a></i></p></div>]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:45:58 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/g3m5hkm37f25hb1hnqo9asaqjiour1t5</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/10/12/investors-should-treat-analysis-of-bond-yields-with-caution </item><item><title><![CDATA[Retail investors have a surprising new favourite: Treasury bills]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>W</span> <small>hen treasury</small> bonds (or <small>t</small> -bills) last yielded as much as they do today—5.5%—punters were relieved that the world had not been destroyed by the millennium bug, Destiny&#39;s Child were atop the charts and the dotcom bubble was going strong. The recent surge in yields has been remarkable (see chart). </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC727.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">Yet bank depositors are seeing just a fraction of these increases. The average American savings account yields just 0.45%. Investors, too, are missing out. For the first time in over two decades, at the end of last year the return offered by six-month Treasuries overtook the earnings yield of <small>s</small> &amp; <small>p</small> 500 companies.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> So retail investors are looking elsewhere. Trading platforms have made short-term Treasury products a big part of their offering. Advertisements for Public, one such platform, ask podcast listeners if they are aware of the meagre savings rate on their deposit accounts. Despite only having been available on the platform since March, Treasuries are now its most purchased asset. One in ten new users buy them as their first trade.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Demand for Treasuries reflects a broader move towards safe, high-yielding options. Money-market funds invest in low-risk, short-duration instruments, including Treasuries. More than $880bn has been added to such funds this year, bringing their total value to an all-time high of $5.7trn. As with retail short-dated Treasury accounts, money-market funds are attractive to savers because they are highly liquid, meaning that cash can be withdrawn quickly if required.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The growing popularity of such alternatives is upsetting the logic of retail banking. Banks get away with providing interest rates well below the interest they receive from short-term government debt because—as Public&#39;s advertisements identify—many depositors pay little attention. By sucking deposits from the banking system, money-market funds are thought to have contributed to financial instability in the spring.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Retail-trading platforms&#39; expansion has made it easier than ever for depositors to transfer funds into short-dated government debt. That may further erode the discount on savings rates that depositors will accept from banks, and make Treasuries a bigger feature in retail-investment portfolios. Savers will, then, be singing along to one of Destiny&#39;s Child&#39;s better tunes: “Bills, Bills, Bills”. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>如需对经济、金融和市场重大事件进行更多专家分析，请订阅我们的每周订阅时事通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/money-talks">Money Talks</a> 。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:42:21 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/t6tmi38is650765uor4ugd868qevt8kr</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/10/12/retail-investors-have-a-surprising-new-favourite-treasury-bills </item><item><title><![CDATA[Corporate America faces a trillion-dollar debt reckoning]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>B</span> <small>ig American</small> companies are living in a debt dreamland. Although cheap borrowing has fuelled the growth of corporate profits for decades, the biggest firms have been largely insulated from the effects of the Federal Reserve&#39;s recent bout of monetary tightening. That is because many of them borrowed plentifully at low, fixed interest rates during the covid-19 pandemic. The tab must be settled eventually by refinancing debt at a much higher rate of interest. For now, though, the so-called maturity wall of debt falling due looks scalable. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC009.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">But not all companies are escaping the impact of the Fed&#39;s actions. Indeed, there is trillions of dollars of floating-rate debt, with interest payments that adjust along with the market, that has suddenly become much more expensive. This pile of debt consists of leveraged loans and borrowing from private debt markets. Companies seldom hedge interest-rate risks, meaning that they now find themselves paying through the nose—the yield-to-maturity of one index of leveraged loans has leapt to almost 10% (see chart 1). Meanwhile, since American economic growth remains resilient, the Fed&#39;s policymakers warn that interest rates will have to stay higher for longer. This will push more borrowers to breaking-point. A market that has grown vast is now asking two miserable questions. How bad will things get? And who, exactly, will lose out?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Since the global financial crisis of 2007-09, companies have borrowed fast and loose. <small>UBS</small> , a bank, estimates the value of outstanding American leveraged loans at around $1.4trn and the assets managed by private credit lenders at more than $1.5trn. The two types of debt are more alike than they are different. Both have grown to service the private-equity buy-out boom of the past decade. Traditional leveraged loans are arranged by banks before being sold (or “syndicated”) to dozens of investors, whereas private lending involves just a handful of funds, which usually hold smaller loans to maturity, creating a less liquid and more opaque market.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Increasing numbers of borrowers are now hitting the rocks. Since 2010 the average annual default rate in the leveraged-loan market has been less than 2%. According to Fitch, defaults rose to 3% in the 12 months to July, up from 1% a year earlier. The ratings agency reckons that they could shoot up to 4.5% in 2024. Restructurings and bankruptcies on this scale amount to spring cleaning rather than the deep distress felt during the financial crisis, when loan defaults exceeded 10%. But if rates stay higher for longer, as central bankers predict, the tally of troubled firms will grow. Although all companies with unhedged floating-rate debt balances are vulnerable, those loaded with debt in private-equity buy-outs at high valuations during the recent deal boom are especially at risk. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_FNC008.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">Slowing profit growth means that borrowers are finding it harder to afford their floating-rate debt. JPMorgan Chase, a bank, analysed 285 leveraged-loan borrowers at the end of June, before the Fed&#39;s most recent rate rise. Firms where borrowing consisted only of leveraged loans saw their annual interest expense soar by 51% year-on-year. Their fortunes are diverging sharply from those that instead tapped high-yield bond markets for fixed-rate funds. According to the study, the interest expenses of such businesses have increased by less than 3%. Coverage ratios, which compare a firm&#39;s profits with its interest costs, have begun an ominous decline (see chart 2).</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the private debt market, where default rates tend to be higher, borrowers are confronting similar woes. According to Bank of America, interest costs now consume half of profits at firms where loans are held by the largest business-development companies, a type of investment vehicle. A big rise in distress would not only make it harder to find institutions willing to plough money into private debt funds, with investors normally attracted by the promise of smooth returns, but also spill over to the leveraged-loan market.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Now that a reckoning looks imminent, attention is turning to which investors will be left holding the bag. Lenders today expect to recover less of their investment after a firm defaults than in earlier eras—and this year so-called recovery rates across junk-rated debt have been well below their long-run averages. According to Lotfi Karoui of Goldman Sachs, another bank, the rise of borrowers that rely solely on loans, rather than borrowing from bond markets too, could depress recoveries still further. This trend has concentrated the pain caused by rising interest rates. It is also likely to leave less value for leveraged-loan investors when they find themselves round a restructuring table or in a bankruptcy court, since there will be more claims secured against a firm&#39;s assets.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Other long-term trends could exacerbate the leveraged-loan market&#39;s problems. Maintenance covenants, commitments that lenders can use as a “stick” to force a restructuring, have all but disappeared as the market has matured. In 2021 nearly 90% of new loans were “covenant-lite”. This could mean that companies take longer to reach default, and are in worse health when they get there. Excessive “add backs”, flattering adjustments to a company&#39;s profitability measures, might also mean that leveraged borrowers are in worse shape than the market believes.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The performance of private markets is also being closely scrutinised. Advocates for private debt have long argued that they are better suited to periods of higher defaults, since the co-ordination costs between a small group of lenders are lower, making the correction of vexed balance-sheets easier. If private markets do indeed fare better than leveraged loans during the forthcoming turmoil, it would bolster their attempts to attract finance in future.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Problems in floating-rate debt markets are unlikely to cause a financial crisis, but the murkiness and growing size of private markets in particular mean that regulators have decided to take a closer look. In August America&#39;s Securities and Exchange Commission announced rules to increase transparency, including demanding quarterly financial statements. The following month, the International Organisation of Securities Commissions, a global regulatory body, warned about the risks of leverage and the opacity of private debt markets. Few investors, however, think they need help predicting a coming crunch. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"><i>如需对经济、金融和市场重大事件进行更多专家分析，请订阅我们的每周订阅时事通讯<a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/money-talks">Money Talks</a> 。</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:40:29 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/f722qrqku5juqo93o5ci6018o6qtpnos</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/10/12/corporate-america-faces-a-trillion-dollar-debt-reckoning </item><item><title><![CDATA[Will Israel’s agony and retribution end in chaos or stability?]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>na static</small> decades-long conflict that has rotted for the past 20 years, it can be hard to believe that real change is possible. Be in no doubt, however, that Hamas&#39;s murderous assault has blown up the status quo between Israel and the Palestinians. The coming weeks will determine whether war in Gaza sinks the Middle East deeper into chaos or whether, despite Hamas&#39;s atrocities, Israel can begin to create the foundations for regional stability—and, one day, peace.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Change is inevitable because of the <a href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2023/10/12/hamas-has-failed-to-rally-the-middle-east-to-its-cause">gravity of Hamas&#39;s crimes</a> . More than 1,200 Israelis, most of them civilians, many of those women and children, were murdered in their homes, on the street, in kibbutzim, at a music festival. Perhaps 150 more have been dragged to Gaza and shut in makeshift dungeons. Israel&#39;s belief that it could indefinitely manage Palestinian hostility with money and air strikes crumpled early on October 7th, as the first Hamas bulldozer breached the security fence. Hamas has chosen mass murder and there is no going back.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Gaza is now awaiting a huge Israeli ground offensive. Its extent and success will determine the legacy of Hamas&#39;s bloody assault. So will the fundamental choice that Israel&#39;s politicians face after the worst catastrophe in their country&#39;s history: do they unite or continue to exploit divisions for their own advantage? A third factor is the choices of Israel&#39;s Middle Eastern neighbours, including Iran.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> In the weeks and months ahead Israel&#39;s leaders carry a heavy responsibility to temper their understandable desire for fire and retribution with a hard-headed calculation about their country&#39;s long-term interests and an unwavering respect for the rules of war. They left their people vulnerable by failing to foresee Hamas&#39;s looming attack. They must not compound their error by failing to see ahead clearly for a second time.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The need for vision begins with the imminent ground offensive. The Israel Defence Forces will rightly strike deep and hard at Hamas. But how deep and how hard? Israel will be tempted to unleash a spasm of briefly satisfying violence. Its defence minister has called Hamas fighters “human animals”, and announced a blockade of food, water and energy. Israeli officials—and President Joe Biden—have taken to comparing Hamas to Islamic State, or <small>ISIS</small> , an Islamist group that America vowed to eradicate.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> That comparison is dangerous because, although Hamas deserves to be eradicated, achieving that goal in an enclave of 2m impoverished people with nowhere to flee will be impossible. A better comparison than <small>ISIS</small> is the 9/11 attacks in 2001, not just because of Israel&#39;s agony, but also because America&#39;s invasions of Afghanistan and Iraq show how steeply the costs of invasion mount—which is precisely Hamas&#39;s calculation.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> At such a moment, self-restraint matters more than ever. It is in Israel&#39;s interest, because street fighting is perilous and the hostages are defenceless. It makes the operation militarily sustainable and preserves international support. It avoids playing into the hands of foes who calculate that dead Palestinian women and children will further their cause. By clinging to its identity as a state that values human life, Israel becomes stronger.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Restraint in the ground offensive depends on the choices of Israel&#39;s politicians. Before the war they were tearing the country apart over a new law curbing the Supreme Court. For now grief and horror have brought people back together, but the left blames the far-right government of Binyamin Netanyahu, the prime minister, for poisoning relations with the army and security services over the court, and neglecting security in Gaza because of a fixation with helping Jewish settlers in the West Bank. The right counters that calls for civil disobedience by senior officials opposed to Mr Netanyahu were a green light for Hamas.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Mr Netanyahu must try to use his new war cabinet, announced this week, to unite Israel. Only by healing its own politics will the country be able to deal with Gaza. Mr Netanyahu will not want to help his most plausible rivals for office. Yet he was the man in charge when Hamas struck and his political career is ending. Having spent a lifetime seeking power at any price, he should finally put his country before himself.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A unified, centrist government would also be better placed to cope with the last set of challenges: the politics of the Middle East. Israel will be in grave peril if the war in Gaza spreads to its northern border with Lebanon, where tensions with Hizbullah, a formidably armed militia, are already growing ominously. The longer and bloodier the fighting in Gaza, the more Hizbullah will feel it must be seen to support its brethren. There is also a possibility of war with Iran, which has replaced Arab governments as the sponsor of Palestinian violence. Even Iran hawks in the West should not wish for that.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> A wider war would wreck the détente, built on the Abraham accords, between Israel and its Arab neighbours, including Bahrain, Morocco, the United Arab Emirates and potentially Saudi Arabia. This grouping stands for a new Middle East that is pragmatic and focused on economic development rather than ideology. It is still inchoate, but it has the potential to become a force for moderation—and possibly even security.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Simply by surviving, the Abraham accords could emerge from this crisis stronger. However, Hamas has shown that the signatories&#39; neglect of the Palestinians is a mistake. Israel and its Arab partners need a new, optimistic vision for Gaza and the West Bank, as an alternative to Iran&#39;s cult of violence and killing.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> And that leads back to the fighting in Gaza. How does it end? Israel has no good options: occupation is unsustainable, a Hamas government is unacceptable; rule by its rival, Fatah, is untenable; an Arab peacekeeping force is unattainable; and a puppet government is unimaginable. If Israel destroys Hamas in Gaza and pulls out, who knows what destructive forces will fill the vacuum left behind?</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Israeli strategists must therefore start thinking about how to create the conditions for life alongside the Palestinians, however remote that seems today. All those elements may have a part: a short period of martial law in Gaza, a search for Palestinian leaders acceptable to both sides, and the good offices of Arab intermediaries. The only way to eradicate Hamas is for Israel and its Arab allies to create stability—and, one day, peace. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <i>For subscribers only: to see how we design each week&#39;s cover, sign up to our weekly <a href="https://www.economist.com/newsletters/cover-story">Cover Story newsletter</a> .</i></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:34:25 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/e7l1nfpqpicsd2mc77e7ii58m8qca8cn</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/12/will-israels-agony-and-retribution-end-in-chaos-or-stability </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to deal with the global anti-climate backlash]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>T</span> <small>he shift</small> to electric cars is “a transition to hell” that will destroy “your beautiful way of life”, says Donald Trump. He is far from the only politician to oppose greenery. Rishi Sunak, Britain&#39;s prime minister, has kicked plans to phase out petrol cars years into the future, saying: “It cannot be right…to impose such significant costs on working people.” On October 8th voters in two big German states walloped the parties of the green-tinged ruling coalition. Even Sweden has cut fossil-fuel prices several times in the past year. A <a href="https://www.economist.com/international/2023/10/11/the-global-backlash-against-climate-policies-has-begun">backlash against climate-friendly policies</a> is under way in rich democracies.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It has many causes. Some voters deny that climate change is happening. Others accept that it is, but do not want to pay higher taxes or energy prices to tackle it. Many object to the hassle of installing new equipment. Some, especially the old, resist any kind of change. Others ask why they should make sacrifices when other countries, especially ones they dislike, are doing less.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Under this cauldron of grievances, populist politicians have heaped lighted coals. Many exaggerate the costs of going green, embellish the details (Britain&#39;s opposition had no plans for a meat tax, whatever Mr Sunak says) and seek to turn climate into a culture-war battleground: the metropolitan elite will grab your car and make you eat tofu! Such tactics have proved potent. Although awareness of climate change has increased, a political divide has opened. Voters on the left in Australia, Canada, Germany and Sweden are 23-44 percentage points more likely than those on the right to see it as a “major threat”; in America the gap is a stunning 63 points, according to Pew, a pollster. Such polarisation means bigger flip-flops when power changes hands: imagine France under the wind-farm-loathing Marine Le Pen. Everywhere, making climate policy less predictable makes it harder for investors to plan for the long term, as they must.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> What can be done? President Joe Biden&#39;s approach has been to throw hundreds of billions of dollars at everything from batteries to smart grids, and to call it a programme to create jobs and face down China. Even voters who do not care about greenery like jobs and fear China, goes the calculation, and a future Republican president would shrink from scrapping subsidies that are popular with recipients in red and blue states alike. All true, but this approach has big drawbacks.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> First, framing green energy as a matter of industrial policy and national security opens the door to protectionism, which raises the cost of green technology by shutting out some of the best suppliers. Second, a subsidy-based approach will be far more expensive than one that makes more use of carbon pricing, which encourages the reduction of emissions throughout the economy. The <small>IMF</small> estimates that in a typical rich country, trying to reach net zero using mostly subsidies would raise public debt by an unsustainable 45-50% of <small>GDP</small> by 2050. Using a well-designed mix of carbon taxes and other measures would raise debt by a more manageable 10-15% of <small>GDP</small> .</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The downside of carbon taxes is that voters don&#39;t like the sound of them, since they are, as the name implies, taxes. Governments have typically succeeded in putting a price on carbon only by stealth: using emissions-trading schemes that few voters understand. Carbon prices now cover almost a quarter of global emissions, but that is not nearly enough.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To curb carbon fast enough without generating too much resistance, climate policies should be designed to inflict as little hassle and cost on households as is practical. To reduce hassle, governments should remember that voters&#39; time is valuable and many green chores are dull. So, for example, instead of placing the burden on householders to install heat pumps, governments could place it on the utilities that hook up homes to the grid. Such firms could work their way across a country, installing a big heat pump in each road and connecting all the nearby houses to it—a process a bit like the roll-out of broadband over the past two decades.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To curb costs, governments should create predictable incentives to reduce emissions efficiently, meaning far more use of carbon pricing. Workers in industries that will eventually be shut down, such as coal, should be offered help, including training for new jobs. Judicious regulation can also play a role. If car firms are given a deadline to stop selling new petrol cars, they will strain to bring down the price and extend the range of electric vehicles. If deadlines are realistic, cleaner tech may already be cheaper than the dirty sort before it is compulsory.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Plenty of clean technologies are cheaper in the long run but have stiff upfront costs. Many voters in rich countries will need help with these. So will developing countries, where the high cost of capital still makes many green projects unaffordable. Globally, politicians who care about the climate should take the backlash seriously. That means being honest with voters about the inevitable disruption, and striving to minimise the pain. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:07:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/kmqav5jhmpfsfc8kk050jvn8hb5hdqh9</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/12/how-to-deal-with-the-global-anti-climate-backlash </item><item><title><![CDATA[Europe should not copy Bidenomics]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="css-1746s8a e1ey6m752"><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> <span>I</span> <small>t is not</small> hard to see why Europe feels the urge to copy President Joe Biden&#39;s economic policies. The loss of cheap Russian fossil fuels has made the clean-energy transition feel like a matter of national security. Germany, Europe&#39;s biggest economy, fears its automotive industry will lose market share to state-subsidised electric carmakers in China and America. And the euro zone&#39;s economy is increasingly falling behind America&#39;s. As we report, the worst-suffering European economies are grappling with inflation of over 10%, rapid ageing, high public and private debts and exposure to autocracies. This week the <small>IMF</small> said the euro-zone economy would grow by only 0.7% in 2023. It expects America to grow three times as fast.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Europeans increasingly see Biden-style industrial policy as the answer. The <small>EU</small> has loosened state-aid rules that restrict subsidised investment, and aims to set targets for the bloc&#39;s production of green goods. France and Germany are at loggerheads over how (not whether) to subsidise electricity for industrial users. <a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2023/10/11/britains-labour-party-embraces-supply-side-social-democracy">Britain&#39;s Labour Party</a> , which will probably form its next government in 2024, also aims to spend lavishly on industry. </p><div class="css-1bzwzkr eitqf4z1"><figure class="css-qts40t e1197rjj0"><img alt width="608" sizes="300px" srcset="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=16,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 16w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=32,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 32w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=48,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 48w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=64,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 64w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=96,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 96w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=128,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 128w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=256,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 256w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=360,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 360w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=384,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 384w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=480,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 480w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=600,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 600w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=834,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 834w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=960,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 960w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1096,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 1096w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1280,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 1280w, https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png 1424w" src="https://www.economist.com/cdn-cgi/image/width=1424,quality=80,format=auto/content-assets/images/20231014_LDC031.png"><figcaption class="css-18w36g1 edweubf2"><span class="css-6pzdis edweubf1">图片：经济学人</span></figcaption></figure></div><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0">Yet copying Bidenomics is a mistake. As in America, luring manufacturing with subsidies will waste money and, over time, encourage firms to compete for subsidies rather than customers. And though it is true that France, whose <i>dirigiste</i> economic philosophy is in the ascendant in Brussels, has had some successes with industrial policy, the web of institutions and norms that restrain the excesses of French interventionism are difficult to copy—just as Germany&#39;s economic model could not be transplanted elsewhere when it was held up as a paragon.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> Europe&#39;s recent experiences are in fact a case study of the power of markets. After Russia invaded Ukraine, German industry claimed that the loss of Russian gas would cause an economic catastrophe. Instead, industrial production held up as firms quickly adapted. Unlike America, the <small>EU</small> already has a uniform carbon-price mechanism in place. After a rocky start in the 2000s the emissions-trading scheme ( <small>ets</small> ) has in recent years <a href="https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2023/10/01/how-carbon-prices-are-taking-over-the-world">become the gold standard</a> for carbon pricing, incentivising the private sector to find the most efficient ways to cut emissions.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> The best policies for Europe would build on its past market-friendly approach. The <small>eu</small> should foster a common and contested green single market—including services and capital—which means restraining state aid. It should let the carbon price for new sectors increase faster than planned, and get serious about a climate dividend for citizens. And it should trade freely with allies so that the vast tasks of decarbonisation, de-risking sensitive supply chains and boosting defence can be undertaken at the lowest cost. The <small>EU</small> would be neither more secure nor richer if it had national champions producing 27 different types of tank.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> To boost growth, new government spending should focus on infrastructure, not handouts. Germany should fix a railway system that has rotted to the point of collapse. France should stop blocking interconnectors that could channel solar power from sunny Spain to the rest of Europe. And governments could write procurement rules that insist on greenery or security but which respect the single market and the principles of free trade.</p><p class="css-1hno3qs e190yofl0"> It might be tempting for Europeans to think that if America is protectionist, everyone else must follow suit or be left in the dust. Actually, America&#39;s long-running economic advantage over the rest of the world stems from the fact that it has been more committed to markets, not less. That makes its recent turn towards statism an aberration rather than an example to follow. <span class="ufinish">■</span></p></div> ]]>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:06:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> /content/2lmec9lc5j7mdr2onjeg2dqbqojfjpim</guid><link/> https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/10/12/europe-should-not-copy-bidenomics</item></channel></rss>