<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 7 日星期一 01:54:35 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>提出提升沟通技能的理由</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a>是硅谷通信公司<a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a>的首席执行官。她是六本书的作者，包括<cite>《DataStory：解释数据》和《通过故事激发行动》</cite> （Ideapress Publishing，2019 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[ROI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It’s hard to find a job posting that doesn’t mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Duarte-Upskilling-ROI-pie-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>公司表示，他们迫切需要能够有效沟通的员工——领导们在研讨会上一直告诉我这一点——但有多少人是真心实意的呢？很难找到一份<em>没有</em>提到沟通技能作为关键要求的招聘启事。然而，当面对候选人实际拥有的技能和他们薄弱的技能时，招聘经理发现自己在做出权衡，特别是为了满足紧迫的技术需求：<em>这个人可以像没有明天一样编码，但他的沟通很糟糕一个挑战。我们快点把他弄到这里来吧。我们会辅导他。它可以等待。</em></p><p>问题是，沟通技巧<em>不能</em>等待。人力资源、学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 等“人员职能”领域的高管明白，沟通和说服技巧在所有业务领域都至关重要，甚至在软件开发和会计领域也是如此。那些设计、管理、实施和跟踪员工发展计划的人已经知道善于影响组织中的同事和其他人所带来的商业利益。</p><p></p><p>那么，您如何向组织中的深刻怀疑者（例如，数据科学家们轻蔑地看待“说服”一词，将其视为<em>操纵的</em><em>委婉</em>说法）表明，在沟通技巧上进行认真投资是值得的？</p><p>您可以通过为投资回报提供可靠的理由来做到这一点。你可以从 L&amp;D 的那些人那里得到启发。他们对衡量培训计划投资回报率的方法以及传达这些人才的好处的最佳方式进行了长时间的思考。</p><h3>基于测量的案例，提高软技能</h3><p>在最近为我公司客户举办的一次活动中，我们的客户执行副总裁主持了一场小组讨论，讨论大型技术品牌建立软技能的方式以及投资回报率对他们的影响。两位 L&amp;D 高管分享了他们在组织中传达这种价值的发现：Catherine (Cat) Lang，负责为 ServiceNow 的客户和合作伙伴提供产品培训和认证，ServiceNow 是一家位于加利福尼亚州圣克拉拉的数字工作流程公司；诺埃尔·安德森 (Noelle Anderson)，Snap 的支持总监，Snap 是视觉消息应用 Snapchat 的母公司。以下是他们谈话中的五个关键见解。</p><h4>收集您在之前的培训中看到的投资回报率示例。</h4><p>一种开始方法是回顾组织中以前的学习工作，看看可以为利益相关者联系哪些点。例如，在您的组织取得重大胜利（例如获得利润丰厚的项目或赢得主要客户）之前，是否举办过有关呈现数据的内部研讨会？明确这种相关性并指出其他类似的相关性。您的某些软技能培训的投资回报率记录可能比您意识到的要多。</p><p></p><h4>帮助确定未来培训的价值。</h4><p>当您考虑或开发未来的培训时，请寻找更直接的方法来衡量技能提升的结果。例如，在 Snap，支持团队开发了一个推介辅导计划，销售人员、客户经理和创意策略师共同合作，为现有客户开发推介。参与者在制定、构建和练习自己的演讲时，会从经验丰富的沟通者那里获得大量指导和发展反馈——这是报名参加该计划的一大动力。他们还通过制作真实的推介内容来创造真实的、可衡量的价值。</p><p>回报——无论是续签合同还是销售新产品或服务——都是可以量化的。 “我们在后端所做的，”Anderson 说，“是与我们的 CRM 团队合作，在 Salesforce 中创建一个复选框，以表明每个演示是否是我们推介计划的一部分。”从那里，团队可以筛选出哪些推介带来了收入。</p><p>尽管 Snap 的 Anderson 团队向销售团队而不是公司 L&amp;D 汇报，但他们与 L&amp;D 作为“姐妹团队”合作，以确定和培养销售方面所需的软技能。这种方法可以在两个方向上带来红利：整个组织的团队可以向 L&amp;D 报告其领域的投资回报率证据，从而支持对全公司学习计划的进一步投资。就其本身而言，学习型组织可以就哪些类型的发展可以提高员工满意度和保留率分享更广泛的见解。 L&amp;D 可以根据团队认为哪些方面对日常绩效和销售影响最大来完善其技能建设计划。</p><h4>认识到质量影响——包括更好的员工保留率。</h4><p>即使有类似推介计划之类的东西，也很难用冷硬的美元来计算软技能培训的成本——尤其是当培训是由人力资源员工在内部进行或由经理和同事非正式地进行时。其好处也很难衡量，因为技能提升的大部分价值是间接的。</p><p>例如，考虑一下推介计划对员工的主要好处之一：提高高层领导的知名度。这对个人和组织都有回报，但不会立即体现在资产负债表上。安德森表示，批量的提案会分轮开发和呈现，到第三轮时，提案最好的两个小组可以向执行团队展示他们的想法，以获得更多反馈，然后再与客户分享任何内容。</p><p>当然，与高管的这些互动可以让推销本身变得更好。但想想其他好处：它们启动了指导关系，开辟了更多的发展和成长机会以及更多的晋升之门——所有这些都可以增强员工的体验、积极性和忠诚度。</p><p>你能量化这些结果吗？有时你做不到，所以你可以定性地衡量价值。这可能意味着就培训计划对员工行为、工作效率和团队合作方法的影响征求经理和团队领导的意见。从员工的角度考虑定性影响也很重要，因为人才保留对投资回报率具有重大影响。要证明这些无形资产为何重要，请考虑<a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/03/09/majority-of-workers-who-quit-a-job-in-2021-cite-low-pay-no-opportunities-for-advancement-feeling-disrespected/">皮尤研究中心 2022 年的一项调查</a>，该调查发现“没有晋升机会”和“工资太低”是美国工人离职的首要原因。或者考虑一下 LinkedIn 2022 年 3 月的《 <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220506202443/https://business.linkedin.com/glint/resources/employee-well-being-report-march-2022">员工幸福感报告</a>》的调查结果，该报告发现工作文化的第一大驱动力是“学习和成长的机会”。</p><p> Lang 表示，在 ServiceNow，她的团队正在“关注员工保留率和对发展的满意度”，并将这些“与我们的员工声音调查非常非常紧密地联系起来”，以全面了解技能提升对保留率的影响。她说，“当我们开始试行新的软技能项目时，她看到了快速的采用。”人们对 Snap 的此类技能提升也表现出了浓厚的兴趣：安德森表示，员工将其视为公司重视他们的证据，因为它“通过对个人及其发展进行投资，展示了对个人的信任”。她还指出，“这些技能可以帮助人们在内心获得自己的动力、自己的行动，并以人们真正会做出反应的方式提出自己的想法。”</p><h4>制定策略，确定首先关注哪些类型的工作。</h4><p>与任何组织变革工作一样，提高员工技能需要战略规划。为了帮助这样的计划获得关注，在更广泛地推广之前，确定您将在哪里看到最大的直接回报并计划集中在那里是很有用的。</p><p></p><p> Lang 在 ServiceNow 的团队首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员，因为他们对日常工作的完成方式有很大的发言权，并负责使员工的努力与组织目标保持一致。他们越早清晰地传达这些目标并制定令人信服的绩效目标，公司就能越早获得实现这些目标的回报。首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员也会产生级联效应，使他们能够通过一对一的辅导、指导对话，甚至是课程或其他学习内容的推荐，与团队分享他们所学到的知识。</p><p>安德森说，另一方面，Snap 更愿意首先提高一线经理的技能。因为她负责监督销售组织的学习，而员工的沟通技巧对客户关系有直接影响，所以她认为第一线是投资回报最快的地方。</p><h4>正面解决时间紧迫的问题。</h4><p></p><p>即使组织的利益相关者同意，在理想的情况下，他们应该优先帮助员工掌握软技能，但时间限制也会使其变得困难。在重要事项与紧急事项之间的长期斗争中，紧急事项往往会赢得领导者的关注和资源。安德森描述了她所谓的“此时此地”有时如何妨碍 Snap 实现更广泛的学习目标：“在很多课程中，人们都会说，‘我太兴奋了。我等不及要走了。他们出现了，但随后就不得不退出。”工作承诺和最后期限常常让人心烦意乱。</p><p></p><p>从文化上解决这一挑战的一种方法是公开承认它，并展示如何在学习计划和课程设计中适应它。创造这样一种期望：人们只在力所能及的范围内参与就可以了。考虑将内容分成更短的模块或小型研讨会，以便忙碌的员工更容易消化。在工作日留出时间用于技能发展。学习者在工作场所需要这种类型的支持，组织也会受益。如果高管犹豫不决，请提醒他们，让学习变得可行可以提高投资回报率<em>，并</em>在紧张的劳动力市场中增强员工对组织的承诺。</p><p>您可能需要稍微调整项目截止日期，或者在人们进行开发工作时减少他们的任务，这样他们就不会感到在下班后做“真正”工作的压力。开发<em>是</em>实实在在的工作。作为管理者，要以这种方式对待它，并与利益相关者进行讨论。如果您已采取措施帮助他们了解投资的所有好处，那么销售就会更容易。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>首席执行官可以促成（或破坏）组织重新设计</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz. <p><a href="https://akordeon.com/who-we-are/">Herman Vantrappen</a>是 Akordeon 的董事总经理，这是一家总部位于布鲁塞尔的战略咨询公司。 Frederic Wirtz 是 The Little Group 的负责人，为全球各地的公司提供有关组织设计问题的建议。 Vantrappen 和 Wirtz 是<cite>《组织设计指南：深思熟虑、高效和成功的重新设计的实用框架》</cite> （Routledge，2023）的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com The Research This article draws on the dozens of major organization redesign exercises the authors have accompanied in the past 30 years across continents in a wide range of sectors, including B2B (such as payroll services) and B2C (such as fast-food retail), products (such as automotive) and services (such as engineering), and for-profit [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Vantrappen-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>本文借鉴了作者在过去 30 年中在各大洲的广泛领域进行的数十次重大组织重新设计实践，包括 B2B（例如薪资服务）和 B2C（例如快餐零售）、产品（例如汽车）和服务业（例如工程），以及营利性和非营利性。</p></aside><p>首席执行官的基本职责之一是在认识到组织结构不再适合创造和交付价值后，领导重新配置组织的工作。有些重新设计是全公司范围内的重大改革，例如宝洁公司在 2019 年创建了六个基于行业的部门业务部门，其首席执行官将其描述为“过去 20 年来我们做出的最重大的组织变革”。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>其他重新设计工作的范围较小，侧重于特定的部门、功能或问题。</p><p>对于首席执行官来说，组织重新设计不同于其他大规模变革举措。例如，在公司战略调整中，首席执行官受董事会决策的约束，并遵循强有力的分析方法。在职能计划中，例如制定公司的数字战略，首席执行官可以将领导权委托给管理团队中的某人并承担监督角色。但在企业组织重新设计计划中，首席执行官必须积极带头，因为由此产生的变革将对文化和员工产生深远影响，也因为只有首席执行官拥有降低风险所需的全面视角。任何特定的重新设计选择都会产生严重的意外和不良后果。</p><p></p><p>多年来，我们在与组织的合作中见证了许多重新设计举措，并确认首席执行官对这些工作的领导是他们成功的关键。但令我们惊讶的是，有多少首席执行官仍在努力取得有效成果。我们发现，尽管管理文献中提供了大量且往往明智的建议，但计划经常会误入歧途或陷入死胡同。这里有些例子：</p><ul><li>商业服务提供商的新任首席执行官希望更广泛地重新考虑公司中心和组织的角色。管理团队的每个成员都有自己喜欢的重组想法：一个人受自组织团队的影响，另一个人坚持他们以前雇主使用的框架，第三个人认为公司应该只是一家小型企业的控股公司。区域性企业。即使是最小的对齐也需要很长时间。</li><li>多边机构的首席执行官发起了一项活动，以减少组织的孤立性。与管理团队的激烈辩论和几次异地会议导致了许多重大决策，包括共享资源和扩大首席执行官控制范围的计划。但经过一些幕后操纵后，决定被撤销了。</li><li>一家家族工程和建筑公司的创始人兼首席执行官退休，将权力移交给了他的一个孩子。新领导者计划使公司的业务流程和治理专业化，但退休的创始人却不断想方设法绕过首席执行官，破坏改善公司运作的任何努力。</li></ul><p>当我们回顾过去 30 年来所进行的重大组织重新设计（参见“研究”）并反思为什么某些举措不如其他举措有效时，我们认识到首席执行官可能会陷入以下两个陷阱之一：使用适当的框架，而且很简单，未能在整个过程中保持足够的领导力。在本文中，我们将提出首席执行官可以遵循的组织重新设计的系统方法，并解决高管如果要在整个组织重新设计和实施过程中保留完全所有权就必须防止的特定行为。</p><h3>应对组织重新设计的框架</h3><p>许多学者和顾问开发了支持组织设计系统思考的框架。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>我们在此介绍的框架强调了两个经常被忽视的方面。</p><p>首先，该框架认识到管理者在重新设计组织时永远不会从零开始。总有一个现有的组织可以为任何重新设计提供重要信息。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>即使现有设计已变得功能失调，最初采用它通常也有充分的理由，并且这些理由不应被忽视。因此，一个好的框架需要包含过去和未来之间的动态联系。</p><p>其次，管理文献中当前的大部分建议都集中在计划的上游方面（例如，确定公司的目的、价值观和愿景）或下游方面（例如执行和变革管理）。关于该学科的中游核心——即结构、流程和系统等硬性内容——的讨论较少。一个好的框架应该恢复这个重要的中游部分，同时将其与上游部分（通过考虑变革的驱动因素）和下游部分（通过确保第一天上线做好准备）无缝集成。</p><p>我们通过工作逐步开发的框架旨在通过尊重变革的动态本质并关注硬组织设计变量来克服这两个缺点。从第一条原则出发，它将组织设计思维的各个组成部分整合成一个逻辑流程，从理解组织<em>变革的驱动因素</em>到<em>概念设计</em>的选项、<em>详细设计的</em>可操作性、<em>过渡</em>阶段的实施以及重组的实际<em>执行</em>过程中必要的路线修正。 （参见“组织重新设计指南”。） </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>组织重新设计指南</h4><p class="caption">该框架将熟悉的构建块集成到逻辑流程中，以指导重组计划。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig1.jpg" alt="组织重新设计指南"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>处于组织重新设计前端的首席执行官需要了解此框架中突出的五个总体原则：</p><p> <strong>1. 组织是达到目的的手段。</strong>管理者改变组织设计，期望新的设计能够更好地帮助公司实现其业务目标。该期望基于以下假设：这些目标将明确、得到管理团队的接受、利益相关者的认可，并保持相当稳定。一家目标模糊或波动的公司很可能会经历破坏性的组织重组，而其业绩却没有太大改善。这就是为什么我们的设计框架首先要确定变革的外部和内部驱动因素。</p><p> <strong>2. 最好的设计是不可知的。</strong>可以说，做出组织设计选择比做出业务战略选择更困难。战略选择归结为从各种替代方案中选择一种能够最大化既定目标（例如 EBITDA 增长）的方案。通过战略，领导者权衡可用信息、假设和不确定性、资源限制以及他们自己的风险偏好。组织选择则不然。它们不是来自数学优化，而是来自对支持和反对多种设计方案中每一种的论据权重的判断。这就是为什么设计框架鼓励首席执行官考虑替代组织概念。</p><p> <strong>3.概念设计先于详细设计——只有后者才是参与性的。</strong>在概念阶段，定义了新设计的原则。这些涉及基本的组织变量，特别是架构（例如，集中什么和分散什么）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>在考虑替代设计概念后，选择一个并进行详细设计（例如，端到端业务流程中各种功能的角色）。详细设计可以而且应该在管理者和直接相关人员的广泛参与下完成：他们最了解什么是有效的，必须在设计结果范围内运作，并且可以充当变革大使。然而，很少建议在概念设计中采用这种参与式方法，因为概念设计往往需要熟悉公司的（通常仍然是机密的）愿景和战略选择，避免与公司各种职能的命运和速度有关的利益冲突。</p><p> <strong>4. 组织设计通过故意跳跃和紧急跳跃的模式演变。</strong>深思熟虑的战略和紧急战略的概念在战略制定的学科中根深蒂固：在公司深思熟虑的战略的指导下，组织中各级经理每天都会做出无数的决策，逐渐改变该战略的具体形式。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>在组织设计中也观察到类似的模式：高级管理层有意决定对组织进行重大重新安排（飞跃），之后进行一系列调整（跳跃）以弥补原始设计中不可避免的缺陷。这种跳跃式的模式是完全正常的，甚至是可取的，因为完美的设计是难以捉摸的，而且公司的环境一直在变化。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>这就是为什么设计框架会显示循环，将缺陷反馈回设计中，以便解决这些问题。</p><p> <strong>5. 设计的证明仅在第一天后才会公布。</strong>第一天是指批准的详细设计投入使用的那一刻，重新设计开始对大量人员的日常运作产生直接影响：他们做什么、如何做以及与谁一起做。为了管理信誉、尊重员工以及对业务的影响，错误应该尽可能少。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>因此，在第一天之前就开始仔细的变革管理流程至关重要。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>任何员工都不应该对自己在重新设计的组织中的地位一无所知。</p><p></p><h3>为什么首席执行官的持续参与很重要</h3><p>在战略制定过程中，首席执行官通过一段时间内的临时干预措施来保持参与可能是完全足够的，例如参加异地高管会议、领导指导委员会或向董事会汇报。另一方面，在组织设计练习中，我们发现最高效的首席执行官几乎每天从开始到结束都密切关注流程的脉搏。</p><p>他们这样做的原因之一是，这为他们提供了形成自己关于适合目的的设计的想法的机会，并可能从根本上改变他们的思维模式。他们花时间让自己的想法成熟，因为没有单一的最佳设计，最终的选择很大程度上是对许多有效替代方案的定性判断。</p><p>他们还始终如一地参与，因为他们意识到组织设计过程是相当无情的。每个阶段都建立在前一阶段做出的选择的基础上，逐渐涉及越来越多的人。在此过程中做出的明确或隐含的微观承诺的数量——关于角色、边界、界限、人员、人数和其他因素——不断增加。不得不回头是痛苦的，部分原因是它是广泛可见的。如果说战略制定就像种树，那么组织设计就像种草：其效果立竿见影、遍及各处，需要引起重视。</p><p></p><p>日常参与的第三个原因是帮助组织内部建立对新设计的认可。高效的首席执行官坚持充分参与有关设计活动结果的沟通，与其说是通过众所周知的“致全体员工的备忘录”，不如说是通过与现场人员交谈。只有全身心投入到实际的设计工作中，他们才能做到可信和令人信服。</p><p>最重要的是，首席执行官每天都会参与这个过程，因为他们认识到人员和互动最终将成就（或破坏）组织。充分参与设计过程为首席执行官提供了独特的机会，可以观察和影响直接报告之外的企业人员方面。</p><h3>领导力弱点如何破坏重新设计</h3><p>在我们观察到的领导者无法完全控制上述重新设计过程的情况下，他们的弱点往往反映出以下四个特征之一：三心二意、绥靖、优柔寡断或无能。我们根据对组织重新设计工作的观察，提炼出以下四种原型：</p><p><strong>半心半意的首席执行官。</strong>虽然战略制定活动的触发点往往很明确，但组织设计活动可能是由某些利益相关者的游说而不是明确的业务需求推动的。在某些情况下，管理团队或董事会成员可能会提出疑虑。首席执行官可能最初并不认为这种担忧很重要，或者倾向于发起变革，但他们可能希望让利益相关者满意，结束辩论，从而同意考虑组织重新设计——私下里认为这些计划不会有任何进展。或者，首席执行官可能对重新设计的动机感到困惑、不清楚或守口如瓶，让项目团队来填补空白。在其他情况下，首席执行官可能会自愿或非自愿地离职。在所有这些情况下，首席执行官在项目开始时都缺乏充分的承诺，导致项目开局不利。</p><p><strong>绥靖的首席执行官。</strong>每一次转型都需要仔细的变革管理，通过深思熟虑的活动将公司从目前的状态转变为期望的未来状态，并帮助人们采用变革。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>然而，首席执行官在邀请人们参与时可能会太过分，这可能会导致流程过于复杂，步骤、参与者和审批点过多。例如，邀请更多评论而不是做出决定并冻结流程可能会拖延设计阶段。旨在表现出倾听意愿的安抚行为通常是出于好意，旨在发挥利益相关者管理的作用，但它也可以反映出首席执行官自己对设计概念的不确定性。</p><p><strong>优柔寡断的首席执行官。</strong>决策无能、无法做出决策或坚持坚定决策的首席执行官虽然很少见，但并未绝迹。一个典型的症状是，首席执行官在后期“在我的尸体上”威胁屈服，而经理不同意经过深思熟虑的执行团队决策。由于担心产生负面影响，首席执行官有时会在最后阶段做出妥协。在这样的组织中，不管首席执行官如何，事情都会发生。</p><p><strong>丧失行为能力的首席执行官。</strong>有缺陷的治理可能会让首席执行官很难在整个过程中掌控重新设计。在首席执行官不兼任董事会主席的公司中，董事会可能会干扰首席执行官对组织重新设计的处理。在私营公司中，退休创始人等有权势的董事会成员可能会干预设计并让首席执行官短路，保护旧的最爱或以其他方式扰乱有序的流程。这种对首席执行官的损害——无论是在概念设计、详细设计还是过渡阶段——通常在较低层次上是可见的，并且具有很高的破坏性。</p><p>计划重新设计组织的首席执行官最好考虑这些领导力薄弱的模式。他们应该根据自己的特质和阻碍其领导力的背景因素来评估自己的脆弱性，然后考虑如何克服这些脆弱性。</p><p>他们可以首先问自己四个问题：</p><ol><li>我完全相信这个倡议吗？</li><li>我会听取正确的人的意见而不让流程偏离正轨吗？</li><li>我是否准备好在需要时做出艰难的决定并坚持下去？</li><li>我能控制我需要拉动的所有杠杆吗？</li></ol><p>这种反省很重要，因为一旦首席执行官了解他们在这一关键变革工作中的领导力可能薄弱的地方，他们就可以努力减轻这些弱点。 （参见“首席执行官如何减少他们的脆弱性。”）想象一下，一位知道自己倾向于安抚的首席执行官。他们可能认识到，在概念阶段，他们应该咨询有限的高级管理人员，在过渡阶段，他们应该采用一种“遵守或解释”流程（当任何偏离概念设计的情况都必须得到解释和解释）只有在获得批准该概念的治理机构批准后才能接受）并冻结设计，向员工保证公司将在启动后根据需要进行路线修正。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性</h4><p class="caption">倾向于四种可能破坏组织重新设计的行为原型中的任何一种的首席执行官可以在流程的每个阶段采取行动来加强他们的领导力。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig2.png" alt="首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>我们与一家工业公司的首席执行官合作，他承认自己有一些无能力和优柔寡断的典型特征。他能够通过一些聪明的、具体的方式来弥补可能导致进程脱轨的倾向：</p><ul><li>由于首席执行官几乎经常出差，他任命了一位具有互补技能的首席变革官，与他密切合作，负责总部的日常项目事务。然而，首席执行官仍然负责这项工作。</li><li>首席执行官提议让公司的提名和薪酬委员会在概念设计阶段充当指导委员会。这为董事会主席提供了一个受管理的渠道，董事会主席对运营事务的频繁干预有时会损害首席执行官的利益。</li><li>在概念设计阶段的结果得到提名和薪酬委员会正式认可并得到董事会批准后，首席执行官能够在详细设计阶段更轻松地实施“遵守或解释”规则。为了避免概念蔓延，任何偏离概念的行为都必须再次通过委员会。</li><li>首席执行官鼓励公司各部门和职能部门各自任命一名过渡阶段大使。这些代表属于各自部门和职能的管理团队，并参与了详细设计阶段。他们每月与首席变革官会面，分享双向进展信息。</li><li>在上线之前，使用一个简单的跟踪器来监控一系列特定过渡目标的进展情况。完成百分比统计数据由首席执行官定期审核，并根据部门和职能公开发布。这产生了一些健康的同行压力，并帮助该过程保持吸引力。</li></ul><p></p><p>这个例子表明，首席执行官对他们明显的行为倾向以及可以防止重新设计工作脱轨的行动进行一些预先、明确和诚实的反思是值得的。</p><p></p><p>持续的组织重新设计是企业生活的一个事实。在大多数情况下，考虑重新设计有充分的商业理由，尽管它往往会消耗大量的额外时间、资源和情感能量。 But the CEO&#39;s full-on engagement is needed to make the redesign succeed. Even then, however, redesign exercises often go astray. CEOs may lack an appropriate design framework or simply fail to maintain sufficient leadership throughout the process. They should start with an assessment of their vulnerabilities — both their own behavioral tendencies and governance-related constraints. And they should find ways to demonstrate that they are full-hearted, conclusive, decisive, and, ultimately, in control.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Learning From and With AI: Duolingo&#39;s Zan Gilani</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Cognitive Technologies]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gamification]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Zan Gilani came to the U.S. from Pakistan to complete his undergraduate studies, he chose to study Chinese because it was rumored to be a difficult language. At the time, the tech industry was booming, and he quickly became interested in applying his passion for foreign languages and learning more generally in a technology-rich [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> When Zan Gilani came to the US from Pakistan to complete his undergraduate studies, he chose to study Chinese because it was rumored to be a difficult language. At the time, the tech industry was booming, and he quickly became interested in applying his passion for foreign languages and learning more generally in a technology-rich environment.</p><p> Those interests led Zan to Duolingo, where he has been working in product management for eight years and now oversees the app company&#39;s experiential AI team. What excites him about working at the language-learning app company is his ability to help build solutions that enable personalized education at scale: The app boasts over 16 million daily active users, and AI-driven functionality motivates them through frequent notifications, personalizes learning experiences by adjusting the difficulty of questions in practice sessions, and observes and critiques learners&#39; performance.</p><p> Zan joins the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast to outline the specific ways Duolingo uses AI and machine learning to drive user engagement, and discuss how the technology can be used to support learning more generally. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E5-Gilani-Duolingo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Zan Gilani"></p><h4> Zan Gilani, Duolingo</h4><p> Zan Gilani is a principal product manager at Duolingo. For the past eight years, he has helped grow the company&#39;s learner base from 3 million to 16 million daily active users by working on retention, acquisition, growth in Asia, gamification, and the new-user experience.</p><p> He currently leads Duolingo&#39;s Experimental AI team, which uses generative AI to build features that teach learners more effectively. More broadly, Gilani is working on setting Duolingo up for success using generative AI, through external partnerships and internal education.</p><p> Gilani grew up in Karachi, Pakistan, and is currently based in New York City. He has bachelor&#39;s degrees in political science and East Asian studies from Columbia University.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-gilani"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Learning a new language is a complex process. One app company looks to AI to help with personalization, context, and motivation. Learn more on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> I&#39;m Zan Gilani from Duolingo, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome. Today, Shervin and I talk with Zan Gilani, principal product manager at Duolingo. I&#39;m personally pretty excited about today&#39;s episode because Duolingo is in a really interesting position. In a lot of our show, we end up talking about how organizations are using AI to augment or to improve human decision-making, and that&#39;s great. But Duolingo goes further and focuses on how humans are learning with AI — personalized education at scale, which is something that appeals to me. Anyway, that&#39;s enough from me. Let&#39;s hear it from Zan. Zan, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Thank you. It&#39;s a pleasure to be here.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Zan, first, can you give us an overview of Duolingo and the company, and what your role is?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Absolutely. Duolingo is basically an app that teaches languages. We teach 40-plus languages right now. Most of those people, by the way, are learning English, and most of our learners are also learning on mobile phones, so Android and iOS devices. And we are the most-downloaded and the most-used educational app there is, languages and otherwise. We have around 16 million DAU, or daily active users, and 40-plus million monthly active users as well. And I&#39;ve been at the company just coming around to eight years, where I am a principal product manager for the Experimental AI team.</p><p> My primary role is leading this team that is working to teach more effectively using generative AI, and also, more broadly, I help set the company up for success when it comes to generative AI.</p><p> One of the main use cases we have now specifically for generative AI is a new subscription tier. Duolingo is a freemium product. The mission is to provide the highest-quality education possible [and] make it accessible to as many people [as possible]; all you need is an internet connection. So we have this free version of the app, which is what most people are on. That&#39;s really good; most people at the company spend time on that. And then we have subscription tiers.</p><p> And we recently just launched a new AI-powered subscription tier called Duolingo Max, and I&#39;m happy to go into the features [of that] as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So Experimental AI … it&#39;s sort of like your R&amp;D lab, if you will?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Well, I&#39;d say actually more than half of the company is working on R&amp;D broadly — kind of all of the people who work on product, and [among] the folks who work on learning or teaching effectively, you could think of it as a lab, yes.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Great. Maybe, for our audience, you could list the variety of use cases or places that AI is being used. I mean, of course, [aside] from the obvious one — personalization and gamification — that a lot of the apps have. But just tell us how AI is being used.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Duolingo has been using AI for as long as the app has been around, which is coming up to a decade. In fact, it was founded by a computer science professor, Luis von Ahn at Carnegie Mellon University, and his graduate student at the time, Severin Hacker. Right now, it&#39;s used in a number of different ways. On the growth side, for example, a lot of work goes into optimizing notifications.</p><p> The thing about Duolingo that makes it different from other apps is that it really tries to help you stay motivated. For us, pedagogically, we think that the hardest thing about learning a language is actually staying motivated, because remember: This is something tough to do. It&#39;s especially tough to do by yourself, on a phone — that&#39;s really a tough thing. So notifications and the timing of when you get them, the messaging that it has, really does affect someone&#39;s ability to stick with it in the long term. So we put a lot of effort into machine learning for notifications.</p><p> We also use it on the content-generation side, so we are trying to create useful, appropriate content; we use it there as well. And then, in a separate arm of the company, which is the Duolingo English Test, which is basically an English proficiency test that students have to take when going to university — kind of a competitor to the TOEFL or TOEIC or IELTS; most Americans haven&#39;t had to experience this — we use it for detecting cheating. We use it for generating content in a bunch of different places as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s fascinating. And on the actual core of the app, which is teaching you language, how dynamic is that? How personalized is it when it adjusts to a person&#39;s way of learning?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Personalization plays a role, but a lot of the experience is curated by learning scientists, by educational content developers. For most people, the order in which you want to learn things is going to be roughly similar. For example, everyone learns the present tense before you then go on into other complicated tenses. But where we do use AI for personalization specifically is for something called Birdbrain, and this is basically a system we have that is optimizing for the difficulty of questions that you are going to see in practice sessions.</p><p> And one thing to note over here about Duolingo is that it&#39;s completely interactive. It&#39;s meant to feel like a game. So every time you&#39;re learning, you&#39;re kind of answering a mini exercise, and then you get it right or wrong. You always get feedback. So the point of Birdbrain is to try to come up with a Goldilocks level of difficulty, because basically, if something is too hard, it&#39;s frustrating and you lose motivation. If something&#39;s too easy, it&#39;s boring and you lose motivation. Birdbrain is one of those things that we use for personalizing practice in particular.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Shervin, one thing I think that&#39;s funny about that is that, in describing his product, we just took for granted the speech synthesis, speech recognition. These were avant-garde things 10 years ago, and now, Zan, you didn&#39;t even bother to mention those as applications of AI. I think that&#39;s sort of stepping back [and] seeing what now is normal.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s right. And I think one thing you have that&#39;s quite interesting and maybe unique is just the number of feedback loops you must have. I mean, usually, in a lot of other applications, when you think about corporations and retail and banks and telecom, etc., it takes some time to get feedback. And you&#39;re almost getting instantaneous feedback on so many experiments or mini experiments from so many people. Maybe tell us a little bit more about just the speed of learning and the speed of adaptation of your algorithms.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> There&#39;s a nice bit of mirroring over here, which is that there are principles for learning effectively that we try to impart into the product itself. And then, as a company and as an organization, we are trying to operate on those principles as well. Getting fast feedback really matters when you&#39;re learning a language. But it also matters when you are working on the product itself, and, from a very early time, we basically built out our own A/B testing infrastructure, and it&#39;s pretty core to the product process; that&#39;s the central component of how we do product at Duolingo.</p><p> At any given moment in time, you have hundreds of experiments being run on things that are very granular — the positioning of buttons [indicating] the pricing on the page for the price of our subscriptions, your classic bread-and-butter experiments — to also huge new features, new tabs. Basically, if it&#39;s not a bug, it&#39;s probably the case that we&#39;re running this in the form of an experiment. We&#39;ve gotten very, very good and very, very sophisticated at doing this.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Shervin&#39;s going to roll his eyes because I&#39;m going to go academic for a minute, but you&#39;re a classic case of experiential learning. And actually, I&#39;m going to give you a little bit of segue to talk about your <a href="https://blog.duolingo.com/duolingo-max/">Max product</a> here, because I think there are two pretty exciting parts of that. There&#39;s Roleplay, which is getting to the academic, concrete experience part of experiential learning, and then this Explain My Answer, which is a reflective observation and critique. So tell us a little bit about both of those and how those are tied to learning outcomes.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Definitely. I think it&#39;s useful to talk about where we were before adding those two features. Pedagogically, Duolingo has always been about implicit learning, so learning without telling you explicitly, “This is what you&#39;re going to learn, and this is how it works.” And that is the DNA of the experience, because we think it&#39;s just more automatic when you do it that way. People also get really demotivated and put off by complicated grammar tables, etc. And then, the second is that you&#39;re learning on an app, and you&#39;re doing this interactive thing — these almost gamelike exercises.</p><p> The two things that have been missing or limited is that, one, some people do actually want explanations, and that can be really efficient and effective when done in the right amount and in the right way. So Explain My Answer is a solution to that problem, and the nice thing about Explain My Answer that really only works thanks to modern large language models is that the large language models are really good at providing jargon-free, concise explanations of the mistakes you make. It&#39;s really tough, even for teachers, to try to do that without using jargon and also without being right on the money. And so we are able to do that with Explain My Answer pretty well. It can give you follow-up illustrations, it can give you examples — all of these things that make large language models, by the way, just good for anyone trying to learn anything by themselves. For me, it&#39;s life-changing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Or anyone trying to give a speech.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Or anyone trying to give a speech, yes. And then the second one, Roleplay, is that, ultimately, for most people, language learning is not an academic exercise. They&#39;re trying to use it as a skill in the real world, and that&#39;s a skill in and of itself. So how do you give people the ability to practice that? How do you get them to simulate this? Chatbots are exactly one way to do so, because now, what you have is something that can speak to you at the level of difficulty that you&#39;re at, has infinite patience, and can then actually give you feedback afterward as well.</p><p> Even if people had access to native speakers, which they don&#39;t generally, you&#39;d still need a native speaker who has infinite patience and who really, really can understand what you&#39;re looking for. So Roleplay is basically trying to provide that experience in the app, rather than just having a text interface like ChatGPT and just having you speak back and forth. Basically, what we&#39;ve done is we&#39;ve broken down conversations or scenarios into these bite-size experiences, where you&#39;re talking to a chatbot who&#39;s going to be a barista or a friend that you&#39;re borrowing something from, and then you try to go through a very specific, short experience.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Sam, I have a question for you because, Sam, as you know, is a distinguished professor, and he&#39;s been teaching people — including people that are not in his class, like me — a lot of things. So my question, Sam, is … in all seriousness, though, what makes a good teacher, in your opinion?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Actually, Zan hit on a couple things right there, and that&#39;s part of why I was feeling somewhat convicted in his conversation. This infinite patience that he talks about — that&#39;s really important, and it&#39;s also really hard.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Impractical.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah. And meeting people where they are is a fundamental problem that we have in education. I mean, I sit in front of a room with 35, 40 people, and they are not homogeneous. And meeting people where they are is exactly what Zan was talking about. So, yeah, you have to know the material well, you have to keep people engaged, but you also have to keep track of where people are and what they know — present stuff that&#39;s not too easy and not too hard — and I&#39;m very attracted to this model.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So, what&#39;s next?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, yeah, that&#39;s exactly where I was going.下一步是什么？ I mean, if we can do this with language, what else can we do this with? Where does it work?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I meant just for language. So meeting people where they are, having very good knowledge of the student and their progress, and then being able to do role-playing and lots of experiential learning, and being able to explain and guide in a more jargon-free way and in a way that you could repeat it and I don&#39;t have to rush to take notes. I mean, all of these things, right?缺什么？ I&#39;m hearing this and this is better than a regular teacher, it sounds like. But in your view, what is missing for this to be a perfect teacher — in Zan&#39;s view?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> I think we are still a very, very, very long way away from being the perfect teacher, for a number of reasons. I&#39;d also say, we don&#39;t believe, and I certainly don&#39;t believe, that at the end of the day, all you need is a chat interface and most people will be able to get really far with whatever they&#39;re trying to learn. So, to answer the first part about why we&#39;re far away from a teacher, well, some of this, I think, is unknown, but there is a real impact to developing a relationship with another human being when you&#39;re learning.</p><p> There is an emotional part of learning something new, and there is a human connection that can be as simple as the fact that you show up for your tutoring appointments because you don&#39;t want to let your teacher down, to also the fact that that tutor can be really engaging with their facial expressions, with the cadence of their voice, with the illustrations that they can tell, the way they can relate to maybe their own lives.</p><p> So that, we&#39;re still very far away from. And then, when it comes to just “Hey, why can&#39;t a chatbot teach you everything?” for most people, you still have to be organized, and being organized is quite exhausting. For example, just deciding what to eat next is often what you spend all your time doing, or deciding what movie to watch. And, similarly, deciding what to learn next is tough. So someone on the product side has to figure out the right sequencing of things for you to learn.</p><p> Similarly, being creative is exhausting as well. For a real-life tutor, it would be really difficult for them to put on a lot of different personas and do a lot of role-playing. Then you&#39;d need a tutor who is also an amazing actor. And AI gives you the ability to do that with a virtual teacher, but even then, we don&#39;t want a learner to have to come up with these scenarios all the time themselves.</p><p> The last two things I&#39;ll mention is that learning is also multisensory. It&#39;s also contextual. What you&#39;d want, ideally, is some kind of learning and context happening as well instead of just with a chatbot.</p><p> And the last thing to mention is, people really do need a sense of progression in order to stay bought into learning a language, because actual progress is so slow and so incremental, it&#39;s really hard to see. And so what you have to do is, you have to show people progress bars that are filling up, and you have to check in. I think there are probably ways that you could simulate that in a tutor experience, but those are some of the reasons why I think we care about building the experience outside of that as well and building a path that you go along, and all of these other things that go into making Duolingo what it is.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Zan, I want to come back to one thing you were talking about that I&#39;m pretty attracted to, [which] is this idea of figuring out what&#39;s the next thing that you need to learn. I mean, historically, every class that I had in languages, we had a book and we moved from Chapter 1 to Chapter 2. And somebody, somewhere, really thought through the sequence of that.</p><p> But at the same time, I don&#39;t know that that&#39;s necessarily optimal for all students. And we think about recommendation systems and Netflix, or in music; you know, we&#39;ve talked to Spotify, Shervin. This seems like a great opportunity here. What&#39;s the one thing that I could learn right now that would make the most difference? Or what&#39;s the one thing that I don&#39;t know that&#39;s keeping me from opening up this next section? That seems like a huge opportunity.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Yeah. And I would break that into two pieces as well. One of them is just, generally, what&#39;s an effective order to learn in, and what&#39;s an effective order to teach in? And it&#39;s especially useful for people who have some prior proficiency, which is most people who are trying to learn a language in Duolingo — particularly English learners, because they&#39;ve done it in school in some kind of way, and their knowledge is patchy, as we like to say.</p><p> And in those cases, the order is going to be quite different person to person because of different experiences. And then the second aspect of it is the things that you specifically are having trouble with in the moment that you need to focus on more. Maybe you&#39;re just making way more mistakes for a particular concept. Maybe it&#39;s verb conjugations that are the problem, or maybe you just don&#39;t know how to introduce yourself well. And so there&#39;s an opportunity to, say, actually spend more time in that part of the experience.</p><p> It&#39;s not that every curriculum is custom made for a unique student, but it is that where you put your attention and your focus, and the amount you put in, and the order in which you do it in is directed by some kind of tutor. I will say that&#39;s a tough thing to do. It really is a tough thing to do. We&#39;re not there, but that&#39;s part of the dream, certainly.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So the show is <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , and we didn&#39;t learn a lot about you and yourself. So maybe tell us a bit about your background — how you ended up in this role, and what the journey was like.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Yes. How far back should I go? Do I start with grandparents?父母？ Myself?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Up to you.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> OK. I&#39;ll skip the extended biography. I grew up in Karachi, Pakistan. That&#39;s where I was raised, and I came to the US for undergraduate studies. And I actually studied political science and East Asian studies in college because, one, I was interested in languages, so I took Chinese, and when I was learning languages in college, one of the most exciting things was always trying out tools to see what was effective or not.</p><p> So it&#39;s the interest in languages, it&#39;s the interest in technology that got me to Duolingo. And actually, I started in marketing because I&#39;d done some marketing and advertising internships before that. At that time, we were around 50 people at Duolingo, and we went from having just one team that worked on the app to having teams that worked on monetization, learning, and growth. And so I started working on growth as a marketing person, and then, about a year and a half in, I switched to being a product manager. And for most of my time at Duolingo, I have worked on growth, which is to say user retention, whether that&#39;s new users or existing users, growing our presence in Asia; that was super interesting. Things like that. And motivation and what gets people motivated and what keeps them motivated has always just been an interest of mine.</p><p> And then, the switch to working on AI as the focus and leading this Experimental AI team came at the end of last year because, basically, we ended up partnering with OpenAI for their GPT-4 launch. And the reason why we ended up doing this partnership was actually because I knew the product manager for the GPT-4 launch at OpenAI, and when we got together, we quickly realized Duolingo is the perfect use case for the launch, because for the launch, what they really wanted was to show that companies are actually using this to transform their businesses and these are also companies that are trying to do good for the world, etc. And so we, as a company, based on that partnership and getting access to GPT-4 early, shifted a bunch of priorities [and] started really leaning into AI, and one of those things was to start this team that&#39;s trying to work on experimental features.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Very exciting. And actually, from a motivation standpoint, you&#39;ll be thrilled to know that my son is very proud of his Spanish language streak, so …</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Amazing.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We&#39;ve got a segment where we ask you a series of questions, and these are just rapid-fire; say the first thing that comes to your mind. What&#39;s your proudest moment in AI?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> We, as a company, launching Duolingo Max has been super exciting and just paving the way for a new era of teaching. It&#39;s been created, actually, by the Max team at Duolingo, which is led by Edwin Bodge and Bill Peterson, and it&#39;s super exciting.</p><p> I&#39;d say personally, actually, the first product that my team has been working on is actually — the experiment is going live. You could kind of think of it like TikTok for reading, but it&#39;s something where all the content is generated by GPT-4. It&#39;s giving you a huge breadth of content because people need reading practice in lots of different varieties, and it&#39;s also listening as well. So I&#39;m very excited to see how that goes.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Very cool. What worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> I&#39;m generally very optimistic, but I think the thing that worries me is just that the pace of change is so quick that it will be destabilizing. And the goal for us as a society is to make sure we can stay stable in the face of very, very rapid change, because rapid change is what we want, actually. We want progress to come quickly but without all of the destabilizing effects. So that&#39;s the fear. I think it&#39;s a solvable problem, but that&#39;s the fear.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> I play a lot of soccer. Funnily, there is technology involved with that, as it turns out, but, yes, I play a lot of soccer. That&#39;s one of my favorite activities to do.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So, what first career did you want? Poli-sci, I think you mentioned. What did you want to be when you grew up when you were a kid?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Lots of different things. There was never one answer. I wanted to be a writer, a journalist, a cricket player — a cricketer — and work in international development; I even wanted to be an architect.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You ran the table there.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Yeah, a lot of different things.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI? What are you hoping we can get from this?</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> I think AI is the way that we can create the fastest progress, where [by] “progress” here I just mean as many human beings [as possible] are living the lives that they choose to live — that they&#39;re flourishing. I think that is the highest-level goal, and that is the meaning of life for most people. I&#39;m very excited to be part of that effort.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, it sounds like you are. Zan, thanks for taking the time to talk to us. I genuinely feel like this is a hugely different and exciting opportunity for how we as humans can get better. And it sounds like Duolingo is doing a lot of that. Thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Thank you so much.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for joining us. Next time, Sam and I speak with Jeremy King, senior vice president and head of engineering at Pinterest. See you then.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Taming the Counterfeiting Epidemic</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Handfield, Anand Nair,  and Thomas Y. Choi. <p>Robert Handfield ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robhandfield">@robhandfield</a> ) is the Bank of America University Distinguished Professor of Supply Chain Management in the Poole College of Management at North Carolina State University. Anand Nair is a professor of supply chain and information management in the D&#39;Amore-McKim School of Business at Northeastern University. Thomas Y. Choi is the AT&amp;T Professor and a professor of supply chain management in the WP Carey School of Business at Arizona State University.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted research into the state of counterfeiting from 2017 through early 2020. Funding was provided by CAPS Research, a joint venture of Arizona State University and the Institute for Supply Management. During the discovery phase, they ran an in-person workshop and attended the October 2017 annual strategic summit of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Handfield_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Neil Webb/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><ul><li> The authors conducted research into the state of counterfeiting from 2017 through early 2020. Funding was provided by CAPS Research, a joint venture of Arizona State University and the Institute for Supply Management.</li><li> During the discovery phase, they ran an in-person workshop and attended the October 2017 annual strategic summit of the Center for Anti-Counterfeiting and Product Protection of Michigan State University.</li><li> The authors conducted individual interviews with more than 20 subject-matter experts in 2017 and 2018.</li><li> The authors also conducted in-depth surveys with 21 supply chain executives in June and August of 2018.</li></ul></aside><p> Whether their leaders know it or not, many companies are losing significant revenue to counterfeiters and unscrupulous supply chain partners. Anyone perusing handbags at a street market knows how common it is to find fake products that look identical to the real thing but might not function the same way. In some cases, this can put consumers at risk: A pharmaceutical company, for instance, discovered counterfeit versions of its product on the black market that contained no active pharmaceutical ingredients. As well, a company&#39;s legitimate product may be diverted for unauthorized sales, as when a global electronics company discovered that distributors in its network, who had ordered components supposedly for customer repairs, were selling them on the gray market.</p><p> High-demand products in every industry are lucrative targets for fraudulent criminal activity. Unfortunately, counterfeit products are a problem that many companies do not want to acknowledge or raise to their boards or shareholders. Senior executives often try to explain away the problem, rationalizing that counterfeiters will always find a way to copy products or that piracy represents only a small percentage of sales and is not worth going after. That plays right into the hands of what counterfeiters want businesses to do: ignore them.</p><p></p><p> When companies do begin to quantify the level to which counterfeiters are affecting their bottom lines, they may attack the problem with piecemeal approaches to try to prevent it from growing. But that&#39;s not enough.</p><p> Our research suggests that successfully combating counterfeits requires the attention of a broad collection of organizational functions. It works best with a multilayered strategy encompassing diverse methods and engaging the entire organization and its partners.</p><p></p><p> We recommend that organizations tackle counterfeiting with a cohesive plan for identifying, containing, and preventing it. This comprehensive process means routinely keeping tabs on contract manufacturers and charting how products move through the supply chain. It includes scoping out what is for sale in consumer markets, deploying covert markings, reviewing warranty claims, educating customers, and partnering with key agencies and competitors.</p><h3> Conventional Tactics Aren&#39;t Working</h3><p> Companies that pay any attention to counterfeiting have traditionally relied on a brand security function to track down criminal activity. These teams often detect counterfeiting using tactics such as applying covert and overt markings on legitimate products, attaching RFID tags that track product locations, and using serialization combined with blockchain to create transaction records that are resistant to tampering. For example, barcodes compliant with the GS1 Global Traceability Standard are used to track COVID-19 vaccines. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> For many organizations, though, these tactics are not enough.</p><p> Counterfeiting and illegal diversion of product remains pervasive: Our 2018 survey of 21 supply chain executives revealed that nearly half had an issue that was ongoing or had experienced an incident in the previous year. More than 70% said they&#39;d had an incident in the previous five years. (See “The Research.”) One executive told us that his company discovered that the equivalent of an entire factory&#39;s monthly production of its products was being sent into black markets, largely due to diversion from one of its own suppliers.</p><p> Counterfeiting has grown into a problem that the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development says was worth $464 billion in 2019, or 2.5% of world trade. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> It was once thought that counterfeiters went after only high-value or luxury items such as pharmaceuticals, designer handbags, or perfume. But now the marketplace is full of fake footwear, pesticides, cosmetics, toys, automotive parts, and medical equipment. Counterfeiters are targeting any industry and any product line where there is an easy profit to be made.</p><p> While companies may never completely eliminate bad actors from copying products or diverting goods from authorized channels, they can significantly reduce counterfeiters&#39; market penetration and restore lost revenue. Successful approaches may involve cutting off counterfeiters&#39; access to markets, eliminating their supply of unauthorized goods, or making a product more difficult to copy. Here, we&#39;ll go into detail on the three activities that a robust action plan comprises: identification, containment, and prevention.</p><h3> Identification: Gain Insight Into the Extent and Nature of the Problem</h3><p> Getting a baseline on the severity of the counterfeiting problem is a critical first step. As the size of the issue becomes clear, the potential return on investment in shutting it down also comes into view. This can help establish performance metrics for the anti-counterfeiting team that can be aligned with business objectives and outcomes. Examples of metrics include the dollar amount or percentage of revenue lost annually due to illegal product trade, total top-line revenues recovered (dollars that were previously unknowingly lost to counterfeit sales), and the number of confirmed incidents of illicit trade, counterfeiting, diversion, and tampering.</p><p> <strong>Create a cross-functional brand security team.</strong> Developing realistic measures of the current problem often requires an intensive investigation that involves applying market channel analyses that explore multiple sources of sales data and other information from both inside and outside the organization. To be effective, a brand security team should include participants from sales, marketing, operations, purchasing, logistics, finance, and accounting, as well as core brand security functions. Such teams are typically led by a global brand protection officer who in many cases has a law enforcement background and usually reports to the chief operating officer.</p><p> <strong>Examine internal and market data to flush out suspicious activity.</strong> Companies can struggle to find, much less measure, counterfeiting activity, given that clues are usually buried in data about sales, warranties, returns, and other product metrics. Unless someone is looking for it, unusual activity can easily go unnoticed.</p><p> A good first step is to start by looking at what&#39;s being sold online. E-commerce has emerged as a perfect channel to fuel the counterfeit goods industry. Consumers may unwittingly buy products from online retailers that don&#39;t verify the source of the products on their platform and whether they are legitimate. Despite counterfeit sites being shut down regularly by Amazon (and, in China, Alibaba), operators trading in fake goods regularly open up again under a different name the next day. Amazon reported that it blocked 10 billion fake listings and destroyed 2 million counterfeit products in 2020 alone. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Since e-commerce sites are frequently a counterfeiter&#39;s primary source of sales, companies can begin by investigating where their products — either genuine or fake — are being sold online. Looking for common attributes of counterfeiter websites can narrow down the pool of suspicious activity. For instance, a company might find four different sellers on Amazon offering an exact copy of its handbag, listing the same details and even photos. An indicator of potential counterfeiters might include spelling or grammatical errors, blurry photos, or other details that don&#39;t look quite right.</p><p> Another important data source is warranty returns. When a consumer sends a product back because it is defective (and counterfeits often are), detective work can track down where it was purchased and how. This can lead to the origin of market entry for counterfeit goods and a starting point to find their downstream source. A global medical products company we looked at hired a global brand protection officer who examined warranty and returns data, field service requests, and sales data. In his first 100 days, he found 1,000 confirmed incidents of illicit trade, counterfeiting, diversion, and tampering. This amounted to $1.4 billion — 2% of revenue — lost annually to illegal product trade.</p><p> Estimating counterfeit sales is a difficult but essential task: Companies must establish a baseline against which to gauge the effects of anti-counterfeit measures. Having an accurate understanding of the scope of the problem is a prerequisite for deciding how much to invest and what ROI to expect from anti-counterfeiting measures. In many cases, business decision makers are unaware of the extent to which their revenue and reputation are in jeopardy.</p><p> <strong>Map the supply and distribution chain.</strong> Many companies are surprised to learn that bad actors are active within their own supply chains. Overproduction, black-market sales, and unauthorized distribution are common sources of leakage that may result in a product, or copies of it, being sold through channels that a company knows nothing about. That&#39;s why an important early step is to identify the manufacturing and distribution channels through which the company&#39;s products travel.</p><p></p><p> The brand owner at a large global apparel company told us that he had heard through his distributor network that the brand was being sold in Mexico even though the company had no authorized retail presence there. To track where these products were coming from, the director hunted down bills of lading and shipping records for the ocean freight shipments that were going to Mexico. The paper trail showed that the goods were shipped from a port in Israel — by the same authorized manufacturer that was producing the company&#39;s branded product in the United States. The apparel company eventually tracked down the clothes, which were genuine products, made under the same specifications and from the same materials, but were being illicitly distributed outside of the contractual agreement between the parties. When the apparel company set up a global brand security function and mapped its entire supply network, it found that similar cases of product diversion were occurring all over the world.</p><p> Analyzing how much is being spent on raw materials in the upstream supply chains is a good place to start mapping a supply base. Procurement can reach out to the accounting team to track all third-party purchases being made on the company&#39;s behalf (a document generally known as a <em>spend analysis</em> ). If a supplier is buying more raw materials and is operating at a higher production level than what the company is ordering, this is a telltale sign that the additional product may be moving into the black market. This requires full visibility into the supply chain, beyond just Tier 1 suppliers (which is increasingly important for other reasons, in particular to manage risk related to labor or environmental violations). Some suppliers may be reluctant to disclose their upstream suppliers for competitive reasons but can be reassured that the query is for security purposes and not an attempt to cut them out of the chain.</p><p></p><h3> Containment: Limit the Problem&#39;s Spread</h3><p> With a dedicated team in place, an initial sense of the problem&#39;s scope, and an understanding of the particular counterfeiting and diversion risks that it&#39;s most vulnerable to, a company can begin to manage the problem systematically in order to contain it.</p><p> <strong>Analyze product segments.</strong> One of the key tasks for the investigation team is segmenting products by channel, margin, volume, and risk of counterfeit activity. This ensures that the team&#39;s attention is being directed toward the most vulnerable market channels first.</p><p> In many cases, a current-state analysis of a company&#39;s supply and distribution processes helps reveal a common set of product segments that counterfeiters go after. In particular, our research found that product lines with high complexity based on the variety of finished products, level of finished-product customization, geographical span of suppliers, number of tiers in the supply chain, predictability of demand, and variation in manufacturing volumes. Examples of items in this category include aircraft and automotive replacement parts, toys, high-end apparel, branded pharmaceutical products, and consumer electronics. Counterfeiters are more likely to opportunistically target product segments characterized by a greater level of complexity and exploit this complexity to their advantage.</p><p> We interviewed executives at a biotech manufacturer who knew that counterfeit products were showing up in the market but did not know the source. The brand protection team started by segmenting products into those that were big targets for counterfeiters (in this case, high-margin items) and analyzing data to estimate the number of incidents per brand. The team — formed through a close collaboration among franchises, brand owners, and regional sales managers — then rolled out a plan to franchise partners and country business units. This established brand protection priorities by product line and provided a system to track customer-reported incidents by brand and conduct data reviews every six months.</p><p> At the same time, analysts began collecting market intelligence on supply chain vulnerabilities, including potential logistics disruptions and the threat of regulatory intervention, that posed significant risks for business plans and growth targets by region. Cumulatively, these efforts helped the manufacturer prioritize those businesses and regions where brand protection could best safeguard market revenue from sudden disruptions. In the process, the team identified a significant counterfeit and diversion activity affecting a blockbuster infusion drug that was putting many patients at risk. The company said it was able to eventually reduce the number of incidents from 100 per year to zero. This required persistent efforts to deduce the source of each incident through detailed analysis and the introduction of countermeasures — including sending a message to counterfeiters warning that they would be pursued, in hopes of convincing them to go look for an easier target.</p><p> This kind of analysis begins with identifying an initial clue and following the thread of activity. The initial problem may manifest itself as a minor issue such as a customer warranty problem, a dealer who seems to be ordering too many replacement parts, or a spate of customer returns on a particular brand of product. Any of these issues may be a hint that leads to a channel of counterfeiting activity.</p><p> <strong>Start with e-commerce sites, and reach out to customs and other authorities.</strong> A team of analysts should be hunting down in-the-open counterfeit operations on e-commerce sites on an ongoing basis and reporting them to the platform operator, such as Amazon, and to law enforcement. At the very least, this introduces more friction into some bad actors&#39; businesses to slow them down.</p><p> Counterfeit products almost always have to cross borders and pass through transshipment points and customs inspections overseen by law enforcement entities. These are critical players in the supply chain, and organizations must think of them as partners in the battle against revenue loss and intellectual property theft. These relationships are particularly important in highly regulated environments, such as pharmaceuticals, food, aerospace, and automotive manufacturing, where counterfeit products can endanger their users.</p><p> An official with US Customs and Border Protection (CBP) told us that it can be challenging to get brand owners to understand the CBP&#39;s process and play their part in helping the agency fight the problem. “We are in the field, inspecting containers,” he said. “If a CBP officer opens a container and sees something that looks suspicious, they will first look in our internal database of registered brands. If the officer doesn&#39;t see anything, there is nothing they can do.” Registering brands with the CBP and US Patent and Trademark Office is a critical step in containing counterfeiting.</p><p> <strong>Educate (and warn) customers.</strong> It is imperative that consumers are educated about the possibility and risks of buying fake goods. Companies should make customers aware, through brand marketing, that if they buy from an unverified online third-party seller, they bear the risk of not having the product covered by warranty — or, worse yet, having it fail with dire consequences. One company we know of began adding a statement on its Amazon website warning that products returned to it that were not licensed would not be under warranty. Companies should also emphasize to customers the importance of registering the product serial number for warranty purposes, which protects them if a legitimate product they&#39;ve purchased turns out to be flawed or faulty. If a customer tries to register the serial number for a counterfeit product, it will show up as an error and alert the brand security team to a problem.</p><h3> Prevention: Stop Future Counterfeit Ops Before They Start</h3><p> Once an organization discovers how the spread of counterfeit products in its market channels works and has taken initial steps to contain the problem, it must continue to monitor criminal activity and establish strong preventive measures. There are important roles for numerous functions in the company to play at this stage.</p><p> <strong>Product packaging experts should explore digital tracing technology.</strong> Features in current tracing technologies offer positive product authentication, can indicate tampering, can increase the difficulty of replication, and permit product tracking and tracing. Secure markings — which use a variety of packaging, blockchain, and serial marking technologies — are one method for tracking products. Many industries are working with standards organizations like ASTM International or GS1 to develop common methods for verifying products. This can help avoid the problem where counterfeiters try to copy not just the product but the digital marking, too.</p><p> In the biotech example mentioned previously, the brand protection team worked with the business to identify covert and overt authentication capabilities, which created automatic alerts when counterfeit products were being sold through market channels. The team also created a comprehensive customer communication plan using web advertisements, targeted email and Twitter campaigns, and retailer alerts about the dangers of buying from unauthorized sources. The campaign created awareness in the company&#39;s sales partner network and set the stage to identify where new counterfeit sales were occurring.</p><p> <strong>Quality assurance should review data to track down instances of product problems and returns.</strong> QA can create triggers in its data collection processes that flag potential illegitimate activities. We know of a company that noticed an uptick in its product returns, discovered that the products were not legitimate, and tracked them down to the point of sale — which revealed the source of the counterfeiting.</p><p> <strong>Supply management should step up efforts to audit suppliers.</strong> It can be particularly fruitful to track overproduction by suppliers, as well as how they dispose of products that don&#39;t conform to quality standards — products that can end up moving through black market channels and thus avoiding trade compliance policies. One large apparel company began monitoring the inventory levels within its supplier&#39;s facilities and noticed that the supplier&#39;s inbound raw-material inventories were much greater than the volume of finished goods it was shipping to the company. This was an indication that product was being produced and sold elsewhere through other channels.</p><p> <strong>Logistics should map supply routes to document compliance on the part of transportation providers.</strong> This can help ensure chain of custody along global supply chains, particularly at handoff points such as ports, warehouses, and distribution centers. Companies with multitier distributor channels should document every logistics handoff and conduct random audits to determine whether there are proper security personnel and locked gates at all distribution centers.</p><p> <strong>Human resources might want to consider monitoring employees who are dealing directly with targeted products.</strong> This may include conducting background checks, as well as increasing training to enhance staff awareness. If there is a high level of missing inventory or a sudden increase or drop in product sales, investigations may be required.</p><p> <strong>Aftermarket sales should track warranty claims and parts sales to identify product-quality problems.</strong> As with the quality assurance team, those at the front line of aftermarket sales are in a position to learn that products aren&#39;t performing as expected, which, again, may indicate that counterfeits are entering market channels. For example, a large retailer made the decision to limit its distribution channels and authorized resellers, recognizing the high potential for counterfeit products in these particular sales channels, especially e-commerce.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Counterfeiting and product diversion are not crimes that a single organization can combat. They require the diligence of brands, retailers, packaging companies, and logistics businesses. This is a rare instance where joining with competitors can yield important insights. Companies should consider joining a consortium and partnering with industry counterparts. Industry-specific groups include the Automotive Anti-Counterfeiting Council for vehicle manufacturers and Rx-360 for pharmaceutical companies. Members of React, a large anti-counterfeiting network, include Marvel Entertainment, Mattel, Pfizer, Philips, Prada, and Timberland.</p><p> Counterfeiting is also not just a private-sector supply chain problem. Labor and human rights advocates, consumer education agencies, customs agents, federal and state law enforcement agencies, local police, and consumers of counterfeit products all have an interest and role in ferreting out unauthorized activity. While counterfeiting and product diversion cannot be eliminated, dedicated efforts can curtail both significantly.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Dismantle Career Roadblocks for More Equitable Outcomes</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian is a cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts. That was the message from [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/W23-QA03_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts.</p><p> That was the message from Haig R. Nalbantian, cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute, during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023. Nalbantian helps organizations apply evidence-based, empirical methods to strengthen their DEI efforts and retention strategies and asserts that “the surging use of analytics in the HR domain to inform work and workforce management” is a big part of the future of work.</p><p></p><p> While talent and drive are important in shaping careers, situational factors profoundly affect what happens to employees at work. They include employees&#39; access to “accelerator” roles, such as customer-facing jobs; how employees navigate flexible work arrangements, such as part-time status; and employees&#39; reporting relationships, such as whether they report to higher-level or high-performing supervisors. Nalbantian noted that these easy-to-identify circumstances, which he called <em>explained differences</em> , are prevalent.</p><p></p><p> Many organizations also have pervasive and sizable <em>unexplained disparities</em> regarding who gets chosen for promotions. Nalbantian said that in both his own studies and others, “women are actually more likely to be highly rated” by their managers at elite, large employers — all things being equal — “but in the majority of companies, they&#39;re less likely to be promoted.”</p><p> He said it is critical that companies address the explained differences and explore the unexplained disparities.</p><p> Nalbantian wasn&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the event, so he answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> Does your research address intersectionality in its analysis? You talked about women and people of color, but what about women of color and other people with multiple intersecting minority identities?</h6><p> In many of the client cases covered in my study, we did indeed examine intersectionality directly. We&#39;ve done this quite a bit in larger US-based organizations that have adequate populations of these demographic groups for modeling purposes.</p><p> One of the areas of particular interest to client organizations is intersectionality with respect to reporting relationships. That is, do the specific demographics of one&#39;s supervisor affect whether the employee is promoted, is highly rated, or gets higher pay increases? For example, do White male supervisors treat Black female reports worse than White male or White female reports? Do White female supervisors help the prospects of their female reports, regardless of color?</p><p> I can say that there are few regularities in these results — certainly far less than the results I&#39;ve reported with respect to performance ratings, roles, supervisor performance and level, and flexible working.</p><p></p><h6> Has this research mapped across socioeconomic status as an intersectional influence?</h6><p> Unfortunately, we&#39;ve had much more limited data on socioeconomic factors, in part because most of our clients focus these studies on their salaried populations, ignoring their hourly workers. This concerns me, as it reveals a tendency to discount front-line workers. I try to remind organizations that what happens in their front-line ranks can have a major impact on business results. I&#39;ve seen and documented this in client assignments. Still, the tendency of organizations is to prioritize their salaried employees — professionals, managers, and executives.</p><h6> You mentioned that being younger than comparable peers is an attribute favorable to success. Can you elaborate more on what your studies have found regarding age inequalities?</h6><p> The negative impact of age is close to universal among our analytical findings with client organizations. The simple fact is that once an employee gets beyond the median age of their cohort, all things turn negative: They&#39;re less likely to be promoted, they&#39;re less likely to receive a high performance rating, and their pay growth levels off or declines.</p><p> The one positive is that there is less turnover with older employees, often substantially less. Indeed, it may be that it is precisely because older employees tend to stay that employers don&#39;t feel the need to promote, pay, or recognize them in the same way as they do their younger employees. The latter have more outside opportunities, so they may need to be constantly wooed.</p><p></p><p> These negative signals about older workers can be very misleading. We often find that groups with more older workers actually outperform those with more younger workers. There&#39;s a discordance between what&#39;s found at the individual level compared with the group or organizational level.</p><p> This suggests that the productivity of older workers shows up not in their own measures of individual performance but in the performance of those with whom they work. We call this a <em>spillover effect</em> . So, for example, if older workers are less likely to turn over, they can cause their younger colleagues to follow suit, thereby bringing more stability to their work groups and making them more productive. For more evidence about the productivity of older workers, see the recent study I conducted with Richard A. Guzzo and Nicholas L. Anderson, which we discuss in the article “ <a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">Age, Experience, and Business Performance: A Meta-Analysis of Work Unit-Level Effects</a> ” in the journal <cite>Work, Aging and Retirement</cite> .</p><h6> How can organizations ensure that age diversity and inclusion are integrated into their equity and diversity initiatives?</h6><p> Again, it is a common view among business leaders that older workers are less productive. And because they tend to cost more, they are viewed more as a liability than an asset, despite significant evidence to the contrary. For some reason that I find hard to explain, combating ageism is not high on the DEI agenda, certainly not as compared with efforts to address gender and racial inequity. I fault the DEI community for not being more aggressive on this front.</p><p> The aging workforce is a fact of life almost everywhere. Organizations that don&#39;t deal effectively with the repercussions of this secular trend and ensure that they are managing their older workers effectively run the risk of undermining organizational performance. In effect, they may make their unfounded stereotypes a self-fulfilling outcome.</p><p></p><p> I always urge my clients to undertake the kind of disciplined diagnostic work to evaluate the realities of their own workforce — to determine whether spillover effects are indeed at work in their organization, and to respond accordingly. Through this process, many of them will find that they have an asset to protect rather than a liability to discard.</p><h6> Is there any analysis done on the correlation between company performance or share price and the situations demonstrated by the survey?</h6><p> I&#39;ve undertaken client studies in which we link workforce characteristics and management practices to various business outcomes, including profitability, financial and operational productivity, revenue growth, and customer retention, among others. Our results have been mixed. In some, we&#39;ve seen that greater diversity in work group or unit composition improves business performance; in others, we&#39;ve found no effect or statistically negligible results. The most robust review and synthesis of the results of these studies is the meta-analysis of the effects of age and tenure noted above. That study did not focus on the effects of race and gender.</p><h6> What concrete steps can organizations take to battle these biases?</h6><p></p><p> My article in the summer 2023 issue of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/">Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</a> ,” speaks directly to this question. I explain how organizations can use the results of this kind of modeling to help eliminate or reduce the influence of demographics on how well employees are positioned to succeed at work. The reality is that all too often, situational factors inordinately affect the ability of employees to succeed and that women and people of color are situationally disadvantaged.</p><p> Employers who recognize that they are not positioning this talent to succeed can deploy an approach I call <em>proactive career management</em> to change this reality on the ground. This may involve getting more women and people of color into supervisory or other accelerator roles, changing reporting relationships, and neutralizing the negative effects of flexible working, among other things. I share a case study in my article to illustrate this approach in action.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do Consumers See Your Business as a Force for Good?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cynthia E. Clark. <p>Cynthia E. Clark, Ph.D., is a professor of management at Bentley University. She is also a coauthor of <cite>Business and Society: Ethical, Legal, and Digital Environments</cite> (Sage Publications, 2020) and the author of <cite>Giving Voice to Values in the Boardroom</cite> (Routledge, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[The public’s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s efforts to impose fines on businesses for greenwashing, point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald’s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Clark-Eco-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> The public&#39;s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the US Federal Trade Commission&#39;s efforts to impose <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/04/13/ftc-is-expected-crack-down-greenwashing/">fines on businesses for greenwashing</a> , point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald&#39;s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic waste. Last year, <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/blog/2022/04/55-million-total-ftc-settlements-kohls-and-walmart-challenge-bamboo-and-eco-claims-shed-light">both Kohl&#39;s and Walmart</a> reached settlements of $2.5 million and $3 million, respectively, for falsely claiming that dozens of rayon textile products were actually made from environmentally friendly bamboo.</p><p> When such large, visible companies issue false claims or fail to act, it results in missed opportunities, a growing performance-expectation gap, and, eventually, reputational damage among consumers. So, what makes a business a force for good when it comes to the future of our environment? To find out, Bentley University and Gallup recently conducted a survey of 5,757 Americans to assess how they feel about business and its potential to have a positive impact on society and the environment. The <a href="https://www.bentley.edu/news-Announcing-the-Bentley-Gallup-Force-for-Good-survey-results">results of the Force for Good survey</a> highlight areas in which businesses, small and large, are failing to meet people&#39;s expectations — and how they can do better.</p><p></p><p> The public&#39;s expectations of large companies like Kohl&#39;s, McDonald&#39;s, or Walmart were made clear in our research. A slight majority of our respondents (53%) said that businesses overall have a negative environmental impact. Almost two-thirds (65%) said they feel this way about <em>large</em> businesses, whereas 16% said that <em>small</em> businesses have a negative impact on the planet/environment. Younger respondents in our study had higher expectations of businesses overall, with a whopping 81% of those age 18 to 29 saying that large businesses have a negative impact on the planet, compared with 54% of respondents age 70 or older.</p><p> Drilling down into the data, we found that more than 9 in 10 respondents rated four social and environmental concerns that businesses could act on as extremely or somewhat important: practicing sustainable manufacturing (92%); promoting increased access to education and training (92%); investing time and money into local communities (92%); and operating in a way that is sustainable for the environment (91%). Just 1 in 3 people surveyed said that businesses are currently doing an excellent or good job in any of these areas, and about 1 in 4 (26%) said that businesses are doing an excellent or good job of operating in an environmentally sustainable way.</p><h3> The T-Shirt Experiment</h3><p> One perspective on sustainability is that companies should practice environmental responsibility for the greater good — the “doing good to do good” perspective. Another approach focuses on the importance of “doing good to do well” so that both business and society benefit from leaders&#39; actions. But are these approaches in tension? Need they be?</p><p> One section of the Force for Good survey — what we called our T-shirt experiment — was aimed at getting a better read on how people think about this tension. Amid rising prices for almost everything, we asked whether respondents would be willing to pay extra for a T-shirt depending on a variety of company characteristics. Sixty-three percent of respondents said they would be willing to pay extra — 82% more — for a T-shirt if the company that made it was known for having a positive impact on the environment. The numbers are even higher for respondents age 18 to 29 and for women: Young people were most likely to say they would pay more — about 8 in 10 — and almost 7 in 10 women. (See “Results of the T-Shirt Experiment.”) Both of these consumer groups are key markets for many companies.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Results of the T-Shirt Experiment</h4><p class="caption"> To differing degrees, depending on age and gender, respondents indicated their willingness to pay more for the same product based on a business&#39;s sustainability practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig1-1.png" alt="Results of the T-Shirt Experiment" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> When people were asked how much they would pay for the T-shirt without being given any additional information, the median response was $10. This held true for those with personal incomes between $24,000 and $179,000. In other words, personal income had little effect on the value they assigned to the product.</p><p></p><p> Respondents were then asked how much more they would pay if the company were known for various attributes: having a positive environmental impact, making a positive impact on the local community, treating employees well, and contributing to charities. Among the four attributes, the premium was highest for companies known to have a positive environmental impact, with a median response of $7.</p><p> Our data indicates that Americans are, in fact, willing to reward companies for doing good. A company known for positive environmental performance can charge more for its products — evidence that “doing good to do well” works.</p><p></p><h3> A False Dichotomy?</h3><p> Most of the respondents didn&#39;t see a trade-off between good environmental performance and good financial performance. In other words, they believe that both can happen concurrently, despite business leaders&#39; arguments that sustainable practices harm financial performance. About 7 in 10 respondents (69%) said businesses that prioritize making a positive impact on society are just as profitable (47%) or more profitable (22%) than their competitors. People who said they have expertise in owning, leading, or managing a business were no less likely than those without such expertise to say that businesses that prioritize making a positive impact are at least as profitable as their competitors.</p><p> Members of different political parties had notable differences of opinion regarding the importance of sustainability. For example, 84% of Democrats said it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner, compared with 31% of Republicans and 59% of independents. However, a large majority of Republicans (80%) said that sustainability is at least <em>somewhat</em> important. These perspectives might affect a host of company actions, such as choosing content and spending amounts for advertising in red versus blue states and the very design of their products.</p><p></p><p> Likewise, we found significant differences across ethnic identities. Seventy percent of Black respondents, 82% of Asian respondents, 65% of Hispanic respondents, and 59% of White respondents said they believe it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner. When asked how they feel about focusing on long-term benefits like those for the environment versus short-term benefits like profits, 77% of Asian respondents said they are likely to support that focus — compared with 56% of respondents overall. The figures for both Black and Hispanic respondents hovered around 60%.</p><p> Even when we asked the question in a slightly different way, respondents did not see it as a trade-off but as more of a “both and” situation. For example, when asked about meeting the financial goals of investors, 79% said they believe it is somewhat or extremely important. Eighty-eight percent of respondents also said that making the world a better place is somewhat or extremely important.</p><h3> How Can Your Company Become a Force for Good?</h3><p> Results from this deep dive into what a broad and varied set of Americans believe suggest several actions companies can take or plan for.</p><p> <strong>Pay attention to your local footprint.</strong> Small companies are perceived as better at most stakeholder-related activities. Respondents were twice as likely to say small businesses positively impact people&#39;s lives than large businesses (82% and 41%, respectively). What&#39;s more, respondents are more likely to think large businesses have a negative impact on Americans&#39; lives in general (38%) than they are to say the same about small businesses (4%). This data, combined with the results across age and gender in the figure below (see “Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?”) on positive community impact, suggests that companies — particularly large ones — should improve their relationships with their surrounding communities.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize that younger Americans expect more.</strong> Millennials (born between 1981 and 1996) and Gen Zers (born between 1997 and 2012) expect more from businesses in terms of both social and environmental responsibility than older respondents do. In our T-shirt experiment, 82% of respondents age 18 to 29 were willing to pay more for a T-shirt from a company known for having a positive impact on their local community. Again, young respondents (73%) agreed more than any other age group that businesses&#39; efforts to reduce their carbon footprints and/or emissions are important. Companies will need to account for their environmental stewardship among their customers and future employees.</p><p> <strong>Mind the performance-expectation gap.</strong> Environmental stakeholders and regulators are on the lookout for any discrepancy between expectations of a company&#39;s responsible environmental management and what it is actually doing — the performance-expectation gap. The vast majority of respondents (89%) said businesses have “a great deal” or “some” power to make a positive impact on people&#39;s lives, but just 57% said that businesses are very or somewhat effective at doing so. In terms of the environment, the findings revealed performance-expectation gaps of at least 30 percentage points between “the importance of” and “the performance of” several environmental goals. On questions about reducing businesses&#39; carbon footprints, engaging in sustainable manufacturing, and making the world a better place, we found considerable gaps: On those three points, 52% to 57% of respondents indicated that it is extremely important for businesses to do so, but only 24% to 28% thought they are excellent or good at it.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?</h4><p class="caption"> There is a considerable gap between respondents&#39; opinions on the importance of sustainability practices and their perceptions of businesses&#39; actual practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig2.png" alt="Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> While having a dedicated sustainability leader, support from senior management, and education for employees and executives is necessary, it&#39;s important to stay vigilant in addressing the widening performance-expectation gap. In what has become a hypercritical business environment, leaders must pay greater attention to how perceptions of what their company is doing compare with what they are actually doing.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Set sustainability goals.</strong> Think carefully about how to measure what you&#39;re doing. This is a logical next step after gaining the support of senior management, and it can help your company determine the progress it has made and where it has soft or blind spots. In fact, regulators have proposed requiring companies to disclose how they set climate-related targets and measure their progress toward meeting them. Consider signing on to broadly recognized and accepted goals like the United Nations Global Compact&#39;s (UNGC&#39;s) <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals</a> , which can help your company publicly commit to a plan of action, step by step. The UNGC also requires annual statements on progress to help ward off greenwashing.</p><p></p><p> With increasing attention on environmental sustainability, gaining an understanding of how various stakeholders perceive your statements and actions is vital. By identifying and understanding current perceptions and their implications, as the Bentley-Gallup study does, companies can amend their environmental commitments and processes to ensure that they invigorate their efforts to be a force for good, which will benefit the company, its stakeholders, and, most importantly, the environment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Myth of the Mainstream</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus Collins. <p>Marcus Collins is a clinical marketing professor at the University of Michigan&#39;s Ross School of Business and former head of strategy at Wieden+Kennedy New York. He is the author of <cite>For the Culture: The Power Behind What We Buy, What We Do, and Who We Want to Be</cite> (PublicAffairs, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com For years, McDonald’s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension. The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Collins_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> For years, McDonald&#39;s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension.</p><p> The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about its updated menu, which offered healthier alternatives more in line with contemporary diet trends — but to no avail. Year over year, McDonald&#39;s sales declined, and its brand perception continued to spiral downward.</p><p></p><p> Finally, the company decided to go on the offensive. Instead of combating the opposition&#39;s hate and attempting to win over those in the middle, McDonald&#39;s decided to focus on its fans — the people who self-identify as McDonald&#39;s devotees despite the vitriol directed at the brand. The company&#39;s tactics included launching its Famous Orders campaign, which celebrated the favored menu items of superstar fans (like hip-hop mogul Travis Scott and K-pop megastars BTS); creating adult-targeted Happy Meals; and promoting fans&#39; own menu hacks. In doing so, it tapped into what these devotees love about McDonald&#39;s and not only activated their collective consumption but also inspired them to spread the word on behalf of the brand. The result of this strategy was a 10.4% increase in global revenue for McDonald&#39;s from 2018 to 2021 and the return of dormant customers: more than a quarter of those who came in to buy the Travis Scott meal, for example, hadn&#39;t visited the chain in over a year. Seemingly overnight, McDonald&#39;s went from being a cautionary tale to the darling of brand marketing and a case study for advertising effectiveness.</p><p></p><p>这里发生了什么？ Conventional wisdom would tell us that in a world of increasingly polarized opinions, our best bet is to appease the middle, if only because that&#39;s where the majority of the market is. That also seems like a safe bet to many companies, as a middle-of-the-road position is less likely to alienate potential customers. But McDonald&#39;s demonstrated what can happen when you dismiss this conventional approach. Instead of trying to speak to the mass market, it chose a side. It chose to embrace the love instead, fighting the hate, and it abandoned the notion of enticing the large but indifferent middle of the market. By doing so, McDonald&#39;s marketing efforts activated a legion of fans who not only consumed but also won over others as well. What McDonald&#39;s realized is an important lesson for contemporary marketers: If you want to get people to move, you must choose a side. The notion that you can win by playing to the middle is a misleading myth.</p><p></p><h3> Choose a Side</h3><p> The core function of marketing is to influence people to adopt a desired behavior. That is to say, we go to market to get people to move — to buy, to vote, to recycle, to subscribe, to download, to watch, to evangelize, to wear a mask — and to drive a host of other desirable behavioral outcomes that will benefit our organization or interests. And what influences people the most? Well, according to everything we know about human behavior, we are most influenced by other people — not ads, not value propositions, but other people. More specifically, we are most influenced by <em>our</em> people: the individuals who abide by the same culturally established conventions and expectations that dictate what is considered acceptable behavior for people like us. These individuals typically share a similar worldview and, therefore, adhere to a shared way of life in an effort to promote social solidarity among themselves — their subculture. They consume the way the subculture consumes, vote the way it votes, and behave the way it behaves, because that is what is expected of people like them.</p><p> If these people are against you because of the shared conventions and expectations of people like them (their culture), then the likelihood of getting them to take action on your behalf will be slim. That&#39;s why right-wing Republicans won&#39;t bother trying to convert left-leaning Democrats. Instead, Republicans speak to their base — the collective of people who see the world similarly, express a similar set of cultural characteristics as the brand, and are more inclined to move in step with the brand as an act of social solidarity. They identify as members of this group and follow its behavioral norms.</p><p> Those in the unaffiliated middle of the population, on the other hand, are by nature indifferent and risk averse. While they may have opinions, they lack strong convictions in either direction and are therefore less likely to take action. In politics, they don&#39;t vote in primaries or campaign for candidates; instead, they sit on the sidelines and wait to see how things shake out. Their behavior is the same when it comes to brands.</p><p> The middle doesn&#39;t adopt new products with any urgency. They are not the first to respond to marketing communications, nor are they likely to weigh in on a debate between advocates and detractors. They mitigate their own risk of moving out of step with what might be considered generally acceptable by stepping back and observing other people&#39;s responses first.</p><p> The red herring is that we perceive this indifference as an opportunity to persuade them to one side or the other. But the truth is, they are not typically convinced by any marketing communications. Instead, they, too, take cues from other people — sometimes those who are for you, and at other times those who are against you.</p><p></p><p> With this in mind, it becomes abundantly clear that in a polarized scenario, the chances of marketers getting people to move are far greater when we activate the collective of the willing as opposed to trying to convince detractors or even persuade the indifferent. And yet, historically, marketers have focused their efforts on the middle because it represents the biggest market opportunity. However, our chances of successfully influencing behavior increases when we choose to address the people who are most likely to take action. When we do so effectively, we catalyze a propagation effect that causes the product, behavior, or idea to cascade throughout the population, thanks to the process of social contagion — the spread of affects, behaviors, cognitions, and desires due to direct or indirect peer influence of people “like us.”</p><h3> The Power of Propagation</h3><p> The idea of propagation demands that marketers leave behind the conventional approach of targeting the middle, where the majority of the population resides. Besides being of questionable effectiveness, as discussed above, reaching the middle requires costly media spending (think prime-time TV and Super Bowl ads) and places marketing messages in an arena that is noisy and saturated with competing messages. Marketers pay little attention to the fringe, a population that conventional wisdom tells us is too small and too niche. But everything that is now mainstream once started on the fringe: It started within a subculture and propagated out to become popular culture.</p><p> For instance, if you were into comic books 20 years ago, you would have been considered a nerd. Today, however, many of the most-viewed movies across the globe, such as Marvel&#39;s <cite>Avengers</cite> series, originated from comics. Twenty years ago, if you were into video games, you would have been perceived as an immature adult. Today, gaming is not only considered cool but is also a multibillion-dollar industry. Indeed, what is now normal was once fringe. Thanks to social contagion, the cultural characteristics of a community propagate from the fringe to the middle — from the subculture to popular culture. It happens from the outside in, not the inside out.</p><p></p><p> Unlike traditional marketing communications, the reach and subsequent adoption that is achieved through this kind of propagation does not rely on people hearing a message from a company or brand. (It helps, but it&#39;s not necessary.) Instead, people hear about it from someone they trust — someone like them — which increases their likelihood of adoption. As the network scientists Nicholas Christakis and James Fowler contended, “When a small group of people begin acting in concert — displaying similar visible symptoms — the epidemic can spread along social network ties via emotion contagion and large groups can become quickly emotionally synchronized.” This is the network effect that is catalyzed when you activate the collective of the willing. Don&#39;t focus on the middle: Focus on the people who see the world the way you do. Choose a side, and they will convince the bystanders, the passive, the indifferent.</p><p></p><p> Although broadcast messaging might get our attention, it&#39;s the influence of people like us, people with whom we identify, that changes our outlook and, subsequently, our behaviors. This provides a new perspective, and corresponding strategies, for marketers who aim to communicate with consumers in a culture where ideological binaries seem to divide the market. Like McDonald&#39;s did, marketers benefit from choosing a side that is most likely to move and then activating its members so that they might convert people on the brand&#39;s behalf. Status quo practices position the middle as a safe bet. However, the dynamics of cultural diffusion subvert these long-standing best practices for connecting with consumers and influencing behavioral adoption, and demand that today&#39;s practitioners develop new strategies and accompanying tactics.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sustainability Progress Is Stalled at Most Companies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[CB Bhattacharya and Rob Jekielek. <p>CB Bhattacharya is director of the Center for Sustainable Business and the HJ Zoffer Chair in Sustainability and Ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business at the University of Pittsburgh. Rob Jekielek is managing director of The Harris Poll.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Sustainability & Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability-Driven Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else’s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual.1 On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bhattacharya-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else&#39;s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming their business models to be more sustainable have embedded sustainability into their corporate DNA. This means that they have endowed their employees with a sense of sustainable ownership, spurring them to engage in more sustainability-supporting behaviors. When every employee integrates environmental and social concerns into every business decision, sustainability progress is accelerated — an aspirational goal for all companies.</p><p> To shed light on the state of play in embedding sustainability and identify key bottlenecks, the Center for Sustainable Business at the University of Pittsburgh collaborated with The Harris Poll to conduct a survey of US employees. We wanted to find out whether their employers were taking measures that our earlier research had identified as important to prompting employees to conduct business through a sustainability lens. Our survey drew responses from 1,056 employees, representative of the US employee base. We defined sustainability for the respondents as “integrating environmental and societal concerns into business decisions and actions.”</p><p></p><p> We asked respondents to rate their level of agreement with a series of 19 statements about the status quo, such as “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance,” on a 4-point Likert scale (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”). We also presented respondents with a series of 12 issues that could pose challenges to sustainability progress, such as “Sustainability is not built into our business strategy,” and asked them to rate the extent to which that is an actual challenge at their company (from “major challenge” to “not at all a challenge”).</p><p> Roughly one-third of the respondents asserted that their employers have made significant strides in their sustainability journeys. Although that number might sound low given the enormity of the task facing us, the good news is that there is momentum, which we can help accelerate by pointing out the roadblocks as perceived by employees. Below, we provide six key recommendations that emerged from our data for managers seeking to embed sustainability in the organizational culture and business models.</p><p> <strong>Establish a purpose based on values.</strong> Purpose is a business&#39;s raison d&#39;être — the answer to the all-important question, “Why do we do what we do?” Paul Polman, former CEO of Unilever and a leader in the corporate sustainability movement, has said, “Sustainability is totally driven by purpose.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Organizations that are successful at embedding sustainability articulate the societal benefit they aim to deliver to their stakeholders, and this overarching purpose guides everything the organization does.</p><p> In our study, 36% of the respondents strongly agreed with the statement “My company wants to make a difference in people&#39;s lives, not just make profits,” while 33% strongly agreed with “My company has a higher purpose beyond profit maximization.” If purpose is the starting point for sustainability, we aren&#39;t doing very well; it is apparent that the profit-maximization narrative is alive and well. Consistently, 43% of employees cited short-term focus, a lack of investor interest, and, importantly, “Our leaders don&#39;t believe in sustainability,” as challenges. Unless CEOs and top management teams realize that profit is the <em>consequence</em> of value creation for all stakeholders and not the starting point for strategy development and execution, progress will be stifled. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p></p><p> <strong>Bake sustainability into corporate strategy.</strong> Academic researchers and others have noted that efforts to make meaningful progress toward sustainability must be driven by corporate strategy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Doing so increases the likelihood that, over time, “doing the green thing” will be seen as a normal part of employees&#39; jobs, and more and more decisions will be made through the lens of sustainability. With only 29% of respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance” and 27% with “Sustainability is core to how my company executes our business strategy,” it appears that we have a long way to go. Consistent with the status quo, 43% agreed that their company&#39;s failure to build sustainability into its business strategy represents a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Train employees, and incentivize actions that advance sustainability.</strong> Companies that are successful in engaging their workforce have invested in training that gives employees guidance on how to improve sustainability. With only 30% of employees surveyed strongly agreeing with the statement “I understand how I can improve my company&#39;s sustainability performance through my role,” there seems to be a dearth of role-specific knowledge at the individual employee level. Lack of training was cited as a major/moderate challenge by 44%, while a similar number (45%) indicated that they don&#39;t know what actions to take to improve sustainability performance. Companies need to invest more in training and sustainability knowledge creation so that employees know <em>what</em> they can do in their roles and <em>how</em> to do what needs to be done.</p><p> Managers must also do more to provide employees with incentives to advance the sustainability agenda: Forty-nine percent of those surveyed found the lack of such incentives to be a major or moderate hurdle to improving sustainability performance. Leaders should also consider whether the management culture encourages engagement and intrinsic motivation by giving employees the autonomy to solve sustainability challenges, which often require creative thinking. However, when we asked survey respondents to rate their level of agreement with the statements “My company allows me to make a lot of sustainability-related decisions on my own” and “My company gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out sustainability initiatives,” we found that, at most, 29% of respondents strongly agreed.</p><p> <strong>Create a sustainability culture in your organization.</strong> Managers can keep sustainability salient in the organizational culture by communicating progress, celebrating milestones, recognizing achievements, and collaborating on solutions both internally and with industry partners. Our research has identified the lack of a sustainability culture as one of the biggest impediments to progress, with 48% of respondents indicating that that is a major or moderate impediment at their organization. Communicating sustainability progress to employees is a key component of a sustainability culture, because it keeps issues top of mind. Celebrating successes will pique employee interest and legitimize the importance of sustainability to the organization — but only 31% of respondents strongly agreed that their company celebrates sustainability successes.</p><p></p><p> Collaborating with traditional competitors — which is increasingly necessary to address those complex “ <a href="https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/tragedy-of-the-commons-impact-on-sustainability-issues">tragedy of the commons</a> ” problems — signals to employees that the company is serious about transformational change and reinforces the culture to employees. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> With only 25% of survey respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company collaborates with other organizations to address complex sustainability issues,” it is evident that much work is required to open corporate leaders&#39; eyes to the potential of progress via collaboration.</p><p> <strong>Conduct business through a sustainability lens.</strong> Imagine the progress we would make if every employee in every company — from the mailroom to the boardroom — integrated environmental and social issues into every business decision they made. This, in our view, is conducting business through the lens of sustainability — an aspirational but necessary goal to reach if we are to surmount our existential crises. As previous research has shown, employees taking individual ownership of sustainability is a key driver for engaging in sustainability behaviors. In our survey, 28% of respondents strongly agreed with the statement “Employees at my company take ownership of improving sustainability performance,” while 45% identified a belief among employees that “sustainability is someone else&#39;s responsibility” as a challenge. This lack of personal ownership of sustainability performance is reflected in our survey results: Only 27% of respondents strongly agreed that they “invested ideas and creativity” to help their company be more sustainable, and just 24% strongly agreed that every business decision they make is viewed through the lens of sustainability.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Bridge the last mile.</strong> We noted a significant difference between how corporate and front-line employees responded to our questions. Compared with front-line nonmanagers working in roles such as customer support, managers working in corporate roles were, on average, about 15% more likely to see sustainability as embedded.</p><p> To ensure that their commitment to sustainability is real and provides tangible benefits to their organizations, leaders must address this last-mile gap between corporate and front-line employees. Broadly communicated messaging about the corporate purpose and environmental, social, and governance targets might not suffice in this instance; there is a real need to drive sustainability through practical initiatives and actions that can be integrated into daily tasks and routines that employees perform across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> Interestingly, perceiving sustainability as more embedded in the organization also opens employees&#39; eyes to the roadblocks and challenges that impede progress. Our data shows that employees who are more engaged and perceive sustainability to be more embedded also perceive more roadblocks, on average, than those who are less engaged.</p><p> The implication here is that as companies bridge the last-mile gap in embedding sustainability, they should be prepared to field more questions and listen to more opinions as employee engagement on the issue increases. Companies should use one-on-one coaching, action playbooks, and tailored communication to make sustainability everyone&#39;s job. Companies need to be prepared to invest more resources into embedding sustainability — and get the entire organization to conduct business through the sustainability lens.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Robots Can Enhance Performance Management for Humans</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Hong and Lynn Wu. <p>Bryan Hong is associate professor of entrepreneurship and management at the Bloch School of Management at the University of Missouri-Kansas City. Lynn Wu is associate professor of operations, information, and decisions at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Efficiency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to invest in robotics for their business. Our research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Wu-Robots-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/advanced%20electronics/our%20insights/growth%20dynamics%20in%20industrial%20robotics/industrial-robotics-insights-into-the-sectors-future-growth-dynamics.ashx">invest in robotics</a> for their business. Our research has found an equally and perhaps more important transformation taking place: The adoption of robots is improving companies&#39; ability to recognize and reward good employee performance.</p><p> Within every organization, leaders face a fundamental question: How do we get the best from our people? One of the most common methods is offering monetary rewards — usually, periodic bonuses — that are linked to performance. This practice is grounded in the idea that better performance should be more highly rewarded. But that approach is rarely simple to implement in practice because it requires that performance be measured well enough to be evaluated effectively. This is challenging to accomplish for most roles and even more so for individual employees. Because so much work is done in teams and managers can&#39;t monitor the specific activity of each employee or accurately measure individual performance, many organizations choose to pay bonuses based on team or company performance rather than on individual performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p></p><h3> Measuring Human Performance When Colleagues Are Robots</h3><p> What does all this have to do with robots? In our research, we have found that companies that adopt robots improve their ability to measure human performance. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> To illustrate, let&#39;s say you&#39;re working in a team of two. Your manager can see and evaluate your combined productivity as a team but not what each of you is doing individually at all times. In theory, both of you are supposed to be contributing equally; in practice, you&#39;re doing far more of the work, which isn&#39;t visible to your busy manager.</p><p> Then, let&#39;s say your teammate is replaced with a robot. As a machine, the robot is much more precise and consistent in doing its work tasks and might even provide data about its performance while operating. Because it&#39;s so consistent and transparent, any disruptions or spikes in productivity can much more clearly be identified as coming from either the robot or from you. If there are others in your organization who work with the same type of robot in a similar way, then it&#39;s much easier to see how their individual productivity varies from yours.</p><p> In other words, because robots are, by their very nature, much more consistent and transparent than humans, human activity becomes easier to observe if robots join the team. The more robots there are relative to humans, the easier it is to distinguish and measure individual human performance.</p><p></p><p> In one real-world example, a repair facility at a major US-based electronics company experienced a dramatic improvement in its ability to observe employee productivity after robots were implemented to assist workers in the repair process. Because robots, unlike humans, do not get physically tired while performing repetitive tasks, they were able to perform more consistently. This reduced variance in the production process and allowed managers to more clearly observe individual employee behaviors. Many employees followed a regular pattern of being more productive in the morning than in the afternoon, with substantial variance in their afternoon productivity. As a result, many workers ended up with more repairs to finish later in the day as they rushed to meet their daily quotas. This “cramming” of work was especially problematic because it typically resulted in more errors due to the workers having rushed.</p><p> Integrating robots into the repair process eased the tracking of individual employee productivity in two ways. First, robots made different types of errors than humans. The robots&#39; errors were consistent, which made human errors easier to distinguish. Second, the robots themselves provided precise data about their own performance, which made it easier to isolate performance outcomes, both positive and negative, caused by human behavior. This data generation capability allowed managers to better monitor productivity overall and to more easily detect weaknesses in the production process. Managers at the repair facility, for example, hadn&#39;t been aware of the extent of the afternoon cramming behavior until robots were incorporated into the production process. Once the problem was clearly identified, they were able to reorganize the work process to reduce errors; overall error rates at the facility have since improved.</p><p></p><p> These types of improvements in performance measurement can have especially dramatic effects on productivity in combination with performance-based incentives. If it&#39;s easier to observe and measure the performance of individual employees within organizations, good performers — who may have received little reward or recognition because of measurement challenges — become easier to identify and reward, and leaders really can do better in getting the best from their teams. And this is exactly what we find in our research: Companies that adopt robots are also more likely to adopt bonus incentives tied directly to individual performance as opposed to team or organizational performance. With better measurement comes increased rewards for an organization&#39;s good performers, and a more productive workplace. Using robots is fairer for the people who work at an organization.</p><p></p><p> Robots are changing the nature of work. Beyond eliminating some jobs and creating new ones, robots are also changing organizations&#39; ability to get the best from their people, as well as the way we experience work itself. Robots offer an exciting opportunity for businesses to redesign the roles and responsibilities of the humans that work with them, giving those companies a competitive edge over rivals not because of superior technology but because of better processes. The robot revolution isn&#39;t going to eliminate the need for humans. Rather, it&#39;s bringing both new challenges and opportunities for identifying, rewarding, and managing human talent.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Detecting the Good and the Bad With AI: Airbnb&#39;s Naba Banerjee</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operational Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Predictive Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Psychological Safety]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Naba Banerjee’s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Naba Banerjee&#39;s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to let curiosity be her guide as she applies her previous data science experience to the travel industry.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Naba joins hosts Shervin Khodabandeh and Sam Ransbotham to talk about how she and her team use AI and machine learning to increase the safety of the guests and hosts who use Airbnb&#39;s platform. She also discusses collaboration between humans and machines and the importance of recognizing that neither is an infallible decision maker. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-S7-E1-Banerjee-Airbnb-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Naba Banerjee"></p><h4> Naba Banerjee, Airbnb</h4><p> Naba Banerjee is the director of trust product and operations at Airbnb, overseeing the company&#39;s efforts to combat fraud, build trust between hosts and guests, and stop bad actors from using the platform. Her most recent work includes the development of Airbnb&#39;s reservation screening technology, which helps to identify users making potentially high-risk reservations and prevent them from taking advantage of the platform.</p><p> Banerjee has over two decades of experience building products that deliver innovative, customer-centric solutions. She joined Airbnb after spending 13 years at Walmart.com, where she played an instrumental role in the evolution of product management, including shipping packages to customers more quickly and building mobile apps to enable customers to check out faster.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-banerjee"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Machine learning can detect fraudulent activity, but it may also miss good behavior. Find out how one platform company manages these risks and trade-offs on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m Naba Banerjee from Airbnb, and you are listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Today, Shervin and I are speaking with Naba Banerjee, director of trust product and operations at Airbnb. Naba, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you; a pleasure to be here.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think most people know Airbnb, but maybe tell us a brief overview of the company and what you do.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Airbnb stands for a place which fosters connection and belonging. Millions and millions of hosts open up their homes to complete strangers, and you and I and our families get to travel to an exotic destination, and instead of staying at a hotel, you actually get to truly immerse yourself in the local culture. And at times, if you&#39;re really lucky, you get to stay at the house of a host and actually experience hosting as it&#39;s meant to be, thereby creating and fostering connection and belonging.</p><p> And in this world that is increasingly becoming insular and connection is becoming a rare thing, I am so glad to be part of a company that is trying to create more connection. And what my team does, the trust and safety team at Airbnb, is along the entire customer journey, right from the time that you create an account on Airbnb throughout the journey. At times, it is possible that something could go wrong: A fake account could get created, or your account could get taken over. The listing you&#39;re trying to stay at could be a fake listing; the reviews you&#39;re looking at may not be exactly genuine. But our job is to make sure that you can focus on your magical stay, the host can focus on being the perfect host, and we try to anticipate some of these risks, and we minimize the risk of those kinds of issues from happening. And using technology and data to enable that magical user journey is what my team does.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think we all hear headlines where something goes wrong. How much goes wrong in the course of the gazillions of transactions that you do?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. In 2021, we had around 70 million trips that happened on Airbnb, and less than 0.1% of those trips resulted in a host or a guest reporting potentially an issue that happened in that stay. And when our team went in and investigated and actually looked at where the real harm happened or somebody had to be removed from the platform, that number is even smaller.</p><p> I know that even one bad incident is probably too bad and should not be happening, but in the bigger scale of things, what you come back to realize is the majority of people are actually good. Ninety-nine point nine percent of people are meaning to just go about their daily business, enjoy a great stay, or be a great host. But sometimes, [on] that very rare occasion when that bad thing happens, we want to make sure that we reduce the risk of that.</p><p> If you really look at where a person is causing harm to another person, those incidents are like a fraction of a fraction of a fraction. But when we talk about safety, we&#39;re looking at [things like] a carbon monoxide gas leak. It could be slip and fall; it could be property damage, where glass broke and you probably had a stain on your carpet. We are also looking at those kinds of issues.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I&#39;m hearing from what you&#39;re saying is, your role is, No. 1, a good role. You&#39;re the protector of the good and the “warder-offer” of evil, right?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I love that. You should be part of our branding team.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s a good thing, right? It&#39;s a very purposeful role. And the second part of it is, you&#39;re talking about microscopically small incidents.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, needles in a haystack.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Right? And those are fun problems. Tell us more about under the hood — what happens?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I would say it&#39;s three parts. One is, we start with the “why,” which is — you framed it really well — that we are the protector of the good and trying to ward off the bad. We can never say that we stop everything bad. Like, to Sam&#39;s point, you cannot do that. But how are we learning and getting better? And that&#39;s where AI and ML [machine learning] comes in, where [we ask], “How can we use [the] power of data and technology to learn and get better?” And every year, the risks don&#39;t stay the same; the data keeps growing.</p><p> And then the second thing is, “How do we use technology responsibly?” Which is, you could go too blunt and try to block as much as possible to specifically look at fraud and safety incidents and keep them down, but then, if the data that you are using to make these decisions has bias in it, is potentially creating unfairness, then you could close off your doors to a lot of good people who genuinely are just trying to have a good stay. So [it&#39;s about] using technology responsibly. … It is having self-governing mechanisms, which is, we have our privacy team, our data privacy team, our infosec team, our anti-discrimination teams, which are … almost like mirrors to the trust team. [There are also] other teams in Airbnb, where every time we are really laser-focused on this particular fraud vector, this bot detection, this account-takeover detection or party detection, they are constantly making sure that are we using the data in a safe way and a transparent way, giving users control and then not introducing bias.</p><p> And then, lastly, having ways for us to give people a path back, which is, we are going to — based on the data available to us, and the technology available to us, and the maturity of that technology — make our best possible decision. But if we get it wrong, can we create transparency and a process for users to appeal and get back on the platform when we do block them or remove them so that, again, we can learn and get better? So that, at the highest level, is how my team is working under the hood.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And what are some of the use cases?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> One of the use cases that we have talked about quite a bit is, you know … I&#39;ll take you on a little story, which is, when I joined the trust team in 2020, the world had just shut down; the pandemic was raging. And very similar to how the world was waiting for a vaccine, while waiting for a vaccine, we went into lockdown mode.</p><p> That was a blunt instrument … to prevent people from exposing themselves to situations which would make them unsafe. Similarly, Airbnb became an unfortunate product-market fit for unauthorized house parties. When the hotels and bars shut down, unfortunately that less than 1% or 0.1% of users who were looking for places where they could throw these parties, they started renting out Airbnbs. And as a result, we realized that it was causing a lot of pain to our communities of hosts and guests who use this platform, which was based on a foundation of trust. So initially, we had to use some very blunt instruments.</p><p> We first instituted our global party ban, saying that Airbnb does not allow for any kind of party whatsoever. Second, we started looking at some patterns and found that someone under 25 booking an entire home for just one night or two nights less than 50 or so miles away from their home — those seem to be all signals that lead to parties. When parties happen, we usually find … that account was created yesterday. Then we implemented a blunt rule called “under 25,” and we put that in place. Now, we had to be careful, because those rules don&#39;t exactly work globally. But that worked in North America, and we saw right away that there was a reduction in the number of unauthorized parties.</p><p> But over time, just as it happens with rules, we saw that people started to game those rules. They would get an older friend to book the reservation for them. And instead of one night, they would book it for three nights, and so on and so forth. [And] the impact on good users was so high that we said, “We kind of need to move to machine learning. We need to get smarter.” And so we did our first pilot in Australia, where we segmented the place and looked at the place that had this new party model that we&#39;d built versus the other. Do we see a reduction? And again, this is like looking for a needle in the haystack, but we still saw 35% fewer parties in the area that had the party model versus not. And when we started experimenting in North America, we did see that it was as effective as the heuristic, with lesser impact to good users.</p><p> And that kind of gave us the confidence to keep moving forward, because not doing anything was not an option. We had to do something and had to be smart about it. That was one of the use cases where we could go out and talk about it — not claiming that we are stopping all parties, but at least Airbnb is taking a strong stance about it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> One common thread that I&#39;m hearing in how you&#39;re describing the problem and the solution is a need for constant adaptability and ongoing learning, and using the right instrument for the right job. At times it&#39;s a rule, then maybe its unsupervised learning, then there&#39;s a human intervention. It does sound quite multidisciplinary, including the part where the rules change, or the fraudster&#39;s mode of operation changes, and you also have the issue of “Is it too blunt? Does it limit some unintended but good or benign behaviors?” How does the human and machine collaboration or interaction work in these situations?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You summarized it really well, Shervin, which is, it&#39;s not a one-and-done thing. You build it, and then you have to constantly learn and optimize from even the kind of decisions you are making, as well as how the world around you is evolving. And that is an area [that] humans are really good at, which is, you do have to have the discipline of training your models with the latest data, with the right data, making trade-off decisions on what is the optimal threshold at which you are going to say, “OK, this is risky, and we are ready to use that risk.”</p><p> At Airbnb, we have been constantly on this journey of how to leverage humans in the loop. I have a trust operations team in addition to the product and planning teams. This operations team constitutes full-time employees as well as agents globally. And whenever we build a new model, in the beginning we often have the model make a risk threshold-based decision: “This is the top 1%. This is the next tranche. This is the next tranche.” And at times, we will route that to human beings to then create labels on top of that to say, “I agree with the model&#39;s decision,” or, “I don&#39;t agree with the model&#39;s decision,” which then serves as training data back to the model.</p><p> And then, when we have more confidence in the decision-making capability of the model, we would go toward auto-decisioning. This party model, to your point, right now it&#39;s completely auto-decisioned. But what ends up happening is, when we get an appeal back from a user saying, “I was incorrectly blocked,” that then serves as data that&#39;s coming by the customer telling us. And then an agent looks at that appeal and says, “Actually yes, this decision was incorrect.” And if the agent made a correct decision, that customer appealed correctly, and no incident happened, we know that that was a false positive.</p><p> But let&#39;s say the agent approved, and then that customer went on to throw a party; that was a false negative. We are learning from that continuously, but we do it iteratively. First, we try to have the model direct to a human. And again, there is no guarantee that the human is better at decision-making than the model, but we constantly measure the performance. Then we go toward higher-order decisioning [with less] human decisioning. And sometimes we will also have … let&#39;s say the party model makes decisions. People go about their merry way, have the reservation. Sometimes after the reservation has been booked, we will also still have humans look at the top 1% risky reservations to try and correct anything that they can.</p><p> So it is either trying to balance that out as to, when are humans the right people to make the decision? When should the machine make the decision? It&#39;s been a not-easy, nonlinear journey that we have been on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned at first you&#39;re maybe reviewing more cases and then learning from those cases. But at the same time, you have people … these 70 million transactions are happening constantly. And, for example, when you gave the illustration of the hotel … shutdown at the beginning of the pandemic, that&#39;s a time where it&#39;s happening to individual hosts and customers. How do you balance that trade-off of needing to get something in place quickly [while] at the same time needing to go through a process?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That probably is the hardest thing, and the hardest thing in my entire career I would say that I have dealt with. Before this, I was managing all of product for Samsclub.com, which is part of Walmart, and I thought my job was hard then. And while we were serving customers, helping them check out, it still felt like we were on a growth path, and we could choose how fast we grew or how slowly we grew. And I always had teams that were looking at people who were trying to check out [but] couldn&#39;t and serving them while we were building longer-term architecture, but people&#39;s lives were not at stake; [it was] people&#39;s money — fraudsters using stolen credit cards and swindling the company of millions of dollars.</p><p> There is a team at Airbnb that is trying to protect the good and ward off the bad. What we do is that you have to get really good at prioritization, which is also very hard to do in the world of trust and safety.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And in many ways, I mean, the choices are what, Sam, you said in the beginning: These kinds of economies are not risk-free. They cannot be risk-free. And the good collectively outweighs the evil, so then it becomes all about prioritization. But I have to say, we&#39;ve talked to many people in analogous roles that you have, in other organizations — you mentioned Sam&#39;s Club, others — where they&#39;re using technology, digital AI/ML to drive a variety of use cases. I think yours stands out in the sense that it is a continuous balancing act, and the stakes are high. And then you have this sort of thread of purpose and the humility of saying, “Well, we believe that we&#39;ll make mistakes, and the system cannot be mistake-free.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But over time, things are getting better. Which brings me to my next question: How do you measure this, your effectiveness? Is it in terms of number of incidents, and some severity and frequency of bad things happening?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m glad you asked this question, because I was naturally going to go toward this, which is, at the highest level, the metrics that we measure ourselves on are number of fraud incidents per million trips, number of safety incidents per million trips, as well as good user impact. That&#39;s the balancing metric to see “How many good listings did we block? How many good hosts and good guests did we prevent from moving forward to truly understand our false positives and false negatives?” But at the end of the day, it&#39;s good trips that we are looking at across the board.</p><p> We are also looking at dollars in terms of fraud loss that is potentially happening. We are looking at customer support tickets that are coming in, user NPS [Net Promoter Scores] resulting from anyone who encounters a friction that is thrown by our teams. So at a basic level, we are looking at these metrics. But one of the challenges that, for the first time, again, in my career I&#39;ve run into — not so much in the fraud world, where we can A/B test — we are constantly iterating our models.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You are probably also, when you do that, preventing quite benign behaviors and intentions as well. But as you said, there is a point where the human judgment needs to trump and say that this is something where even the risk to one person might be too high. And yes, I mean, we always talk about exploration and exploitation when it comes to machine learning, and sort of ongoing feedback loops, but there&#39;s a cost to learning, always, right? But when I send you a marketing message you may not like, the cost of learning is very minimal, so I will send you many of them, and I&#39;ll do all kinds of A/B/X testing. But when I do that kind of A/B testing to groups or populations where the stakes are higher, then you might as well make that human judgment call of not doing it and relying on retrospective data.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I think you elucidated that point quite well for us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And one question that we ask ourselves is, what makes a human being trust another human being? What makes a human being trust Airbnb? And we are realizing that we can [train] all kinds of models in the background, and you wouldn&#39;t even know whether you were in the risk threshold 1% or 2%, or marked as a good user.</p><p> But there is also a dialogue that needs to happen between Airbnb and you as a guest or you as a host, or between the host and the guest, that truly instills trust. Like when we ask someone, “Would you be comfortable sending your 17-year-old girl to a stranger&#39;s house in Greece, when she wants to backpack before joining college?” You can probably tell this is a personal experience. I have a 17-year-old who&#39;s about to go to college. And I realized that the first thought is, “No — not happening,” and I run trust and safety at Airbnb. But then when I think, “Well, if I could talk to the host; if she&#39;s going to stay with someone else in a house; if that person is a mom like me …”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And we as Airbnb could say, “We are running all these models in the background; don&#39;t worry, your daughter is safe” — I don&#39;t think that&#39;s going to fly. I think as a parent, you will want to have the information you need to see, even though your judgment may not be better than the machine&#39;s. So we are also working on, what is it that we need to say, that we need to do? And sometimes when we say things like, “Airbnb is not going to allow one-night stays that are booked at the last minute within the same neighborhood,” I think it makes a lot of parents feel better too, that OK, at least this option is gone. They will probably figure something else out. And that message cannot be convoluted. That message has to be simple. That message has to be clearly understood. And in addition to asking people what not to do, we also need to encourage people on what good behaviors they should do, like, talk to the host, talk to the guest, ask questions.</p><p> We have launched a program for solo female travelers because we were starting to see a slightly higher rate of maybe personal safety incidents in private rooms with solo female travelers. We started encouraging [women to] find out, is there going to be a lock in your room? Is that lock going to be working? Will you have access to the bathroom just by yourself? Which spaces are shared? Which are not? So this was not a model that was stopping anything. This was simply an educational module that we had published in multiple languages, which was really helpful for our solo travelers. Part of my team&#39;s work is not just to build invisible defenses but also to create trust and the perception of trust upfront through education and messaging.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. I have to say, you mentioned you&#39;re a mother of five. And I have to say, I think you stand on very solid ground when it comes to telling your kids what they can and cannot do, because you have so much data and so much experience, versus me when I say something and they&#39;re like, “Well, how would you know?” And you could say, “Well, trust me; I do 70 million transactions a year, and I know what&#39;s going on.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And growing.是的。 I&#39;m happy to talk to your kids, by the way.任何时候。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes, that would be great. I&#39;ll take you up on that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing about your measurements that I thought was interesting, maybe come back a little bit to that. You mentioned some positive metrics, too. So I think it&#39;s a little tempting, and I think even in this conversation we&#39;ve done that, is we titrate toward the negative. And that&#39;s the news problem in general — is that bad news sells papers. Well, I think in the course of this conversation, we&#39;ve shifted toward that. But some of the metrics you mentioned I thought had a more positive ring to them, didn&#39;t they?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And this was an epiphany that we have been having over the past few years, because any kind of machine learning model typically does well when there is a lot of data to learn from. And with these kinds of cases, where out of 70 million-plus trips, when 0.1% of those result in even a report, and a fraction of a fraction of those results in an actual incident where someone gets removed, there is very little to learn from, and as a result, these models take time to mature. Of course, with technology evolving, that is going to get better, but we realized that we have a lot more data about good user behavior.</p><p> We have a lot more users who are actually coming in, booking their stay months in advance; they are probably checking in on time, leaving the property even better than they found it, communicating with the host and the guests, leaving honest reviews. So if we can actually flip the switch, and while we need to continue to look for the anomalies and the trends and the bad actors, if we can get really good at learning what good behavior looks like while making sure that we are also measuring for potential bias or discrimination and privacy compliance in how we collect and use this data, then that can be really powerful in informing when something does look risky. For example, if an account typically is accessed from the US, [and] suddenly we see that that IP is now accessing from the Philippines, and it feels like “Oh, this is an account takeover.” But if this is a good user who has typically been traveling around the world quite a bit, maybe this is not an account takeover, and there is history there from the good user behavior for us to be smarter about “What does normal look like and what does an anomaly look like?” Not broadly, but very specifically, based on the user segment.</p><p> So this is not new stuff, but I think we sometimes tend to obsess about just really learning what bad behavior looks like and getting good at detecting that, as opposed to complementing what an anomaly looks like [compared] to what normal behavior looks like.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. And you have such a wealth of insights and information in a field that is really an evolving field. I mean, it&#39;s not like a typical collaborative filtering situation where “users like you also bought this.” I mean, so much more goes on in terms of matching. This must be a very interesting and worthwhile problem to get your arms around.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And it requires us to get out of our trust and safety silo and work really closely with our search, relevance, and personalization teams because our job — unlike my job when I used to work in e-commerce — is not just to do the collaborative filtering and say, “People like you bought this, so you should buy this,” or, “You traveled to Paris, so maybe next you want to go to Rome.”</p><p> It&#39;s about … you&#39;re traveling with the family this time. You have little kids; you probably want day care, and we know that this host offers day care, and this location might be great for you. Or with the same customer maybe traveling alone, maybe we need to offer up different recommendations. And having these trust and safety signals embedded into our search-relevance algorithms can get really powerful in matching the right person with the right listing.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Naba, you didn&#39;t start at Airbnb. Tell us a bit about how you got there. You referenced Walmart and some background there, but how did you end up in your current role?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I was the first female engineer in my family. My father took a chance on me and said, “You&#39;re curious. You&#39;re a forever learner. Do you want to do engineering?” And I had no idea what engineering was at that time, but I signed up anyway and went on to become the first female engineer in my family.</p><p> I worked with Tata Consultancy Services, then went on to join Cognizant, came through Cognizant to the US, and worked for some time at AAA. I would just keep going to different projects and different jobs that would help me learn something completely new.</p><p> Walmart happened around 2006. I was asked to work on supply chain at Walmart, which is probably, if you want to learn supply chain at a company, that&#39;s the company to go to. And while I was doing supply chain, every year I kept getting bigger and bigger responsibilities and projects until I found myself, from Walmart, leading almost all of the supply chain teams to going to Sam&#39;s Club, which is a part of Walmart — leading all of product and front end and cart and checkout and marketing and pricing, which I had never done before. But it gave me a chance to get a well-rounded experience learning how the back end of a large retailer works, as well as [how] front-end customer experience works.</p><p> And right after Sam&#39;s Club, I was asked to lead search. Right around that time, I was starting to get really interested in a world that runs on machine learning and AI, and search was a great landing ground for me. I did a course from MIT, interestingly, to learn about the application of AI and ML, and that gave me the courage to take on the search job.</p><p> And from there, Airbnb happened, after 13 years, almost, at Walmart. I was so curious about the travel industry and this marketplace that was so different from anything I had done in Walmart. So the theme here is that I have always gravitated toward something that helps me leverage the skills that I have but then use my curiosity and learning to do something completely new and build myself up as I go along. That&#39;s kind of my background.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Naba, we have a section now where we ask you a series of rapid-fire questions, and just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind. What is your proudest AI/ML moment?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You&#39;re asking me to choose between my different teams, which is career-limiting for me. But I will say that the work that we did on party detection and party risk reduction was groundbreaking, and there&#39;s no one else in the industry who did it the way we did, so that is [a] really proud [moment for me]. But I am proud of all my teams, just for the record.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer. What worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> What worries me is how powerful it is. We had a chance to get to see [OpenAI CEO] Sam Altman up close and in person as he came to Airbnb. And just how fast this technology is improving and how much capability it has … I worry about it falling into the wrong hands. I worry that while my team has this technology, the fraudsters have this technology too, and so I worry about, if today we are worried about fake IDs and fake spam messages being sent to our hosts and guests, how much more advanced this technology is going to get and how much more difficult it is going to get for us to detect the good from the bad. And I think it&#39;ll be AI to the rescue as well in detecting fake AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Your favorite activity that involves no technology?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Painting with watercolors. I love painting nature. And so paper, watercolors, and just peace and tranquility, no technology, is my favorite thing to do. And of course hugging my kids and spending time with them just listening to their day, trying to make them not be on their cellphones while they talk to me. Those two.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I wanted to be a teacher. I come from a family of teachers, and I feel so much joy when I&#39;m seeing someone&#39;s eyes light up with the gift of knowledge. I am a forever learner. Every job that I take has been completely different from my previous job; it&#39;s because I love to learn. And so, yeah, that&#39;s what I wanted to be.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And you probably do a fair amount of teaching in your current role anyway.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I do a lot of mentoring.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;ve taught us quite a lot.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, thank you. I do do a lot of mentoring, because I feel like if someone else can see me do what I do, that will make them feel that they can do it too. So if I can just do that, that&#39;s my life&#39;s mission accomplished.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> My greatest wish for the world, actually, is to not be so afraid; to give it a chance. Because I think sometimes our fear of the bad holds us from embracing the good. There is so much wasted effort that goes into activities that should be automated through AI — so many patients who are not getting treatment; so many companies that probably need help and need so much funding to stand up basic things that can be done by AI; so many countries, probably, who are underdeveloped [but could] get so much advantage. I know that when it falls into the wrong hands, it can be used for bad, but the world has more good people than bad people, and I believe in the power of us using AI for good — using our collective goodness.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think everyone will probably resonate with your idea that the world is better than it is bad. We do tend to hear most of the negative stories, but it&#39;s refreshing to hear how, one, how much attention you&#39;re paying to try and to prevent those, but also to hear something about the good stories too that your platform enables. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. We&#39;ve enjoyed it.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, Sam. Thank you, Shervin. My pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, we&#39;re joined by Zan Gilani, principal product Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Case Against Restricting Stock Buybacks</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Guest, S.P. Kothari, and Parth Venkat. <p>Nicholas Guest is an assistant professor of accounting at the Johnson Graduate School of Management at Cornell University. SP Kothari is the Gordon Y. Billard Professor of Accounting and Finance at MIT&#39;s Sloan School of Management, where he was previously deputy dean. Parth Venkat is an assistant professor of finance at the Culverhouse College of Business at the University of Alabama.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com Are stock buybacks as bad as they’re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Kothari-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Are stock buybacks as bad as they&#39;re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 budget). In addition, senior Democrats have shown interest in barring executives from selling shares for three years after a repurchase, the federal government has suggested that companies that give up buybacks will receive preferential treatment, and the Securities and Exchange Commission has proposed a significant increase in the extent and frequency of repurchase reporting.</p><p> The debate on the economic consequences of stock buybacks has so far tended to focus on small samples or cherry-picked examples. Given that thousands of companies repurchase their shares each year, and aggregate repurchases have exceeded $500 billion annually for the past five years, we decided that a large-sample study of repurchasing behavior was warranted. Our study, published in the journal <cite>Financial Management</cite> , outlines the benefits of the practice, as stated by its proponents, and provides evidence that casts doubt on the alleged costs cited by its critics.</p><p></p><p> Critics of buybacks typically make three arguments against the practice. First, they claim that share repurchases enable companies to manipulate the market either by increasing the demand for — and therefore the price of — shares or by tricking naive investors by inflating earnings per share (EPS). Second, they allege that share repurchases enable insiders to benefit through compensation contracts or the sale of shares at inflated prices. And lastly, critics charge that share repurchases crowd out investment and thus sacrifice innovation and long-term economic growth.</p><p> Meanwhile, those who support or engage in stock buybacks offer several justifications for the practice. First, payouts to shareholders align manager and shareholder incentives by reducing the potential misuse of free cash flow. Second, using repurchases instead of or in addition to dividends gives corporations flexibility in the amount of cash returned to shareholders, the ability to award repurchased shares to employees as equity compensation, a modest tax advantage to shareholders (less pronounced since the 2003 dividend tax cut), and the ability to signal the company&#39;s good prospects to the market. Finally, share repurchases represent well-disclosed and regulated arm&#39;s length transactions at current market prices between willing participants.</p><p> Given the drive to regulate share repurchases, we would expect evidence of their drawbacks to be observable in public data. To test this, we documented trends in repurchases and compared trading volume, share price performance, CEO pay, and corporate financial activities (evidenced by investment and profitability) of companies that do and do not repurchase shares. We segmented the businesses that repurchased shares in two ways: (1) small positive versus large positive repurchase amounts (defined as below versus above median values), and (2) frequent versus infrequent repurchasers (defined as companies that repurchase in one or two quarters as opposed to three or four quarters of the year).</p><p> Our large-sample evidence on thousands of US exchange-listed companies over the past three decades shows that repurchases in the US are a mainstream corporate financial activity that returns several hundred billion dollars of capital to shareholders annually. At an aggregate level, we found that this activity neither creates nor destroys much wealth (that is, it does not produce significant changes in share price). In addition, while repurchases are associated with higher past profitability, they are not associated with excessive CEO pay or underinvestment.</p><p> Trends in aggregate repurchasing activity over time indicate that while repurchases have quickly grown in value, much of the growth can be attributed to inflation and increases in market capitalization. In addition, repurchases are now similar in size to dividends and have not grown faster than dividends for quite some time. However, unlike dividends, repurchases drop precipitously (and temporarily) in times of corporate stress, indicating that they do in fact provide companies with the aforementioned benefit of payout flexibility.</p><p></p><h3> A Closer Look at the Data</h3><p> Through our analysis, we were able to systematically address each of the stated criticisms of stock buybacks.</p><p> First, do companies use share repurchases to manipulate the market by creating excess demand to drive up stock prices? If they do, companies that repurchase shares should have higher trading volumes than those that do not. But average trading volumes have largely remained quite similar for all listed companies, regardless of whether or how often they repurchase shares. In fact, in recent years, the trading volumes for companies that do not repurchase shares have greatly exceeded those of repurchasing companies, suggesting that any excess volume arising from repurchases is dwarfed by other forces.</p><p> If naive investors are tricked into buying shares of companies that engage in repurchasing behavior because of the resulting EPS inflation, we should observe short-term price bumps followed by poor long-term performance. However, regardless of whether or how intensely and frequently companies repurchased shares, we found no evidence that companies significantly outperformed in the quarters with repurchases. While we did find some marginal evidence that companies that intensely repurchase do outperform slightly in the quarter after repurchases, we found no evidence of future reversals in the short or long terms. This pattern of outperformance is more consistent with companies using repurchases to signal undervaluation — a benefit to investors — rather than to manipulate the market.</p><p></p><p> The second critique is that repurchases allow insiders to unfairly profit. If share repurchases as rent-seeking behavior by insiders were a common, systematic abuse, CEOs whose companies buy back shares would receive abnormally high pay, including salary, bonuses, and the value of equity awards. Using a model-generated measure of excess pay that has been vetted in earlier academic literature, we estimate that CEOs of companies that make large positive repurchases earn only $51,000 more than CEOs of companies that do not repurchase shares — a statistically and economically insignificant amount of excess pay. The difference is even smaller — $4,000 — when we compare CEOs of companies that repurchase frequently with those that do not repurchase. These differences are economically tiny in relation to the average CEO&#39;s pay of several million dollars. Surprisingly, CEOs of companies that repurchase infrequently or repurchase small positive amounts earn the least excess pay, less than even the CEOs of non-repurchasing companies. None of this evidence suggests that companies use repurchases to boost CEO pay.</p><p> The third and final critique is that repurchases reduce companies&#39; ability to take advantage of investment opportunities, thereby sacrificing innovation and economic growth. We found that companies that do not repurchase shares invest more but are significantly less profitable than those that do repurchase shares. The companies that repurchase frequently and in large amounts are highly profitable and have steadily made investments in the past, and they continue to make large investments and, at the same time, return capital to shareholders. This suggests that profitable companies repurchase shares while maintaining a steady level of investment, whereas less profitable or loss-making companies do not (or maybe cannot) repurchase shares but are more investment-intensive in the hope of becoming profitable. While there might be isolated examples of poorly governed companies that choose to avoid profitable investments and instead return capital to willing shareholders, it is hard to see how directives encouraging or incentivizing such poorly run companies to retain cash would lead them to make good investments.</p><p> Potential stakeholders who may be affected by repurchase regulations include managers, other employees, shareholders, governments, and society at large. If a company is profitable, a CEO can pay excess cash out to shareholders in the form of buybacks or dividends, keep the money on their balance sheets, or invest in new projects. A small tax on share repurchases may not change corporate behavior significantly and might raise a small amount of revenue for the government. But if the tax rate grows high enough, companies will choose to not buy back shares and instead pay out exclusively via dividends or retain cash. In that case, the government raises no revenue but implements a de facto ban on share repurchases.</p><h3> How a Buyback Ban Could Backfire</h3><p> If a company were to switch to only paying out dividends, shareholders would lose the ability to choose whether to receive a cash payout and could face negative tax ramifications, given that dividends are taxed as income while capital gains are often taxed at a lower rate, and only when gains are realized. In addition, the company would lose important flexibility in difficult times, because cutting dividends is punished more by the market than cutting repurchases.</p><p></p><p> However, the move to restrict stock buybacks seems intended not to motivate companies to shift to paying back shareholders through dividends but to invest more in the business. There is evidence that retained cash is correlated with CEOs making value-destroying decisions, such as pursuing empire-building mergers, accruing personal expenses, or funding pet projects. It seems implausible that restrictions on share repurchases would induce CEOs of poorly governed companies to invest in value-enhancing projects that they otherwise would not have been funding.</p><p></p><p> From an employee standpoint, there is some evidence that labor unions are able to negotiate more successfully if their employers have excess cash, but there is plenty of evidence that constraints on a company&#39;s flexibility to raise and distribute capital is bad for employees, especially during downturns. Empire-building mergers can also be bad for employees, given that M&amp;As often result in the employees of the acquisition target being laid off and employees of the acquiring company being misallocated. In addition, some repurchased shares are reissued to employees, making any actions that are bad for shareholders also bad for stockholding employees.</p><p> Overall, our results show an absence of correlation between share repurchases and price manipulation, return reversals, excess CEO compensation, and underinvestment, which makes it highly implausible that economically significant causal effects of share repurchases still underlie the data. Corporations lose flexibility if they have to rely only on dividends, and evidence shows that poorly governed CEOs who retain cash often spend it on value-destroying mergers, expenses, or pet projects. It is implausible that policies designed to reduce repurchases will also reduce alleged but unobserved malpractices without imposing costs on US public companies and other stakeholders.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>