<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 11 月 30 日星期四 12:00:16 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title>大型语言模型的工作限制</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikhail Burtsev, Martin Reeves, and Adam Job. <p>Mikhail Burtsev 博士是伦敦数学科学研究所的 Landau AI 研究员、人工智能研究所前科学主任，在 AI 领域发表了 100 多篇论文。 Martin Reeves 是 BCG Henderson Institute 的主席，专注于商业战略。 Adam Job 博士是 BCG 亨德森研究所战略实验室主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com Large language models (LLMs) seem set to transform businesses. Their ability to generate detailed, creative responses to queries in plain language and code has sparked a wave of excitement that led ChatGPT to reach 100 million users faster than any other technology after it first launched. Subsequently, investors poured over $40 billion into [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Burtsev-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>大型语言模型（LLM）似乎将改变企业。他们能够用简单的语言和代码对查询生成详细的、创造性的响应，这引发了一股兴奋浪潮，使得 ChatGPT 在首次推出后以比任何其他技术更快的速度覆盖 1 亿用户。随后，投资者在 2023 年上半年<a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/venture-capital-funding-plunges-globally-first-half-despite-ai-frenzy-2023-07-06/">向人工智能初创公司投入了超过 400 亿美元</a>——占全球风险投资总额的 20% 以上——从种子期初创公司到科技巨头，公司都在开发该技术的新应用。</p><p>但是，虽然法学硕士非常强大，但它们生成类人文本的能力可能会导致我们错误地认为它们具有其他人类能力，从而导致技术的误用。通过更深入地了解法学硕士的工作方式及其基本局限性，管理人员可以就如何在其组织中使用法学硕士做出更明智的决策，通过互补技术和人类治理的结合来解决其缺点。</p><p></p><h3> LLM 的机制</h3><p>LLM 本质上是一种机器学习模型，旨在预测单词序列中的下一个元素。早些时候，更基本的语言模型按顺序运行，根据训练数据中单词的概率分布来预测序列中的下一个单词。 （想象一下您的智能手机键盘会建议短信中的下一个单词。）但是，这些模型缺乏考虑单词出现的更大上下文及其多重含义和关联的能力。</p><p>最新的神经网络架构——变压器——的出现标志着现代法学硕士的重大演变。 Transformer 允许神经网络同时处理大量文本，以便在单词与其出现的上下文之间建立更牢固的关系。在越来越多的文本上训练这些变压器已经带来了复杂性的飞跃，使法学硕士能够对提示产生类似人类的反应。</p><p> LLM 的这种能力取决于几个关键因素，包括模型的大小（由可训练权重的数量（称为<em>参数 ）</em>表示）、训练数据的质量和数量（由<em>标记</em>的数量定义，指的是单词或子词单元） ），以及模型可以接受作为提示的最大输入大小（称为其<em>上下文窗口大小</em>）。模型中的每个参数都封装了从训练数据推断出的关系的一些信息，因此参数数量较多的模型往往知识更丰富、更细致。 （例如，OpenAI 的 GPT-3 拥有 1750 亿个参数。）训练数据量也显着影响模型的泛化能力，更大的数据集提供更多样化的语义关系和事实表示。 （GPT-3 接受了大约 5000 亿个令牌的训练。）模型可以接受的提示的大小也会影响其准确性。 （GPT-3 的上下文窗口包含 2,000 个标记。）上下文越详细，模型的预测就越准确。</p><p>为了响应提示，法学硕士利用其训练建立的关系来逐个标记地生成文本的延续。每个步骤都需要根据提供的上下文预测下一个标记的概率，并且算法根据这些概率选择标记。此选择的随机程度由模型的<em>温度</em>设置调节。较高的温度会产生更多“创造性”或不太可能的选择，而较低的温度会产生更可预测的反应。为了提高法学硕士对特定提示的反应的准确性，并限制其产生不适当、不相关或有毒反应的能力，可以通过<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/09/25/technology/chatgpt-rlhf-human-tutors.html">人类反馈强化学习或 RLHF 等</a>技术对预训练模型进行微调，该技术已被用于微调- 调整 ChatGPT 等模型。</p><h3>法学硕士的四个重要限制</h3><p>基于对法学硕士如何工作的理解，我们可以检查当我们将人类直觉应用于看似人类的输出时，它们可能产生的错误印象。</p><h4> 1. 推理的局限性</h4><p><strong>提示：</strong><em>根据2007年卷心菜种植者联盟的报告，收集的卷心菜中80%是重的（超过0.5公斤），10%的卷心菜是绿色的，60%是红色的，50%是大的（直径超过0.5公斤）。 10 厘米）。以下哪项陈述一定是错误的？</em></p><ol><li><em>所有的红甘蓝都不大。</em></li><li> <em>30%的红甘蓝很大。</em></li><li><em>没有既绿又大的卷心菜。</em></li><li><em>一半的卷心菜很小。</em></li></ol><p> <strong>LLM 回复：</strong><em>错误的说法是 4。一半的卷心菜很小。</em></p><p>正确的答案是陈述 1 是错误的——至少有些红甘蓝一定很大。</p><p>与他们可能给人的印象相反，法学硕士并不是为了复杂的推理而建立的。例如，研究发现 OpenAI 最先进的法学硕士 GPT-4 只能在 2.4% 的情况下正确<a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-just-few-months-chatgpt-232905189.html">验证数字为素数</a>，在视觉模式预测方面也存在类似的弱点。其他研究表明，<a href="https://owainevans.github.io/reversal_curse.pdf">法学硕士</a>无法理解训练数据集中单词之间的关系：例如，GPT-4 可以正确回答“谁是汤姆·克鲁斯的母亲？”这个问题。 （玛丽·李·菲佛）但无法推断出“谁是玛丽·李·菲佛的儿子？”的答案。 ——模型正确回答前一类问题的正确率是 79%，而后者的正确率是 33%。</p><p>从本质上讲，法学硕士只学习<em>口头模拟</em>基本逻辑规则，但不具备将它们链接在一起以产生和验证复杂结论的技能。此外，法学硕士在多步骤逻辑推理中很容易出现错误累积，因为该模型的基本概率性质意味着每个步骤都有非零的错误机会。最后，法学硕士无法总能勾勒出得出结论的“思路链”，这使得人们很难确定错误是否发生或发生在何处。</p><p></p><p>最近由波士顿咨询集团 750 多名顾问进行的一项实地实验强调了这一限制对现实生活的影响。使用 GPT-4 的参与者在尝试解决简单的业务问题时，得到错误答案的几率比没有获得 LLM 的对照组高出 23%，因为<a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2023/how-people-create-and-destroy-value-with-gen-ai">GPT-4 不仅经常得到错误答案</a>，而且提供了如此有说服力的答案其解决方案的理由是用户从表面上接受了它。</p><p></p><h4> 2. 知识或专业知识的局限性</h4><p>我们要求一位法学硕士向我们提供五篇发表在同行评审学术期刊上的关于核聚变可行性的论文，包括论文标题、发表年份和主要作者姓名。 LLM返回了五个结果，其中两个是新闻文章，不是同行评审的论文，一个是一篇不存在的论文。</p><p>法学硕士的知识由其培训数据决定。如果数据缺乏特定领域知识、特定概念的实例不足或不是最新的，法学硕士可能无法根据提示显示相关知识。同样，法学硕士可能会重现训练数据中存在的错误。最后，模型可能会通过“幻觉”训练数据中不存在的语句来产生错误。委托 ChatGPT 为各种癌症病例制定治疗计划的研究人员发现，三分之一的<a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/chatgpt-generates-error-filled-cancer-treatment-plans-study-2023-8">法学硕士的回答包含不正确的信息</a>——通常与正确的指示混合在一起，并且以一种让外行人很难识别什么的方式合理地表达出来。是准确的。在另一个备受瞩目的例子中，两名律师及其所在的律师事务所在法庭文件中提交了 ChatGPT 生成的<a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jun/23/two-us-lawyers-fined-submitting-fake-court-citations-chatgpt">虚假引文</a>后被罚款：法学硕士对六个法律案件产生了幻觉，包括司法意见和引述。</p><p>最后，知识的局限性也可能导致缺乏一致性，法学硕士在不同时间点以矛盾的方式回答相同的提示。例如，爱荷华州教育工作者使用 ChatGPT 来确定<a href="https://www.popsci.com/technology/iowa-chatgpt-book-ban/">学校图书馆的图书是否适合</a>遵守新的州法律。他们向法学硕士提供了一份图书馆所有图书的清单，并要求其指出那些包含违法内容的图书，结果导致图书馆删除了 19 种图书。然而，当记者随后向 ChatGPT 查询这 19 款游戏时，得到的答复是，其中只有 4 款游戏包含不符合法律的内容。</p><h4> 3. 理解的局限性</h4><p><strong>提示：</strong><em>蓝色盒子里有一个苹果。蓝色盒子里面还有一个红色盒子。红色盒子上面有一个盖子。我怎样才能得到苹果？</em></p><p> <strong>LLM回复：</strong><em>要从盒子里取出苹果，您可以按照以下步骤操作：</em></p><ol><li><em>打开红色盒子的盖子：由于红色盒子在蓝色盒子里面，并且上面有盖子，所以需要先打开红色盒子的盖子。</em></li><li><em>从蓝色盒子中取出红色盒子：打开红色盒子的盖子后，可以从蓝色盒子中取出整个红色盒子。</em></li><li><em>打开红色盒子：从蓝色盒子中取出红色盒子后，您可以打开红色盒子来访问其内容。</em></li><li><em>取回苹果：最后，你可以把手伸进红色盒子里，取出苹果。</em></li></ol><p> ChatGPT 无法理解苹果不在红框内。</p><p>法学硕士可能无法“理解”所给出的提示。如果缺乏足够的背景，它可能会动摇，其输出可能会变得脱节或不连贯。<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.02312">研究人员分析了 ChatGPT 对在线软件工程论坛 Stack Overflow 上 500 多个人工提交问题的答复</a>。他们发现，52% 的模型回答不准确，其中一半以上的错误是由于 ChatGPT 不理解问题的概念或细节，或者关注问题的错误部分造成的。这意味着当用户缺乏足够的问题知识来提供良好的提示时，法学硕士甚至可能没有多大帮助。</p><h4> 4. 计划和执行的局限性</h4><p>法学硕士可以为所请求的任务提供清晰的分步指导，给人留下模型可以规划实用解决方案的印象。但鉴于法学硕士的推理能力有限和对任务的理解有限，建议的行动可能不切实际或幼稚。例如，当被要求制定一个<a href="https://fortune.com/recommends/mortgages/i-used-chatgpt-as-my-financial-planner/">为拥有住房而储蓄的</a>计划时，ChatGPT 提供了一些总体可靠的财务建议，但没有考虑收入或利率变化的潜在变化。此外，它不考虑人为的错误：它既不质疑目标的现实性，也不质疑用户了解自己确切消费习惯的信念。</p><p>对于企业来说，所有这些限制都会降低可靠性；人们无法确定法学硕士提供的信息是完整的、相关的、可行的或真实的。鉴于这些限制，当然不能指望法学硕士能够自主做出关键决策或执行计划。然而，委派平凡的任务似乎仍然很有吸引力——例如，那些涉及与现有 IT 服务进行编程交互的任务，例如网页浏览和抓取，或社交媒体监控和消息传递。事实上，Auto-GPT——一种由 GPT-4 提供支持的开源应用程序，将 LLM 输出链接在一起以自动执行用户设定的目标——已经允许爱好者创建许多令人印象深刻的自动化演示，包括 <a href="https://lifehacker.com/you-can-try-auto-gpt-the-next-generation-of-chatgpt-r-1850343691">对产品进行研究</a>、对网页进行编码或应用程序，甚至<a href="https://dataconomy.com/2023/04/19/best-autogpt-examples-use-cases/">订购披萨</a>。然而，人工智能研究员吉姆·范 (Jim Fan) 表示，工作演示是<a href="https://twitter.com/DrJimFan/status/1647616587199815684?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1647616587199815684%7Ctwgr%5E53a5539ffd940932a855d641438099af4aa992a5%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechcrunch.com%2F2023%2F04%2F22%2Fwhat-is-auto-gpt-and-why-does-it-matter%2F">“精心挑选的”</a> ——对自主代理的研究表明，在现实环境中，它们的<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.13854.pdf">成功率仅为 10% 左右</a>。</p><h3>克服限制</h3><p>企业不应将法学硕士的应用简单地限制在其局限性不适用或错误不重要的常规情况下（例如生成新产品创意以供进一步考虑），而应在设计所有实施时考虑到这些限制，并通过以下方式对其进行补充：人类监督和其他技术。</p><p>当企业将法学硕士融入其运营时，让人员参与其中至关重要。这应包括验证人工智能生成的输出，以增强对该技术的信心。它还可以扩展到让专家将业务问题转化为人工智能的提示，并通过适当调整输入的上下文和细微差别来确保模型提供的信息充足。</p><p>除了思考如何打造人类和人工智能的最佳系统之外，企业还应该探索能够解决法学硕士局限性的互补技术。在这个快速发展的领域，新的创新不断涌现，有望增强技术的能力，因此不断更新您的理解也至关重要。</p><p>例如，为了增强<em>推理</em>能力，研究人员正在探索<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.07697.pdf">使用推理引擎增强法学硕士</a>，将特定领域的信息编码到代表专业概念和事实之间关系的<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.01157.pdf">知识图</a>中。研究人员还在训练专门的模型来评估提示中的前提与法学硕士输出之间的逻辑一致性。为了增强<em>知识</em>和<em>专业知识</em>，法学硕士正在接受特定领域数据库的培训，例如<a href="https://www.wired.com/story/chatgpt-can-help-doctors-and-hurt-patients/">Google 和 DeepMind 的 Med-PaLM 模型</a>，该模型已被证明在美国医疗执照考试中显着优于通用法学硕士。法学硕士的可靠性也可以通过强化学习和<a href="https://github.com/opendilab/awesome-RLHF">从人类专家收集的反馈</a>来提高。法学硕士还可以通过编程在提供答案之前询问澄清的后续问题，从而提高对用户初始提示的理解。</p><p></p><p></p><p>法学硕士几乎具有普遍的适用性，这意味着企业有理由对探索这项强大的新技术感到兴奋。然而，这些模型生成类人文本输出的不可思议的能力很容易导致我们将它们归因于它们不具备的能力。对它们的局限性的正确理解应该指导它们的实施方式和背景。</p><p>在涉及逻辑推理、事实很重要、可复制性至关重要或风险很高的领域，企业应该特别警惕。在这些情况下，公司需要探索使用补充技术来解决法学硕士的局限性——例如知识图、推理引擎和专业领域模型——并确保有适当的人工输入和监督。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>引领透明爆炸时代</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Melissa Swift. <p>Melissa Swift ( <a href="https://twitter.com/meswift">@meswift</a> ) 领导 Capgemini Invent 北美地区的劳动力和组织实践。她是<cite>《现在在这里工作：像人类一样思考并建立强大的工作场所》</cite> （Wiley，2023 年）的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Frank is having a terrible morning. The seasoned CIO wakes up groggy to a flurry of texts from his team, who found out about the CEO’s retirement from LinkedIn because the internal announcement got stuck in everyone’s spam filters. As Frank huffs and puffs around the park during his [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Swift-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>弗兰克度过了一个糟糕的早晨。</p><p>这位经验丰富的首席信息官在他的团队发来的一连串短信中昏昏沉沉地醒来，他们发现首席执行官从 LinkedIn 退休，因为内部公告被困在每个人的垃圾邮件过滤器中。弗兰克在晨跑时在公园里气喘吁吁，他的老板通过电话询问他全新仪表板上的一些令人不安的数字。到达办公室时，他已经感到四面楚歌，当一封电子邮件提醒他公司的另一位领导在“ <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/quittok?lang=en">QuitTok</a> ”上戏剧性地记录了她的离开时，他把冰咖啡吐到了键盘上——已经获得了 50 万的浏览量。</p><p>他早上的大部分时间都在回答一群软件工程师提出的问题，这些工程师发现工作网站上列出的与他们类似的职位的工资比他们目前的工资高出 20%，而他的营销领导团队则反复讨论新仪表板中的数字是否正确。或者旧的电子表格是正确的。午餐前，他的女儿给他发短信：“爸爸。你最近见过你的 Glassdoor 吗？”她截屏了他公司的糟糕评级，并发表了诸如“我无法确定管理层是否愚蠢、罪犯，或者只是愚蠢到犯罪的程度”之类的评论。</p><p></p><p>当弗兰克摇摇晃晃地走向公司食堂时，他已经经历了一周的痛苦。而且现在才中午。</p><p>欢迎在超透明的世界中发挥领导作用。弗兰克是虚构的，但他面临的挑战是真实的。这句古老的陈词滥调是真实的：当今的信息以光速流动……而且它的传播速度太快了，许多领导人都无法应对。无论是社交媒体渠道将公司的脏衣服公开（或者甚至展示“干净内衣”信息——不是诽谤性的，但并不打算被广泛看到），还是内部技术系统将一系列脱离语境的数据扔到那些不准备解释的人们的屏幕上，技术正在严重侵蚀领导者自职场诞生以来就享有的信息优势。</p><h3>再见饮水机的抱怨；你好退出托克</h3><p>知识就是力量——今天，似乎每个人都拥有知识。</p><p>不幸的是， <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/">有关工资、裁员或多元化等劳动力问题</a>以及微观和宏观层面的业务绩效指标的信息越来越多，这意味着普通工人会受到更多坏消息或至少是不舒服的消息的打击。对于领导者和员工来说，这会引发艰难的对话，从而产生有意义的压力源：我一遍又一遍地从客户那里听到，即使是经验最丰富的领导者也常常难以参与这些具有挑战性的对话，导致双方在离开时更加不安。当他们开始的时候。</p><p>如今，领导者的行动立即在内部和外部平台上以书面形式进行大规模讨论。仅内部消息应用 Slack 就拥有<em>每秒</em>发送 300,000 条消息，每天有 1.45 亿人登录 Microsoft Teams 进行类似讨论。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>每月有 5500 万人使用公司反馈平台 Glassdoor，7.74 亿人在 LinkedIn 上谈论工作。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>截至 2023 年 4 月，带有 #QuitTok 标签的社交媒体内容浏览量已达到惊人的 4100 万次。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>对战略领导决策的反应仅限于饮水机里的抱怨的日子早已一去不复返了。</p><p></p><p>那么，在一个人人都知道一切并无时无刻不在谈论的世界里，领导者如何才能保持理智和高效呢？组织可以采取哪些措施来确保在嘈杂的噪音中发出适当的信号，并且噪音不会挑战他们自上而下雇用的每个人的福祉？</p><p></p><h3>领导者的四项实用策略</h3><p>以下是在超透明世界中实现理智和清晰的四种途径。</p><p> <strong>1. 通过提高组织诚实度来减轻领导者的负担。</strong>阻止困难对话的进行似乎是不可能的，但一位客户最近向我阐明了一个简单的策略：“当我们更加诚实时，对我们的领导者来说会更容易。这样，他们就不必进行那么多艰难的对话。”这句话确实有道理。如果人们无论如何都会看到特定情况的现实，那么从跳跃中就这一现实进行沟通意味着个人领导者在面对团队时不必手忙脚乱和后退。</p><p>现在，这是否需要向每位观众传达每种情况的每一个细节？绝对不。它的真正含义是改变每次沟通的框架，从“我们希望人们相信什么？”到“人们在这种情况下做出明智决策需要哪些基本事实和背景？”这改变了信息级联的性质。</p><p>在旧模型中，领导者将配备一组静态消息，组织认为这些消息将不受干扰地传递到团队手中，并毫无疑问地（或至少礼貌地）采取行动。在新模型中，组织更专注于为一系列新出现的事实建立背景——隐含的理解是，具有挑战性甚至矛盾的信息可能会不请自来。目标从强加一组想法转变为发起讨论，以最大限度地减少人际摩擦并最大限度地提高富有成效的行动，即使存在分歧或信息不断变化。</p><p> <strong>2. 在“同一个世界”的基础上重新构建沟通——结束内部/外部的区别。</strong>人们常说，我们生活在一个上下文崩溃的世界，信息在看似完全不同的通信圈中即时传播，而这些通信圈在过去是断开的或至少是按时间顺序排列的。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>过去，领导者通常会先进行内部沟通，然后再根据信息深思熟虑地选择外部人物。如今，一旦发生某件事，他们可以合理地假设，它将很快在内部和外部、广泛的受众中广为人知。为了解决这一现实，许多组织合并了内部和外部沟通职能，或者迄今已责成以外部为重点的沟通部门确保向内部利益相关者传递消息的一致性。以统一的方式塑造沟通不仅可以在容易泄露的世界中创建稳定的消息传递，而且通常还可以提高内部沟通工作的标准——因为内部消息与向外界发布的声明一样严格地进行压力测试。</p><p>即使组织没有相应地重组其沟通职能，个别领导者也可以努力确保他们的信息在内部和外部受众之间保持一致。虽然这是一项值得尝试的做法，但它可能是一种微妙的平衡行为：领导者面临着模仿社交媒体帖子等语言的挑战，同时敦促他们的同事和主管确保发布足够的信息来满足好奇的内部利益相关者的需求。</p><p> <strong>3.“回到未来”学习基本沟通技巧——但要增加 21 世纪的情商。</strong>尽管超透明的世界是一系列快速发展的技术的产物，但在这种情况下，最终的超级领导力显然是低技术含量的：能够说或写出简单、清晰的句子。就像钟声在拥挤的城镇广场上划破喧嚣一样，具有出色基本沟通技巧的领导者更擅长在喧嚣中让别人听到自己的声音。在刺激快速而疯狂地传递（例如通过社交媒体或内部聊天渠道）并且信息可能从某种程度上到完全不准确的情况下，特别需要简洁的口头交流。我们需要有能力喊“别动！”让每个人都停下来思考。</p><p></p><p>历来被允许支支吾吾或大言不惭的领导者会发现自己很快就会被当代沟通流的冲击力所淹没——无论这些流是否真实或对业务进展是否有帮助。综上所述，仅靠事实和逻辑是不够的。一句伟大的句子一如既往（经典写作指南<cite>《风格的要素》</cite>在 100 多年后仍然保持良好状态），但科学已经教会了我们很多关于人们如何吸收信息的知识。例如，引发情绪反应的信息更有可能在社交媒体上转发，从而使其传播得更快、更广泛。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>被教导要冷静、不带感情色彩地沟通的领导者可能会发现，他们的信息在组织中传播的速度不如同事的情绪化言论那么快。</p><p>在一个超透明的世界中，我们甚至可能想要看看神经科学的发现，这些发现警告我们，区分理性思维和情感思维完全是一种错误的二分法，因此，我们应该停止尝试制作完全无情感的领导信息。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> <strong>4. 增强你和你的团队的判断力。</strong>让我们假设世界和工作场所的透明度从现在开始只会增加。在这样的环境中，你快速而明智地决定如何处理一条信息的能力（你的判断）成为生存和成功的关键工具。领导者希望自己有意识地提高这项技能，但鉴于他们不可能一直参与大量对话中的每一次，他们也希望自己的团队能够更好地做出判断。几年前，我曾工作过的一家银行开始为一线员工提供一些以前为高层管理人员保留的领导力发展机会，其基本原理是，随着信息的可用性增加，这些员工也会获得同样的机会。过去，这些呼叫需要在链条上的许多步骤中进行。</p><p>即使当您不在场时，即使面对奇怪且相互矛盾的信息，能够相信您的团队会做正确的事情也具有巨大的价值。在这方面，练习情景规划是一个有用的工具，即使对于那些可能天生没有很强判断力的团队成员也是如此。对于团队练习评估信息的准确性以做出更好的决策也很有帮助。在生成式人工智能正在兴起的世界中，这是一项关键技能。</p><p></p><p></p><p>当领导者掌握了一些实用策略时，领导一个超透明的世界就不必像驾驶一艘摇摇晃晃的航天器穿过充满冲突、不完整且常常充满情绪信息的小行星带一样。有时我们可能都会经历弗兰克的早晨，但我们也可以经历弗兰克的下午——他清理了日历，开始专注于与公司内外合适的人进行正确的讨论。</p><p>六个月后，有人在社交媒体频道上发布了有关弗兰克公司的帖子：“管理并不完美，但他们试图保持诚实，我非常欣赏。他们确实在努力做正确的事情，这一点你每天都能看到。”</p><p>弗兰克喜欢并分享了这条信息。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为未来的工作构建神经多样性人才管道</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodiversity-talent-pipeline-for-the-future-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodiversity-talent-pipeline-for-the-future-of-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maureen Dunne. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/maureen-n-dunne-ph-d-a2609a45/details/experience/">Maureen Dunne</a>博士是全球公认的神经多样性专家，也是美国第三大社区学院联盟伊利诺伊州社区学院受托人协会的前主席。她是即将<cite>出版的《神经多样性优势：拥抱自闭症、多动症、诵读困难和任何组织的其他神经学差异的基本指南》一书</cite>的作者（Wiley，2024 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Neurodiversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition & Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images During recent economic policy updates, Jerome Powell, chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve, announced that the American labor market is suffering from a structural labor shortage. Its origins are varied — demographic variables such as an aging population and early retirements, the tragic loss or persistent absence of many [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Dunne-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>在最近的经济政策更新中，美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔宣布，美国劳动力市场正面临<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/01/11/briefing/labor-shortage.html">结构性劳动力短缺</a>。其根源各不相同——人口老龄化和提前退休、COVID-19大流行导致许多工人的悲惨损失或持续缺勤以及移民历史性下降等人口变量——但现在的数字太大了忽略。截至去年底，每个可用工人大约有两个职位空缺，劳动力缺口扩大到约1000万工人。政治经济学家<a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2022/09/20/american-post-pandemic-labor-shortage-explained/">尼古拉斯·埃伯施塔特这样表述</a>：“是的，美国面临着大萧条规模的工作问题。”</p><p>与此同时，估计有 30% 到 40% 的神经分歧成年人<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/20/-neurodivergent-workers-help-companies-meet-the-demand-for-talent.html">目前失业</a>。受过大学教育的自闭症患者的失业率可能<a href="https://www.benefitnews.com/news/how-to-create-equitable-workplace-experiences-for-autistic-talent">高达 85%</a> 。目前，美国约有 5000 万人以及 <a href="https://dceg.cancer.gov/about/diversity-inclusion/inclusivity-minute/2022/neurodiversity">全球 15% 至 20% 的人口</a>处于神经分歧的范围内。</p><p></p><p>神经多样性范式主张采用基于优势的方法来理解，包括和评价具有认知类型的神经分歧个体，例如自闭症、注意力缺陷/多动障碍、阅读障碍、计算障碍、联觉和运用障碍等。太多神经分歧的人被遗漏了。这种失败不仅仅是道德问题。在高等教育、我们的工作场所和我们的社区中，缺乏成功且真正的包容神经多样性的途径，这会产生切实的影响，并阻碍世界各地组织的成功。由于有如此多的职位空缺和大量可能的候选人没有得到满足，解决这些不平衡的理论上的双赢解决方案当然值得探索。</p><h3>认知多样性和未来的工作场所</h3><p>利用神经分化个体的潜力可以帮助雇主建立一支更适合未来的劳动力队伍。创造力、横向（或非线性）思维、解决问题的逆向工程、复杂的视觉空间技能、系统思维、直觉洞察力、高度专注和多感官模式识别——神经分歧候选人可能擅长的独特领域——所有这些都将变得越来越重要，因为人工智能已融入我们的日常生活。</p><p>神经分歧型领导人已经在包括军队在内的各个行业占据了高层职位，尽管许多人不愿透露自己的地位。有充分的证据表明，当这些人处于有效且合适的工作环境中时，他们在一系列职位上的表现与神经质同龄人一样好，甚至更好。摩根大通工作自闭症项目负责人詹姆斯·马奥尼 (James Mahoney) 表示，一项内部研究发现，在正确入职的情况下，自闭症员工<a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/viewpoint-how-to-become-a-champion-for-employees-with-autism.aspx">的工作效率比同等职位的神经正常同事高出 140%</a> 。</p><p></p><p>没有两个神经分歧的人是相同的，考虑到不同的人表现出自己独特的优势和挑战，重视各种思想的丰富性和多样性非常重要。也就是说，越来越多的证据表明，不同的神经类型和不常见的技能之间存在相关性，例如原创性或创新思维能力的提高。大量研究的结果表明，神经发散认知与创造力和创新思维的增强呈正相关，并且自闭症患者比一般人群更不容易出现认知偏差，并且<a href="https://psyche.co/ideas/autistic-people-challenge-preconceived-ideas-about-rationality">在做出理性决策时更加一致</a>。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这些独特的观点和技能本质上对雇主在个人层面上有价值，同时提供了额外的群体级别价值作为对集体思维的关键对冲。</p><p></p><h3>社区大学人才管道</h3><p>很大一部分神经异常的人开始了在社区大学的高等教育之旅；一项2015年的一项研究发现，在自闭症上学的人中，有多达80％的人参加了一所社区大学。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>将神经差异带入商业经济的努力应开始或至少与这些机构合作，并可能是改变神经多样性友好的就业机会途径的游戏规则改变者。</p><p>鉴于美国最高法院最近对<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/">大学录取决定的多样性</a>裁决所定的基调，这可能是尤其如此的，该裁决剥夺了精英大学生机构的多样性。致力于这样一种观念的公司，各种多样性都是无价的资产，可能需要更具创造性地思考可以找到多样性的地方。</p><p>然后，负担依靠社区大学的学生扩大机会途径。在担任伊利诺伊州社区学院受托人协会主席期间，我们希望激励社区学院，地方和地区经济发展组织和雇主之间的合作。全州工作委员会的第一个未来，旨在促进与雇主的直接行业合作伙伴关系，以为学生，社区和企业创造新的机会途径，并促进有关新兴行业和职业的对话。</p><h3>与行业建造桥梁</h3><p>英镑，社区大学系统是我们生产合格候选人的最有效方法，以满足教育系统最终用户的需求：公司经济。但是，只有在从一开始就培养和维持的神经多样性友好的机会途径，雇主才能利用该人才池的全部深度和广度。</p><p>社区大学已经充当满足当地雇主需求的强大合作伙伴。如果他们提供诸如心理健康支持，专业辅导，时间管理工具，执行功能指导以及同伴导航员等环绕式支持，神经厌恶的学生将更有可能在学位完成和随后的工作中浏览学位的道路。</p><p>学徒制，付费实习和与社区雇主的工作障碍机会在弥合赚取技能和成功就业之间的差距中起着关键作用。许多社区学院提供了“赚钱和学习”模式的学徒制，例如杜佩奇学院的项目雇用学徒计划，雇主在这里支付学生的学费，以帮助他们在开发新技能的同时学习新技能工作经验在相关角色中工作。</p><p></p><p>鉴于神经化的人在该领域工作，网络安全为此类计划的目标行业提供了一个很好的例子。根据美国劳工统计局的，信息安全分析师职位预计将从<a href="https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/information-security-analysts.htm">2022年到2030年增长32％</a> 。全国各地的社区学院，包括芝加哥城市学院和拿骚社区学院，提供了更多负担得起的网络安全证书计划，该计划将候选人定位在当地需求的职业道路上。基于能力的教育，例如刘易斯和克拉克社区学院的焊接技术计划，代表了一个同样有吸引力的框架，可以为有不同需求的学习者提供灵活的选择，通过技能掌握铺平了赚取的学分的途径。</p><p>神经多样性运动提高了人们对神经异常求职者的才能的认识，并在上学教育和工业之间发展了更强大的协作计划。例如，彭博社报道说，美国情报服务已开始寻找<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-18/people-on-the-autism-spectrum-may-be-ideal-for-some-ai-work#xj4y7vzkg">神经化社区</a>，以增强他们的机器学习和网络安全实践。目睹<a href="https://businesschief.com/human-capital/top-7-companies-hiring-and-nurturing-neurodiverse-talent">EY，JPMORGAN，MICROSOFT</a>和其他备受瞩目的公司之后，完全不同行业的公司遵循诉讼，利用了优先考虑多样性的优势。</p><p>这些努力提供了路线图。行业合作伙伴，经济发展协会和社区大学之间的合作，这些社区学院利用神经多样性友好的环绕式支持计划，学徒制，付费实习和造成工作范围的计划代表了劳动力市场生态系统中的一项新功能。通过依靠这一趋势，我们有机会培养了一条准备工作的神经化的人才管道，能够对合格候选人的外观挑战过时的，无效的假设。</p><h3>在办公的地方</h3><p>为了真正利用神经化的人才库，工作安置协调员和雇主必须实施正确的流程。在雇主方面，人力资源部门应审查招聘和招聘实践，并强调包容性。他们还应努力进一步将同事和管理层的入职策略制度化，以促进对如何支持神经运动团队的更深入的了解。</p><p>从实际层面上讲，这可能需要在入职期间为神经差异人员提供指导 - 提供明确的成功指标，避免歧义，并允许普遍访问噪声遇到的耳机以及其他适应性的工具和实践。此外，在熟悉的环境中，一些神经差异的人的生产力要高得多，因此证明对混合或远程工作场所协议的开放性可能表明对他们的需求更加接受态度。</p><p></p><p>但是，当组织文化未能接受心理安全，信任，反欺凌政策和明确的沟通标准时，这些步骤几乎没有影响。换句话说，无论您有多少阳光和水，花园都不会在有毒的土壤中生长。赌注很高，对于愿意接受真实的神经多样性包容和归属感的前瞻性组织而言，收益可能是巨大的。但是，化妆品的努力不会产生任何影响。</p><p>通过打击刻板印象；允许灵活的结果驱动的工作安排；并促进热情的组织文化，在人们不需要掩盖其认知差异的情况下，我们可以开始集体利用神经多样性劳动力的全部潜力。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodrovesity-talent-pipeline-pipeline-futor-the-future-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>数据科学中连接器角色的兴起</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas C. Redman and Thomas H. Davenport . <p>Thomas C. Redman 是 Data Quality Solutions 总裁，也是<a href="https://www.koganpage.com/hr-learning-development/people-and-data-9781398610828"><em>《People and Data: Uniteding to Transform Your Organization》</em></a> （Kogan Page，2023 年）一书的作者。 Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) 是巴布森学院信息技术与管理学校长杰出教授、牛津大学赛德商学院客座教授以及麻省理工学院数字经济项目研究员。他是<a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047241/working-with-ai/"><em>《Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration》</em></a> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Science]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images For all of the current focus on using data, analytics, and AI to improve organizational decisions and operations, too many data science projects fail. Even for those that succeed, progress is often slow and expensive. Why? Organizational gaps between teams are wreaking havoc with the ability to develop, apply, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Redman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>对于所有当前使用数据，分析和AI来改善组织决策和运营的关注，太多的数据科学项目失败了。即使对于那些成功的人来说，进展往往也是缓慢且昂贵的。为什么？团队之间的组织差距正在造成破坏，具有开发，应用和扩展数据科学项目的能力。需要一种新的角色来弥合这些差距。</p><p>让我们不要最大程度地减少可以使公司绊倒的数据科学的许多方面 - 从定义正确的业务问题到开发解决方案，然后正确支持它。但是，我们对这种情况的诊断，部分与我们的同事罗杰·霍尔（Roger Hoerl）和迭戈·库恩（Diego Kuonen）进行了研究，这表明，许多公司在解决方案方面的挣扎较少，而在组织问题上进行了更多的工作。</p><p></p><p>我们已经确定了三个根本原因。首先，数据科学已被<a href="https://hbr.org/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone">“固定在组织图表上”</a> 。当数据科学用于相对较少的问题时，这可能是可以接受的，但是现在需要在数据科学对每个团队重要的情况下构建。</p><p>其次，数据科学旨在改善日常运营和决策，这意味着中断。但是，大多数线路经理都在努力控制，可预测性和毫无意义。鉴于破坏和控制是极地对立的，因此线路管理和数据科学之间的张力要大得多。</p><p>第三，许多公司似乎期望数据科学家能够做到这一切：神奇地了解业务及其所有细微差别，处理数据质量问题，并说服顽固的经理和工作人员改变其长期以来的流程。许多数据科学家更喜欢简单地创建更好的算法，这意味着这些其他任务通常会遇到短暂的shrift。</p><p>无法最大程度地减少这些问题 - 它们是深刻的，结构性的，并且通常是政治性的，并且很可能需要其他管理策略。在这里，我们将解决组织问题的一个关键方面，即抑制数据科学模型发展和部署的各个部门之间的差距。</p><h3>用连接器缩小间隙</h3><p>弥合组织差距的明显方法是将他们充满。我们通常将这些角色<em>连接器</em>中的人称为。一段时间以来，公司分配了具有工作头衔的人员，例如系统分析师，业务分析师，承保官和系统工程师，以缩小业务和技术部门之间的差距。他们还试图弥合数据科学项目中出现的差距，标记负责这样做的人，数据牧马人，数据工程师，紫色人员和翻译人员。</p><p>尽管许多这样的努力有助于将数据科学项目移动，但通常感觉像是一款精心制作的whack-a摩尔游戏：封闭一个差距，另一个差距弹出。另外，仅这些努力并不能解决一些相关的问题：</p><ul><li>线经理和数据科学家通常不了解彼此。这使得双方特别困难就可以解决问题，并使数据科学家在所需数据中获得和理解细微差别。</li><li>实施模型需要在业务中进行广泛的更改：重新设计的流程，培训模型的工作原理，并为运行它们而努力。</li><li>双方可能看不到IT基础设施决策，例如与技术债务有关的决策。</li></ul><p>由于这些原因，我们建议公司以这三个步骤以更纪律的方式处理该问题。</p><p> <strong>1.定义数据科学项目流程并确定相关人员。</strong>尽管细节可能会有所不同，但该过程应始于构建问题并了解业务上下文，并以监视/更新生产中的新模型结束。关键工作：确定数据科学团队以外的人必须参与每个步骤。</p><p>例如，在解决问题并选择一个项目时，公司希望参与高级领导者和中层管理人员，他们的团队将受到影响。当是时候获取和准备数据时，了解数据细微差别的商业领域专家以及准备数据的IT专业人员应该在房间里。开发模型时，应咨询外部软件提供商。当需要将模型插入流程，业务和流程分析师，受影响流程的经理，培训师和变革专业人员的经理时，都应参与其中。最后，随着组织将模型部署到IT基础架构中，然后监视并更新它时，IT专业人员，构建数据管道以及供应链经理应做出贡献。</p><p> <strong>2.评估连接器可以提供帮助的地方。</strong>本质上，此步骤旨在阐明差距。问：“所有参与的人是否完全联系在一起 - 也就是说，他们了解自己的角色，并且是否有足够的沟通以使工作以相当有效的方式完成？”</p><p>我们发现，答案通常是“否”。确实，我们发现连接器通常以以下方式至关重要：</p><ul><li>通过数据科学解决了要解决的问题：例如，高管可能已经听到了围绕AI的炒作，但对它可以帮助解决的问题或整个组织中的技术潜力缺乏足够深的了解。</li><li>在商业和技术人员之间翻译 - 一个古老的差距尚未封闭。</li><li>处理数据质量问题。</li><li>交流团队中的需求，进度和问题 - 换句话说，将数据科学项目的许多部分绑在一起，并成为不同团队之间的连接器。</li><li>当没有其他人看到大局时，跟踪进步朝着部署和组织变革的整体目标。</li></ul><p> <strong>3.阐明连接器的特定角色并将其放置在适当的位置。</strong>对于单个项目，此步骤通常很简单。我们建议公司还考虑在整个数据科学计划与其他业务之间具有连接器。线经理之间存在 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/to-succeed-with-data-science-first-build-the-bridge/">自然的紧张关系</a>，他们努力地在日常工作中建立控制的量度，而数据科学专业人士则旨在破坏事情。</p><p></p><p>不受组织的检查，这种张力使数据科学团队在公司内建立自己非常困难。计划级别的连接器旨在缓解这种紧张关系：它们帮助高级企业领导者了解数据科学的潜力和挑战，帮助数据科学领导者了解业务面临的最高问题，并建立与企业保持一致的数据科学项目的组合需要。</p><p></p><h3>公司现在正在尝试哪些公司</h3><p>鉴于建立组织成功的组织能力是如此重要，我们很高兴看到公司通过各种连接器角色进行实验和享受成功。例如，地区银行和许多其他组织利用端到端观点的数据产品经理。根据最近<a href="https://aws.amazon.com/data/cdo-report/">对首席数据官的调查</a>，现在有40％的组织采用数据产品管理方法。</p><p>科威特的海湾银行已经建立了一个数据大使网络，以领导部门级别的质量和数据科学项目。瑞士联邦统计办公室采用“数据科学桥”来协调其许多统计功能。克罗格（Kroger）的数据科学子公司84.51º拥有一组它所谓的解决方案设计顾问 - 具有业务背景的人在数据科学家和业务利益相关者之间进行调解。 （84.51º是指子公司辛辛那提办公室的纵向位置，就像经度地图的早期供应商一样，该公司对复杂的数据问题有意义。）克罗格（Kroger数据科学项目从启动到持续的管理层，并使所有各方告知。许多其他组织还采用了此类连接器角色和工具。</p><p>让我们更详细地研究地区银行和瑞士联邦统计办公室的工作。</p><h4>地区银行的数据产品合作伙伴</h4><p>地区银行首席数据和分析官Manav Misra观察到，许多数据科学项目没有成功实施，因此他建立了<em>数据产品</em>的概念以及<em>数据产品合作伙伴</em>的新连接器角色来管理它们。</p><p> Misra将数据产品定义为企业遇到的问题的端到端软件解决方案。他说：“数据产品利用数据和高级分析来提供该解决方案。”数据产品合作伙伴是数据产品经理和与企业合作伙伴一起运作，他们随着时间的推移将产品实现并管理它们。</p><p>每个数据产品合作伙伴都被分配给银行的特定业务或支持部门，并参加与业务合作伙伴的员工会议，以便更好地了解其优先事项。大多数合作伙伴来自银行的业务方面，尽管有些也有分析背景。</p><p>数据产品合作伙伴的工作包括了解业务部门和最终用户的需求，并使用最低可行的产品开始开发周期。在该过程的早期阶段，数据产品合作伙伴是双向翻译人员，将分析和AI的机会与业务需求联系起来。在后期阶段，他们负责评估如何采用和使用完整的解决方案，监视用户界面的工作状况，跟踪有多少人使用它，并确保产品提供或超过该产品中承诺的价值原始业务案例。</p><h4>瑞士的数据科学桥</h4><p>瑞士的联邦统计办公室认识到，如果要满足瑞士政府不断增长的需求，就需要改善其核心数据科学流程，因此它创建了一个数据科学能力中心，这是一种卓越中心。为了确保能力中心与瑞士政府的其他地区完全连接，领导人配备了“数据科学桥”，这是一组专门负责<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-data-science-management-process/">管理六个高级流程的</a>连接器：</p><ul><li>驾驶协作。</li><li>发展人力资本。</li><li>确保数据质量。</li><li>管理项目组合。</li><li>确保积极的业务影响。</li><li>确保以人为本和值得信赖的数据科学应用。</li></ul><p>这座桥正在支付真正的股息。它促进了客户群中的实践社区，帮助人们成为数据工具和报告的更有效的用户，并鼓励他们根据通用语言和理解来交换他们在数据科学和AI方面的经验。在上面列出的六个过程中，该桥正在减少混乱。</p><p>此外，“最重要的决定是在桥上做出的，”库宁指出，他是瑞士数据科学政府的顾问。 （Kuonen还是Statoo Consulting的负责人，Statoo Consulting是一家位于瑞士的咨询公司，也是日内瓦大学经济与管理学院数据科学教授。）Kuonen认为，随着其成熟的成熟，该桥梁将带来更多的价值。</p><h3>连接器管理挑战：五个要问的问题</h3><p>尽管连接器显然具有优势，但管理它们仍带来了一些棘手的问题。在某些方面，连接器在组织图中的“空白空间”中运行，管理层总是很艰难。例如，公司在试图使公司各个数据元素的定义保持一致时，管理数据管理员的运气并没有太多运气。</p><p>公司在定义连接器角色时应该考虑以下问题。答案会因组织情况而有所不同，但是某些模式开始出现。</p><p></p><p> <strong>1.连接器在组织上应该在哪里？</strong>最常见的是，连接器位于主要数据和分析官或数据科学组织下，但有时会在业务组中找到。如果该公司在矩阵管理中成功担任其他角色，则连接器可以向这两个领域报告。</p><p> <strong>2.公司应该如何吸引，评估和保留连接器？</strong>正如数据专家<a href="https://tdan.com/how-to-find-the-right-tweener-for-your-organization/31029">特蕾莎·库什纳（Theresa Kushner）指出的</a>那样，鉴于连接器的角色需要了解业务和数据以及相当大的软技能，因此连接器角色具有挑战性。现在，商学院有数百个分析和数据科学学位课程，这是招募连接器的好地方。组建一个连接团队的组织通常会要求业务领导者评估候选人的此类角色；例如，宝洁（Procter＆Gamble）要求领导者确定每个候选人帮助实现的“突破业务结果”。保留很大程度上取决于为这些员工提供可行的职业道路。</p><p> <strong>3.什么是连接器职业道路？</strong>经验丰富的技术人员很可能认识到需要连接器的需求，但担心如果扮演这样的角色，他们将失去技术优势。经验丰富的商人可能不想在其业务部门或职能中脱离当前的职业道路。在短期内，公司应在数据科学组织中建立越来越多的责任感的角色，例如高级和富有补偿的数据产品经理。我们认为，从长远来看，许多组织都希望每个高级高管都在其背景下具有数据科学经验。</p><p> <strong>4.是否需要多种连接器？</strong>由于某些连接的级别非常高，而其他连接则集中在详细的技术级别上，因此合乎逻辑的答案是“是”。但是，一家公司可能无法负担为一个项目雇用多个项目，因此一些公司也要求数据产品经理也发挥低级连接器的作用。其他组织要求连接器一次在两个或多个项目中扮演角色。</p><p> <strong>5.连接器的职责到底是什么？</strong>由于连接器可能具有一个项目的最佳整体视图，因此通常会向他们收取端到头的管理（就像数据产品经理的角色一样）。如果连接器经历了，并且他们理解并重视数据科学项目的技术角色，这是合适的。如果他们不这样做，则应该更限制其连接器责任，例如不涉及项目成功端到端责任的翻译角色。</p><p>随着时间的推移，您的组织将出现这些问题的更详细的答案。</p><p></p><p>在我们与已成功使用连接角色的公司的合作中，有关的软件供应商和数据科学领导者告诉我们，随着连接器的增殖，数据科学项目的部署百分比已经增加。我们认为，这是一系列重要且持续的角色，几乎每个大型公司都需要进一步的制度化。否则，数据科学可能会成为一门令人沮丧的科学，其部署百分比较低，而改善业务绩效的记录很差。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>问三阴：我怎样才能说服自己我属于领导者？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-in-readhips//<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-i-belong-in-leadhips/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang 是一位 CEO 教练，领导杜克大学 Fuqua/Coach K 领导力与道德中心 (COLE)。需要建议吗？将<a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">电子邮件发送给Sanyin</a> 。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managerial Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Pinnolis/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images I have just moved up to an executive job, and while I know I’m ready, I don’t feel very confident in front of my team. I was the first in my family to go to college and still carry the feeling of having to prove I belong, even though [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AskSanyin_Col05_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Pinnolis/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question">我刚刚从事高管工作，虽然我知道我已经准备好了，但在团队面前我并不有信心。我是我家庭中第一个上大学的人，仍然有证明自己属于的感觉，即使我在这家公司的成就方面有记录。我该如何打击冒名顶替综合症并感觉像个领导者？</p><p>不要因为体验冒名顶替综合症而殴打自己。在扮演更高级角色时，一些自我怀疑是正常的。当您与团队成员建立新的关系时，您可以将其转变为有力的东西，而不是试图放逐它。</p><p>冒名顶替综合症被视为对我们的能力的关注，但是我认为这是由于我们是否觉得自己属于特定的空间引起了人们的关注。关于被看到，包括和接受的不安全感是您团队中其他人有时可能会感到的关系。</p><p></p><p>冒名顶替综合症的最佳解毒剂之一，尤其是对于处于领导地位的人来说，是建立一种归属感和社区感。通过建立联系并促进他人的包容性，我们还可以为自己创造更大的归属感和信心。经理可以使用三种实践来增加包容性并激发团队成员之间的信心。</p><p><strong>承认贡献。</strong>人们在会议上大声疾呼可能需要勇气。但是，当我们无法充分认识说话者或不给予信誉的情况下采用他们的想法时，他们可能会让会议感到闻所未闻或没有欣赏。养成当下承认人们的习惯：“这是一个新的想法 - 谢谢”或“以汤姆的想法为基础……”。经理可以并且必须营造一种氛围，在这里团队成员感到欢迎他们的贡献。</p><p><strong>进行良好的介绍。</strong>通过向人们介绍其优势，专业知识和历史的评论来建立一种归属感。良好的介绍可以帮助他人了解人的角色及其带来的价值，但他们也增强了该人的自我意识，并确认了他们对职责的所有权。作为领导者，以这种方式将团队成员介绍给公司以外的人可能特别有意义。它显示了对他们的尊重，并确认它们很重要。</p><p></p><p><strong>强调超级大国。</strong>我相信每个人都有一个无与伦比的固有礼物 - 他们的超级大国 - 当您在实践中看到一个人的超级大国，这一点很重要。这些能力通常是看不见的，未发现或最小化的。直到有敏锐的领导者或同事指出他们之前，我们许多人都不认识他们。帮助员工看到他们的礼物可以使内心的声音保持安静，告诉他们他们不属于他们。</p><p>经历冒名顶替综合症的领导者通常是那些从较少特权的背景中扮演角色，遵循非传统道路或来自代表性不足的人群群体的领导者。这些经历可以建立我们对自己脆弱性的认识，并了解我们能够独自控制的局限性，即谦卑。为团队成员增添真正的同情心，并猜测什么：您拥有那种在这些挑战时期最有效的领导者的特征。您的团队将为您的领导而拥抱。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-i-belong-in-leadhips/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>多元化推动</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paola Cecchi-Dimeglio. <p>Paola Cecchi-Dimeglio（ <a href="https://twitter.com/hlspaola">@HLSPAOLA</a> ）是妇女和少数民族律师的执行领导力研究计划主席，也是哈佛法学院法律职业中心的高级研究员。她是<cite>《多样性红利：小变革的变革力量，以消除公司偏见、吸引多元化人才、更好地管理每个人——以及赚更多钱》（</cite>麻省理工学院出版社，2023 年）一书的作者，本改编即取自该书。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Roy Scott/Ikon Images Despite their commitments to diversifying their workforces, many companies continue to struggle with attracting, hiring, and retaining employees from underrepresented groups. Achieving workplace diversity is not easy, but leaders can target, address, and nudge specific data points and thoughtfully incentivize behaviors that support it. These interventions are often small, easy to implement, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Cecchi-Dimeglio_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">罗伊·斯科特（Roy Scott）/伊肯（Ikon）图像</p></figcaption></figure><p>尽管他们致力于多元化劳动力，但许多公司仍在努力吸引，招聘和保留人数不足的群体的员工。</p><p>实现工作场所多元化并不容易，但领导者可以瞄准、解决和推动特定的数据点，并深思熟虑地激励支持它的行为。这些干预措施通常很小，易于实施且价格便宜，但是当它们应用于吸引人，招聘，人员的入职以及员工路径周期中的选择，过程和组织杠杆时，它们可以帮助使工作场所变得更加多样化。和包容性。</p><p></p><h3>推销吸引多样性的人才</h3><p>一个电子商务巨头的转换率（CRS）在购物者的某些细分市场中，包括有色人种和中等收入LGBTQIA+人的目标。同时，该公司的主要竞争对手成功地雇用了更多的女性，黑人和拉丁人，太平洋岛民和LGBTQIA+在营销，行为分析和其他角色的人，他们的不同观点正在转化为更高的CRS。</p><p>该公司发起了一项重要的运动，以吸引多样化的人才。它聘请了一家搜索公司，该公司投掷了全国网，并运行了印刷和数字广告，该广告强调了公司对多样性和包容性的承诺。然后，领导人坐下来等待那些不同的候选人出现。在广告闪电战之后的三个半星期内，在线作业发布的景色达到了顶峰，但在第七周就坦率地挂着。不到11％的现场访问者申请了职位。只有三名申请人接受了采访；两个收到的报价，其中一个被拒绝。换句话说，如果您以令人印象深刻的资源和巨大的费用来构建它，那么它们仍然可能不会来。</p><p>正如这家公司发现的那样，仅仅吸引您吸引的潜在候选人的关注是不够的。将适当的人才转换为申请人和候选人需要额外的外展和培养。来自代表性不足的人口统计的人（包括有色人种，被识别为LGBTQIA+的人以及残疾人）通常与竞争性雇主的联系更少，并且知道可以帮助他们在申请过程中导航的人更少。想要提高多样性的组织可以通过使用淡淡的人才（在人才获取过程中提出的语言和内容修改）来吸引更多代表性群体的候选人，这有助于产生多样化的候选人池，在整个过程中维持池，鼓励顶级候选人。接受工作机会，并帮助他们继续上车。</p><p></p><p>午睡可以帮助建立信任并尽早减少信息不对称。在此类干预措施中，一家公司在其领导层中展示了女性和代表性不足的人的数量，以及其多样性和包容性目标和时间表，以及在线职位发布旁边。屏幕右下角的视频中有首席执行官谈到了他对包容和多样性的承诺。这项干预措施增加了妇女和代表性不足的群体的百分比，这些群体在短期内申请了22％，长期申请了18％。来自不同社会经济背景的候选人总体上升了17％。而且，重要的是，从申请工作到接受职位的转换率上升了8个百分点。</p><p>提高对潜在雇主的熟悉程度的轻推可以在整个过程中帮助维持申请人池。例如，即使求职者不认识公司的某人，促进连接也可以使公司更具吸引力。一项在线实验在提交申请和公司听到之前，将1,276名申请人随机分配给了四个条件之一：</p><ul><li>申请人有机会在申请正在进行时向公司雇用的妇女提出问题。</li><li>申请人有机会在申请正在进行时向公司雇用的男性提出问题。</li><li>申请人有机会问一个由一名男性雇员和一名女雇员组成的小组的问题。</li><li>申请人没有机会问任何员工的问题。</li></ul><p>当妇女可以提出有关该公司雇用的妇女的问题时，这些候选人在面试中的表现要比其他任何条件下的情况要好。他们所评估的访调员评分增长了34％。这些相同的候选人也对申请过程和公司的形象更加满意。那些未收到工作机会的人更有可能在接下来的24个月内重新申请。</p><p>同样，在一家科技公司的在线实验中，我在提交申请后和在收到公司听到之前，将1,478名申请人随机分配给了几个条件之一。一些申请人被分配为求职者作为伙伴，如果他们被选为面试，他们可以与他们一起练习所需的任务；有些则不然。在那些分配好伙伴的申请人中，有些女人与女人配对，有些女人与男人配对，有些男人与男人配对。</p><p> Job seekers who were partnered with a buddy after applying experienced a 40% higher interview selection rate; the impact was particularly notable among underrepresented groups and for junior positions. Women who were paired with men received interview scores that were 9% higher than in other conditions. Candidates participating in the buddy system were more satisfied with the process, even if they were not selected for an interview or if they were interviewed but not offered a position. This increase in satisfaction was 28% for women and 29% for men.</p><p> Having a friend or acquaintance in the industry can reduce the trepidation felt by people who are seeking employment in areas that have traditionally excluded them. These candidates are seeking information: “What is it like?我应该穿什么？我应该如何准备？ What should I say or not say?如果什么 …？” Knowing takes away much of the fear, and potential employers can fill that information gap by recognizing this condition and intervening to redesign the dynamic. Balancing the exchange with information that candidates are seeking mends the divide and engenders trust. Information provided by a potential employer lets candidates decide whether the company is a good fit, whether they can see themselves working there, and whether they will be embraced by the organization.</p><p> Consider the transport and logistics industry, for instance, which is overwhelmingly male-dominated. Closing such a wide gender gap requires creativity. One company that sought to hire more women took photographs of each woman employed at the company. It then graphically illustrated the gender gap by placing the women&#39;s pictures adjacent to a blank space that represented the additional women required to close the gender parity gap. The date by which the organization wanted to hire enough women to fill in the empty space was also included in the illustration.</p><p> Not only did the company display the image and text on its website, but it also talked to all of the relevant search and recruitment firms and launched a major campaign aimed at getting women to apply. Over six months, the efforts produced a 30% increase in female applicants, including more women from underrepresented groups.</p><p> The design of job applications can also affect the number of candidates who apply. Small things like requesting information related to gender and race on applications have proved significant in previous experiments and interventions, but the placement of these requests can either repulse or attract candidates. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> A company study that involved 320 applicants sought to determine the impact of collecting gender information at the beginning of the application, at the end, and not at all. Where gender identity was requested at the end, 7% more women completed the application than in the other two conditions.</p><p></p><h3> Nudges for Recruiting Diverse Talent</h3><p> Dropping demographic indicators from CVs can allow unbiased assessment of the candidate. At one global company, applicants were directed to enter their CVs in an online portal, which made the look, feel, and format identical for everyone. All of the reviewers saw the same thing, and all indicators of race and gender were removed. The stripped data included names, affiliations, volunteer activities associated with a religious or cultural group, hobbies, language skills, or connections to special advocacy or community organizations.</p><p> The removal of such data reduced the likelihood of bias and made job experience the primary focus of the hiring teams. Candidates were also asked to describe their workplace results and contributions. This neutral format focused the assessment process and increased the pool of underrepresented groups, in both Europe and the United States, by roughly 40% within 18 months. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> Applying similar principles during a consulting engagement with a tech company, we used AI voice alteration to mask gender. Candidates used a tool called Gap Jumper to solve skill-based challenges without disclosing their gender, as well as a voice modulation device to anonymize gender and ethnic or racial background. The resulting increase in job offers was almost 16% for women and 18% for members of underrepresented racial groups.</p><p> After a fair and neutral process has been designed, it is still necessary to make a hiring decision. When practicing the art of hiring, a useful strategy is to change the question from “Whom should we include?” to “Whom should we exclude?” In this case, rather than struggling with criteria that indicate who should be chosen, decision makers determine who should be excluded and, from that, are able to identify a smaller group of the strongest candidates. Although this approach might seem counterintuitive in the context of seeking to be more inclusive, it forces decision makers to focus closely on core qualifications and exclude candidates who do not meet them.</p><h3> Nudges for Onboarding Diverse Talent</h3><p> At a global financial services company with multiple offices in the New York City area, several partners were celebrating the hiring of eight new staff members. The group was diverse in gender, race, and age — a mix of millennials, Gen Xers, and a baby boomer.</p><p> The millennials seemed to have no trouble finding their footing, and the Gen Xers were familiar with the organization and had many colleagues who were already part of their network. But the onboarding process didn&#39;t welcome and assimilate Carlton, a Black man in his late 50s hired at the executive level, like it had the seven others. Although he was impressively talented and skilled, Carlton had diminished access to information, and it impacted several of his assigned projects. In less than 18 months, shortly after his first performance review, he left the company for a competitor. His departure measurably damaged the company. In the short term, the cost of replacing him would range between $1.5 million and $1.75 million. In the long term, his assessment of the company as a place of employment would negatively resonate throughout his network.</p><p> The data has found a link between individuals leaving an organization after 12 to 24 months and their onboarding experience — a correlation that stands out more than any other factor in the life of the employee at the company. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> In short, get onboarding right or pay the price.</p><p> An effective onboarding process ensures that new hires are brought fully and inclusively into the organization. Small modifications enable new hires to better navigate this process and access the information and services that can help them integrate comfortably and become productive.</p><p> Like new immigrants, new employees seek information about the norms, policies, politics, and behaviors that will help them function successfully in the new setting. New hires require clarity regarding roles and expectations. They want background information about the company. They want to know how to thrive, what it takes to excel and get promoted, and what it takes to master their jobs. They also want to know what constitutes a high standard and where they should aim.</p><p> One large professional services firm nudged its onboarding process by sending a series of short videos featuring the CEO, some board members, and some members of the executive team to candidates as soon as they received job offers. These three-minute videos were aligned with company strategy and were sent each day for 15 days. They were paired with messaging about the company&#39;s commitment to diversity, what it felt like to be part of the company, what to expect if you were to make a mistake as part of a team, and how people were expected to handle such an occurrence. The videos also discussed what it meant to have equal opportunities to succeed.</p><p> In another variation, the new hires were assigned to a work project for a large client right away. The data showed that the 15 videos plus the assignment to a large project upfront resulted in improved performance among women and individuals from underrepresented groups because the interventions increased job clarity. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> In the banking industry, an effective onboarding nudge featured stakeholder meetings at two weeks, three months, six months, nine months, and 12 months. In the meetings, the hires heard from people who had been at the organization for at least five years, who discussed problems the new employees had encountered during onboarding, how they had overcome those challenges, and their perceptions of the company as they moved through the 12-month process.</p><p> A variation of that approach used intervals of six months, 12 months, 18 months, and 24 months, during which stakeholder meetings took place every six weeks. The result was a higher retention rate for women and underrepresented groups 48 months after hiring.</p><p> One of the important elements of onboarding is the opportunity to create and structure one&#39;s network. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> The network brings with it access to information and opportunities for mentorship. It sets a social-emotional tone and influences how at ease a new hire will feel in the job.</p><p> One intervention at a financial institution hinged on sharing with new hires a list of 10 people that they were encouraged but not required to contact within 12 months. Each list included a mix of employees, some of whom were at the executive level. Some of the newcomers received an explanation of why they should reach out to the people on their lists, while others did not. And some participants in the experiment received email reminders to contact the people on the list at three months, six months, and nine months.</p><p></p><p> Individuals were selected for inclusion on a given new hire&#39;s list based on information that had been captured during the recruitment process. If an employee had expressed interest in a particular business unit, the list included a partner from that area. The list might also include leaders or HR contacts from cities or regions where the new hire&#39;s close family members lived. If the employee needed to relocate to take care of a parent or other family member, that essential information had already been provided.</p><p> Individuals from underrepresented groups who received a contact list, an explanation of why they should make contact, and email reminders performed better in their jobs. There was an acceleration in their network spread, which was measured along their lifetime at the company. Even 72 months later, people who had received all three elements of the intervention were still expanding their network faster than those who had not received all three elements of the intervention. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> A large company with many offices discovered that the onboarding process at its smaller workplaces seemed more effective. People felt more integrated, and their networks were established faster than in the large offices. In contrast, at the larger sites, new lateral hires were not mixing across generations and were not building their networks.</p><p> In response, the company applied a nudge that involved the cafeteria. Employees were assigned plate colors based on the number of years they had been at the company. New people were assigned a blue plate, employees who were six months into a role got a yellow plate, and other employees had green plates. Once a week, when people dined together, people with the same color plates could not sit together. Color mixing created interaction among employees who would otherwise be invisible to one another.</p><p> The strategy made onboarding easy because people were creating new networks. The intervention led to a 34% shift in the degree of directness characterizing an individual&#39;s connections within the network. It also produced an 18% increase in “betweenness centrality,” a metric quantifying an individual&#39;s role in passing information within the network.</p><p></p><p> Throughout my research, consulting, writing, and experimentation, 10 points along the career trajectory stand out as places where specific kinds of nudges and interventions can support the goal of building and sustaining a diverse workforce. In addition to attracting, recruiting, and onboarding candidates, diversity nudges can be applied to skill-building, avoiding office drudgery, flexibility and well-being, pay equality, origination and credit, feedback and promotion, and networking and sponsorship.</p><p> To benefit an organization and become part of a company&#39;s strategic advantage, women, people of color, and individuals from other underrepresented groups must be intentionally welcomed, integrated fully into the organization, and sustained. This process should be data-driven, harnessing the potential of big data and AI to achieve sustainable inclusion. They must be purposely supplied with the same or equalizing information, connections, skills, projects, and support that are provided to others within the organization. Inequalities must be recognized, and intervening actions must be devised to nudge these conditions in a manner that creates equality and inclusivity. The companies that win at diversity are the ones that design processes that are advantageous to and level the playing field for everyone.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>具有 Gen AI 的微型实用程序：Shopify 的 Miqdad Jaffer</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。 He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh.我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Experimentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[High-Tech Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Online Retail]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Miqdad Jaffer brings a background in engineering to his role as director of product for digital marketplace platform Shopify. Users might recognize the commerce platform as one that enables a fast and secure online checkout experience. On the merchant side, Shopify enables business owners to set up e-commerce sites where they can list and sell [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Miqdad Jaffer 拥有工程学背景，担任数字市场平台 Shopify 的产品总监。用户可能会认为该商务平台能够提供快速、安全的在线结账体验。 On the merchant side, Shopify enables business owners to set up e-commerce sites where they can list and sell their products.</p><p> Using generative AI, the platform also now offers merchants the ability to complete administrative tasks much more quickly, including writing product descriptions and customizing their sites. As Miqdad explains on this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, a key to enhancing Shopify&#39;s offerings with generative AI technology is ensuring that users always remain in control. He shares Shopify&#39;s approach to doing this while incorporating cutting-edge tools to help entrepreneurs start, operate, and grow their businesses more efficiently. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E4-Jaffer-Shopify-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Miqdad Jaffer"></p><h4> Miqdad Jaffer, Shopify</h4><p> Miqdad Jaffer is the director of product for Shopify, where he is responsible for the oversight and development of the company&#39;s AI-powered offerings. He joined the company in 2018 and has overseen the launch of Shopify Magic, its suite of AI-powered tools, and Shop.AI, an AI-powered shopping assistant. Before joining Shopify, Jaffer was the director of product management for the mobile consumer marketplace app Flipp. He has more than 15 years of product development and oversight experience.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How can generative AI tools help grow businesses while keeping users in control? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I&#39;m Miqdad Jaffer from Shopify, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Hi, everyone. Today Shervin and I are pleased to be joined by Miqdad Jaffer, director of product at Shopify. Miqdad, thanks for taking the time to talk with us.让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Thanks for having me. I&#39;m happy to be here and excited to talk a little bit about AI.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Great. We all use Shopify, but we may not know it. Can you give us a brief overview of Shopify and tell us what a director of product actually does?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Sure. So Shopify is a platform for entrepreneurs to be able to set up their storefronts online. You may have seen Shopify whenever you&#39;re going to purchase an item from a retailer. You may have gone to the checkout and seen that purple Shop Pay button, and for many of us, that&#39;s probably where you&#39;ve been exposed to Shopify. It&#39;s a way for an entrepreneur to be able to set up their storefront on the internet and for … you as a buyer to be able to transact in the fastest, simplest way possible to be able to make sure that the item arrives at your door.</p><p> In other cases, you may have seen Shopify on a platform like Shop.ai, where you might have searched for a specific event that you&#39;re putting together, a specific product that you&#39;re looking for, and tried to filter it all down across the many merchants on Shopify.</p><p> A merchant would go into Shopify and log in. There is a product section on the left, as an example. They would go into the product section, they would click “Add a new product,” and then within “Add a new product,” there is space for a title, description, and some other fields.</p><p> In terms of my role, my responsibilities are, how do we think about AI and how can it fit into that realm of entrepreneurship, and what can we do to accelerate our merchants&#39; success and progress as they build up their storefronts, sell their products, and grow as entrepreneurs?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So how does that involve artificial intelligence? I hear a lot of “e-commerce,” I hear a lot of “connecting,” but how does that involve artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah, it&#39;s a great question. I think that when people are looking to start as an entrepreneur, there&#39;s a lot to it, so there are considerations of “What&#39;s the right product? What&#39;s the right price? What&#39;s the right placement? What&#39;s the right promotion? How do I set up everything with my storefront? How do I maintain what &#39;good&#39; looks like as I grow and as I advance?” What we&#39;ve seen is that AI is an opportunity to make entrepreneurship accessible for everyone.</p><p> With every business unit, we wanted to utilize AI to create more efficiency, from managing administrative tasks to supporting business operations. Administrative tasks can be as simple as creating a new product description [or] figuring out what the right subject line for an email could be. And then, the business operation side of it could be just about everything from understanding the business, figuring out the analytics of it, what questions should I ask, what&#39;s the strategy that I should employ? And we view AI as a powerful assistant that can weave itself in and out of that process.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What you&#39;re saying is, Shopify is letting the entrepreneurs focus on the actual product and their brand and all of that kind of stuff but then have Shopify be a platform for how they take that to market, how they want their brand to appear, and a lot of the back-end operations. Obviously, AI could be quite prevalent across all of those. Was AI embedded from day one as it launched?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> We&#39;ve had AI in its most traditional sense embedded since early days. We did things along the lines of fraud detection, where a transaction comes in — and it&#39;s not as easy to tell whether this is fraudulent or nonfraudulent. We&#39;ve done basic classification models to be able to determine whether something <em>is</em> fraudulent and then provide a score back to the merchant in a reasonable fashion. That&#39;s been in there from the start.</p><p> Then generative AI comes along, and there are opportunities to be able to do a lot more, and what we&#39;ve seen is, we&#39;ve created a suite of products called Shopify Magic. And the idea behind this was, how do we embed this directly into the workflows that our merchants are having to go through, and how do we make that easier to start, run, and grow your business?</p><p> We did things like Autowrite, where we can create a description for a product, create a blog, create a new page, help with the subject line of an email, create the body of an email, and look at ways, on the customer service side, to be able to provide responses for a merchant as they interact with their customer. So those are some of the early stages, but we&#39;re trying to accelerate it even more these days.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> A lot of companies are thinking about generative AI, and it seems like you&#39;ve been <em>doing</em> it for quite some time. Can you comment a bit on when you started thinking about it, prepping for it, and, I would assume, to some extent, redirecting or upscaling or reskilling some of your technical folks to be able to actually take these things to market.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I&#39;ll give you a little bit of the genesis of how we kind of started with the first thing and accelerated it even more. We have some general themes that come up every year in terms of things that we should be looking at, and one of the ones that&#39;s usually pretty prevalent on there is [that] staying on the cutting edge of technology is critical. What we want to do is try to bring as much of the latest technology into the hands of our merchants so they have every advantage possible.</p><p> And we&#39;ve always tried to do things with AI, and one of the more recent ones, even before generative AI, was product classification — so the idea of being able to determine the category of a product using its text as well as its image to be able to figure out where this belongs. It helps in channels. It helps you basically market to a wider audience and get a reasonable taxonomy set.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> When ChatGPT came out, the question was, what can we do with this technology to put it in front of merchants? And this was one where we wanted to lean in for a couple reasons. One, it&#39;s important to get this in the hands of merchants as fast as possible, staying with the cutting edge of the technology side. And the other part of it was, we actually saw that there was utility for the first time, and that utility was important to get out there and to see whether our merchants would use it and what we could learn from it.</p><p> So we started with a simple path of “What&#39;s the thing that merchants are struggling with?” And we saw them struggling with product descriptions daily. There&#39;s billions of them across Shopify, and we saw that as a wide space to work in, and we had all of the conditions around what would make a good product description. And then we felt “OK, let&#39;s get this in and see how people use it and see whether this is something that&#39;s palatable.”</p><p> So we quickly spun up a team, and we relied upon a couple different principles. Shopify generally builds off of a set of principles and allows the team to go fast. Some of the principles we worked off of were, this has to be easy, this has to be integrated into their workflow, and the merchant needs to be able to have final say as to what goes out there to represent their business.</p><p> It&#39;s a simple start. We said, “OK, let&#39;s figure out what the rules of a good product description are.应该多长？ What&#39;s the tone it should be used in? What are the types of words that will be used, and what makes it really good?” We did the basic thing of prompting against that and then said, “OK, what additional context should the merchant provide, and what should we look for to be able to help them?”</p><p> And so we said, “OK, well, they can probably list out a couple keywords about their product, and that fits into the realm of knowledge <em>they</em> know about, and the rest of it should be us. Like, this should be as simple as like pressing a button. It should feel like magic.” So apropos to that, we named it Shopify Magic, and we wanted to stick with that. All a merchant has to do is they enter a couple keywords, they pick a tone of voice, and they press “Generate.”就是这样。 That was the first version. We tried to ship that real quick and see what would happen, and the feedback we got was, “This is amazing. Can you do this everywhere?”</p><p> So it&#39;s like, “OK, so there&#39;s, there&#39;s some positivity here. So, what can we do next?” And so we added a “special instructions” field, and initially in our trials, we were doing things like “Add a quote from a famous celebrity that would relate to my product,” just as, like, a meme for how to try it 。 And then we saw merchants using it in different ways.</p><p> We saw them using it for language, and this was an interesting one. We introduced the ability to support eight languages, and we saw people writing translations with it, and that was expected, but it was interesting to see. And I think one of the most interesting ones we saw was, there were merchants that didn&#39;t speak English and wanted to sell to an English audience and saw product descriptions as a way to bridge that gap — unexpected, but at the same time, it&#39;s one of those things where you put the product in the hands of the user and then the user decides what they&#39;re going to use it for. And it was remarkable to see that we opened up entrepreneurship for even a small window more of people than were there previously.</p><p> And that&#39;s what kind of got the ball rolling on the AI efforts. After that, it was every team wanted a piece, every team wanted to do something, and we accelerated it in every way we could. We&#39;ve tried to systematize things from a UX [user experience] perspective; whenever a merchant sees something, they know that this is what that&#39;s going to do. And we&#39;ve also tried to look into building Sidekick, which is a first-of-its-kind AI-enabled assistant, purpose-built for commerce. And so that&#39;s kind of been the journey that we&#39;ve gone into. We have dedicated teams that are working on specific features, and then we have the entire company that is looking at opportunities of where AI can accelerate commerce.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So when Shervin and I first heard about what you were doing, I think what kind of got us excited was how pervasive this is. The effect of something like Shopify integrating artificial intelligence into its tool is huge. And I think we were talking earlier, you had talked about introducing this product in February [2023]. This is very early on in the generative [AI] days.</p><p> A lot of people are investigating generative, but this was an exciting story where you&#39;re using these tools in production very quickly. I&#39;m sure that was a little bit painful — maybe you could speak a little bit about any of the pain or difficulty you had; maybe other people have learned from that, but also at how pervasive it is. Both of those are interesting ways that people can learn from what you&#39;ve done.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. Early days came with the challenges, but I think that that&#39;s kind of the fun of it. It was interesting because this was the latest technology. There was so much utility to it, and we just wanted to get that in the hands of our users. Along the way we had to figure out things like, how do you do evaluation? What is this prompting stuff? How do you systematize this and make this make sense? What&#39;s all this RAG stuff about — RAG being <em>retrieval augmented generation</em> ? How do I bring more data into this context of a prompt, and how do I make this make sense?</p><p> And the crazy part was, every week, a months&#39; or a years&#39; worth of other technology time passes, and all of a sudden there&#39;s a new thing to try and a new thing to explore, and we didn&#39;t want to miss that ， 任何一个。 Every time something new came out, we tried, we explored. And I think that the culture at Shopify is one of exploration and one of crafters and builders. And what we tried to do is put this in the hands of people that could build, and to try things. And we also did things internally to encourage the use of AI, and we built our own kind of internal ChatGPT instance equivalent. We have it for our internal wikis for search and discovery. And what we&#39;ve tried to do is just make this into the fabric of the company.这是正常的。这是预期的。 And then, all of the risks and challenges that come with it — hallucinatory included — are things that people are familiar with. And once we got them familiar with it, then we figured out ways to work around it and to embrace it in some cases, too.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I think that&#39;s a very important point you&#39;re making because as I reflect back on my own experience and BCG&#39;s experience in this field, we&#39;re working with many companies, and many of them have the same mindset and ambition as you&#39;ve described and are putting solutions in production and are embracing it. And then there are some that are, I would say, quite reserved about this. And some of that is based on, I would say, some unfounded fears.</p><p> I mean, the reality is this is new technology and it comes with a lot of risk, and maybe a little bit more risk than traditional AI because of how pervasive it can become. But I think the mentality of waiting for all of the risks to be figured out by other people then puts you at somewhat of a huge disadvantage, because the only way, as you describe — I mean, I love how you said it — the only way to actually get ahead of these things is to start experimenting with it and getting comfortable with it.</p><p> I&#39;m sure at the board level there were some risks and some concerns. Maybe just comment on what many people thought back then versus what the reality was and put it in perspective for some of our listeners so that they understand that these risks can be mitigated versus you just stay away forever.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. One of the first things I&#39;ll say is that I want to describe who an entrepreneur is, to even put this into context. Every entrepreneur I have ever come across has the highest risk tolerance of anyone I&#39;ve ever met. They are willing to drop everything in their life to start a business, and sometimes they don&#39;t know anything except that they want to start a business. And these people are inherently risk tolerant, so our user group is very different than others. And obviously, you&#39;re going to get a spectrum of tolerances across that user base, but by nature, this is a group that is willing to dive in, take risks, and try things. And then one of the things that we observed was that they were already using it. So we already had merchants that were using ChatGPT or whatever was out there, to be able to prompt it, figure out alternatives, and use it directly into their software.</p><p> We did a brief round of research where we asked a number of merchants: Is this something that you know about? How have you used it?你用它做什么？ And many of them were like, “Yeah. Well, I mean, I just ask it everything, and so I&#39;m just getting to figure it out.” And we already saw that happening. So for us it was, “All right. Well, we already have this risk-tolerant merchant base, and the biggest concerns that we have are typically on two vectors.”</p><p> Vector one is a fear of losing control. So asking questions along the lines of “What&#39;s it going to say? What do I do if it hallucinates? Is this going to be right for me? Is it going to speak to my buyer?” So all of those initial questions and that fear of losing control was easily mitigated. So we said, “OK. Well, here&#39;s a quick fear. How do we mitigate this fear?” And we mitigate a fear of losing control by putting the control back in the hands of the user.</p><p> So the carte blanche principle was “The AI will never write without user intervention,” and so the merchant will always be able to see what the message is that&#39;s going to go out there. So all of the hallucination risk, all of the “What&#39;s it going to do?” risk is gone because now it puts control right back in the hands of the user.</p><p> The second risk is around whether it&#39;s factually accurate or not, and that&#39;s typically one that a lot of people come across. The way that we&#39;ve tried to manage that is, the person that knows the most is the person selling the product. The thing that they know the most about is their product, and that&#39;s what they&#39;re trying to talk about, and they&#39;re trying to talk about <em>their</em> brand. And so that one didn&#39;t feel as risky for us either because it was going to be up to the merchant to decide how they were going to be represented in a factual way.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You talk about this in such a matter-of-fact way, but when you think about the actual key word here, it&#39;s the <em>user</em> , which is actually, when you think about it, Sam, a lot of our work around human and AI versus just human alone or AI alone. Thanks for talking about that. That&#39;s very key.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One of the things I really like, too, is you keep using the word <em>utility</em> . A lot of the examples that Shervin and I talk about, we&#39;ll ask people for an example, and they&#39;ll bring out some AI-heavy application that they&#39;ve implemented that crosses lots of parts of their organization and it&#39;s a big deal, and those are great. But the utility you&#39;re talking about seems like micro utility. And so, what I mean by that is that, as you mentioned, people may have already been going out to some large language model and generating some text and then pasting it into Shopify.</p><p> Your incremental utility here was saving them some back and forth between those two tools, but also then incrementally making it work better within your tools and within your context. And I think that&#39;s exciting, when you think about how all those tiny pieces multiply by the billions. And that&#39;s a different story than what Shervin and I see sometimes, which is, “We have a big system which has a big utility, and there may be not so many users of it.”</p><p> I want to come back to something that you mentioned earlier — and maybe I just picked up on your tone of it — but you were talking about fraud detection and these somewhat traditional uses of artificial intelligence. That feels like an oxymoron now, but you said, “Oh, yeah. We&#39;re using it for fraud. We&#39;re using it for back-end business optimization and these sorts of things.耶耶耶。 We do all that stuff, but here&#39;s the really cool stuff.” It seems really exciting that you&#39;re able to stay forward.下一步是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> It&#39;s a great question. I think the hope for us is that we want AI to lower the barrier of entry for entrepreneurship, period. And I think the idea for us is, let&#39;s look at everything that&#39;s on the space. So we did something relatively recently about image generation. And we saw this as “OK, well, we can lean in here, too. There&#39;s different modes of operating that we can play with.” So we release the Hugging Face pipeline, and the idea behind this was “Let&#39;s put this out into the market, let&#39;s see how people are going to use it, and let&#39;s do it in a way that&#39;s going to be innocuous.”</p><p> The idea behind it is you upload a product image, and then you pick what background needs to be switched out. And some of this, there&#39;s some fun stuff behind the scenes of uplift, upscaling the image, figuring out the right mask for it, making sure that the reflections and shadows are going to be good, and then generating all sorts of backgrounds that make sense in the vein of commerce. And what we see from this is the ability to explore in a different way. What we&#39;ve tried to do with AI, and to your point about the risk tolerance of our user base, it&#39;s not meant to be something that is just disruptive to their existing workflows. Many of them — especially established ones — have existing workflows where they do everything in their specific way, and that&#39;s what works for them.</p><p> All we&#39;re doing is, for anyone that needs that extra push or needs that extra piece, there&#39;s a button to click, a way to invoke this, and it is their choice to make on that. And, Shervin, I like some of the stuff that you were talking about in terms of putting the user in place, and our adage has always been that this is meant to be something that augments and isn&#39;t a replacement. So this is always going to be something that helps a user be the best version of themselves.</p><p> And with image generation, we see the opportunity for them to holistically change their storefront if they want to. If they have a Thanksgiving sale coming up and they want to be able to change all the backgrounds to be fall themed, it&#39;s a quick, easy move for them to do. Their product stays at the forefront, their branding stays at the forefront, but they can merchandise just for the specific event — if it&#39;s Thanksgiving, if it&#39;s Christmas, if it&#39;s New Year&#39;s, whatever it might be. Something that would require additional photo shoots might be a lot easier to achieve now than [it was] previously.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Exactly. Let&#39;s just remember how complex and unnecessarily process-oriented something like this would have been, you know, a few years back, where you have just agreeing on the background and the photoshoot and the look and feel and impact on brand and all of that, and now you&#39;re putting it all in the hands of the merchant.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> For us, it was really important that many people across Shopify were using this, asking the right questions, pushing the boundaries, and understanding some of the nomenclature around it. When I say “hallucination,” I can almost guarantee that 99% of Shopify knows what that means and how that happens and [how] that works. And that makes the conversation much different every time you go toward product development, because it&#39;s not bringing it up and relitigating it every single time. It&#39;s people trying a solution around the normal problems that come up with this technology.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> If I squint, I kind of see something developing over this market of artificial intelligence. You alluded to it with the ease of transfer learning. You&#39;re able to take these existing models and augment them slightly, and I see that as an improvement over the past decade from “Oh, yeah.当然。 You can download these tools and build them yourselves” to “Hey, no, you can take what we&#39;ve done and what we&#39;ve trained our GPUs and burned up our GPUs on and incrementally burn up a little GPU on your own but then继续前进。” I think that&#39;s a dynamic that&#39;s happening in this market here.</p><p> But let me go darker here and talk about another dynamic. Is there, let&#39;s say, a race toward mediocrity? And I think that&#39;s a little charged way of saying it, but if all of your users in Shopify are using the same tools to generate the same sort of product descriptions, isn&#39;t that going to lead to a sort of vanilla feeling of all product descriptions? How do we push back and get beyond that? It&#39;s great that we get everybody to mediocre well; how do we get people distinctive? Where do we build off of that? How do we make that beyond mediocre?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. The problem you&#39;re talking about is a local maxima, effectively, right? So everyone moves toward this standard, simplistic, homogeneous, boring thing. And what we&#39;ve looked at is that all of the tools that we provide will get you started. The idea is not to be “This is the finish line.” The finish line is the merchant. The finish line is their product. The finish line is their brand and being able to represent accordingly. For many cases, this is about getting you something, which is better than nothing, and getting you started and thinking.</p><p> We had one merchant that really described it well for me. He wanted to set up an outlet store for some of the overstock inventory that they had, and they had 3,000 SKUs that they wanted to put together — 3,000 different products that they wanted to put on this initial outlet store. And what he said to me was, “Typically, what I would have done is I would have hired a team, we would have taken three months to get this thing spun up, and we would have tried to put it together.” And he said, “I spent the weekend by myself, and I just used your generation feature.这让我开始了。 I made a couple changes. And in three days, I had an outlet store stood up and ready to go for all my products. And I made the changes necessary. I don&#39;t like the style that you had, so I gave it some specific instructions, and it got to what I wanted.”</p><p> And I think the idea is flexibility within the framework. So provide a framework, let them get started, but give them all the flexibility in the world to do what is appropriate for their business and for them to be able to differentiate to their audience. And I think the key is, every audience is different, and nobody understands that better than the merchant themselves. The idea is capability and augmentation, not replacement.你是对的； there could be a point of local maxima for people. But we want to leave every escape hatch possible so that they can get out of that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing I want to stick back to, and you&#39;d alluded to it, was the deterministic versus stochastic nature of this. That seems really difficult to work with [from] a production standpoint — that you&#39;re using tools that have stochastic outputs, but you&#39;d like to have a “defined, tested, refined” process. And those two things seem antithetical to me in many ways.你怎么处理那件事呢？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Part of it is, there needs to be a risk tolerance built in. So there needs to be almost an expectation that the system will fail and that the user needs to have a way to be able to work through that failure. So product description is a great one. We actually see that it takes multiple generations before the user is happy with what they have in front of them. So with that in mind, you have to allow for that second, third, fourth, fifth generation to take place with no effort whatsoever.</p><p> And so that&#39;s an error case that we know is going to happen, so we plan for it. So there&#39;s this “Regenerate” button right there; it presents multiple options. In other cases, we will try to present as many options as we possibly can to make it easier. So subject lines: You get three options to choose from.你可以改变它。做任何你想做的事。 Then, the other part of this is that we understand that technology is going to change, and the way that people use it is going to change, and their expertise level is going to change.</p><p> So there are people that are going to try and break the system, and there are people that are going to try and work around the system. It&#39;s important that we plan for that scenario, too. So every risk and every failure case has to be considered upfront. And then you almost do it in a fun way, and the one that is typical is prompt hacking, where people are trying to figure out what the prompt was that was used for this. In most of those cases, you do the best you can, but you expect that the prompt will get out there. So you write the prompt in a way that, when it gets out there, it&#39;s like, “Hey, you found me.那太棒了！ You want to apply for a job or something?” There are lots of different ways to like think about this.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Your human in the loop solves a lot of this too.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Correct.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Your whole design philosophy, it really addresses, I think, a lot of the backstops, a lot of the stochastic nature too. Can you give us a bit of your background?你是如何找到自己的角色的？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I started out as an engineer. I think since I was, like, 12 years old I was programming and trying to figure out how to make the computer do what I wanted it to do. And I took an initial role as an engineer and was introduced to product management in what was then meter data management. So it was like big data for utilities had just come out. I got to work in that space, and then I moved into document classification, then ad tech, and then retail data platform management.</p><p> I&#39;ve always been adjacent to data, and at Shopify, my journey had been [to] build our infrastructure and data platforms, work on our machine learning platforms, and figure out what needs to be built there. And I always had one toe in the machine learning/AI pool at all times. Then I had teams that were focused on the analytics side of it and what merchants were going to experience and how they were going to understand their business. And the mandate was always like “How do I optimize my business with data?” And we looked at opportunities with ML, we looked at opportunities with AI. And then, when generative AI came out, it was just the next step along the way.</p><p> So it&#39;s by luck, by accident, by design — who knows? But I&#39;ve always been in data for the last 15, 20 years, and this was the next step.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK. Time for five questions. Miqdad, do you know what that is?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I do not.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I mean, I know what five questions are, but …</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Good! So we&#39;re going to ask you five questions rapid-fire style. Just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Sure.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What do you see as the biggest opportunity for AI right now?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I think the biggest opportunity is solving cold start for many people. What I mean when I say “cold start” is looking at a blank screen and not knowing what to do, whether it&#39;s how to navigate a system, write a thing, or whatever it might be — just that unknown moment. I think that&#39;s where AI steps in and does the biggest [benefit].</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I love that. What is the biggest misconception about AI?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> That it will take over. I think that there&#39;s a long way to go. It&#39;s an augmentation, not a replacement, and I think it&#39;s the same as when Photoshop came out. Designers got much better and much more creative, and I think this will raise the bar for everyone in terms of what they can do.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is there such a thing as too much AI? When is there too much?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I think it&#39;s too much when the user is out of the loop. I think the user needs to have a stronghold in how they use AI and how they interact with it. I think this is not about replacing, and I think this is a matter of augmenting and helping the user be better.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What was the first career you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I wanted to be a doctor, but I faint at the sight of blood, so that didn&#39;t work out so well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What is the one thing you wish AI could do that it cannot do right now?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I wish we could incorporate all of the modes of a user wanting to interact, whether it be a combination of voice, facial expressions — just to be able to get that semantic meaning behind the scenes that words can&#39;t do by themselves 。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We really appreciate the idea that what you&#39;re doing is using generative AI right now, just barely after it got started. I think a lot of people are wringing their hands and wondering how to use these technologies, and what you&#39;ve shown is a great example of how people can get real utility from this tool right now. Thanks for taking the time to join us today.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Thank you so much for having me, both.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Ellen Nielsen, chief data officer at Chevron.请加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>使用开源进行更安全的生成人工智能实验</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aron Culotta and Nicholas Mattei. <p>Aron Culotta 是杜兰大学计算机科学副教授兼社区参与人工智能中心主任。尼古拉斯·马泰 (Nicholas Mattei) 是杜兰大学计算机科学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Security]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Open Source]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Integrating artificial intelligence into the daily workflow of employees across organizations, from upper management to front-line workers, holds the promise of increasing productivity in tasks such as writing memos, developing software, and creating marketing campaigns. However, companies are rightly worried about the risks of sharing data with third-party AI services, as in [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Culotta-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Integrating artificial intelligence into the daily workflow of employees across organizations, from upper management to front-line workers, holds the promise of increasing productivity in tasks such as writing memos, developing software, and creating marketing campaigns. However, companies are rightly worried about the risks of sharing data with third-party AI services, as in the well-publicized case of a Samsung employee exposing proprietary company information by uploading it to ChatGPT.</p><p> These concerns echo those heard in the early days of cloud computing, when users were worried about the security and ownership of data sent to remote servers. Managers now confidently use mature cloud computing services that comply with a litany of regulatory and business requirements regarding the security, privacy, and ownership of their data. AI services, particularly generative AI, are much less mature in this regard — partly because it is still early days, but also because these systems have a nearly inexhaustible appetite for training data.</p><p></p><p> Large language models (LLMs) like OpenAI&#39;s ChatGPT have been trained on an enormous corpus of written content accessed via the internet, without regard for the ownership of that data. The company now faces a lawsuit from a group of bestselling authors, including George RR Martin, for having used their copyrighted works without permission, enabling the LLM to generate copycats. Proactively seeking to protect their data, traditional media outlets have engaged in licensing discussions with AI developers; negotiations between OpenAI and <cite>The New York Times</cite> , however, broke down over the summer.</p><p> Of more immediate concern to companies experimenting with generative AI, however, is how to safely explore new use cases for LLMs that draw on internal data, given that anything uploaded to commercial LLM services could be captured as training data. How can managers better protect their own proprietary data assets and also improve data stewardship in their corporate AI development practice in order to earn and maintain customer trust?</p><h3> The Open-Source Solution</h3><p> An obvious solution to issues of data ownership is to build one&#39;s own generative AI solutions locally rather than shipping data to a third party. But how can this be practical, given that Microsoft spent hundreds of millions of dollars building the hardware infrastructure alone for OpenAI to train ChatGPT, to say nothing of the actual development costs? Surely, we can&#39;t all afford to build these foundational models from scratch.</p><p> Safer experimentation with generative AI is becoming increasingly possible thanks to a burgeoning open-source AI movement that recalls the excitement around Linux in the 1990s. Back then, the development of a free operating system whose source code could be read and edited by anyone birthed an international community of developers who built upon one another&#39;s work to develop a mature suite of software tools that run much of the internet today.</p><p></p><p> Such a <a href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2023-01-30-ai-linux">“Linux moment” for AI</a> has now arrived. Open-source models such as <a href="https://bigscience.huggingface.co/blog/bloom">Bloom</a> , <a href="https://lmsys.org/blog/2023-03-30-vicuna/">Vicuna</a> , and Stable Diffusion, among many others, provide foundational models that can be fine-tuned to specific tasks. Research into highly optimized training routines (such as <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2106.09685">LoRA</a> and <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2106.10199.pdf">BitFit</a> ) has found that they can be fine-tuned using commodity hardware, leading to a burgeoning <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3545111">ecosystem of models</a> approaching the performance of ChatGPT (though many <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.15717.pdf">technical challenges</a> remain). A leaked memo in which a Google researcher laments “we have no moat” reveals that some see this explosion of open-source innovation as threatening the tech giants&#39; control of LLMs. Still, capitalizing on the rapid developments of these emerging open-source tools safely and responsibly will require new investments in people and processes.</p><p></p><h3> Managing the Risks of Open-Source AI</h3><p> While locally controlled AI solutions keep proprietary data in hand, managers must still take a number of actions to ensure their safe, effective, and responsible use.</p><p> <strong>Navigate model and data licenses.</strong> The term <em>open source</em> is, in many cases, misleading. While some models allow commercial uses, others are restricted to academic or nonprofit use. Sometimes the source code is released with the model; other times, only one or the other is released. Recently created types of licenses restrict specific use cases deemed to be harmful or irresponsible. For example, Bloom and Stable Diffusion are released under <a href="https://www.licenses.ai/">Responsible AI Licenses</a> , which might legally prevent their use in certain criminal justice and health applications. One must also consider the types of data the model was trained on. While including copyrighted material in data sets for training AI models might be considered fair use in some scenarios in the US, case law is far from settled. Having a thorough accounting of the data fed into each model will help organizations better navigate these issues. Emerging efforts like the Data Nutrition Project are adding more structure and reporting requirements to data sets to help users better understand their contents and risks.</p><p> <strong>Prevent data leakage.</strong> Even without submitting data to third-party AI services, organizations risk leaking their own data through open-ended user interfaces such as chatbots. An emerging use case allows LLMs to serve as a conversational interface to a database, which can be a powerful way to let customers quickly find answers to common questions that are customized to their own data. However, preventing the LLM from revealing private information about other customers, or proprietary data of the company, can be challenging. Research by Pew shows that these conversational agents are a <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/science/2023/02/22/60-of-americans-would-be-uncomfortable-with-provider-relying-on-ai-in-their-own-health-care/">concern for many users</a> , especially around sensitive topics like health care. Safeguarding data is made even more difficult by <em>prompt injection attacks</em> , in which malicious users attempt to trick the agent into revealing information it was explicitly instructed not to reveal. In an adversarial setting, the same aspect of AI systems that allows them to be creative and flexible also becomes a security threat.</p><p> <strong>Adapt to changing data.</strong> Another complication with hosting on-premise models is ensuring that they are using the latest data. While the initial release of ChatGPT (GPT-3) famously could not answer questions about events past 2021, more recent models can combine current data with models pretrained on historical data. Firms must balance updating the system with new information while also maintaining stability and consistency in user experience.</p><p> <strong>Mitigate systemic biases.</strong> AI systems can easily perpetuate and amplify social and economic inequalities encoded in the training data. It is well known that LLMs are prone to stereotyping based on gender, race, and ethnicity — such as assuming that nurses are female and doctors are male. While there has been considerable research into how to reduce such behavior, in the end this problem will not be solved by solely technological solutions. Organizations should continuously audit AI systems, measuring their performance and results to ensure that different subpopulations are being treated equitably.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Build trust with customers.</strong> Companies should anticipate heightened sensitivities over how personal data is used and be transparent with customers about any intentions to use their data for AI training — and, ideally, allow individuals to opt in. This is particularly important when it comes to data that is perceived as being extremely personal, such as audio, video, and health data. Simply updating the terms of service and sending out notifications about the change, as some companies have done, can leave customers feeling exploited and broadly damage trust. For example, after Zoom&#39;s recent move to claim such rights to using customer data made news, blowback from users and privacy advocates compelled the videoconferencing provider to not only walk back the changes but declare in its terms of service that it would never use such data to train AI models.</p><h3> Responsible Data Use in the AI Era</h3><p> If open-source AI models continue to be adopted across industries, it will not just be Big Tech facing concerns over data ownership. Every company that wants to deploy these models for tasks as wide-ranging as internal help tools and public-facing chatbots will have to confront issues related to how data is collected and used by AI systems.</p><p></p><p> While there are <a href="https://mozilla.ai/">startups</a> , <a href="https://data.humdata.org/dataset/2048a947-5714-4220-905b-e662cbcd14c8/resource/60050608-0095-4c11-86cd-0a1fc5c29fd9/download/ocha-data-responsibility-guidelines_2021.pdf ">governmental working groups</a> , and <a href="https://responsibledata.io/">academic communities</a> all working on these topics, best practices and recommended policies are still emerging. Stanford Law School&#39;s <a href="https://law.stanford.edu/2023/03/09/a-data-stewardship-framework-for-generative-ai/">AI Data Stewardship Framework</a> specifically addresses generative AI techniques. The Association for Computing Machinery, the world&#39;s largest computing professional organization, has also recently released a set of guidelines around the <a href="https://www.acm.org/binaries/content/assets/public-policy/ustpc-approved-generative-ai-principles">design and deployment of generative AI</a> systems, including LLMs. Those resources cover some of the issues discussed here, including limits on deployment, data and output ownership, and personal data control. We recommend that organizations of all sizes looking to capitalize on open-source AI keep a close eye on relevant guidelines and frameworks for the responsible and ethical collection and use of data for training models. They can be helpful for thinking through the potential technical and social risks of any potential project, and for developing rigorous auditing and monitoring processes to ensure safe and effective deployment.</p><p> At Tulane, we have recently established the <a href="https://tulanecs.github.io/tuceai/">Center for Community-Engaged Artificial Intelligence</a> to investigate such issues. Through a cross-disciplinary team of technologists, social scientists, and civil rights activists, we are working with nonprofits and community groups in New Orleans to understand how AI affects their work. We are brainstorming new ways of building AI systems that cede control over the data and technology behind AI to the people most affected by it. Our work is part of growing efforts around participatory or human-centered AI and data, which recognize that all stakeholders need to be included in the value created by these systems. As corporations move deeper into AI development, adhering to similar values might help them be better stewards of the data that they collect and use.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Start Smart With a Talent Marketplace</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Williamson and Donncha Carroll. <p>杰夫·威廉姆森 (Jeff Williamson) 是博思艾伦 (Booz Allen) 的人力资源主管。在 2019 年加入公司之前，他曾担任美国邮政服务首席人力资源官兼执行副总裁。 Donncha Carroll 是 Lotis Blue Consulting 的合伙人，也是该公司的数据科学负责人。他拥有近30年的咨询经验。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Networks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Many leaders can now make a strong case for establishing an internal talent marketplace, but getting one off the ground remains difficult. At Booz Allen, we experienced that truth during the first year after launching our pilot project. Here, we’ll examine some of the challenges we faced, how we overcame them, and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> Many leaders can now make a strong case for establishing an internal talent marketplace, but getting one off the ground remains difficult.在博思艾伦，我们在启动试点项目后的第一年就经历了这一事实。 Here, we&#39;ll examine some of the challenges we faced, how we overcame them, and what we learned about change management and talent marketplaces.</p><p> Having a talent marketplace represented an important change for Booz Allen. For years, we&#39;d been deploying professional staff members through informal, internal networks that operated based on who you knew and who you trusted. But this path limited our flexibility to make use of available resources and match the right talent to the right work. More importantly, it limited our people&#39;s control over their own career paths, and that hurt engagement and retention.</p><p></p><p> To test a better approach, Booz Allen launched a talent marketplace pilot project in partnership with Lotis Blue Consulting in January 2022. With the pilot, we sought to address talent management challenges that constrained growth and hurt our ability to deliver a compelling value proposition to employees — namely, issues in hiring, deployment, talent development, technology and its adoption, and culture change. We wanted to solve these problems systematically and holistically rather than introduce point solutions, which often fail to compound value.</p><p> But the level of cultural transformation required to activate and operate a talent marketplace is significant. It takes a sustained effort to work through several human behavioral- and perception-driven issues — and overcoming these issues is key to success.</p><h3> The Road to a Talent Marketplace</h3><p> Booz Allen wanted to end its reliance on traditional hiring networks centered around clients or teams. These highly localized networks made it tough to find resources in other parts of the organization that would meet enterprise, regional, or local needs. In contrast, the marketplace established a centralized approach to assess demand and source talent enterprisewide (via external hiring, internal deployment, or upskilling) and created the capability to deploy people across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> The marketplace pilot focused on skills rather than networks. This gave employees new visibility to open opportunities across the enterprise and managers new insights into talent who could do the work. This high-resolution view on job and development opportunities vastly expanded the scope of what people could explore, improving employee engagement and delivering higher levels of individual and business performance. The pilot doubled the internal fill rate on open positions for the pilot population and garnered positive employee feedback on transparency and ease of pursuing new opportunities. Additionally, this skills-based approach gave underrepresented candidates more opportunities in technical domains with public sector clients.</p><p> In the early months of the pilot, we needed to overcome a few important challenges to build interest and excitement. Most importantly, we needed to seed the marketplace with a sufficient number of high-quality opportunities and available talent to engage both employees and managers. In so doing, we learned several important lessons — especially around change management.</p><h4> Lesson 1: Bring on the gamification.</h4><p> As our clients&#39; environments and needs are changing, the nature of our work is evolving, and we are seeing a rapid shift in in-demand skill sets. Our technical talent&#39;s ability to deliver against a client&#39;s mission depends on how quickly they can learn and adapt.</p><p> To address this, Jim Hemgen, Booz Allen&#39;s strategic talent development leader, and his learning and development (L&amp;D) team designed and launched a badging program alongside the marketplace pilot. The program aimed to develop strategic enterprise capabilities by illuminating different career pathways and the skills required to access different opportunities. To qualify for a badge, an employee needed to both earn the credential and have a manager validate that they had applied the skill on the job. This gamified learning and offered recognition and rewards to employees who invested in their own development.</p><p> The L&amp;D team engaged a large segment of the company&#39;s technical workforce in building strategic capabilities through a combination of internal badging and external certifications. In the past year, employees have earned more than 4,000 badges or certifications that are critical to the future of the business.</p><p></p><h4> Lesson 2: Data goals must be relevant to individual career goals.</h4><p> We encountered several technical challenges associated with the pilot, including data structure (establishing the right job architecture), data quality (ensuring that skills data was complete, for example), and algorithm design (how best to perform the recommendation process for talent and open职位）。</p><p> To get the complete skills data, we needed wide adoption. In reality, adoption closely correlated with the value that users expected to extract from the platform. We had a slow start as employees and managers explored the functionality and benefits.</p><p> That changed once John Grumbine, the marketplace operations leader, helped launch the Career Hub, an internal web app, in January 2023. The app served as a one-stop shop for employees to find jobs, training and development, mentors, and communities in the talent marketplace based on their skills and preferences. Employees now had a vested interest in keeping their skills and preferences up to date because that information drove recommendations for the opportunities, training, and the mentors they could access; further, it drove how they might be discovered or identified by project managers seeking to fill roles.</p><p> Launching the Career Hub app led to a substantial increase in talent marketplace adoption. As of September 2023, more than 50% of Booz Allen employees had onboarded into the Career Hub and were accessing job, learning, and mentoring opportunities.</p><h4> Lesson 3: Even change management needs to change.</h4><p> In the realm of cultural transformation, we quickly experienced four key challenges after launching the pilot. (See “Four Culture Challenges to Conquer.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Culture Challenges to Conquer</h4><p class="caption"> You&#39;re likely to encounter these issues as you lead through the culture change related to a talent marketplace:</p><table id="Chart#" class="no-mobile"><thead><tr><th>挑战</th><th>Business Implications</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>Managers want to keep their best resources or are concerned about becoming a net exporter of talent in an open market.</strong><p></td><td><p> Instead of leaving the team, high-performing talent leaves the organization.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Employees are reluctant to seek out reassignment openly for fear that they will appear disloyal to their current supervisors.</strong><p></td><td><p> Engagement and performance of captured staff declines over time.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Project managers are reluctant to accept resources they don&#39;t know personally and to trust recommendations from managers outside of their personal network.</strong></p></td><td><p> Assembling the right team for each project is much more challenging. The hiring process takes longer and is more susceptible to hiring manager bias.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Hiring managers are rejecting less-than-perfect applicants who often require only a small investment to close skill gaps.</strong></p></td><td><p> Staff members become less engaged, and performance degrades on work misaligned with their personal interests. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson_Talent_Essay_Table.png" alt="Four Culture Challenges to Conquer" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> Those challenges were causing a lot of problems. In response, our team prioritized several important actions to drive the culture change we needed:</p><ul><li> Build, refine, and map out skills-based talent profiles to provide greater clarity on the work people can do or have done.</li><li> Focus (initially) on high-volume in-demand job profiles to create enough liquidity in the system that participants have the opportunity to move.</li><li> Form a small, agile, and action-oriented operations team to collaborate with subject matter experts (for example, from business leadership and talent acquisition) as different challenges arise.</li><li> Provide human-centric support in the form of marketplace navigators — people specifically tasked with helping all participants (employees and managers) follow marketplace rules and guidelines and get the most value from the platform.</li></ul><p> All of these steps can be built into a launch plan for a talent marketplace.</p><h4> Lesson 4: Momentum, motivation, and measurement matter a great deal.</h4><p> At a high level, it&#39;s important to launch several services of an integrated talent management system simultaneously in order to exceed expectations and build adoption momentum.</p><p> To effect behavioral change, leaders must deeply understand what motivates different people, as well as how the changes they&#39;re making will address people&#39;s needs. The pilot provided valuable feedback on marketplace utility, helped prioritize enhancements, and established the level of change management required to support evolving and scaling the design.</p><p></p><p> Monitoring and measuring marketplace performance helped our team try new things, fail fast, and continually enhance the marketplace&#39;s value to participants. More specifically, our metrics included the number of opportunities posted, trends within those opportunities, the level and breadth of employee interest by type of posting, the percentage of aging opportunities (those that went unfilled for a long time), and the percentage of positions填充。 This data helped us evaluate the health and strength of the platform and gave us insight into how system adjustments were influencing performance.</p><h3> Commit to Continuous Improvement</h3><p></p><p> Through the talent marketplace and our other talent system investments, we are delivering a better employee value proposition. Our employee retention improved more than 4% after the pilot. However, this journey never ends. Continuous investment in evolving talent, as well as the solution, is essential to success for the business.</p><p> Addressing obstacles that come up along the way is part of the journey and ultimately leads to a better design and better results. A talent marketplace offers important benefits in today&#39;s evolving labor market: By prioritizing employee mobility and development, companies can better adapt to the changing skill requirements and realize higher levels of innovation, collaboration, and flexibility within their workforces.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Balancing Change and Continuity During a Transformation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/balancing-change-and-continuity-during-a-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/balancing-change-and-continuity-during-a-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Carsten Lund Pedersen and Laurianne McLaughlin. <p>Carsten Lund Pedersen is an associate professor at the IT University of Copenhagen, Denmark. Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading C.L. Pedersen, &#8220;Cracking the Culture Code for Successful Digital Transformation,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, April 6, 2022. As digital transformation work unfolds, many companies find cultural barriers insurmountable. Why? Because leaders often fail to strike the right balance between continuity and change, creating cultural chaos that stalls progress. Carsten Lund Pedersen, associate professor [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>CL Pedersen, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cracking-the-culture-code-for-successful-digital-transformation/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Cracking the Culture Code for Successful Digital Transformation</a> ,&quot; <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , April 6, 2022.</p></aside><p> As digital transformation work unfolds, many companies find cultural barriers insurmountable.为什么？ Because leaders often fail to strike the right balance between continuity and change, creating cultural chaos that stalls progress.</p><p> Carsten Lund Pedersen, associate professor in digital transformation at the IT University of Copenhagen in Denmark, helps organizations find that balance.</p><p>在本次网络研讨会中，您将了解到：</p><ul><li> Why many organizations suffer from identity crises during digital transformation.</li><li> Why leaders need to demonstrate <em>both</em> openness to change and respect for the existing culture.</li><li> How to balance change and continuity using a matrix tool and examples from companies that succeeded with culture shifts that supported real transformation.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/balancing-change-and-continuity-during-a-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The End of Averages for Marketing Budgets</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nader Tavassoli and Christine Moorman. <p>Nader Tavassoli is a professor of marketing and co-academic director of the Leadership Institute at London Business School. He is also the UK director of The CMO Survey. Christine Moorman is the T. Austin Finch Sr. Professor of Business Administration at Duke University&#39;s Fuqua School of Business. She is founder and director of The CMO Survey and former editor in chief of the <cite>Journal of Marketing</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Resource Allocation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR In his 2015 book The End of Average, Todd Rose warns against “averagarians” designing systems based on the mean or judging success in terms of the deviation from the mean. He highlights Gilbert Daniels, an anti-averager hero, whose research in the 1950s led the U.S. Air Force to design planes with personalized [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Moorman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> In his 2015 book <cite>The End of Average</cite> , Todd Rose warns against “averagarians” designing systems based on the mean or judging success in terms of the deviation from the mean. He highlights Gilbert Daniels, an anti-averager hero, whose research in the 1950s led the US Air Force to design planes with personalized cockpit features to suit pilots of all shapes and sizes rather than just the average male pilot — an innovation that dramatically increased safety记录。</p><p> Marketing strategy also hinges on the principle of acting on differences. Think segmentation: Marketers tend not to design a product or service for the average consumer. Indeed, polarizing brands such as Red Bull pride themselves on the notion that as many people hate their product as love it.</p><p> Yet when it comes to marketing budgets, a common but flawed practice is to use average figures touted by well-meaning researchers. Two of the most established CMO surveys that examine marketing budgets are The CMO Survey, conducted biannually by Duke University (and run by this article&#39;s second author since 2008), and Gartner&#39;s annual CMO Spend and Strategy Survey. The CMO Survey has found that 2023 marketing budgets, on average, represent 11% of revenues in the US, and Gartner has found that 2023 budgets represent 9.1% of total company revenues across North America and parts of Europe. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> We know from experience that these averages are too often taken at face value. When budgets are lower than average, CMOs inevitably yammer for more spending power. And when they are higher than average, the CFO can find reasons to tighten the financial thumbscrews.</p><p> We argue, however, that an average marketing budget can be highly misleading for planning purposes. CMOs should heed the Monty Python film <cite>Life of Brian</cite> — “You&#39;re all individuals. … You&#39;ve all got to work it out for yourselves!” — and select appropriate peer benchmarks. To help leaders do this, we analyzed marketing budget data through a new lens.</p><p></p><h3> The Key Differentiator: A CMO&#39;s Realm of Control</h3><p> So if the average marketing budget is not correct, which size does fit?这得看情况。 First, the average glosses over systemic sector differences. As The CMO Survey shows, for example, at an average of 13.9% of revenues, B2C marketing budgets tend to be higher than B2B budgets, which average 9.3%. Taking a different view, product brands tend to have higher marketing budgets, at 11.4% of revenues, than service brands, at 10.3%. Companies with $10 million or less in sales have the largest budgets (16.8% of revenues), but this number drops to 9.5% for companies with $10 billion or more in sales. Similarly, budgets exceed 17% at companies with 50 or fewer employees, but they drop to 9.8% for companies with 10,000 or more.</p><p> But why does company size matter, and why are B2C and product brand budgets higher than B2B and service brand budgets? To examine this question, The CMO Survey asked 314 marketing leaders about the breadth of their strategic responsibilities. We found that a significant factor affecting marketing budgets is the realm of control CMOs have at different types of companies. The results highlight significant deviations in marketing budgets based on these responsibilities and entirely account for variations based on company size. In fact, the marketing responsibilities we refer to below account for over 71% of the differences between sectors. In other words, although a peer-benchmark budgeting approach might be appealing, it is also misleading.</p><p></p><p> Our research showed that in 28% of companies surveyed, marketers&#39; job descriptions did not extend beyond communications to operational responsibilities such as sales or e-commerce. And for those “comms-only” companies, marketing budgets were roughly half of the average, at 5.6%. (Almost universally, communication activities included positioning, brand advertising, digital brand promotion, PR, social media, and/or lead generation.) In B2B comms-only companies, marketing budgets stood at 5.9%, or less than two-thirds of the sector average, and in B2C companies, they stood at a meager 4% — less than one-third of the sector average. Comparisons for service (6.1%) and product brands (5.1%) tell a similar story. Surprisingly, for these comms-only brands, budgets are actually larger for B2B and service companies than for B2C and product brands — the opposite of what we see in the average analysis.</p><h3> Strategic Marketers Have the Biggest Budgets</h3><p> In companies where marketing is responsible not only for communications but also for at least one key <em>operational</em> activity — such as sales, distribution, customer service and experience, e-commerce, or customer relationship management — the average budget is higher, at about 7.6%的收入。</p><p> As in the comms-only organizations, B2B budgets (8.1%) are higher than B2C budgets (5.7%). However, among these marketing-plus-operations companies, budgets are back to being higher for product brands (8.6%) than for service brands (6.8%), which makes sense given the potentially higher channel costs for the former. Having said that, even for this broader realm of control, budgets are still lower than the average, even at the sector level.</p><p> The real difference maker is the addition of at least one <em>strategic</em> activity, such as new products and innovation, market selection and entry, pricing, or growth, to a company&#39;s marketing responsibilities. Among them are areas that business schools have traditionally taught as marketing functions but are not under the auspices of marketing in many companies. The average budget for marketing functions responsible for communications, operations, and strategy stands at 13.4% across companies. Among these, it is now higher for B2C brands (15%) than B2B brands (11.8%) because B2C marketers tend to have a broader realm of control than B2B marketers do. Interestingly, budgets for these companies are also higher for service (14.5%) than for product brands (12.8%), perhaps due to customer experience expenditures.</p><p> Many more areas of control could be considered. When marketing is responsible for privacy in addition to the more traditional marketing functions above, overall budgets leap to 17.7% of revenues. And when managing talent is added to the mix, marketing budgets account for a whopping 23% of revenues. However, comparisons here become unreliable, especially at the sector level, because there are relatively few companies at which marketing is responsible for areas such as talent (11.5%) or privacy (9%).</p><p></p><p></p><p>这个故事的寓意是什么？ If your budget-setting process relies on averages as a benchmark or the wisdom of crowds, make sure you&#39;re using the right crowd as a peer comparison. This requires identifying a benchmark that matches the responsibility profile for your company. Our CMO Survey analysis now provides a way to do so. While the above numbers don&#39;t provide a personalized benchmark, they are far more meaningful than the broad averages typically kicked around in research reports and the popular press.</p><p> A final thought for CMOs is that it&#39;s not all about the money. Above-average budgets come with above-average responsibilities. And that is a topic for organizational design: selecting a distribution of responsibilities that fits the company&#39;s strategy and marketing capabilities.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>