<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 18 日星期三 14:39:50 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>推动护理危机的真正问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">杰克戴利</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论的自由文本。对于每条评论，我们分析了它是否提到了 200 个主题之一，并评估了护士对该主题的评价是积极还是消极。这些主题源自对员工体验的各个要素的研究，包括文化、薪酬和福利、工作时间表以及感知的组织支持。我们将相关主题聚集成两打更广泛的主题。</p><p>我们将这些主题用作 XGBoost 模型中的特征，该模型以 5 分制预测每位护士对其现任或前任雇主的总体评分。然后，我们计算 SHAP 值（为模型中的每个特征分配一个重要性值），以直接比较不同主题在预测工作满意度方面的相对重要性（通过每个护士给雇主的总体评分来衡量）。我们还使用文本分析来比较旅行护士与医疗保健系统工作人员的护士谈论话题的积极程度。</p><p>使用护士提到的主题以及他们对每个主题的情绪作为预测变量，我们的模型解释了护士之间 29% 到 39% 的评分差异——几乎比我们使用所有权、组织类型和位置所能解释的要高一个数量级作为预测因子。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></p></aside><p>医疗保健领导者面临着一系列艰巨的挑战——成本上升、向数字医疗的过渡以及支付模式的转变等等。但根据美国医疗保健高管学院最近的一项调查，医院首席执行官面临的第一大问题是员工短缺和倦怠。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> 90% 的受访首席执行官将护士短缺视为一个特别严重的痛点。</p><p> 2021年，在美国工作的注册护士总数出现40年来最大降幅，其中年轻护士的流失率最高。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>到 2025 年，美国医疗保健系统可能会短缺多达 45 万名护士，比患者护理所需的护理人员数量少 20%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p>高度的工作不满和倦怠正在驱使护士离开这个行业。 COVID-19大流行给所有医护人员带来了巨大压力，但自大流行结束以来，护士的不满和倦怠并没有改善。从某些角度来看，情况可能会变得更糟：2021年，近三分之二的注册护士会鼓励其他人成为一名护士，但只有一半的人表示他们会在两年后推荐护理作为职业。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>了解护士不满情绪的最丰富来源之一是他们在 Indeed 和 Glassdoor 等招聘网站上如何用自己的话描述自己的工作。这些信息数量庞大，但难以综合，因为其中大部分采用非结构化自由文本的形式。为了了解护士面临的挑战，我们分析了自疫情爆发以来，其中 15 万名护士在 Glassdoor 评论中如何描述其雇主。 （参见“研究”。）在本文中，我们分享了该分析的重要见解，并就如何解决护士最紧迫的问题向医疗保健领导者提供建议。</p><h3>医疗保健领导者脱节</h3><p>护士认为他们的经理与患者护理的日常现实脱节。我们将他们对管理者的评价分为近 50 种领导特质。第二个最常被提及的特征是，管理者没有意识到护士在工作场所面临的挑战。当护士们讨论管理者如何理解床边生活时，十分之九的评论都是负面的。</p><p></p><p>护士们尤其批评高级管理团队成员的脱节。高层团队因脱节而受到批评的可能性是一线主管和中层管理人员的 10 倍。我们的结果证实了另一项调查，其中近一半的医院护士表示，他们认为管理层没有倾听他们的担忧。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>为了解决不满和倦怠问题，医疗保健领导者必须首先了解床边发生的情况。这可能具有挑战性，特别是在拥有数千名护士跨多个地点和专业工作的大型医疗保健系统中。</p><p>从历史上看，领导者一直在努力系统地分析护士挫败感的金矿，这些见解可以从员工调查或外部审查中的评论中收集到。阅读、理解和分析大量非结构化文本数据根本不切实际。然而，人工智能的最新进展使得识别大量文本中的深层模式并大规模理解反馈成为可能。领导者现在可以挖掘自由文本，以深入了解导致护士不满和倦怠的问题，并利用这种洞察力改善护理人员的工作生活。 （请参阅“文本分析入门”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>文本分析入门</h4><p>我们的研究分析了来自数百个组织和数十万名护士的数据，但您也可以更深入地研究自己员工的反馈。无论您是在内部、通过劳动力分析功能还是与外部合作伙伴一起开发人工智能文本分析功能，您都应该牢记这些原则，以最大限度地提高文化衡量的有效性。</p><p><strong>精确度很重要，但记忆力也很重要。</strong>精确度（被正确分类为讨论某个主题的文本实例的百分比）是自由文本分析的关键要素。召回率也是如此——文本分析平台捕获的文本正文中主题提及总数的百分比。如果您仅通过精度来衡量成功，那么您最终会得到一个高度准确的分析平台，但会忽略员工实际所说的大部分内容。复杂的人工智能工具将识别俚语、习语、首字母缩略词、文化参考和组织特定的语言，以捕获很少提及但信息丰富的术语的长尾。</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p><strong>让主题专家了解情况。</strong>文本分析的核心是将自然语言分类为有意义的主题。理想情况下，衡量文化的人在开发分析主题时应聘请主题专家。主题专家可以确保所选择的文化和工作场所主题得到明确定义、与现有研究相关联并得到适当衡量。</p><p><strong>李克特问题有严重的缺点，但适度使用会非常有帮助。</strong>太多的李克特量表问题可能会导致调查者进入自动驾驶模式。但李克特的问题不应该被完全抛弃。有效的文化衡量将广泛主题（例如参与度、流失意图和其他重要衡量标准）的李克特规模结果与自由文本数据相结合，以确定在数百个自由文本主题中哪些对结果具有最强大的影响。</p><p><strong>透明度很重要，而且未来可能会更加重要。</strong>虽然人工智能将如何受到监管还有待观察，但立法者或法院可能不会善待黑盒模型做出的重要决策，而不解释这些模型如何得出结论。领导者经常依靠文化衡量来做出重要决策，例如薪酬政策、人事变动以及如何优先考虑资源。他们应该警惕完全依赖做出人类无法理解的决策的模型。</p><p><strong>员工们讨厌你监视他们——而且你不会学到太多关于文化的知识。</strong>领导者应该抵制诱惑，将文本分析工作扩展到电子邮件、Slack 渠道、电话消息和其他并非旨在提供员工反馈的沟通形式的内容。许多员工认为监听他们的工作谈话是窃听或更糟的行为。此外，工作电子邮件和 Slack 消息所包含的文化信息往往比明确邀请员工讨论组织中有效和无效的问题提示少得多。让员工倾听双方同意的意见，并让老大哥远离工作场所。</p></div></article></aside></div><h3>通过基准测试确定相对优势和机会</h3><p>不同雇主的护理满意度差异很大。我们确定了美国 200 家最大的医疗保健雇主，包括医院和医疗保健系统、家庭医疗保健提供者、老年生活设施运营商以及人才中介机构。对于每位雇主，我们计算了从 COVID-19 大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月，护士在 Glassdoor 上对组织和高级领导层的评价<a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">。6</a></p><p>在大型雇主中，护士的 Glassdoor 评分范围从很差（2.6）到近乎完美（4.9）（满分 5 分）。护士对大流行期间和之后高级领导表现的评估更加多样化，在相同的 5 分制中，从 2.1 到 4.9 不等。 Glassdoor 评级的巨大差异与另一项调查一致，该调查显示美国 60 家医院中护士不满意的比例从 2% 到 48% 不等。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工可以使用我们的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">交互式工具</a>来查看他们的组织相对于其他组织的排名。该指数根据护士的总体评分、对最高领导层的评估以及护士满意度的四个最有力的预测因素进行排序：薪酬、工作量、组织支持和有毒文化。 </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4>护士如何评价他们的雇主？</h4><p class="caption">使用护理满意度指数来比较护士如何评估 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工体验。</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p>平均而言，在人事代理机构工作的护士（有时被称为旅行护士）比其他护士更满意。我们样本中排名最高的五家雇主（前十名中的六家）是人才中介机构。</p><p>当然，较高的薪酬是造成这种差异的部分原因，但不是全部。我们比较了在人才中介机构工作的护士与医院和医疗保健系统雇用的护士谈论 200 个话题的积极程度。 （参见“人事机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高”。）虽然机构护士对薪酬的看法更有利，但围绕解决护士问题和开放、诚实的沟通问题，两组之间的情绪差距更大。通过将护士视为客户，人才中介机构擅长提高满意度，而不仅仅是支付更高的工资。其他医疗保健领导者可以从他们的例子中学习，我们将在下面提出一些具体建议。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高</h4><p class="caption">我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月期间美国 Glassdoor 护士评论的自由文本，以了解他们对各种话题的积极评价。然后，我们将在人才中介机构工作的护士的积极情绪与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士的积极情绪进行了比较。虽然人事代理机构在许多关键主题上的评分较高，包括诚实沟通、有效解决问题和建立信任，但医院和医疗保健系统在学习和发展、福利、同事和晋升机会方面表现更强。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3>优先考虑工作满意度的驱动因素</h3><p>为了了解护士工作满意度的驱动因素，我们分析了样本中护士自 COVID-19 大流行开始以来撰写的所有评论的自由文本，并将文本分为近 200 个主题。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>然后，我们将主题分为两打更广泛的主题，并使用这些主题来预测护士对其雇主的总体评分。然后我们比较了每个主题在预测收视率方面的相对重要性。 （参见“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素。”）</p><p></p><p>薪酬是护士对当前雇主满意度的首要预测因素，这并不奇怪，因为在我们分析的期间，通货膨胀侵蚀了实得工资的购买力。工作量的重要性是第二重要的驱动因素，这与另一项大规模调查的结果相吻合，该调查发现人员配备不足是护士工作不满、倦怠和辞职意愿的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p>工作量和薪酬是护理危机必须解决的根本原因，但它们并不是影响护士工作满意度的唯一因素。我们的分析揭示了工作环境的其他方面，包括有毒文化、组织支持、工作时间表、沟通、学习和发展机会，领导者可以关注这些方面来改善护士的工作生活。</p><p>该分析还强调了不太可能改善护士工作场所体验的领域。福利固然不错，但无法弥补繁重的工作量或跟不上通货膨胀的工资。强调促进患者健康的企业使命也无济于事。护士们已经知道他们的工作有更高的目标；这就是为什么他们中的大多数人首先成为护士。</p><h3>挖掘自由文本以获得可行的见解</h3><p>许多医疗保健组织依赖年度员工调查，其中有数十个项目按 5 分制评分，并事后添加了一些开放式问题。面对一长串的多项选择题，员工很容易转向自动驾驶仪，并为非常不同的项目分配相似的分数。问题的选择限制了员工可以讨论的内容，而且很少有空间来扩展他们为什么选择特定的数字答案。</p><p>开放式的自由文本反馈提供了丰富的细致入微且可操作的见解来源。当护士可以决定要写哪些主题时，他们会利用自己的自由来讨论对他们来说最重要的事情。开放式问题为护士提供了用自己的语言阐述他们的担忧、提供关键背景并针对他们面临的问题提出具体和可行的解决方案的空间。个人自由文本回复可以汇总为更广泛的主题，以确定领导者可以集中注意力和有限资源的优先顺序，以最大程度地提高护士满意度。</p><p>虽然组织平均值很有用，但重要的是要记住，不同的亚文化可以在同一组织内共存。对于通过并购发展起来的大型医疗保健系统来说尤其如此。例如，一家全国性连锁医院在近 50 个地点的评级范围为 1.9 到 3.9。医疗保健领导者不能仅仅依赖组织平均水平，而必须衡量和分析地点、部门、职能、团队和个人领导者之间的差异。</p><p>女性、代表性不足的少数族裔和年长员工也会体验到与其他员工截然不同的组织文化。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>了解不同员工群体工作满意度和倦怠的驱动因素至关重要。</p><p></p><p>领导者可以挖掘免费文本，详细了解特定群体最关键的痛点，并相应地调整干预措施。例如，日程安排对护士的工作满意度有重大影响，但日程安排的哪些方面最重要将取决于具体职位。轮班安排的灵活性和不间断工作休息的能力对于医院和初级保健机构的护士来说非常重要，而家庭保健护士则非常看重可预测的时间表。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p>护士的意见为改善工作场所和患者护理提供了宝贵的实用建议。例如，我们研究的 Glassdoor 评论包括数十条关于雇主如何改进日程安排的可行建议。有些是易于实施的行动，例如使用应用程序更容易接班或调换班次，或者向最后一刻接班的护士支付 20 至 50 美元的奖金。其他则是更为系统性的改变，比如让护士加入一个制定时间表的委员会，或者确保接受学费援助的员工能够安排他们的课程的工作。</p><h3>倾听离开您组织的护士的心声</h3><p>大多数组织将调查范围限制在现任员工。离职面谈如果有的话，也是随意进行的，而前员工的反馈往往被视为不满者的咆哮。但忽视前员工的反馈是一个很大的错误。 </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p>对前员工进行访谈或调查可以揭示他们离职的原因，并找出留住人才的最有效行动。由于没有报复的威胁，即将离开（或已经离开）组织的护士更有可能提供坦诚的反馈，甚至是当前员工不愿讨论的禁忌问题。通过收集离职者的反馈，组织可以发现潜在的盲点。</p><p>在我们的样本中，超过三分之一的 Glassdoor 评论是由前员工撰写的，这些评论提供了对用脚投票的护士最重要的见解。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a>图左侧的条形图“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素”对预测离职护士如何评价其前雇主的因素进行了排名，它揭示了护士可能离职的一个关键原因。</p><p>在 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">之前的一篇文章</a>中，我们认为五种行为属性——不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待——将组织文化标记为有毒。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>在辞职的护士中，有毒文化对他们总体满意度的预测作用是薪酬或工作量的两倍多。有毒工作场所对辞职护士的重要性与早期的研究一致，该研究发现毒性是大辞职的前六个月内行业调整后人员流失的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p>在大流行后时代，有毒文化对于护士来说变得更加重要。当我们比较哪些因素最能预测护士在大流行前后对雇主的评价时，发现在 COVID-19 之后，有毒文化的相对重要性获得了最大的提升（其次是工作量、幸福感和薪酬）。如果您的组织遭受文化毒性，我们的另一篇文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">如何修复有毒文化</a>”提出了几种基于证据的干预措施，医疗保健领导者可以用来为自己的组织排毒。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素</h4><p class="caption">我们将超过 150,000 条护士的 Glassdoor 评论文本分为两打影响员工体验的主题，然后分析哪些主题最能预测护士如何评价其雇主。该图表通过显示每个主题对整体预测的贡献程度，对每个主题在预测这些评级中的重要性进行排名。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3>学习人才中介机构的做法</h3><p>正如“人事机构在许多关键因素上评分较高”这一数字所示，护士对人事机构为快速有效地解决问题而制定的流程非常积极。在提及人事代理机构流程效率的护士中，75% 的护士持积极态度，而只有 23% 的护士对医疗保健系统表示积极看法。对于旅行护士来说，常见的流程问题包括入职、获得所需的证书和执照、合同谈判和报销。最好的人才中介机构会听取反馈，深入了解旅行护士面临的典型问题，并优化工作流程来解决这些问题。</p><p>专职护士遇到的许多痛点与机构护士所遇到的痛点有所不同。然而，医疗保健系统、家庭保健机构和长期护理提供者可以采用类似的方法来捕获和分析护士的反馈，优先考虑他们面临的最常见和令人沮丧的挑战，并与工作人员合作解决这些问题。</p><p>持续倾听反馈并采取行动也可以与护理人员建立信任。与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士相比，人事机构的护士更积极地认为拥有心理安全感，可以说出困难的问题并让别人听到。</p><p>然而，如果管理层对护士提出的问题反应迟缓，心理安全的好处就会减弱。护士们高度评价人才中介机构对她们的问题和疑虑的快速反应。相比之下，护士经常抱怨其他类型的雇主即使得到回复，也对提出问题的电子邮件回复缓慢。护士还非常重视与主管的多种沟通渠道，包括短信、电子邮件、Facebook、Jabber 和 24/7 热线。</p><p>我们研究的另一个见解是护士重视诚实和透明度。他们和任何人一样了解医疗保健面临的挑战，并且希望就组织中正在发生的事情、它如何影响他们以及做出决定的原因进行诚实的沟通。 Triage 是一家人才中介机构，也是我们研究的第四高评价的大型雇主，它将诚实的沟通置于其价值主张的中心：“我们按事实说话，这样你就不会对其进展感到惊讶。” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p>医疗保健系统可以向人才中介机构学习，但也可以利用自己的独特优势来吸引和留住护士。全职护士在组织生活的三个重要方面对医院和医疗保健系统的评价高于人才中介机构：学习和发展（包括晋升机会和培训报销）、福利和同事。这三个因素是护士评价雇主的十大预测因素之一。医疗保健系统应投资于其比较优势，并在向潜在和现有员工传达其价值主张时强调这些优势。</p><p></p><h3>将反馈转化为行动以建立信任</h3><p>收集员工反馈是一回事，但持续根据这些见解采取行动则是另一回事。如果员工认为管理者不会采取行动，他们就不太可能提出问题或提出潜在的解决方案。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>更糟糕的是，如果员工认为管理层缺乏权力、资源或兴趣根据他们的建议进行变革，他们更有可能辞职。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a>近一半的护士认为管理层不会解决临床工作人员提请他们注意的问题。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p>组织需要建立适当的结构，以一致地根据员工的反馈采取行动。一个著名的例子是 Kaiser Permanente 的单位团队 (UBT)，该团队由经常在特定单位或部门一起工作的临床工作人员和管理人员组成。 <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a>这些团队每月至少召开一次会议，对其部门的绩效负责，并由一名经理、一名劳工代表以及通常还有一名临床工作人员共同领导。</p><p> UBT 确定了四个方面的改进机会：质量（包括患者治疗结果）、患者服务、负担能力和员工体验。团队利用员工反馈来识别改进机会并确定其优先顺序。接下来，团队使用最佳实践和基于证据的方法开发和测试解决方案。一旦解决方案被认为有效，就会在整个单位、部门，或者在某些情况下整个组织中实施。然后，UBT 监控这些变化对患者治疗结果、员工满意度和成本降低的影响。</p><p></p><p>自 COVID-19 爆发以来，我们对美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论进行了研究，结果显示，护士对雇主的整体评价存在很大差异，特别是在薪酬、工作量、有毒文化和组织支持方面——这四个因素对雇主的影响最大。塑造护士的工作满意度。我们认为，这种变化传达了希望的信息。尽管所有医疗保健组织都面临结构性挑战，但<em>仍有</em>可能提供一个让护士每天都期待上班的环境。</p><p>许多组织，包括一些最大的护士雇主，都有很大的改进空间。这些排名的目的不是为了“点名羞辱”，而是为了让医疗保健领导者意识到他们的组织绩效与为护士提供健康工作场所的可能性之间存在巨大差距。我们还希望有关医疗保健组织如何在对护士最重要的因素上排名的客观数据可以为他们的领导者提供改进的动力，并提供证据让所有利益相关者相信变革的迫切需要。</p><p></p><p>领导者不应该做的是要求护士更加努力地工作，承受更多的挫折和压力，却不能理解和解决使许多人的生活变得悲惨的组织因素。当工作人员辞职、工人成立工会以及州和联邦立法者制定保护护士利益的法规时，继续照常营业的领导者不应感到惊讶。</p><p>为了改善护士乃至所有卫生保健工作者的工作生活，领导者必须收集他们的反馈并根据他们的反馈采取行动，认识到组织的不同部门和不同人群将面临独特的挑战和问题。倾听护士的心声表明，医疗保健领导者可以采取一些有意义的措施来解决护理危机。最重要的一步是首先倾听他们的意见。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>探索护士如何评价他们的雇主</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>为了了解护士面临的工作挑战，医疗保健领导者需要倾听护士自己关于职业倦怠的说法。我们分析了自 COVID-19 大流行开始以来美国护士撰写的 150,000 条 Glassdoor 评论的自由文本，并将这些文本分为两打主题，我们用这些主题来预测护士对其雇主的总体评分。</p><p>我们计算了每个主题在预测护士总体满意度方面的相对重要性。有毒文化、组织支持、薪酬和工作量这四个因素成为护士对其雇主满意度的最强预测因素。</p><p></p><p>对于医疗保健领导者来说，一项重要发现是：在辞职的护士中，与薪酬或工作量相比，有毒文化对他们总体满意度的预测能力是其两倍多。</p><p>雇主之间护士的工作满意度差异很大。我们的交互式护理满意度指数显示了护士如何评估美国 200 家最大的医疗保健雇主的员工体验，其中包括医院和医疗保健系统、家庭医疗保健提供者、老年生活设施运营商和人才中介机构。</p><p>对于每位雇主，我们计算了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月，护士在 Glassdoor 上对组织和高级领导层的评价。我们还报告了护士对薪酬、工作量、有毒文化和组织支持的评价如何。每个雇主在所有维度上的得分均以高于/（低于）所有 200 名雇主的平均值的标准差表示。</p><p><a href="#interactive-launcher">探索上面的索引</a>。</p><p class="attribution">图片来源：杰克·戴利</p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>医疗保健领导者需要了解哪些内容来应对护理短缺：护士的发言</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的多媒体编辑。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>护士们精疲力尽并离开这个行业，人们担心迫在眉睫的护理短缺将影响患者护理的许多方面。是什么导致了这种倦怠？对于护士的工作满意度来说，最重要的是什么？医疗机构中有毒培养物有多常见？医疗保健领导者可以采取哪些措施来改善这些问题？在这段视频中，我们与五位现任和前任护士交谈，了解医疗保健工作的现实，包括他们经历过的有毒文化和压力源，并从他们和医疗保健专家那里获得有关需要改变的建议。</p><p>文章作者兼研究员 Donald Sull 还讨论了护士在工作网站 Glassdoor 上对 150,000 条雇主评论的分析所揭示的工作满意度真相，以及医疗保健领导者可以从中学到什么。</p><p></p><p> “我们的研究中关键的、可操作的发现是，护士通常会非常详细地告诉你什么对他们不起作用，并且他们会提供具体的建议来解决这些问题。他们想提供帮助。他们希望自己的声音被听到，并且希望产生积极的影响，”萨尔说。</p><p> “作为一名护士，最困难或最令人沮丧的事情之一就是没有足够的时间陪伴病人，”曾担任儿科肿瘤科和 ICU 注册护士 18 年的 Jennie Evans 说。 “在那些时刻，你可以坐下来，与患者交谈，握住他们的手，与家人交谈，真正了解他们，不仅了解疾病，还了解患者可能存在的其他潜在焦虑或恐惧。”</p><p>观看视频，更多地了解护士们希望医疗保健领导者了解有毒文化、心理健康、成长机会以及对护理人员至关重要的其他问题。</p><p class="attribution">图片来源：杰克·戴利</p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>升级文化以促进增长和转型</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander 是霍特国际商学院的战略顾问和实践教授。他在决策、解决问题和文化方面的研究成果发表在<em>《哈佛商业评论</em>》、 <em>《麻省理工斯隆管理评论</em>》和<em>《沃顿知识》上</em>。 Per shares his thoughts and ideas on his blog <a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">leadershipbackbone.com</a> . Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> P. Hugander, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , May 22, 2023.</p></aside><p> Many leaders know that their organization&#39;s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don&#39;t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and growth. But despite ambitious efforts to infuse such skills into their culture, many organizations fail. The secret to success: Shorten the time to reward when people experience the new skills helping teams beat longtime challenges.</p><p> Per Hugander has helped leaders at organizations including Swedish financial services group SEB make progress on complex strategic challenges. His practical approach helps people to link psychological safety to tangible business results.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why many organizations fail at culture change: Just testing the waters can be dangerous.</li><li> How to go deep — not wide — on culture change and win over skeptics.</li><li> How to put the new skills to use quickly on the organization&#39;s toughest problems and create lasting culture benefits.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Steps to Build and Sustain Diversity in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> , Ed.D., is a managing partner and the US practice leader of CEO and Board Services at Boyden, a global executive search firm. He built his career as a turnaround (glass cliff) specialist in corporate America and writes on issues related to diversity, governance, and strategic growth for private and public corporations and boards.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; however, less attention is paid to what happens after the hire. Only when we effectively create a more equitable landscape and support women and people of color in navigating it can we benefit from the full engagement and contributions of all of our people and avoid losing them to turnover or disengagement.</p><p> Occupational minorities — those individuals who are <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">relative rarities</a> in their profession due to their gender or sexual identity, ethnicity, age, or other factors — have accomplished what countless more have only dreamed of: They have broken through the glass ceiling, navigated the often inhospitable <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">corporate jungle</a> , and often successfully negotiated the <a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">glass cliff</a> . Although the executives who represent diverse populations in your organization have successfully overcome these challenges, an important task remains: building a path for others to follow. This is hard, painstaking work that requires many different tools and competencies, yet it is necessary if others are to safely navigate the landscape.</p><p></p><h3> Steps to Sustaining Diversity</h3><p> Although various resources offer suggestions for how professionals from underrepresented populations can navigate and overcome organizational challenges, it is equally essential that organizations identify where <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">persistent systemic bias and racism</a> lurk and take concrete action to address them. Organizations can take the following five steps to begin the process of creating more inclusive environments where all employees have equal opportunities to thrive and advance in their careers.</p><h4> Step 1: Establish leadership commitment to diversity with sponsorship.</h4><p> Leadership throughout the organization must demonstrate a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion. When leaders model these behaviors, employees throughout the organization naturally follow their example. However, this commitment cannot be limited to one-off efforts or statements on corporate values.</p><p> Leaders must consciously exhibit their commitment to hiring people from underrepresented populations by helping to develop and equip these candidates for advancement. Specifically, every leader, regardless of organizational level, should identify at least one such candidate to intentionally sponsor. After getting to know the candidate&#39;s background, career goals, and support needs, the leader should (1) counsel them in navigating the organization, (2) support them in developing the competencies needed to advance in their career, and, critically, (3) help them secure progressive leadership positions.</p><p></p><p> Although formal mentoring, sponsorship, and buddy programs can be helpful in this effort, relationships that develop informally often are equally, if not more, rewarding and beneficial and tend to continue long after one or both individuals have advanced in or moved out of the organization.</p><h4> Step 2: Remove glass ceilings by addressing systemic factors.</h4><p> The metaphor of the glass ceiling depicts the systems of discrimination that prevent certain groups of people (typically women and people of color) from accessing high-level opportunities for career growth and advancement. Clues that glass ceilings exist within your organization include a lack of diversity within the upper-management and executive ranks compared with your overall workforce; pay disparities between individuals with similar roles and qualifications; limited mentorship, sponsorship, development, or advancement for certain groups of people; explicit or implicit biases regarding which groups are a better fit for leadership roles than others; and attrition levels within underrepresented groups that exceed those of other groups.</p><p> To identify and eradicate glass ceilings in your organization, closely scrutinize every aspect of the employee experience. For example, address biased hiring and promotion practices using blind recruitment techniques; review salary ranges and promotion criteria to ensure that equal pay is awarded for equal work; and make clear career paths and development opportunities available to all employees. Diversity goals, inclusion initiatives, and employee education on recognizing and avoiding unconscious biases also can support a diversity-conducive climate. Supporting flexible work arrangements and work-life balance can encourage the full participation of employees who might otherwise be overlooked due to their needs to balance personal and professional responsibilities.</p><p></p><h4> Step 3: Reduce glass cliffs through due diligence.</h4><p> The term <em>glass cliff</em> describes a phenomenon in which women and other minorities are preferentially selected for leadership positions in times of crisis, placing them at increased risk for failure. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This phenomenon occurs across industries and geographies, and for women and ethnic minorities alike. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The problem with giving people from underrepresented populations leadership opportunities only in times of crisis is that those who lead during turbulent times tend to be seen as part of the problem, which perpetuates stereotypes and reduces future opportunities for such candidates. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> To avoid this outcome, care must be taken to recognize and fully examine the situation before assigning a leader to address it. While the temptation to dive in and do something to “stop the bleeding” is overwhelming, taking the appropriate time to first fully understand the problem is a small price to pay for a much-improved chance of success. The diagnosis process should include identifying project parameters (such as performance targets, deadlines, and budget), project stakeholders, past actions taken, the current situation, and desired outcomes — from the perspectives of all stakeholders. My article on the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">glass cliff phenomenon</a> provides more details on the process of due diligence and the questions that can be used to diagnose these situations. Only after diagnosing the problem will it be possible to select the most appropriate candidate to lead the effort.</p><h4> Step 4: Broaden the pathway by changing the conversation.</h4><p> Corporate environments can be fraught with challenges for women and people of color. Many challenges are systemic, such as organizational cultures that <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">disadvantage certain groups</a> versus others, or workloads and behavioral expectations that require long hours in the office and around-the-clock responsiveness. These systemic challenges can make the corporate landscape seem foreign and antagonistic. In turn, occupational minorities might compensate by nursing cognitive biases that result in too much or too little confidence; limiting their social networks to similar peers rather than nurturing<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">vital connections</a> to sponsors, mentors, and career guides; and failing to strike an appropriate work-life balance.</p><p> Although leaders must deliberately sponsor occupational minorities (Step 1), mentors, sponsors, and allies throughout the organization also play important roles in guiding candidates toward success because they, too, have already successfully navigated the organization. Supporting emerging leaders means changing the typical mentoring conversation. Typical conversations involve identifying a mentee&#39;s short- and long-term goals and seeking the mentor&#39;s situational advice, guidance on skill development, and feedback on performance. Mentoring that supports diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging should be adapted to include a clear framework for professional development, an explanation of how various opportunities and positions contribute to the candidate&#39;s career goals, and a discussion of how to navigate the organizational culture — all in light of the glass ceilings, glass cliffs, and systemic challenges they face as occupational minorities.</p><p> Cognitive biases also should be part of the conversation so that candidates can avoid the traps of both being overconfident and overcompensating for perceived shortcomings. Evaluation and adjustment of cognitive biases might be best accomplished by gathering 360-degree feedback regarding the mentee&#39;s performance on key tasks and engaging the mentee to describe their feelings, thoughts, and general experiences related to performing those tasks. Overconfidence might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is at or below average while their own experience of that task reflects strong enthusiasm, satisfaction, and a sense of achievement. In contrast, overcompensation might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is evaluated as or above average yet their described experiences suggest that they are spending too much time on tasks or that they harbor concerns about their performance.</p><h4> Step 5: Measure and track progress.</h4><p> A popular business adage is that we must inspect what we expect. This truism applies equally to any diversity effort. The process begins with defining what success looks like according to key diversity metrics such as hiring, retention, and advancement for various employee populations. It might be tempting to stop there; however, defining the goal is only the beginning. Additionally, it is necessary to measure the organization&#39;s current performance on these KPIs and then examine why that is the current state. Understanding the organization&#39;s current performance requires the following assessments:</p><p> <strong>1. Gauge buy-in.</strong> To what extent do organizational leaders and members understand and agree that the KPIs defined are the right indicators and performance targets?</p><p> <strong>2. Gauge feasibility.</strong> What organizational structures, processes, and other features facilitate the achievement of the KPI? What features threaten or obstruct achievement?</p><p> <strong>3. Gauge support needs.</strong> Leaders are taught to adapt to the needs of individual subordinates based on each person&#39;s skill level. In the same way, leaders throughout the organization need to adjust the amount of oversight, encouragement, and direction they provide as departments and employees across skill levels work to achieve diversity goals. For example, a recruiting department that is relatively inexperienced at hiring professionals from underrepresented groups will need strong, step-by-step guidance and frequent feedback until their competency grows, while a manager who is highly skilled at developing and including such professionals generally should be allowed the autonomy to exercise their talents to their fullest.</p><p></p><p> As initiatives are implemented, continue to regularly assess these metrics to gauge your progress and fine-tune your efforts. As the saying goes, “What gets measured gets done.” Achievement of your diversity goals will happen only if they are deliberately defined and regularly assessed.</p><p></p><p></p><p> I often have been one of few Black leaders in the organizations where I&#39;ve worked. At one point in my career, I was a town hall presenter at two meetings separated by level — one attended by rank-and-file employees, and the other attended by management. Although the Black customer service representatives were pleasantly surprised to see someone who looked like them in an executive role, I was shocked and dismayed to realize that nearly our entire customer service representative force was Black while all of our supervisors and managers were White. This was puzzling because the leadership team seemed to care about diversity from a recruiting standpoint, but it was glaringly obvious that systemic barriers were obstructing the retention and advancement of professionals from underrepresented groups.</p><p> Often, it is only when executives, board members, or the HR team notices a lack of diversity in their organization&#39;s upper levels that problems in the talent management system are noticed — but typically poorly understood and only rarely solved. Such disparities in advancement might be at least partially explained by inhospitable organizational settings and the need to broaden the pathway for these professionals from underrepresented populations to succeed.</p><p> Organizational leaders, coaches, mentors, sponsors, and other potential career enablers all have a part to play in eliminating sources of inequity and equipping occupational minorities to survive and thrive in corporate environments. As more and more diverse groups of professionals travel the pathway to career success, the pathway will become smoother and broader, resulting in an ongoing and cumulative organizational transformation.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why Pay Transparency Regulations Are a Strategic Management Opportunity</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>Tamara Montag-Smit is an assistant professor of management at the University of Massachusetts (UMass) Lowell. Karoline Evans is an associate professor of management at UMass Lowell. Brandon Smit is an assistant professor of management at Bentley University. Cassondra Batz-Barbarich is an assistant professor of business at Lake Forest College.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Annalisa Grassano</p></figcaption></figure><p> Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, <a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">pay transparency laws</a> are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women&#39;s Law Center reports that altogether, more than one-quarter of US employees live in a location where <a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">pay information is regulated</a> .</p><p> By and large, pay transparency regulations have emphasized disclosing a salary range for advertised positions and internal opportunities for advancement. These laws are designed to ensure equal pay for equal work and effectively close the gender wage gap. The logic is simple: If underpaid employees, including women and minorities, aren&#39;t aware of what their coworkers are paid, they are at a significant disadvantage in leveling the playing field through litigation and negotiation. How can inequities be addressed when they remain in the dark? Without pay transparency, enforcement of existing laws, such as the <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">Equal Pay Act of 1963</a> , becomes difficult. Based on <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">recent cases</a> and notable discrepancies that have been exposed (some spanning years of underpayment), it seems that greater transparency has an important role to play.</p><p></p><h3> Organizational Responses to the Changing Regulatory Landscape</h3><p> Despite the increasingly widespread adoption of pay transparency regulations, many organizations have responded with pushback, resistance, and minimal compliance. After Colorado became the first state to require organizations to disclose pay ranges in advertised positions in 2021, organizations soliciting applicants from across the country began <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">explicitly excluding Colorado residents</a> from consideration to skirt the new laws, prompting the state&#39;s department of labor to issue <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">warnings and fines</a> . Another organizational tactic is to comply with pay information requirements with pay ranges that are so wide that applicants cannot meaningfully predict what salary they might be offered. In one notable example, Netflix posted a job with a salary range that <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">spanned $90,000 to $900,000</a> .</p><p> While approaches to compliance with transparency laws at the organizational level have taken many forms, leaders have expressed several common concerns regarding the potential negative consequences of pay transparency to their business operations and culture:</p><ul><li> <strong>Will everyone just ask for more money?</strong> More pay information might prompt more conversations about pay (and why someone is receiving what they are). Managers worry that they&#39;ll be caught in the middle trying to juggle competing goals around budgeting and employee satisfaction.</li><li> <strong>What happens if some employees find out that they&#39;re paid less than others?</strong> Explaining to long-standing employees why they are paid the same as a new hire is likely to be uncomfortable and prompt substantial criticism of the employer.</li><li> <strong>Will pay transparency affect our ability to work together?</strong> Pay transparency can elicit jealousy and counterproductive competition when individuals perceive themselves as inequitably rewarded. Managers worry that employees might fight and undermine one another when discrepancies are exposed.</li></ul><p></p><h3> New Insights Into Managing Pay Transparency</h3><p> Our work provides new insights into addressing some of the main questions organizations have about transparency. Most new laws focus exclusively on creating pay transparency by requiring organizations to disclose pay ranges for open positions. In academic research, this form of transparency is referred to as <em>distributive transparency</em> , because it reveals information only regarding the <em>amount</em> of money employees are paid.</p><p> In our research, however, we have delineated several ways in which pay information can be transparent. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> With <em>procedural transparency</em> , the emphasis is on sharing information about how pay <em>decisions</em> are made; at the most transparent level, this would include a formula for calculating compensation (such as base pay or a merit-based raise).</p><p> Distinguishing between distributive versus procedural transparency is crucial because, as our research shows, procedural transparency can mitigate many of the risks and drawbacks associated with distributive transparency.</p><p> Implicit in pay transparency regulations is the idea that underpaid employees will take it upon themselves to <a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">negotiate for a fairer wage</a> . In fact, a large-scale study of over 100,000 academics over the past two decades found that changes in pay transparency were related to significantly more wage parity between men and women. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> However, the research also showed that transparency doesn&#39;t equate to <em>everyone</em> asking for more.</p><p> To explore this further, we conducted a series of four experiments to better understand <em>how</em> and <em>when</em> pay transparency can encourage employees (especially women) to more effectively negotiate for fair wages. In our first study, lab participants were paid for their performance after four rounds of a popular word search game and were given the opportunity to negotiate for better compensation. In studies 2, 3, and 4, online participants prepared themselves to go into a performance review, armed with varying degrees of information regarding performance and pay, to possibly negotiate for a better annual raise. They were told that they were slated for a 3% raise but that raises could range from 3% to 10%. Across these studies, we varied the amount of information participants could access regarding both the amount other people were paid and participants&#39; performance relative to their peers&#39;.</p><p> These studies yielded four important findings regarding distributive and procedural pay transparency:</p><p> <strong>1. People made clearer comparisons.</strong> We found that the best predictor of whether someone tried to negotiate for higher pay was their performance relative to that of peers. Compared with average performers, high performers were approximately 50% more likely to request higher pay when they knew their ranking relative to others. It&#39;s important to note that in our study, participants saw the previous year&#39;s performance and pay data for their team members, and it was clear that increased performance was directly related to increased pay. Although not an explicit formula indicating performance-based pay, this information provided a clear signal to participants that pay raises were largely determined by performance.</p><p> <strong>2. People negotiated fairly.</strong> Average performers were more likely to accept the minimum raise offered to them, often citing the raise as fair based on their performance. As one person stated, “Considering I only met expectations throughout the year rather than exceeded them, asking for a higher raise seems fruitless and unearned.” Generally, average performers rarely asked for the maximum raise, in part because they considered the fact that they were performing at a lower level than some peers. This was true, though, only when they had all of the information. When they were told nothing about their performance, 85% of people requested the maximum pay amount. Lacking performance information, average performers asked for the highest raises available within the pay range.</p><p> <strong>3. Women <em>do</em> ask for higher pay.</strong> Counter to a pervasive assumption, women didn&#39;t seem to need much encouragement to negotiate. In fact, when the percentage of participants who negotiated is considered, women were often more likely than men to negotiate (though this was not a statistically significant difference). These findings cast some doubt on the idea that one reason for the gender wage gap is that women negotiate less often than their male counterparts. Recent research combining information from dozens of negotiation studies has come to the same conclusion: Many of the negotiation gaps between men and women have largely disappeared in recent years. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Although this is good news, it does little to close the gender pay gap as it currently stands.</p><p> <strong>4. People were motivated to perform better.</strong> Average performers expressed motivation to work harder and perform better to earn a higher raise during the next review cycle. When asked why they did not negotiate for more money, one participant stated, “My numbers did not show that I deserved a higher raise. With better numbers the following year, a case would be made for a higher raise.” Another stated, “I knew I&#39;d done an average job, so I hope to do better in the future and hope to get a better raise next year.”</p><p> Our findings replicate and extend an old but powerful notion in management research: the <em>fair process effect</em> . <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Employees will accept unfavorable outcomes if they believe those outcomes were produced by a fair system. Put differently, if people know <em>why</em> they are being paid less (in other words, there is procedural transparency), they will not respond negatively and might even work harder.</p><h3> Make Pay Transparency a Win-Win for Your Organization</h3><p> Pay transparency can be a win-win opportunity rather than a compliance hurdle. But simply listing pay data in job postings without any context in response to regulations might be a big mistake. These practices not only disregard the spirit of the laws but also come at a heavy price and forfeit significant opportunities. Leaders should think beyond compliance and consider ways to strategically leverage pay transparency for their organization to improve applicant attraction and employee retention. Our research offers some insights into how this can be done.</p><p> <strong>Make pay only <em>part</em> of the transparency equation.</strong> Counter to some pervasive fears that transparency will increase labor costs, cause jealousy, and create conflict, the reality is that secrecy around pay creates problems of its own. As researchers at Payscale found, most employees are <a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">unsure whether they are paid fairly</a> , with many believing they are underpaid when they are not, which leads to greater turnover and dissatisfaction. Our research suggests that without a reference point for performance, employees have little to no basis for judging what compensation would be fair and are therefore more likely to make unreasonable requests. Transparency in both performance <em>and</em> pay can enable employees to better assess the fairness of their pay and make more reasonable requests.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on the pay decision-making process.</strong> Procedural transparency helps managers more clearly communicate with employees about pay because salaries/bonuses are based on performance rather than on seemingly intangible or, worse yet, bias-laden factors. Providing information on how pay is determined helps incumbent employees understand why their pay is higher or lower than their peers&#39; and, more importantly, how to move up. Managers can&#39;t be accused of favoritism and bias when pay is directly determined by performance, which puts them in a collaborative role during pay conversations. With a focus on performance, these conversations can focus on development and examine how employees can perform better and earn higher raises.</p><p> <strong>Recognize that (distributive) pay transparency will not fix inequity on its own.</strong> There&#39;s an assumption that distributive pay transparency will close pay gaps; however, evidence suggests that this alone is not enough to create an equitable workplace. Research has shown that women and men are <em>asking</em> for salary increases in <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">relatively equal proportions</a> , but women are still less successful at getting what they ask for. Distributive pay transparency can help reduce some ambiguity, but both performance and pay transparency (procedural transparency) together equip employees with the tools they need to ask for what they deserve. When people know what to expect from negotiations (that is, what the bargaining zone is and what&#39;s reasonable to ask for), gender differences are minimized. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> For example, <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">women of color</a> don&#39;t often take advantage of opportunities to negotiate roles, responsibilities, or flexible work arrangements, creating long-term inequities that explain pay gaps beyond starting salary. Broader transparency helps reduce the ambiguity that often leaves women and members of other minority populations hesitant to negotiate, even when they know they could.</p><p> <strong>Consider the benefits for current employees <em>and</em> applicants.</strong> Simply posting pay ranges is only one piece of the puzzle. Applicants have negative reactions to excessively wide pay ranges because they don&#39;t offer useful information. In this case, pay is still essentially secret. As we found in our study, without meaningful information, individuals are inclined to ask for the maximum amount to see what is possible. This creates yet another headache for hiring managers. A better approach would be to leverage procedural transparency to clearly outline the factors used when determining a salary offer, and perhaps even how heavily those factors are weighted. For example, Buffer, a marketing company, has done a great job of creating a <a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">pay system</a> that balances simplicity (for better understanding) and complexity (for capturing nuance) by using a standard formula for making pay decisions: salary = job type x seniority x experience + location + $10,000 or equity.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Despite organizational concerns and hesitancy to implement government regulations around pay transparency, such policies continue to gain traction and are just one force behind growing expectations around salary disclosures. In a 2022 report from HR technology firm Visier, 79% of surveyed employees said they want <a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">pay transparency</a> ; Gen Z employees were the strongest proponents of it.</p><p> Our research highlights the potential for procedural transparency to strategically mitigate the perceived organizational risks while also meeting legal requirements and social expectations. While changes are clearly happening, we hope business leaders think more deeply and creatively about <em>how</em> to make pay transparent in ways that both support organizational goals and meet employee needs.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Delicate Dynamics of Challenging a Superior</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>Benjamin Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one&#39;s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person and the situation.</p><p> For those keen on maintaining professional decorum and growing in their roles, this guide can help ensure that your challenging conversations are both constructive and respectful.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Choose your battles wisely.</strong> Workplaces are vibrant ecosystems of opinions, processes, and methodologies. It can be enticing to address every single discrepancy or divergence in opinion that one encounters, but wisdom lies in discerning which battles are worth fighting. Every time a potential disagreement arises, consider: Is this issue so significant that it warrants a confrontation? Minor differences in opinion might be addressed more effectively through passive channels or should even be overlooked. But larger concerns, especially those affecting team dynamics, company culture, or broader business objectives, require a more direct approach.</p><p> <strong>Understand the importance of timing.</strong> In the world of professional communication, timing can be everything. Choosing the right moment can make the difference between a concern being genuinely considered or hastily dismissed. Before even considering challenging a superior, it&#39;s crucial to pause and assess the situation from a holistic viewpoint. Is your concern so immediate that it demands to be addressed immediately? Alternatively, would it be better to earmark it for a detailed, private discussion later? It&#39;s wise to avoid confronting superiors during high-pressure situations or public forums because it can be misconstrued as an attempt at disruption or showmanship. By choosing the optimal time, you create a smoother path for constructive dialogue.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prioritize private discussions.</strong> The environment in which you choose to voice your concerns plays a pivotal role in how those concerns are received. Engaging in public disagreements or conflicts can lead to multiple unforeseen complications, including being perceived as aggressive or confrontational. By choosing a private setting for these discussions, you provide both yourself and your superior with an atmosphere conducive to open and genuine dialogue. This approach not only minimizes distractions and potential biases but also reinforces the idea that the intent is constructive feedback, not public criticism.</p><p> <strong>Master the art of “I” statements.</strong> Effective communication is as much about content as it is about delivery. The words we choose and the manner in which we frame our concerns can significantly influence the reception of our message. Instead of adopting a potentially confrontational tone, use “I” statements to express observations, feelings, and suggestions. For instance, instead of bluntly stating, “You&#39;ve overlooked this crucial aspect,” a more collaborative approach would be, “I feel that this particular aspect could benefit from further attention.” This approach ensures that the focus remains on the issue at hand and not on personal biases or confrontations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Embrace the feedback process.</strong> The journey of challenging a superior or expressing concerns is inherently bilateral. It&#39;s not just an avenue for you to voice your thoughts but also an opportunity to understand the other person&#39;s perspective. Demonstrating a genuine openness to feedback, even if it&#39;s contradictory to your viewpoint, is vital. This approach not only paves the way for mutual respect but also fosters a culture of continuous learning and collaboration within the organization.</p><p> <strong>Align with like-minded peers, but tactfully.</strong> While individual concerns have their merit, there&#39;s undeniable strength in numbers. Finding allies or colleagues who share your perspective can provide additional weight to your concerns. However, it&#39;s imperative that this alignment is not perceived as cliquey or divisive. The primary focus should always remain on the collective benefit of the organization rather than on forming factions within the team.</p><p> <strong>Keep the organization&#39;s goals at the forefront.</strong> Any concerns or challenges you raise should inherently resonate with the broader objectives and goals of the organization. By consistently aligning your feedback and suggestions with the company&#39;s mission and values, you reassure your superiors of your commitment to the collective success of the organization over your individual aspirations.</p><p> <strong>Brace for a spectrum of outcomes.</strong> While we all hope for positive and constructive outcomes from our disagreements, it&#39;s essential to be prepared for a variety of reactions. Your superior might be receptive, indifferent, or even defensive. By anticipating these potential responses and planning your strategies accordingly, you ensure that you remain balanced, constructive, and professional, irrespective of the immediate feedback.</p><h3> The Aftermath: Reflect, Adapt, and Evolve</h3><p></p><p> Every professional interaction, especially those involving challenges or confrontations, provides a rich opportunity for personal and professional growth. After the discussion, take the time to evaluate the effectiveness of the conversation, the strategies employed, and the outcomes achieved. These reflections will bring invaluable lessons to light and help you to continuously refine and enhance your communication skills for future challenges.</p><p> Ultimately, while the task of challenging a superior might seem steeped in potential pitfalls, with the right strategies and a focus on mutual growth and respect, it can be navigated with tact and professionalism. Encouraging open dialogue and a culture of feedback is the bedrock of innovative and forward-thinking organizations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Ghost Scenarios Haunt Strategy Execution</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang is a senior fellow in management practice at the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Collaborative Strategy Lab. Rafael Ramírez is professor of practice at Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Scenarios Programme.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, have observed that business leaders are inclined, and their organizations configured, to work with only a single implicit view of the future. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That view is typically deeply embedded within their strategies as a set of unquestioned assumptions about the future context. We call these sets of unexamined assumptions <em>ghost scenarios</em> because they are invisible — and because they may come back to haunt executives and companies in unanticipated and unwelcome ways.</p><p></p><p> Underpinning every ghost scenario is a small set of implicit trends that leaders project into the future without questioning whether they might change. Consider the ways in which dramatic changes in climate have come to haunt rail services in Britain. In July 2022, temperatures above 40 degrees Celsius (104 degrees Fahrenheit) were recorded in the country for the first time. These high temperatures heated the rails to slightly over 62 C (143 F), causing them to bend. As a result, many train trips were canceled and service on other routes slowed to 60 mph. The rail tracks had been engineered for a future in which the air temperature did not exceed 27 C (80 F). In short, the British rail network was designed and built to work not in the scenario in which it found itself in 2022 but in a scenario that made the implicit assumption that historical climate trends would continue unchanged.</p><h3> Assumptions Hide in Plain Sight</h3><p> Research on human perception has demonstrated that people differentiate the object of their visual focus from its background by bringing that object to the forefront of their attention while everything else recedes. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Humans can focus on either the figure or the background but never both at the same time.</p><p> The <a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">Rubin vase illusion</a> is a well-known example of this figure-ground (or background) perception challenge. Depending on how you look at the picture, you will see either a vase or two faces in profile. Importantly, however, you cannot see both at the same time: One or the other perceptually recedes to become the background of the figure you see. To see both figures, you must alternate between them.</p><p> It&#39;s important that executives are able to recognize how people&#39;s ability to focus can also blind them to important contextual information, since leaders often fail to see the background upon which their strategies will play out — and on which their strategies depend. They may consider hard infrastructure — such as rail tracks — to be a relatively static background issue and focus their attention on trends that seem more salient to business planning, such as changes in customer preferences and habits. But that can lead executives to implement a strategy that may be unexpectedly disrupted by the unexamined assumptions about its context that are woven through its background issues.</p><p></p><p> Particularly today, given the fast pace of change, soaring uncertainty, and high levels of turbulence, failing to surface the assumptions built into strategic planning is risky, as is a failure to consider multiple possible alternative futures through <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">scenario planning</a> . <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Scenario planning exercises can help executives explore how their strategies might play out in different business contexts and conditions, with an eye toward honing those strategies to be more effective.</p><p> To understand how scenario planning can keep executives from being haunted by a ghost scenario, let&#39;s look at two global organizations we recently worked with in the Oxford Scenarios Programme. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA Examines Its ESG Assumptions</h3><p> Insurance company <a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a> serves 95 million clients in over 50 countries with products and services in the areas of property-casualty insurance, life insurance and savings, and asset management. One of the company&#39;s key strategic goals is to sustain its climate leadership position. Wisely, executives from AXA decided to make the future context of that goal the focus of their attention for a limited period of time so that they could explore how it might change and how they might need to adapt if it did.</p><p> The company was particularly interested in understanding how future environmental, social, and governance (ESG) trends might affect its stated goal. For example, what might be the impact of some US states&#39; proposed legislation that would penalize financial institutions pursuing ESG investment strategies? Or, how might the public react if companies are seen as greenwashing or misrepresenting their ESG credentials? Thus, instead of letting ESG requirements, as currently understood, be the ghost scenario, the company asked questions about the future of ESG and, more broadly, about the emerging sustainability context for corporations.</p><p> Participants and facilitators in the scenario-planning exercise worked in teams to look at the future environment. One scenario imagined that stand-alone insurance companies had been swallowed up by dominant tech platforms whose own ESG priorities superseded those of the insurers. In another scenario, governments set stringent regulations regarding ESG issues, with compliance implications for companies&#39; strategic choices. In yet another imagined future, climate change accelerated more than expected, causing businesses to shift their priorities to urgently address climate-related crises — or to focus exclusively on reducing CO2 emissions, abandoning social and governance agendas.</p><p> By explicitly engaging with the ghost scenario and its equally plausible alternatives, AXA came to understand that continuing to strive to deliver superior ESG performance as it is currently understood might not be the only future it should be preparing for. Within AXA, these insights have been used to inform a conversation about future ESG challenges and their implications for possible announcements and commitments to be made, including when and with whom. They&#39;ve prompted AXA to start preparing alternative strategies in the event that delivering great performance against current ESG expectations becomes irrelevant.</p><p></p><h3> Swift Anticipates Digital Currencies</h3><p> Swift (the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication) is a member-owned cooperative that enables financial messaging and related services for cross-border payments around the world. It currently delivers over 30 million messages a day for more than 11,000 institutions in over 200 countries and territories. It was created in the early 1970s by 239 banks in 15 countries to solve the growing problem of clunky, slow, and costly cross-border payments communications via a new technology platform. With disruption as part of its origin story, Swift is proactive about potential changes in its context.</p><p> In 2021, Swift executives were interested in understanding how digital currencies, including those issued by central banks, might evolve in the years ahead. The category more than doubled in 2021, to more than 9,000 cryptocurrencies.</p><p> Rather than assuming this unfolding and rapid growth in digital currencies to be the only possible scenario, executives at Swift paused to better understand what other developments might occur, how they might shape the future digital currency ecosystem, and how Swift might be affected. For example, economists and other experts have pointed to the lack of intrinsic value of many digital currencies, as well as concerns about <a href="https://concerned.tech/">the security and reliability of their underlying technologies</a> .</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Where the Ghosts Hide in Common Strategic Planning Processes</h4><p> <strong>In a SWOT analysis,</strong> leaders consider their organization&#39;s strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats in relation to only the current scenario and to known competitors, suppliers, customers, regulatory rules, and the like. When identifying and analyzing risks, executives implicitly assume that there is only one scenario. However, in another context (a different scenario), risks might evaporate and new opportunities might arise.</p><p> <strong>In stakeholder mapping,</strong> leaders make an assessment about the attention and power of stakeholders now and in one expected future. An implicit scenario is the background to this assessment. But the importance of stakeholders could change significantly if the context unexpectedly changes.</p><p> <strong>In game theory and war-gaming,</strong> competitors&#39; moves are considered within the context of a ghost scenario, and war games are typically conducted with no consideration of a different future other than the one that is underway. However, changing scenarios could require new tactics and surface unforeseen future combatants.<br /></article></aside></div><p> Swift&#39;s own stance on digital currencies was open and neutral. It would potentially support them if they were properly regulated and added value to the economies, businesses, and communities it served.</p><p> The scenarios developed for Swift&#39;s executives explored different ways in which trust in the technology might evolve. In some of them, trust associated with digital currencies would disappear as the opaque technology and algorithms upon which they are based became suspect. In other scenarios, digital currencies could be manipulated, and thus the authenticity of what was being exchanged could no longer be guaranteed. And in another scenario, a more generalized lack of trust in for-profit financial institutions would spread to providers of digital currencies, leading some segments of society to hesitate to engage with either, with related consequences.</p><p> For the Oxford participants envisioning these scenarios, it was not clear that the values held by those promoting the technology, or the values that the technology supposedly enabled, would be accepted by governmental regulators or by those in society at large in all imaginable future contexts. Swift&#39;s executives have since explored those sets of scenarios, which provided rich and divergent insights about the ways digital currencies might pan out. Those insights have helped them avoid relying on overly simplistic views of the future — and being swayed by hype.</p><h3> How to See a Ghost Before It Haunts You</h3><p> Based on our experience leading scenario planning exercises for AXA, Swift, and many other organizations, we have developed the following suggestions for executives who want to bring their ghost scenarios into view and make the figure-ground reversal a key part of their strategy practice.</p><p> <strong>Use scenario planning to acknowledge implicit assumptions.</strong> Recognize that every organization&#39;s strategy presumes a future scenario that often remains unquestioned. That is, every executive engages in a form of implicit scenario planning, whether they are conscious of it or not. Making scenario planning a regular part of the strategy-making process achieves two important goals: It alerts leaders to how turbulent conditions could change the context within which they work and compete, and it acknowledges the reality that current conditions themselves present a hypothetical future scenario, not a fixed reality.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize the figure-ground dilemma.</strong> Acknowledge that the figure that is attended to (most often, the organization&#39;s strategy) and the background that is so often ignored (the unexamined ghost scenario) cannot successfully be the focus of attention at the same time. Instead, executives need to flexibly and sequentially shift between the two to investigate each fully and avoid the trap of making implicit assumptions about the other. AXA took the time to deliberately explore the future of ESG rather than assuming there would be no changes to how it is currently used and understood. Swift purposefully focused on understanding the potential future contexts of digital currencies rather than just implicitly assuming subsequent options from the existing trends.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Dedicate executive time and resources to the problem.</strong> Organizations must intentionally create a time and space for leaders to explore how relevant economic, political, technological, social, and environmental factors might be changing. Contrast a small set of future scenarios with the ghost scenario to pinpoint where current strategy might need to be adapted to be well positioned for the range of ways the context might develop. Some organizations even have dedicated units, such as the <a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">Global Business Environment scenarios team</a> at Shell International. <a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">Policy Horizons Canada</a> plays this role for the Canadian government.</p><p></p><p> For all of these efforts to be truly useful, scenario planning outputs must be fed back into strategic decision-making rather than written up in a report and placed on a shelf. They should also be disseminated more widely in an organization so that people at all levels and functions can consider possible implications from their own perspective — implications that might not occur to leadership. For a strategy to be successful when the context changes, executives need to have a balanced approach — recognizing both figure and ground as important areas for discernment. That is, they must recognize the importance of the background or ground upon which their actions will play out, even as they plan their next move. Savvy executives know that they must both envision and embrace change. The trick is learning to adeptly shift one&#39;s attention between the figure and the ground to see how the context might unfold, so it doesn&#39;t leave your strategy ungrounded.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Fueling Interdisciplinary Innovation With AI: Volvo&#39;s Anders Sjögren</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automotive Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory. On this episode of the Me, Myself, and AI podcast, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Anders joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to explain the ways the carmaker uses data and artificial intelligence to inform manufacturing — ensuring that parts are made consistently and as efficiently as possible — as well as driver experience and safety. He also outlines some specific ways smart technology keeps drivers alert and aware of conditions around them and describes Volvo&#39;s approach to technology-driven innovation. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/MMAI-S8-E1-Sjogren-Volvo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Anders Sjögren"></p><h4> Anders Sjögren, Volvo Cars</h4><p> Anders Sjögren is senior technical leader for Volvo Cars. He focuses on strategy, research, innovation, and transformation, with the key objective of ensuring that the automaker understands and executes within the continuously emerging areas of data, analytics, and artificial intelligence. Application areas include creating AI-enabled intelligent customer functionality and using AI to reform Volvo&#39;s operations and development activities. Sjögren has an academic background in mathematical statistics (large-scale and computational aspects) and an industrial background in data-centric methods development and software product development.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one carmaker use AI to bring together all of the complex systems required to engineer a safe and high-performing vehicle? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m Anders Sjögren from Volvo Cars, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Today, Sam and I are delighted to be joined by Anders Sjögren, senior technical leader, data, analytics, and AI-enabled engineering, at Volvo Cars.让我们开始吧。 Anders, welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So tell us a little bit about your role at Volvo Cars.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m a technical leader in data, analytics, and AI in the engineering part [of the organization], so that&#39;s the R&amp;D. So, essentially, what comes in is a wish for a car, and what comes out is drawings and code. In that area, there are, of course, a lot of possibilities for data analytics and AI, both during the development process and also as part of the actual functions in the car — so intelligent functions and personalized functions and so on.</p><p> So my purpose here is really to make sure that we get the value that we can through data, analytics, and AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is [your focus] the AI and data analytics that go into the car — like the sensors and all kinds of intelligent devices in the car that make driving safer and more interactive, and things like that? Or is it also customer acquisition and dealer networks and all kinds of data analytics to run a business of making and selling cars?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yes. So, I mean, all of those apply to Volvo Cars, but the part I&#39;m really active in is more in the part of the making of the car.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think that&#39;s a great point because when most people think about cars and artificial intelligence, I think they immediately jump to this idea of fully self-driving cars. And what you&#39;re pointing out is how much other stuff that there is going on, even in the production of cars, that can benefit from artificial intelligence. You know, I think perhaps everyone&#39;s frustrated that we don&#39;t have fully automated cars now, but there&#39;s so much going on behind the scenes that people don&#39;t get a chance to see. What are some of the examples of the ways that you&#39;re using artificial intelligence in the production process?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we take a little bit of a step back, the goal of Volvo Cars is really to give people the freedom to move in a personal and sustainable and a safe way.</p><p> If we start with “personal,” then it&#39;s really critical that we understand you and make you feel special as a customer or as someone in the car. And there, of course, it has to do with starting with the sensors and then really interpreting those values. That can be cameras, different types of steering input …</p><p> Another area is definitely sustainability. AI is being used there to make sure that we have as many lightweight parts as possible. So using AI, one can, for example, get mechanical parts with the same strength and those kind of properties, but with much lower weight and less material that&#39;s being used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In the design process, you&#39;re talking about, right? As engineers consider all the different permutations of parts, yeah?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> In the design process — yes, exactly. That&#39;s really the essence of AI, I think, in lots of engineering activities, is that we go from manually deciding first what we want to do, but then actually performing all the different steps. That&#39;s the current way of doing it, while in the AI era, it&#39;s much more about deciding and describing what are the aspects I want to reach to? What are things I want optimized, and what are maybe the boundary conditions? And then the AI helps you get there.</p><p> So in the context of the mechanical parts, you might say, “These are the attachment points. These are the strength and stiffness properties I want. Give me the part with those properties but [make it] as light as possible and also, of course, possible to produce.”</p><p> That could be one area. And also, it is super important for sustainability that we use as little material as possible and also have as low a rate as possible.</p><p> And then, of course, the third point was about [safety]. And, of course, we have autonomous cars, but also, even before that, there are other types of functionality being used. For example, understanding the driver: Is the driver aware or not? Should we maybe nudge him to take a cup of coffee or something if he seems to be tired?</p><p> In the later versions of our cars, we understand if there are some pets or children left in the car, maybe on a hot day, and then preventing them [from getting] hurt in such a situation and so on.</p><p> I&#39;d say that those are some of the areas where AI can really be a core technology in bringing us toward our purpose.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s really interesting because lots of times organizations tell us they start with a problem they&#39;re trying to solve and then find a technology to solve it, and that makes sense, because otherwise you&#39;re trying to find a problem to fit a solution, which seems backward. You mentioned that your cars can sense … if a person or a pet is accidentally left in the car. How did Volvo make the decision to focus on that particular problem to solve?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> A lot of what we do is really created by real-world safety in that we actually see what are the actual causes of people getting injured. I mean, if we take the analogy with crashes and that type of safety, we have teams that go out to sites when there has been a crash to really see what actually happened in reality and not just on certification [from] that type of crash test and so on.</p><p> And, going back to this example, if we look here, pets and kids do get hurt — hopefully not in a Volvo car, but that&#39;s reality, right?</p><p> But what you mentioned there is really super interesting because then it also goes the other way around: Like, now that we have these sensors, what are the other really valuable functionalities that we can provide our customers with through this, of course, taking privacy into account and so on?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is quite intriguing because Volvo … I remember as a child that my uncle used to say, “You want a safe car, you get a Volvo.” And it&#39;s always been synonymous with safety, and it&#39;s really amazing to step back and think about ... for a company who has put one of its main goals for safe experience, now, with the availability of this amount of data and all of this massive amount of processing, I could imagine there are so many use cases that, to Sam&#39;s point, are being thought about. So that&#39;s really, really encouraging.</p><p> What [does] the road map here look like? I mean, is this a constant sort of innovation ideation approach going on to say, “What else could we do in these three pillars of personal, safe, and sustainable?” What is the process for coming up with these ideas and picking up the good ones and pursuing them or not?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think that those ideas can either come from the technology side and be really inspired by that, or it could come from the analytics side. And often it&#39;s when the new technology and the really customer-centric needs … where they meet, and also, of course, where we have the agility in the organization to execute on it. That&#39;s really where we have something that&#39;s really fruitful. It&#39;s typically a mix of different sources of this: innovations and new directions, I would say.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And there&#39;s a mechanism to create this interdisciplinary inspiration in the company?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I would say so. I would say that there are both formal mechanisms but also informal mechanisms. [As] a car company, Volvo Cars is not super big. Of course there are also smaller ones, but I think it&#39;s also an advantage that, I mean, pretty much all the different steps, from product strategy, design, the R&amp;D, engineering, and then the later stages …</p><p> The headquarters is in Gothenburg [in Sweden], within walking distance. The US department is literally 50 meters from where I&#39;m sitting right now, while 50 meters in the other direction, there are the crash test facilities and the safety center.</p><p> So, what I want to say with that is that it&#39;s more easy to get connections and to create this kind of — how should I put it? — informal innovation activities.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is where relatively smaller size and colocation really, really helps. To have teams that close to each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s funny to talk about it being small, because it&#39;s certainly not a small company.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, I guess. As we&#39;re chatting, I&#39;m thinking about some of the people we&#39;ve talked to before, and one of the recurring themes that people have mentioned is, oh, this idea [of] starting with a business problem: “You don&#39;t have AI and find a place to use it. You start with a business problem and then solve it.” But this is kind of a nice mix on that — that it sounds like there&#39;s a lot that starts with a business problem, but then, interestingly, once these processes are in place, and once these technologies are in place, then there becomes a grassroots innovation to say, “All right; how can we use that?” And that&#39;s an interesting perspective that, I think, hasn&#39;t come through strongly — or maybe I&#39;m forgetting something — but it seems like that hasn&#39;t come through as strongly. This is a nice mix of that, that maybe works in this size organization … this colocated organization.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, and not least in the prototyping and ideation stages. But, then, of course, before it actually goes into the product, it needs to go through a more thorough review and so on.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> There&#39;s been quite a few investments and acquisitions of smaller AI startups and firms by Volvo. Tell us a bit about the overall ecosystem of internal and vendor and partner companies that come together to bring to life some of these AI-enabled ideas that you&#39;re talking about. Is it internal? Is it external? Is it a mix? How do you think about the ecosystem?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I would definitely say that it&#39;s a mix. Some of the things … we need to do it ourselves to get the full understanding or where we really want to be in the forefront, and [in] some other areas, we definitely want to partner with other companies that are strong in those areas. Traditionally speaking, a car is a super complex product. It has hundreds or thousands of different parts that all need to come together. And, of course, it is a space where there is traditionally a lot of suppliers supplying different parts.</p><p> Lately, we are moving more toward bringing software implementation in-house to increase the speed and agility in the development process.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That seems particularly complicated in auto manufacturing because if I think about how cars got started, they were independent systems. There was a braking system, and a power train system, and an air conditioner, and an infotainment system, and all these were separate. And that&#39;s kind of nice because then we have a certain, different standard than we would have for the infotainment system than we would have for the braking system — or at least I hope that there would be. But what you&#39;re pointing out is, each one of these may be using sensors that come from a different area, and how the whole car has become more complicated independently, but it&#39;s also become more complicated cohesively, trying to connect all these parts and have them work together.</p><p> And that seems, on the one hand, an opportunity for artificial intelligence but, at the same time, a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah. It&#39;s 100% true. It&#39;s both a really big opportunity, but that also means that&#39;s really one of the core challenges — I mean, how to build the cohesive understanding of both the inside and the outside of the car.</p><p> We speak about the customer digital twin and vehicle digital twin and so on, and in some sense, those aspects can mean a lot of different things. But, of course, these different systems that you speak about, they are traditionally in different parts of the company, so that also means that there is a lot of cross-functional collaboration that is needed. But we really need to bridge those kind of organizational borders.</p><p> I think that that&#39;s really one of the key points — that is, in order to get successful adoption of the analytics and AI, it really means that different parts of the company need to work together to make it happen. Because otherwise, it will just become a silo. Some people will not really have the benefits of it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You know, it&#39;s very true. It&#39;s a common theme, and in our work at BCG, we have this rule of thumb — the 10:20:70 — where we say 10% is the data and algorithms, and 20% is the technology and the digital platform, but 70% of it is the business integration and implementation and bringing different parts of the organization together. This, perhaps, is nowhere more true than at a car company, where you have, as you said, Sam, seemingly disparate systems that are coming together to create a bigger system, but each one of these units has been perfected individually, and now you want the collective perfection as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we talked a lot about Volvo. How did you personally get interested in artificial intelligence, in data, in technology and analytics? What&#39;s your origin story?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think I&#39;ve always been interested in computers. My father was really an addict, so I kind of grew up with that.</p><p> I started out as an engineering student [and got a] master&#39;s in computer science. And then I started off as a research engineer in the medical area, at the university hospital in Gothenburg, then found out fairly quickly that in order to really make use of data — conclusions and so on come from data … so I then went into the area of mathematical statistics.</p><p> So I did a Ph.D. in that, then went back to software product development. After some time, I went back to academia for a couple of years, did a postdoc, and then was offered a good opportunity at Volvo Cars. So I&#39;ve essentially been here for seven years now. That&#39;s a bit of my history.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Quite inspiring.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we also want to ask you a few rapid-fire questions, and the idea is just to answer it as quickly as you can. These are not particularly Volvo questions.</p><p> What have you been proudest of that you&#39;ve done with artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The problem is that most of the things, I can&#39;t speak about.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer too.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You have to wait and see. OK, well, what worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The worries?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Oh, I think, of course, one is the longer term — the kind of singularity things. But I think a bit closer to now, so to speak, we definitely see that this super-fast progression of large language [models] and what they can do, and also the kind of systems that don&#39;t just take one problem and give one answer but can really produce a series of steps, in sequence. And that is a super-powerful technology, but a super-powerful technology can be used both for good and for bad.</p><p> That&#39;s both something that makes me super excited but also a little bit worried. What will the world look like in 20 years?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Motorcycling, but obviously using technology. But it&#39;s more of a … yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Technology&#39;s involved. Everything&#39;s involved in technology in some way.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, pretty much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were a kid? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Medical doctor.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, that ties with your first career in working in the medical company, then.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I think so, but then I found mathematics and those things to be super exciting, so I went into that area.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What do you hope that we can gain from the advent of these technologies?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we say the greatest wish, I think it is that we find a way to use it in a way for our common good. We need to find a way to integrate it into society, and I think that that is really my biggest wish for it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In a relatively short time, we learned so much about various uses of data, AI, and technology, in just what it takes to build a car in new ways, and all the different ways that AI and tech are helping and serving the people who are driving them. It&#39;s been really enlightening, Anders. Thank you for joining.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thanks for having me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Ways Leaders Can Turn Pushback Into Progress</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phillip G. Clampitt and Bob DeKoch. <p>Phillip G. Clampitt is the Blair Endowed Chair in Communication at the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay. Bob DeKoch is the founder of leadership consulting firm Limitless and former president of the Boldt Co. They are the coauthors of <cite>Leading with Care in a Tough World</cite> (Rodin Books, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it’s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Clampitt-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it&#39;s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns and raising questions to active opposition and sabotage. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> Effective leaders think of pushback as an opportunity to boost their team&#39;s learning while moving their organization forward. The objective should be to increase people&#39;s understanding and build support by tempering both advocate enthusiasm and contrarian pessimism. This deeper level of understanding, while not necessarily satisfying to all in the moment, fosters a climate of candor, humility, adaptation, and trust, thereby subtly steering pushback away from latent disruptive tendencies.</p><p></p><p> Drawing on decades of research, C-suite observations, and interviews, we&#39;ve identified the major mistakes leaders make when encountering pushback and offer five guidelines to help them better respond.</p><h3> What Doesn&#39;t Work</h3><p> Leaders make three primary mistakes when facing ambivalence, disagreement, or resistance:</p><p> <strong>Suppressing uncertainty.</strong> Pushback increases uncertainty when questions are raised that might not have immediate answers or perspectives are introduced that might have recently emerged or been sidelined or overlooked. Some leaders respond to uncertainty-induced pushback by marginalizing concerns, offering placating assurances, or invoking authoritarian voices. Such practices offer false certainty that undermines trust in the long term.</p><p> According to our research, even employees who seek more certainty in their work lives want their organizations to embrace uncertainty. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Effective leaders avoid the temptation to paper over uncertainty, even when they face demands for a level of certainty that simply doesn&#39;t exist. Even if they don&#39;t know the answers now, they can provide an operating level of certainty by discussing how they will find those answers.</p><p> <strong>Ignoring power dynamics.</strong> Leaders with positional or acquired status directly or subtly influence the nature of the pushback. Highly authoritarian power structures tend to drive pushback underground. Likewise, more subtle power signals can suppress open discussion of legitimate concerns. Leaders might then wrongly equate silence with agreement. Some people will feign acceptance while others sow dissent in the “meeting after the meeting,” thereby revealing and often amplifying people&#39;s fears.</p><p></p><p> We had an opportunity to observe one seasoned executive group&#39;s reaction — which consisted of tepid and token feedback — when their CEO proposed a new initiative. The CEO, sensing a lack of candor, probed for more input. One frustrated executive eventually blurted out, “We don&#39;t share our thoughts on this issue because you are going to do what you are going to do, regardless of what we say.” This remarkably candid comment suggested a deeper challenge: How do powerful people with strong views on particular issues encourage candor? Effective leaders take active steps to mitigate disruptive dialogue — discussed below — because they recognize that inherent power dynamics greatly influence the quality of any discussion.</p><p> <strong>Assuming that the loudest voices represent a consensus.</strong> Pushback takes many forms: Some of them are obvious, like complaints or employee petitions, while others are more subtle, like queries in meetings or a lack of engagement. Leaders are often tempted to pay more attention to the most vocal employees, assuming the people with the biggest megaphones represent majority opinion. They may or may not.</p><p> When the loudest or most politically powerful voices dominate the discussion, such dynamics often create an inaccurate impression of the level of support or divisiveness. Effective leaders recognize the peril at either extreme: the enthusiasts glossing over concerning issues or the contrarians undermining potential support.</p><p></p><h3> Recommendations for Engaging With Pushback</h3><p> Effective leaders not only avoid suppressing uncertainty, ignoring power dynamics, and assuming that the most vocal represent consensus opinion — they also take active countermeasures that reflect the following guidelines.</p><p> <strong>1. Set ground rules for the conversation.</strong> Ground rules like the following drive expectations, temper disrespectful advocacy, and increase the value of pushback opportunities for everyone:</p><ul><li> <strong>Seek to understand viewpoints you don&#39;t agree with.</strong> When discussing contentious issues, many people&#39;s first instinct is to offer an instant rebuttal or counterpoint. Resist that temptation by demonstrating a willingness to engage with a differing point of view.提出问题或重新表述别人的论点（尤其是那些你不同意的论点）等简单的策略可以缓和反驳，并且几乎神奇地增强对话语气。同样，诸如“告诉我我的想法可能是错误的”或“我可能错过了一些东西；我可能错过了一些东西”之类的陈述。请说更多”表明对新想法持开放态度。</li><li><strong>尊重地不同意别人的观点。</strong>用诸如“让我提供另一个观点”之类的语言尊重地表达分歧，可以设定正确的讨论基调，同时也鼓励那些比较犹豫的人大声说出来。不愿分享不同观点通常表明存在潜在的信任缺陷。有时，尽管房间里存在固有的权力差异，领导者仍需要鼓励其他人分享他们的担忧。</li><li><strong>避免两极分化、扎根的断言。</strong>过于确定地倡导很可能会引发权力动态问题。表明概率水平，例如“我对这个事实有 95% 的把握”，通常会引发更激烈的辩论。</li><li><strong>消除阻力的个性化。</strong>如果一项决定被贴上“首席执行官计划”的标签，许多人会进行自我审查，并因为害怕冒犯当权者而避免提出担忧。通过在白板上记录问题而不进行归因来消除个性化的阻力，可以减轻这种权力动态，同时缓和强烈的情绪。</li><li><strong>随着讨论的进展改变你的观点和反应。</strong>经常需要提醒员工，在考虑新证据或获得新观点后改变观点并不是软弱的表现。没有人应该担心因为改变观点而丢脸。事实上，有效的领导者会在他们的观点发生转变时通过发表诸如“我看到一个不在我的雷达屏幕上的问题”之类的声明来强调。随着对话的出现，重新构建关键问题以强调新的观点。</li></ul><p> <strong>2. 引导团队了解阻力机会。</strong>许多会议或倡议的推出都以问答期结束，而没有首先向与会者提供有关阻力的期望的方向。由于缺乏清晰度，人们常常会做出各种未经检验和未言明的假设，这些假设可能并不准确。</p><p>一些员工因抵制机会而被剥夺了权利，因为他们认为自己的所有想法都应该被完全接受。他们不期望发生合理的辩论或对<em>他们的</em>抵制进行反击。这就是为什么明智的领导者会仔细地引导员工了解可能的结果，而不是接受/拒绝极端的情况。他们提出了其他替代方案，例如调整计划、引入测试期、推迟实施、修改决定或重新考虑提案。</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. 选择正确的论坛和设置。</strong>有些场合，比如市政厅聚会或在线论坛，往往会鼓励更情绪化的观点表达、姿态和发泄。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>这种情况可能会阻碍那些不太愿意进行情绪化争论的人进行有用的询问和提问。合适的场所和论坛可以最大限度地增加富有洞察力的提问、深思熟虑的讨论和相互尊重的辩论的机会。通常，配备适当讨论参数的小团体效果最好。同样，对较小群体的在线论坛进行适当监控可以鼓励更好的抵制动力。</p><p>领导者还需要注意，有些人不愿意在别人面前分享担忧，因为他们担心被视为团队合作能力差，或者他们对如何表达担忧或捍卫自己的观点缺乏信心。为了鼓励那些不太愿意发言的人，提前向他们提供会议的讨论要点并鼓励他们写下他们的担忧和疑问通常会有所帮助。</p><p> <strong>4.先教育后倡导。</strong>熟练的教育工作者很快就会放弃这样的想法：一个好的解释就足以建立理解。通常，他们会讨论得出结论的方法，包括相反的观点和现有的问题。这种方法将不确定性融入结论，为进一步讨论和相反观点腾出空间。</p><p>相比之下，倡导者很少讨论可能与他们坚定的观点相矛盾的证据或方法。当他们确实接受相反的观点时，他们常常会轻视或嘲笑这些观点。支持者可能会回避任何批评，淡化不确定性，并认为简短的解释会启发其他人。即使是聪明的高管也常常陷入这个陷阱，高估了他们教育工作的程度和深度。</p><p>在教育之后的某个时候，倡导可能会发挥作用，但最终，有效的领导者认为允许人们表达担忧会带来好处。短期来看，阻力可能会导致调整，从而提高长期接受度和顺利实施。</p><p> <strong>5.路标拐点。</strong>随着决策、举措和政策的发展，领导者对阻力的确定性和开放程度也会发生变化。在领导层对这些拐点缺乏明确说明的情况下，员工会采用有关抵制的潜规则，例如以下内容：</p><ul><li>规则A：如果领导还没有做出最终决定，那么我可以大声说出我的观点。</li><li>规则B：如果领导者有很强的立场或者已经做出了最终决定，那么我支持它或者闭嘴。</li><li>规则 C：如果我在一个问题上争论足够长的时间，领导者就会屈服。</li></ul><p>如果潜规则 A 和 B 强化了阻力动态，那么领导者可能会高估某项举措或决策的支持程度。为什么？因为按照规则 B 运作的员工认为反馈请求是为了剧院或旨在制造支持；他们进行自我审查或仅提出象征性的反对。结果，不同意见和潜在有价值的声音都消失了。</p><p></p><p>规则 C 恰恰相反，引发了无穷无尽的争论。这会在决策被调整、修改或最终确定后滋生抱怨文化。高效的领导者知道，开放并不意味着可以进行无休止的讨论。毕竟，反推反推可以永远持续下去。</p><p>阻止这些无声规则扎根的最佳方法是在抵制期间明确指出拐点。以开放之名掩饰自己情绪的领导人破坏了整个对话的坦诚。相反，有效的领导者会分享他们对调整拟议计划的开放程度，宣布他们的情绪何时发生变化，并明确表明抵制的时间何时结束。</p><h3>一个成功的反击故事</h3><p>Capital Credit Union 首席执行官劳里·布茨 (Laurie Butz) 经常使用这些指导方针来进行抵制，以充分了解员工认为随着新举措的推出，他们正在失去什么。例如，随着 COVID-19 威胁的消退，她试图重新启动面对面的全体员工会议，以增强包容性，并就悬而未决的举措进行更强有力、深思熟虑的讨论。她认为教育过程是双向的，这需要更多的面对面论坛，鼓励遵守比屏幕发泄更富有成效的讨论基本规则。</p><p>然而，这一消息遭到了员工的强烈抵制，因为他们需要长途跋涉才能参加一年两次的聚会。一些人通过在线调查表达了对费用和时间的担忧，而另一些人则直接向直接主管表达了不满，认为“Zoom 会议在新冠疫情期间效果很好”。</p><p>巴茨承认了这些担忧，同时恭敬地为现场聚会辩护，因为毕竟，“你可以举办一场 Zoom 婚礼，但会缺少一些重要的东西。”类似的信息在她的“大使”（意见领袖）的更个人渠道中得到了回应。</p><p></p><p>随着时间的推移，面对面的会议 (1) 提高了员工参与度，(2) 重新激发了员工参与流程的兴趣，(3) 引发了对关键问题更深入的讨论。定量证据支持了这些观察结果。例如，在恢复面对面会议后，全员调查的参与率从 60% 增加到 91%，83% 的调查受访者表示他们“高度投入工作”。轶事证据也出现了：员工在离开现场会议时经常询问，“我们什么时候还有机会像这样见面？”</p><p></p><p>通过抑制不确定性、引发权力动态以及过多关注最敢于表达的员工来抑制阻力，很可能会导致短期的顺从和服从，但代价是<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/decision-downloading/">破坏长期信任</a>。巧妙而尊重地管理阻力需要预先投入时间，让员工参与进来，同时提供前进的动力。好处是：领导者学会更巧妙地影响员工如何解释趋势、事件和决策，并对新出现的问题有更深入的洞察。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> ChatGPT 如何帮助经理设计更好的工作角色？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fangfang Zhang and Sharon K. Parker. <p>张芳芳博士是科廷大学变革性工作设计中心的研究员。她还是 CEPAR（人口老龄化研究卓越中心）研究员。她的研究兴趣包括工作设计、工作重塑、工作未来、资历过高和老龄化。莎伦·K·帕克 (Sharon K. Parker) 是科廷大学约翰·科廷杰出教授、澳大利亚研究委员会获奖者、变革性工作设计中心主任。她是澳大利亚社会科学院和工业与组织心理学会的院士。她是 SMART 模型的创建者和 Thrive at Work 计划的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Today’s leaders are pushing to increase employee engagement and decrease turnover but face a harsh reality: widespread employee burnout. To fight it, managers need to offer employees more healthy and meaningful work. In surveys conducted in the United States by Gallup in 2022, 40% of employees reported that their [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Parker-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>当今的领导者正在努力提高员工敬业度并减少人员流动，但面临着严峻的现实：员工普遍倦怠。为了应对这一问题，管理者需要为员工提供更健康、更有意义的工作。盖洛普 2022 年在美国进行的调查显示，40% 的员工表示，他们的工作对他们的心理健康产生了负面影响，约 30% 的员工表示，他们经常感到倦怠。此外，到 2022 年，美国员工敬业度创下七年来的最低点，盖洛普调查显示，只有 32% 的员工表示自己敬业度很高，17% 的员工表示自己在 2022 年积极脱离敬业度<a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">。1</a>在全球范围内，员工缺乏敬业度估计会给雇主带来损失7.8 万亿美元——相当于全球国内生产总值的 11%。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>脱离和工作压力的根本原因往往在于组织如何设计人们的工作。数十年的广泛研究一致认为，糟糕的工作设计与员工的负面结果有关，包括精神紧张、高流动率、工作不满、生产力下降和学习障碍。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>现在许多公司都在努力做得更好。</p><p></p><p>不幸的是，我们的研究表明，许多管理者缺乏设计高质量工作的必要理解。这就是 ChatGPT 等人工智能技术可以发挥关键作用的地方，它可以弥合管理者的知识差距并帮助设计对员工和组织都有利的高质量工作。然而，对于管理者来说，首先了解使用 ChatGPT 进行工作设计的利弊非常重要。让我们来探讨一下我们的研究为管理者带来的一些启示。</p><h3>管理挑战：平凡且没有成就感的工作</h3><p>哪些因素决定了一份工作是否高质量？ <a href="https://www.futureofworkinstitute.com.au/smart-workdesign">SMART 工作设计模型</a>是 Sharon K. Parker 创建的一个框架，它将高质量工作定义为具有<em>刺激性的</em>工作（具有任务多样性和发展新技能的机会的工作），并融合了<em>掌握</em>（例如角色清晰度和工作反馈） ，是<em>代理性的</em>（例如工作自主性和变革参与），是<em>关系性的</em>（可以获得社会支持和积极的团队合作），并且是<em>可容忍的</em>（具有可管理的工作时间和合理的时间压力水平）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>尽管设计良好的工作有很多好处，但设计​​不当的工作仍然普遍存在。根据盖洛普 2019 年优秀就业调查，只有 40% 的美国人从事具有 SMART 特征的工作。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>另一方面，16% 的人发现自己的工作缺乏基本的 SMART 特征，44% 的人的工作只具备一些令人满意的 SMART 特征。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>当今的管理者缺乏对工作设计的了解可能可以解释这一发现。我们最近进行的一项研究探讨了人们如何为他人设计工作。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>在线模拟（模拟 1）的参与者被要求设计一个行政工作角色。半职工作全部由四项复印和归档任务组成。参与者被要求从 11 项任务列表中选择 4 项额外任务来全职完成这项工作，其中包括 5 项重复性复印和归档任务以及 6 项更有意义和有趣的任务，例如问候访客或帮助同事安排会议。</p><p></p><p>参与者的评分范围为 0 到 4，分数越高表明创造了更具刺激性的工作设计。近一半（45%）的大学管理专业学生和从事公共服务行业的专业人士/经理倾向于从事重复性和单调的工作，这表明在高质量工作设计方面存在知识差距。</p><p>在第二次模拟（模拟 2）中，参与者被要求扮演经理的角色并解决四种场景中的劳动力问题。在每种情况下，工作角色设计显然都很糟糕。为了解决这些问题，参与者评估了他们采取策略的可能性，其中包括“修复工人”方法（将问题归咎于员工）和“修复糟糕的工作设计”方法（承认质量差）。工作设计。</p><p>例如，在一种情况下，一名仓库工作人员尽管经常跑去取货，但在收集产品并将其运送到调度方面始终未能满足 50% 的规定期限。虽然大多数参与者关注的是改进工作设计的选择（例如，“让员工及其同事参与审查，以确定可以更好地组织他们的工作的方式”或“重新组织工作，以便任务不需要”），令人惊讶的是，数量惊人的参与者（40％）仍然选择了旨在固定工人的策略（例如“谨慎观察该人的行为，看看他们移动的速度有多快”）。这些发现证实了我们的发现，即管理者和员工缺乏工作设计知识。</p><h3>生成式人工智能可以提出强有力的工作设计</h3><p>在研究的下一阶段，我们研究了 ChatGPT 等人工智能驱动的工具是否可以帮助管理者做得更好。简短的回答是：ChatGPT 有潜力增强工作设计中的决策。然而，对于管理者来说，了解 ChatGPT 能做什么、不能做什么很重要。</p><p>我们使用 ChatGPT 为行政工作设计模拟（模拟 1）做出假设的工作设计决策。我们运行模拟任务 20 次，每次都在 ChatGPT 中使用新的独立聊天会话并提供相同的提示。生成式人工智能模型始终从提供的列表中选择丰富任务，在创造有趣且有意义的工作方面优于学生和专业人士/经理。 ChatGPT 的表现与工作设计专家的表现相似。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>不同组的工作设计决策得分</h4><p class="caption">当模拟 1 的参与者被要求设计行政工作角色时，45% 的参与者大多选择为工人分配重复且单调的任务（评分从 0 到 4 表示参与者选择的丰富任务的数量）。当模拟 2 的参与者被要求解决四个设计不良的工作角色中的问题时，40% 的人选择了旨在修复工人而不是不良设计的策略（得分从 1 到 5 表示参与者将采用这些策略的程度，1=极不可能，5=极有可能）。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023_1005_Parker_Fig1-1.png" alt="不同组的工作设计决策得分"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>然后，我们要求 ChatGPT 处理模拟 2，解决四种管理人员场景（包括上面提到的理论仓库工人），从列表中选择策略。在每种情况下，ChatGPT 始终选择旨在修复工作设计的策略（有利于员工福祉、积极性和绩效的良好策略），而不是专注于修复员工的策略。与模拟 1 一样，ChatGPT 在专注于解决劳动力问题的工作设计方面优于学生、经理和专业人士。</p><p>然而，ChatGPT 在模拟 2 中的得分不如工作设计专家，这表明需要谨慎对待。例如，在一次针对错过最后期限的仓库工人的会议中，ChatGPT 总体得分为 4，但选择了“当员工和她的同事按时完成任务时，我会给他们奖金”的策略，这忽略了该角色的不合理时间分配。</p><p></p><h3>一大教训：具体提示是关键</h3><p>为了进一步评估 ChatGPT 独立生成建议的能力，我们运行了模拟 2 工作设计任务，但没有提供多项选择解决方案列表。我们在关闭聊天记录功能的新帐户和独立的新聊天中运行每个测试，以便 ChatGPT 的输出不会受到之前输入的影响。</p><p>首先，结果令人担忧。当我们简单地指示人工智能模型在错过最后期限的情况下“提供有效的策略来解决问题”时，ChatGPT 倾向于通过尝试修复工人并创建老式的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-progressive-roots-of-management-science/">泰勒主义工作系统方法来</a>解决问题，例如进行计时和运动研究。例如，ChatGPT 提出了时间管理技能和额外培训等解决方案，以帮助我们命名为 Karen 的仓库员工提高绩效（例如，“重点提高 Karen 在仓库中查找和收集物品的速度和准确性”） 。它还建议提供绩效反馈和激励措施，以激励凯伦更快地行动（例如，“通过将绩效与奖励联系起来，将鼓励凯伦专注于提高速度和效率”）。这些解决方案中的每一个都隐含地假设问题是工人的动机或能力而不是工作设计。</p><p>在得知这种开放式方法并非最佳选择后，我们接下来指示 ChatGPT 使用特定提示来解决相同的场景：“考虑为 Karen 设计一份高质量的工作”； “考虑凯伦的健康、幸福、动力、满意度和工作意义”；和“考虑凯伦的工作设计。”然后，AI 模型提供了与改进 Karen 的工作设计相关的解决方案，包括以下内容：</p><ul><li>审查时间分配和工作量以设定切合实际的时间目标。</li><li>让凯伦参与决策过程，并寻求她对改善工作的意见。</li><li>提供支持性反馈和认可，以提高员工满意度和积极性。</li><li>提供充足的培训和技能发展机会，以增强信心和参与度。</li></ul><p>这些策略将提升凯伦的 SMART 工作设计特征，提高需求的容忍度，增强能动性，提高掌握程度，并使工作更具刺激性。</p><p> ChatGPT 还提出了一些解决方案，例如营造支持性的工作环境、鼓励团队支持和协作、提供职业发展机会以及促进工作与生活的平衡。这些解决方案都与工作设计和幸福感的广泛研究相吻合，将使工作变得“更智能”，从而培养出更健康、更有生产力的员工。</p><p>我们从 ChatGPT 的这个特殊实验中了解到，生成式人工智能可以做出有价值的工作设计决策，但管理者需要提供明确的指示，优先考虑员工的结果。例如，要求ChatGPT“设计高质量的工作”而不是简单地要求“良好的工作设计”可以产生更相关和有效的策略。因此，为了提高ChatGPT生成的策略建议的质量，管理者需要在问题提示中提及具体的、理想的目标，例如高质量的工作；员工的健康、福祉和积极性；和工作的意义。</p><p></p><p>好消息是：不经常使用 ChatGPT 的经理可以学习如何通过 ChatGPT 工具本身编写有效的提示。例如，当被问及“如何制作结构良好且清晰的提示来有效应对工作设计挑战时？” ChatGPT 提供了有关如何编写有效提示的分步指南。 ChatGPT 建议我们确定核心问题并具体化——可以通过使用提示将建议应用于工作设计，例如“设计高质量的工作，增强销售团队的积极团队互动和协作”或“设计有意义的工作”促进员工接受工作中的技术变革。”</p><p>实验还表明，有效的提示需要进行审查和测试。难以编写有效的 ChatGPT 提示的经理可以通过使用诸如“以下提示旨在从工作设计专家的角度向 ChatGPT 寻求建议的提示”来提高自己的技能。请分析并提出改进建议，以便从 ChatGPT 获得可行且实用的建议。”在这种情况下，ChatGPT 将提供更具体的建议，以推动更高质量的输出。</p><h3>给管理者的五个教训</h3><p>为了解决工作角色设计不佳及其有害影响这一普遍问题，采用创新解决方案至关重要。根据我们的研究，ChatGPT 已成为一种很有前途的人工智能工具，可以帮助管理者设计更健康、更高效的工作。但它不是万能药，需要明智地使用。我们对管理者的建议：</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 无法替代培训。</strong>管理者需要<em>意识到</em>，糟糕的工作设计可能会产生员工问题，而工作设计反过来又会影响员工的福祉、积极性和工作意义。这意味着，在使用ChatGPT设计更好的工作之前，管理者仍然需要进行工作设计理念的基础培训。要开始了解此主题，请参阅相关文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-well-designed-work-makes-us-smarter/">精心设计的工作如何让我们变得更聪明</a>”和<a href="https://www.smartworkdesign.com.au/">SMART 工作设计网站</a>。</p><p><strong>管理者需要获得支持，以实现创建精心设计的工作的目标。</strong>管理者需要有<em>动力</em>为员工创造更好的就业机会。这意味着管理者本身需要将创建健康的员工工作角色视为合法且重要的责任，而不是只关注底线。例如，如果管理者纯粹根据生产力成就获得晋升，他们就没有太多动力为团队设计 SMART 工作。</p><p><strong>管理者本身也需要健康的工作。</strong>管理者需要足够的时间来关注员工的工作设计得如何。这意味着管理者自己的工作必须是<em>可以忍受的</em>，并且没有过多的时间压力。</p><p></p><p><strong>管理者需要学习ChatGPT提示技巧。</strong>应鼓励管理者使用生成式人工智能来帮助应对工作设计挑战，但他们需要关于如何有效使用它的清晰而全面的指导。例如，管理者在向 ChatGPT 寻求工作设计建议时需要具体并提及员工福祉和动机等目标。</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 将增强而不是取代人们设计更好的工作。</strong>与模拟不同，现实生活中的工作设计情况通常具有模糊性和复杂性，并且存在许多可能影响结果的变量。真实情况需要对背景、人类情感、社会动态以及政治和道德考虑因素有深入的了解，所有这些对于像 ChatGPT 这样的人工智能工具来说要完全掌握都是具有挑战性的。我们建议使用 ChatGPT 作为人类管理者的<em>补充</em>，而不是<em>替代</em>它们。</p><p>通过将 ChatGPT 的建议与人类专业知识相结合，组织可以提高员工敬业度、工作满意度和整体绩效。在管理者和人工智能之间实现这种协同作用可以为工作设计和员工体验的更美好未来铺平道路。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>