<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 20 日星期五 17:44:23 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>您的组织在负责任的人工智能方面投资足够吗？我们的数据表明“可能不会”</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Priorities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year’s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团连续第二年组建了一个国际人工智能专家小组，帮助我们了解全球组织如何实施负责任的人工智能 (RAI)。对于今年研究周期的最后一个问题，我们要求学术界和从业者小组成员对这一挑衅做出回应：<em>随着商业界越来越意识到人工智能的风险，企业正在对 RAI 进行足够的投资。</em></p><p>尽管他们的理由各不相同，但大多数小组成员都承认 RAI 投资未能满足需要：13 人中有 11 人不愿意同意组织对负责任的人工智能的投资是“足够的”。小组成员在很大程度上肯定了我们<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/building-robust-rai-programs-as-third-party-ai-tools-proliferate/">2023 年 RAI 全球调查</a>的结果，其中不到一半的受访者表示他们相信他们的公司准备对 RAI 进行足够的投资。对于优先考虑人工智能并必须管理人工智能相关风险的公司来说，这是一个紧迫的领导挑战。</p><p> H&amp;M 集团负责任的人工智能和数据主管 Linda Leopold 表示，扩大 RAI 投资的需要标志着一个重大转变，因为“人工智能相关的风险不容忽视”。虽然对 RAI 进行足够的投资曾经是一个重要但不是特别紧迫的问题，但 Leopold 表示，生成式人工智能的最新进展和第三方工具的激增已经表明此类投资的紧迫性。</p><p>由于衡量方面的挑战，对 RAI 进行充分投资变得复杂。没有提供指导的行业标准，因此您如何知道您的投资何时或是否足够？更重要的是，理性的高管对于什么是充分投资可能有不同的看法。显而易见的是，认知问题不应成为行动的障碍，尤其是当人工智能风险构成真正的业务威胁时。</p><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3>小组成员回应</p></h3><h2>目前尚不清楚组织是否对 RAI 进行了适当的投资。</p></h2><p>大多数小组成员不愿意同意组织正在对 RAI 进行“足够”的投资。</p><p><a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">跳转至下面小组成员的详细回复。</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-Chart.jpg" alt="图：0 强烈同意； 15% 同意，46% 既不同意也不不同意； 39% 不同意； 0% 强烈不同意"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source">资料来源：由 13 名人工智能战略专家组成的 Responsible AI 小组。 </p></p></div><p><path id="Path" d="M0,0,14.067,15.065,28.941,0" transform="translate(1.096 1.054)" fill="none" stroke="#fff" stroke-miterlimit="10" stroke-width="3" /> <a href="" class="callout-chart-add__button"><span class="callout-chart-add__button-text"><strong>显示</strong>全球调查结果</span></a></p><div class="callout-chart-add"><div class="callout-chart-add__container"><div class="callout-chart-add__info"><h4></h4><h3> 2023 年全球高管调查的回复<br /></h3><p>“您认为您的组织在多大程度上准备好投资（减少收入、增加成本）以遵守负责任的人工智能计划？” </p></p></div><div class="callout-chart-add__chart"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-survey.jpg" alt="条形图：中等或较大程度：48%；在某种程度上：29%；较小程度：8%；完全没有：3%；不知道：12%" class="mt0"></p><p class="callout-chart-add__source">资料来源：对代表年收入至少 1 亿美元的组织的 1,240 名受访者进行的调查数据。这些受访者代表了 87 个国家/地区 59 个行业的公司。在中国进行的调查是本地化的。</p></p></div></p></div></p></div></div><h3>公司正在投资 RAI，但还不够</h3><p>小组成员提出了公司没有对负责任的人工智能进行足够投资的几个原因。几位小组成员表示，利润动机是一个因素。联合国大学校长兼联合国副秘书长 Tshilidzi Marwala 认为，“只有 20% 意识到人工智能风险的公司正在投资 RAI 项目。其余的人更关心如何利用人工智能来实现利润最大化。”新加坡国立大学大卫·马歇尔教授兼副教务长西蒙·切斯特曼 (Simon Chesterman) 补充道：“围绕生成式人工智能的淘金热导致科技公司的安全团队规模缩小，新产品的上市路径也缩短了。 ......在许多组织中，即使不是全部，对错过的恐惧正在战胜风险管理。”</p><p>投资不足的另一个原因是，在整个企业中更多地使用人工智能会扩大 RAI 的范围并增加所需的投资。正如 Armilla AI 的人工智能政策主管 Philip Dawson 所观察到的那样，“对人工智能功能的投资继续大大超过对人工智能安全和实施人工智能风险管理的工具的投资。企业正在一场艰苦的战斗中追赶，而且只会变得更加艰难。”利奥波德补充说，生成式人工智能和越来越多的可能应用“显着增加了负责任的人工智能项目必须覆盖的受众规模”。</p><p></p><p>第三个原因是，对人工智能风险的认识不断增强并不总是转化为对这些风险的准确评估。非洲负责任人工智能观察站的政策专家 Oarabile Mudongo 表示，一些公司可能没有对其 RAI 项目进行足够的投资，因为它们“低估了人工智能风险的程度”。</p><h3>您如何知道自己的投资是否足够？</h3><p>其他小组成员指出，尽管对RAI进行足够的投资很重要，但很难衡量投资是否足够大或有效。企业应如何计算 RAI 投资回报？什么才算是“足够”的回报？什么才算投资？ Aboitiz Data Innovation 首席执行官兼菲律宾联合银行首席数据和人工智能官 David R. Hardoon 问道：“如果 (1) 所有公司都不受相同水平的标准，（2）我们尚未就什么是“足够”或“可接受”达成一致，或者（3）我们没有验证第三方的机制？”</p><p> Dataiku 的 AI 负责人 Triveni Gandhi 对此表示同意：“在那些花时间投资 RAI 项目的公司中，这些项目的实际设计和实施方式存在很大差异。对于如何实施或实施 RAI 价值观缺乏一致或明确的期望，使得组织很难开始有效的投资。”</p><p> Stemly 联合创始人、首席运营官兼首席科学家朱塞佩·马奈 (Giuseppe Manai) 表示：“很难确定公司在负责任的人工智能项目上进行了多大程度的投资，因为人们的认知度和相关性非常广泛。”华为技术（英国）研究总监艾莎·纳西尔（Aisha Naseer）补充道：“目前尚不清楚这些投资是否足够，因为这些投资的规模从微不足道到巨额资金都被分配用于控制人工智能和相关风险缓解。”</p><p></p><h3>建议</h3><p>对于寻求充分投资 RAI 的组织，我们建议如下：</p><p> <strong>1. 培养领导层对人工智能风险的认识。</strong>领导者需要意识到，使用人工智能是一把双刃剑，既会带来风险，也会带来好处。专注于增加人工智能收益的投资，而不相应地关注管理其风险，会从两个方面损害价值创造。一是，如果没有适当的护栏，人工智能的好处可能不会令人印象深刻：我们的研究发现，当 RAI 实践到位时，人工智能的创新就会增加。其次，人工智能带来的风险与其所嵌入的工具一样迅速扩散。对人工智能风险和收益的强烈认识支持领导层努力管理风险和发展公司。建立管理意识可以采取多种形式，包括高管教育、讨论论坛和 RAI 计划，这些计划拥有不同类型的人工智能风险暴露（和经验）的利益相关者。</p><p> <strong>2. 接受 RAI 投资将是一个持续的过程。</strong>随着人工智能开发和使用的增加（没有可预见的结束），RAI 实践和实施也需要适应。这需要持续的 RAI 投资来不断发展 RAI 计划。随着欧盟、美国和亚洲的监管格局即将发生变化，领导者将面临越来越大的压力，要求其发展以人工智能为中心的风险管理系统。等待在技术、文化和财务方面对这些系统进行投资（或停止投资）可能会损害业务增长。当新的法规和行业标准生效时，为满足合规性要求而快速调整流程可能会干扰人工智能相关的创新。最好将 RAI 程序与 AI 开发共同发展，这样它们就能相互补充，而不是造成这种不必要的干扰。随着公司扩大人工智能投资，他们的 RAI 投资也需要增长。但那些已经落后的公司需要迅速采取行动，积极投资 RAI，以避免始终落后。</p><p> <strong>3. 制定 RAI 投资指标。</strong>投资 RAI 很复杂——这种投资的回报是什么样的？就像网络安全投资一样，最好的 RAI 回报可能是在人工智能相关问题在品牌声誉受损、监管问题和成本增加之前被发现时保持沉默。也就是说，沉默不应被误认为是充分的投资。正如我们的调查结果所示，投资最少的公司可能不会仅仅因为不寻找问题而发现问题。领导者应就 RAI 投资的构成、评估这些投资的适当指标以及由谁来决定投资水平达成一致。随着时间的推移，衡量 RAI 计划成功与否的指标对于支持 RAI 计划是必要的，但它们可能是一个滞后指标。指标还应该评估前瞻性维度，例如领导承诺、计划采用、培训和劳动力需求以及文化变革。领导者还必须确定 RAI 资金与 AI 项目资金的关系。每个大型人工智能项目都应该为 RAI 留出预算吗？或者 RAI 资金是否应该独立于具体项目或基于项目（分散）和机构（集中）投资的某种组合？</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>推动护理危机的真正问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">杰克戴利</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论的自由文本。对于每条评论，我们分析了它是否提到了 200 个主题之一，并评估了护士对该主题的评价是积极还是消极。这些主题源自对员工体验的各个要素的研究，包括文化、薪酬和福利、工作时间表以及感知的组织支持。我们将相关主题聚集成两打更广泛的主题。</p><p>我们将这些主题用作 XGBoost 模型中的特征，该模型以 5 分制预测每位护士对其现任或前任雇主的总体评分。然后，我们计算 SHAP 值（为模型中的每个特征分配一个重要性值），以直接比较不同主题在预测工作满意度方面的相对重要性（通过每个护士给雇主的总体评分来衡量）。我们还使用文本分析来比较旅行护士与医疗保健系统工作人员的护士谈论话题的积极程度。</p><p>使用护士提到的主题以及他们对每个主题的情绪作为预测变量，我们的模型解释了护士之间 29% 到 39% 的评分差异——几乎比我们使用所有权、组织类型和位置所能解释的要高一个数量级作为预测因子。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></p></aside><p>医疗保健领导者面临着一系列艰巨的挑战——成本上升、向数字医疗的过渡以及支付模式的转变等等。但根据美国医疗保健高管学院最近的一项调查，医院首席执行官面临的第一大问题是员工短缺和倦怠。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> 90% 的受访首席执行官将护士短缺视为一个特别严重的痛点。</p><p> 2021年，在美国工作的注册护士总数出现40年来最大降幅，其中年轻护士的流失率最高。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>到 2025 年，美国医疗保健系统可能会短缺多达 45 万名护士，比患者护理所需的护理人员数量少 20%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p>高度的工作不满和倦怠正在驱使护士离开这个行业。 COVID-19大流行给所有医护人员带来了巨大压力，但自大流行结束以来，护士的不满和倦怠并没有改善。从某些角度来看，情况可能会变得更糟：2021年，近三分之二的注册护士会鼓励其他人成为一名护士，但只有一半的人表示他们会在两年后推荐护理作为职业。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>了解护士不满情绪的最丰富来源之一是他们在 Indeed 和 Glassdoor 等招聘网站上如何用自己的话描述自己的工作。这些信息数量庞大，但难以综合，因为其中大部分采用非结构化自由文本的形式。为了了解护士面临的挑战，我们分析了自疫情爆发以来，其中 15 万名护士在 Glassdoor 评论中如何描述其雇主。 （参见“研究”。）在本文中，我们分享了该分析的重要见解，并就如何解决护士最紧迫的问题向医疗保健领导者提供建议。</p><h3>医疗保健领导者脱节</h3><p>护士认为他们的经理与患者护理的日常现实脱节。我们将他们对管理者的评价分为近 50 种领导特质。第二个最常被提及的特征是，管理者没有意识到护士在工作场所面临的挑战。当护士们讨论管理者如何理解床边生活时，十分之九的评论都是负面的。</p><p></p><p>护士们尤其批评高级管理团队成员的脱节。高层团队因脱节而受到批评的可能性是一线主管和中层管理人员的 10 倍。我们的结果证实了另一项调查，其中近一半的医院护士表示，他们认为管理层没有倾听他们的担忧。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>为了解决不满和倦怠问题，医疗保健领导者必须首先了解床边发生的情况。这可能具有挑战性，特别是在拥有数千名护士跨多个地点和专业工作的大型医疗保健系统中。</p><p>从历史上看，领导者一直在努力系统地分析护士挫败感的金矿，这些见解可以从员工调查或外部审查中的评论中收集到。阅读、理解和分析大量非结构化文本数据根本不切实际。然而，人工智能的最新进展使得识别大量文本中的深层模式并大规模理解反馈成为可能。领导者现在可以挖掘自由文本，以深入了解导致护士不满和倦怠的问题，并利用这种洞察力改善护理人员的工作生活。 （请参阅“文本分析入门”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>文本分析入门</h4><p>我们的研究分析了来自数百个组织和数十万名护士的数据，但您也可以更深入地研究自己员工的反馈。无论您是在内部、通过劳动力分析功能还是与外部合作伙伴一起开发人工智能文本分析功能，您都应该牢记这些原则，以最大限度地提高文化衡量的有效性。</p><p><strong>精确度很重要，但记忆力也很重要。</strong>精确度（被正确分类为讨论某个主题的文本实例的百分比）是自由文本分析的关键要素。召回率也是如此——文本分析平台捕获的文本正文中主题提及总数的百分比。如果您仅通过精度来衡量成功，那么您最终会得到一个高度准确的分析平台，但会忽略员工实际所说的大部分内容。复杂的人工智能工具将识别俚语、习语、首字母缩略词、文化参考和组织特定的语言，以捕获很少提及但信息丰富的术语的长尾。</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p><strong>让主题专家了解情况。</strong>文本分析的核心是将自然语言分类为有意义的主题。理想情况下，衡量文化的人在开发分析主题时应聘请主题专家。主题专家可以确保所选择的文化和工作场所主题得到明确定义、与现有研究相关联并得到适当衡量。</p><p><strong>李克特问题有严重的缺点，但适度使用会非常有帮助。</strong>太多的李克特量表问题可能会导致调查者进入自动驾驶模式。但李克特的问题不应该被完全抛弃。有效的文化衡量将广泛主题（例如参与度、流失意图和其他重要衡量标准）的李克特规模结果与自由文本数据相结合，以确定在数百个自由文本主题中哪些对结果具有最强大的影响。</p><p><strong>透明度很重要，而且未来可能会更加重要。</strong>虽然人工智能将如何受到监管还有待观察，但立法者或法院可能不会善待黑盒模型做出的重要决策，而不解释这些模型如何得出结论。领导者经常依靠文化衡量来做出重要决策，例如薪酬政策、人事变动以及如何优先考虑资源。他们应该警惕完全依赖做出人类无法理解的决策的模型。</p><p><strong>员工们讨厌你监视他们——而且你不会学到太多关于文化的知识。</strong>领导者应该抵制诱惑，将文本分析工作扩展到电子邮件、Slack 渠道、电话消息和其他并非旨在提供员工反馈的沟通形式的内容。许多员工认为监听他们的工作谈话是窃听或更糟的行为。此外，工作电子邮件和 Slack 消息所包含的文化信息往往比明确邀请员工讨论组织中有效和无效的问题提示少得多。让员工倾听双方同意的意见，并让老大哥远离工作场所。</p></div></article></aside></div><h3>通过基准测试确定相对优势和机会</h3><p>不同雇主的护理满意度差异很大。我们确定了美国 200 家最大的医疗保健雇主，包括医院和医疗保健系统、家庭医疗保健提供者、老年生活设施运营商以及人才中介机构。对于每位雇主，我们计算了从 COVID-19 大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月，护士在 Glassdoor 上对组织和高级领导层的评价<a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">。6</a></p><p>在大型雇主中，护士的 Glassdoor 评分范围从很差（2.6）到近乎完美（4.9）（满分 5 分）。护士对大流行期间和之后高级领导表现的评估更加多样化，在相同的 5 分制中，从 2.1 到 4.9 不等。 Glassdoor 评级的巨大差异与另一项调查一致，该调查显示美国 60 家医院中护士不满意的比例从 2% 到 48% 不等。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工可以使用我们的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">交互式工具</a>来查看他们的组织相对于其他组织的排名。该指数根据护士的总体评分、对最高领导层的评估以及护士满意度的四个最有力的预测因素进行排序：薪酬、工作量、组织支持和有毒文化。 </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4>护士如何评价他们的雇主？</h4><p class="caption">使用护理满意度指数来比较护士如何评估 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工体验。</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p>平均而言，在人事代理机构工作的护士（有时被称为旅行护士）比其他护士更满意。我们样本中排名最高的五家雇主（前十名中的六家）是人才中介机构。</p><p>当然，较高的薪酬是造成这种差异的部分原因，但不是全部。我们比较了在人才中介机构工作的护士与医院和医疗保健系统雇用的护士谈论 200 个话题的积极程度。 （参见“人事机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高”。）虽然机构护士对薪酬的看法更有利，但围绕解决护士问题和开放、诚实的沟通问题，两组之间的情绪差距更大。通过将护士视为客户，人才中介机构擅长提高满意度，而不仅仅是支付更高的工资。其他医疗保健领导者可以从他们的例子中学习，我们将在下面提出一些具体建议。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高</h4><p class="caption">我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月期间美国 Glassdoor 护士评论的自由文本，以了解他们对各种话题的积极评价。然后，我们将在人才中介机构工作的护士的积极情绪与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士的积极情绪进行了比较。虽然人事代理机构在许多关键主题上的评分较高，包括诚实沟通、有效解决问题和建立信任，但医院和医疗保健系统在学习和发展、福利、同事和晋升机会方面表现更强。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3>优先考虑工作满意度的驱动因素</h3><p>为了了解护士工作满意度的驱动因素，我们分析了样本中护士自 COVID-19 大流行开始以来撰写的所有评论的自由文本，并将文本分为近 200 个主题。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>然后，我们将主题分为两打更广泛的主题，并使用这些主题来预测护士对其雇主的总体评分。然后我们比较了每个主题在预测收视率方面的相对重要性。 （参见“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素。”）</p><p></p><p>薪酬是护士对当前雇主满意度的首要预测因素，这并不奇怪，因为在我们分析的期间，通货膨胀侵蚀了实得工资的购买力。工作量的重要性是第二重要的驱动因素，这与另一项大规模调查的结果相吻合，该调查发现人员配备不足是护士工作不满、倦怠和辞职意愿的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p>工作量和薪酬是护理危机必须解决的根本原因，但它们并不是影响护士工作满意度的唯一因素。我们的分析揭示了工作环境的其他方面，包括有毒文化、组织支持、工作时间表、沟通、学习和发展机会，领导者可以关注这些方面来改善护士的工作生活。</p><p>该分析还强调了不太可能改善护士工作场所体验的领域。福利固然不错，但无法弥补繁重的工作量或跟不上通货膨胀的工资。强调促进患者健康的企业使命也无济于事。护士们已经知道他们的工作有更高的目标；这就是为什么他们中的大多数人首先成为护士。</p><h3>挖掘自由文本以获得可行的见解</h3><p>许多医疗保健组织依赖年度员工调查，其中有数十个项目按 5 分制评分，并事后添加了一些开放式问题。面对一长串的多项选择题，员工很容易转向自动驾驶仪，并为非常不同的项目分配相似的分数。问题的选择限制了员工可以讨论的内容，而且很少有空间来扩展他们为什么选择特定的数字答案。</p><p>开放式的自由文本反馈提供了丰富的细致入微且可操作的见解来源。当护士可以决定要写哪些主题时，他们会利用自己的自由来讨论对他们来说最重要的事情。开放式问题为护士提供了用自己的语言阐述他们的担忧、提供关键背景并针对他们面临的问题提出具体和可行的解决方案的空间。个人自由文本回复可以汇总为更广泛的主题，以确定领导者可以集中注意力和有限资源的优先顺序，以最大程度地提高护士满意度。</p><p>虽然组织平均值很有用，但重要的是要记住，不同的亚文化可以在同一组织内共存。对于通过并购发展起来的大型医疗保健系统来说尤其如此。例如，一家全国性连锁医院在近 50 个地点的评级范围为 1.9 到 3.9。医疗保健领导者不能仅仅依赖组织平均水平，而必须衡量和分析地点、部门、职能、团队和个人领导者之间的差异。</p><p>女性、代表性不足的少数族裔和年长员工也会体验到与其他员工截然不同的组织文化。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>了解不同员工群体工作满意度和倦怠的驱动因素至关重要。</p><p></p><p>领导者可以挖掘免费文本，详细了解特定群体最关键的痛点，并相应地调整干预措施。例如，日程安排对护士的工作满意度有重大影响，但日程安排的哪些方面最重要将取决于具体职位。轮班安排的灵活性和不间断工作休息的能力对于医院和初级保健机构的护士来说非常重要，而家庭保健护士则非常看重可预测的时间表。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p>护士的意见为改善工作场所和患者护理提供了宝贵的实用建议。例如，我们研究的 Glassdoor 评论包括数十条关于雇主如何改进日程安排的可行建议。有些是易于实施的行动，例如使用应用程序更容易接班或调换班次，或者向最后一刻接班的护士支付 20 至 50 美元的奖金。其他则是更为系统性的改变，比如让护士加入一个制定时间表的委员会，或者确保接受学费援助的员工能够安排他们的课程的工作。</p><h3>倾听离开您组织的护士的心声</h3><p>大多数组织将调查范围限制在现任员工。离职面谈如果有的话，也是随意进行的，而前员工的反馈往往被视为不满者的咆哮。但忽视前员工的反馈是一个很大的错误。 </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p>对前员工进行访谈或调查可以揭示他们离职的原因，并找出留住人才的最有效行动。由于没有报复的威胁，即将离开（或已经离开）组织的护士更有可能提供坦诚的反馈，甚至是当前员工不愿讨论的禁忌问题。通过收集离职者的反馈，组织可以发现潜在的盲点。</p><p>在我们的样本中，超过三分之一的 Glassdoor 评论是由前员工撰写的，这些评论提供了对用脚投票的护士最重要的见解。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a>图左侧的条形图“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素”对预测离职护士如何评价其前雇主的因素进行了排名，它揭示了护士可能离职的一个关键原因。</p><p>在 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">之前的一篇文章</a>中，我们认为五种行为属性——不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待——将组织文化标记为有毒。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>在辞职的护士中，有毒文化对他们总体满意度的预测作用是薪酬或工作量的两倍多。有毒工作场所对辞职护士的重要性与早期的研究一致，该研究发现毒性是大辞职的前六个月内行业调整后人员流失的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p>在大流行后时代，有毒文化对于护士来说变得更加重要。当我们比较哪些因素最能预测护士在大流行前后对雇主的评价时，发现在 COVID-19 之后，有毒文化的相对重要性获得了最大的提升（其次是工作量、幸福感和薪酬）。如果您的组织遭受文化毒性，我们的另一篇文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">如何修复有毒文化</a>”提出了几种基于证据的干预措施，医疗保健领导者可以用来为自己的组织排毒。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素</h4><p class="caption">我们将超过 150,000 条护士的 Glassdoor 评论文本分为两打影响员工体验的主题，然后分析哪些主题最能预测护士如何评价其雇主。该图表通过显示每个主题对整体预测的贡献程度，对每个主题在预测这些评级中的重要性进行排名。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3>学习人才中介机构的做法</h3><p>正如“人事机构在许多关键因素上评分较高”这一数字所示，护士对人事机构为快速有效地解决问题而制定的流程非常积极。在提及人事代理机构流程效率的护士中，75% 的护士持积极态度，而只有 23% 的护士对医疗保健系统表示积极看法。对于旅行护士来说，常见的流程问题包括入职、获得所需的证书和执照、合同谈判和报销。最好的人才中介机构会听取反馈，深入了解旅行护士面临的典型问题，并优化工作流程来解决这些问题。</p><p>专职护士遇到的许多痛点与机构护士所遇到的痛点有所不同。然而，医疗保健系统、家庭保健机构和长期护理提供者可以采用类似的方法来捕获和分析护士的反馈，优先考虑他们面临的最常见和令人沮丧的挑战，并与工作人员合作解决这些问题。</p><p>持续倾听反馈并采取行动也可以与护理人员建立信任。与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士相比，人事机构的护士更积极地认为拥有心理安全感，可以说出困难的问题并让别人听到。</p><p>然而，如果管理层对护士提出的问题反应缓慢，心理安全的好处就会减弱。护士们高度评价人才中介机构对她们的问题和疑虑的快速反应。相比之下，护士经常抱怨其他类型的雇主即使得到回复，也对提出问题的电子邮件回复缓慢。护士还非常重视与主管的多种沟通渠道，包括短信、电子邮件、Facebook、Jabber 和 24/7 热线。</p><p>我们研究的另一个见解是护士重视诚实和透明度。他们和任何人一样了解医疗保健面临的挑战，并且希望就组织中正在发生的事情、它如何影响他们以及做出决定的原因进行诚实的沟通。 Triage 是一家人才中介机构，也是我们研究的第四大评价最高的大型雇主，它将诚实的沟通置于其价值主张的核心：“我们按事实说话，这样你就不会对其进展感到惊讶。” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p>医疗保健系统可以向人才中介机构学习，但也可以利用自己的独特优势来吸引和留住护士。全职护士在组织生活的三个重要方面对医院和医疗保健系统的评价高于人才中介机构：学习和发展（包括晋升机会和培训报销）、福利和同事。这三个因素是护士评价雇主的十大预测因素之一。医疗保健系统应投资于其比较优势，并在向潜在和现有员工传达其价值主张时强调这些优势。</p><p></p><h3>将反馈转化为行动以建立信任</h3><p>收集员工反馈是一回事，但持续根据这些见解采取行动则是另一回事。如果员工认为管理者不会采取行动，他们就不太可能提出问题或提出潜在的解决方案。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>更糟糕的是，如果员工认为管理层缺乏权力、资源或兴趣根据他们的建议进行变革，他们更有可能辞职。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a>近一半的护士认为管理层不会解决临床工作人员提请他们注意的问题。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p>组织需要建立适当的结构，以一致地根据员工的反馈采取行动。一个著名的例子是 Kaiser Permanente 的单位团队 (UBT)，该团队由经常在特定单位或部门一起工作的临床工作人员和管理人员组成。 <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a>这些团队每月至少召开一次会议，对其部门的绩效负责，并由一名经理、一名劳工代表以及通常还有一名临床工作人员共同领导。</p><p> UBT 确定了四个方面的改进机会：质量（包括患者治疗结果）、患者服务、负担能力和员工体验。团队利用员工反馈来识别改进机会并确定其优先顺序。接下来，团队使用最佳实践和基于证据的方法开发和测试解决方案。一旦解决方案被认为有效，就会在整个单位、部门，或者在某些情况下整个组织中实施。然后，UBT 监控这些变化对患者治疗结果、员工满意度和成本降低的影响。</p><p></p><p>自 COVID-19 爆发以来，我们对美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论进行了研究，结果显示，护士对雇主的整体评价存在很大差异，特别是在薪酬、工作量、有毒文化和组织支持方面——这四个因素对雇主的影响最大。塑造护士的工作满意度。我们认为，这种变化传递了希望的信息。尽管所有医疗保健组织都面临结构性挑战，但<em>仍有</em>可能提供一个让护士每天都期待上班的环境。</p><p>许多组织，包括一些最大的护士雇主，都有很大的改进空间。这些排名的目的不是为了“点名羞辱”，而是为了让医疗保健领导者意识到他们的组织绩效与为护士提供健康工作场所的可能性之间的差距有多大。我们还希望有关医疗保健组织如何在对护士最重要的因素上排名的客观数据可以为其领导者提供改进的动力，并提供证据来说服所有利益相关者迫切需要进行变革。</p><p></p><p>领导者不应该做的是要求护士更加努力地工作，承受更多的挫折和压力，却不能理解和解决使许多人的生活变得悲惨的组织因素。当工作人员辞职、工人成立工会以及州和联邦立法者制定保护护士利益的法规时，继续照常营业的领导者不应感到惊讶。</p><p>为了改善护士乃至所有卫生保健工作者的工作生活，领导者必须收集他们的反馈并根据他们的反馈采取行动，认识到组织的不同部门和不同人群将面临独特的挑战和问题。倾听护士的心声表明，医疗保健领导者可以采取一些有意义的措施来解决护理危机。最重要的一步是首先倾听他们的意见。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>探索护士如何评价他们的雇主</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>为了了解护士面临的工作挑战，医疗保健领导者需要倾听护士自己关于职业倦怠的说法。我们分析了自 COVID-19 大流行开始以来美国护士撰写的 150,000 条 Glassdoor 评论的自由文本，并将这些文本分为两打主题，我们用这些主题来预测护士对其雇主的总体评分。</p><p>我们计算了每个主题在预测护士总体满意度方面的相对重要性。有毒文化、组织支持、薪酬和工作量这四个因素成为护士对其雇主满意度的最强预测因素。</p><p></p><p>对于医疗保健领导者来说，一项重要发现是：在辞职的护士中，与薪酬或工作量相比，有毒文化对他们总体满意度的预测能力是其两倍多。</p><p>雇主之间护士的工作满意度差异很大。我们的交互式护理满意度指数显示了护士如何评估美国 200 家最大的医疗保健雇主的员工体验，其中包括医院和医疗保健系统、家庭医疗保健提供者、老年生活设施运营商和人才中介机构。</p><p>对于每位雇主，我们计算了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月，护士在 Glassdoor 上对组织和高级领导层的评价。我们还报告了护士对薪酬、工作量、有毒文化和组织支持的评价如何。每个雇主在所有维度上的得分均以高于/（低于）所有 200 名雇主的平均值的标准差表示。</p><p><a href="#interactive-launcher">探索上面的索引</a>。</p><p class="attribution">图片来源：杰克·戴利</p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>医疗保健领导者需要了解哪些内容来应对护理短缺：护士的发言</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的多媒体编辑。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>护士们精疲力尽并离开这个行业，人们担心迫在眉睫的护理短缺将影响患者护理的许多方面。是什么导致了这种倦怠？对于护士的工作满意度来说，最重要的是什么？医疗机构中有毒培养物有多常见？医疗保健领导者可以采取哪些措施来改善这些问题？在这段视频中，我们与五位现任和前任护士交谈，了解医疗保健工作的现实，包括他们经历过的有毒文化和压力源，并从他们和医疗保健专家那里获得有关需要改变的建议。</p><p>文章作者兼研究员 Donald Sull 还讨论了护士在工作网站 Glassdoor 上对 150,000 条雇主评论的分析所揭示的工作满意度真相，以及医疗保健领导者可以从中学到什么。</p><p></p><p> “我们的研究中关键的、可操作的发现是，护士通常会非常详细地告诉你什么对他们不起作用，并且他们会提供具体的建议来解决这些问题。他们想提供帮助。他们希望自己的声音被听到，并且希望产生积极的影响，”萨尔说。</p><p> “作为一名护士，最困难或最令人沮丧的事情之一就是没有足够的时间陪伴病人，”曾担任儿科肿瘤科和 ICU 注册护士 18 年的 Jennie Evans 说。 “在那些时刻，你可以坐下来，与患者交谈，握住他们的手，与家人交谈，真正了解他们，不仅了解疾病，还了解患者可能存在的其他潜在焦虑或恐惧。”</p><p>观看视频，更多地了解护士们希望医疗保健领导者了解有毒文化、心理健康、成长机会以及对护理人员至关重要的其他问题。</p><p class="attribution">图片来源：杰克·戴利</p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>升级文化以促进增长和转型</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander 是霍特国际商学院的战略顾问和实践教授。他在决策、解决问题和文化方面的研究成果发表在<em>《哈佛商业评论</em>》、 <em>《麻省理工斯隆管理评论</em>》和<em>《沃顿知识》上</em>。 Per 在他的博客<a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">Leadershipbackbone.com</a>上分享了他的想法和想法。 Laurianne McLaughlin 是<cite>《麻省理工斯隆管理评论》</cite>的数字高级编辑。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>P. Hugander，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">采取基于技能的方法进行文化变革”</a> ，《<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite> ，2023 年 5 月 22 日。</p></aside><p>许多领导者知道他们组织的文化正在阻碍颠覆性技术带来的机会，但他们不知道该怎么办。软技能和心理安全可以实现推动转型和成长所需的协作。但是，尽管许多组织雄心勃勃地努力将这些技能融入到他们的文化中，但还是失败了。成功的秘诀：当人们体验帮助团队克服长期挑战的新技能时，缩短获得奖励的时间。</p><p> Per Hugander 帮助瑞典金融服务集团 SEB 等组织的领导者在应对复杂的战略挑战方面取得了进展。他的实用方法帮助人们将心理安全与有形的业务成果联系起来。</p><p>在本次网络研讨会中，您将了解到：</p><ul><li>为什么许多组织在文化变革上失败：仅仅试水可能是危险的。</li><li>如何深入而不是广泛地进行文化变革并赢得怀疑论者的支持。</li><li>如何快速运用新技能解决组织最棘手的问题并创造持久的文化效益。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>在组织中建立和维持多样性的五个步骤</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> ，教育学博士，是全球猎头公司 Boyden 的执行合伙人兼首席执行官和董事会服务美国业务负责人。他的职业生涯是作为美国企业界的扭亏为盈（玻璃悬崖）专家，并撰写有关私营和上市公司和董事会的多样性、治理和战略增长问题的文章。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>无论求职者的渠道有多么多样化，如果我们没有适当地准备我们的组织环境，那么我们努力寻找、招募和欢迎有才华的专业人士的可能性就会很大。许多组织已制定措施来监控和增加其多元化招聘；然而，很少有人关注雇佣后发生的事情。只有当我们有效地创造一个更加公平的环境并支持女性和有色人种驾驭它时，我们才能从全体员工的充分参与和贡献中受益，并避免他们因人员流动或脱离而流失。</p><p>职业少数群体——那些因性别或性身份、种族、年龄或其他因素而在其职业中<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">相对稀有的</a>人——已经实现了无数人梦寐以求的事情：他们突破了玻璃天花板，驾驭了通常不友善的环境 <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">企业丛林里</a>，往往能成功渡过<a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">玻璃悬崖</a>。尽管代表组织中不同群体的高管已经成功克服了这些挑战，但仍然有一项重要任务：为其他人开辟一条可以遵循的道路。这是一项艰巨、艰苦的工作，需要许多不同的工具和能力，但如果其他人想要安全地航行，这是必要的。</p><p></p><h3>维持多样性的步骤</h3><p>尽管各种资源为来自代表性不足人群的专业人士如何驾驭和克服组织挑战提供了建议，但组织识别<a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">持续存在的系统性偏见和种族主义的</a>根源并采取具体行动解决这些问题同样重要。组织可以采取以下五个步骤来开始创建更具包容性的环境，让所有员工都有平等的机会在职业生涯中茁壮成长和进步。</p><h4>步骤 1：通过赞助建立领导层对多元化的承诺。</h4><p>整个组织的领导层必须表现出对多样性和包容性的坚定承诺。当领导者树立这些行为榜样时，整个组织的员工自然会效仿他们的榜样。然而，这一承诺不能仅限于一次性的努力或企业价值观的声明。</p><p>领导者必须通过帮助培养和装备这些候选人以获得晋升，有意识地表现出他们对聘用代表性不足的人群的承诺。具体来说，每位领导者，无论组织级别如何，都应该至少确定一名这样的候选人来有意赞助。在了解候选人的背景、职业目标和支持需求后，领导者应该 (1) 在组织中为他们提供咨询，(2) 支持他们发展职业发展所需的能力，并且最重要的是，(3 ）帮助他们获得进步的领导地位。</p><p></p><p>尽管正式的指导、赞助和伙伴计划可能对这一努力有所帮助，但非正式发展的关系往往同样（如果不是更多的话）有回报和有益，并且在一个人或两个人晋升或离开组织后往往会持续很长时间。</p><h4>第二步：通过解决系统性因素来消除玻璃天花板。</h4><p>玻璃天花板的比喻描述了阻碍某些群体（通常是女性和有色人种）获得职业发展和晋升的高水平机会的歧视制度。表明您的组织内存在玻璃天花板的线索包括，与整体员工队伍相比，高层管理人员和高管人员缺乏多样性；具有相似角色和资格的个人之间的薪酬差异；对某些人群的指导、赞助、发展或晋升有限；对于哪些群体比其他群体更适合领导角色存在明显或隐含的偏见；代表性不足的群体中的人员流失率超过了其他群体。</p><p>要识别并消除组织中的玻璃天花板，请仔细审查员工体验的各个方面。例如，使用盲目招聘技术解决有偏见的招聘和晋升做法；审查薪资范围和晋升标准，确保同工同酬；为所有员工提供清晰的职业道路和发展机会。多元化目标、包容性举措以及关于识别和避免无意识偏见的员工教育也可以支持有利于多元化的氛围。支持灵活的工作安排和工作与生活的平衡可以鼓励员工的充分参与，否则他们可能会因为平衡个人和职业责任的需要而被忽视。</p><p></p><h4>第三步：通过尽职调查减少玻璃悬崖。</h4><p> <em>“玻璃悬崖”</em>一词描述了一种现象，即在危机时期优先选择女性和其他少数群体担任领导职务，从而使她们面临更大的失败风险。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这种现象跨行业、跨地区、女性和少数民族都有发生。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>仅在危机时期为代表性不足的人群提供领导机会的问题在于，那些在动荡时期担任领导的人往往被视为问题的一部分，这使陈规定型观念长期存在，并减少了此类候选人未来的机会。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>为了避免这种结果，在指派领导者解决问题之前，必须注意认识并充分检查情况。虽然一头扎进去并采取措施“止血”的诱惑是巨大的，但花适当的时间首先充分理解问题只是为了大大提高成功机会而付出的很小的代价。诊断过程应包括从所有利益相关者的角度确定项目参数（例如绩效目标、截止日期和预算）、项目利益相关者、过去采取的行动、当前情况和期望的结果。我关于<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">玻璃悬崖现象的</a>文章提供了有关尽职调查过程以及可用于诊断这些情况的问题的更多详细信息。只有诊断出问题后，才有可能选择最合适的候选人来领导这项工作。</p><h4>第四步：通过改变对话来拓宽途径。</h4><p>对于女性和有色人种来说，企业环境可能充满挑战。许多挑战都是系统性的，例如<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">使某些群体相对于其他群体处于不利地位的</a>组织文化，或者需要长时间在办公室工作和全天候响应的工作量和行为期望。这些系统性挑战可能会使企业环境显得陌生和敌对。反过来，职业少数群体可能会通过护理认知偏差来弥补，这些偏差会导致信心过高或过低。将他们的社交网络限制在类似的同伴身上，而不是培养与赞助商、导师和职业指南的<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">重要联系</a>；未能实现适当的工作与生活平衡。</p><p>尽管领导者必须刻意支持职业少数群体（步骤 1），但整个组织中的导师、支持者和盟友在引导候选人走向成功方面也发挥着重要作用，因为他们也已经成功地领导了组织。支持新兴领导者意味着改变典型的指导对话。典型的对话包括确定受训者的短期和长期目标，并寻求导师的情境建议、技能发展指导和绩效反馈。支持多样性、公平性、包容性和归属感的指导应包括一个清晰的职业发展框架、对各种机会和职位如何有助于候选人职业目标的解释，以及如何驾驭组织文化的讨论——所有这些鉴于他们作为职业少数群体所面临的玻璃天花板、玻璃悬崖和系统性挑战。</p><p>认知偏见也应该成为谈话的一部分，这样候选人就可以避免陷入过度自信和过度补偿所察觉到的缺点的陷阱。认知偏差的评估和调整最好通过收集有关受训者在关键任务上的表现的 360 度反馈并让受训者描述他们与执行这些任务相关的感受、想法和一般经验来完成。当受训者的任务绩效处于或低于平均水平，而他们自己对该任务的体验反映了强烈的热情、满足感和成就感时，可能会出现过度自信。相反，当受训者的任务绩效评估为或高于平均水平时，可能会发生过度补偿，但他们所描述的经历表明他们在任务上花费了太多时间，或者他们对自己的绩效心怀担忧。</p><h4>第 5 步：衡量并跟踪进度。</h4><p>流行的商业格言是，我们必须检查我们的期望。这一不言而喻的道理同样适用于任何多元化努力。该过程首先根据关键的多样性指标（例如不同员工群体的招聘、保留和晋升）来定义成功是什么样子。也许你会忍不住想就此打住。然而，确定目标仅仅是开始。此外，有必要衡量组织当前在这些 KPI 上的绩效，然后检查为什么会出现这种当前状态。了解组织当前的绩效需要进行以下评估：</p><p> <strong>1. 衡量买入。</strong>组织领导者和成员在多大程度上理解并同意定义的 KPI 是正确的指标和绩效目标？</p><p> <strong>2. 衡量可行性。</strong>哪些组织结构、流程和其他功能有助于实现 KPI？哪些特征威胁或阻碍成就？</p><p> <strong>3. 衡量支持需求。</strong>领导者被教导要根据每个下属的技能水平来适应每个下属的需求。同样，整个组织的领导者需要调整他们提供的监督、鼓励和指导的程度，因为不同技能水平的部门和员工都致力于实现多元化目标。例如，招聘部门在从代表性不足的群体中招聘专业人员方面相对缺乏经验，需要强有力的、循序渐进的指导和频繁的反馈，直到他们的能力得到提高，而在培养和吸纳此类专业人员方面技能娴熟的经理通常应该允许他们自主地充分发挥自己的才能。</p><p></p><p>随着计划的实施，继续定期评估这些指标，以衡量您的进展并调整您的努力。俗话说：“凡事经过衡量，才能完成”。只有经过精心定义并定期评估，您的多元化目标才会实现。</p><p></p><p></p><p>我经常是我工作过的组织中为数不多的黑人领导人之一。在我职业生涯的某个时刻，我曾在两次按级别分开的会议上担任市政厅发言人——一次由普通员工参加，另一次由管理层参加。尽管黑人客户服务代表很惊喜地看到一个看起来像他们的人担任行政职务，但我感到震惊和沮丧地意识到我们几乎整个客户服务代表队伍都是黑人，而我们所有的主管和经理都是白人。这令人费解，因为从招聘的角度来看，领导团队似乎很关心多样性，但显而易见的是，系统性障碍正在阻碍来自代表性不足群体的专业人士的保留和晋升。</p><p>通常，只有当高管、董事会成员或人力资源团队注意到组织高层缺乏多样性时，人才管理系统中的问题才会被注意到——但通常人们对此知之甚少，也很少得到解决。这种晋升上的差异至少可以部分解释为不友善的组织环境以及需要拓宽这些专业人员从代表性不足的群体中获得成功的途径。</p><p>组织领导者、教练、导师、赞助商和其他潜在的职业推动者都可以在消除不平等根源和帮助职业少数群体在企业环境中生存和发展方面发挥作用。随着越来越多的多元化专业人士群体走上职业成功之路，这条道路将变得更加顺畅和广泛，从而导致持续和累积的组织转型。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为什么薪酬透明度法规是一个战略管理机会</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>塔玛拉·蒙塔格-斯密特 (Tamara Montag-Smit) 是马萨诸塞大学 (UMass) 洛厄尔分校管理学助理教授。卡罗琳·埃文斯 (Karoline Evans) 是麻省大学洛厄尔分校管理学副教授。布兰登·斯密特是本特利大学管理学助理教授。卡森德拉·巴茨-巴巴里奇 (Cassondra Batz-Barbarich) 是森林湖学院 (Lake Forest College) 的商学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">安娜丽莎·格拉萨诺</p></figcaption></figure><p>薪酬透明度法被誉为解决性别工资差距的一种补救措施，美国各地州和地方各级越来越多地推出<a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">薪酬透明度法</a>。截至 9 月份，包括纽约在内的九个州目前正在规范薪酬披露的某些方面。国家妇女法律中心报告称，总共有超过四分之一的美国雇员居住在<a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">薪酬信息受到监管的</a>地区。</p><p>总的来说，薪酬透明度法规强调披露广告职位的薪酬范围和内部晋升机会。这些法律旨在确保同工同酬，有效缩小性别工资差距。逻辑很简单：如果工资过低的员工，包括女性和少数族裔，不知道他们的同事的工资是多少，那么他们在通过诉讼和谈判创造公平竞争环境时就会处于明显的劣势。当不平等现象仍然蒙在鼓里时，如何解决不平等问题呢？如果没有薪酬透明度，现有法律（例如<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">1963 年《同工同酬法案》）</a>的执行就会变得困难。根据<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">最近的案例</a>和已暴露的显着差异（有些跨越多年的少付），更大的透明度似乎可以发挥重要作用。</p><p></p><h3>对不断变化的监管环境的组织反应</h3><p>尽管薪酬透明度法规得到越来越广泛的采用，但许多组织的反应却是抵制、抵制和最低限度的合规性。科罗拉多州于 2021 年成为第一个要求组织披露广告职位薪资范围的州后，在全国范围内招募求职者的组织开始<a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">明确将科罗拉多州居民排除</a>在考虑范围之外，以规避新法律，促使该州劳工部发出 <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">警告和罚款</a>。另一种组织策略是遵守薪资信息要求，薪资范围过大，以至于申请人无法有意义地预测他们可能会得到的薪资。在一个著名的例子中，Netflix 发布了一份薪资范围<a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">为 90,000 美元到 900,000 美元的</a>职位。</p><p>虽然组织层面遵守透明度法律的方法有多种形式，但领导者对薪酬透明度对其业务运营和文化的潜在负面影响表达了一些共同的担忧：</p><ul><li><strong>每个人都会要求更多的钱吗？</strong>更多的薪酬信息可能会引发更多关于薪酬的讨论（以及为什么有人会得到他们的工资）。经理们担心，他们会陷入困境，试图兼顾预算和员工满意度方面的相互竞争的目标。</li><li><strong>如果一些员工发现他们的工资低于其他人，会发生什么？</strong>向老员工解释为什么他们的薪酬与新员工相同可能会让人感到不舒服，并会引发对雇主的严厉批评。</li><li><strong>薪酬透明度会影响我们的合作能力吗？</strong>当个人认为自己得到不公平的回报时，薪酬透明度可能会引起嫉妒和适得其反的竞争。经理们担心，当差异暴露出来时，员工可能会互相争斗并破坏彼此的利益。</li></ul><p></p><h3>管理薪酬透明度的新见解</h3><p>我们的工作为解决组织在透明度方面的一些主要问题提供了新的见解。大多数新法律只专注于通过要求组织披露空缺职位的薪酬范围来创造薪酬透明度。在学术研究中，这种形式的透明度被称为<em>分配透明度</em>，因为它仅披露有关员工工资<em>金额</em>的信息。</p><p>然而，在我们的研究中，我们描述了几种使薪酬信息透明的方法。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a><em>程序透明</em>，重点是共享有关如何制定薪酬<em>决策的</em>信息；在最透明的层面上，这将包括计算薪酬的公式（例如基本工资或基于绩效的加薪）。</p><p>区分分配透明度和程序透明度至关重要，因为正如我们的研究表明，程序透明度可以减轻与分配透明度相关的许多风险和缺点。</p><p>薪酬透明度法规隐含的理念是，工资过低的员工将自行协商<a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">争取更公平的工资</a>。事实上，过去二十年对超过 100,000 名学者进行的一项大规模研究发现，薪酬透明度的变化与男女之间的工资平等程度显着提高有关。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>然而，研究还表明，透明度并不等于<em>每个人都</em>要求更多。</p><p>为了进一步探索这一点，我们进行了一系列四项实验，以更好地了解薪酬透明度<em>如何</em>以及<em>何时</em>可以鼓励员工（尤其是女性）更有效地谈判公平工资。在我们的第一项研究中，实验室参与者在四轮流行的单词搜索游戏后根据他们的表现获得报酬，并有机会谈判以获得更好的报酬。 In studies 2, 3, and 4, online participants prepared themselves to go into a performance review, armed with varying degrees of information regarding performance and pay, to possibly negotiate for a better annual raise. They were told that they were slated for a 3% raise but that raises could range from 3% to 10%. Across these studies, we varied the amount of information participants could access regarding both the amount other people were paid and participants&#39; performance relative to their peers&#39;.</p><p> These studies yielded four important findings regarding distributive and procedural pay transparency:</p><p> <strong>1. People made clearer comparisons.</strong> We found that the best predictor of whether someone tried to negotiate for higher pay was their performance relative to that of peers. Compared with average performers, high performers were approximately 50% more likely to request higher pay when they knew their ranking relative to others. It&#39;s important to note that in our study, participants saw the previous year&#39;s performance and pay data for their team members, and it was clear that increased performance was directly related to increased pay. Although not an explicit formula indicating performance-based pay, this information provided a clear signal to participants that pay raises were largely determined by performance.</p><p> <strong>2. People negotiated fairly.</strong> Average performers were more likely to accept the minimum raise offered to them, often citing the raise as fair based on their performance. As one person stated, “Considering I only met expectations throughout the year rather than exceeded them, asking for a higher raise seems fruitless and unearned.” Generally, average performers rarely asked for the maximum raise, in part because they considered the fact that they were performing at a lower level than some peers. This was true, though, only when they had all of the information. When they were told nothing about their performance, 85% of people requested the maximum pay amount. Lacking performance information, average performers asked for the highest raises available within the pay range.</p><p> <strong>3. Women <em>do</em> ask for higher pay.</strong> Counter to a pervasive assumption, women didn&#39;t seem to need much encouragement to negotiate. In fact, when the percentage of participants who negotiated is considered, women were often more likely than men to negotiate (though this was not a statistically significant difference). These findings cast some doubt on the idea that one reason for the gender wage gap is that women negotiate less often than their male counterparts. Recent research combining information from dozens of negotiation studies has come to the same conclusion: Many of the negotiation gaps between men and women have largely disappeared in recent years. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Although this is good news, it does little to close the gender pay gap as it currently stands.</p><p> <strong>4. People were motivated to perform better.</strong> Average performers expressed motivation to work harder and perform better to earn a higher raise during the next review cycle. When asked why they did not negotiate for more money, one participant stated, “My numbers did not show that I deserved a higher raise. With better numbers the following year, a case would be made for a higher raise.” Another stated, “I knew I&#39;d done an average job, so I hope to do better in the future and hope to get a better raise next year.”</p><p> Our findings replicate and extend an old but powerful notion in management research: the <em>fair process effect</em> . <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Employees will accept unfavorable outcomes if they believe those outcomes were produced by a fair system. Put differently, if people know <em>why</em> they are being paid less (in other words, there is procedural transparency), they will not respond negatively and might even work harder.</p><h3> Make Pay Transparency a Win-Win for Your Organization</h3><p> Pay transparency can be a win-win opportunity rather than a compliance hurdle. But simply listing pay data in job postings without any context in response to regulations might be a big mistake. These practices not only disregard the spirit of the laws but also come at a heavy price and forfeit significant opportunities. Leaders should think beyond compliance and consider ways to strategically leverage pay transparency for their organization to improve applicant attraction and employee retention. Our research offers some insights into how this can be done.</p><p> <strong>Make pay only <em>part</em> of the transparency equation.</strong> Counter to some pervasive fears that transparency will increase labor costs, cause jealousy, and create conflict, the reality is that secrecy around pay creates problems of its own. As researchers at Payscale found, most employees are <a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">unsure whether they are paid fairly</a> , with many believing they are underpaid when they are not, which leads to greater turnover and dissatisfaction. Our research suggests that without a reference point for performance, employees have little to no basis for judging what compensation would be fair and are therefore more likely to make unreasonable requests. Transparency in both performance <em>and</em> pay can enable employees to better assess the fairness of their pay and make more reasonable requests.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on the pay decision-making process.</strong> Procedural transparency helps managers more clearly communicate with employees about pay because salaries/bonuses are based on performance rather than on seemingly intangible or, worse yet, bias-laden factors. Providing information on how pay is determined helps incumbent employees understand why their pay is higher or lower than their peers&#39; and, more importantly, how to move up. Managers can&#39;t be accused of favoritism and bias when pay is directly determined by performance, which puts them in a collaborative role during pay conversations. With a focus on performance, these conversations can focus on development and examine how employees can perform better and earn higher raises.</p><p> <strong>Recognize that (distributive) pay transparency will not fix inequity on its own.</strong> There&#39;s an assumption that distributive pay transparency will close pay gaps; however, evidence suggests that this alone is not enough to create an equitable workplace. Research has shown that women and men are <em>asking</em> for salary increases in <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">relatively equal proportions</a> , but women are still less successful at getting what they ask for. Distributive pay transparency can help reduce some ambiguity, but both performance and pay transparency (procedural transparency) together equip employees with the tools they need to ask for what they deserve. When people know what to expect from negotiations (that is, what the bargaining zone is and what&#39;s reasonable to ask for), gender differences are minimized. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> For example, <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">women of color</a> don&#39;t often take advantage of opportunities to negotiate roles, responsibilities, or flexible work arrangements, creating long-term inequities that explain pay gaps beyond starting salary. Broader transparency helps reduce the ambiguity that often leaves women and members of other minority populations hesitant to negotiate, even when they know they could.</p><p> <strong>Consider the benefits for current employees <em>and</em> applicants.</strong> Simply posting pay ranges is only one piece of the puzzle. Applicants have negative reactions to excessively wide pay ranges because they don&#39;t offer useful information. In this case, pay is still essentially secret. As we found in our study, without meaningful information, individuals are inclined to ask for the maximum amount to see what is possible. This creates yet another headache for hiring managers. A better approach would be to leverage procedural transparency to clearly outline the factors used when determining a salary offer, and perhaps even how heavily those factors are weighted. For example, Buffer, a marketing company, has done a great job of creating a <a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">pay system</a> that balances simplicity (for better understanding) and complexity (for capturing nuance) by using a standard formula for making pay decisions: salary = job type x seniority x experience + location + $10,000 or equity.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Despite organizational concerns and hesitancy to implement government regulations around pay transparency, such policies continue to gain traction and are just one force behind growing expectations around salary disclosures. In a 2022 report from HR technology firm Visier, 79% of surveyed employees said they want <a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">pay transparency</a> ; Gen Z employees were the strongest proponents of it.</p><p> Our research highlights the potential for procedural transparency to strategically mitigate the perceived organizational risks while also meeting legal requirements and social expectations. While changes are clearly happening, we hope business leaders think more deeply and creatively about <em>how</em> to make pay transparent in ways that both support organizational goals and meet employee needs.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Delicate Dynamics of Challenging a Superior</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>Benjamin Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one&#39;s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person and the situation.</p><p> For those keen on maintaining professional decorum and growing in their roles, this guide can help ensure that your challenging conversations are both constructive and respectful.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Choose your battles wisely.</strong> Workplaces are vibrant ecosystems of opinions, processes, and methodologies. It can be enticing to address every single discrepancy or divergence in opinion that one encounters, but wisdom lies in discerning which battles are worth fighting. Every time a potential disagreement arises, consider: Is this issue so significant that it warrants a confrontation? Minor differences in opinion might be addressed more effectively through passive channels or should even be overlooked. But larger concerns, especially those affecting team dynamics, company culture, or broader business objectives, require a more direct approach.</p><p> <strong>Understand the importance of timing.</strong> In the world of professional communication, timing can be everything. Choosing the right moment can make the difference between a concern being genuinely considered or hastily dismissed. Before even considering challenging a superior, it&#39;s crucial to pause and assess the situation from a holistic viewpoint. Is your concern so immediate that it demands to be addressed immediately? Alternatively, would it be better to earmark it for a detailed, private discussion later? It&#39;s wise to avoid confronting superiors during high-pressure situations or public forums because it can be misconstrued as an attempt at disruption or showmanship. By choosing the optimal time, you create a smoother path for constructive dialogue.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prioritize private discussions.</strong> The environment in which you choose to voice your concerns plays a pivotal role in how those concerns are received. Engaging in public disagreements or conflicts can lead to multiple unforeseen complications, including being perceived as aggressive or confrontational. By choosing a private setting for these discussions, you provide both yourself and your superior with an atmosphere conducive to open and genuine dialogue. This approach not only minimizes distractions and potential biases but also reinforces the idea that the intent is constructive feedback, not public criticism.</p><p> <strong>Master the art of “I” statements.</strong> Effective communication is as much about content as it is about delivery. The words we choose and the manner in which we frame our concerns can significantly influence the reception of our message. Instead of adopting a potentially confrontational tone, use “I” statements to express observations, feelings, and suggestions. For instance, instead of bluntly stating, “You&#39;ve overlooked this crucial aspect,” a more collaborative approach would be, “I feel that this particular aspect could benefit from further attention.” This approach ensures that the focus remains on the issue at hand and not on personal biases or confrontations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Embrace the feedback process.</strong> The journey of challenging a superior or expressing concerns is inherently bilateral. It&#39;s not just an avenue for you to voice your thoughts but also an opportunity to understand the other person&#39;s perspective. Demonstrating a genuine openness to feedback, even if it&#39;s contradictory to your viewpoint, is vital. This approach not only paves the way for mutual respect but also fosters a culture of continuous learning and collaboration within the organization.</p><p> <strong>Align with like-minded peers, but tactfully.</strong> While individual concerns have their merit, there&#39;s undeniable strength in numbers. Finding allies or colleagues who share your perspective can provide additional weight to your concerns. However, it&#39;s imperative that this alignment is not perceived as cliquey or divisive. The primary focus should always remain on the collective benefit of the organization rather than on forming factions within the team.</p><p> <strong>Keep the organization&#39;s goals at the forefront.</strong> Any concerns or challenges you raise should inherently resonate with the broader objectives and goals of the organization. By consistently aligning your feedback and suggestions with the company&#39;s mission and values, you reassure your superiors of your commitment to the collective success of the organization over your individual aspirations.</p><p> <strong>Brace for a spectrum of outcomes.</strong> While we all hope for positive and constructive outcomes from our disagreements, it&#39;s essential to be prepared for a variety of reactions. Your superior might be receptive, indifferent, or even defensive. By anticipating these potential responses and planning your strategies accordingly, you ensure that you remain balanced, constructive, and professional, irrespective of the immediate feedback.</p><h3> The Aftermath: Reflect, Adapt, and Evolve</h3><p></p><p> Every professional interaction, especially those involving challenges or confrontations, provides a rich opportunity for personal and professional growth. After the discussion, take the time to evaluate the effectiveness of the conversation, the strategies employed, and the outcomes achieved. These reflections will bring invaluable lessons to light and help you to continuously refine and enhance your communication skills for future challenges.</p><p> Ultimately, while the task of challenging a superior might seem steeped in potential pitfalls, with the right strategies and a focus on mutual growth and respect, it can be navigated with tact and professionalism. Encouraging open dialogue and a culture of feedback is the bedrock of innovative and forward-thinking organizations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Ghost Scenarios Haunt Strategy Execution</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang is a senior fellow in management practice at the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Collaborative Strategy Lab. Rafael Ramírez is professor of practice at Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Scenarios Programme.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, have observed that business leaders are inclined, and their organizations configured, to work with only a single implicit view of the future. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That view is typically deeply embedded within their strategies as a set of unquestioned assumptions about the future context. We call these sets of unexamined assumptions <em>ghost scenarios</em> because they are invisible — and because they may come back to haunt executives and companies in unanticipated and unwelcome ways.</p><p></p><p> Underpinning every ghost scenario is a small set of implicit trends that leaders project into the future without questioning whether they might change. Consider the ways in which dramatic changes in climate have come to haunt rail services in Britain. In July 2022, temperatures above 40 degrees Celsius (104 degrees Fahrenheit) were recorded in the country for the first time. These high temperatures heated the rails to slightly over 62 C (143 F), causing them to bend. As a result, many train trips were canceled and service on other routes slowed to 60 mph. The rail tracks had been engineered for a future in which the air temperature did not exceed 27 C (80 F). In short, the British rail network was designed and built to work not in the scenario in which it found itself in 2022 but in a scenario that made the implicit assumption that historical climate trends would continue unchanged.</p><h3> Assumptions Hide in Plain Sight</h3><p> Research on human perception has demonstrated that people differentiate the object of their visual focus from its background by bringing that object to the forefront of their attention while everything else recedes. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Humans can focus on either the figure or the background but never both at the same time.</p><p> The <a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">Rubin vase illusion</a> is a well-known example of this figure-ground (or background) perception challenge. Depending on how you look at the picture, you will see either a vase or two faces in profile. Importantly, however, you cannot see both at the same time: One or the other perceptually recedes to become the background of the figure you see. To see both figures, you must alternate between them.</p><p> It&#39;s important that executives are able to recognize how people&#39;s ability to focus can also blind them to important contextual information, since leaders often fail to see the background upon which their strategies will play out — and on which their strategies depend. They may consider hard infrastructure — such as rail tracks — to be a relatively static background issue and focus their attention on trends that seem more salient to business planning, such as changes in customer preferences and habits. But that can lead executives to implement a strategy that may be unexpectedly disrupted by the unexamined assumptions about its context that are woven through its background issues.</p><p></p><p> Particularly today, given the fast pace of change, soaring uncertainty, and high levels of turbulence, failing to surface the assumptions built into strategic planning is risky, as is a failure to consider multiple possible alternative futures through <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">scenario planning</a> . <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Scenario planning exercises can help executives explore how their strategies might play out in different business contexts and conditions, with an eye toward honing those strategies to be more effective.</p><p> To understand how scenario planning can keep executives from being haunted by a ghost scenario, let&#39;s look at two global organizations we recently worked with in the Oxford Scenarios Programme. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA Examines Its ESG Assumptions</h3><p> Insurance company <a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a> serves 95 million clients in over 50 countries with products and services in the areas of property-casualty insurance, life insurance and savings, and asset management. One of the company&#39;s key strategic goals is to sustain its climate leadership position. Wisely, executives from AXA decided to make the future context of that goal the focus of their attention for a limited period of time so that they could explore how it might change and how they might need to adapt if it did.</p><p> The company was particularly interested in understanding how future environmental, social, and governance (ESG) trends might affect its stated goal. For example, what might be the impact of some US states&#39; proposed legislation that would penalize financial institutions pursuing ESG investment strategies? Or, how might the public react if companies are seen as greenwashing or misrepresenting their ESG credentials? Thus, instead of letting ESG requirements, as currently understood, be the ghost scenario, the company asked questions about the future of ESG and, more broadly, about the emerging sustainability context for corporations.</p><p> Participants and facilitators in the scenario-planning exercise worked in teams to look at the future environment. One scenario imagined that stand-alone insurance companies had been swallowed up by dominant tech platforms whose own ESG priorities superseded those of the insurers. In another scenario, governments set stringent regulations regarding ESG issues, with compliance implications for companies&#39; strategic choices. In yet another imagined future, climate change accelerated more than expected, causing businesses to shift their priorities to urgently address climate-related crises — or to focus exclusively on reducing CO2 emissions, abandoning social and governance agendas.</p><p> By explicitly engaging with the ghost scenario and its equally plausible alternatives, AXA came to understand that continuing to strive to deliver superior ESG performance as it is currently understood might not be the only future it should be preparing for. Within AXA, these insights have been used to inform a conversation about future ESG challenges and their implications for possible announcements and commitments to be made, including when and with whom. They&#39;ve prompted AXA to start preparing alternative strategies in the event that delivering great performance against current ESG expectations becomes irrelevant.</p><p></p><h3> Swift Anticipates Digital Currencies</h3><p> Swift (the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication) is a member-owned cooperative that enables financial messaging and related services for cross-border payments around the world. It currently delivers over 30 million messages a day for more than 11,000 institutions in over 200 countries and territories. It was created in the early 1970s by 239 banks in 15 countries to solve the growing problem of clunky, slow, and costly cross-border payments communications via a new technology platform. With disruption as part of its origin story, Swift is proactive about potential changes in its context.</p><p> In 2021, Swift executives were interested in understanding how digital currencies, including those issued by central banks, might evolve in the years ahead. The category more than doubled in 2021, to more than 9,000 cryptocurrencies.</p><p> Rather than assuming this unfolding and rapid growth in digital currencies to be the only possible scenario, executives at Swift paused to better understand what other developments might occur, how they might shape the future digital currency ecosystem, and how Swift might be affected. For example, economists and other experts have pointed to the lack of intrinsic value of many digital currencies, as well as concerns about <a href="https://concerned.tech/">the security and reliability of their underlying technologies</a> .</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Where the Ghosts Hide in Common Strategic Planning Processes</h4><p> <strong>In a SWOT analysis,</strong> leaders consider their organization&#39;s strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats in relation to only the current scenario and to known competitors, suppliers, customers, regulatory rules, and the like. When identifying and analyzing risks, executives implicitly assume that there is only one scenario. However, in another context (a different scenario), risks might evaporate and new opportunities might arise.</p><p> <strong>In stakeholder mapping,</strong> leaders make an assessment about the attention and power of stakeholders now and in one expected future. An implicit scenario is the background to this assessment. But the importance of stakeholders could change significantly if the context unexpectedly changes.</p><p> <strong>In game theory and war-gaming,</strong> competitors&#39; moves are considered within the context of a ghost scenario, and war games are typically conducted with no consideration of a different future other than the one that is underway. However, changing scenarios could require new tactics and surface unforeseen future combatants.<br /></article></aside></div><p> Swift&#39;s own stance on digital currencies was open and neutral. It would potentially support them if they were properly regulated and added value to the economies, businesses, and communities it served.</p><p> The scenarios developed for Swift&#39;s executives explored different ways in which trust in the technology might evolve. In some of them, trust associated with digital currencies would disappear as the opaque technology and algorithms upon which they are based became suspect. In other scenarios, digital currencies could be manipulated, and thus the authenticity of what was being exchanged could no longer be guaranteed. And in another scenario, a more generalized lack of trust in for-profit financial institutions would spread to providers of digital currencies, leading some segments of society to hesitate to engage with either, with related consequences.</p><p> For the Oxford participants envisioning these scenarios, it was not clear that the values held by those promoting the technology, or the values that the technology supposedly enabled, would be accepted by governmental regulators or by those in society at large in all imaginable future contexts. Swift&#39;s executives have since explored those sets of scenarios, which provided rich and divergent insights about the ways digital currencies might pan out. Those insights have helped them avoid relying on overly simplistic views of the future — and being swayed by hype.</p><h3> How to See a Ghost Before It Haunts You</h3><p> Based on our experience leading scenario planning exercises for AXA, Swift, and many other organizations, we have developed the following suggestions for executives who want to bring their ghost scenarios into view and make the figure-ground reversal a key part of their strategy practice.</p><p> <strong>Use scenario planning to acknowledge implicit assumptions.</strong> Recognize that every organization&#39;s strategy presumes a future scenario that often remains unquestioned. That is, every executive engages in a form of implicit scenario planning, whether they are conscious of it or not. Making scenario planning a regular part of the strategy-making process achieves two important goals: It alerts leaders to how turbulent conditions could change the context within which they work and compete, and it acknowledges the reality that current conditions themselves present a hypothetical future scenario, not a fixed reality.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize the figure-ground dilemma.</strong> Acknowledge that the figure that is attended to (most often, the organization&#39;s strategy) and the background that is so often ignored (the unexamined ghost scenario) cannot successfully be the focus of attention at the same time. Instead, executives need to flexibly and sequentially shift between the two to investigate each fully and avoid the trap of making implicit assumptions about the other. AXA took the time to deliberately explore the future of ESG rather than assuming there would be no changes to how it is currently used and understood. Swift purposefully focused on understanding the potential future contexts of digital currencies rather than just implicitly assuming subsequent options from the existing trends.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Dedicate executive time and resources to the problem.</strong> Organizations must intentionally create a time and space for leaders to explore how relevant economic, political, technological, social, and environmental factors might be changing. Contrast a small set of future scenarios with the ghost scenario to pinpoint where current strategy might need to be adapted to be well positioned for the range of ways the context might develop. Some organizations even have dedicated units, such as the <a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">Global Business Environment scenarios team</a> at Shell International. <a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">Policy Horizons Canada</a> plays this role for the Canadian government.</p><p></p><p> For all of these efforts to be truly useful, scenario planning outputs must be fed back into strategic decision-making rather than written up in a report and placed on a shelf. They should also be disseminated more widely in an organization so that people at all levels and functions can consider possible implications from their own perspective — implications that might not occur to leadership. For a strategy to be successful when the context changes, executives need to have a balanced approach — recognizing both figure and ground as important areas for discernment. That is, they must recognize the importance of the background or ground upon which their actions will play out, even as they plan their next move. Savvy executives know that they must both envision and embrace change. The trick is learning to adeptly shift one&#39;s attention between the figure and the ground to see how the context might unfold, so it doesn&#39;t leave your strategy ungrounded.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Fueling Interdisciplinary Innovation With AI: Volvo&#39;s Anders Sjögren</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automotive Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory. On this episode of the Me, Myself, and AI podcast, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Anders joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to explain the ways the carmaker uses data and artificial intelligence to inform manufacturing — ensuring that parts are made consistently and as efficiently as possible — as well as driver experience and safety. He also outlines some specific ways smart technology keeps drivers alert and aware of conditions around them and describes Volvo&#39;s approach to technology-driven innovation. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/MMAI-S8-E1-Sjogren-Volvo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Anders Sjögren"></p><h4> Anders Sjögren, Volvo Cars</h4><p> Anders Sjögren is senior technical leader for Volvo Cars. He focuses on strategy, research, innovation, and transformation, with the key objective of ensuring that the automaker understands and executes within the continuously emerging areas of data, analytics, and artificial intelligence. Application areas include creating AI-enabled intelligent customer functionality and using AI to reform Volvo&#39;s operations and development activities. Sjögren has an academic background in mathematical statistics (large-scale and computational aspects) and an industrial background in data-centric methods development and software product development.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one carmaker use AI to bring together all of the complex systems required to engineer a safe and high-performing vehicle? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m Anders Sjögren from Volvo Cars, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Today, Sam and I are delighted to be joined by Anders Sjögren, senior technical leader, data, analytics, and AI-enabled engineering, at Volvo Cars.让我们开始吧。 Anders, welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So tell us a little bit about your role at Volvo Cars.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m a technical leader in data, analytics, and AI in the engineering part [of the organization], so that&#39;s the R&amp;D. So, essentially, what comes in is a wish for a car, and what comes out is drawings and code. In that area, there are, of course, a lot of possibilities for data analytics and AI, both during the development process and also as part of the actual functions in the car — so intelligent functions and personalized functions and so on.</p><p> So my purpose here is really to make sure that we get the value that we can through data, analytics, and AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is [your focus] the AI and data analytics that go into the car — like the sensors and all kinds of intelligent devices in the car that make driving safer and more interactive, and things like that? Or is it also customer acquisition and dealer networks and all kinds of data analytics to run a business of making and selling cars?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yes. So, I mean, all of those apply to Volvo Cars, but the part I&#39;m really active in is more in the part of the making of the car.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think that&#39;s a great point because when most people think about cars and artificial intelligence, I think they immediately jump to this idea of fully self-driving cars. And what you&#39;re pointing out is how much other stuff that there is going on, even in the production of cars, that can benefit from artificial intelligence. You know, I think perhaps everyone&#39;s frustrated that we don&#39;t have fully automated cars now, but there&#39;s so much going on behind the scenes that people don&#39;t get a chance to see. What are some of the examples of the ways that you&#39;re using artificial intelligence in the production process?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we take a little bit of a step back, the goal of Volvo Cars is really to give people the freedom to move in a personal and sustainable and a safe way.</p><p> If we start with “personal,” then it&#39;s really critical that we understand you and make you feel special as a customer or as someone in the car. And there, of course, it has to do with starting with the sensors and then really interpreting those values. That can be cameras, different types of steering input …</p><p> Another area is definitely sustainability. AI is being used there to make sure that we have as many lightweight parts as possible. So using AI, one can, for example, get mechanical parts with the same strength and those kind of properties, but with much lower weight and less material that&#39;s being used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In the design process, you&#39;re talking about, right? As engineers consider all the different permutations of parts, yeah?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> In the design process — yes, exactly. That&#39;s really the essence of AI, I think, in lots of engineering activities, is that we go from manually deciding first what we want to do, but then actually performing all the different steps. That&#39;s the current way of doing it, while in the AI era, it&#39;s much more about deciding and describing what are the aspects I want to reach to? What are things I want optimized, and what are maybe the boundary conditions? And then the AI helps you get there.</p><p> So in the context of the mechanical parts, you might say, “These are the attachment points. These are the strength and stiffness properties I want. Give me the part with those properties but [make it] as light as possible and also, of course, possible to produce.”</p><p> That could be one area. And also, it is super important for sustainability that we use as little material as possible and also have as low a rate as possible.</p><p> And then, of course, the third point was about [safety]. And, of course, we have autonomous cars, but also, even before that, there are other types of functionality being used. For example, understanding the driver: Is the driver aware or not? Should we maybe nudge him to take a cup of coffee or something if he seems to be tired?</p><p> In the later versions of our cars, we understand if there are some pets or children left in the car, maybe on a hot day, and then preventing them [from getting] hurt in such a situation and so on.</p><p> I&#39;d say that those are some of the areas where AI can really be a core technology in bringing us toward our purpose.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s really interesting because lots of times organizations tell us they start with a problem they&#39;re trying to solve and then find a technology to solve it, and that makes sense, because otherwise you&#39;re trying to find a problem to fit a solution, which seems backward. You mentioned that your cars can sense … if a person or a pet is accidentally left in the car. How did Volvo make the decision to focus on that particular problem to solve?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> A lot of what we do is really created by real-world safety in that we actually see what are the actual causes of people getting injured. I mean, if we take the analogy with crashes and that type of safety, we have teams that go out to sites when there has been a crash to really see what actually happened in reality and not just on certification [from] that type of crash test and so on.</p><p> And, going back to this example, if we look here, pets and kids do get hurt — hopefully not in a Volvo car, but that&#39;s reality, right?</p><p> But what you mentioned there is really super interesting because then it also goes the other way around: Like, now that we have these sensors, what are the other really valuable functionalities that we can provide our customers with through this, of course, taking privacy into account and so on?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is quite intriguing because Volvo … I remember as a child that my uncle used to say, “You want a safe car, you get a Volvo.” And it&#39;s always been synonymous with safety, and it&#39;s really amazing to step back and think about ... for a company who has put one of its main goals for safe experience, now, with the availability of this amount of data and all of this massive amount of processing, I could imagine there are so many use cases that, to Sam&#39;s point, are being thought about. So that&#39;s really, really encouraging.</p><p> What [does] the road map here look like? I mean, is this a constant sort of innovation ideation approach going on to say, “What else could we do in these three pillars of personal, safe, and sustainable?” What is the process for coming up with these ideas and picking up the good ones and pursuing them or not?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think that those ideas can either come from the technology side and be really inspired by that, or it could come from the analytics side. And often it&#39;s when the new technology and the really customer-centric needs … where they meet, and also, of course, where we have the agility in the organization to execute on it. That&#39;s really where we have something that&#39;s really fruitful. It&#39;s typically a mix of different sources of this: innovations and new directions, I would say.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And there&#39;s a mechanism to create this interdisciplinary inspiration in the company?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I would say so. I would say that there are both formal mechanisms but also informal mechanisms. [As] a car company, Volvo Cars is not super big. Of course there are also smaller ones, but I think it&#39;s also an advantage that, I mean, pretty much all the different steps, from product strategy, design, the R&amp;D, engineering, and then the later stages …</p><p> The headquarters is in Gothenburg [in Sweden], within walking distance. The US department is literally 50 meters from where I&#39;m sitting right now, while 50 meters in the other direction, there are the crash test facilities and the safety center.</p><p> So, what I want to say with that is that it&#39;s more easy to get connections and to create this kind of — how should I put it? — informal innovation activities.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is where relatively smaller size and colocation really, really helps. To have teams that close to each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s funny to talk about it being small, because it&#39;s certainly not a small company.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, I guess. As we&#39;re chatting, I&#39;m thinking about some of the people we&#39;ve talked to before, and one of the recurring themes that people have mentioned is, oh, this idea [of] starting with a business problem: “You don&#39;t have AI and find a place to use it. You start with a business problem and then solve it.” But this is kind of a nice mix on that — that it sounds like there&#39;s a lot that starts with a business problem, but then, interestingly, once these processes are in place, and once these technologies are in place, then there becomes a grassroots innovation to say, “All right; how can we use that?” And that&#39;s an interesting perspective that, I think, hasn&#39;t come through strongly — or maybe I&#39;m forgetting something — but it seems like that hasn&#39;t come through as strongly. This is a nice mix of that, that maybe works in this size organization … this colocated organization.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, and not least in the prototyping and ideation stages. But, then, of course, before it actually goes into the product, it needs to go through a more thorough review and so on.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> There&#39;s been quite a few investments and acquisitions of smaller AI startups and firms by Volvo. Tell us a bit about the overall ecosystem of internal and vendor and partner companies that come together to bring to life some of these AI-enabled ideas that you&#39;re talking about. Is it internal? Is it external? Is it a mix? How do you think about the ecosystem?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I would definitely say that it&#39;s a mix. Some of the things … we need to do it ourselves to get the full understanding or where we really want to be in the forefront, and [in] some other areas, we definitely want to partner with other companies that are strong in those areas. Traditionally speaking, a car is a super complex product. It has hundreds or thousands of different parts that all need to come together. And, of course, it is a space where there is traditionally a lot of suppliers supplying different parts.</p><p> Lately, we are moving more toward bringing software implementation in-house to increase the speed and agility in the development process.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That seems particularly complicated in auto manufacturing because if I think about how cars got started, they were independent systems. There was a braking system, and a power train system, and an air conditioner, and an infotainment system, and all these were separate. And that&#39;s kind of nice because then we have a certain, different standard than we would have for the infotainment system than we would have for the braking system — or at least I hope that there would be. But what you&#39;re pointing out is, each one of these may be using sensors that come from a different area, and how the whole car has become more complicated independently, but it&#39;s also become more complicated cohesively, trying to connect all these parts and have them work together.</p><p> And that seems, on the one hand, an opportunity for artificial intelligence but, at the same time, a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah. It&#39;s 100% true. It&#39;s both a really big opportunity, but that also means that&#39;s really one of the core challenges — I mean, how to build the cohesive understanding of both the inside and the outside of the car.</p><p> We speak about the customer digital twin and vehicle digital twin and so on, and in some sense, those aspects can mean a lot of different things. But, of course, these different systems that you speak about, they are traditionally in different parts of the company, so that also means that there is a lot of cross-functional collaboration that is needed. But we really need to bridge those kind of organizational borders.</p><p> I think that that&#39;s really one of the key points — that is, in order to get successful adoption of the analytics and AI, it really means that different parts of the company need to work together to make it happen. Because otherwise, it will just become a silo. Some people will not really have the benefits of it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You know, it&#39;s very true. It&#39;s a common theme, and in our work at BCG, we have this rule of thumb — the 10:20:70 — where we say 10% is the data and algorithms, and 20% is the technology and the digital platform, but 70% of it is the business integration and implementation and bringing different parts of the organization together. This, perhaps, is nowhere more true than at a car company, where you have, as you said, Sam, seemingly disparate systems that are coming together to create a bigger system, but each one of these units has been perfected individually, and now you want the collective perfection as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we talked a lot about Volvo. How did you personally get interested in artificial intelligence, in data, in technology and analytics? What&#39;s your origin story?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think I&#39;ve always been interested in computers. My father was really an addict, so I kind of grew up with that.</p><p> I started out as an engineering student [and got a] master&#39;s in computer science. And then I started off as a research engineer in the medical area, at the university hospital in Gothenburg, then found out fairly quickly that in order to really make use of data — conclusions and so on come from data … so I then went into the area of mathematical statistics.</p><p> So I did a Ph.D. in that, then went back to software product development. After some time, I went back to academia for a couple of years, did a postdoc, and then was offered a good opportunity at Volvo Cars. So I&#39;ve essentially been here for seven years now. That&#39;s a bit of my history.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Quite inspiring.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we also want to ask you a few rapid-fire questions, and the idea is just to answer it as quickly as you can. These are not particularly Volvo questions.</p><p> What have you been proudest of that you&#39;ve done with artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The problem is that most of the things, I can&#39;t speak about.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer too.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You have to wait and see. OK, well, what worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The worries?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Oh, I think, of course, one is the longer term — the kind of singularity things. But I think a bit closer to now, so to speak, we definitely see that this super-fast progression of large language [models] and what they can do, and also the kind of systems that don&#39;t just take one problem and give one answer but can really produce a series of steps, in sequence. And that is a super-powerful technology, but a super-powerful technology can be used both for good and for bad.</p><p> That&#39;s both something that makes me super excited but also a little bit worried. What will the world look like in 20 years?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Motorcycling, but obviously using technology. But it&#39;s more of a … yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Technology&#39;s involved. Everything&#39;s involved in technology in some way.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, pretty much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were a kid? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Medical doctor.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, that ties with your first career in working in the medical company, then.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I think so, but then I found mathematics and those things to be super exciting, so I went into that area.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What do you hope that we can gain from the advent of these technologies?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we say the greatest wish, I think it is that we find a way to use it in a way for our common good. We need to find a way to integrate it into society, and I think that that is really my biggest wish for it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In a relatively short time, we learned so much about various uses of data, AI, and technology, in just what it takes to build a car in new ways, and all the different ways that AI and tech are helping and serving the people who are driving them. It&#39;s been really enlightening, Anders. Thank you for joining.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thanks for having me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Ways Leaders Can Turn Pushback Into Progress</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phillip G. Clampitt and Bob DeKoch. <p>Phillip G. Clampitt is the Blair Endowed Chair in Communication at the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay. Bob DeKoch is the founder of leadership consulting firm Limitless and former president of the Boldt Co. They are the coauthors of <cite>Leading with Care in a Tough World</cite> (Rodin Books, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it’s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Clampitt-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it&#39;s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns and raising questions to active opposition and sabotage. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> Effective leaders think of pushback as an opportunity to boost their team&#39;s learning while moving their organization forward. The objective should be to increase people&#39;s understanding and build support by tempering both advocate enthusiasm and contrarian pessimism. This deeper level of understanding, while not necessarily satisfying to all in the moment, fosters a climate of candor, humility, adaptation, and trust, thereby subtly steering pushback away from latent disruptive tendencies.</p><p></p><p> Drawing on decades of research, C-suite observations, and interviews, we&#39;ve identified the major mistakes leaders make when encountering pushback and offer five guidelines to help them better respond.</p><h3> What Doesn&#39;t Work</h3><p> Leaders make three primary mistakes when facing ambivalence, disagreement, or resistance:</p><p> <strong>Suppressing uncertainty.</strong> Pushback increases uncertainty when questions are raised that might not have immediate answers or perspectives are introduced that might have recently emerged or been sidelined or overlooked. Some leaders respond to uncertainty-induced pushback by marginalizing concerns, offering placating assurances, or invoking authoritarian voices. Such practices offer false certainty that undermines trust in the long term.</p><p> According to our research, even employees who seek more certainty in their work lives want their organizations to embrace uncertainty. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Effective leaders avoid the temptation to paper over uncertainty, even when they face demands for a level of certainty that simply doesn&#39;t exist. Even if they don&#39;t know the answers now, they can provide an operating level of certainty by discussing how they will find those answers.</p><p> <strong>Ignoring power dynamics.</strong> Leaders with positional or acquired status directly or subtly influence the nature of the pushback. Highly authoritarian power structures tend to drive pushback underground. Likewise, more subtle power signals can suppress open discussion of legitimate concerns. Leaders might then wrongly equate silence with agreement. Some people will feign acceptance while others sow dissent in the “meeting after the meeting,” thereby revealing and often amplifying people&#39;s fears.</p><p></p><p> We had an opportunity to observe one seasoned executive group&#39;s reaction — which consisted of tepid and token feedback — when their CEO proposed a new initiative. The CEO, sensing a lack of candor, probed for more input. One frustrated executive eventually blurted out, “We don&#39;t share our thoughts on this issue because you are going to do what you are going to do, regardless of what we say.” This remarkably candid comment suggested a deeper challenge: How do powerful people with strong views on particular issues encourage candor? Effective leaders take active steps to mitigate disruptive dialogue — discussed below — because they recognize that inherent power dynamics greatly influence the quality of any discussion.</p><p> <strong>Assuming that the loudest voices represent a consensus.</strong> Pushback takes many forms: Some of them are obvious, like complaints or employee petitions, while others are more subtle, like queries in meetings or a lack of engagement. Leaders are often tempted to pay more attention to the most vocal employees, assuming the people with the biggest megaphones represent majority opinion. They may or may not.</p><p> When the loudest or most politically powerful voices dominate the discussion, such dynamics often create an inaccurate impression of the level of support or divisiveness. Effective leaders recognize the peril at either extreme: the enthusiasts glossing over concerning issues or the contrarians undermining potential support.</p><p></p><h3> Recommendations for Engaging With Pushback</h3><p> Effective leaders not only avoid suppressing uncertainty, ignoring power dynamics, and assuming that the most vocal represent consensus opinion — they also take active countermeasures that reflect the following guidelines.</p><p> <strong>1. Set ground rules for the conversation.</strong> Ground rules like the following drive expectations, temper disrespectful advocacy, and increase the value of pushback opportunities for everyone:</p><ul><li> <strong>Seek to understand viewpoints you don&#39;t agree with.</strong> When discussing contentious issues, many people&#39;s first instinct is to offer an instant rebuttal or counterpoint. Resist that temptation by demonstrating a willingness to engage with a differing point of view. Simple tactics like asking questions or rephrasing someone else&#39;s argument — particularly those with which you disagree — can temper the rebuttal and almost magically enhance the conversational tone. Likewise, statements like “Tell me how my idea might be wrong” or “I may have missed something; please say more” signal openness to new ideas.</li><li> <strong>Respectfully disagree with others.</strong> Respectfully framing the disagreements with language such as “Let me offer another perspective” sets the right discussion tone while also encouraging those who are more hesitant to speak up. Reluctance to share differing points of view often signals an underlying trust deficit. Sometimes leaders need to encourage others to share their concerns despite the inherent power differences in the room.</li><li> <strong>Avoid polarizing, stake-in-the-ground assertions.</strong> Advocating with too much certainty may well trigger power-dynamic issues. Indicating probability levels, such as “I&#39;m 95% certain on this fact,” often stimulates more robust debate.</li><li> <strong>Depersonalize pushback.</strong> If a decision is labeled as “the CEO&#39;s program,” many people will self-censor and avoid raising concerns out of fear of offending the person in power. Depersonalizing pushback by recording concerns on a whiteboard, without attribution, mitigates this power dynamic while tempering strong emotions.</li><li> <strong>Shift your opinions and reactions as the discussion evolves.</strong> Employees often need to be reminded that changing their opinion after considering new evidence or gaining a fresh perspective is not a sign of weakness. No one should fear a loss of face for shifting their opinion. In fact, effective leaders highlight when their opinions shift by making a statement such as “I see an issue that wasn&#39;t on my radar screen.” As the dialogue emerges, reframe key issues to underscore new perspectives.</li></ul><p> <strong>2. Orient the team about pushback opportunities.</strong> Many meetings or initiative rollouts conclude with question-and-answer periods without first offering attendees an orientation on expectations around pushback. Absent clarity, people often make a variety of untested and unspoken assumptions that might not be accurate.</p><p> Some employees become disenfranchised by pushback opportunities because they think all of their ideas should be accepted in totality. They don&#39;t expect reasoned debate or pushback to <em>their</em> pushback. That&#39;s why wise leaders carefully orient employees about possible outcomes other than the accept/reject polarized extremes. They introduce other alternatives, such as tweaking the plan, introducing a test period, delaying implementation, modifying a decision, or rethinking the proposal.</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. Select the right forums and settings.</strong> Some settings, like town hall gatherings or online forums, tend to embolden more emotive expressions of opinions, posturing, and venting. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Such situations might discourage useful inquiry and questions from those less inclined to engage in emotive scrums. The right venues and forums maximize the opportunities for insightful queries, deliberative discourse, and respectful debate. Typically, smaller groups of people who are equipped with the proper discussion parameters work best. Likewise, properly monitored online forums for smaller groups can encourage better pushback dynamics.</p><p> Leaders also need to be mindful that some people are reluctant to share concerns in front of others because they fear being viewed as poor team players or they lack confidence in how to express concerns or defend their views. To encourage people who are more reluctant to speak up, it&#39;s often helpful to provide them with the meeting&#39;s discussion points in advance and encourage them to write down their concerns and queries.</p><p> <strong>4. Focus on educating before advocating.</strong> Skilled educators soon learn to jettison the idea that a single good explanation will suffice to build understanding. Typically, they discuss their methods for arriving at their conclusions, including the opposing viewpoints and extant questions. This approach bakes uncertainty into conclusions, making room for further discussion and contrary views.</p><p> In contrast, advocates rarely discuss evidence or approaches that might contradict their firmly held viewpoints. They often trivialize or deride opposing views when they do entertain them. Advocates might short-circuit any criticism, downplaying uncertainty and reasoning that a brief explanation will enlighten others. Even smart executives often fall into this trap, overestimating the degree and depth of their educational efforts.</p><p> Advocating might play a role at some point after educating, but ultimately, effective leaders assume that allowing people to voice concerns reaps benefits. Short term, the pushback might result in tweaks that will increase long-term acceptance and smooth implementation.</p><p> <strong>5. Signpost inflection points.</strong> As decisions, initiatives, and policies evolve, a leader&#39;s level of certainty and openness to pushback shifts. In the absence of leadership clarity about these inflection points, employees apply unspoken rules regarding pushback, such as the following:</p><ul><li> Rule A: If the leader has not made a final decision, then I can speak up and candidly share my perspectives.</li><li> Rule B: If the leader has a strong position or has made a final decision, then I support it or shut up.</li><li> Rule C: If I agitate on an issue long enough, leaders will yield.</li></ul><p> If unspoken rules A and B undergird the pushback dynamics, then leaders might overestimate the degree of support for an initiative or decision.为什么？ Because employees operating under rule B assume that requests for feedback are for theater or designed to manufacture buy-in; they self-censor or offer only token opposition. Consequently, dissenting and potentially valuable voices go silent.</p><p></p><p> Rule C animates pushback dynamics in precisely the opposite direction, with endless debate; this fosters a culture of complaint after decisions have been tweaked, modified, or finalized. Effective leaders know that openness does not provide a license for never-ending discussion; after all, pushback to the pushback can go on forever.</p><p> The best way to inhibit these silent rules from taking root is to clearly signpost inflection points during pushback. Leaders who camouflage their sentiments in the name of openness undermine the candor of the entire conversation. Instead, effective leaders share their level of openness to tweaking proposed plans, proclaiming when their sentiments have shifted, and clearly signaling when the time for pushback has ended.</p><h3> A Pushback Success Story</h3><p> Laurie Butz, the CEO of Capital Credit Union, routinely uses these guidelines to lean into pushback to fully understand what employees believe they are losing as new initiatives roll out. For example, as the COVID-19 threat faded, she sought to restart face-to-face all-employee meetings to enhance inclusiveness and engage in more robust, thoughtful discussions about pending initiatives. She believes that the educational process goes in both directions, which requires more face-to-face forums that encourage adherence to more productive discussion ground rules than screen-enabled venting.</p><p> Yet that announcement was greeted with considerable pushback by employees who faced a long commute to the twice-a-year gatherings. Some used online surveys to voice concerns about the expense and time, while others expressed their discontent directly to their immediate supervisor, arguing that “Zoom meetings worked pretty well during COVID.”</p><p> Butz acknowledged these concerns while respectfully justifying the in-person gathering because, after all, “you could have a Zoom wedding, but something important would be missing.” Similar messaging was echoed in more personal channels by her “ambassadors” (opinion leaders).</p><p></p><p> Over time, the in-person meetings (1) increased employee engagement, (2) renewed employee interest in being a part of the process, and (3) spawned more thoughtful discussions of key issues. Quantitative evidence backed up these observations. For example, participation in all-employee surveys increased from 60% to 91% after the in-person meetings resumed, and 83% of survey respondents reported that they were “highly engaged in their work.” Anecdotal evidence also emerged: Employees often left the in-person meetings inquiring, “When will we have another opportunity to meet like this?”</p><p></p><p> Suppressing pushback by repressing uncertainty, invoking power dynamics, and paying too much attention to the most vocal employees may well induce short-term conformity and compliance at the expense of <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/decision-downloading/">undermining long-term trust</a> . Adroitly and respectfully managing pushback involves an upfront time commitment that engages employees while supplying forward momentum. The bonus: Leaders learn to more subtly influence how employees interpret trends, events, and decisions and develop greater insight into emerging issues.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>