<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 6 月 20 日星期二 11:28:04 +0000</lastbuilddate><language>英文</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1个</sy:updatefrequency><generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>人工智能的社会科学：英特尔的 Elizabeth Anne Watkins</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 的 AI 实践）的共同负责人。可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"><cite>我、我自己和 AI</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团的合作播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制片人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Relationships]]></category><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Elizabeth Anne Watkins started her doctoral program, she landed a research role studying journalists’ use of security and privacy technologies — but she found the security tools confusing and difficult to use. Today, as a research scientist in the social science of AI at Intel Labs, she advocates for other end users faced with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins) 开始攻读博士学位时，她获得了一项研究工作，研究记者对安全和隐私技术的使用——但她发现安全工具令人困惑且难以使用。如今，作为英特尔实验室人工智能社会科学的研究科学家，她倡导其他面临理解和使用新技术的最终用户。</p><p> Elizabeth 利用社会科学来了解执行复杂芯片制造过程的技术人员的担忧，以便开发新的 AI 系统以更好地为这些人类专家服务。在此过程中，她还帮助技术人员认识到人工智能作为支持技术的作用——甚至是同事——而不是人类的替代品。</p><p>她加入了<cite>“我、我自己和 AI</cite> ”播客的这一集，讨论她作为一名从事技术工作的社会科学家的角色，以及英特尔应用计算机视觉和自然语言处理等人工智能技术改进半导体制造流程的一些方式。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-s7-e2-Watkins-intel-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯"></p><h4>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯，英特尔</h4><p>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins) 是英特尔实验室的研究科学家，也是负责任人工智能咨询委员会的成员。她推动社会科学方法的战略和执行，以扩大人类在人类与人工智能协作中的潜力，并在人工智能工具（如计算机视觉、自然语言处理和机器人。</p><p> Watkins 是数据与社会研究所 AI 实地的附属机构，曾与学术界和工业界的研究中心合作、咨询和合作。她在哥伦比亚大学获得博士学位，在麻省理工学院获得硕士学位，并且是普林斯顿信息技术政策中心及其人机交互小组的博士后研究员。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的 AI for Leaders<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>我、我自己和 AI</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">现在加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>我、我自己和 AI</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-watkins"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们知道人工智能工具正在增强人类的表现，但人们对此有何真实感受？在今天的节目中，了解一家公司如何在考虑最终用户的情况下开发 AI 工具。</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>我是来自英特尔的 Elizabeth Anne Watkins，您正在听<cite>我、我自己和 AI</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎收看<cite>我、我自己和 AI</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每一集，我们都会向您介绍一位利用 AI 进行创新的人。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的 AI 和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来，<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在研究和发布 AI，采访了数百名从业者，并调查了数千家公司，了解如何构建、部署和扩展 AI 功能，并真正改变组织的运作方式。</p><p><strong>山姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天我们有一位伟大的客人：伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯，英特尔的研究科学家。伊丽莎白，感谢您今天加入我们。让我们开始吧。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>非常感谢你今天邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>作为世界上最大的半导体制造商，英特尔可能是大多数人都已经知道的公司，但是您能给我们介绍一下英特尔实验室的总体情况，也许还有您的具体职责吗？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>正如您所说，目前围绕 AI 和 AI 行业以及 AI 领域的大型讨论中，我们并不总是最重要的，但英特尔内部正在开展许多引人入胜的工作，我们有这样一个对该领域的独特视角和进入该领域的独特方式，我很高兴今天能在我们的谈话中介绍其中的一些内容。</p><p>我去年 8 月刚刚加入英特尔，与这么多不同的团队会面已经是一次非常不可思议的经历。我作为人工智能社会科学的研究科学家加入了英特尔，并在英特尔实验室的 Lama Nachman 手下工作。该小组称为智能系统研究。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>伊丽莎白，你提到英特尔实验室正在用人工智能做一些独特的事情。您介意与我们分享您正在做的一些事情吗？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>我特别兴奋的一个项目叫做 MARIE，它是工业环境中多模态活动识别的首字母缩写词。所以基本上，我将从一个比喻开始：想象一下，你的电脑可以看着你组装，比方说，你在互联网上订购的一件家具。当你读到手册的难点时，或者你拿着螺丝刀，拿着一块胶合板，你无法回到手册，想象一下你的电脑可以看到你在做什么，知道手册要告诉您[做什么]，然后帮助您将这两者联系起来。想象一下，你的计算机实际上可以告诉你，“嘿，我想你要把架子 A 拧到支架 B 上，”或者类似的事情。而且我知道，每次我收到他们说里面有一把扶手椅的扁平包装时，我都很难从 A 地到 B 地。</p><p>我们的员工在我们的设施内进行的正是这些过程，他们实际上是在建造和制造半导体芯片。因此，在我们工厂内部工作的人，我们的技术人员，正在做非常复杂和非常精细的工作，为工厂车间发生的各种手动操作处理零件和工具。因此，他们所做的所有工作与将扁平背包放入扶手椅一样复杂——有时甚至更复杂。涉及到很多工具。有各种不同的工艺，不同的设备，不同尺寸的设备。因此，我们正在构建的计算机系统有点像我描述的那个说，“嘿，你的意思是把螺丝 A 放到支架 B 上吗？”我们正在构建系统来帮助我们工厂内部的人员完成这种非常仔细和非常复杂的工作。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>实际上，这是一个有趣的类比。我的意思是，我想我们都觉得扁平包装很有挑战性，也许吧，尽管我不得不承认我有点喜欢它们。但我敢肯定，英特尔内部的情况要复杂得多。我喜欢这个例子的一点是，我觉得我们经常谈论自动化：我们能否让机器学习如何做人类所做的事情？这是机器学习 [ML] 的核心。然后我们谈论增强，以及机器如何帮助人类做出决定？这让我觉得有点不同。这是下一步。</p><p>所以在这种情况下，我们不会试图让机器组装扁平包装。我们并不是要让机器组装半导体。仍然是人类在做这件事。因此，需要在这里学习的是人类。这似乎比我们之前讨论过的更进一步。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>山姆，我很高兴你明白了这一点。这正是我们在英特尔实验室内部谈论的，即人类是专家。人是知道如何与这些系统交互的人，他们知道如何将这些位拧在一起。他们知道将这些微小且非常精密的组件组合在一起所需的所有物理和动态复杂性。</p><p>我们不想训练计算机来做那件事。计算机<em>无法</em>做到这一点。这种组装和清洁过程的方式——因为，当然，所有这些过程都发生在这些超级洁净室里，每个人都必须穿着防护服和手套……我们想支持正在做这件事的人。没有计算机可以做到这一点。这需要人为判断；需要人类的专业知识才能以全面、真正动态并能够应对新压力的方式进行这些过程。</p><p>如果机器的较大部件以特定方式弯曲，或者如果螺钉以特定方式掉入孔中——计算机将需要很多很多年才能评估、诊断和修复这些类型的持续动态问题.但你知道谁真正擅长这样做是人类。因此，我们正在努力以人为本，以人为本。这表明我对 MARIE 感到非常兴奋的双重原因是，既有技术方面，也有人性化的一面。在技​​术方面，我认为 MARIE 非常令人兴奋，因为它是多模式的。它通过环境感应结合了许多不同类型的人工智能系统。它将使用活动识别的计算机视觉与音频传感相结合，并与自然语言处理 [NLP] 相结合，以一种可以帮助在技术人员周围构建周围环境的方式，最终帮助他们 [with] 他们所做的事情。</p><p>但在系统可以帮助他们 [with] 他们所做的事情之前，系统必须真正学习，并且是人类专家教系统如何学习和教系统它需要知道的东西。因此，据我所知，这是一种将人工智能系统部署到新领域并将其应用于新问题的全新方法。 ......我们正在面对和应对人工智能发展的一大挑战，即数据收集。</p><p>您需要大量数据才能进入新域。您需要大量以适当方式标记的数据，根据您要解决的问题类型进行标记。因此，我们有点颠倒了脚本：我们没有在部署系统<em>之前</em>尝试获取所有数据，而是继续部署一个系统，然后与当地专家合作，他们教授系统——通过大声说话和通过动态数据标签——他们教会系统它需要知道什么。因此，希望用于帮助人们完成这些任务的数据将由第一批使用该工具的人生成。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这似乎是一个很好的类比，因为正如你所说，它让我想起了如果是一个新的人类合作伙伴加入该项目你会怎么做。你会经历那些相同的步骤。</p><p> Shervin 和我进行了一些研究，我们发现<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/achieving-individual-and-organizational-value-with-ai/">60% 的人将 AI 视为同事</a>，而这正是您所描述的那种关系。但这让我想到了这里的一点危险。假设当你把那个系统放在那里时，它知道的不多，而且你已经让人类训练了它们。好的;我是一个人。我觉得我有点恼火。我想，“为什么我必须如此努力地训练这个同事？”你如何保持这种活力？你提到这个项目有技术方面，但也有社会方面。我觉得这在社交方面可能比在技术方面更难。</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>这正是我接下来要谈的，因为这正是我要做的。我开始与人们谈论他们对这些系统的实际想法——你是对的。有时他们确实觉得这很烦人，他们会问，“等等——所以我把这个非常复杂的乐器放在一起，系统问我在做什么，这是<em>错的</em>？那么我应该如何不仅花时间做我的工作，还要教这台机器如何做我的工作呢？”</p><p>所以我真的很高兴我能成为实地的社会科学家。我们仍在深入开发，当然，在部署某些东西之前，以及当真正的部署原则出现时，公司通常会尽可能多地进行测试——比如用户体验和用户界面设计——那些通常更接近开发过程的结束。但在这里，社会科学和对人们需要什么、人们可能会觉得烦人的东西以及他们需要信任与他们合作的机器的理解是开发的 DNA。因此，我不断地与我们为其构建系统的技术人员交谈，并向他们提出问题，就像您所描述的那样，问他们，“您认为这很烦人吗？这怎么可能更有帮助？我们可以在系统中构建哪些其他可供性，以使其对您更有帮助？”</p><p>并且还提出更深层次的问题，不仅是关于他们与系统的二元关系，而且还关于他们更大的社会技术工作背景。询问，比如，“你的日程安排是什么样的？”以及，“你们的老板对这个系统有什么看法？”并且，“有没有一种方法可以让我们尝试通过这个系统促进更富有成效的关系，不仅是与你的老板，还有与你的其他同事？”因此，我们的目标是建立一个非常深刻的理解，不仅仅是对一项任务，而是对整个工作空间，并询问我们的系统如何通过成为这个空间内人类的同事，以最佳方式帮助扩大人类潜能, 但也 [问], “如何在了解他们的工作环境的情况下建立它以促进长期关系？”</p><p>因为我们依靠人们提供数据并依靠人们帮助我们实际进行数据标记这一事实所要求的其中一件事是我们需要他们参与，我们需要他们喜欢与系统，我们需要他们发现它值得信赖、可靠和有用。要了解如何实现所有这些目标，需要深入了解社会背景、社会习惯、工作习惯和任务流程。所以这正是我们现在正在做的事情。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我认为你的想法似乎不仅仅局限于这个项目，这真的很有趣。有“好吧，我如何让这个特定项目到位”的元素，但是你正在谈论的很多事情的基础是，“我们如何找出最好的方法来引入，本质上，一个新系统？我们如何找出转变和实现我们整体愿景的最佳方式？”这超越了单个项目。你是如何尝试学习这些课程的？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>这是一个非常好的问题。我真的为我们的实验室和我们在人类与 AI 协作方面所做的一些重大赌注感到自豪，以及有多少来自社会科学的投入、贡献和见解正在被采纳，并且在英特尔历史上一直被采纳，在他们的整个研究项目中。当我们在教育、制造和无障碍等垂直领域开展研究项目和构建产品时，各个团队都进行了深入投资，以促进和鼓励与像我这样的人——与社会科学家进行对话。</p><p>我们经常把这些非常棒的团队聚集在一个房间里，那里有工程师、数据科学家、政策制定者和社会科学家，不仅包括我，还有一个由人类学家 Dawn Nafus 领导的优秀团队，以及另一个社会科学家团队那有心理学家。我们所有人都非常紧密地合作，以确保我们构建的产品不仅是为了解决一个问题而设计的，而且它们是围绕最佳解决方案进行适当设计的，我们利用我们的所有不同类型的多模式可供性工具可以提供，并且我们深刻理解我们所有产品将部署到的社会和组织环境。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为，在我们第一次谈论这些模型和工具与使用数据之间似乎经常发生一种转变：事情非常注重数据和工具，同时又非常注重科学。这很有意义，因为我们不知道如何做其中的一些事情。现在，作为一个社会，我们正在学习如何使用这些工具和模型建筑。但是你在那里提到的很多团队——人类学、心理学——这些并不是我们可能认为 [as] 是生产 AI 应用程序不可或缺的传统事物，但这些正是你碰巧提到的。你为什么选择那些？我猜这是你的一些社会科学背景，对吧？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins)：</strong>是的，在我的研究生学习和博士后工作中，我一直非常关注用户和人。我总是对人们可以多么古怪、多么有创造力和多么创新，以及人们如何经常以他们的开发人员没有预料到和没有预见到的方式使用技术着迷。</p><p>虽然这其中有一些危险因素，正如我们在各种滥用和双重用途应用程序中看到的那样，但人们也已经找到了很多非常奇妙和美妙的方法，让技术更适合他们在他们的上下文或为他们工作更顺利一点。因此，看到英特尔有何不同，因为他们作为半导体制造商的历史，对硬件的深入投资以及采用生态系统方法来部署人工智能工具的方式，真的向我展示了他们是一家关心的公司，就像我一样，关于将要使用这些工具的人以及这些人所处的社会结构，以及构建不仅可以匹配购买或使用这些工具的人，还可以匹配这些技术所融入的生活和社区的工具会被插话。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Elizabeth，很明显，正如我们一直在讨论的那样，您已经了解了很多背景，但我们能否退后一步，问一下您是如何最终担任英特尔实验室的这个角色的？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins)：</strong>我想我担任这个角色的道路很早就开始了，可能是在我研究生生涯的开始。在我毕业于麻省理工学院并开始攻读博士学位后。在哥伦比亚大学，有人可以为一个关于记者安全和隐私行为的项目做出贡献。我的导师说，“嘿，我给你安排了这个项目的面试。”我说，“我对安全和隐私一无所知。”她说，“去面试吧。我给你面试了去吧。”所以在面试的前一天晚上，我想，“哦，我最好有话要说。 PGP — Pretty Good Privacy — 每个人都在谈论 PGP。我最好下载 PGP，这样我就可以假装我知道 PGP 是什么。”我试图弄清楚，但这很难。我想不通……我去了网站，我想，“网站并没有真正解释这里发生的事情。钥匙在哪里？我下载了密钥，但密钥也保存在数据库中，但我将密钥写在我的电子邮件中？哦，我好……我做不到。我很不擅长这个。这不适合我。”</p><p>第二天我接受了出色的项目负责人 Susan McGregor 的采访，我说，“你知道吗？这份工作不适合我。我试着做 PGP；这太难了。有一些关于它的东西，我只是......我不能完全理解这种语言。她说，“我认为这让你非常适合这份工作，因为我们正试图弄清楚为什么安全和隐私对工作人员来说如此困难，尤其是记者，他们是许多不同行为者攻击的高价值目标，我们正在努力弄清楚如何为他们制定更好的安全和隐私协议，所以听起来你对安全的设计方式感到沮丧。”我说，“是的，那令人沮丧。”她说，“好吧，让我们做点工作吧。”</p><p>所以我们最终一起工作了几年，研究记者。我们有一个特别令人痛心的项目，研究发表巴拿马文件的记者。为此，他们拥有数 TB 的数据。有记者在世界各地工作；他们都没有在同一地点，也没有一次突破口。他们从来没有一次泄露所有这些数据。因此，我们将其视为一个成功的故事。我们说，“好的。我们总是听到有关数据泄露和攻击的坏消息；我们从来没有听说过成功的故事。”因此，我们采访了为巴拿马文件撰稿的记者，并与他们讨论了他们的组织文化，以及让所有记者统一协议如何有助于灌输团队合作意识和相互保护的意识。看到文化的力量和围绕像 PGP 和安全协议这样困难的行为的共同使命......这真的很鼓舞人心。</p><p>大约在那个时候，我开始关注面部识别，从那里开始关注人工智能并围绕“为什么这很难理解？”提出类似的问题。我们如何才能以更具战略性的方式将其传达给人们，从而更好地了解他们正在做的工作和他们需要做的工作？我们如何才能以一种对真实的人有意义和可以理解的方式为这些系统带来一些透明度？”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>其中一件有趣的事情是，安全总是那样。如果做起来有点困难，那么我们都倾向于不去做，因为这是明天的问题与今天的问题的对比。 ......这是我们人类最可怕的事情。而且你知道，我认为我们在很多方面都失败了 [at] 没有将其构建到基础架构中，因此它是默认设置。人工智能有很多类比：我们正在构建东西，如果我们不让默认设置易于使用或容易做正确的事情，那么人们就会做错事——或者人们会做容易的事事情或短期的事情。你提到了面部识别：我们应该在我们的基础设施中构建什么样的东西，这样我们才不会传播基于 AI 的错误？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>这是一个很好的问题。在我的研究生生涯和在英特尔的整个研究生涯中，推动我的研究的是一种认识，即人们是自己生活中的专家，我们确实需要在整个开发流程中与人们和用户互动，以便构建不仅仅是系统，还有解决方案，以及针对实际发生的实际问题的解决方案。一家公司尽可能地包括社会科学的专业知识，以及社会科学家可以带来什么严谨而强大的工具来研究人们的生活方式、他们使用的语言种类、他们拥有的价值观种类以及什么对他们来说真正重要他们以及他们想要保护的东西和他们想要保持安全的东西，以及将不同种类的选择和不同种类的途径构建到同一技术中，这些技术可能会被不同级别的人以不同的方式使用，这些都是我很乐意看到整个领域都占据一席之地。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong><em>听起来</em>不错。我的意思是……就像低买高卖听起来不错。公司实际上是如何做到这一点的？他们需要采取哪些步骤才能在这些方面取得进展？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>这是一个很好的问题。我们在英特尔做这件事的方式是，我们正在促进我们的技术团队之间的对话——他们正在围绕机器人技术和辅助工具和教育工具构建真正令人惊叹的系统——并将社会科学家嵌入所有这些团队，以便我们可以问关于“嘿，这个系统的假设是什么？”的一些问题？你和老师谈过吗？您是否与将要在地面上使用该机器人的人员交谈过？您与这些解决方案的服务对象之间的对话是怎样的？”</p><p>我真的很幸运，我能处在这样一个地方，我们将这种专业知识嵌入到问题制定阶段和项目制定阶段，贯穿整个开发流程。我也很高兴英特尔与负责任的 AI [咨询] 委员会一起建立了道德影响评估流程。因此，这是一个稳健而严格地构建开发管道的过程，整个英特尔和所有业务部门的团队 [使用]。这是一种注入专业知识的方式，不仅是社会科学家，还有负责任人工智能 [咨询] 委员会的每一个人，包括工程师和政策制定者以及法律界人士和标准界人士，并促进与这个多学科负责任人工智能的对话 [咨询] 通过提交道德影响评估与开发团队协商。</p><p>道德影响评估是我们将价值观付诸实践并确保围绕人类监督、人权、隐私、安全、保障以及多样性和包容性的价值观的一种方式——这些是我们确保将这些价值观融入其中的方式英特尔 BU [业务部门] 在整个组织中整合的工具。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>好的，我们有一个环节，我们向客人提出一系列五个快速问题。只需回答您想到的第一件事。第一：你最自豪的 AI 时刻是什么时候？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>哦，天哪。这是一个很好的问题。我真的很自豪能够向正在构建这些系统的这些工程师和数据科学家团队代表我们在场的技术人员的声音。由于英特尔构建的流程，我可以与正在构建计算机视觉、动作识别和 NLP 的工程团队坐在一起，选择围绕任务的语义框架中的短语，以及任务是如何构建的以及如何构建的他们可以得到认可，能够像我对技术人员进行的采访那样，在引入这项技术时询问他们的担忧，我们可以做些什么来确保他们的担忧得到解决，询问他们需要了解的透明度，他们需要什么来信任这个系统，所有这些都是为了加强人们正在做的工作。</p><p>事实上，我可以获取这些信息并将其始终如一地提供给工程师，并查看他们的响应速度。就像，“哦，好吧，我们可以建造这个，我们可以建造那个。如果我们将其构建到 UI 中会怎么样？如果我们将其内置到对话中会怎样？”这是一个令人难以置信的令人信服的过程，尤其是在来自学术界之后，我会写一篇论文，然后需要一年的时间才能发表。进而 …</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>哦，一年听起来很快。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>对。如果我幸运的话，需要一年的时间。我认为我最长的记录可能是 3.5 年才得以发表。我不知道。你的记录是什么？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>呃，10。所以……</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>十！</p><p><strong>山姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>是的。不过我们不要谈论它，因为我会很难过的。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>哦，不。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以你提到了人们的担忧。你对人工智能有什么担忧？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>嗯，当我开始与技术人员交谈时，他们最大的担忧之一是他们将被替换。</p><p>我说，“好吧，让我们谈谈吧。你觉得这是干什么的？”他们说：“我看到了新闻。我知道你正试图制造一个机器人来做我所做的事情，所以我想我正在训练我的替代者。”我想，“哦，不！这太可怕了。”我必须与我们的技术人员进行很多对话，我必须说，“那<em>不是</em>我们正在做的。我们不是要取代你。你是专家。我们需要你。事实上，我们需要你教系统，这样系统才能去帮助像你这样的人。因此，通过训练系统，您实际上是在帮助全球英特尔晶圆厂 [半导体制造厂] 的许多其他人，并且您确保他们以您希望获得帮助的方式获得帮助。”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>几年前我和 Shervin 参与的一些研究完全集中在你提到的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning">组织学习</a>方面——这是一种让每个人都能更快地学习和传播知识的方式。</p><p>您最喜欢不涉及技术的活动是什么？你的世界里有什么<em>不是</em>AI 的？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>嗯，最近发生了很多事情，有时似乎很难弄清楚什么是人工智能，什么不是。</p><p> [在]我的个人生活中，我做了很多烘焙工作。好久没做面包了。我经常做饭。我很幸运能和我的丈夫住在纽约市，所以我们进行了很多探索——事实上，只是走出去。这可能是最大的非人工智能活动，用我们自己的两只脚走到外面，用我们自己的眼睛环顾四周。那总是让人耳目一新。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>你年轻时想要的第一份职业是什么？你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白安妮沃特金斯：</strong>我想成为一名艺术家，这是一条颠簸曲折的道路。我在加州大学欧文分校读本科，我学的是视频艺术。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>你对人工智能未来最大的愿望是什么？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong> AI 可以做很多人类做不到的事情，但也有很多人类可以做而 AI 做不到的事情。我认为这是一个巨大的挑战，至少对我来说是这样，我希望在未来几年与我共事的人能够弄清楚这种平衡到底是什么，以及我们如何系统化“人们真正做的是什么”需要人工智能系统可以做的帮助吗？”但要真正透彻地了解人们在做什么以及他们是如何做的。</p><p> Now that the AI systems are becoming so advanced, but oftentimes in a lab or in a vacuum, as they mature into the real world, I think it&#39;s really exciting what they can do, but we&#39;re facing a lot of work in getting them there. And I think it&#39;s going to be other social scientists and multidisciplinary teams like the ones that we have at Intel all working together to make sure that these systems can really be deployed as solutions.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a good cap for the episode. Thanks for talking to us. I think one of the things that has come through [is], you&#39;re talking about projects and things you&#39;re working on, but you&#39;re also giving us a hint about what&#39;s going to happen in the future as we move off of the, let&#39;s say, tool-focused “Can we get the ML right? Can we get the model right? Can we get the data right?” You&#39;re talking a lot about what happens next, what happens once we check off some of those check marks — what are those checks? And I think a lot of people can learn from that. Thanks for taking the time to talk with us today.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh my gosh, it&#39;s been such a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, Shervin and I speak with David Hardoon from Aboitiz Data Innovation. We&#39;re once again talking about chemical engineering, so you won&#39;t want to miss this one.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>生成式人工智能对好莱坞和娱乐业的影响</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) 是巴布森学院信息技术与管理学院院长特聘教授、牛津大学赛德商学院客座教授，以及麻省理工学院数字经济计划研究员。他是<cite>《Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）的合著者。 Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) 是行业思想领袖、作家、创始人兼首席执行官，目前担任全球咨询公司 Wavestone 的数据战略创新研究员。他是<cite>《Fail Fast, Learn Faster: Lessons in Data-Driven Leadership in an Age of Disruption, Big Data, and AI》一书</cite>的作者（Wiley，2021 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Knowledge Workers]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[One of the many topics involving generative AI that is receiving a lot of attention is its potential effects on Hollywood and the entertainment industry. It’s an obvious concern because generative AI can create the types of outputs that the industry uses — text (in the form of stories, scripts, ad copy, and reviews), marketing [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Davenport-Bean-Hollywood-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>涉及生成式 AI 的众多话题中受到广泛关注的话题之一是它对好莱坞和娱乐业的潜在影响。这是一个明显的问题，因为生成式 AI 可以创建行业使用的输出类型——文本（以故事、脚本、广告文案和评论的形式）、营销活动以及动态和静态图像。该行业的各个部门都面临着经济压力，这增加了对生产力和更便宜的“产品”的需求。当前娱乐的很大一部分是过去内容的衍生品，这使得它非常适合基于……过去内容进行训练的生成技术。</p><p>生成式 AI 创造的娱乐还处于早期阶段，但很明显，大事正在发生。 <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-hollywood-intellectual-property-spongebob-81fd5d15"><cite>《华尔街日报》</cite>最近的一篇文章</a>指出，广泛使用的人工智能工具可以建议故事情节、人物弧线和对话；它甚至包括一个交互式模块，让读者可以亲身体验 ChatGPT 在给出一些提示时如何轻松编写基本脚本。文章还提出了有关图像知识产权的问题：“如果用户提示 AI 工具构建一个受海绵宝宝影响的新角色，原始创作者是否必须授予许可？谁拥有它？新作品本身可以受版权保护吗？”</p><p></p><p>生成式 AI 被用于<a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/05/05/runway-generative-ai-chatgpt-video">制作 2022 年的电影<cite>Everything Everywhere All On Once</cite></a> ， <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/oscars-2023-everything-everywhere-all-at-once-most-awards/">我们知道结果如何</a>。 Tom 最近写了一篇关于使用生成式 AI 来创建<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2023/03/13/cuebric-generative-ai-comes-to-hollywood/">电影和电视背景图像的</a>文章。已经有可以创建视频的生成 AI 系统，尽管它们很短且相对原始。 AI 正被用于提供关于<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/democratizing-data-in-hollywood-jumpcuts-kartik-hosanagar/">不寻常的故事情节将如何吸引观众的</a>数据驱动预测。</p><p>那么，这对行业意味着什么？正如<a href="https://variety.com/vip-special-reports/generative-ai-entertainment-a-special-report-1235564989/">Variety Intelligence Platform 的一份新报告</a>所暗示的那样，这个问题有许多不同的组成部分。 5 月，美国作家协会 (WGA) 举行罢工，主要是针对电影和电视编剧<a href="https://time.com/6277158/writers-strike-ai-wga-screenwriting/">从流媒体服务节目中获得的收入</a>，但它也要求制作公司“<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/29/business/media/writers-guild-hollywood-ai-chatgpt.html">规范使用人工智能或类似技术制作的材料</a>。”由于关于该技术何时以及如何发生的事情存在太多不确定性，因此我们就该主题与两位专家进行了交谈。两者都位于 - 毫不奇怪 - 洛杉矶，并且都参与了南加州大学 (USC) 的中心。然而，他们并不一起工作，而且他们对这项技术有着截然不同的方法。</p><p></p><h3>坚决反对生成式人工智能</h3><p>Jonathan Taplin 是南加州大学<a href="https://www.annenberglab.com/">Annenberg 创新实验室</a>的名誉主任。他在娱乐行业拥有很长的职业生涯，之前曾担任音乐家的巡回演出经理，包括鲍勃迪伦和乐队。此外，他还是电影制片人、银行家和作家。他的最新著作<a href="https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/jonathan-taplin/the-end-of-reality/9781541703155/?lens=publicaffairs"><cite>《现实的终结：四位亿万富翁如何推销元宇宙、火星和加密货币的幻想未来》</cite></a>将于 9 月发行。正如您可能从标题中推断的那样，他不喜欢大型科技公司的生成式 AI 工具是如何开发或发布的。</p><p> “他们训练模型的方式是吸收互联网上的所有内容，不考虑版权，”Taplin 告诉我们。 “谷歌有一个音乐生成 AI 训练过 YouTube 上的每个音频文件。你可以发出类似“给我写一首听起来像泰勒·斯威夫特、悲伤的结局、快节奏的歌曲”这样的提示，然后生成的歌曲听起来有点像她。有人可以免费将其包含在视频游戏或电影中的酒吧场景中。”他补充说，生成式人工智能可以对工作室拥有的视频内容进行同样的再利用。</p><p> Taplin 主要担心的是，生成式 AI 将取代人类作家、艺术家、摄影师以及艺术和娱乐行业的其他创意专业人士所做的部分工作。他还认为，这将加剧已经使电影和电视行业陷入困境的问题。 “电影最大的问题是公式太多。缺乏原创性，这就是该行业表现不佳的原因，”他说。他补充说，生成式 AI 只能生成更多公式化的内容，并且会使可预测性更差。 “娱乐依赖于新创意，而这项技术无法产生新创意，”塔普林补充道。</p><p>他说，他担心生成式 AI 会继续减少可以在各自领域谋生的表演者的数量。大部分娱乐收入已经流向了极少数艺术家。这就是<a href="https://www.digitalmusicnews.com/2014/03/05/toponepercent/">音乐家的现实</a>，尤其是在<a href="https://themusicnetwork.com/few-artists-generate-most-streams/">流媒体服务</a>方面，并且在好莱坞大片中少数几位主要演员所产生的巨额<a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/655480/all-time-top-grossing-actors-box-office/">票房收入</a>中也得到了回应。塔普林说，当你进入“算法经济”时，“算法会缩小漏斗，少数人会获得巨额薪水。”他希望集体许可制度——类似于音乐采样的制度——能够在艺术家的内容被用于训练生成人工智能时保护他们。</p><h3>拥抱生成式人工智能，但有一些顾虑</h3><p>Yves Bergquist 是南加州大学<a href="https://www.etcenter.org/">娱乐技术中心</a>媒体项目人工智能和神经科学的主任，该中心由好莱坞电影公司资助。你可以猜到，他对生成式 AI 的看法可能比 Taplin 的要好得多。是的，尽管他说他确实对人工智能对媒体和娱乐业的潜在影响有些担忧：“这是一种完全革命性的技术”，其特点是错误信息和“一些疯狂”。</p><p>我们问 Bergquist 电影制片厂是否会接受生成式 AI。他说，他们中的一部分人已经在这样做了。 “工作室中的一些团队精通技术，例如首席技术官和所有视觉效果艺术家和技术人员。他们非常成熟，并且已经在与生成人工智能公司合作。制片厂在电影中做了很多后期制作工作——尤其是在动画中——而且降低成本的压力很大。后期制作公司拥有软件开发文化，因此他们将拥抱生成式人工智能。”</p><p>他还相信，许多制作公司会接受这项技术，因为他们已经在大型 LED 屏幕上拍摄，并且需要生成图像。 Bergquist 表示，他预计提供虚拟演员和语音合成的工具将被在 TikTok 或 YouTube 上发布作品的短片创作者以及视频游戏制作人最积极地采用。 “流媒体频道、数字广告、游戏——这就是现在孩子们看的东西，”他指出。 “媒体行业不再垄断娱乐。”硬件（例如相机）制造商也在尝试生成相机内视觉效果。</p><p></p><p> Bergquist 观察到，传统电影制片厂的业务部门有时更不愿意接受人工智能，这仅仅是因为他们没有相同类型的数据或软件文化。 “它正被强加给尚未准备好的组织和人员，”他说。即使是像 Netflix 和 Prime Video 这样的新流媒体工作室，在他们的 AI 之旅中也经历过很多成长的痛苦。</p><p> Bergquist 说，在 5 月 WGA 罢工开始之前，许多编剧告诉他，他们将 ChatGPT 之类的东西视为“伟大的创意辅助工具”，但不会取代人类作家。 “它善于集思广益，但只会输出一般的内容，”伯格奎斯特断言。 “它远不具备剧本开发所需的符号抽象能力，也无法输出具有叙事结构和人物弧线的剧本。”至少不是现在。未来具有更高智能水平的语言模型和人工智能的新范式可能能够做到这一点。</p><p></p><p> Bergquist 认为生成式 AI 不仅会对娱乐产生巨大影响，也会对教育产生巨大影响。他认为，包括南加州大学电影艺术学院在内的学校需要迅速加强教学，以跟上几乎每周发布的新生成人工智能工具的热潮。 Bergquist 正在为电影和电视工程师协会准备有关技术的课程，这是一个代表媒体技术专家的组织。</p><h3>两位专家都对吗？</h3><p>尽管 Taplin 和 Bergquist 似乎对生成式 AI 的看法截然不同，但他们对其影响的看法可能都是正确的。经济压力可能会诱使该行业（至少是其中的某些部门）采用这些新工具。生成式人工智能将导致制作和后期制作、发行和知识产权所有权发生巨大变化。这项技术可能对传统艺术家和雇用他们的公司不利，但它可能会在未来几年内导致该行业发生重大变化——希望有的变好，有的变坏。也许唯一纯粹的好消息是，两位专家都不认为人类会很快被完全取代。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>回顾工作/23：大转变</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:09:56 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Career Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Download the Event Summary Download (PDF) The pandemic irrevocably changed the how, why, and where of work. At Work/23: The Big Shift, a half-day summit held May 4, 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review brought together company executives and academic experts in talent management, hybrid work, employee well-being, and workplace culture. Together, they explained how organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"><strong>下载活动摘要</strong></h5><p class="is-button"><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cb2792f94c.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">下载 (PDF)</a></p></aside><p>大流行不可逆转地改变了工作的方式、原因和地点。 At Work/23：大转变是 2023 年 5 月 4 日举行的为期半天的峰会， <cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>汇集了公司高管和人才管理、混合工作、员工福利和工作场所文化方面的学术专家。他们一起解释了组织如何在这个变化的世界中转向创新、提高生产力并实现平衡。</p><p> <cite>MIT SMR</cite>主编 Abbie Lundberg 和编辑总监 Elizabeth Heichler 共同主持了此次活动。</p><p> Work/23 包括以下主题和演讲者：</p><h4 class="work23-title" id="nalbantian">消除职业障碍以获得更公平的结果</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Haig R. Nalbantian，劳动力科学研究所</h5><p>即使是专门致力于促进多样性、公平性和包容性 (DEI) 的组织也难以以可持续的方式提高代表性。 Nalbantian 概述了公司解决女性和有色人种继续面临的障碍的方法——这些障碍通常是由于情境因素造成的，例如人们所扮演的角色或他们向谁报告。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">部分时间戳：1:02</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="berwick">基于技能的人才实践的原因、内容和方式</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Beth Berwick，人生的毕业典礼</h5><p>现在比以往任何时候都更多的工作需要四年制大学学位，包括许多过去从未做过的工作。但该标准排除了 64% 的人口——包括 76% 的美国黑人和 80% 的拉丁美洲人。 Berwick 是呼吁取消学位要求的人之一。她解释了组织如何根据他们需要的技能来有效地招聘。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">段时间戳：33:24</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="smith">获取人才的新世界</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">迈克·史密斯，任仕达企业； David Kiron，<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR</cite></h5><p>公司正在改变他们处理和应用技术以找到他们需要的人的方式。<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR</cite>的 Kiron 和我们的合作伙伴的首席执行官讨论了创新组织如何设计自己的人才库、建立自己的人才品牌以及将 DEI 计划扩展到自己的边界之外。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">部分时间戳：54:44</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="dervin">灵活<em>有效</em>：混合工作场所的领导力策略</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Julie Dervin，Atlassian； Brian Elliott，未来论坛； N. Sharon Hill，乔治华盛顿大学商学院； Abbie Lundberg，<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR</cite></h5><p>在混合工作场所拥有健康的工作场所文化和高绩效是可能的；它只需要一种深思熟虑的管理方法。本次会议的演讲者扩展了他们的研究和配置混合工作安排的实际经验，并讨论了如何实现员工自主权和组织协调的正确组合。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">部分时间戳：1:07:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="kellerman">在新的工作世界中茁壮成长</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">加布里埃拉·罗森·凯勒曼，BetterUp；宾夕法尼亚大学的 Martin Seligman；<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR 的</cite>伊丽莎白·海克勒 (Elizabeth Heichler)</h5><p>对于认识到压力正在驱逐有才能的员工的领导者来说，员工福利是一个紧迫的问题。与人合着了<cite>Tomorrowmind</cite>一书的演讲者详细介绍了帮助个人在充满压力的工作环境中蓬勃发展的技能，包括<em>前景</em>——想象我们的选择、规划未来和恢复我们的代理权的能力。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">段时间戳：1:42:29</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="gigliotti">如何为所有人提供职业发展</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Tony Gigliotti，UPMC； Pernod Ricard 北美的 Lani Montoya； George Westerman，麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院</h5><p>本次会议的发言人概述了具有前瞻性的公司如何帮助所有员工——而不仅仅是少数被选中的员工——规划有回报的职业道路。他们解释说，公司正在通过提供学习和实践新技能的方法以及提供丰富的反馈来做到这一点。公司还使途径可见，展示与员工当前级别及更高级别的机会。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">段时间戳：2:13:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="altman">劳动力生态系统的综合方法</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">伊丽莎白·J·奥特曼，麻省大学洛厄尔分校； David Kiron，<cite>麻省理工学院 SMR</cite></h5><p>演讲者的研究发表在<cite>《劳动力生态系统》</cite>一书中，发现大多数领导者认为他们的劳动力比全职员工更广泛，包括临时工、专业服务公司，甚至包括客户服务聊天机器人等技术。 Altman 和 Kiron 解释了如何协调和成功管理扩大后的员工队伍。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">段时间戳：2:49:49</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="barnes">四天工作周：如何在您的组织中发挥作用</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Andrew Barnes，全球 4 天周</h5><p>巴恩斯在世界上最大的试验中坐在前排，试验将每周工作时间从 5 天缩减到 4 天会发生什么。这始于他自己公司的一项实验，他说，“只要我们获得 100% 的产出，我们就支付 100% 的收入，80% 的时间。”他创办了一家非营利组织，以帮助其他公司自己尝试，现在拥有来自 91 个参与组织的数据。</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp">段时间戳：3:14:02 </h6><p></p><style>.work23-title {margin-bottom:0!important;}.work23-speaker {margin-top:0!important;}.work23-timestamp {margin-bottom:25px!important;color: #005b9c!important;text-transform: uppercase;letter-spacing: 1px!important;font-size: 1.4rem!important;margin-bottom:25px!important;}</style> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>什么，我担心？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Elizabeth Heichler ( <a href="https://twitter.com/eheichler">@eheichler</a> ) 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>杂志的执行编辑。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades Call me shortsighted, but I am not losing sleep over the prospect of a supercharged AI gaining consciousness and waging war on humans. What does keep me up at night is that humans are already wielding the power of artificial intelligence to control, exploit, discriminate against, misinform, and manipulate other humans. Tools that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-Edit-Letter-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><p>说我目光短浅，但我并没有因为超级人工智能获得意识并对人类发动战争的前景而失眠。</p><p>让我夜不能寐的是，人类已经在运用人工智能的力量来控制、利用、歧视、误导和操纵其他人。可以帮助我们解决复杂和棘手问题的工具也可以被网络犯罪分子使用，或者赋予专制政府前所未有的权力来监视和指导其公民的生活。我们可以建立模型来开发新的、更可持续的材料或重要的新药——我们可以建立模型，将有偏见的决策嵌入到系统和流程中，然后让个人陷入困境。</p><p></p><p>换句话说，AI 已经让我们担心了很多。我们不应该被反乌托邦的狂热梦想分散注意力，这些梦想会误导我们对当今风险的注意力。</p><p>最近出现的 ChatGPT 和类似的大型语言模型引起了更广泛的公众意识，这提高了人们对 AI 的潜在好处和危险的普遍兴趣。在我写这篇文章的前几天，人工智能领域的巨人 Geoffrey Hinton 辞去了他在谷歌的职位，他告诉<cite>纽约时报</cite>，他想自由地谈论生成人工智能的风险. “很难看出你如何才能阻止坏人利用它来做坏事，”他告诉该报。</p><p>那里确实是我们应该关注的地方。纵观人类历史，新技术已被用于推动文明进步，但它们也被不良行为者武器化。这次的不同之处在于，不仅这项技术极其复杂，而且大多数人都难以理解——潜在的结果也是如此。</p><p>如果我们希望 AI 利大于弊，那么我们所有人都必须准备好攀登一条陡峭的学习曲线。对这些工具的可能用途的兴奋必须通过关于如何做出自动化决策、如何训练人工智能系统以及因此产生了哪些假设和偏见的好问题来缓和。企业领导者尤其需要意识到声誉和物质风险和价值破坏的可能性，因为它们是利用人工智能的机会。</p><p></p><p>虽然人工智能的发展可能会继续以任何公开信都无法阻止的惊人速度进行，但我们其他人应该谨慎行事。在“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dont-get-distracted-by-the-hype-around-generative-ai/">不要被围绕生成式 AI 的炒作分散注意力</a>”中，Lee Vinsel 提醒我们，技术泡沫伴随着大量噪音。我们需要放下对错失恐惧症 (FOMO) 的恐惧，采取审慎、理性的方法来评估新兴技术。</p><p>在<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite> ，我们将继续为商业领袖提供头脑清醒的决策制定和明智的实验所需的研究和情报。我们持续<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">关注负责任的 AI 实践</a>，由牛津大学的客座编辑 Elizabeth Renieris 领导，这是该承诺的关键部分。</p><p>我们都是人工智能革命的利益相关者。让我们承担起这一责任，并努力确保好人多于坏人。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>我们的 2023 年夏季刊指南</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Algorithms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here’s How to Keep Them on Track. Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi Key Insight: When algorithms aren’t updated to account for changes in the environment, they deliver poor-quality predictions. Top Takeaways: AI models designed to dynamically account for new circumstances don’t always do so effectively. This [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-EXECSUM-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="no-underline">预测模型可能会失去情节。以下是如何让他们走上正轨。</a></h4><h6> Vern L. Glaser、Omid Omidvar 和 Mehdi Safavi</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>当算法未更新以应对环境变化时，它们会提供低质量的预测。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>旨在动态解释新情况的 AI 模型并不总是有效。这种情况称为<em>算法惯性</em>，可能会导致指导不力和决策错误。作者通过调查信用评级机构穆迪及其在 2008 年金融危机前几年使用算法模型对抵押贷款支持证券进行评级的情况，探讨了算法惯性的原因和后果。他们发现，算法惯性最重要的影响因素是隐藏的假设、表面的重塑、对未知未来的模拟和专门的划分。公开数据和假设，以及定期重新设计算法例程，是消除这种惰性的两个关键做法。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="no-underline">风险情报和有弹性的公司</a></h4><h6>Ananya Sheth 和 Joseph V. Sinfield</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>采取更合乎逻辑的风险管理方法可以帮助领导者在混乱和不确定的情况下维持价值创造。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>在当今相互关联的世界中，构建大型复杂企业的弹性至关重要。风险情报——严格解释风险及其对公司造成的后果或机会的磨练能力——通过帮助领导者识别和管理随着时间的推移和不断变化的业务对公司价值交换系统的广泛潜在威胁，支持组织的弹性上下文。为加强组织的风险情报，领导者应系统地对风险事件进行分类和解释，区分不确定性并减少其影响，并构建企业风险网络并将其置于情境中。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="no-underline">专业服务公司如何避免颠覆</a></h4><h6>朱利安·伯金肖和大卫·兰斯菲尔德</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>长寿的专业服务公司为其他试图在动荡的市场中生存下来的企业提供了经验教训。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>十年前，大型专业服务公司似乎处于以技术为动力的新竞争对手的十字准线，但许多公司保持甚至巩固了自己的地位。这些咨询巨头、顶级律师事务所和其他机构在诊断潜在中断的不同原因并做出相应响应的能力中发现了弹性。他们在解决客户最具挑战性的问题以及在高影响、大规模、高风险情况下提供建议和合规性方面加倍发挥传统优势——并为此收取额外费用。他们学会了务实地承认自己的基本面是健全的，同时对新兴技术和竞争对手抱有一丝偏执的怀疑。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="no-underline">未能扩大规模背后缺失的纪律</a></h4><h6>安迪·宾斯和克里斯汀·格里芬</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>为新企业开发扩展路径既是一门艺术，也是一门科学，但领导者可以利用它来学习和迭代。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>公司在开发新业务计划方面进行了大量投资，但很少有人遵循严格的途径来广泛实施这些计划。虽然 80% 的公司声称构思和孵化新企业，但只有 16% 的公司成功地扩大了规模。扩展路径需要明确的雄心壮志等于机会的规模；一套合理的战略选择，用于确定实现这一目标所需的资产；就如何获得这些资产进行聪明的头脑风暴；以开放的态度引入新的领导者以支持不断扩大的活动范围；为不可避免的高风险时刻做好准备，此时决策需要做出即使并非不可能也难以逆转的承诺。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="no-underline">帮助神经分歧的员工取得成功</a></h4><h6>Emily R. Russo、Dana L. Ott 和 Miriam Moeller</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>公司可以通过制定具有神经包容性的招聘策略和工作环境来扩大人才库。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>在工作场所的招聘、管理和保留方面，有神经系统差异的人，尤其是自闭症谱系的人，经常被雇主低估，这对每个人都不利。将神经多样性纳入有关工作场所多样性、公平性和包容性的更广泛对话很重要，不仅因为这是公平的事情，而且因为神经分歧的个人可以做出有价值的贡献。创建一个神经包容性组织需要有利于神经分歧员工和更广泛员工队伍的特定培训和发展工作。管理人员是这些项目取得成功的关键，需要接受有关如何支持神经分歧员工的培训。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="no-underline">您的财务办公室的数字化成熟度如何？</a></h4><h6>克里斯托夫·斯托海森</h6><p><strong>重要见解：</strong>许多财务办公室都停留在传统的运营角色中，无法从高级分析中受益。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>各行各业的财务领导者都在尝试整合数据和分析以改善运营，但并非所有 CFO 都破解了密码。特别是，许多人没有利用新机器学习应用程序的前景。能够挑战通常保守、谨慎的文化并设法成功部署高级分析的首席财务官可以提供更多实时见解，减少人为错误和偏见，并加快流程和决策制定。更重要的是，虽然更多的传统财务领导者通常会保护他们拥有的数据，但那些采用高级分析的人（作者称之为<em>数字财务领导者</em>）成为了跨公司孤岛实现数据民主化的强烈倡导者。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="no-underline">兑现卓越</a></h4><h6>罗伯特·D·奥斯汀、罗伯特·H·海耶斯和理查德·L·诺兰</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>太多的领导者从事<em>绩效黑客活动</em>——提供特定指标以提供有效领导的表象，但没有产生真正的绩效。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>最近的破坏性事件，如欧洲的流行病和战争，暴露了因短视的领导决策而削弱的企业。对西南航空公司、波音和通用电气的分析着眼于为什么成功的公司会牺牲他们多年来建立的卓越业务——包括作为其基础的价值观和关系——以换取短期的财务收益，例如成本削减和股价上涨最终损害利益相关者。作者分享了表明领导者正在参与实践的典型警告标志。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="no-underline">打开职业公平的快速通道</a></h4><h6>黑格·R·纳尔班提安</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>了解推动员工晋升的因素可以帮助管理者更公平地定位女性和有色人种以获得晋升。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>新研究表明，与员工的知识、能力或行为无关的因素对职业发展有巨大影响。向高绩效人员报告、担任主管等职业加速器角色以及不利用灵活的工作选择等情况都对晋升和加薪起到了主导作用。绩效评级的差异也会产生连锁效应，对有色人种产生不利影响：在作者的研究中，大多数公司的有色人种获得高绩效评级的可能性降低了 50%。由于评级往往会持续存在，一年的高评级预示着下一年的高评级的可能性，从一开始就被拒之门外会严重阻碍职业发展。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="no-underline">工作中同伴支持的不平等回报</a></h4><h6>南希·贝姆和康斯坦斯·努南·哈德利</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>工作满意度部分来自人们对他们的组织认可和重视他们为同事提供的社会支持的感觉。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>员工之间的支持行为可以提高敬业度和生产力，但研究表明，男性从这种努力中获得的收益比女性多。社会支持包括情感帮助、增强自尊、社会陪伴、信息或建议以及工具性帮助。在作者的研究中，与男性相比，更多的女性将精力集中在倾听、表现出个人兴趣和赞美同事上，而男性则报告说更频繁地提供职业建议。尽管男性表示他们提供的社会支持总体上比女性少，但他们获得了更高水平的组织鼓励、奖励和工作满意度。管理者可以通过让看不见的东西变得可见和有价值来鼓励更公平的同行文化——明确哪些行为很重要，同时修改绩效管理系统。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="no-underline">超越实验孤岛，走向人工智能无处不在</a></h4><h6>Amit Joshi、Ivy Buche 和 Miguel Paredes Sadler</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>从孤立的实验开始人工智能工作可能是有意义的，但需要新的、全公司范围的结构来扩展它们并获得更广泛的利益。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>人工智能通常在组织内的孤立实验中扎根，许多公司因为难以超越这些试点而在 AI 之旅中停滞不前。扩展技术需要不同类型的正式结构：作者发现，人工智能项目通常以实验孤岛开始，然后围绕企业<em>卓越中心</em>聚集在一起。然后，一小部分人转向建立在知识、系统、流程和工具的集中基础以及分散的嵌入式功能之上的复杂的<em>专业知识联合</em>模型。有 AI 雄心的企业如果打算发挥该技术的潜力，就需要准备好在启动阶段进行两次结构性飞跃。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="no-underline">管理您的劳动力生态系统，而不仅仅是您的员工</a></h4><h6>伊丽莎白·J·奥特曼、大卫·基隆、杰夫·施瓦茨和罗宾·琼斯</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>需要新的组织结构来协调包括大量外部员工和合作伙伴在内的劳动力生态系统。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>大多数高管同意“劳动力”的概念正在重新定义。他们说它比组织的全职员工更广泛，而是包括承包商、临时工、服务提供商甚至技术的生态系统。这些网络需要创新的管理实践，因为分层的、命令和控制的领导不适合跨越内部和外部边界的劳动力。在开发新实践时，领导者必须解决三类问题：结构设计（与劳动分工、目标和激励有关）、政治（与资源、权力和地位有关）和文化（影响个人对身份的寻求）和意义）。有意识地协调一个考虑所有参与者的视角，可以更细致地了解组织及其合作伙伴如何合作以实现其战略目标。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><p></p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>专业服务公司如何避免颠覆</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:23:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Julian Birkinshaw and David Lancefield. <p>朱利安·伯金肖 (Julian Birkinshaw) 是伦敦商学院战略学教授，兼任副院长。大卫·兰斯菲尔德 (David Lancefield) 是 CEO 催化剂、战略家和教练，曾任普华永道高级合伙人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors conducted in-depth interviews with more than 25 senior professionals in consultancies and law firms. They also reviewed case studies of a dozen would-be disrupters and carried out an extensive review of the literature. Professional services firms have been threatened with disruption for a long time. In 2015, Richard and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Birkinshaw_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者对超过 25 位咨询公司和律师事务所的高级专业人士进行了深入访谈。</li><li>他们还回顾了十几个潜在颠覆者的案例研究，并对文献进行了广泛的回顾。</li></ul></aside><p>专业服务公司长期以来一直面临中断的威胁。 2015 年，Richard 和 Daniel Susskind 预见到技术将导致“对传统有血有肉的专业人士的需求稳步下降”，而最近，CB Insights 表示“结构性破坏正在冲击管理咨询”。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>更早之前，克莱顿·克里斯滕森 (Clayton Christensen) 及其同事警告说：“虽然我们无法预测咨询行业颠覆的确切进展，但我们可以非常有信心地说，无论其速度如何，一些现任者都会措手不及。” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2个</a></p><p>但事情并没有像预期的那样发展。在咨询和法律领域，成熟的公司一如既往地具有影响力和盈利能力。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>许多潜在的破坏者已经出现。有些失败了，有些获得了强大的利基地位，但没有人挑战——更不用说推翻——现有秩序了。大多数老牌领导者都使用了广泛的战略和策略来快速适应威胁。</p><p></p><p>与许多成熟行业的情况一样，专业服务市场由一小部分可清楚识别的顶端群体和大量在其影子下运营的低端公司主导。咨询的巨头包括麦肯锡、波士顿咨询集团和贝恩；科技公司 Accenture 和 Capgemini；以及四大会计师事务所安永、德勤、毕马威和普华永道。在法律领域，顶级律师事务所包括五家总部位于伦敦的律师事务所，非正式地称为“魔圈”——年利达律师事务所、高伟绅律师事务所、富而德律师事务所、安理国际律师事务所和斯劳特梅律师事务所——以及凯易律师事务所、瑞生律师事务所和欧华律师事务所。</p><p>这些公司为何如此有韧性？我们的研究包括对 25 位高管的访谈以及对十几个潜在颠覆者的案例研究的回顾，揭示了许多因素在起作用。最有效的公司的区别在于它们有能力诊断潜在的破坏原因并做出相应的反应。</p><p>我们将<em>行业颠覆</em>定义为对既定秩序的颠覆，现有企业输给新的竞争对手。正如 Joshua Gans 所说，当现有公司对客户的需求存在盲点（需求方效应），或者当新技术使现有公司的现有能力过时（供应方效应）时，就会发生颠覆——或者是以下因素的组合他们俩。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> （参见“咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁</h4><p class="caption">专业服务公司在需求和供应方面都面临着威胁。</p><p class="caption">随着在职者交付的能力对客户的价值下降，供应方中断会增加。需求方中断随着客户行为变化的增加而增加。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Birkinshaw-Figure.png" alt="咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>由于每种情况都需要自己的应对措施，因此了解供需双方影响的动态可以使任何部门的高管更容易识别潜在的破坏者并将其拒之门外。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5个</a></p><h3>需求方和供应方的威胁</h3><p>根据我们的研究，我们将人工智能技术确定为最大的供应方风险，威胁要接管专业人士传统上视为自己的工作。在需求方面，威胁来自客户寻求更好地控制他们购买和使用专业服务的方式。还有其他潜在的颠覆者同时从供需双方挑战现有企业。与此同时，新的精品和专业公司已经出现，以满足利润丰厚的业务领域的特定客户需求，尽管它们很少真正具有颠覆性。下面，我们将详细介绍每个潜在威胁。</p><p><strong>人工智能破坏了商业模式。</strong> 2022 年 11 月推出的生成式 AI 加速了专业服务工作许多方面的持续转型，从而提高了准确性并显着节省了成本。</p><p>在律师事务所，人工智能工具扫描法律文件并审查合同。基于人工智能的服务公司，如 Kira Systems、Clio、Reveal-Brainspace、iManage 和汤森路透，在发现、尽职调查以及合同管理和审查方面提供帮助。 97% 的大型律师事务所使用汤森路透的服务。</p><p>这些公司并不将自己定位为律师事务所的竞争对手，但随着它们规模的扩大和技术能力的增强，它们可能会开始破坏这些公司的商业模式。例如，Clio 的法律软件可以对索赔进行电子发现，甚至可以通过扫描先例案例进行诉讼分析，从而有可能减少公司可以向客户收取的计费小时数。</p><p>在咨询中，人工智能可以帮助专业服务公司发现新的关系、识别客户行为模式并突出节省成本的机会，从而提供额外的价值。 “与一个比其他任何人都更了解这个行业的团队一起出现已经不够好了，”一位四大咨询合伙人说。 “你还需要一个数据集或算法来提供额外的价值来源。”</p><p>但人工智能也可以成为强大的破坏者。 Palantir Technologies 开始使用 AI 来检测欺诈，后来扩展到应用最先进的机器学习来解决各种政府和私人客户的问题。它支持政府监督的工作引起了争议，但其预测分析帮助一家大型汽车供应商在其工程和制造职能方面取得了巨大的效率提升。这样的结果代表了咨询公司可以提供的洞察力的严谨性和质量的重大进步。</p><p>老牌公司已经通过收购和内部开发建立自己的人工智能能力来应对威胁。自 2013 年以来，麦肯锡收购了 12 家主要是小型人工智能公司，其中包括总部位于英国的 QuantumBlack，该公司使用先进的数据分析来提高组织绩效。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>在法律方面，总部位于旧金山的 DLA Piper 开发了 Aiscension，这是一种监控合规风险的人工智能产品。保险律师事务所 Kennedys 创建了 Kennedys IQ 衍生产品，它使用人工智能来评估医学证据并建议赔偿金额。</p><p>这些收购和合作伙伴关系提供的不仅仅是新功能；他们可以扩大他们的公司可以为客户处理的问题的范围。</p><p>现任者也在加强他们作为高接触可信顾问的作用，这是人工智能无法复制的。几家大型咨询公司通过投资体验中心扩大了他们的产品范围——客户和顾问在物理和虚拟环境中使用设计思维和其他创造性技术来设想可能的未来。在过去五年中，IBM、德勤、埃森哲和其他公司收购了 200 多家创意机构来帮助开发这些中心。</p><p><strong>客户控制：拆分服务。</strong>最深远的需求方威胁是分拆，因为越来越精明的客户正在寻找降低成本的方法，并对他们与服务公司的关系施加更大的影响。这可能意味着回收以前由外部公司处理的活动或求助于专家而不是大型专业公司的广泛服务。这两种选择都可以帮助客户建立内部能力，并对业务成果承担更大的责任。但分拆威胁到现有公司的杠杆模式，因为它剥夺了通常分配给许多初级和低薪通才的工作。</p><p>在法律上，替代法律服务提供商 (ALSP) 的出现证明了这种需求方威胁。 ALSP 本身并不是律师事务所，但它们以较低的成本提供广泛的法律服务，例如文件审查或合同管理。 2017 年，位于弗吉尼亚州的 IT 服务公司 DXC Technology 将其几乎全部法律职能外包给了位于堪萨斯州欧弗兰帕克的 ALSP UnitedLex。 DXC 将 150 名内部律师转移到 UnitedLex，只保留了少数高级专业人员。虽然外包内部法律部门并不少见，但律师事务所认为这是一个巨大的威胁，因为这是当时同类交易中最大的交易，而且它涉及 ALSP，可以提供更低的成本结构。</p><p>咨询网络的兴起（例如总部位于伦敦的 Eden McCallum）和在线平台（例如总部位于纽约的 Gerson Lehrman Group）也面临着类似的挑战。这些公司在逐个项目的基础上为客户匹配顾问，绕过大公司。总部位于伦敦的 Kubrick Group 与公司签订合同，提供数据科学家和技术专家团队，客户稍后可以聘用他们。</p><p>这种安排让客户有责任定义其问题并整合工作团队——传统上由大型咨询公司处理的事情。但是除了最大和最复杂的项目外，它们消除了雇用大公司的需要。如果没有现任者更高的管理费用，费用就会低得多。</p><p>客户也在改变商业安排，越来越多地要求基于结果的交易，要求顾问证明他们对预期结果直接负责，例如成本降低 5%。因为对于涉及顾问影响之外的因素（例如收入增长）的项目，这可能更难做到，所以大多数公司只有在他们有信心为预期结果做出贡献时才会同意基于结果的交易。</p><p>现有公司正在以多种方式应对这些需求方的挑战。律师事务所已经成立了自己的 ALSP；总部位于伦敦的 Allen &amp; Overy 于 2013 年创建了 Peerpoint，这是一个独立的业务，拥有 350 名主要是自由职业的律师和 5300 万英镑（6400 万美元）的收入。在咨询方面，德勤创建了一个名为 Pixel 的部门，将客户问题分解成各个组成部分，然后使用众包平台寻找合适的专家来处理每个部分。</p><p>大公司也在加倍发挥其传统优势：解决客户最大和最具挑战性的问题。他们的价值来自他们在高影响、大规模、高风险情况下提供建议和合规的能力，并且他们可以为服务收取额外费用。 “我们做的是心脏直视手术，而不是提供 [全科医生] 服务，”一位资深律师说。</p><p><strong>精品店和专家在市场关注中找到优势。</strong>随着前顶级合作伙伴建立自己的精品店或风险投资公司支持新的创业公司，专业服务领域不断出现新的竞争对手。成功的公司在特定的利基市场占据了市场份额，但很少引起顶级公司的关注。它们对需求或供应方造成的干扰有限，它们只是反映了市场的异质性和复杂性。</p><p>在咨询方面，总部位于伦敦的 Baringa 通过专注于能源行业、确定可再生能源等热门话题并聘请使用情景建模来预测未来能源价格的专家，实现了快速发展。总部位于纽约的 AlixPartners 专注于扭亏为盈、诉讼支持和转型。两家公司都有 1,000 多名员工。法律行业见证了专家的快速成长，例如美国的 Caldwell Intellectual Property Law 和英国和新加坡的争议专家 Mishcon de Reya。这些公司的成功表明，深厚的专业知识可以如何创造一个可以抵御基础广泛的竞争对手的可防御的利基市场。</p><p>大公司并不将这些小企业视为直接威胁，而且常常完全忽视它们。 “他们不在我们与 C-suite 的工作中，”伦敦一家大型律师事务所的合伙人说。尽管如此，它们仍可以帮助现任者保持警惕。</p><p>其一，它们为不断变化的市场提供了一个窗口，通常会促使老牌公司进入它们原本可能被忽视的业务领域。例如，德勤针对专业精品公司的出现推出了数字业务。贝恩创建并剥离了 The Bridgespan Group，以专注于非营利组织。</p><p>专业公司还可以暴露顶级公司工作方式中需要注意的弱点。例如，专注于电信、媒体和技术领域的全球最大战略咨询公司 Altman Solon 吸引了最高管理层的关注，这在很大程度上是因为整个公司由在这些领域具有深厚专业知识的专家组成，这与许多填补初级职位的大公司不同有很多聪明的多面手。因此，它已经跟上了其运营所在行业的步伐，因此能够更好地快速制定客户特定的战略。</p><p><strong>潜在的破坏者会带来供需双方的风险。</strong>现任者的噩梦场景是同时影响供需双方的中断。这最终就是杀死柯达和宝丽来的原因：数字技术改变了图像的创建方式和消费方式，让现任者没有任何价值可以依靠。摄影行业的幸存者，如富士和佳能，是通过进入邻近市场而不是留下来战斗来做到这一点的。</p><p>这些挑战者已经出现在专业服务领域，但到目前为止，他们还没有成为颠覆者。例如，成立于 2013 年的 HourlyNerd 雄心勃勃，希望成为连接技术客户与自由顾问的市场，以比典型采购流程更快的速度为客户提供更广泛的顾问选择。 “我们喜欢将自己视为可能聘请咨询公司的替代者，”其中一位联合创始人说。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Axiom Law 成立于 2000 年，致力于通过员工和合作伙伴网络提供随需应变的法律人才，从而更有效地提供法律服务。 “Axiom 有机会颠覆一个世纪以来未发生实质性变化的行业，”一位投资者表示。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8个</a></p><p>两家公司都做得不错。 HourlyNerd 于 2016 年更名为 Catalant，转向软件即服务模式，如今拥有数百名员工。 Axiom 是一家中型律师事务所，拥有约 1,600 名员工，年收入为 8.425 亿美元，其商业模式比大多数竞争对手都更加灵活。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>但两者都没有达到它所期望的破坏性效果。</p><p></p><h3>地平线上的破坏性威胁</h3><p>那么，是什么迫在眉睫的干扰让管理咨询和律师事务所的高管们夜不能寐？</p><p>我们采访的高级专业人士指出的一个因素是人工智能和分析能力的显着加速。在法律中，编纂——捕捉经验丰富的合作伙伴的法律推理并将其转化为可以应用于未来案件的算法的过程——可能会消除专业人士现在所做的大部分认知工作。 “那将是破坏性的，”伦敦一家大型公司的合伙人说。</p><p>其他一些人表示，近期最大的威胁很可能来自科技巨头：尤其是谷歌、亚马逊、微软和 Salesforce。每个人都建立了面向客户的能力，其中一些来自大型咨询公司，以增强他们销售针对客户技术挑战的解决方案的实力。</p><p>凭借其人工智能能力和全球影响力，它们可能会影响专业公司业务的供需双方。例如，Amazon Web Services 利用其掌握的大量数据，可以利用其对客户行为的独特洞察力为零售客户提供在线购物趋势预测。</p><p> “Amazon Web Services 的最大影响不在于其作为云服务供应商的地位，而在于其关于消费者购买行为的信息的非凡规模和深度，这是任何传统咨询公司都无法与之竞争的，”他说一家大型咨询公司的合伙人。</p><p>其他人淡化了威胁。 “像谷歌这样的公司实际上并不擅长客户服务，”一位受访者说。虽然一家科技公司有可能收购一家大型咨询公司，但这将代表与咨询公司发展合作伙伴关系的典型方法的重大战略转变，并将减少未来可以合作的公司数量。</p><h3>保持敏捷</h3><p>大型专业服务公司并没有仅仅因为他们采取的行动就避免了颠覆。更重要的是他们对商业环境变化的警惕性和反应能力。虽然咨询公司和律师事务所的高管经常贬低他们看似过时的工作方式，但事实证明，他们的专业合作模式非常有弹性。</p><p>从我们的访谈中，我们确定了三个值得强调的成功要素，它们也可能适用于其他行业。</p><p><strong>创新努力致力于解决客户问题。</strong>这与许多其他企业形成鲜明对比，在这些企业中，创新活动是与组织面向客户的部分分开进行的。最好的专业服务公司会根据他们在客户业务中发现的共同限制、摩擦和机会来追求产品和服务创新。然后，他们与选定的客户和合作伙伴组织（例如技术提供商）一起开发、测试和改进这些创新，然后再将它们推广到他们的客户组合中。</p><p><strong>合伙人及其后辈与客户密切合作。</strong>这些公司的学徒制模式意味着感觉-反应差距——感知客户需求然后采取适当行动解决这些需求之间的差异——比领导者与从事工作的人相差很远的公司要小。</p><p><strong>公司对投资新活动持谨慎态度。</strong>虽然这在瞬息万变的世界中似乎是一个弱点，但事实是，大多数新兴技术都需要很长时间才能发挥其潜力，而且许多公司都因行动过快而失败。由于其工作基于项目的性质，专业公司能够测试新技术，了解哪些有效，然后根据项目成功和客户需求向前推进。</p><h3>保持领先于中断</h3><p>专业服务公司在抵御潜在破坏方面的经验表明，其他行业的公司可以采取四种行动来准备和应对变化。</p><p><strong>诊断威胁。</strong>虽然每一个新的竞争对手或技术都可以被视为潜在的威胁，但有必要评估风险的大小以及它可能影响的业务部分。我们研究的咨询公司和律师事务所在分离需求和供应方面的影响方面大多非常周到。 （有关如何应用此逻辑，请参阅“诊断破坏性威胁的性质”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>诊断破坏性威胁的性质</h4><p class="caption">考虑您所在行业的新兴技术或新竞争对手，并回答以下问题以确定破坏性威胁的性质。</p><p class="print no-mobile no-desktop caption">在 https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/ 进行评估</p><p><a id="interactive-modal" href="#modal-container" class="is-button aqua no-print" style="max-width:275px">立即进行评估</a></p><p class="caption"><svg height="20.25" viewBox="0 0 18.183 20.25" width="18.183" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><clipPath id="a"><path d="m0 0h18.183v20.25h-18.183z"></path></clipPath><g clip-path="url(#a)"><path d="m17.081 12.4a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v5.648a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1 1.1h-15.981a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1-1.1v-5.648a1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1-1.1 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v4.546h13.642v-4.546a1.324 1.324 0 0 1 1.24-1.1m-11.71-4.135 2.618 2.617v-9.642a1.214 1.214 0 0 1 1.102-1.24 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v9.643l2.617-2.48a1.012 1.012 0 0 1 .827-.276 1.958 1.958 0 0 1 .827.276 1.254 1.254 0 0 1 0 1.653l-4.545 4.548c-.138.138-.276.138-.413.276a.878.878 0 0 1 -.827 0c-.138 0-.276-.138-.413-.276l-4.546-4.684a1.081 1.081 0 0 1 0-1.515 1.257 1.257 0 0 1 1.653 0" fill="#000000"></path></g></svg> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a3e29f5546.pdf" target="_blank" class="marketing_click" id="Download_Assessment[Birkinshaw_article]" rel="noopener">下载记分卡 (PDF)</a></p><div id="modal-container"><div  id="btn-close-modal" class="close-modal-container"> ← 返回文章</div><div class="modal-content"><iframe src="https://survey.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_eWAtUnHf3GCdswu" width="100%" frameborder="0"></iframe></div></p></div><p><script>$("#interactive-modal").animatedModal({modalTarget:'modal-container',animatedIn:'fadeInRightBig',animatedOut:'fadeOutRightBig',animationDuration:'.6s',color:'#292929',overflow:'hidden'});</script></p></article></aside></div><p><strong>匹配挑战的响应。</strong>一旦绘制了供求效应图，就可以针对适当的响应进行定位。需求方的挑战需要试验如何预测、理解、满足和调整客户的需求。专业服务公司天生就擅长于此。项目团队有权提出创造性的解决方案，并试验建立合作伙伴关系和提供服务的替代模型。对于那些已经变得过于“公司化”且决策从上到下流向合作伙伴和团队的公司来说，这应该是一个警示。</p><p>相比之下，供应方的变化需要对新能力进行投资，并对重组甚至外包内部活动持开放态度。这通常需要更高级别的集中化，通常需要一个从外部聘用或进行小规模收购的专门团队。挑战在于将它们与客户项目团队整合，以便将它们部署到市场中。</p><p></p><p><strong>专注于组织的真正使命。</strong>虽然那里有很多真正的威胁，但也有很多噪音。过分关注周而复始的所有变化可能会导致领导者看不到大局。对于专业服务公司而言，客户关系超越一切，对需求和供应驱动威胁的适当回应是加倍加强这种关系。 “我们希望保持整体关系，专注于优质工作领域，”伦敦一家大型律师事务所的合伙人表示。 “争论的焦点是我们留了多少……给其他律师事务所，我们保留了多少，并通过第三方或替代交付模式做了多少。”</p><p><strong>平衡实用主义与健康的偏执狂。</strong>我们在采访中与之交谈的法律和咨询合作伙伴真的被撕裂了。一方面，他们几乎没有看到任何证据表明他们的强势地位受到威胁，他们一致认为十年前关于颠覆的可怕预测是没有根据的。另一方面，他们不想表现得沾沾自喜，当然也不想向下级同事传达未来没有中断风险的信息。高管们必须学会接受双重心态：务实地承认基本面是好的，同时偏执地怀疑新兴技术或新竞争对手。毕竟，克里斯滕森和他的同事们认为，那些可能会措手不及的现任者最有可能被颠覆。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>风险情报和有弹性的公司</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:05:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ananya Sheth and Joseph V. Sinfield. <p>Ananya Sheth ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ananyasheth">@ananyasheth</a> ) 是史蒂文斯理工学院商学院的博士后研究员。 Joseph V. Sinfield 是普渡大学土木工程教授兼创新科学研究所所长。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Business Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors undertook a holistic study of enterprise resilience that began with the extraction of corporate risk factors from two decades of 10-Ks filed by S&#038;P 500 companies, investment analyst reports, and academic databases. They organized the risks into a value-centric framework composed of eight functions and 99 major risk categories; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Sheth_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者对企业弹性进行了全面研究，首先从标准普尔 500 强公司提交的 20 年 10-K 报告、投资分析师报告和学术数据库中提取企业风险因素。</li><li>他们将风险组织成一个以价值为中心的框架，该框架由八个功能和 99 个主要风险类别组成；然后，他们将类别和功能与来自 10 个经济部门和 26 个行业的风险专家和领导者的意见交叉链接，以创建一个量化风险网络。</li><li>他们还分析了标准普尔 500 10-K 五个行业的网络安全风险确认情况。</li><li>本材料基于国家科学基金会资助的工作，资助号为2049782。</li></ul></aside><p>在当今充满不确定性和相互关联的世界中，增强大型复杂企业的弹性至关重要。当一艘搁浅在苏伊士运河的集装箱船可以吞噬世界贸易的 12%，或者病毒可以扰乱商品、零部件和人才的全球流动时，一家公司在面对不断发展的事件时快速适应的能力对其生存和繁荣至关重要。</p><p>业务弹性是一种动态属性，可通过企业价值在不断变化的环境中的稳定性和持久性进行回顾性衡量。实时性体现在企业对业务环境的即时变化和渐进变化的及时适应。</p><p>我们的工作采用了企业的复杂适应性系统视图，表明弹性源自三种基本的适应能力：感知和监控，以识别商业环境中出现的新变化；业务模型组合开发，以构建和测试跨运营环境的能力；和基础能力建设，以长寿驱动增长，避免企业停滞。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>此外，这些能力中的每一项都取决于<em>风险情报</em>能力的发展。</p><p></p><p>我们将风险情报定义为严格解释风险及其给公司带来的后果或机会的磨练能力。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>它使领导者能够看穿环境的复杂性，并系统地识别、分类和解释风险。这使他们能够超越已知的风险因素，有意识地探索未知的风险，从而拥抱而不是避免不确定性。重要的是，风险情报让人们认识到，个别风险或它们表现出来的形式远不及它们对公司价值交换系统的共同后果——即管理、识别、创造、传达、交付、获取、保护和维持价值。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>最后，它为领导者提供了风险的网络视图，不仅阐明了风险的直接后果，还阐明了风险在公司价值交换系统中级联的方式，从而能够更有效地分配风险缓解资源。在本文中，我们将风险情报分解为可操作的元素，领导者可以追求这些元素，以帮助长期加强他们的组织。</p><h3>识别、分类和解释风险事件</h3><p>领导者无法准确预测特定的风险事件，也无法让公司为所有风险做好准备。然而，他们可以系统地识别、分类和解释风险事件，揭示看似不同的事件可能产生相似的后果。</p><p>第一步是研究每个业务价值函数，并确定可能对其有效性产生影响的似是而非的风险事件。为了帮助完成这一过程，我们构建了一个与行业无关的清单，将我们的研究中确定的与个体价值交换系统组件相关的 99 个主要风险类别分为三层。 （请参阅“价值函数风险清单”。）虽然不可避免地并不详尽，但该资源可作为识别任何企业面临的潜在风险的可靠起点。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig1"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>价值函数风险清单</h4><p class="caption">这份源自标准普尔 500 指数 20 年数据的风险清单显示了公司价值交换系统（绿色节点）的功能如何与业务功能及其各自的风险类别相关联。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig1.png" alt="价值函数风险清单"/></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>接下来，领导者应该根据风险事件的影响<em>范围</em>、它们引起的变化的<em>持久性</em>以及事件发生的<em>频率</em>来描述和分组风险事件。 （参见“风险特征”。）领导者随后可以解释每组风险事件与公司价值交换系统组成部分之间的联系。</p><div class="callout-highlight" id="fig2"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>表征风险</h4><p class="caption">每一种风险都可以根据其影响的广泛程度、它引起的变化可能持续多长时间以及它发生的频率来描述。例如，大雪事件具有行业内范围、诱发临时变化、发生频率低等特点。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig2.png" alt="表征风险" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>风险分类从了解风险事件的范围开始，它传达了一种风险影响在受影响的利益相关者范围内的感受范围。 COVID-19 大流行的广泛范围在整个价值网络中产生了供需方面的影响，而范围狭窄的事件，例如单个制造工厂的罢工，往往会产生更有限的影响。当多个利益相关者经历同时或相继的中断时，影响的复杂性增加会阻止系统自组织恢复常态。这种情况也可能会引起主权国家或国际组织的干预，它们可以帮助恢复或充当新的破坏力量。</p><p>要对风险事件进行全面分类，领导者还必须考虑其后果的持久性。大流行和 2021 年苏伊士运河堵塞都造成了供应方中断，但每个事件引起的变化的持久性差异很大。虽然运河堵塞等供应链冲击通常遵循自组织修正机制，即价格上涨降低需求并使滞后供应正常化，但同样的公式不能用于应对像大流行这样的长期情况。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>在规划和实施响应策略之前了解持久性很重要。例如，大流行造成的业务中断范围更广，后果更持久，与运河堵塞的影响更有限相比，影响的价值体系功能要多得多。</p><p></p><p>风险事件发生的频率也很重要，因为处理频繁事件所需的企业机制可能不同于处理单一事件的机制。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>尽管公司从所有事件中学习，但他们对重复发生的事件的响应通常会转化为标准操作程序。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>例如，采用条形码和扫描仪实时跟踪和管理库存，在很大程度上消除了由于数据不匹配而导致的库存记​​录错误和延误。</p><p>我们的范围、持久性和频率 (SPF) 框架提供了一个结构化视图，显示风险事件本身如何不如其后果重要。当多个风险事件同时发生时，该框架特别有用，因为它为管理人员提供了一种通用的、合乎逻辑的方法来考虑它们并快速获取信息和理解。然后将这些事件与公司的价值交换系统联系起来，经理们可以更容易地看到不同的风险何时仍然会对其价值函数产生类似的后果。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p>考虑一家制造商与一家海外供应商打交道，其产品因贸易战而突然被征收高得多的关税，以及一家价值链合作伙伴的破产。这些风险事件具有 SPF 特征（两者的范围都是公司间的，它们的持久性是可逆的，并且它们的频率很低），并且同样重要的是，这两个事件也会影响相同的价值函数。破产和贸易战都可能会减缓投入并提高供应方的成本，并使满足客户需求变得更加困难。两者还需要制造商确保新的供应来源并稳定运营现金流。通过根据 SPF 框架描述这些潜在风险事件的特征并将它们与价值函数联系起来，管理人员可以将它们更简单地视为对公司的特定价值函数具有共同后果并需要类似准备和响应的风险组。</p><h3>划分和减少不确定性</h3><p>Uncertainty about the consequences of a risk event is unavoidable, but it can be managed based on where the level of uncertainty falls on a spectrum between complete knowledge and complete ignorance (both of which are extreme and unlikely). <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Leaders should then seek to convert risks with higher levels of impact uncertainty to lower levels. (See “Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column" id="fig3"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty</h4><p class="caption"> Once managers have mapped risks to the appropriate level, they should take the critical action recommended to convert higher-order risks to lower-order risks. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig3.png" alt="Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p> Risk events causing level 1 uncertainty usually entail a very limited number of future scenarios with clear intrafirm effects, where causal linkages between risk events and the enterprise&#39;s value exchange system can be accurately known. Examples of such events include routine variation in production, expected sales losses, and human errors in performing manual tasks. When specific types of level 1 events occur frequently, they are indicative of errors in process or oversight that can be rectified permanently if diagnosed correctly. For instance, cargo thefts — a recurrent problem at logjammed transport hubs — can be prevented using optical character recognition scanners that track container freight and maintain real-time records. Importantly, at level 1, the overall uncertainty of the impact on firm value is within an expected, acceptable range.</p><p> Risk events causing level 2 uncertainty involve a larger number of alternate future scenarios and have interfirm consequences; however, even though they are more challenging, the probability that they will occur and their effects can be estimated. Businesses&#39; formal scenario planning exercises often involve level 2 events in which previously acquired knowledge regarding the impact of risk factors leads to improved accuracy and an effective exercise overall. The six-day Suez Canal blockage was predictable because a multiship pileup had closed the canal for two days in 2018. As a result, the Pentagon had already worked a longer blockage into its normal operational preparedness. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Risk events causing level 3 uncertainty involve a bounded set of scenarios where certain known risk events may affect the company in unknown ways. There is limited knowledge about how a chain reaction of consequences from a risk event might manifest at this level. Typically, these risks include less frequently occurring events with intra-industry scope and multistakeholder implications, which should be considered worst-case scenarios.</p><p> <a href="https://www.portrevel.com/">Port Revel</a> , a training facility situated on a lake in the French Alps, reduces level 3 uncertainty by helping ocean shipping companies simulate worst cases and identify the previously unknown consequences of operating increasingly large container ships through shipping infrastructure largely designed for smaller vessels. It closely replicates conditions at the trickiest spots in maritime transport, allowing trainee pilots to navigate scaled giant container ships through strong gusts of wind across a mini-Suez, steer and dock cruise ships in a crowded mini-San Francisco Bay, and maneuver oil tankers through an imitation Port Arthur. These exercises draw out unanticipated ship performance and pilot behaviors, helping to identify and address previously unknown event consequences.</p><p> Level 4 uncertainty encompasses events with unknown risk factors that could have a variety of negative consequences, the repercussions of which can&#39;t be estimated. These unknown unknowns are usually expressed in 10-Ks through statements such as “Other unknown risks may impact our business operations and projected performance.” It is challenging to develop scenario models in the presence of unknown unknowns. The models are incomplete representations of the world that could entail risks unimagined while developing them.</p><p> Once leaders order the uncertainty of impact into levels, they can focus on converting higher-level impact uncertainty into lower levels by discovering unknowns through data, simulation modeling, and logical analyses. For instance, the three-year gap between the UK&#39;s Brexit referendum in 2016 and its departure from the European Union in 2019 offered leaders an opportunity to convert the imagined event into likely scenarios and capture its vast trade implications. By focusing on the most vulnerable aspects of their value chains, such as those with the highest number of cross-border transactions, leaders could have recognized the imminent redistribution of goods passing through congested ports and modeled rerouting scenarios. For example, Felixstowe was known to be handling 48% of the UK&#39;s container trade, which could have been sent instead to multiple smaller and less busy ports. Evidence of impending port congestion also could have implied the high likelihood of delays and the need to hold more inventory in the UK to guarantee on-time deliveries.</p><p> Systemwide changes that are likely to have permanent effects are typically caused by noticeable megatrends, such as technological breakthroughs, changes in consumer demand patterns, global events, or regulatory body interventions. Once these trends are on a company&#39;s radar, they can be tracked and rapidly interpreted (if the necessary observation and modeling capabilities are in place). For instance, the European Union&#39;s carbon border tax, which was enacted in December 2022 after years of debate, won&#39;t be fully implemented until 2026, offering companies several years to reduce the uncertainty arising from it.</p><p></p><p> Further, for potential events that may be infrequent yet high impact, businesses can examine other industries where the consequences of similar events might be better recognized; then they can interpret the implications for their own value exchange system. For example, Brexit strategists could have studied cross-border trade between the US and Canada and the US and Mexico in the automobile and white goods sectors to help them navigate looming free-trade agreements and border regulations.</p><p> The active identification of plausible risk events and their potential consequences are the kinds of actions that contribute to building true risk intelligence. However, our research indicates that companies place little emphasis on discovering unknown and plausible risk events and their outcomes and instead focus attention on managing known risks. We also find that companies do not have a similarly complete knowledge of risks, even when those risks are publicly disclosed by direct competitors. Our study of 10-Ks revealed significant variation in the acknowledgment of risk factors, even among companies in the same industry. For instance, there was a lag of as much as eight years in acknowledging cyber risks after the first public data breach within a group of 18 comparable companies in the financial sector. This pattern was consistent in four additional sectors — including retail, telecom, technology, and health care.</p><p> Moreover, our analyses revealed only marginal levels of acknowledgment of causal relationships between risk factors, which are how risks impact companies in the real world. It is only logical that a known or unknown risk factor, when manifested, would likely influence other linked known and unknown risk factors, thereby creating a cascade of consequences. This ultimately would affect a company in potentially known but unexpected (or, worse, misunderstood) ways.</p><p></p><p> While most companies think they are preparing for risk events, they tend to focus only on level 1 and 2 uncertainty and therefore develop highly specific but narrow mitigation plans. Take Maersk, for example, which in 2017 fell victim to a ransomware cyberattack that brought down its entire network for days and halted its operations at 76 port terminals globally at a cost of roughly $300 million. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Yet the shipping company did not publicly acknowledge the risk of a cyberattack until its 2013 annual report, despite the risk of hacking and other cyberthreats having been well known since the late 1990s (although perhaps not seriously regarded as a primary risk for shippers). Thus, few risks are entirely unknown, and industry-specific unknowns may not be unknowns in other sectors.</p><h3> Construct and Contextualize an Enterprise Risk Network</h3><p> To gain clearer insight into level 3 and 4 uncertainty, it is important to understand the linkages among enterprise risks. Developing quantified risk networks (QRNs) can help. A QRN is a weighted map that links all identified potential risks to a company&#39;s value exchange system functions and helps decision makers interpret related impacts. Moreover, QRNs can reveal counterintuitive insights, such as a function&#39;s indirect exposure to risks typically associated with a different but connected function. For example, the risk of inaccurately forecasting shipping demand in a freight company directly affects its operating expense management function and indirectly affects facility capacity, operational capability, and customer concessions, as well as the company&#39;s reputation.</p><p> Companies should build their own risk networks for three reasons. First, each company has its own unique value exchange system that is best understood by its leaders. Second, resilient companies need to build in redundancies, which is challenging to do in resource-constrained environments. Custom QRNs highlight the most connected — and most vulnerable — value functions, creating an order of priority for allocating resources to bolster the enterprise. Third, custom QRNs provide a shared picture of risk for company leaders, who may or may not agree on critical vulnerabilities. The QRN-building activity focuses managerial attention on the often disregarded but potentially crucial functions and related risk categories to ultimately help leaders anticipate and prepare for the future.</p><p> To begin constructing your company&#39;s risk network, identify the risk events that are particularly relevant to your business by working from critical value functions upon which it relies and from the risk categories captured in the inventory. Identify plausible risk events in each category from data sources such as company memos, public risk disclosures, investment analyst reports, and historical knowledge. For example, leaders managing the operations function can use inventory risk categories, such as facilities and process management, sourcing, and distribution, to build a list of plausible risk factors or events (such as an unexpected storm, an equipment malfunction, input shortages, drained emergency supplies, worker health emergencies, communications interruptions, or labor strikes) that could affect business continuity. Note that these lists will likely contain several risk factors under each risk category.</p><p> Next, characterize relevant risks using the SPF framework, identify plausible scenarios related to the company&#39;s value functions, and identify potential responses. This exercise gives managers the opportunity to pay extra attention to less appreciated risks and helps them reduce the overall level of uncertainty of the impact of risks on the company&#39;s value exchange system.</p><p> Since the archetypal company is organized by function, the consequences of potential risks on individual functions (such as a labor strike&#39;s effect on sourcing) and the interconnectivity between different value functions themselves should be estimated for each functional node in the QRN. For instance, once managers define the level of interconnectivity between the sourcing and operations functions in their company, they can deduce the direct consequences of a labor strike for sourcing and its indirect consequences for operations. Weighting impacts, even using relative terms such as high, medium, and low, provides a common language for managers to discuss significant risks and plausible scenarios and can help resolve debate on what is likely or what is important. Functions identified as particularly important or vulnerable should be analyzed by experts to develop a deeper understanding of the risks affecting them and their interconnectivity.</p><p> We created a generalized QRN, beginning by asking leaders with sector and functional expertise to indicate interconnectivity between their function and other business functions on a 10-point scale. (See “A Quantitative Risk Network.”) Then we asked the leaders to indicate the potential impact of specific risks to their functional area arising from these connections. For example, a sales and marketing expert who indicated significant interconnectivity with the business strategy function was asked whether sales forecasting risks, sales execution risks, and reputation risks would have a high, medium, or low impact on business strategy. Companies can follow this process to build a codified understanding by leveraging their internal leaders as well as external experts. Once coded, the data forms the basis for a network representation of risks and a company-specific QRN. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig4"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> A Quantitative Risk Network</h4><p class="caption"> This visual representation of a generalized QRN reveals the linkages between risk categories and enterprise functions. It illustrates how companies can isolate and identify key value functions that link several connected risks and are therefore particularly significant in building enterprise resilience. The more central the function, the larger its font size; the thick links in the QRN imply high-impact relationships between functions and risk categories. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig4.png" alt="A Quantitative Risk Network" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Such a QRN helps leaders better understand a company&#39;s vulnerability to risk events by illuminating those functions that are central to the value exchange system. A risk event affecting a central function would imply a strong cascade of negative effects across the company&#39;s value exchange system. For example, financial capital management connects directly to 15 financial risk categories and indirectly to 30 risk categories from other functions. Any event occurring in any one of the risk categories affecting financial capital management will have implications for all other connected functions; for instance, significant currency exposure will likely affect the company&#39;s sourcing decisions. Thus, protecting the financial capital management function is critical to resilience. In contrast, a negative effect on the marketing and sales function is unlikely to cause a cascading impact in this company. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Expert knowledge, industry insights, experience, and the simulations are all useful in building a network view of enterprise risks. QRNs are baseline resources that help a company isolate and objectively model for worst-case scenarios, estimate cause-effect patterns, and effectively reduce level 3 and 4 uncertainty.</p><p> A company with a well-honed QRN will be able to differentiate between the scope and consequences of a business interruption due to, say, a pandemic and a transport route blockage. It will also be able to pinpoint the parts of the business that will likely experience significant consequences from these events, such as value delivery, value creation, and value protection, and identify the precise business functions that should be guarded for each of these events. In the case of the pandemic, these functions would include financial capital management, market risk assessment, and technology management; for the lower-scope blockage, these would include operations management and operating expense control. Furthermore, the company could use the value function risk inventory and build scenario models for risk events identified within each of these functions.</p><p> Ultimately, pairing the knowledge of plausible risk events and their likely interactions with the company&#39;s value functions enables strategists to develop tailored mitigation plans and response strategies. Leaders who recognize the need to better understand a specific set of scenarios can invest in developing precise models to reduce the uncertainty of their impact on the company.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The value exchange system that drives any large, complex enterprise is continuously challenged as contexts vary in the dynamic business environment. This raises the stakes for anticipating change, exploring new variations of business models, and continuously pursuing the next wave of growth-enabling capabilities. Risk intelligence helps leaders in this work, enabling them to better focus on maintaining continuous value exchange and fostering the adaptability needed to achieve resilience.</p><p> To create and nurture risk intelligence, a company needs a central risk management function that is staffed with broad functional expertise and given the resources required to identify and categorize risks. It needs to embrace a mindset of risk uncertainty versus risk avoidance and reduce the levels of uncertainty. It needs a company-specific quantified risk network that is updated in a dynamic manner. And finally, it needs a culture of risk intelligence in which leaders across the organization share a common framework and language for interpreting risks and guiding resource allocation for risk mitigation efforts. Ultimately, honing a risk intelligence capability represents the key to building a resilient enterprise.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here&#39;s How to Keep Them on Track.</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:57:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi. <p>Vern L. Glaser is an associate professor in the Department of Strategy, Entrepreneurship and Management at the University of Alberta&#39;s Alberta School of Business. Omid Omidvar is an associate professor in Organisation and Work at the University of Warwick&#39;s Warwick Business School. Mehdi Safavi is a senior lecturer in strategy and organization in the Strategy Group at Cranfield University&#39;s Cranfield School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Algorithms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Business Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors took a historical case study approach to explore the causes and consequences of algorithmic inertia, centering on the use of algorithms by Moody’s to rate mortgage-backed securities before the 2008 financial crisis. They drew on government reports on official investigations into the financial crisis, which included extensive witness testimony [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM_Glaser_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors took a historical case study approach to explore the causes and consequences of algorithmic inertia, centering on the use of algorithms by Moody&#39;s to rate mortgage-backed securities before the 2008 financial crisis.</li><li> They drew on government reports on official investigations into the financial crisis, which included extensive witness testimony that enabled them to effectively reconstruct changes to the Moody&#39;s credit rating routine during the years prior.</li><li> They gained useful information about the Moody&#39;s credit rating routine from an investigation of select credit rating agencies performed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission, as well as from a report by the Securities Industry and Financial Markets Association Credit Rating Agency Task Force.</li><li> They also gathered historical data from Moody&#39;s, such as annual reports and public statements, and reviewed media coverage.</li></ul></aside><p> Organizations are increasingly turning to sophisticated data analytics algorithms to support real-time decision-making in dynamic environments. However, these organizational efforts often fail — sometimes with spectacular consequences.</p><p> In 2018, real estate marketplace Zillow launched Zillow Offers, an “instant buyer” arm of the business. It leveraged a proprietary algorithm called Zestimate, which calculates how much a given residential property can be expected to sell for. Based on these calculations, Zillow Offers planned to purchase, renovate, and resell properties for a profit. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> While it had some success for the first few years, the model failed to adjust to the new dynamics of a more volatile market in 2021. Zillow lost an average of $25,000 on every home it sold in the fourth quarter that year — resulting in a write-down of $881 million. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2个</a></p><p>This is an example of what we call <em>algorithmic inertia</em> : when organizations use algorithmic models to take environmental changes into account but fail to keep pace with those changes. In this article, we explain algorithmic inertia, identify its sources, and suggest practices organizations can implement to overcome it.</p><p></p><h3> A Credit-Rating Catastrophe</h3><p> To understand the phenomenon of algorithmic inertia, we conducted an in-depth study of another organization that failed to respond to changes in the environment: Moody&#39;s, a financial research firm that provides credit ratings for bonds and complex financial instruments such as residential mortgage-backed securities (RMBSs). These securities aggregated bundles of individual mortgages into distinct tranches with unique characteristics during the period leading up to the global financial crisis of 2008. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Moody&#39;s made a concerted effort to account for environmental changes in its credit ratings by developing a proprietary algorithmic model in 2000 called M3 Prime. The model analyzed data about properties, mortgage holders, and the economy to estimate two parameters central to calculating a credit rating: expected losses for the mortgage pool and the loss coverage protection required for a security to maintain a AAA rating. An analyst would present a recommendation to Moody&#39;s credit rating committee, which assigned a publicly posted rating for the security. Moody&#39;s monitored these ratings and upgraded or downgraded RMBSs as the environment changed. The M3 Prime model achieved early success, so in 2006, Moody&#39;s expanded its scope of algorithmic analysis by introducing a derivative model, M3 Subprime.</p><p> Between 2000 and 2008, Moody&#39;s provided credit ratings for thousands of RMBSs, but it ended up downgrading 83% of AAA-rated mortgage-backed securities valued at billions of dollars by 2008. The US government, along with 21 states and the District of Columbia, held Moody&#39;s responsible for the role that its inflated ratings of those and other products played in precipitating the financial crisis. In 2017, the agency agreed to pay $864 million to settle the allegations. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> This is a particularly illustrative example of algorithmic inertia with devastating societal consequences. Moody&#39;s decisions offer an excellent context for exploring algorithmic inertia because the organization was explicitly responsible for analyzing environmental changes as part of its core service. Moreover, we were able to access detailed information about its algorithmic model from a report produced by the Financial Crisis Inquiry Commission that includes extensive interviews conducted under oath with Moody&#39;s executives who were involved in the business at the time. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5个</a></p><p>Our analysis enabled us to identify the most significant contributing factors to algorithmic inertia — buried assumptions, superficial remodeling, simulation of the unknown future, and specialized compartmentalization — described below. (See “Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia</h4><p class="caption"> Organizational and process issues can result in algorithms that don&#39;t keep up with environmental changes in the decision domain. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Buried Assumptions</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> The organization uses legacy data inputs for the algorithmic model despite recognizing significant changes in the environment. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;border-bottom-color:black;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Superficial Remodeling</strong></p></td><td  style="background-color:#f0f0f0;;border-bottom-color:black;"><p> The organization makes only minor modifications to the algorithmic model in response to substantive changes in the environment. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Simulation of the Unknown Future</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> The organization overconfidently relies on the algorithmic model to predict the future environment.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Specialized Compartmentalization</strong></p></td><td style="background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Responsibilities for the algorithmic routine are divided between team members in distinct roles based on their specialized expertise. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Glaser_Table_1.png" alt="Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Buried assumptions.</strong> Failing to revisit fundamental assumptions undergirding inputs of the algorithmic model in light of changes in the environment contributes significantly to algorithmic inertia. For example, loan originators were increasingly underwriting mortgages based on lower credit standards and substantially less documentation than before. So an original assumption undergirding Moody&#39;s M3 Prime model — that the technology that mortgage originators were using to streamline the loan application process was also enabling a more accurate assessment of underlying risks — wasn&#39;t modified to reflect the changing lending environment. The managing director of credit policy at Moody&#39;s told a federal inquiry panel that he sat on a high-level structured credit committee that would have been expected to deal with issues like declining mortgage underwriting standards, but the topic was never raised. “We talked about everything but … the elephant sitting on the table,” he said. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p></p><p> Moody&#39;s model also assumed that consumers&#39; FICO credit scores were the primary predictive factor in loan defaults. But the quality of this data input significantly diminished over time: As the use of these credit scores became increasingly common, individuals found ways to artificially inflate them. As a result, low- and no-documentation mortgages carried latent risk that was not being taken into account in Moody&#39;s algorithmic model. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> <strong>Superficial remodeling.</strong> This phenomenon occurs when organizations make only minor modifications to the algorithmic model in response to substantive changes in the environment. At Moody&#39;s, some major changes to the environment included a growing number of loan originators, increasingly low-quality mortgages, and an unprecedented decline in interest rates.</p><p> Moody&#39;s response to these changes was to seek to capture more business in the rapidly growing market, so it fine-tuned the model to be “more efficient, more profitable, cheaper, and more versatile,” according to its chief credit officer — not to be more accurate. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> When it modified M3 Prime to introduce the M3 Subprime model, it extrapolated loss curves for subprime loans based on premium loans rather than developing fresh loss curves for subprime loans.</p><p> <strong>Simulation of the unknown future.</strong> Relying on an algorithmic model to produce viable scenarios for the future environment can also leave organizations vulnerable to algorithmic inertia. Moody&#39;s constructed a simulation engine featuring 1,250 macroeconomic scenarios that enabled it to estimate possible future losses based on variations in economic markers such as inflation, unemployment, and house prices. However, the simulation engine was limited by its underlying structure and assumptions, so analysts did not consider the changes that were occurring, did not update scenarios, and failed to accurately represent the changing macroeconomic environment. Based on the belief that detailed performance histories could more precisely reveal causal links between economic stresses and loan behavior, Moody&#39;s used estimates based on historical parameters rather than expected pool loss distributions to examine behavior in stress scenarios. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> <strong>Specialized compartmentalization.</strong> This situation arises when experts in different domains are involved in an algorithm&#39;s design and use and there is no overarching single ownership or shared understanding of the model. At Moody&#39;s, responsibilities for the credit rating routine were divided between the domain experts (credit rating committee members) who used the quantitative model and the quantitative analysts who had developed it.</p><p> Because ownership and use of the model were distributed, and Moody&#39;s didn&#39;t strictly define how to use it, credit rating committee members established ad hoc rules to adjust the results of the model when its outputs didn&#39;t conform to what their expert judgment led them to believe it ought to produce. Model outputs weren&#39;t considered final; rather, the models were seen as tools to be used in conjunction with other approaches, and there was much divergence in how different ratings committees made their determinations.</p><p> The models were developed and modified by individuals who were distant from the domains in which they would be applied; disparate groups of domain experts then used the models in inconsistent ways without understanding their underlying logic. The managing director for rating RMBSs described the model as so technically complex that few people understood how it worked. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a></p><p> This issue is at the heart of what makes algorithmic inertia hard to tackle: The models and algorithms are often so complex that domain experts can hardly grasp the details of their functioning, while data scientists are disconnected from how their models are being used in the real world.</p><h3> Develop Practices That Combat Algorithmic Inertia</h3><p> We have described how each of the causes of algorithmic inertia played out in Moody&#39;s use of an algorithmic model to dynamically incorporate changes in the environment into its credit ratings. Despite recognizing flaws in the model and making active attempts to change it, the organization was unable to effectively adapt to the environment, thereby substantially contributing to the 2008 financial crisis.</p><p> To prevent similar degradation of critical algorithms&#39; predictive value, we suggest that organizations implement the four practices described below. (See “Keeping Algorithms Relevant.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Keeping Algorithms Relevant</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations can increase the likelihood that algorithmic tools will effectively adapt to changes in the environment by following four practices. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Expose Data and Assumptions</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Articulate and document the data and the fundamental assumptions in the algorithmic model. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;border-bottom-color:black;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Periodically Redesign Algorithmic Routines</strong></p></td><td  style="background-color:#f0f0f0;;border-bottom-color:black;"><p> Periodically redesign — and be willing to overhaul — the algorithmic model and how it fits into broader organizational routines. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Assume That the Model Will Break</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Actively consider scenarios outside the scope of algorithmic models by challenging predictive assumptions, assuming that the model will be fundamentally flawed, and envisioning qualitative alternative predictions of the future.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Build Bridges Between Data Scientists and Domain Experts</strong></p></td><td style="background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Ensure that data scientists and domain experts work closely together to design the algorithmic model and the organizational routine in which it is to be embedded. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Glaser_Table_2.png" alt="Keeping Algorithms Relevant" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p></p><p> <strong>Expose data and assumptions.</strong> Organizations should articulate and document the data used in their algorithmic models, including data sources and fundamental assumptions underlying their data selection decisions, which can have deleterious effects. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> Models often include operationalizations of many concepts, and it is easy for organizations to lose track of these parameters, which can be buried in layers of software code. Parameters representing the environment need to be documented to ensure that they remain visible. Similarly, the fundamental assumptions undergirding the model should be articulated and periodically revisited.</p><p> Moody&#39;s used a data set on premium mortgages to train a model that was intended to be used to rate RMBSs composed of subprime mortgages. Initially, this might have been a reasonable choice due to the availability of data. But when a model&#39;s initial data set isn&#39;t refreshed, algorithmic inertia can result. As the Moody&#39;s case suggests, data is never completely accurate, objective, and flawless. Therefore, making the sources of data and assumptions about those sources transparent to algorithm users, and continually reflecting on the appropriateness of that data, are critical practices for organizations seeking to avoid algorithmic inertia.</p><p> Organizations must keep data sources clearly organized and evaluate them periodically. Different data sources have different qualities and characteristics. Ensuring that these sources are distinguished from one another before they are fed into algorithmic models, processed, and constantly compared against one another enables data scientists to identify and eliminate algorithmic inertia sooner rather than later.</p><p> The assumptions underpinning the use of an algorithm should also be documented and articulated. Any attempt to model the environment involves quantification — transforming aspects of reality into numerical data. Such quantification inevitably involves making assumptions about how the environment works. However, while quantification is necessary for algorithmic models to work, details about how it is performed can get lost in the complex process of designing and using algorithmic models. Therefore, maintaining a living record of such assumptions may prevent the emergence of algorithmic inertia.</p><p> <strong>Periodically redesign algorithmic routines.</strong> Organizations should regularly redesign — and be willing to overhaul — their algorithmic model and reconsider how it fits into broader organizational routines. The initial design of an algorithmic model can take a lot of work, and it is natural for an organization to want to reap the benefits of that work. However, in a dynamic and quickly changing environment, it&#39;s important to be willing not just to make incremental changes to a model but to fundamentally overhaul it if necessary.</p><p> Of course, organizations face a trade-off when it comes to overhauling an algorithmic routine: It can be very expensive to completely re-architect an algorithmic model. However, the consequences of failing to do so can be disastrous.</p><p> For example, when Moody&#39;s had to rate an increasing number of subprime-dominated RMBSs, the organization chose to incrementally modify the M3 Prime model. However, it may have been more effective to specify the distinctions between the prime and the subprime markets and do a deeper overhaul of the original model. In addition to rethinking the algorithmic model itself, an organization can consider how it is deployed in practice: Hypothetically, Moody&#39;s could have applied the M3 Prime model differently to different types of RMBSs — perhaps simply requiring more human intervention for tranches composed of lower-quality loans.</p><p> Redesigning and overhauling an algorithmic model is contingent upon understanding what organizational processes interrelate with the model and analyzing the implications that changes in the environment have for it. If it becomes clear that either the model or the processes that it relies on or feeds into have been rendered obsolete or ineffective, an overhaul should be seriously considered.</p><p> <strong>Assume that the model will break.</strong> It can be dangerous for an organization to think of potential future scenarios only through the prism of what algorithmic models predict: All assumptions embedded in a model limit the potential futures that can be considered. To address algorithmic inertia associated with the simulation of an unknown future, it is important to assume that the model will break. Consider scenarios beyond the scope of the algorithmic model; this requires challenging predictive assumptions as well as presuming that the model is fundamentally flawed.</p><p> An active practice of considering scenarios that are <em>outside</em> the model can help motivate and inspire the prior two practices — exposing data and assumptions and periodically redesigning algorithmic routines — by forcing team members to actively consider the limitations of algorithmic models.</p><p></p><p> One particularly useful approach might be to make use of qualitative predictions of the future instead of quantitative predictions that rely on available data from the past. These forms of scenario planning offer opportunities to consider radically different visions of what the future may hold. This might also entail developing hybrid algorithms that do not precisely rely on past data to predict scenarios but also embed in them qualitative measures and expert rules introduced by domain experts.</p><p> <strong>Build bridges between data scientists and domain experts.</strong> Organizations must create processes for data scientists and domain experts to work closely together to design their algorithmic routines. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> Practically speaking, data scientists and AI specialists approach problems very differently than domain experts do. Domain experts focus on organizational routines and idiosyncratic situations, whereas data scientists focus on developing generalizable constructs based on mathematical principles. To overcome algorithmic inertia, data scientists and domain experts must work closely together to understand how characteristics of organizational routines and idiosyncratic situations map to the mathematical parameters used in an algorithmic model.</p><p> When the worlds of data scientists and domain experts are completely separate, there is also the danger that data scientists and domain experts will shift responsibility by superficially trusting each other&#39;s work. Such assumptions can actually prevent crucial dialogue between the two worlds. For instance, Moody&#39;s ended up subverting the results of its credit rating model because the credit rating analysts didn&#39;t attempt to understand why the model might be generating results that didn&#39;t fit with their intuitions. Building bridges between data scientists and domain experts enables domain experts to obtain an intuitive grasp of how the algorithmic model works. Such common ground could enable organizations to create and use models that better adapt to changes in the environment.</p><p> One structural bridge-building practice that organizations can use to facilitate communication between data scientists and domain experts is establishing a position such as a product manager. This should be held by one individual with both domain and data science experience who has direct responsibility for overseeing algorithmic routines. For example, some data experts have called for the creation of a new organizational structure that includes an “innovation marshal” role — someone who is respected by both data scientists and field experts. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> Given their knowledge and expertise in both areas, these people can gain the respect of the organization by developing and maintaining “high-bandwidth, bidirectional communication channels” that help ensure that algorithmic routines are able to adapt to environmental changes. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p></p><p> Another bridge-building practice is called <em>model explainability</em> : describing the algorithmic models in a practical and comprehensible manner. For data scientists, such explainability can facilitate access to the expert knowledge needed to counteract the sources of algorithmic inertia; for domain experts, such explainability can help them develop a deep and intuitive understanding of how the model takes environmental changes into account. Model explainability establishes common ground between two groups of professionals who have different types of expertise. Such practices enable organizations to build bridges instead of just talking about them.</p><p></p><p> Organizations seeking to reap the benefits of powerful predictive analytics are increasingly confronting the problem of algorithmic inertia. Despite leveraging dynamic algorithms to adapt to changes in the environment, organizations may find that the results are not keeping pace with new developments. By exposing data and assumptions, periodically redesigning algorithmic routines, assuming that their models will break, and building bridges, organizations can increase the likelihood that their substantial investments in algorithmic solutions will pay off with better decision-making.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> We Should Bring Moore&#39;s Law to Climate Action</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) is a globally recognized expert on how to build resilient, profitable companies that help people and the planet thrive. He is coauthor of <cite>Net Positive: How Courageous Companies Thrive by Giving More Than They Take</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Gordon Moore, cofounder of Intel and a towering figure of the early semiconductor business, died earlier this year at the age of 94. He leaves behind one of the more successful companies in history and, of course, his famous Moore’s law. He predicted in 1965 that the density of transistors on a microchip would double [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Winston-MooresLaw-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Gordon Moore, cofounder of Intel and a towering figure of the early semiconductor business, died earlier this year at the age of 94. He leaves behind one of the more successful companies in history and, of course, his famous <a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/news/gordon-moore-obituary.html">Moore&#39;s law</a> . He predicted in 1965 that the density of transistors on a microchip would double every year and adjusted his forecast in 1975 to “just” doubling every two years. The latter projection has held true for nearly 50 years.</p><p> It&#39;s often said that the phones in our hands have more computing power than the 1969 Apollo moon mission. That&#39;s true, but it&#39;s also a vast understatement — our phones actually have <a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/moon-mars/a25655/nasa-computer-iphone-comparison/">more power than all of NASA at the time</a> , a fact that demonstrates the shocking reality of exponential change.</p><p></p><p> We humans tend to think in linear terms: If things grew a bit last year, they&#39;ll grow a bit more this year. It&#39;s hard for us to grasp what happened with semiconductors. In 1971, there were around 2,400 transistors per microprocessor. Fifty years later, a chip holds 58 billion transistors, and Intel intends to make it <a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/opinion/moore-law-now-and-in-the-future.html">1 trillion by 2030</a> . If something doubles every two years, it grows roughly 30 times per decade, 1,000-fold in 20 years, and 1 million times in 40 years. In 60 years, you&#39;ll get something 1 billion times faster.</p><p> It&#39;s hard to overstate what this speed of change has wrought on the world. At the fun end of things, my teenage boys are utterly unimpressed that they can look up nearly any fact or stream any video or song nearly instantly. At the same time, misinformation can travel much faster. As for AI? It will get rapidly better at both the good and the bad. (Look up “deepfakes” if you want to be scared.)</p><p> Moore&#39;s law has also led to some of the most classic failures in business history. Kodak didn&#39;t get ready for digital photos. Blockbuster was blindsided as well, as downloading a movie went from impossible to a real-time capability in just a handful of years. Once streaming movies became a trivial act, the rent-a-video model was dead.</p><p> In all of this, I see two critical lessons. First, we can make remarkable progress if we enable early success, believe much more is possible, compete like crazy to do it, and <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/">invest what&#39;s necessary</a> . The core point here is that, to state the obvious, Moore&#39;s law is not a law. Nobody mandated the big chip companies to cut the width of a transistor down to nanoscale over decades. They did so because of competition, massive public and private spending to build markets for chips, and impressive levels of innovation in theories, manufacturing technologies, device design, and marketing. (Did we <em>need</em> iPads once they were feasible?) Moore&#39;s law proved to be a powerful and bold prediction of what an industry could accomplish, based on early experience and success.</p><p> Second, we can draw parallels to the critical business challenge of our times: how to thrive and grow while managing our social and environmental impacts (especially climate change). We can embrace rapid change to operate in a sustainable or net-positive way.</p><h3> We Can Embrace the Exponential Again</h3><p> Like in the 1960s and &#39;70s, once again we&#39;re barreling down a path we&#39;re not sure how to travel, driven by external goals — most importantly, how fast science tells us the world should decarbonize. “Science-based targets” are a quasi-Moore&#39;s law for fighting climate change. Keeping up with these aggressive targets is an important creator of business value, a path to excellence in innovation and performance, and a core way to stay relevant to customers, employees, and other stakeholders (and not get Blockbuster-ized).</p><p></p><p> So far, many clean technology sectors are doing a good impression of the semiconductor world. The cost of clean power and battery storage has been, if not halving every two years, still declining very quickly. According to the International Energy Agency, <a href="https://www.iea.org/data-and-statistics/charts/evolution-of-solar-pv-module-cost-by-data-source-1970-2020">the cost per watt of new solar modules</a> dropped 96% between 2000 and 2020. Over 45 years, solar costs have plummeted 500-fold, halving roughly every five years. While not the pace of Moore&#39;s law, it&#39;s been plenty fast enough to shake up entire sectors and create vast new opportunities. The cleantech transition is a multitrillion-dollar shift in how we travel, build buildings, make things, and much more.</p><p> Like with semiconductors, this performance in the cleantech sector has come from a combination of innovation, investment, policy support, and the massive build-out of manufacturing capacity at scale (mainly in China). But perhaps most important in both cases is that the pace of change has required willpower and new mental models. When those of us in the sustainable business world started pushing the idea of science-based targets 10-plus years ago, the pushback was palpable. “How could we possibly move that fast?” many would ask. “ <em>Why</em> would we move that fast, given how much it costs?” But skepticism flips to enthusiasm when you cross cost and mental tipping points.</p><p></p><p> As powerful as Moore&#39;s law has been in driving deep technological and social change in society, again, it was a man-made goal. Companies were driven to move toward it by competition, innovation, and profit motivations. This time, with climate objectives, we&#39;re using global planetary thresholds to shape the goals on how fast we need to go — not just with carbon but with water use, the amount of toxics or plastics in the environment, the prevalence of human rights abuses in supply chains, and more.</p><p> These are not nice-to-haves if we want our world to thrive. The sustainability “laws” we&#39;re grappling with are decidedly <em>not</em> theoretical or invented — they&#39;re based on the laws of nature and physics. Smart companies will see these nonnegotiable realities as the incredible opportunity that they are and get moving.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Manage Your Workforce Ecosystem, Not Just Your Employees</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth J. Altman, David Kiron, Jeff Schwartz, and Robin Jones. <p>Elizabeth J. Altman is associate professor of management at the Manning School of Business at the University of Massachusetts Lowell. David Kiron is editorial director, research, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . Jeff Schwartz is vice president for insights and impact at Gloat and an adjunct professor at Columbia Business School. Robin Jones is a principal at Deloitte Consulting LLP and serves as the Workforce Transformation Practice leader. They are the authors of <cite><a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047777/workforce-ecosystems/">Workforce Ecosystems</a></cite> (MIT Press, April 2023), from which this article is adapted.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jon Krause/theispot.com “How do you define your workforce?” We have posed this question to dozens of executives and in multiple global management surveys. The most common answer is also the most surprising. A confident minority of executives say their workforce is just their employees. But the overwhelming majority, especially leaders on the front lines of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM_Altman_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jon Krause/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> “How do you define your workforce?” We have posed this question to dozens of executives and in multiple global management surveys. The most common answer is also the most surprising.</p><p> A confident minority of executives say their workforce is just their employees. But the overwhelming majority, especially leaders on the front lines of organizational transformations, takes a broader view that goes beyond just employees. Increasingly, they characterize the workforce as all of the people and groups involved in achieving the company&#39;s business objectives. Organizations&#39; extended workforces have become so essential to their businesses, brands, and approaches to value creation that they need to think differently about, and act differently toward, their entire workforce.</p><p> That represents a shift in management perspective since we began our study of the future of the workforce a few years ago. We are seeing this change across industries and a variety of organizations, large and small — and it is challenging leaders to redefine who and what constitutes their workforce and to develop new management practices and organizational structures.</p><p></p><p> Hierarchical, command-and-control, internally focused management practices are ill suited for workforces that span internal and external organizational boundaries. Using siloed functions to independently manage employees and external contributors, for example, is fraught with challenges: Ill-defined decision rights, governance processes, and power dynamics can undermine even the most well-intentioned executives. In addition, the technology systems for managing employees are typically different and disconnected from those for accessing and tracking external contributors. This lack of integration creates inefficiencies that can thwart efforts to obtain and maintain strategically valuable capabilities.</p><p> We define <em>workforce ecosystem</em> as a structure that encompasses actors, from within the organization and beyond, working to create value for an organization. Within the ecosystem, actors work toward individual and collective goals with interdependencies and complementarities among the participants.</p><p> Workforce ecosystems include employees as well as external contributors and partners of various kinds — long- and short-term contractors, gig workers, application developers, service providers, and crowdsourced actors. An ecosystem perspective explicitly recognizes that accessing and engaging workforces is no longer the sole purview of the human resources function but requires cross-functional actions involving leaders in the C-suite, IT, procurement, finance, legal, and other areas.</p><p> Intentionally orchestrating a workforce ecosystem requires leaders to coordinate activities across their own organization and with external contributors. To meet this challenge, companies need to reassess coordination between functions such as human resources, procurement, and IT. Decisions also need to made about how to govern relationships with external contributors, such as application developers and subcontractors. We developed the concept of <em>integration architectures</em> to define both that internal coordination and how organizations interact with their extended workforce.</p><p></p><p> Our integration architecture model contrasts with the default, siloed approach to managing interactions in most workforce ecosystems. Typically, contingent workers are the responsibility of procurement. Partners and alliances are often handled by strategy, and AI and automation are part of the tech organization (but rarely regarded as part of the broader workforce ecosystem). HR typically oversees full- and part-time employees. In this common approach, multiple groups work independently to govern the contributors for which they have a mandate, but efforts across the organization are uncoordinated.</p><p> Managers in different departments frequently use combinations of external and internal workers without any centralized coordination. These decentralized approaches may be efficient on a local level, where each business unit and functional manager retains maximum control, but they are suboptimal at an aggregate level.</p><p> Indeed, decentralization can have substantial drawbacks when orchestrating a workforce ecosystem. Dispersed efforts may not be aligned with overall strategic priorities and may undermine a business&#39;s pursuit of new strategic directions. The lack of integration may limit available data about who (and what) is contributing to an organization. It may lead to cost inefficiencies as contingent workers are sourced on an ad hoc basis. And it likely means that both internal workers and external contributors (existing and potential) have less visibility into opportunities to contribute. While decentralization is currently the most common approach to managing employees and the extended workforce, it is almost always uncoordinated.</p><h3> Why Centralized Integration Architectures Appeal</h3><p> Given the shortcomings of decentralized architectures, many organizations orchestrating workforce ecosystems are creating integration architectures that are more centralized and cross-functional in their design. In some organizations, HR coordinates workforce ecosystem management with the procurement and IT functions; in these cases, business leaders and teams work with HR and others to proactively manage risks. Other companies are adopting a more cross-functional approach to managing all types of individual workers and providers; in these cases, HR plays a key but less central role, with talent marketplaces playing a more prominent role in supporting workforce needs across business units and functions.</p><p> Swiss global health care company Novartis, for example, has set up a cross-functional steering committee to manage its approximately 100,000 internal workers and roughly 50,000 external ones. Novartis is working to provide managers with visibility into internal and external talent sources, an effort driven by data culled from a variety of partners and platforms. The process will be facilitated by curators called workforce strategists, who will grant managers real-time access to teams of employees, contractors, and technologies.</p><p> The pandemic prompted HR at another global company we studied to get more involved with overseeing the broader workforce because of the concerns it raised about remote and onsite work policies, pay continuity, absences, and sick leave for both contingent workers and employees. Before the pandemic, HR paid close attention only to what was going on with full-time-equivalent or part-time employees, the company&#39;s vice president of HR reported; often, with contingent workers, “HR was not in the loop at all,” she said. At that time, there wasn&#39;t even a shared understanding of who comprises the company&#39;s contingent workforce. The pandemic lent urgency to the idea that the company would have to be more centrally integrated and agile to take care of its contingent workers. It also underscored that the company needed to better manage the reputational, legal, operational, and cost risks of the broader workforce, and to use the entire workforce to its fullest competitive advantage.</p><p> At this same company, hiring processes and procedures had historically differed by department — and departments tended not to communicate with one another. HR supported decisions about hiring permanent employees, while procurement brought in contingent workers. Meanwhile, unbeknownst to HR, managers were often converting contingent workers into full-time employees. A newly developed clearinghouse platform that involved HR, procurement, and finance gave the company data-based cross-functional visibility into tracking and approving external workers.</p><p> Management of the contingent workforce had been a hot potato at the company, according to the chief procurement officer: “Anybody who was at the center was on the hook for all the risk and none of the benefit.” But he described the company as having shifted to thinking of its relationship with contingent workers in strategic rather than transactional terms, which involves managing the contingent workforce cross-functionally. As the vice president of HR explained, “There was an acknowledgment between our CFO, our chief general counsel, our CHRO [chief human resources officer], and our chief operating officer that they all had skin in the game.”</p><p> Talent marketplaces are another great tool for anchoring a centralized and more cross-functionally integrated architecture. NASA, for example, used to have six talent-market platforms spread across multiple units, each of which independently matched employees with gigs and projects. Now the space agency uses a single talent marketplace — one orchestrating mechanism — to coordinate access to internal human talent across the organization. Extending its internal talent marketplace to external contributors is on NASA&#39;s horizon.</p><p></p><h3> Integration Architecture Challenges</h3><p> While centralized and cross-functional integration architectures are enabling organizations to achieve higher levels of coordination in their workforce ecosystems, these efforts are in their nascent stages. Even among companies on the leading edge of workforce ecosystem transformations, leaders emphasize that these efforts are just starting to gain traction. In our research and consulting work, we see that most organizations still take reactive, local, and uncoordinated approaches to enlisting and retaining external talent and complementary contributors. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1个</a></p><p>Leaders realize that such decentralized efforts are both cost- and resource-inefficient and risk demotivating internal employees. Yet they struggle to establish a centralized cross-functionally integrated architecture for workforce ecosystem orchestration. We have heard the following concerns:</p><ul><li> How do you identify the right set of stakeholders to create a centrally integrated architecture for workforce ecosystem orchestration?</li><li> How do you get stakeholders to engage in local workforce ecosystem experiments to tailor shared goals to specific contexts?</li><li> How do you promote coordinated learning from local experimentation?</li><li> How do you improve your workforce ecosystem implementation process over time?</li></ul><p> To create an integrated workforce ecosystem, at least three types of issues need to be addressed: structural design (pertaining to the division of labor, goals, and incentives), politics (relating to resources, power, and status), and culture (affecting individuals&#39; search for identity and meaning). We recommend taking a phased approach to these issues, which intertwine, overlap, and can reinforce one another. This process is likely to be most appropriate for large, established organizations that are starting to embrace workforce ecosystems, but key elements should be helpful for those in small and medium-size enterprises. (See “Four Phases of Orchestrating an Integrated Workforce Ecosystem.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Phases of Orchestrating an Integrated Workforce Ecosystem</h4><p class="caption"> The graphic below describes the key challenges associated with orchestrating workforce ecosystems and the phases associated with addressing them. <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a> </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Altman_Figure.png" alt="Four Phases of Orchestrating an Integrated Workforce Ecosystem" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> In the first phase, we propose creating an orchestration team to develop a working plan, goals, and metrics in consultation with relevant local and central stakeholders, both internal and external. This team should focus on integration considerations within the organization (functional roles and responsibilities) and on relationships with external participants. By working with groups within the organization that already engage external workers, the team can get a head start with managers experienced in orchestrating parts of workforce ecosystems. From a structural design perspective, they can quickly begin to highlight and address previously identified skills gaps.</p><p> To deal with political concerns, the team can choose local well-respected and action-oriented champions to lead transformations. Additionally, the team can include representatives from external contributors to bring their perspectives to the efforts. Team members should be able to speak for functional areas, product groups, and business units as appropriate; the key is to obtain participation from across stakeholder groups. Finally, to grapple with cultural challenges, at least one team member should play the role of a boundary spanner, serving as a go-between among the central team, local teams, and other affected groups.</p><p> In the second phase, we suggest promoting local experimentation. Central orchestration teams can introduce pilot programs to explore potential configurations of workforce ecosystem relationships. These experiments can address structural issues, such as staffing projects with a mix of internal and external workers, identifying necessary skills, ensuring competencies, and measuring the quality of outcomes. They can address political challenges, such as internal employees resisting contributions from external workers and local leaders feeling tension as they lose some control over team composition. Finally, cultural questions may arise as employees adapt to shifts in responsibilities, especially if they need to take on more of a facilitation role coordinating participants from various sources.</p><p> In the third phase, we emphasize coordinated learning and resourcing, which spans challenges (and successes) identified by local teams and overseen by the central team. Structural impediments, such as existing policies and procedures (intellectual property licensing models or training rules, for example) may serve the organization well in a traditional employee life-cycle model but require revision for a workforce ecosystem. Resourcing issues may arise as local managers hire more external workers or partner more easily with subcontractors but then refuse to release employees to accept other opportunities. Even when the C-suite and lower levels embrace changes, midtier managers might be resistant because they are often tasked with managing the day-to-day challenges of these sometimes highly disruptive transformations.</p><p> In the fourth and final phase, we consider workforce ecosystem expansion. Once initial pilots are analyzed and new practices are starting to be institutionalized, leaders should consider what other new systems, tools, goals, metrics, and processes have proved successful enough to adopt. These should be regularly reviewed as the organization continues to gain knowledge and experience. Leaders may want to expand the central orchestration team to include representation from other internal groups. And they may want to consider connecting their workforce ecosystems with others — for example, working more closely with client organizations and their ecosystems. Culturally, leaders may consider more actively promoting distributed learning and workforce ecosystem activities through storytelling and other communication tools. They will likely want to highlight growth opportunities while also beginning to address the myriad concerns that inevitably accompany such transformations.</p><p> This four-phase approach offers a practical way to engage, connect, and activate key stakeholders. From there, organizations can begin to shape their own strategies and pathways by experimenting with new types of integration architectures and quickly iterating as they learn what does and doesn&#39;t work across different contexts.</p><p> Echoing the way that integration architectures define how internal functions and business units work together to orchestrate workforce ecosystems, leaders need to define how to govern relationships with external contributors. Leaders face several decisions about which integration architectures are appropriate for external contributors.</p><p> The choice of third-party integration architectures may determine the degree to which partners are willing to expend resources to participate in (or contribute to) the workforce ecosystem. Decisions around how to coordinate with developer ecosystems, for instance, can be critical to effective workforce ecosystems. Google Play is Google&#39;s distribution marketplace for apps and content. In comparison to Apple&#39;s App Store, through which Apple distributes apps and content, Google has a lighter touch, with less-strict requirements and compliance testing. Apple&#39;s policies are known to be much more stringent. Integration architectures with external developers may have more or less rigidity and be more or less welcoming.</p><p> Crafting integration architectures with third parties raises questions about who should own these relationships within the enterprise. For example, video game console manufacturers often enable third-party developers (complementors) to create games that work on their systems; frequently, it is the demand for these third-party games that drives sales of particular consoles. Should developer relations be the responsibility of a business development or strategy group (that may also handle strategic alliances) or a separate group with specific responsibilities for developer ecosystems? An integration architecture helps define responsibilities and adjudicate potential conflicts among internal groups with competing interests.</p><p></p><p> Implementing integration architectures in your organization begins with an assessment of how your workforce ecosystem currently functions. How much visibility and control does your organization&#39;s HR function currently have over internal and external contributors? If these contributors are currently managed in a decentralized manner, evaluate whether your organization is best served by this architecture.</p><p></p><p> If you recognize that a more centrally integrated and orchestrated workforce ecosystem would be a better approach for your organization, decide which groups and individuals should be part of the orchestration team. Should someone (or some group) be centrally responsible for overseeing the entire workforce ecosystem?</p><p> Throughout our research, we have heard leaders describe their struggles to engage talent essential to their company&#39;s success within an increasingly complex and connected workforce ecosystem. We have observed time and again that intentionally orchestrating a workforce ecosystem perspective can help leaders take a much richer and more nuanced view of their own organization and the people, partners, and technologies upon which they rely to meet their strategic goals and objectives.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian is coleader and cofounder of the Workforce Sciences Institute and a former senior partner at Mercer.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com The Research The author conducted the research underlying this article while coleading Mercer’s Workforce Sciences Institute.i The author analyzed results of his research team&#8217;s statistical analyses of three to five years of employee data for 20 large and midsize, mostly global, employers representing manufacturing and services companies in a range of industries, including [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Nalbantian_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The author conducted the research underlying this article while coleading Mercer&#39;s Workforce Sciences Institute. <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a></li><li> The author analyzed results of his research team&#39;s statistical analyses of three to five years of employee data for 20 large and midsize, mostly global, employers representing manufacturing and services companies in a range of industries, including consumer and industrial products, pharmaceuticals, technology, financial services, and professional services. Collectively, these companies employed over 700,000 people. About 40% of the employees were based in the United States.</li></ul></aside><p> Business leaders tend to focus their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) efforts on addressing bias and discrimination because these practices are pervasive and discrimination is illegal. But in the process, they overlook situational factors that play a leading role — and are easier to address — in determining whether women and people of color get promoted and are among the higher paid.</p><p> Career and pay equity are inextricably linked. Women and people of color continue to be underrepresented among managers and executives, and often among senior professionals as well. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> While pay equity is improving for these demographic groups, the raw pay gaps (average and median differences between women and men, and between people of color and White employees) remain high in many companies. These pay gaps will persist until women and people of color occupy the career levels and roles that command the highest pay at a rate that reasonably reflects their representation in the workforce.</p><p></p><p> Inequity not only hurts individual employees; it also deprives businesses of the talent that is overlooked. If leaders understand how situational factors affect their employees&#39; prospects for advancement, they can apply <em>proactive career management (PCM)</em> — identifying and removing barriers to employee success — to make their workplaces more equitable and more productive.</p><p> To better understand the factors underlying these differences in career outcomes, I examined the results of analyses of multiple years of promotion, retention, performance, and pay data in 20 large and midsize companies that collectively employed more than 700,000 people. The findings confirmed that significant gender and racial differences in promotion probability for women and people of color are attributable to four factors that are consistently consequential to employees&#39; success: performance ratings, role assignments, reporting relationships, and flexible working arrangements.</p><p> With the exception of performance ratings, these factors are related to an employee&#39;s circumstances, not their knowledge, skills, or behavior. For instance, if career progress requires experience in certain roles but women are proportionally underrepresented in those roles relative to men, the net result is that fewer women will advance.</p><p> Certainly, bias and discrimination are also in play: In most of the organizations, we found large, unexplained gender and racial disparities in the likelihood of promotion that cannot be accounted for by any business-relevant factors. And we found universal and sizable racial disparities in performance evaluations, with people of color, particularly Black employees, less likely to receive high ratings. These are a logical focus for corporate diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts because they are evidence of bias or discrimination.</p><p> But because the explained differences often have the greatest influence on career advancement and pay equity, it&#39;s important to address them directly. The good news is that these factors are often the easiest to address successfully. Proactive career management is a data-driven approach that offers a solution that works.</p><h3> Four Factors Drive Who Advances at Work</h3><p> Let&#39;s look more closely at the four factors I identified that explain who receives promotions, high performance ratings, and larger pay increases at work and why women and people of color tend not to see those benefits.</p><p> <strong>Performance ratings.</strong> Because performance ratings affect all other outcomes, such as promotion, retention, and pay, disparities in this area have a cascading effect. In 89% of the companies studied, Black employees were less likely to receive high performance ratings. The differences can be sizable, with the majority at 25% or higher. Moreover, because performance ratings tend to persist from year to year — a high rating one year predicts the likelihood of a high rating the next — the tendency for people of color to get lower ratings becomes a virtual blockade to their progress. Interestingly, women are generally more likely to be highly rated than otherwise comparable men, but that doesn&#39;t translate into a higher probability of promotion for them.</p><p> <strong>Access to accelerator roles.</strong> In every company, certain roles are career accelerators and others are dead ends, regardless of who occupies them. In this study, having a supervisor role at any level almost universally improved the chance that an employee would be promoted and receive high ratings. However, we almost always found that women and people of color were far less likely to be in such roles than men or White employees, respectively.</p><p> The differences are often stark and steep. For example, in a global financial services company we studied, US-based employees who were supervisors were 50% more likely to be promoted and 55% more likely to receive high performance ratings than those who were not supervisors. Outside the US, supervisors were 89% more likely to be promoted and 37% more likely to get high ratings. These effects were even larger for female supervisors than for male supervisors. But across the company, women were half as likely to be supervisors. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2个</a></p><p>Further, because women are more likely than men to face career disruption during their child-rearing years, they may take on supervisor roles later. In such cases, they don&#39;t experience the same compounding benefit of being in such roles as their male colleagues.</p><p> <strong>Reporting relationships.</strong> Whom one reports to can have a decisive impact on the trajectory of one&#39;s career. We generally found that people who reported to supervisors with high performance ratings were significantly more likely to receive a high rating as well. The probability that they would be promoted also increased.</p><p> We saw similar effects for employees whose managers were higher up in the corporate hierarchy than the norm for someone at their level and thus had more clout. To the extent that women and people of color are less likely to report to high-performing and higher-level supervisors, they are less likely to receive high ratings or promotions themselves.</p><p> They may also be less likely to benefit from these relationships when they do have them. At a global insurance company, those who reported to a top-rated supervisor were about 50% more likely to be promoted and 30% more likely to receive high performance ratings. Those whose supervisors were at a level higher than the norm were 9% more likely to be promoted and 14% more likely to be highly rated. However, having a high-performing or higher-ranked supervisor did not help women and people of color as much as it helped White men.</p><p> <strong>Flexible working.</strong> Increasingly, organizations view flexible work arrangements as essential to attracting and retaining talent, particularly women and younger employees. Since the COVID-19 pandemic, more companies and employees have embraced such arrangements, but historically, they have been career killers. For example, those who work part time or remotely or take family leave are less likely to be promoted, are paid less, and are more likely to leave their companies.</p><p> At a business I&#39;ll refer to as ConsumerCo, opting for flexible work arrangements hurt both women and people of color. The percentage of women working part time was three times that of men; for people of color, it was two times that of White employees. Overall, working part time reduced promotion probability by 50% and the likelihood of receiving a high rating by 70%. It also increased turnover probability by 25% compared with similarly situated full-time workers.</p><p> Likewise, leaves of absence were disproportionately taken by women and people of color. Those on leave were about 50% less likely to be promoted or receive high ratings and much more likely to turn over — at least 150% more likely in the US and at least 80% more likely globally. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Unless companies do something to mitigate the negative consequences of flexible working on employees, the phenomenon of higher levels of flexible work arrangements risks further undermining career progress for women and people of color.</p><h3> The Case for Proactive Career Management</h3><p> With the exception of performance ratings, these drivers of career progress, or lack thereof, are situational. This is telling. It indicates that whether employees advance is not just a reflection of the talents and skills they bring or what they do, but also of how well their employers position them to succeed. All too often, women and people of color simply aren&#39;t positioned to succeed in the same way their White male counterparts are.</p><p> This is not to say that bias and discrimination are not factors, as mentioned above. However, employers can make measurable progress on DEI when they understand the extent of the positioning issues in their workforce and deal with them in a purposeful, systematic way. This is where PCM comes into play.</p><p></p><p> The idea behind proactive career management for DEI is simple: Identify and rank the factors that most influence career success and retention; if and where they skew significantly against certain demographic groups, intervene to eliminate or reduce the disparities. In other words, work to ensure that demographic characteristics bear no relationship to how well or poorly positioned an employee is to stay and succeed at work.</p><p> Every organization has talent flows that shape their workforce. Employers hire, train, and develop employees. And they value employees by giving them promotions, high ratings, raises, and other forms of compensation for the knowledge, capabilities, behavior, and experience they bring, the effort they deliver, and, ultimately, how they perform. Meanwhile, employees&#39; decisions to stay or leave are influenced by whether their careers are progressing.</p><p> These talent flows and rewards define the internal labor market of an organization and produce the supply of people with the attributes needed to meet the demands of the business. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> But as we have seen, different demographic groups within an organization do not have the same opportunities to acquire these attributes or be rewarded for them.</p><p> By not distributing opportunities equitably, companies effectively restrict their talent supplies. Women and people of color become more likely to leave or, if they stay, become less engaged because their careers are stalled. Knowing how the internal labor market functions for different demographic groups within an organization is thus crucial for a company to execute its DEI strategy.</p><p> To implement PCM, organizations should start by creating a success profile that identifies and ranks the factors that drive who advances. From there, they can examine how each factor influences the probability that employees from different demographic groups get promoted and whether the organization is valuing their capabilities and efforts equitably.</p><p></p><p> Small organizations might rely on the four factors described in the previous section. For them, controlled, statistical analyses of their own internal labor market data are likely infeasible. Such organizations might complement the research with qualitative input about the keys to career progress from their leaders and employees who have successfully risen in the ranks there.</p><p> Large employers with complex organizations will be best served by developing an objective success profile based on empirical evidence that identifies and ranks the critical individual and situational factors that drive success in the organization. The natural place to start is with the factors that drive promotions. But organizations might examine other markers of success as well, like pay, ratings, and retention, to see how well the results align with those from the analysis of promotions.</p><p> After creating the profile, the next step is to examine how the profile plays out for different demographic groups. There are two questions to answer.</p><p> First, are the factors that most influence employee success distributed similarly across demographic groups, or do they tend to be concentrated more in some groups than in others? These are <em>quantity effects</em> , and they reflect the relative frequency of the factors across groups. For instance, are women and people of color as likely as men and White employees to have the prized characteristics or to work in circumstances associated with success?</p><p> Second, when people possess the prized characteristics or work in favored circumstances, do they benefit equally from those attributes, or do some demographic groups benefit more? These are <em>price effects</em> . They reflect whether the employer values the attribute, behavior, or situation in question differently for one group than for another.</p><p> Objectively answering these questions is the foundation of PCM, as illustrated in the case of ConsumerCo.</p><p></p><h3> Positioning Employees for Success at ConsumerCo</h3><p> ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders were committed to improving career and pay equity in both their salaried and front-line workforces.</p><p> The company recognized that having a diverse workforce was not a luxury or a concession to social good; it was essential to its success. With an increasingly diverse customer base and growth occurring mostly in markets outside the US and Europe, having a leadership team and a workforce well attuned to the preferences and norms of local cultures was important to achieving growth targets.</p><p> HR and DEI leaders modeled their workforce data to uncover and assess the success profile for their salaried workforce. They identified 12 factors that were most likely to predict whether someone would be promoted. Situational factors dominated this success profile — a finding that stunned company leaders, who viewed the culture as a meritocracy. Of the top 12, only performance ratings and tenure were specific to the talents or accomplishments of an individual employee. The rest were purely circumstantial.</p><p> Being an expat (working outside one&#39;s home country) was the most positively influential factor. Reporting to a supervisor at a higher level than is typical had the least impact among the top 12 factors, but the effect was statistically significant.</p><p> Other factors included three of the four described earlier: having a high performance rating, being in a supervisory role, and reporting to a highly rated supervisor. In addition, working in certain functions or business lines mattered a lot to how one&#39;s career progressed.</p><p> Similar modeling showed that even the probability of receiving a high rating was inordinately influenced by situational factors. This finding suggested that performance ratings were not accurate measures of individuals&#39; contributions.</p><p> When ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders mapped the success profile to women in the company, they found that when women were positioned in situations conducive to their future progress, they usually fared as well as men. But overall, they were less likely to be so positioned. (See “Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile.”) For instance, women who were expats were more likely to be promoted from those roles than otherwise comparable men, but women were less represented among the expat population.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile</h4><p class="caption"> A global consumer products retailer identified the 12 attributes that most strongly influenced whether an employee would be promoted. It found that in most cases, when women possessed any of these attributes, they were as likely to be helped by it as men were. However, women were less likely than men to possess 9 of the 12 attributes. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.) </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:45%;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Traits Favorable to Promotion<br /> <span class="normal">(in order of impact)</span></th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Likelihood That Women Possess Trait Compared With Men</th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Relative Impact of Trait Compared With Men</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>1. Being an expat</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>2. In Function M</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>3. In Function C</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>4. In Country A</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>5. In Bonus Plan F</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong style="color:crimson;">降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>6. In Function H</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>7. In Function S</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>8. Receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>9. Supervisor receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>10. Being a supervisor</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>11. Longer tenured</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>12. Reporting up</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>Similar</strong> </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Nalbantian_Table_1.png" alt="Mapping Women’s Experiences to a Success Profile" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p> Being a supervisor is also an important stepping stone to success at ConsumerCo, but the company learned that women were less represented in supervisor roles. When they did have those roles, it did not help their careers to the same extent as comparable men, for reasons that were not clear. ConsumerCo leaders could see that female employees faced a double whammy of sorts: Not only were they blocked from this accelerator role, but they also didn&#39;t get the same lift to their promotion prospects as their male colleagues when they did have that role.</p><p> When the company looked at people of color, it found that they tended to be both less well positioned and less valued than White employees. ConsumerCo needed to change its internal labor market dynamics to achieve career and pay equity for women and people of color.</p><h3> A Checklist for Change</h3><p> Focusing on situational factors has a distinct advantage: They&#39;re easier to address than individual characteristics. For instance, although tenure is an important driver of success, it is a fact of people&#39;s employment history, not something that ConsumerCo could change overnight.</p><p> Still, ConsumerCo identified several areas where it could act reasonably quickly, such as changing reporting relationships for women and people of color, finding opportunities for them to gain more supervisory experience earlier in their careers, and addressing the disparities in performance ratings for people of color.</p><p> The company had found that taking a leave of absence thwarted career advancement, especially for women, and so it is also developing new leave and career development policies to address imbalances for that group.</p><p> Here&#39;s where the “proactive” part of PCM comes in.</p><p> The analysis of ConsumerCo&#39;s success profile made it possible to create a simple checklist of green lights (career advancers) and red flags (success blockers) that managers could use to evaluate the positioning of individual employees. By considering whether women and people of color on their teams were experiencing more green lights or red flags, line managers and supervisors could identify who was well positioned to stay and thrive, as well as who might be at risk of stalling in their career or leaving the organization. (See “Green Lights, Red Flags.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Green Lights, Red Flags</h4><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> A global consumer products retailer created a checklist of attributes that help or hurt employees&#39; career progress. Managers use the checklist to identify whether women and people of color on their teams are well positioned to advance or might be at risk of stalling in their careers or leaving the organization. They can then take any steps needed to increase access to success drivers and mitigate unintended consequences. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.)</p><h4 style="color:#43BD29;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> GREEN LIGHTS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>FAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceptional” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being more tenured than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceeds” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being younger than comparable peers</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being an expat<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being a supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in function M, C, S, or H<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in bonus plan F or L<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a higher-level supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a top-rated supervisor</p><h4 style="color:crimson;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> RED FLAGS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>UNFAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Having a longer time in grade than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being part time<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Recently on leave<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Receiving a “medium” rating</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working in distribution<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working on the night shift<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Not in top brands<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Experienced a change in supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a female supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being on teams with more older colleagues (reduces promotion likelihood, but increases chances of getting top rating)<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a supervisor with a larger number of direct reports</p></article></aside></div><p> Meanwhile, HR and DEI leaders used the analysis to evaluate at the aggregate level how employees from different demographic groups were positioned to succeed. For each factor, they could effectively evaluate the situational reality of different groups and tailor their interventions to address the most significant gaps.</p><p> For instance, they found that female, Black, and Hispanic employees were less likely to be reporting to highly rated supervisors, while Asian employees were more likely to have this advantage. And although women were less likely to be reporting to a manager one grade higher than usual, there were no such disparities for people of color. Also, while every non-White racial group was significantly underrepresented in one of the core functions that most contributed to advancement, women were more likely to work in that function than men.</p><p> ConsumerCo is in the early stages of rolling out interventions to address its disparities. But other companies I have worked with have pursued a variety of solutions.</p><p> Closing gaps due to flexible work arrangements often requires changing the culture. In many companies, part-time work is looked upon as evidence of lower commitment, and it can be difficult to shake these perceptions. However, companies can make quick progress on pay if they stop factoring leaves of absence into the statistical models that they use to assess pay equity and adjust wages and salaries to close gaps.</p><p> Situation-based racial disparities in performance ratings have been reduced in some companies through the calibration process used to align ratings by different supervisors. Some have also eliminated forced rankings that provide for a very limited percentage of employees to receive top ratings. These tend to favor people with more tenure, whom supervisors have known longer, and presumably better — and who are more likely to be White.</p><p> Some clients have addressed the importance of supervisor roles by expanding training, both to reinforce the importance of these roles and to help supervisors understand the impact they have on employees&#39; prospects. Leaders can offer training to help women and people of color gain the experience they need to advance — and close the gap between women and men in these positions.</p><h3> Proactive Career Management Has Benefits and Risks</h3><p> Because a success profile is built from an organization&#39;s data, it is more likely to reflect reality than the assumptions that leaders make about how employees succeed. Leaders may be prone to thinking that what got them to the top could get anyone else there as well, and they may oversimplify their own path. Further, people tend to generalize based on their own experiences, even if they don&#39;t represent the organizational norm.</p><p> A good empirical model can counter the tendency of people to engage in wishful thinking or to cling to belief. It can also account for the effects of being in different business lines, functions, geographies, and job families. This is something that&#39;s hard to do based on personal observation and experience alone.</p><p></p><p> Another value of PCM is that it is grounded in what creates value for the business. If, for instance, a role becomes critical to growth, one would expect the employer to accord more value to that role and the employees who successfully deliver value in it. And to the extent that an organization&#39;s DEI strategy helps ensure that high-potential women and people of color are able to access these newly valuable roles and perform them ably, it will serve the greater business need.</p><p> If there is a downside to PCM, it relates to the sharing of sensitive data and intelligence. PCM proceeds from objective modeling of the drivers of success and how they affect different groups. Invariably, the models will surface potentially damaging information about the existence of systemic gender or racial disparities in outcomes and opportunities, which creates legal risk.</p><p> PCM works best when managers understand the realities uncovered by the models and the reasons why specific actions are warranted. Thus, it requires a reasonable level of transparency. Corporate legal departments may, however, object to exposing what they may believe to be strong evidence of bias and inequity.</p><p> There&#39;s a delicate balance to be achieved. Most organizations I work with accomplish it by sharing high-level information with business and line leaders, and sometimes employee groups, about the reasons for particular actions while restricting the more granular data to a smaller group of top executives and HR and DEI leaders. Legal counsel almost always presides over such decisions; however, such advisers have become more understanding of the need for data-driven DEI strategies, appreciating that people can&#39;t solve problems they don&#39;t know about or understand.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The unexplained disparities in career opportunity and advancement at many organizations are important to address because they signal the potential influence of bias and discrimination. But doing so should not override attention to differences that can be explained by legitimate, business-relevant factors. The surest, most sustainable way to create career equity and equitable representation across all levels of an organization is to address the organization&#39;s career development practices (or lack thereof) that systemically impede the progress of women and people of color.</p><p> Of course, the work that employees do, their knowledge and skills, and how hard and effectively they work influence whether they will succeed. But success is also determined by how individuals are positioned to succeed — and organizations can do better at ensuring that all high-potential talent can gain experiences that will set them up for growth.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>