<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 11 月 14 日星期二 12:00:11 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title> RAI 项目是否为第三方和生成式人工智能做好了准备？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Infographic]]></category><category><![CDATA[Policy Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[In 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review and BCG completed their second year of researching responsible AI (RAI). In addition to producing a series of articles that draw on insights from an expert panel and a survey-based research report, the team has highlighted its key findings in this infographic. Although many organizations are prioritizing RAI and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> 2023 年，<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和 BCG 完成了<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">负责任人工智能 (RAI) 研究</a>的第二年。除了根据专家小组的见解和基于调查的研究报告撰写一系列文章外，该团队还在该信息图中强调了其主要发现。</p><p>尽管许多组织正在优先考虑 RAI 并开发程序来负责任地管理人工智能工具，但大多数公司依赖第三方 AI 工具（他们购买、访问或许可的工具，包括 ChatGPT 和 Bard 等生成式 AI 工具）具有重大风险。显然，大多数组织还没有准备好应对这些新风险，但我们的研究使我们能够制定一套建议来帮助他们正确实施 RAI。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何在棘手的话题上有效地表达不同意见</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenji Yoshino and David Glasgow. <p>Kenji Yoshino ( <a href="https://twitter.com/kenji_yoshino">@kenji_yoshino</a> ) 是纽约大学法学院首席大法官厄尔·沃伦宪法学教授，也是梅尔策多样性、包容性和归属感中心的教职主任。 David Glasgow ( <a href="https://twitter.com/dvglasgow">@dvglasgow</a> ) 是梅尔策多样性、包容性和归属感中心的执行主任，也是纽约大学法学院的兼职教授。他们是<cite>《说正确的事：如何谈论身份、多样性和正义》</cite> （Atria Books，2023 年）的合著者，本文正是基于该书。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cultural Differences]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com &#160; Conversations about identity, diversity, and justice are some of the thorniest human interactions of our time. Consider Uber’s head of diversity, who hosted a workplace event titled “Don’t Call Me Karen” to highlight the “spectrum of the American White woman’s experience” and foster an “open and honest conversation about race.” Following backlash [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Yoshino_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼尔·韦伯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p></p><p>关于身份、多样性和正义的对话是我们这个时代最棘手的人类互动之一。以 Uber 的多元化负责人为例，她举办了一场名为“别叫我凯伦”的工作场所活动，以强调“美国白人女性的经历谱系”，并促进“关于种族的公开和诚实的对话”。由于有色人种员工的强烈反对，她被安排休假。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>或者想想斯坦福大学法学院负责多样性的副院长，他在保守派法官凯尔·邓肯的演讲中试图“缓和”学生的抗议活动。院长试图安抚因法官的反 LGBTQ+ 观点而愤怒的学生，同时给法官完成演讲的空间。但她的干预引起了公众的愤怒，因为人们认为她将学生的感受置于法官的言论自由权之上。她也被安排休假。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p>如果这些对话阻碍了高级多元化、公平和包容性 (DEI) 专业人士的发展，那么普通领导者还有什么希望呢？比你想象的还要多。</p><p>我们领导纽约大学法学院的一个研究中心，致力于研究多样性、包容性和归属感问题。我们共同或单独教导了来自各行各业的数以万计的人如何跨越差异进行更有意义和有效的对话。我们集中精力指导掌权者，因为他们有最大的机会改变这些互动的动态——培养同理心，而不是引发恐惧和分裂。</p><p>虽然我们辅导的人在多种类型的身份对话中遇到困难，但分歧往往是最令人痛苦的。当你和对方意见一致时，参与身份对话相对容易。当你不同意时，你可能会充满焦虑和自我怀疑。你可能会想：<em>我真的像我想象的那样开明吗？人们会感到被我伤害或背叛吗？</em></p><p>你可能会想通过屈服于谈话伙伴所说的任何内容来应对这种焦虑。然而这种做法往往并不可取，因为它损害了你的尊严和真实性。我们相信，即使在当今两极分化和过热的政治气候下，在身份问题上仍然可能存在分歧。关键是要尊重地去做。就是这样。</p><h3>在争议等级上找到对话</h3><p>我们都是同性关系——Kenji 于 2009 年与他的丈夫结婚，David 于 2014 年与他的丈夫结婚——而且我们在许多论坛上参与了有关同性婚姻的辩论。我们从来不喜欢这些讨论，但我们发现其中的一个特点特别糟糕：我们的对手很少承认这场辩论对我们或其他 LGBTQ+ 人群意味着什么。</p><p>在一本反对婚姻平等的著名著作中，作者坚持认为，人们可以拒绝同性婚姻，“但不要诋毁受同性吸引的人，或忽视他们的需求”。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>他们在现场对话中采取了相同的立场。在一场有关同性婚姻的电视辩论中，主持人要求作者之一瑞安·安德森（Ryan Anderson）向女同性恋财务顾问苏兹·奥曼（Suze Orman）解释“她出了什么问题”。 “我不认为你有什么问题，”安德森告诉奥曼。 “问题是，什么是婚姻？我认为婚姻本质上是……一男一女的结合。” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>尽管这听起来很外交，但这种回应并没有意识到，从许多同性恋者的角度来看，安德森反对同性婚姻在逻辑上意味着他认为奥曼是二等公民。然而，在我们关于这个话题的无数次对话中，我们可以用一只手数出对方认识到我们可能会认为他们的观点是对我们基本人性的攻击的次数。这种方法并不要求他们改变观点。它只是要求他们承认这种观点可能会如何传播到另一方。</p><p>部分由于这种挫败感，我们开发了一个争议量表，将分歧的主题沿直线绘制出来。左边是最安全的话题，在这些话题中存在分歧是可以预料的，甚至是值得庆祝的。右边是最有争议的话题，对话最有可能变得丑陋。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>如何表达不同意见</h4><p class="caption">在这种争议规模上定位对话主题可以帮助您在更有可能进行尊重性讨论的层面上构建一个困难的主题。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Yoshino_Essay_Winter_2024_Figure-1.png" alt="如何表达不同意见" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>关于个人品味的分歧通常是温暖而善意的。当朋友嘲笑我们喜欢垃圾电视节目时，这些分歧会加强而不是削弱我们的关系。对事实的分歧也相对舒服，只要这确实是关于事实的辩论（例如谁、什么、何时、何地或如何），而不是关于价值观的几乎不加掩饰的辩论（被定义为“另类事实”或“假新闻”） ）。当话题在争议规模上进一步向右漂移时，真正的危险就来了。最激烈的对话是其中一方或双方都感到他们的平等人性受到质疑的对话。</p><p>想象一下，您是工作场所多元化和包容性倡议的拉丁裔支持者，而您正在与反对该计划的非拉丁裔同事进行辩论。我们认为，讨论该倡议是否成功地提高了拉丁裔在工作场所的代表性（事实），您会觉得不舒服，但可以控制。您会发现很难争论是否应在晋升决策（政策）中考虑多样性因素。你会发现争论心理学家理查德·赫恩斯坦和政治学家查尔斯·默里臭名昭著的假设，即智商在种族和族裔群体之间存在差异（人性平等）是令人痛苦的。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>身份分歧的问题在于，特权较高的对话伙伴几乎总是将问题定位在争议规模上的不同位置，而不是特权较少的对话伙伴。如果您认为您的公司过于关注反种族主义，您可能会将这场争议视为关于组织应如何优先考虑其使命的不同方面的政策辩论。你的谈话对象是一位亚裔美国同事，她可能会认为你轻视了她对公司的归属感。毕竟，她是那个必须与工作场所的反亚裔偏见作斗争的人。您将该问题定位在“政策”争议范围的中间位置。她将其定位于“人性平等”的右极端。</p><p></p><p>您可能会发现，在认识到对方在争议范围内的位置后，您会重新评估分歧的性质，使问题更接近他们所定位的位置。但你可能不会，我们也不会强迫你这样做。我们所要求的只是您明确承认对方的立场。在谈话开始时，你可能会这样说：“对我来说，这是一场政策辩论，但我知道这对你来说可能是非常个人化的，在分享我的观点时，我会尽力尊重这一现实。 ”有时，在谈话期间或之后，您可能会意识到自己将这个话题视为纯粹的智力练习，并且需要认识到讨论可能对对方产生的影响：“我一直在将政策论点摆到桌面上，但我能问一下，作为一个生活可能更直接受到这个问题影响的人，你对这次讨论有何感受？”</p><p>我们认为，您会惊讶地发现，承认自己的相对主题立场可以在多大程度上消除分歧带来的伤害或激烈情绪。即使这些立场对双方来说都是显而易见的，这一点仍然成立。通常，我们需要的不是更多的知识，而是对共享知识的更多认可。</p><p></p><h3>发现不常见的共同点</h3><p>在 1987 年的电影<cite>《铁血战士》</cite>中，达奇（阿诺·施瓦辛格饰演）和狄龙（卡尔·韦瑟斯饰演）以史诗般的握手方式互相打招呼。 “狄龙，你个王八蛋。”达奇说道，他们走到对方面前，双手紧握在一起，粗壮的手臂摆成V字形，就像要扳手腕一样。他们拒绝放开彼此的手。然后握手就变成了一场真正的扳手腕比赛。这几乎是对过度阳刚之气的模仿。</p><p>如果不是病毒式传播的模因，这个场景可能已经被遗忘了。当社交媒体用户想要展示两个看似无关的人、团体或概念却有着惊人的共同点时，他们会发布一张达奇和狄龙握手的照片。他们在达奇的手臂上贴了一个标签，在狄龙的手臂上贴了另一个标签，并将共同点放在中间。在一个例子中，复仇和冰淇淋就“冷食最佳”这句话握手言和。史诗般的握手还催生了其他尝试，使用维恩图来突出不可预测的重叠。我们了解到，银行劫匪、DJ 和传教士都在分享“举起手来”。这些图像帮助我们看到每场扳手腕比赛中隐藏的握手。</p><p>这种能力至关重要，而且培养这种能力比看起来更难。传统观点认为，当与某人意见不同时，提供一致意见是一种有效的策略。但正如哲学家丹尼尔·丹尼特（Daniel Dennett）指出的那样，找到“并非普遍或广泛同意的问题”的观点特别有帮助。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>这个想法是为了找到不常见的共性，让你从默认的情况中感到惊讶。很多时候，人们会满足于那些感觉像是空洞的平淡的举动。这就像发布银行劫匪、DJ 和传教士表情包，并将这些共性变成“职业”。</p><p>相反，尝试找到不常见的共性，这些共性可以解放你和你的谈话伙伴，并有助于使最具煽动性的话题更容易讨论。近年来，成群结队的忧心忡忡的家长涌入通常沉闷的市政厅会议，对在孩子的教室里进行的有关种族的谈话表示愤怒。巴特·格拉斯哥（Bart Glasgow）就是这样一位家长（与大卫没有关系），他是一位来自佐治亚州坎顿的保守派福音派基督教白人，他在一次学校董事会会议上发言反对在当地学区雇用一名 DEI 管理员。</p><p></p><p>巴特和他的妻子科利决定与四位专家就种族问题进行交谈。其中之一是卡罗尔·安德森（Carol Anderson），她是埃默里大学非裔美国人研究教授兼主席，也是多本书的作者，其中包括<cite>《白色愤怒》</cite> 。从表面上看，安德森和格拉斯哥夫妇没有什么共同之处。然而，在长达一个小时的谈话中，双方都付出了相当大的努力来寻找联系点。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>巴特·格拉斯哥指出，他的大学毕业论文主题是公民抗命，研究了亨利·大卫·梭罗、圣雄甘地和马丁·路德·金等人物。“我认为金博士所做的事情令人惊叹，”他说。 “遵循圣经的原则，当你受到仇恨时，要转过另一边脸来表达爱。”安德森指出，她的父亲是“职业军人”，并描述了她在教堂和“敬畏上帝”的社区中长大的经历。他们都因家里有<cite>《世界图书百科全书》</cite>和带他们“去柴棚”的父母一起成长的经历而结下了不解之缘。他们继续分享在教育环境中成为少数群体的经历。安德森是黑人，他谈到了被送往一所白人占多数的高中的经历。白人科利·格拉斯哥 (Coley Glasgow) 表示，她在两所历史悠久的黑人大学完成了高等教育。</p><p>这种对共同点的探索得到了回报。随着谈话的继续，他们表达了不同意见。巴特·格拉斯哥反对强调系统性种族主义；安德森不同意。后来，巴特主张发放学券，允许家长将孩子从表现不佳的当地学校转出，但安德森再次不同意。然而这些分歧是非常文明的。谈话结束后，巴特对安德森说：“我可以和你聊几个小时。我真的可以。”安德森回答说：“非常感谢您来到这里，提出这些精彩的问题并参与这次精彩的对话。谢谢。我喜欢它。”</p><p>下次当你遇到分歧时，试着问问自己与谈话伙伴有哪些共同点可能会让他们感到惊讶。如果您正在辩论同性婚姻，您可能会指出许多人（异性恋和同性恋）认为婚姻是一种过时的制度。因此，尽管存在分歧，你们都相信婚姻作为一种制度的重要性。找到这些不常见的共性需要一点聪明才智，有时可能会让人感到费力。但回报是巨大的：找到它们可以让你们双方摆脱本能和无意识的感觉，即你们在谈话中是对手。</p><h3>展示你的作品</h3><p>在我们推出梅尔策多样性、包容性和归属感中心后不久，我们收到了一封来自一位受人尊敬的同事的令人不安的电子邮件。她要求我们利用我们作为多元化和包容性学者的平台，为那些没有为自己或孩子充分接种疫苗的人发声。在她看来，因违反疫苗规定而将人们排除在学校和工作场所之外，会对多样性、包容性和归属感的价值观产生“令人不安”的影响。她邀请我们与她讨论这个问题，以便在整个大学范围内解决这个问题。</p><p>在 COVID-19 大流行使疫苗成为白热化问题之前，我们就收到了这一请求。即便如此，我们知道这次谈话可能会很困难。我们强烈反对她的观点，但我们担心，无论是承认她在争议规模上的立场还是提供一次史诗般的握手都是不够的。</p><p>因此，我们深入分享了我们的推理。我们礼貌但坚定地表示，我们认为反对疫苗不属于我们中心的工作范围。我们解释说，该中心的主要职能是解决针对边缘化社会群体（例如有色人种或女性）的偏见。我们承认，一些群体，比如宗教少数群体，因为他们的信仰而不是因为他们的身体特征而受到虐待。但特别是作为一个新成立的中心，我们并不急于将边缘化群体的定义延伸到根据对单一问题的看法来定义的人们。我们还注意到，疫苗犹豫的话题引发了我们专业知识之外的复杂的医学、伦理和公共卫生问题。</p><p>我们并不抱有任何幻想，认为这种方法会改变我们同事的想法。但这表明我们真正考虑了她的观点，也为她提供了指出我们可能错的地方的机会。她感谢我们深思熟虑的回应，指出她完全理解我们的立场，并邀请我们参加一个单独主题的活动。</p><p>我们对同事询问的方法是展示你的工作的一个例子——也就是说，尽可能详细地解释分歧，向对方证明你已经仔细考虑过这个问题。强调分歧点的建议似乎与我们之前强调寻找共同点的不一致。但你可以而且应该做到这两点——详细寻找共识点并分享分歧点。全面描述您所持不同意见所依据的事实和价值观、任何影响您当前想法的研究和对话，以及您持有的任何剩余疑虑或不确定性。在你的对话伙伴的一生中，他们可能遇到过很多人，他们基于粗制滥造或不完整的工作而本能地反对他们的观点。展示你所付出的努力将使你从那些对手中脱颖而出。这将帮助他们回应你，而不是回应他们过去的所有声音。</p><p>需要注意的是：在展示你的作品时，不要在立即驳回反对意见之前对它进行草率的总结。作家莫伊拉·韦格尔将这个错误比作高中论文的“最后一段第一句话”：“我已经想到了另一面。别怪我没有想到对方！” <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>不要采取这种粗略的方法，而是花时间研究和理解相反的观点，然后慷慨地分享这种理解，然后再解释为什么你仍然以不同的方式看待问题。展示你的作品以表达你的尊重。</p><h3>管理期望</h3><p>一般来说，许多人对分歧的容忍度较低。如果在会议室桌上出现有争议的身份问题，他们会立即改变话题。如果他们与某人发生争执，他们会在脑海中重播这场对话数周。不幸的是，大卫就是这样的人之一。他会逃避表达不同意见以避免冲突，然后独自因对方不同意他的观点而感到沮丧。无论出于何种原因，他似乎有一种不切实际的期望，即身份对话应该始终以集体拥抱结束。</p><p>人们有时会问我们这样痛苦的问题：“我是一个无神论者和坚定的自由主义者，但我团队中的一位同事是一位保守的福音派基督徒。尽管存在分歧，我们如何才能合作？”我们的答案是：降低你的期望。我们承认这个建议可能不会出现在励志海报上。但我们认为，将分歧中的热情强度与关系的强度进行衡量是完全合适的。</p><p></p><p>兰德尔·芒罗 (Randall Munroe) 创作的一幅漫画中，一个火柴人猛烈地敲击着电脑键盘，而另一个房间里传来一个声音：“你要上床睡觉吗？”火柴人回答说：“我不能。这个很重要。网上有人<em>说错了</em>。” <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>大多数人都有足够的视角，不会太在意与随机的互联网巨魔的分歧。但在其他情况下培养这种健康的本能也是值得的。如果我们与配偶在身份问题上存在重大分歧，我们每个人都会陷入困境。尽管如此，我们还是会监督和促进那些与我们意见不同的学生的职业生涯，因为师生关系不如婚姻关系那么密切。对于同事、邻居和熟人来说也是如此。当关系不那么密切时，达成一致的必要性就会降低。</p><p>您还可以管理您对一次对话中可以实现的目标的期望。与围绕某个沉重话题的任何争议一样，身份冲突往往无法在一次遭遇中得到彻底解决。第一次谈话可能会进行得很糟糕，但第二次可能会更好，第三次可能会更好。在取得进展之前，您可能需要通过多个出口和入口来进行对话。</p><p></p><p>当人们与持相反观点的人进行有关身份、多样性和正义的对话时，我们鼓励他们实践我们描述的四种策略：</p><ul><li>在争议范围内找到对话。对你来说，对话可能是事实或政策辩论，但对另一个人来说，这可能是关于平等人性的辩论。</li><li>寻找不常见的共同点——并非广泛共识的共识点。</li><li>展示你对剩余分歧的研究，以证明你已经仔细考虑过这个主题。</li><li>管理你的期望。将你对分歧的关心程度与关系的强度进行衡量。</li></ul><p>尽管我们分享了这些例子，但您可能会认为，通过实践这些策略，您能够在身份问题上达成一致意见，这是不切实际的。确实，他们无法确保所有对话都取得积极成果。但我们相信，如果您遵循这些准则，您会发现对话质量立即得到改善。</p><p></p><p>当然，有时你和对方之间的裂痕会太大。有时，一次尝试的对话可能会在没有解决方案的情况下结束。有时关系本身就会结束。尽管这种结果让人感觉很糟糕，但有时这是必要的。我们并不是要保证每一次分歧都会有圆满结局。相反，我们希望帮助您在摆脱鸿沟之前确保鸿沟确实无法弥合。</p><p>当然，其他时候你可能会以积极的方式感到惊讶。很少有（如果有的话）有意义的关系是没有冲突的。如果处理得当，紧张的时刻可以加深联系。分享深思熟虑的不同意见可以向对方表明你足够重视他们，可以对他们诚实，而不是不真诚地点头或提供虚假的意见。此外，通过建模如何有效地表达不同意见，您可以为整个组织中的其他人如何应对当今最棘手的对话定下基调。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>演示成功的真正衡量标准</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a>是硅谷通信公司<a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a>的首席执行官。她是六本书的作者，包括<cite>《DataStory：解释数据》和《通过故事激发行动》</cite> （Ideapress Publishing，2019 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Historically, it’s been tough to quantify the success of events, presentations, and speeches. We’ve long known that the spoken word is a powerful tool for influence and action, but how do you measure that power? When many organizations flipped from in-person to virtual and hybrid meetings and events, presentation [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Duarte-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>从历史上看，很难量化活动、演示和演讲的成功。我们早就知道口头语言是影响力和行动的强大工具，但如何衡量这种力量呢？</p><p>当许多组织从面对面会议和活动转向虚拟和混合会议和活动时，演示分析成为一种全新的游戏。过去，演讲者主要通过调查人们并阅读房间内的文字来衡量影响力。虽然这些形式的反馈仍然提供有关消息是否以及如何落地的有用信息，但演示者现在可以使用许多其他指标。</p><p></p><p>这是一个简单的例子：几十年来，我的公司为一家大公司的年度软件开发人员大会构建了所有平台。当会议因新冠肺炎 (COVID-19) 疫情而改为远程会议时，我们为虚拟观众重新设计了所有内容（每次分组会议以及主题演讲）。在那次会议之后，组织者对最受欢迎的会议进行了排名，并意识到他们在创建获得 40 次观看次数的会议上投入的精力与创建获得数十万次观看次数的会议所投入的精力是相同的。组织者还获得了积极参与会议的参与者百分比的数据，以及下载和分享的相关数据。结合与会者评论的实质内容，这些见解告诉会议人员哪些主题能引起广泛而深刻的共鸣，帮助他们管理时间投资，并决定他们选择以虚拟方式举行会议。</p><p>这只是您可以进行切片、切块和分析的多种方法之一。但要衡量演示是否成功，您应该<em>衡量</em>什么？在上面的示例中，一个关键的组织目标是让开发人员学习并将新的软件功能构建到产品中，因此会议人员专门关注每个与会者在关键会议中停留的时间、他们在学习会议中的活跃程度，以及他们下载的工具，以及活动结束后开发人员推出了多少应用程序。一旦活动团队知道哪些会议最有用，他们就可以为下一次会议创建更有针对性的内容。</p><p>所有这些标准都衡量某种形式的行动。事实上，这就是所有演讲者都应该寻找的：他们已经推动人们去<em>做某事</em>的证据，无论是学习新技能、采用新的组织文化方法、改变根深蒂固的流程或行为，还是以不同的方式对待客户。</p><p>为了衡量演讲是否成功，您需要在演讲前、演讲中和演讲结束后评估听众的感受和行为。</p><p></p><h3>演讲之前</h3><p>为了定义你所追求的基线结果——也就是说，你希望人们在离开你的演讲后采取什么行动——这有助于了解你的听众。在研究了数百篇强有力的演讲（甚至从斯坦福大学图书馆查阅了追溯到 20 世纪 50 年代的商业演讲）时，我发现他们的大多数<a href="https://www.duarte.com/how-to-write-a-call-to-action-in-a-persuasive-speech/#:~:text=Who's%20in%20Your%20Audience%2C%20and,they%20bring%20to%20the%20table.">行动呼吁都</a>针对四种受众类型之一：<em>实干家</em>，他们可以煽动活动并推动组织内的事情向前发展；<em>供应商</em>，他们可以提供实现预期目标所需的资源和其他类型的支持；<em>有影响力的人</em>，可以动员其他人采用新的想法或方法；或<em>创新者</em>，他们可以产生新的想法并运用他们的智慧来解决问题或抓住机会。</p><p>您将在演讲中针对哪种类型的听众？一旦你弄清楚了关键的“谁”，你就可以分析“什么”和“如何”让人们采用和实施你的想法。具体来说，您可以采取以下方法之一。</p><p><strong>深入了解听众的想法和感受。</strong>问问自己想要接触的人：他们现在对你的想法<em>有何</em>看法？如果他们还没有注意到这一点，那么当他们听到你所说的话时会有<em>什么</em>感觉？您希望他们的想法和感受如何因您的演讲而<em>改变</em>？</p><p></p><p>这不仅仅是一个假想的实事求是的练习。提前收集这些信息——并阐明你想要让人们<em>接受</em>和<em>接受</em>的观点——将决定你提出问题的方式以及可能的回应方式。这可能意味着进行一些研究或调查受众，以评估人们目前对您的主题的了解以及他们对此的感受。例如，您可能会采访最接近您的客户或文化的人。他们对你的想法感到兴奋还是持怀疑态度？他们对此有什么疑问？您不仅会弄清楚您从什么基线开始 - 您还可能获得有关受众的见解，这将有助于您<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-storytelling-techniques-to-bring-your-data-to-life/">精心设计您的信息</a>。您还可以在演示结束后确定一个衡量基准，例如组织的 KPI 之一或重要的人才招聘指标。</p><p><strong>预测情绪症结点。</strong>您试图在受众中引发的转变越大，量化就越困难，特别是如果这是一种情感转变。当你研究听众头脑中当前正在发生的事情时，也要考虑他们的内心。无论论点多么合乎逻辑，证据多么可靠，你的信息中最难让人们接受或处理的部分是什么？您可以识别哪些潜在阻力来源？如果你确实赢得了人们的青睐，你怎么知道你什么时候也赢得了他们的心呢？</p><p>情绪变化通常不会显示在仪表板上。即使允许组织<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/employee-emotions-arent-noise-theyre-data/">跟踪客户或员工情绪的</a>技术也无法收集您需要了解的所有数据。有时，只有当您稍后在新行为中看到情绪阻力时，您才会知道自己已经克服了情绪阻力——例如，当员工停止抵制重要举措时，或者当客户改变主意并购买您的新产品时。</p><h3>演讲期间</h3><p>您可以在演讲进行时评估其成功的可能性。为此，您将通过几种方式衡量受众的反应。</p><p><strong>观察房间内或网上的观众行为。</strong>最直接的测量形式是实时观察人们对演示的反应。当每个人都拿出手机拍摄幻灯片时，您就知道有什么东西吸引了他们的注意力。还要注意，当人们大笑、喘气或鼓掌时——这些基本的行为线索表明<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-data-insights-visually-consumable/">你演讲中的哪些时刻引起了共鸣</a>。科技在这里真的派上用场。如果您的演讲（无论是亲自演讲还是远程演讲）被录音，您可以轻松返回并寻找观众做出明显或可听反应的地方。</p><p><strong>看看参加人数。</strong>如果您在行业聚会等大型活动中向人群发表演讲，另一个有用的指标是在本来可以参加其他会议的情况下出席听您演讲的人数。如果你的物理或虚拟房间挤满了人，这意味着你在开口之前就已经有效地准备好了你的演讲。当我今年在 Salesforce 会议 Dreamforce 上发表演讲时，我的大多数听众都是年轻人，对我的工作不熟悉，但演讲仍然超额订阅，超额与会者聚集在门口。吸引人的不是我的名字，而是我为这条信息命名和构建的方式，这触动了我的神经。当与会者对演讲进行评分时，数据显示它没有辜负标题和项目描述中的承诺。</p><p><strong>激发并跟踪社交参与。</strong>如果您的演讲引起了每个人的热烈讨论，尤其是在大型活动中，他们可能会在社交渠道上实时分享您演示中的引言或图片。请务必将您的社交句柄和特定于事件的主题标签添加到您的幻灯片中，以便您的观众更轻松地标记您，并让您更轻松地跟踪他们最感兴趣的想法。 （这些帖子、评论、点赞、转发和其他即时社交反应稍后可以在活动后报告中捕获。）您还可以通过以易于共享的格式提供重新打包的演示内容来加速和衡量想法的传播例如信息图表或<a href="https://www.duarte.com/resources/books/slidedocs/">幻灯片文档</a>（幻灯片有更多文本，因为它们是供观众阅读而不是简单地由演讲者呈现）。我们的一位技术客户要求我们将他们的主题演讲制作成可浏览的电子书，其中包含脚本和幻灯片视觉效果以及其他材料的可跟踪链接。</p><h3>演讲结束后</h3><p>您的演讲后指标可以跟踪对演示的满意度以及观众为实现想法而采取的一些步骤。</p><p><strong>使用调查来评估受众满意度。</strong>许多演讲者在演讲后使用调查来衡量观众的情绪。如果您在演讲之前也对人们进行了调查，您将能够了解您的演讲是否使听众中的实干家、供应商、影响者或创新者更加接近您的观点。我们合作的一家财富 100 强科技公司也使用观众收视率作为管理工具来激励演讲者表现出色。每个人都想获得尽可能高的分数，而那些得分不好的人可能会在下次演讲时努力提高分数，或者不会被邀请回来。</p><p><strong>检查说话者自己的满意度。</strong>在没有强大衡量文化的公司中，有时最明显的成功标志之一就是演讲者自己认为他们的演讲进行得如何。这可能看起来有些自作多情，但这比大多数人想象的要重要。如果一个领导者不断地提高自己作为沟通者的技能和表现，并且对观众的暗示很敏感，那么他认为自己已经进行了有效的演讲，那么他们的机会实际上很大。而且，嘿，当你的首席执行官想要感觉自己像个摇滚明星，而他们走下舞台时也感觉像个摇滚明星，我称之为胜利。</p><p></p><p><strong>量化所采取的行动。</strong>在这里，您可以回到您定义的基线结果 - 您在开发演示文稿时想要引发或改变的观众行为。虽然满意度和认同等反应很重要，但行动更重要。演讲的目的是说服人们采纳并实施你的想法。因此，请看看您的倡议因您的演讲而获得的关注。您的员工是否填写了人力资源团队在福利演示中提到的注册表？您的销售团队是否下载了您在启动时推出的新公司概述？最终完成了多少笔交易？我在我的幻灯片中嵌入了二维码——大多数人都知道如何使用它们——并分享我的幻灯片。这使得与会者可以对概念进行更深入的“双击”。我的营销团队可以跟踪所有活动以进行会谈后分析。</p><p></p><p>如果您试图阻止某些行为，那么衡量这些行为也很重要。有一年，一家公司聘请了我的团队来帮助他们发布计划重组的消息，这是最难发布的演示文稿之一。高管们尤其担心两种后果：高价值员工沮丧地离职，以及生产力下降。因此，他们决定在公告发布后跟踪两个数据点：未来几个月的辞职人数，以及未来几周客户关系管理数据中反映的生产力下降情况。收到这些报告后，他们欣慰地发现这两个数字都比公司领导层的预期要好得多。在这种情况下，衡量成功意味着在传递精心设计的消息后跟踪<em>缺乏</em>（即消极）行动的情况。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>化学品披露迫在眉睫的挑战</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lori Bestervelt, Colleen McLoughlin, and Jillian Stacy. <p>Lori Bestervelt 博士是前全球运营主管，Colleen McLoughlin 博士、DABT、ERT 是 Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry 毒理学总监。 Jillian Stacy 是 Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry 的业务经理。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Life Cycle]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Practices]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Sam Falconer/theispot.com New and emerging rules in the U.S. and Europe that make companies responsible for the environmental impacts of products through their entire life cycles are forcing brands to confront a striking knowledge gap: their often inadequate understanding of the chemicals found in their supply chains. The European Green Deal’s Circular Economy Action Plan, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bestervelt_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">萨姆·法尔科纳/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>美国和欧洲的新规则要求公司对产品整个生命周期对环境的影响负责，这迫使品牌面临一个巨大的知识差距：他们对其供应链中发现的化学品往往了解不足。</p><p> 2020年3月通过的<a href="https://environment.ec.europa.eu/strategy/circular-economy-action-plan_en">欧洲绿色新政循环经济行动计划</a>；新提出的影响时装和纺织品<a href="https://wwd.com/sustainability/business/legislation-moves-in-the-eu-new-laws-in-france-germany-and-the-netherlands-1235458823/">的生态设计规则</a>；拟议的<a href="https://commission.europa.eu/business-economy-euro/doing-business-eu/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence_en">企业可持续发展尽职调查指令</a>将要求公司披露对人权和环境的任何风险。它们适用于整个产品生命周期，从成分和材料的配方到产品制造、包装和分销以及回收和处置。在美国，加利福尼亚州、科罗拉多州、缅因州和俄勒冈州这四个州已经通过了<a href="https://www.packworld.com/news/sustainability/article/22419036/four-states-enact-packaging-epr-laws">针对包装材料的生产者延伸责任法</a>，该问题将成为美国证券交易委员会最终<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-46">范围 3 供应链要求</a>的焦点。除了此类立法之外，世界各地的司法管辖区还推出了一系列新的监管行动，重点关注<a href="https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billTextClient.xhtml?bill_id=202120220SB54">材料采购和处置</a>、<a href="https://www.nysenate.gov/legislation/bills/2021/S8922">全球供应链安全</a>以及保护员工安全和人权。</p><p></p><p>这些规则对许多制造、营销和销售我们穿的衣服、我们使用的化妆品以及我们孩子玩的玩具的品牌提出了挑战，因为他们的公司对其产品的详细化学成分知之甚少。 。</p><p>面对监管的发展，时尚品牌不得不重新考虑对材料、染料和大量与森林砍伐和污染有关的化学品的使用。他们还需要能够通过供应链中的每个环节追踪这些化合物。</p><p>追踪一件衣服的化学成分并不是一件容易的事，因为一件衣服中使用的数十种物质和材料来自不同的供应商，并在不同的阶段融入到产品中。像牛仔裤这样的基本服装将由来自数十个不同供应商的面料组合、染料、柔软剂、褪色酶、杀菌剂和防腐剂制成，采用不同的配方，需要使用不同的技术来应用。所有这些因素都会在供应链和整个产品生命周期的各个环节造成环境危害。</p><p></p><h3>超越安全数据表</h3><p>销售消费品的知名品牌面临监管机构清理供应链的最大压力。尽管许多公司已公开<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/companies-rush-to-trace-sprawling-supply-chains-as-sustainability-rules-loom-11674512050">承诺</a>提高其可持续性，但获得供应商和合作伙伴所需的合作一直是一个挑战。大多数品牌都依赖其供应商提供的安全数据表 (SDS) 来获取有关产品化学成分的信息。然而，这些文件的主要目的是披露可能伤害供应链中工人或其他人的化学品和化合物的信息。它们没有提供有关产品中使用的每种材料的化学成分的详细信息，也没有提供有关其对回收和处置的影响的任何有意义的见解。</p><p>在我们为一些全球最大品牌进行化学危害评估和产品毒理学分析的过程中，我们审查的 SDS 中大约有三分之一包含有关其所涵盖的产品和材料的化学成分的不完整或不准确的信息。无论这是供应商故意遗漏信息的结果，还是 SDS 作为披露工具的局限性的反映，最终结果是负责这些产品的品牌往往对产品内部的内容一无所知。</p><p>填补 SDS 中提供的基本信息与全球当局即将要求的详细披露之间的差距，已成为许多品牌冲突和困惑的根源。一些供应商不愿意分享详细的化学配方以保护商业秘密，许多品牌也不愿意（或无法）投资于昂贵的化学评估。</p><p></p><p>我们预计这个问题将通过两种方式得到解决。首先，市场可能会转向能够证明其产品和流程安全的供应商。我们已经开始在时尚行业看到这一点：Gucci、H&amp;M、Stella McCartney 和 Zara 等品牌最近承诺从可持续纺织厂<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fashion-giants-vow-to-buy-more-recycled-fibers-in-boost-to-sustainable-textile-mills-11668451031">购买更多回收材料</a>。其次，公司必须投资于详细的化学品筛选，以提供更全面的危害评估和完整的配方披露。随着品牌寻求确定性和评估供应商的客观方法，这种方法也越来越受欢迎。</p><p>在这两种情况下，处于可持续发展转变中心的大品牌的关键目标都是透明度。品牌需要开始与供应商进行坦诚对话，了解其产品中的具体成分以及定期报告和披露的预期内容。他们可能需要增加人员，以便有足够的资源与供应商合作，特别是在寻求将工作关系扩展到第一层之外的情况下。品牌可能还必须协调组织多个部门的信息请求以获得认可。参与整个供应链可能是一项乏味而艰苦的工作。</p><p></p><p>这些并不总是轻松的对话。我们在这里看到的最常见的沟通障碍是保密问题，供应商表示他们太忙了，无法处理客户提出的一系列化学成分问题，以及对询问内容和原因的误解。品牌不一定知道向供应商提出什么要求。他们也不知道在获得信息后如何评估化学品的影响。品牌可能还必须管理多个内部化学品库存系统，并协调不同平台供应商的数据。</p><p>为了让各方达成共识，品牌需要标准化一个流程，以确定要问什么问题、要问谁以及如何管理收集到的信息。品牌还需要向供应商解释为什么这些信息对企业很重要以及他们将如何使用这些信息，以减轻隐私问题。</p><h3>通过数字评估化学品风险</h3><p>正如我们所指出的，当更多品牌无法从供应链合作伙伴那里获得可靠信息时，我们预计更多品牌会提供其产品化学成分的确凿证据。</p><p>提供产品化学风险客观确定性的唯一方法是进行化学危害评估，识别产品生产中使用的特定化学成分，并根据已知毒素的综合列表对其进行筛选，以提供危害评分。不过，它们并不便宜。公司预计每次评估每种物质的花费为 3,000 至 10,000 美元；对于有大量必须仔细审查的科学文献的物质来说，其成本处于该范围的较高端。因为即使是最基本的服装、化妆品、玩具和消费品也含有数十种单独的化学品，因此成本也会迅速上升。</p><p>除了这些成本之外，一旦发现有毒物质，在生产过程中重新装备和更换有毒物质也面临挑战，人们开始清楚地看到，迫在眉睫的最后期限（例如欧洲绿色协议的 2050 年净零排放目标）比看上去要近得多。</p><p></p><p>从供应链中去除有毒物质的过程中关键的第一步是系统地识别它们。例如，我们最近与一个全球鞋类品牌合作开展了一个项目，该品牌的全公司使命是使其橡胶供应链更加环保可持续。首先，它建立了当前化学品库存的综合数据库，并根据其运营所在司法管辖区的已知毒素和受管制化学品清单检查所有条目。只有这样，它才能开始转向更安全的化学品。</p><p>随着品牌的进步，品牌需要将这些机构知识融入到其采购和产品开发流程中，以减轻或消除未来产品在其整个生命周期中的有害化学影响。</p><p>从长远来看，这些举措将带来更安全、更可持续的消费品。然而，在短期内，随着越来越多的品牌开始认识到，在当今以可持续发展为导向的经济中，经过考验的制造和分销方法已不再足够，预计供应链将出现大量中断和重组。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何让人们重新学习技能：语言课</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Carl Clarke, Zsófia Belovai, Michelle Davies, Nicha Surawattananon, and James Elfer. <p>卡尔·克拉克 (Carl Clarke) 是沃达丰的人才、学习、领导力、技能和人员绩效总监。 Zsófia Belovai 是 MoreThanNow 的行为科学主管。米歇尔·戴维斯 (Michelle Davies) 是沃达丰学习、绩效和再培训战略的负责人。 Nicha Surawattananon 是 MoreThanNow 的行为科学家。 James Elfer 是 MoreThanNow 的创始人兼首席执行官。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Reskilling has become an imperative rather than merely a growth opportunity. Technology advancements like generative AI have led the World Economic Forum to project that 44% of employees will experience skill disruptions in 2023. On the surface, organizations seem to be rising to this challenge: Thirty-four percent of Fortune [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Belovai-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>重新培训已成为当务之急，而不仅仅是增长机会。<a href="https://www.ilo.org/global/about-the-ilo/newsroom/news/WCMS_890740/lang--en/index.htm">生成式人工智能</a>等技术进步促使<a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2023/05/future-of-jobs-2023-skills/">世界经济论坛预测，</a>到 2023 年，44% 的员工将经历技能中断。从表面上看，组织似乎正在迎接这一挑战：财富 50 强公司中有 34% 已经进行了再培训和培训根据波士顿咨询集团的研究，提高技能是首要战略优先事项，并指定了年度预算的 1.5% 来支持这些优先事项。</p><p>然而，尽管对学习计划和人才技术平台等再培训基础设施的投资水平很高，但我们发现组织低估了通过有效的敬业度策略<em>改变员工行为的</em>必要性。如果人们不报名参加，那么即使拥有精心设计的再培训计划也对组织没有任何帮助。为了实现转变，领导者必须了解如何以鼓励人们学习的方式将人们与再培训计划联系起来。</p><p></p><p>在咨询公司 MoreThanNow 和全球电信公司沃达丰的行为科学家团队进行的一项实验中，我们发现，虽然大多数领导者将重新技能视为<em>个人</em>进步的机会和/或实现公司战略的手段，但更坦率、自信的信息让他们的技能与数字化未来相关的想法促使更多的人采取行动。我们提供了有关如何改变行为的证据，以帮助领导者将员工与组织在再培训和技能提升方面进行的大量投资联系起来。</p><p></p><h3>职业相关性引起共鸣</h3><p>我们的随机对照实验包括全球 800 名沃达丰员工的样本，旨在确定最能吸引人们探索沃达丰变革案例的语言和动机。我们比较了四种不同的消息类型，介绍了公司的学习产品以及员工应该注册的原因：</p><p> <strong>1. 个人发展：</strong>您将投资自己的职业道路并在数字化未来中蓬勃发展。<br /> <strong>2. 公司战略：</strong>您将帮助沃达丰转型为一家面向数字未来的科技公司。<br /> <strong>3. 学习乐趣：</strong>每天发现新技能和能力时，您会将学习的乐趣融入到工作中。<br /> <strong>4. 职业相关性和安全性：</strong>您将为数字化未来培养技能和能力。</p><p>虽然大多数领导者和组织在谈论再培训时倾向于使用信息 1 和 2，但我们发现，第四条更直接的“职业相关性和安全性”信息对对以技术为中心的角色进行再培训的态度具有最大的积极影响。与收到其他消息的员工相比，收到该消息的员工平均对更广泛的职业选择持更开放的态度，考虑再培训的可能性高出 4.9%，尽管该计划需要时间和精力。虽然这些数字可能看起来很小，但它们具有统计意义，来自语言的无成本变化，并且是可扩展的。</p><p>也许更值得注意的是，实验表明，收到“职业相关性”信息的人更有可能（14.7%）在沃达丰内部网站上探索再培训机会，这提供了一种切实可行的方法来衡量沃达丰员工如何实际投入时间来发展他们的技能。</p><h3>领导者的三个再培训沟通技巧</h3><p>信息 4 通过公开、诚实和明确的关于重新技能的必要性的信息产生了更大的影响。</p><p>数十年的研究表明，为什么损失比收益更大，以及如何将其用作改变思想和行为的有效语言工具。例如，当人们被要求评估失去或获得金钱的情感影响时，他们系统地<a href="https://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/document?repid=rep1&type=pdf&doi=e89e139fc94470c62f0904b69c229816bba4c2ba">认为损失具有更大的影响</a>。同样，在与经济学家进行的<a href="https://www.ssoar.info/ssoar/bitstream/handle/document/28311/ssoar-jebo-2009-3-gachter_et_al-are_experimental_economists_prone_to.pdf?sequence=1">现场实验</a>中，告诉参与者他们将因迟到的会议注册而被罚款的消息比为提前注册提供折扣的消息要有效得多。</p><p>这些研究和我们自己的研究得出了以下三个技巧，可以帮助管理者在人工智能和生成人工智能等颠覆性技术兴起的情况下更有效地与员工讨论重新培训技能的问题。</p><p><strong>设定背景：新兴技术对员工职业生涯的潜在影响要令人放心但保持透明。</strong>诚实地对待人工智能和其他技术对工作角色可能产生的影响的不确定性，而不是只传达其优点。员工常常担心人工智能会抢走他们的工作，但它更有可能改变和扩大他们的工作。谈论如何积极主动地应对这些变化，并参与技能提升和再培训机会，以驾驭变革浪潮。这可以促使员工更积极地尝试探索增加技术知识并相应发展其角色的好处。</p><p><strong>使其相关：给出个人的、具体的例子。</strong>讨论新技术对个人特定工作领域的影响，并概述可能会给团队带来哪些变化。也许您的团队开发演示文稿、处理数据或根据客户反馈采取行动的方式将会改变。确定具体场景将帮助您和您的员工思考不断发展的技术环境中所需的技能，并制定切实可行的行动计划。</p><p><strong>让它成为现实：为未来提供最佳选择。</strong>消息灵通、开放。谈论员工需要将培训计划视为未来的技能，而不是作为一种可有可无的福利。员工很容易迷失在海量的再培训计划信息中，作为经理，您有责任引导他们选择公司提供的最佳未来职业选择。例如，与其说“我希望你考虑一个培训计划来发展你的职业生涯”，不如说“我希望你考虑一个培训计划；未来你的角色的某些部分可能会实现自动化，因此我们需要确保你的技能不断发展。”</p><p></p><p></p><p>沃达丰的实验取得了成功：公司领导者改变了他们的语言，从传达“个人进步”福利改为更坦诚的“职业相关性和安全性”信息。当沃达丰推出第一批再培训计划时，它利用这种预先沟通方式成功吸引了 4,000 名意大利员工。目前，约 300 名员工已成功接受再培训，并从联络中心重新部署到其他内部职能部门。沃达丰员工总共完成了 100 万小时的学习时间。</p><p>我们鼓励领导者效仿沃达丰的做法，以更开放、更直接的方式与员工讨论再培训问题。您的数字化未来以及您的员工成功驾驭变化的世界的能力可能取决于它。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>利用生成式人工智能进行营销：哈佛商学院的 Ayelet Israel</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Market Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[As an associate professor at Harvard Business School and cofounder of the Customer Intelligence Lab at the school’s Digital Data Design Institute, Ayelet Israeli’s work is focused on how data and technology can inform marketing strategy, as well as how generative AI can be a useful tool in eliminating algorithmic bias. One of the products [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>作为哈佛商学院副教授和该校数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的联合创始人，Ayelet Israel 的工作重点是数据和技术如何为营销策略提供信息，以及生成式人工智能如何成为营销策略中的有用工具。消除算法偏差。她最近的工作成果之一是她与两位微软经济学家和研究人员合着的一篇<a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4395751">论文</a>，内容涉及如何使用生成式人工智能来模拟焦点小组和调查以确定客户偏好。</p><p> Ayelet 加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，讨论生成式人工智能在市场研究中的机遇和局限性。她详细介绍了研究的进行方式以及人工智能技术如何帮助营销人员减少与传统客户研究方法相关的时间、成本和复杂性。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E3-Israeli-HBS-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="阿耶莱特·以色列"></p><h4>阿耶莱特·以色列，哈佛商学院</h4><p>阿耶莱特·以色列 (Ayelet Israel) 是哈佛商学院营销部门工商管理学马文·鲍尔 (Marvin Bower) 副教授。她也是该校数字数据设计学院客户智能实验室的联合创始人。她的研究重点是数据驱动的营销，重点是企业如何利用内部数据、客户数据和市场数据来改善结果。她的研究兴趣包括零售、定价策略、渠道管理、营销分析和算法偏差。以色列拥有博士学位。西北大学凯洛格管理学院营销学博士。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>使用生成式人工智能如何帮助我们了解消费者的偏好？在今天的节目中，听听一位教授讲述她的市场研究。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我是哈佛商学院的阿耶莱特·以色列，你们正在听的是<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>大家好。今天，谢尔文和我很高兴阿耶莱特·以色列加入。她是哈佛商学院数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的副教授和联合创始人。 Ayelet，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>非常感谢您邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通常，我们首先会询问客人的职业。但作为一名教授的好处在于人们知道这意味着什么。但我仍然认为很高兴听到一些关于你的背景和简历的信息。那么您能花一点时间介绍一下自己并告诉我们您对什么感兴趣吗？</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>好的。我是哈佛商学院的营销学教授。我真正感兴趣的是我们如何更好地利用数据和人工智能来获得更好的结果，如果这对公司、客户和整个社会都有好处的话。我正在进行的一些工作是围绕人工智能以及企业如何利用它来更好地获取消费者信息和偏好。在我所做的其他工作中，我思考如何消除决策中的算法偏差。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>几个月前我看到了您关于使用生成式人工智能的演讲，这真的让我觉得很有趣，因为很多人都在谈论生成式人工智能，但我们还没有很多证据。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>证据……并不是说它不存在，而是即将到来。但你开始通过你正在进行的这项研究获得一些证据。我们可以在市场研究中使用 GPT 和生成式做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我和我在 Microsoft 的两位同事 Donald Ngwe 和 James Brand 开始思考，我们真的可以使用 GPT 进行市场研究吗？这个想法是，有些人已经证明，你可以通过向 GPT 提出问题来复制非常著名的实验，包括著名的 Milgram 实验。我们在想，“我们作为研究人员和实践者所做的工作就是为了更好地了解客户的偏好；也许我们可以使用 GPT 来实际提取这些类型的偏好。”</p><p>对于大型语言模型，其想法是它们将为您提供最有可能的下一个单词。语言就是这样产生的。我们在想，“也许如果我们要求 GPT 或诱导它在两件事之间做出选择，也许答案（最有可能的下一个词）实际上会反映人群中最可能的反应。从这个意义上说，我们本质上会查询 GPT，但会得到我们在人群中看到的偏好的潜在分布。”我们开始尝试这个想法。我们专注于消费产品——因为我们假设 GPT 所了解的数据主要围绕消费产品，可能来自评论网站或类似的东西——看看这个想法是否真的可行？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>有点！</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>那太棒了。请告诉我们更多信息。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我们的第一反应是，“好吧，让我们看看它是否能产生我们对经济学所期望的非常基本的东西。例如，当价格较高时，它是否知道拒绝报价？它知道在价格和选择之间进行权衡吗？”我们确实看到了一条向下倾斜的需求曲线，这正是我们在查询 GPT 数千次以获得答案时所期望看到的。我们还看到这样的事情，“哦，我们可以告诉它一些关于它的收入的信息，它会对此做出反应。”当它的收入较高时，它对价格的敏感度就会降低，这是有道理的——这也是我们对人们的期望。</p><p>我们还看到，它可以对有关自身的信息做出反应：“哦，上次您在这个类别中购买时，您购买了这个特定品牌”，这使得它将来更有可能选择这个品牌。所以这些是我们对“它是否真的以人类在调查中的方式做出反应？”的测试。然后我们更进一步，我们试图让人们愿意为产品或某些属性付费。然后我们基本上将价格分布与我们在市场上看到的价格分布进行比较，这非常一致。</p><p>对我们来说，真正有趣和令人兴奋的事情是能够了解为属性付费的意愿，因为这是我们作为营销人员都希望找到的东西。在我们的例子中，它是牙膏，我们试图弄清楚有多少人愿意为氟化物支付多少钱，这是我们很难考虑的事情。如果有人问你——“我不知道。”我确实知道我更喜欢买这款牙膏，但我不知道编号是多少。所以这让我们更好奇，GPT 是否可以像我们询问消费者的方式一样为我们提供这个数字。研究人员多年来已经表明，提出这些问题的最佳方法是通过联合研究。本质上，您为人们提供 10 到 15 个选择，通过他们的不同选择，您能够了解他们正在做出的权衡，并实际量化他们愿意支付的差异。</p><p>我们基本上就是这么做的。我们使用 GPT 进行了联合类型分析，并将结果与​​即将发表的论文刚刚运行的人体研究进行了比较，并得到了非常相似的结果，所以我们对此感到非常兴奋。当然，结果并不相同。我们需要做更多的工作来弄清楚一些问题出在哪里，以及这在多大程度上具有普遍性，但我们能够解决这个问题的事实就令人难以置信地令人兴奋。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这对公司来说似乎很令人兴奋，因为我猜测对很多人进行市场研究的成本比仅仅通过 ChatGPT 进行一堆 API 调用要高得多。这一定是吸引力。还有其他上诉吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>基本上，这些类型的研究非常耗时、昂贵且复杂。 Ideally, you would like to ask people to make a lot of trade-offs, but you&#39;re limited by the human ability to do that. With GPT, you can query it a lot of times. But at this point, I&#39;m not going to tell anyone, “Replace all your human studies with GPT or with another LLM,” because there is a lot more work to be done to figure out how to do that right.</p><p> One of the things around GPT is that it&#39;s pretrained. It will give me preferences, but these preferences are relevant for the time period in which it was pretrained. And a firm wants to know, “What are the customers interested in right now?” So that&#39;s kind of a limitation.</p><p> What we&#39;re testing now is, maybe we still have to query people, but less people than you would normally have to. So usually when you run these studies, you need thousands of users to get something that would be robust and statistically significant from an academic or statistical standpoint. We&#39;re trying to look at, maybe I can collect information from much fewer humans and combine it with LLM through fine-tuning and generate something useful. But really, a big advantage would be cost savings and time savings.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> The time was a big one.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah. And we&#39;re talking so far about consumer products, but you can think about business-to-business type surveys, which are way more expensive and harder to do. So perhaps there is potential there as well. We haven&#39;t tested that yet.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I love the idea. I mean, when you think about most use cases for generative AI, there&#39;s a lot about taking drudgery out of the work or creating images and content and summarizing text. And then there&#39;s more-advanced ones around planning and inventory management. But the one you&#39;re talking about is literally replacing humans with this, right? I mean, that&#39;s basically what it is.</p><p> And it&#39;s a beginning of something that could be quite interesting, because you&#39;ve proven, at least, that it&#39;s sort of rational, right? I mean, you&#39;re asking it all these questions, and it is economically, I guess, rational. But then, as a marketer [like] you are yourself, not all marketing strategies are based on rationality. In fact, many of them are based on completely irrational desires.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What are your thoughts on the nonrational choices that many people make that create these big brands and $20,000 handbags and all kinds of stuff like that? How do you tap into that?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Before I answer your question, the first thing I was nervous about as an academic is when you used the word <em>proven</em> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Prove — I heard it!</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I see Sam is ...</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I smiled when I said it.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I would say we showed evidence consistent with that. And we also know that these models are still evolving, and maybe something we showed a month ago will not be relevant in a month from now, which is also a reason why you shouldn&#39;t just go and implement it without testing. So I want to be careful about that.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> So you know there is the more rational view of what is a product, but brands have value that is created that is kind of not measurable to us and hard to quantify. But that&#39;s almost like the example I gave with fluoride. Like, we don&#39;t know how to quantify fluoride. We might find it difficult if I would ask you, “Oh, how much are you willing to pay for a brand name like Colgate versus a toothpaste that I just made up?”</p><p> Actually, the same model of conjoint study will be able to infer those differences. And we see preferences, for example, for Mac over a different computer type. So it&#39;s already embedded in there, in a way.</p><p> Now how accurate it is — it&#39;s an empirical question.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah, no, you&#39;re so right because as I heard you respond to this question, I also realized that my assumption that what you showed some evidence for, vis-à-vis proven, isn&#39;t necessarily rationality. It&#39;s that it&#39;s got an ability to sort of encapsulate what most people do — or what many people do — which is embedded in stuff that it was trained on. So then my second question is, how do you get this to be more segmented or more specific or more nuanced? Because when you do focus groups, you&#39;re looking maybe for a particular flavor/particular nuance mix.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yes, and also, a lot of the uses that we have seen when GPT and other LLMs were just introduced, a lot of the excitement was, “I&#39;m an engineer. I can just ask it a question. It gives me the most common thing. That&#39;s exactly what I want.” And actually, what we are doing is the other side of that. We don&#39;t want the most common thing. We want to understand the distribution.</p><p> That&#39;s why when we query GPT, we ask it every question many, many times — because we want to get many, many different consumers. In our analysis, we only varied income and what you bought before. But we can, in the same way, vary gender, race, anything else that you want … age. And I&#39;ve seen other researchers do that. ……</p><p> There is a really interesting paper by colleagues at Columbia and Berkeley that used GPT to create perceptual maps — how close two brands are to each other. And they also showed differences by gender and age and things like that around cars, which is a market where we expect to see these differences. So you can definitely do that, too, in a similar way. And it was also shown in political science for politics. I can give someone an ideology, and their voting behavior makes sense, their text generation on different topics makes sense. That&#39;s also very exciting as a marketer who cares about heterogeneity and understanding the differences between different consumers.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. If only we could use this for clinical trials.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I saw some paper on better bedside manner of LLMs relative to doctors, so maybe there&#39;s still something there. [Laughs.]</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s GPT-5, maybe.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> As you&#39;re saying that, though, I think about the way these work is a probabilistic estimate of the most likely next word, the most likely next ... and you&#39;ve segmented out “Given that you are low income, high income, given that you are this attribute, that attribute …” That&#39;s interesting, but where do we come up with the weirdness, then? If everything is based off the “most probables,” particularly from predefined [parameters] — not that you&#39;re not brilliant about coming up with a nice search space, but how are we going to find the things we don&#39;t know, then? Isn&#39;t that something that comes out of market research and focus groups?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Certainly, and that&#39;s part of the challenge. Obviously, GPT learns some kind of distribution, but there are people that, you know … let&#39;s say all that it learns is from reviews. There might be a lot of very extreme consumers that don&#39;t write reviews online or don&#39;t have access to the internet but have these interesting extreme ideas. And even if I tell GPT, “I want [as much] randomness as possible, very high variation,” I will not get to those people. So that will definitely be a problem.</p><p> I know already of some startups that are trying to solve this issue and identify these extreme consumers and then take them to the next level by using LLMs to maybe predict what they will do in another case. But at the same time, there has been some work on [the] creativity of GPT and that it creates very creative ideas, which, you know, is not exactly what you&#39;re asking for.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Some of those creative ideas are unconstrained by reality. I think we&#39;ve all seen some of it, [like] the way that it plays chess and decides that that rule is a little bit too confining.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right. So that&#39;s also the problem of hallucinations, which should be tested in different contexts. But I think the way that we induce it to make a choice is less prone to hallucination problems because it provides a choice and you&#39;re not asking for facts or something like that. I&#39;m not trying to say that GPT will outperform any customer survey or anything like this. All I want to see is if it is as good as humans.</p><p> And even with human customers that we talk to, we have to work really hard to find people to do these surveys, and sometimes we miss them. We might be able to get the distribution of some people but still have to work hard on the extremes without AI but with just human conversation.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I find really interesting here is, you said something like, “It&#39;s not as good as a consumer survey,” and now I want to challenge that. Because what I find interesting in this idea that you have is that when you think about other AI or gen AI use cases, there is a sort of burden of proof that you say, “OK, so I&#39;m a human. I&#39;m an engineer. I have a task. Let&#39;s ask GPT,” or any generative AI system, whether it&#39;s, let&#39;s say, knowledge kind of work, whether it could do it as well as a human does.太好了。 Or can it code better than a human does? Or can it create a video or a document or something that you would read and you&#39;d say, “Wow, this is nice. So then <em>you</em> could do it. I don&#39;t need to do it.”正确的？ So that sort of a burden of proof is very clear.</p><p> On this one, I&#39;m not so sure that you even <em>have to</em> have a burden of proof, because in many ways we&#39;re assuming that a focus group of 500 or a thousand people, or any survey — I mean, there&#39;s no focus group that big that I know of — but a survey of that kind is somehow gospel or, like, that&#39;s like what GPT or whoever, whatever —</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Can you talk to the reviewers of our paper? [Laughs.]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Because the reality of it is, if you think about it, it&#39;s that if the only way to know ... so go back. Because, look: Your premise here is like, “We are going to save so much money on all this market research by augmenting this with that,” which is a true premise, and for sure it is. But I also find the burden is lower. And even if you don&#39;t stop a single human-based market research or survey, you&#39;ve still added a ton of value by broadening the universe of responses and options.</p><p> Because I would argue, how do you know 1,000 people or 2,000 people are representative <em>at all</em> or that they have all those nuances? And so this thing is actually bringing in signals that for a fact exist because otherwise you wouldn&#39;t be there. And I find that actually quite inspiring to a marketer. I&#39;m happy to talk to your reviewers.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I think as academics, we are used to a certain level of rigor and robustness and ability to say, like, oh, to actually prove things, and the fact that this tool can provide a simulation of something is nice, but “Can it actually replace humans?” is a higher burden because of this question of, is it actually giving me meaningful, updated responses? Will it match something? And you&#39;re saying, “Well, maybe humans aren&#39;t that great in the first place, so why do we try to … ?”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> No, I&#39;m actually making a different point. I was trained as a scientist, and I get the burden of proof is much higher in science and in academia. And I wasn&#39;t trying to argue that you&#39;ve proven that this replaces humans. I don&#39;t think it&#39;s replacing humans. But what I was trying to say is, the value of this is that it dramatically augments the signals and insights and ideas available to a marketer and because there is no survey or focus group that by definition isn&#39;t limited, and this isn&#39;t limited because it&#39;s got everything that&#39;s there. So my point simply is not that the burden of proof has been met but that I don&#39;t even know if there should be that kind of a burden of proof, because it is addressing a limitation of focus groups and traditional research. So it doesn&#39;t necessarily need to replace it. They&#39;re not perfect to begin with. Nobody would argue with that.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah. I think, at the very least, I feel comfortable saying that we showed that it could be very informative about preferences and what is going on, at least within the data it&#39;s trained on. And that could already change a lot for a lot of firms, given the type of research and the problems with market research and access to humans and all of that. For sure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So there&#39;s multiple different signals coming in here, and I think we&#39;ve addressed this first from the idea of, does this signal replace the other signal from a focus group? But the dependent variable here might be, do people actually buy a product? Do people buy the fluoride? Do they buy the [fake] product?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> And if this signal adds some information to that prediction, then we&#39;ve got a new information source. If it completely supplants it, then we have a different thing.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right. And now we&#39;re going to the problem of these surveys of stated preferences versus revealed preferences that are actually based on what people do. Now, I would argue that GPT might have less [of a] problem than humans because it&#39;s not subject to things like experimenter bias or trying to appease me. So it&#39;s probably giving me something closer, but it&#39;s still giving me something likely closer to stated preferences if it brings the data from review sites or market research and not necessarily [giving me] what people would actually buy. But that is also true about the focus groups and the surveys.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So we think about this as a new source of signal — that there are lots of different signals out there, and it has some overlap, perhaps, with one signal. And I think that itself is fascinating, but it may also have a new signal.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> The other thing that I find fascinating here is that AI solutions have been trained on data, and then, when they&#39;re put in production, they are then trained on data or they get feedback from data in production, and they get better. With generative AI, so much of that feedback also needs to be human-driven versus data-driven, right? Like, this is what it tells you to do. Does it resonate with you? Yes, no, etc. So it also feels like this kind of a technology, where generative AI can be a user of another generative AI&#39;s output.</p><p> So let&#39;s go to the paradigm of, look, it&#39;s replacing a human in the focus group, or we can also replace a human in a company that&#39;s a marketer dealing with a response from generative AI on, like, “How do you design a campaign for this?”</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And so this idea of maybe multiple generative AI agents going at each other to improve the overall quality — what do you think about that?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I think it&#39;s an interesting idea. But I also think that the <a href="http://john-joseph-horton.com/papers/llm_ask.pdf">evidence so far</a> suggests that you still need, at some point, at least one human in the loop …</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> For sure.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> ... because of all of these hallucinations, unrealistic things that come out. But certainly, if these models are getting better and better, more efficient, higher quality, then why not? As we implement these type of things in our organizations, we also need to think about how do we — I don&#39;t know if the word is exactly <em>validate</em> , but how do we ensure that the process still makes sense and that we&#39;re not just wasting everyone&#39;s time with these agents talking to each other?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> No, for sure. You&#39;re 100% right. You need humans in the loop and probably for many decades at least. But you may not need so many of them. You know, if you have some kind of an output that is supposed to be helping, let&#39;s say, a group of 20,000 customer service reps, and it&#39;s going to get better based on the feedback, based on their usage in a pilot of, let&#39;s say, three months, maybe you don&#39;t need to pilot this to 5,000 people. Maybe you could pilot it to a hundred people plus two or three different gen AI agents so that you dramatically accelerate the adoption time.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah, that&#39;s cool.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Although I have to say, when I heard you saying that, Shervin, what it made me think of is when people hold a microphone too close to a speaker and we get these feedback loops — amplifying feedback loops. I do worry that if the two sources of data are too, co-aligned, we&#39;ll get squelched.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s true.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We won&#39;t get craziness. Skip to the back of the chapter here: Give us the answers. People are listening to this, and they&#39;re working in companies, and they have these tools available right now, not 20 years from now, like we&#39;re thinking as an academic. What should people be doing right now with these tools?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Play around with them. Figure out … what do you want to know about your customers? We provide in our paper a whole list of prompts of exactly how to prompt for these types of things and start getting this information. And like Shervin said earlier, what is it exactly? We&#39;re not sure, but it&#39;s a signal. There is information there that we can start finding out, right?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> And so by playing with it, that helps people discover what information is there?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I think testing and discovering. But starting with a concrete question is really helpful because you will just get down so many rabbit holes. You can have these conversations forever.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ayelet Israeli, you&#39;re the only guest we&#39;ve had that has the “AI” initials, which nicely fits into <em>Me, Myself, and Ayelet Israeli</em> , which is <em>Me, Myself, and Myself</em> .</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> [Laughs.]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But tell us more about yourself and your background and how you ended up where you are and what got you interested in all this stuff.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Sure. I&#39;m originally — as my last name might indicate — I&#39;m originally from Israel. Israel is known to be “ <a href="https://www.cfr.org/book/start-nation">Startup Nation</a> .” And when I came through to think about what I want to study in university, there was a special program that was geared toward improving Startup Nation by giving people kind of managerial tools. So it was a bachelor&#39;s in computer science and an MBA combined program in five years.</p><p> And I started doing that, and I like computer science. I actually majored in finance and marketing, but I especially was interested in marketing and, particularly, making sense of a lot of data in this context that is so kind of fun and applied. And then I decided to get a Ph.D. in marketing.</p><p> Over the years, I figured that consumer products or things around customers and transactions are interesting to me. It&#39;s just a fascinating world. You have a lot of data around that because as we move more to online and digital, we can see more and more data. And then the question is, “How can we actually leverage that data more efficiently and also in a responsible manner?” which a part of my research is about as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So we have a segment where we&#39;ll ask you a series of rapid-fire questions to put you on the spot. Just answer the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s the biggest opportunity for artificial intelligence right now?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Biggest opportunity. This is not rapid.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Next question.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Yeah, next question.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Oh, OK.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I&#39;ll think about it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Pass.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Pass. What&#39;s the biggest misconception that you think people have about artificial intelligence right now?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I tend to be around people that work in this and understand this, that it is just a model, but a lot of people still don&#39;t and still envision robots and this magical thing that happens. And that&#39;s why I like to explain very clearly, “Oh, it&#39;s predicting the likelihood of the next word and choosing them on distribution, and that&#39;s all that is happening.” So I think we&#39;re still maybe not as bad as it used to be 10 years ago, but it&#39;s still this magical, artificial thing that happens, and it&#39;s not. It&#39;s still magical, I guess.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s pretty amazing — or can be. What was the first career that you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I don&#39;t know. In Israel, you go into the military. I was in the military; I was a lieutenant in intelligence. I don&#39;t think it&#39;s a career I necessarily wanted. It&#39;s something I did.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> There&#39;s a lot of discussion and excitement about artificial intelligence. Where are people overusing it? Where are people using it where it doesn&#39;t apply?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I think one of the challenges I&#39;ve seen is actually using it to ask it factual questions, because that&#39;s not what it&#39;s about. It&#39;s not a truth-finding mechanism, and that&#39;s just a wrong usage.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK. Is there something that you wish that artificial intelligence could do right now that it can&#39;t do? What&#39;s the next exciting thing? What announcement tomorrow would make you happy?</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> I&#39;ll take that question slightly differently. I think what excites me about AI in terms of my research on responsible use of data and algorithmic bias is that, yes, a lot of people have shown that AI can generate biased outcomes. We also have known for many years that humans generate biased outcomes. And what excites me about AI is that it&#39;s much easier to fix biased outcomes by a machine and to generate processes that will eliminate bias, and it&#39;s so much more difficult with humans. And that&#39;s something that I&#39;m really excited about.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I love that point because we&#39;ve got all this bias and misogyny in our world, not by the machines. The machines are not the people who put us in this situation in the first place. And the fact that they maybe do a little bit of that at the beginning, before we&#39;ve trained them, we shouldn&#39;t just throw them out for starting down that path, because we can adjust the weights in models. We can give feedback to models to improve those in a way that we can&#39;t with bazillions of people.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So I think that&#39;s a huge point.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> And we&#39;ve seen the first models of gen AI images. If you say “doctor,” we&#39;re only [seeing] photos of men or things like that. And over time, this has improved a lot. So that&#39;s really exciting, right? We can try to think about how we fix some societal problems using these things because, yes, machines can be manipulated more easily than humans. Of course, that&#39;s a risk, but that&#39;s for some sci-fi podcast, not for this one.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> The example of the doctor in the image is spot-on because I think so many people were fascinated by how accurate these models are because they felt right. They confirmed our stereotypes. You ask for this image, and it gives you exactly what you think of as that image, but that&#39;s just feeding into the problem again. And that&#39;s going to perpetuate it if we don&#39;t [stop it]. But, like you say, there has been improvement there.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ayelet, thank you so much. This has been really insightful and quite interesting. Thank you for being on the show.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Thank you so much for having me. This was fun.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for joining us today. On our next episode, Shervin and I speak with Miqdad Jaffer, chief product officer at Shopify. Before you do your holiday shopping, please join us to learn how little bits of AI everywhere can add up to big value for all of us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Governance for Smarter KPIs</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron, Michael Schrage, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>David Kiron</strong> is the editorial director, research, of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and program lead for its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">Big Ideas research initiatives</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Schrage</strong> is a research fellow with the MIT Sloan School of Management&#39;s Initiative on the Digital Economy. His research, writing, and advisory work focuses on the behavioral economics of digital media, models, and metrics as strategic resources for managing innovation opportunity and risk.</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at Boston Consulting Group (BCG) and the global director of the BCG Henderson Institute, where his research focuses on the impact of technologies on business and society. He can be contacted at <a href= "mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG&#39;s AI business in North America. He is a leader in BCG X and has over 20 years of experience driving business impact from AI and digital. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong> is a partner and associate director at BCG, where he focuses on applying AI and machine learning to business problems in commercial functions, including optimizing pricing, promotions, sales, and marketing. He can be reached at <a href= "mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In spring 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> About the Research</h4><p> This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> and Boston Consulting Group. In spring 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also interviewed 17 executives leading AI initiatives in a broad range of companies and industries, including financial services, media and entertainment, retail, travel and transportation, and life sciences.</p><p> Our research examines how managers and leaders use AI to enhance strategic measurement to advance strategic outcomes. It explores how organizations have adapted — and even generated new — KPIs with AI to define and deliver measurably better performance.</p></aside><p> Without adaptation and refinement, static business metrics create two types of strategic risk. One is encouraging performance on the wrong measures. The 2008 global economic crisis, for example, was triggered in part by banks&#39; dependence on a then widely used metric: value at risk, which measures potential portfolio losses in normal market conditions at a single point in time. Financial institutions did not adjust this measure as riskier subprime mortgages and securitized default swaps became a larger part of their portfolios. Guided by a metric that severely underestimated potential losses — in some cases, by orders of magnitude — many financial institutions went bankrupt or suffered significant losses.</p><p></p><p> Opportunity costs represent another risk from static key performance metrics. Our research persuasively demonstrates that companies deliberately using artificial intelligence to design and create more dynamic KPIs enjoy greater situational awareness, stronger ties between operations and strategic outcomes, and improved results overall. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These <em>smart</em> KPIs reflect deeper understandings of performance drivers and produce more reliable predictions about future outcomes than comparable KPIs not informed by AI. (See “Three Types of Smart KPIs.”) A “set them and forget them” approach to key metrics is neither desirable nor sustainable in volatile and fast-changing markets.</p><div class="callout-highlight callout-simple"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Three Types of Smart KPIs</h4><p class="caption"><table id="chart1" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th> Type of KPI</th><th>描述</th><th>好处</th><th>例子</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><ul><p><strong>Smart Descriptive KPIs</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Synthesize historical and current data to deliver insights on <em>what happened</em> or <em>what is happening</em> .</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Provide a deeper understanding of performance gaps and their causes.</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Sanofi&#39;s “snackable AI” tool boosts situational awareness by revealing critical interdependencies among different KPIs.</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p> <strong>Smart Predictive KPIs</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Anticipate future performance, producing reliable leading indicators. Provide visibility into potential outcomes. Identify patterns that other techniques or humans cannot, allowing them to draw on a richer range of potentially counterintuitive patterns.</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Enable preemptive actions in order to mitigate risks or leverage opportunities.</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> General Electric has transformed its KPIs to focus on leading indicators and is using AI to analyze order pipelines by comparing orders against the installed base of products and services, helping to accurately identify opportunities to increase future orders and drive stronger revenue and margins.</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p> <strong>Smart Prescriptive KPIs</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Use AI to recommend actions that optimize performance.</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Indicate performance gaps and suggest corrective measures.</ul></p></td><td><ul><p> Sanofi&#39;s smart KPIs align operations and sales by recommending adjustments to sales KPIs based on supply chain performance. </ul></p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_Table.png" alt="Three Types of Smart KPIs" class="no-desktop" /></p><p class="attribution"> Source: D. Kiron, M. Schrage, F. Candelon, et al., “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/strategic-alignment-with-ai-and-smart-kpis/">Strategic Alignment With AI and Smart KPIs</a> ,” <span style="font-style:normal">MIT Sloan Management Review</span> , Sept. 5, 2023.</p></article></aside></div><p> It takes effective governance to ensure that KPIs evolve, remain aligned with strategic aspirations, and are trusted by workers and managers alike. As AI-infused workflows and processes colonize and expand business capabilities, leaders need to update and upgrade their key performance indicators to keep up. From Schneider Electric to Walmart to Maersk, we see strategists, technologists, and business leaders working together to refine and enhance KPIs to ensure their alignment with evolving organizational goals.</p><p> Among these companies, responsibility for making KPIs more predictive, dynamic, and insightful extends beyond strategists and business leaders. They encourage technologists to make a material contribution to the formulation, organization, and prioritization of KPIs. That&#39;s a big change from the way companies have traditionally established and updated KPIs.</p><p> As Schneider Electric chief governance officer and secretary general Hervé Coureil observes, “When processes are digitized, they start to produce &#39;exhaust data&#39; that can be turned into relevant telemetry metrics, providing insights on process behaviors, defects, etc. Secondly, digital transformation triggers significant decisions and investments — portfolio and investment choices, business model implementation, new systems and infrastructure — and therefore, there is a need to measure the impact of those decisions as well as the effectiveness of the various programs that comprise the transformation.”</p><p></p><p> Developing such measures depends on more than executive judgment, intuition, and experience. Transforming static, legacy performance metrics into smarter, more dynamic KPIs demands a greater role for data, analytics, and AI. We suggest that leaders adopt a three-pronged approach to governing the development and use of AI-driven KPIs and, more broadly, their strategic measurement systems. This governance approach rests on three factors:</p><ol><li> A solid data foundation with responsible data and analytics practices.</li><li> Organizational structures with responsibility and accountability for evolving KPIs.</li><li> Trust in KPIs trained to adapt to and learn from changes in circumstances.</li></ol><h3> Governance of Smart KPI Development: Get Your Data in Order</h3><p> Effective KPI governance requires effective data governance. Every organization participating in our research emphasized data quality and discipline as the technical enabler for its AI-driven KPI initiatives. Most legacy IT and database systems, however, aren&#39;t configured to generate or make accessible the quality data necessary for measuring or defining smart KPIs.</p><p> Pierre-Yves Calloc&#39;h, the chief digital officer at Pernod Ricard, recalls that the spirits giant realized it needed three years&#39; worth of weekly consumer sales data to enable meaningful AI interventions. A preliminary review revealed huge gaps. “When we started, we had almost no data governance,” says Calloc&#39;h. “Almost 80% of the data we needed wasn&#39;t there because it was mainly external data. Our statistical experience is that you need weekly data; if you have monthly data, it doesn&#39;t work, so you need to source the information manually. We even called it &#39;archeology&#39; because of the level of effort needed, even going into old PowerPoint and Excel files in mailboxes. In addition, you need a strong business case for the project, because without clear benefits in mind, people will not invest the time.” Essentially, the business case for AI-powered KPIs could not be made without technically reliable and robust governance that transformed data <em>archaeology</em> into data <em>architecture</em> .</p><p> Jon Francis, General Motors&#39; chief data and analytics officer, who previously oversaw Starbucks&#39;s digital transformation, echoed Calloc&#39;h&#39;s observations. “It&#39;s actually really hard to just create a KPI because of the underlying data challenges,” he says. “It takes all of your effort, usually, to create the KPI and report on it.” Poor data and metadata governance undermines an organization&#39;s ability to develop the right metrics. Francis notes that technology systems are often just “spooling data that&#39;s not defined or useable” and, as a result, “you end up with these data dumping grounds.” He candidly observes that for most organizations, the generation of data from production systems is an afterthought.</p><p> Effective KPI governance remains contingent upon a company&#39;s technological capabilities to harness data: It demands diligent data governance, a structured approach to analytics management, and a path for technologists and business unit leaders to collaborate on developing optimal KPIs on an ongoing basis.</p><p></p><h3> Embedding Governance in Teams or Functions</h3><p> Our research finds top management rethinking how to develop and continuously improve their key performance measures and metrics. While approaches vary, a common theme among interviewed executives is choosing to locate responsibility for transforming KPIs in a specific team or group of teams.</p><p> At Schneider Electric, leadership came to recognize that the company&#39;s legacy metrics could become incompatible with its aspirations to strategically collaborate and innovate with its global customers. Coureil helped sponsor the creation of a Performance Management Office within the company&#39;s data team to oversee performance measurement. The office was deliberately positioned in the governance team to ensure a neutral cross-functional perspective.</p><p> The Performance Management Office helped top management transform their portfolio of KPIs and align them with operations. It also pushed the businesses to become far more data-driven and aware of the links between improvement against a given performance metric and enhanced outcomes. “Measurement has been very core for us,” adds Coureil. “We actually tried to make metrics a complete, integral part of our digital transformation, as opposed to an afterthought.”</p><p> What&#39;s the desired outcome of a given KPI? “It&#39;s an ontology or taxonomy question at some point: What behaviors are you looking for?” asks Coureil. “I think people put a lot of things in the KPI basket, and we&#39;ve spent a lot of time trying to be extremely clear about what we&#39;re looking at: What is the desired outcome? It looks very simple, but it is not that simple, actually … being extremely sharp on what the desired outcome of a given KPI is.” That&#39;s why having a performance management office is proving to be essential to strategically coherent and consistent KPI governance, Coureil says.</p><p> Instead of using a performance management office, DBS Bank governs KPI development through cross-functional teams that create value maps linking customer journeys to desired outcomes. The Singapore-based financial services leader revisited its operating model to reflect the fact that using smarter KPIs could measurably improve outcomes for both the business and its customers. “Over the past three years, we moved to something we call a data-driven operating model,” says group chief analytics officer and managing director Sameer Gupta.</p><p> At the heart of the model are cross-functional squads. Representatives from various functions, such as product, risk, data, marketing, call center, and human resources, form a squad, Gupta explains. Every squad member is then aligned on the same set of outcomes mapped to four categories: customer experience, employee experience, profitability, and risk.</p><p> The factors driving performance on each outcome are represented in a value map that connects performance metrics with the four types of outcomes. Each squad is responsible for identifying and optimizing these factors. “The squads look at optimizing those drivers,” says Gupta. “We look at many things to optimize those drivers: experimentation, data, customer immersion, AI, machine learning — all kinds of tools to try and continuously optimize in coordination and consultation with control towers and management dashboards.”</p><p> The result, Gupta notes, is not just greater data-driven operational efficiencies and effectiveness but KPIs that expand the boundaries of the DBS client and customer experience. Revisiting processes for KPI governance have led to both better KPIs and better KPI outcomes.</p><p> While the specific approaches vary, most leaders we spoke with are in the early stages of building governance structures to help make their KPIs more intelligent, detailed, and predictive.</p><h3> Effective KPI Governance Is Based on Trust</h3><p> While these technological and organizational investments in KPI governance are crucial to enhancing KPIs, our research suggests that their practical value to teams is contingent upon people&#39;s willingness to trust them. During Schneider Electric&#39;s digital transformation efforts, Coureil recognized that “one of the changes, versus a more traditional way of doing business, is that you don&#39;t build your dashboard anymore. Somebody else does it for you. So you have to trust those metrics.”</p><p> Anecdotal evidence indicates that establishing trust in AI-sourced metrics can be challenging.</p><p> At Maersk, for instance, the long-held assumption was that getting a vessel out of port and on its way to the next one as quickly as possible was ideal. A digital twin simulation, however, showed that being on time was better than being early: With an end-to-end connected schedule, as is also the situation for commercial airlines, the port that a vessel is heading to next can&#39;t adjust its schedule to immediately accommodate earlier arrivals. In other words, “faster isn&#39;t better” was a counterintuitive assertion from the data team, and it was only after the on-time approach was put into practice that the front-line operators — and even those at the most senior levels managing the entire terminal — were finally convinced.</p><p> Cultivating the trust necessary to develop and use dynamic, AI-enhanced KPIs is a critical leadership and governance challenge. Developing data-savvy managers who are receptive to developing and embracing AI-driven KPIs is a significant part of that challenge. At one media organization, an executive interviewee noted that she&#39;d had a hard time persuading her superiors to look at KPIs and make decisions based on data. Their usual retort was that executives are “paid millions for their gut instincts” — in other words, experience and intuition were valued over data-driven insight.</p><p></p><p> Building a data-oriented management community is one way to create trust among the leaders using enhanced KPIs. At Sanofi, the most senior 150 leaders, representing various functions and businesses, are being trained in boot camps to become more data-centric and to seek out more information before making decisions. As chief digital officer Emmanuel Frenehard says, “Our goal as part of our cultural change is that these 150 people, when they leave the boot camp, are far more inclined to adopt that data-centric view and better understand the potential of AI for us. We are making sure that the core of our leadership is trained on how to use the next generation of AI-driven KPIs.”</p><h3> Further Considerations</h3><p> To ensure that their AI-enabled smart KPIs are setting them up for strategic success, leaders must prioritize the technological, organizational, and cultural dimensions of KPI governance discussed above. As they begin to do so, these related considerations should be top of mind.</p><p> <strong>Establish a steering committee to guide continuous improvement.</strong> Transforming legacy KPIs into enhanced KPIs demands regular experimentation to ensure that key performance is focused on the right outcomes. Determining where this experimentation happens, who does it, and how often are critical leadership and governance decision points. Is it in a central team, like a performance office, or is it more widely distributed? Should certain KPIs be revisited and reviewed more frequently than others? Who has decision rights when changing KPIs changes accountability? There are no one-size-fits-all answers to these questions. Leaders need flexible processes to effectively govern KPIs that might be siloed or cross-functional. We suggest establishing a cross-functional KPI steering committee with business and technical expertise to elicit necessary input and buy-in from relevant stakeholders.</p><p> <strong>Oversee investment in capabilities to optimize groups of KPIs.</strong> Does your company have the capability to assess whether its KPIs are good enough or fully optimized? Our research suggests that AI can play a valuable role in assessing KPI quality, prioritizing KPIs, and addressing trade-offs among them. AI can help determine, for example, under what conditions customer-centricity imperatives should take priority over improving operational efficiencies, or when to prioritize revenue considerations over market share investments. Integrating AI into the process for developing, setting, and prioritizing KPIs can be a disruptive change for managers who are accustomed to making these decisions themselves. To preempt or address such disruptions requires organizational, technological, and cultural investments.</p><p> <strong>Govern KPIs like assets, not tracking tools.</strong> Enhanced KPIs can redefine key performance, not just track it: That makes KPIs, and the capability to enhance them, valuable assets. As with other assets, KPIs can depreciate with time or inattention. Governing KPIs like assets, not tracking tools, ensures that they become more valuable, insightful, and predictive over time. Given a wide variety of asset management frameworks, effective governance means choosing the appropriate asset management framework for KPI assets, including relevant, underlying data assets. Some companies are already beginning to explore using KPIs for KPIs to ensure that the value of their KPI assets consistently improves.</p><p> <strong>Elevate KPI oversight.</strong> As KPIs become more intelligent and more effective proxies for corporate strategy, it becomes more important for boards to be involved with governing KPI development and use. To be sure, developing and using KPIs are management functions. However, boards sign off on strategies that KPIs both embody and inform. Signing off on strategy but not the company&#39;s approach to developing KPIs is short-sighted and can undermine strategic aspirations. Engage the board directly in efforts to develop organizational capabilities for enhancing KPIs. Investing in enhanced KPIs is just as strategically relevant as investing in improving performance itself.</p><p></p><h3>结论</h3><p>Our three-pronged approach to governing the development and use of KPIs expands on the idea that AI can transform KPIs into strategic assets that do more than track performance. They serve as a GPS for the organization, delivering greater foresight and a deeper understanding of interdependencies among key performance drivers.</p><p> Making the transition to AI-enhanced KPIs is not an incremental shift. It is a dramatic change from exclusively human, top-down approaches to setting and refining KPIs. Organizations that have made this transition are putting technology in the (KPI development) loop.</p><p> In the future, KPIs will no longer be passive tools for measurement but active agents for empowering decision makers. Ongoing innovation using generative AI promises to expand the purpose, power, and potential of smart KPIs. Holding conversations with chat-enabled smart KPIs, for instance, is already a goal for several of the executives we interviewed. With proper governance, empowering smart KPIs will empower strategists and managers alike.</p><p> <em>Editor&#39;s note: The authors would like to thank Gaurav Jha, David Zuluaga Martínez, Allison Ryder, and Barbara Spindel for their contributions to this article.</em></p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Make Data Monetization Everybody&#39;s Business</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, Leslie Owens, and Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Barbara H. Wixom is a principal research scientist at MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research and chair of the center&#39;s Data Research Advisory Board. Cynthia M. Beath is a professor emerita at the McCombs School of Business, University of Texas at Austin, and a research associate at MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research. Leslie Owens is the former executive director of MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research and a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management. Previously, she was vice president and research director at Forrester Research, and a manager at Abbott. Elizabeth Heichler is editorial director, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading B.H. Wixom, C.M. Beath, and L. Owens, &#8220;How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Sept. 27, 2023. Most leaders see their organization’s data as an important asset, but few have robust strategies for converting that asset into financial returns. In their new book, Data Is Everybody&#8217;s Business, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> BH Wixom, CM Beath, and L. Owens, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , Sept. 27, 2023.</p></aside><p> Most leaders see their organization&#39;s data as an important asset, but few have robust strategies for converting that asset into financial returns. In their new book, <cite>Data Is Everybody&#39;s Business</cite> , Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, and Leslie Owens argue that leaders must make data monetization a core business activity.</p><p> That requires developing a broad and shared understanding of three key data monetization approaches: improving work with data, wrapping products with data, and selling information offerings. And it also requires educating and involving employees at all levels and functions across the organization.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn how to:</p><ul><li> Implement five sets of practices that convert your organization&#39;s most important data into reusable data assets.</li><li> Establish common language so that everybody can engage in building and/or harnessing data assets.</li><li> Bring business discipline to data investments by measuring financial value realized.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> A Reshoring Renaissance Is Underway</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Erin McLaughlin and Dana M. Peterson. <p>Erin McLaughlin is a senior economist at The Conference Board. Dana M. Peterson is chief economist of The Conference Board.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Offshoring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Kevin Foley/MIT SMR; Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Companies are building manufacturing facilities in the U.S. at a pace not seen in decades. A confluence of factors is driving this trend: Amid supply chain bottlenecks, rising labor and transportation costs, U.S. tariffs on China, and geopolitical tensions, companies recognize the value of reshoring production. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/McLaughlin-Reshoring1-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Kevin Foley/MIT SMR;卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Companies are building manufacturing facilities in the US at a pace not seen in decades. A confluence of factors is driving this trend: Amid supply chain bottlenecks, rising labor and transportation costs, US tariffs on China, and geopolitical tensions, companies recognize the value of reshoring production. US industrial policies favoring domestic manufacturing are also informing these decisions, including new laws seeking to address national security threats, economic disruptions, and dwindling access to key technological components. The result is an early-stage US reshoring renaissance.</p><p> The question for executives is whether their companies should follow this trend. But first, it&#39;s important to understand the trend&#39;s scope and what&#39;s driving it.</p><p></p><p> There have been calls for reshoring since manufacturing began sharply declining in the late 1970s, but COVID-19 marked a turning point for the C-suite. Between the first quarter of 2020 and the third quarter of 2023, executives started talking about onshoring, reshoring, and nearshoring during earnings calls and conferences much more frequently than they had previously, according to an analysis by The Conference Board.</p><p> Such talk started significantly increasing in the second quarter of 2020, as the pandemic set in globally. In the second quarter of 2022, as supply chain pressures again surged, Russia invaded Ukraine, and new federal industrial policies were enacted. Overall, instances of executives mentioning these ideas increased nearly 3,000% in just three years.</p><p> New laws also helped drive this onshoring resurgence, including the 2021 Bipartisan Infrastructure Law, the 2022 CHIPS and Science Act, and the 2022 Inflation Reduction Act. Each contains stipulations regarding the production and procurement of US-made products and components that benefit companies that manufacture domestically.</p><p> Reshoring is now driving a dramatic rise in manufacturing construction activity. Companies are constructing US manufacturing facilities at a higher rate than any other property type. Such spending rose to an annual rate of $114.7 billion in 2022, according to the US Census Bureau — a 40% increase year over year and a 62% increase over the past five years.</p><p> This made manufacturing the fastest-growing asset category in 2022, as the average growth rate for <em>all</em> nonresidential buildings and infrastructure increased just 7.4% compared with 2021. And the building continues: Manufacturing spending was 74% higher in July 2023 than in the same month the previous year.</p><p></p><p> The reshoring renaissance does not apply universally. Sectors requiring large amounts of manual labor, including shoes and apparel, furniture, and home decorative items, are <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/05/business/economy/supply-chain-reshoring-us-manufacturing.html">less likely to reshore</a> . Industries with more complex and expensive products, and those that can use automation and robotics in manufacturing, are leading the US resurgence. The <a href="https://reshorenow.org/content/pdf/2022_Data_Report.pdf">five industries</a> experiencing the greatest US employment growth as a result of reshoring and direct investment are electrical equipment, appliances, and components; computer and electronic products; chemicals; transportation equipment; and medical equipment and supplies.</p><p> Our analysis shows that North America (the US, Canada, and Mexico) has the existing supplier base to support more manufacturing activity than it currently has. In fact, for electrical equipment, North America has 15% of the global supplier base and 7% of global output. Twenty-one percent of the pharmaceutical industry&#39;s global supplier base is in North America, but its share of global output is just 18%, according to <a href="https://www.conference-board.org/publications/TCB-Global-Supplier-Index">The Conference Board Global Supplier Index</a> .</p><p></p><h3> Is Reshoring Right for Your Company?</h3><p> Reshoring results from executives and senior managers reorienting from a “low cost” to a “best cost” supply chain strategy by prioritizing factors such as supply chain resiliency, sustainability, and geopolitical stability over cheap foreign labor. Although onshoring can entail higher costs from building new facilities and paying higher wages, the benefits of minimizing external risks and creating long-term efficiencies might outweigh keeping near-term costs low.</p><p> Business leaders should consider six key factors in deciding whether to adopt this model.</p><p> <strong>1. Labor costs.</strong> Global labor shortages and cost increases — including in China, where wages are rising — make it relatively more affordable to locate manufacturing in the US than it once was. China outpaced G20 countries in real wage growth from 2008 to 2022, according to the International Labour Organization&#39;s “ <a href="https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---ed_protect/---protrav/---travail/documents/publication/wcms_862569.pdf">Global Wage Report 2022-2023</a> .” China&#39;s real monthly wages in 2022 were equivalent to about 2.6 times their real 2008 value.</p><p> <strong>2. Advanced manufacturing.</strong> New automated “smart factories,” which require more engineers and skilled technicians but often far fewer workers overall, including traditional assembly-line workers, make the US labor pool attractive due to its well-educated workforce. Demand for robotics and the advanced technology that supports smart facilities is also surging. <a href="https://www.automate.org/news/robot-sales-in-north-america-have-strongest-year-ever-in-2021">North American robot sales set a record in 2021</a> , with 39,708 units sold, for $2 billion — a 14% increase over the previous high in 2017, and 28% more than the number sold in 2020, according to the Association for Advancing Automation. Plex&#39;s “ <a href="https://www.plex.com/sites/default/files/2022-05/10292_7th_State-of-Smart-Manufacturing_Supply-Chain.pdf">7th Annual State of Smart Manufacturing Report</a> ” notes that smart-manufacturing adoption rates increased 50% in 2022 year-over-year and 83% of manufacturers reported that smart factories are key to their future success.</p><p> <strong>3. Risk mitigation.</strong> The longer and more complex the supply chain, the greater the risks it faces, especially in terms of potential geopolitical instability. There is also renewed scrutiny by the federal government of its own reliance on other economies for critical public health and national defense supplies and components, such as personal protective equipment and semiconductors used in military vehicles and weaponry.</p><p> <strong>4. Sustainability</strong> With companies increasingly needing to meet sustainability goals and reduce their carbon footprints, localizing manufacturing offers several benefits. Constructing new, green facilities domestically can greatly reduce Scope 1 operating emissions from company-owned facilities and vehicles. The US has the world&#39;s largest sustainable-building market, with more than 511 million square feet <a href="https://www.usgbc.org/articles/top-10-countries-leed-demonstrate-green-building-truly-global-movement">certified under the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design</a> rating system, compared with 180 million square feet in China. Plus, manufacturing a product closer to its end customer reduces emissions from transportation.</p><p> <strong>5. Stakeholder sentiment.</strong> Many companies&#39; stakeholders — including employees, corporate boards, industry organizations, government officials, and other companies connected within a supply chain — want executives to consider <a href="https://www.kearney.com/industry/consumer-retail/article/-/insights/the-2021-reshoring-index-the-tides-are-turning">localizing manufacturing operations</a> . Walmart — the largest retailer in the United States — vowed in 2021 to spend an additional $350 billion through 2030 on items made, grown, or assembled in the US, for example.</p><p> <strong>6. Transportation costs.</strong> When deciding whether to onshore manufacturing operations, executives should weigh the benefits of lower international labor and operating costs against the greater cost of ocean freight shipping. Trans-Pacific shipping costs increased fifteenfold in 2021 from January 2020 levels, and while transportation costs have declined as the economy has slowed, the supply chain volatility of the last few years is front of mind for managers.</p><p> The growth in US manufacturing-facility construction will continue as businesses see value in focusing on aspects of risk mitigation, using automation to offset labor challenges, and even building new facilities that emit less carbon. This reshoring renaissance is just beginning; it takes a few years to plan, permit, and acquire property for new-facility construction.</p><p></p><p> Now is the time for manufacturing executives to understand how their businesses fit into this renaissance and determine whether reshoring is right for them. Using the factors above as a framework, executives should consider these five key questions:</p><ol><li> Can a new facility for my products that uses advanced automation offset higher labor costs?</li><li> Does my current supply chain involve countries that present uncertainty due to geopolitics?</li><li> Will the carbon emissions from my company&#39;s current supply chain improve significantly if we build a new facility powered by renewable energy and localize production?</li><li> Are my stakeholders, especially customers, asking for domestically manufactured products?</li><li> Is the cost savings that comes with eliminating transoceanic shipping enough to balance out a likely increase in labor and new-facility construction costs?</li></ol><p> By seeking answers to questions such as these, the C-suite can better navigate their company&#39;s operations through a changing global production landscape.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Managers Everywhere Must Know About Caste</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hari Bapuji, Kamini Gupta, Snehanjali Chrispal, and Thomas Roulet. <p>Hari Bapuji ( <a href="https://twitter.com/haribapuji">@haribapuji</a> ) is a professor of management at the University of Melbourne, Australia, and a cofounder of <a href="https://air-collective.com/">Action to Improve Representation</a> . Kamini Gupta is a lecturer of management at King&#39;s College London, where she also hosts the <a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/events/series/kings-business-school-nisau-india-series">India Series</a> , fireside chats focused on topics of urgent relevance to India&#39;s growth and place in the world. Snehanjali Chrispal is a lecturer of management at Deakin University in Australia, and researches inequality and organizations, particularly human rights issues like gender and caste. Thomas Roulet is a professor of organizational sociology and leadership at the Judge Business School and a fellow of King&#39;s College, both at the University of Cambridge.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Cultural Differences]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Justice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Grundini/Ikon Images As globalization and workforce mobility make many organizations more multicultural, managers find themselves having to broaden their understanding of workplace discrimination’s possible forms. In particular, issues of bias related to caste identity are making headlines around the world more frequently, and maintaining a healthy and productive culture will require leaders to be able [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bapuji_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Grundini/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> As globalization and workforce mobility make many organizations more multicultural, managers find themselves having to broaden their understanding of workplace discrimination&#39;s possible forms. In particular, issues of bias related to caste identity are making headlines around the world more frequently, and maintaining a healthy and productive culture will require leaders to be able to identify, prevent, and mitigate caste-based discrimination.</p><p> The caste system is a sociocultural-economic hierarchy that is pervasive in South Asia and the sizable South Asian diaspora all over the world. An individual&#39;s caste, inherited from their father, is determined solely by their birth and is unchangeable.</p><p> Numerous incidents of caste-based bias in Silicon Valley and elsewhere have been documented in the media. Studies conducted by academics, governments, and advocacy organizations have found that caste discrimination is prevalent in countries with significant South Asian populations, including the US, the UK, Canada, and Australia. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p> Within South Asia, which is home to a quarter of the world&#39;s population, caste bias can have disastrous consequences for individuals and organizations. For example, in June 2023, Vivek Raj, an employee of Indian fashion retailer Lifestyle International, died by suicide after recording a statement alleging <a href="https://www.thequint.com/south-india/vivek-raj-dalit-bengaluru-employee-lifestyle-dies-caste-discrimination">workplace caste discrimination</a> . In another case, Indian food delivery company Zomato faced public backlash for <a href="https://www.thequint.com/opinion/zomato-ad-kachra-lagaan-caste-marketing-teaching-moment">a 2023 advertisement</a> that reinforced derogatory caste stereotypes.</p><p> Multinational companies, such as Alphabet, Amazon, Apple, Dell, and X (formerly Twitter), have recognized the importance of this issue by addressing caste-based discrimination in their corporate policies. Over 20 US universities have also included caste as a protected category in their policies, alongside race, gender, religion, and others.</p><p> In February 2023, the city of Seattle passed a law to outlaw caste discrimination. A similar bill was passed by California&#39;s legislature but was vetoed in October 2023 by its governor, who said that caste-based discrimination was already prohibited under the state&#39;s existing laws. These legislative efforts are in line with laws in countries that have caste systems, such as India, whose constitution outlaws caste discrimination and guarantees affirmative action for low-caste individuals in public education, employment, and political offices.</p><p> Managers everywhere need to understand these issues to help protect employees of South Asian origin from caste-based discrimination, bullying, incivility, and harassment, and to avoid the legal jeopardy that can result from such acts in the workplace. Managers could also improve the well-being and performance of individuals and their organizations by addressing the influence of caste on activities such as hiring, corporate social responsibility, information sharing, and networking. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><h3> What Is Caste, and Why Is It Relevant?</h3><p> The fundamental assumption underlying the caste system is the notion that humans are created as unequal groups. This inequality is manifested by arbitrarily assigning different levels of purity and value to groups of people on an artificially defined hierarchy that gives some of them socially enforced rights and privileges, including the right to practice certain sets of occupations.</p><p></p><p> Caste is a complex system comprising thousands of groups and subgroups across religions. Broadly speaking, among those who practice Hinduism, Brahmins are at the top of the hierarchy. Their occupations have traditionally included religious duties and knowledge professions like recordkeeping, science, and education. Next in the hierarchy are Kshatriyas (who have traditionally occupied military roles), followed by Vysyas (businesspeople and traders) and Shudras (workers and laborers). Similar groups and subgroups are found among those practicing other religions. For instance, <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4357934">among South Asian Muslims</a> , there are high castes (Ashraf, consisting of the Saiads, Sheikhs, Pathans, and Mughals) and low castes (Ajlaf, consisting of artisans and other workers). Among those who practice Sikhism, there are high-caste groups like the Jatts and Khatris. Similarly, <a href="https://scroll.in/article/876000/is-the-caste-system-deep-rooted-among-christians-in-india-a-kerala-bishop-stirs-up-a-hornets-nest">South Asian Christian congregations</a> have formed around distinct caste-based identities.</p><p> Dalits are outside of, and well below, the above groups. They are considered by those following the norms of the caste system as inferior and impure to the point of being subhuman and are relegated to occupations that involve activities like cleaning up excrement and disposing of the dead. Dalits, found across religions, are stigmatized as “ <a href="https://baws.in/books/baws/EN/Volume_05/pdf/14">untouchable</a> ” due to the historic, and still prevalent, practice of other castes avoiding physical contact and spatial proximity with them.</p><p> Adivasis (meaning first inhabitants or, more generally, indigenous peoples) are another group outside the caste system who have historically lived in forest or hill areas remote from urban locations and have often been <a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/02757206.2023.2204866">stigmatized as outlaws</a> .</p><p> Although individuals from each group today engage in occupations other than those assigned to them by caste, an individual&#39;s caste remains a significant determinant of the social and professional opportunities available to them. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><h3> How Caste Shapes Organizations</h3><p> Caste can shape an organization&#39;s internal environment in a few different ways. The talent pool from which a company hires might not have caste diversity due partly to differences in access to education and other resources that have persisted for generations. Caste determines access to capital and valuable business connections. Research has shown that family firms rely on caste-based networks to share knowledge and resources and exert control over markets and industries. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Value chains that pass through South Asia replicate caste hierarchies such that high-caste individuals control important activities in the chain (such as design, research, and marketing) while low-caste individuals are relegated to activities valued less (such as product assembly and manufacturing). <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> The disproportionate control of institutions like educational, regulatory, legislative, and industry bodies by high-caste individuals also shapes the environment in which organizations operate.</p><p> Caste impacts the functioning of organizations as well. Recruiters and managers are likely to introduce biases into decisions about hiring and promotion, even at the level of the C-suite. Such biases might be explicit, such as through stereotyping individuals of certain caste backgrounds; or implicit, in the weight placed on markers such as speaking English with a familiar accent or observing certain social etiquette, even when they&#39;re not relevant to the job. Caste stereotypes can also affect the assignment of jobs, such as when high-caste individuals get promoted to managerial roles while low-caste individuals are relegated to low-end jobs, like data entry and coding in the <a href="https://scholarcommons.scu.edu/soc/67/">IT sector</a> or cleaning jobs across sectors.</p><p> Caste also tends to impact workplace interactions; for example, low-caste individuals might experience harassment, bullying, and incivility through behaviors like name-calling or exclusion, or be subjected to unsafe or demeaning work conditions. In one study on caste-based discrimination in the US, 25% of Dalit respondents reported having faced physical or verbal assault; 67% said they had been treated unfairly at work, and 60% reported experiencing caste-based derogatory comments and jokes. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><h3> Why Caste Poses Unique Challenges</h3><p> Caste predominantly operates indirectly, in the form of <em>identity</em> , <em>resources</em> , <em>networks</em> , and <em>culture</em> . A person&#39;s caste is not evident from their physiological features but can be inferred based on those four dimensions and shape their perceived merit. That perception of merit, rather than their caste, can then be claimed as the basis for decisions and actions affecting them. (See “The Indirect Markers of Caste.”) Here&#39;s how caste manifests in each of these dimensions.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Indirect Markers of Caste</h4><p class="caption"> Caste is often not directly apparent but can be ascertained based on an individual&#39;s identity, resources, networks, and culture. Together, these dimensions shape the perception of an individual&#39;s merit. Caste discrimination in workplaces is therefore not always explicit but can manifest as biases, stereotyping, and exclusionary practices that are difficult to recognize and address. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Bapuji_RF_Winter_2024_Figure-1.png" alt="The Indirect Markers of Caste" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p><strong>身份。</strong> For many people from South Asia, caste is an inalienable part of one&#39;s identity. Inherited by birth, caste is seen as a symbol of one&#39;s ancestry. Caste identity is further reinforced through practices such as endogamy (marrying within one&#39;s caste), which is intended to maintain caste purity. Nearly 95% of marriages among Indians, including Indian-origin people in the US, occur within the same caste. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Even a <a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2021-02-11/caste-system-of-india-and-south-asia-in-australia-dalit-rights/13135622">dating app for South Asians</a> that a US company developed allows users to filter for high-caste groups to find matches. Several other matchmaking service providers also facilitate marriages within castes.</p><p> An individual&#39;s caste identity is often reflected in their name. Many South Asian surnames (such as Bhatia, Kamble, Khan, Sharma, and Yadav) can be markers of caste. South Asians who do not have a caste-revealing name can face probing questions and exclusion, because caste identity shapes resource availability, networks, and cultural affinity.</p><p><strong>资源。</strong> Tangible resources, such as cash, assets, and investments, are unequally distributed along caste lines. Due to historical differences in rights and opportunities to own and accumulate assets among castes, such inequalities have compounded over generations. Research has found that in India, high-caste individuals are overly represented among the top 50% of wealthy individuals, accounting for 90% of the total wealth, while low-caste individuals have a much higher representation in the bottom 50% of individuals in terms of wealth. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> Members of high-caste communities often have systemically greater access to economic capital and the advantages that come with it, such as the ability to attend elite private schools, which affords them greater access to knowledge professions. For instance, <a href="https://theprint.in/india/education/diversity-deficit-in-iims-iits-just-23-sts-and-157-scs-in-9640-faculty-posts/191246/">only 6% of the faculty at the Indian Institutes of Management</a> (premier business schools established by the Indian government) are from the low castes that account for <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/decoded/2021/06/29/measuring-caste-in-india/">the vast majority</a> (69%, according to one estimate) of the Indian population. A similar situation exists in other higher education institutions.</p><p> These differences in resources also affect who can emigrate from South Asia, with high-caste individuals finding it easier to migrate to and get settled in their host countries. For example, nearly 90% of US residents of Indian origin are from high castes. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p><strong>网络。</strong> Caste forms the basis of formal and informal social networks that facilitate economic transactions. Members of one caste are more likely to hire, do business with, and lend financial and nonfinancial support to people from similar caste backgrounds. The long-standing practice of marrying within a caste is one way these networks are formed.</p><p> Caste also shapes networks via other forms of spatial and social segregation. Studies have shown the existence of caste-based segregation in many cities in India due in part to historic factors that allowed each caste to reside in a specific part of the city or town and partly due to individuals&#39; preference to live next to people of their own caste. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Social segregation occurs because of how caste norms shape interactions between castes. For instance, high-caste individuals adhering to such norms might avoid sharing space or a meal with Dalits.</p><p> Formal and informal caste-based associations exist both within South Asia and globally. Such associations can be explicitly caste-based, such as the Brahman Samaj of North America, which is open to all Brahmins, and Pravara Vedika, open only to certain Brahmin subgroups. Some associations represent themselves as broader “community” or linguistic/cultural organizations but are dominated by certain high castes. For example, the Telugu Association of North America is dominated by the Kamma, a high-caste group that actively supports its caste kin; the North American Telugu Association is dominated by the Reddy high-caste group; and the NRI Vasavi Association predominantly comprises members of the Vysya community. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> <strong>Culture.</strong> The dominant culture and norms of a particular South Asian religion or region are often defined in terms of the high-caste culture, even when it is practiced by a numerical minority of the population. These are most often reflected in people&#39;s religious and cultural practices, diets, and spoken languages, which vary by caste. For example, high-caste groups have a hegemony on certain forms of “classical” music and dance because low-caste groups have been excluded from practicing them. These arts are considered superior to folk music and dances practiced by low-caste individuals. Because high-caste individuals have migrated abroad at a higher rate than those from low castes, these cultural artifacts are often perceived as typical of South Asian culture.</p><p> The common misconception in high-income countries that <a href="https://www.livemint.com/Politics/dWUqT4epdPTHNAYuKYVThK/No-vegetarianism-is-not-growing-in-India.html">most Indians are vegetarian</a> is another example of high-caste culture defining the norm abroad. Several organizations and <a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/0963662520903690">higher education institutions</a> in India adhere to vegetarian menus or have separate kitchens and dining spaces for vegetarians, leading to the segregation, stigmatization, and exclusion of low-caste individuals. Perceptions of South Asian culture are reinforced by the widespread representation of high-caste culture in popular media, including film, TV, and music. Because low-caste individuals do not always fit these profiles, non-South Asian managers might unwittingly treat lower-caste individuals differently as well.</p><h3> What Managers Can Do About Caste Discrimination</h3><p> Caste can be inferred from how it manifests as identity, resources, networks, and culture. For managers of South Asian origin, many signals are visible (such as last names or diet) or can be learned through social interactions (such as location of residence or ancestral occupations) and used in organizational decision-making. For example, research has shown that when the resumes of two candidates of the same profile are presented, high-caste individuals are selected over low-caste individuals based only on the status associated with their last names. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p> However, non-South Asian managers can have difficulty discerning cultural cues to caste identity, and since it is a sensitive topic, inquiring about a person&#39;s caste is not appropriate. Low-caste individuals might choose to hide their caste to fit in and avoid exclusion. What, then, can managers do to create a caste-inclusive environment in their organizations?</p><p> To successfully address the challenges of caste, managers need to take a holistic approach that includes making caste a part of organizational diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) policies and practices, raising awareness through training, and addressing caste inequalities in societies where they are systemic. (See “How Organizations Can Address Caste.”) Managers should also take steps to preempt resistance as these efforts get underway.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> How Organizations Can Address Caste</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations can employ four approaches to creating a more caste-inclusive working environment for South Asian employees and partners. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Employee Policies and Codes of Conduct</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Make caste a protected category alongside race, gender, and other aspects of identity.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Include caste in codes of conduct, such as those for suppliers and communication.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Employ equitable procedures for hiring, job assignments, and promotion.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Put protocols in place to address complaints based on caste.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Training and Awareness</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Provide diversity, equity, and inclusion training to identify caste discrimination, and support employees facing such discrimination.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Coach managers on how to manage teams with employees of different castes, create inclusivity in teams, and handle caste-sensitive issues.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Raise awareness of caste privilege and oppression and how they affect individual attitudes and behaviors.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Corporate Social Initiatives</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Provide scholarships, coaching, and training for low-caste individuals where the company has operations, to overcome caste disadvantages and increase access opportunities.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Create opportunities for low-caste individuals and groups to work as suppliers for the company.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Make philanthropic support conditional on nongovernmental organizations and charities having caste-inclusive operations.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Preempting Resistance</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Understand the sources of resistance and the stakeholders involved.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Address resistance through thoughtful and tactful communications to secure buy-in/participation from employees and other stakeholders.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Design external communications to create broad-based support for caste inclusion. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Bapuji_RF_Winter_2024_Table-1.png" alt="How Organizations Can Address Caste" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Explicitly identify caste as a protected category.</strong> DEI policies aim to promote inclusion for people of all identities, and a first step is to explicitly identify caste as a protected category. This recognition should cover all relevant company policies, including those related to the conduct of employees and suppliers, corporate communications, and employee hiring. Companies can explicitly state in their employee conduct policies that caste discrimination will not be tolerated, as <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/caste-california-tech-giants-confront-ancient-indian-hierarchy-2022-08-15/">Apple</a> and <a href="https://www.cisco.com/c/dam/en_us/about/cobc/2021/fy22-code-of-business-conduct-english.pdf">Cisco</a> have done, and implement protocols to comprehensively address reports of caste discrimination in the workplace. Companies can also include caste in their supplier code of conduct (as Canadian retailer <a href="https://www.loblaw.ca/en/supplier-code-of-conduct/">Loblaw</a> has done) to ensure that caste is a protected category throughout their value chains and that suppliers do not alienate or discriminate against low-caste individuals.</p><p></p><p> Policies around company communications and social media messaging should also include guidance on caste-inclusive language. For example, <a href="https://www.dell.com/en-in/dt/policies/social-media-policy.htm">Dell Technologies&#39;</a> global social media policy notes that caste-based hate speech is not tolerated. Companies that host user-generated content should expand their terms of service to prohibit caste-related discriminatory language and slurs, as <a href="https://transparency.fb.com/en-gb/policies/community-standards/hate-speech/">Meta</a> , X, and <a href="https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2801939?hl=en-GB#:~:text=We%20remove%20content%20promoting%20violence,Disability">YouTube</a> have done, and moderate content that promotes caste indirectly. To develop such policies, organizations can partner with advocacy groups such as the International Dalit Solidarity Network, which has released <a href="https://idsn.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Caste-hate-speech-report-IDSN-2021.pdf">studies</a> on caste-based hate speech.</p><p> Existing practices for inclusive hiring can be adapted for caste with relative ease. Anonymizing applicants&#39; resumes can eliminate some signals of caste from the recruitment process. Employers can instruct hiring managers to disregard candidate characteristics that are not salient to the job, such as accent, etiquette, status of educational institutions attended, and family background. Companies, especially those with subsidiaries in South Asia, must proactively diversify their pool of applicants through targeted referrals or recruiting drives directed at low-caste candidates. These individuals account for the vast majority of the population, and failing to reach them means overlooking a huge talent pool. Structured and standardized interviews that more accurately evaluate candidates based on job-relevant skills can minimize bias at the interview stage and combat caste prejudices in hiring.</p><p> <strong>Increase awareness and training.</strong> Given that caste is an invisible inequality, raising awareness about it is one of the most important aspects of addressing caste discrimination. This training should be aimed at preventing caste discrimination, creating a caste-inclusive environment, and understanding the effects of caste privilege and oppression.</p><p></p><p> Training on caste needs to address the forms of discrimination that low-caste individuals commonly experience, including <a href="https://youtu.be/wJwkIxOpqZA?si=N67lxr5AWEEF2wRQ">slurs</a> , jokes, and <a href="https://dalitdiscrimination.tumblr.com/">derogatory comments</a> about them and their leaders. For example, low-caste individuals from India, which has caste-based affirmative action policies, are often at the receiving end of derogatory remarks, such as “quota candidate” or “reservation people,” that demean the use of these policies. The training should also extend to supporting employees who face such discrimination.</p><aside class="callout-info"><h4>其他资源</h4><ul><li>BR Ambedkar, <cite>Annihilation of Caste: The Annotated Critical Edition</cite> (New Delhi: Navayana, 2014).</li><li> “Testimonies of Practice of Caste in the USA,” Ambedkar King Study Circle, accessed Sept. 14, 2023, <a href="https://akscusa.org">https://akscusa.org</a> .</li><li> <cite>Blocked by Caste: Economic Discrimination in Modern India</cite> , eds. S. Thorat and KS Newman (New Delhi: Oxford University Press, 2012).</li><li> I. Wilkerson, <cite>Caste: The Origins of Our Discontents</cite> (New York: Random House, 2020).</li><li> S. Yengde, <cite>Caste Matters</cite> (New Delhi: Penguin Random House India, 2019).</li></ul></aside><p> Managers should be coached on creating a caste-inclusive environment in their teams. This could include raising awareness about the many ways in which caste discrimination might appear and signaling the inappropriateness of caste-sensitive topics in workplace discussions. Further, without violating the privacy of individuals, companies can collect self-disclosed data on individuals&#39; caste or conduct caste audits (for example, using last names as caste indicators) to understand the caste homogeneity/diversity in their organizations and make employees aware of its implications for organizational functioning and performance.</p><p> <strong>Tackle caste discrimination at its root.</strong> Organizations can work on addressing caste not just internally but within the countries where the caste system is prevalent. Directly funding education and development initiatives in India, Nepal, or Pakistan, for example, can improve access to education for individuals from low-caste backgrounds. Mentoring individuals and groups from lower castes can also help minimize the barriers they face to enter an industry or a profession. Companies can make their support of nongovernmental organizations and charitable organizations (including community and cultural organizations) conditional on their being caste-inclusive in their operations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Preempt resistance to addressing caste.</strong> Organizations that attempt to address caste are likely to face resistance. Google <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2022/06/02/google-caste-equality-labs-tanuja-gupta/">canceled a talk on caste</a> by Thenmozhi Soundararajan of Equality Labs in 2022 after some of its employees objected to it, and legislative efforts to address caste in the US have faced stiff resistance from <a href="https://www.fairobserver.com/world-news/us-news/caste-is-now-weaponized-against-indian-americans/">some Hindu lobbying groups</a> . These groups often argue that caste is an issue of the past or not an issue outside of South Asia and that policies protecting caste could be misused to discriminate against people of Hindu faith or Indian ethnicity. Understanding these sources of resistance to addressing caste can help organizations design ways to overcome them and secure buy-in from all employees and other stakeholders, including via external communications that encourage broad-based support for caste equity.</p><p> Caste is a complex and difficult issue, but addressing it is both an instrumental and moral imperative for organizations around the world. Doing so contributes to more equitable outcomes for individuals and affirms organizational commitment to cocreating a fairer and more equal society for all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Economic Incentives Are Key to Driving Sustainability at Scale</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satoshi Ikeda and Simon Glynn. <p>Satoshi Ikeda is chief sustainable finance officer of the Financial Services Agency of Japan. Simon Glynn is founder of Zero Ideas.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Business Case]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR When it comes to mobilizing the economy for climate action, most recent progress has been incremental. To come close to achieving the goals of the Paris Agreement, the pace and scale of change must be much more radical. The scaling up we need is not simply a matter of dialing up what [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Ikeda-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> When it comes to mobilizing the economy for climate action, most recent progress has been incremental. To come close to achieving the goals of the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-paris-agreement-its-down-to-business/">Paris Agreement</a> , the pace and scale of change must be much more radical. The scaling up we need is not simply a matter of dialing up what we have already begun. What we now need is qualitatively different, and today&#39;s approach won&#39;t get us there.</p><p> Merely strengthening disclosure requirements on climate-related data and information could increase regulatory burdens without having a significant productive impact. Regulation needs to be partnered with industrial strategy to create the commercial demand for climate action at scale and for the sustainable finance that is increasingly available. Japan is seeking to do this with a balanced mix of sticks and carrots that is in marked contrast to the approaches of both the United States (mostly carrots) and the European Union (mostly sticks).</p><p></p><p> Today we expect companies to act on climate change without a financial case for doing so. Their nonfinancial rationales might be to do the morally right thing, to satisfy the ESG (environmental, social, and governance) interests of investors, to instill pride and a sense of commitment among workers, or to keep their options open in the face of uncertainty. These are all sound motivations, but they rarely add up to a solid financial case in which cash investments predictably generate surplus cash returns. As a result, they drive incremental commitments but can&#39;t drive action at scale.</p><p> Take, for example, the steel industry, which currently accounts for around 8% of global greenhouse gas emissions. There are multiple technological approaches to decarbonizing steel production, but they are all difficult, speculative, and hugely expensive. As Japan&#39;s Ministry of Economy, Trade, and Industry (METI) observes in its <a href="https://www.meti.go.jp/english/press/2021/pdf/1027_002a.pdf">technology road map for the iron and steel industry</a> , “Replacing the existing process with a new one … will require a huge amount of capital investment, resulting in large capital and operating costs. But these additional costs are only for decarbonization and contribute neither to improving the performance of steel nor increasing its productivity.”</p><p></p><p> In Europe, the “green premium” for low-carbon steel is expected to be above 250 euros ($265) per ton — a premium of upward of 25% on today&#39;s cost. How many customers would choose to pay this added cost for a product that offers no improvement in performance? Some carmakers and construction companies will pay a bit more for the ESG benefit of using green steel, but they can&#39;t afford to pay much because the consumers at the end of the value chain are not choosing to pay more for green steel. And if customers won&#39;t choose to pay the premium, how can the steelmakers afford the huge investment required? The availability of sustainable finance doesn&#39;t solve that problem if steelmakers have no financial case for making the investment.</p><p> Driving climate action at the scale that is needed will require more than nonfinancial incentives for businesses. A reliance on such incentives will limit us to nonmaterial, incremental outcomes and also leave the whole climate effort vulnerable to changes in sentiment — a real risk we&#39;re already seeing in the backlash against ESG in the United States. For material, transformational outcomes, companies need financial incentives to act, with financial returns that justify the costs and risks involved. That is the only way that enough companies will choose to invest at scale.</p><h3> Creating Demand for Sustainable Finance</h3><p> Where will these financial incentives come from? Today, to shape the availability and focus of sustainable finance, we use scenarios for how different industries need to transition. The International Energy Agency, the Transition Pathway Initiative, the Science-Based Targets initiative, the Glasgow Financial Alliance for Net Zero, and others all set out such sectoral pathways. These scenarios illustrate what is needed, but they don&#39;t make it happen. They are descriptive, not prescriptive. Using these scenarios, we can see what changes an industry needs to make and what an optimal path might be — but describing this path does not move an industry along it.</p><p> The challenge is not about finding the money. The supply of sustainable finance is impressive. The challenge is to create the demand for that finance, in step with the growing supply. Today, providers of sustainable finance lament that take-up of the money they have to offer is low because potential borrowers don&#39;t have the risk appetite; in other words, they are not sufficiently confident of a return.</p><p> For governments, directly paying the green premium through subsidies would be hugely expensive. Fortunately, that is not necessary. What is needed is to create conditions in which companies are motivated to invest the money themselves and are rewarded for doing so.</p><p> There are good examples of this happening. The automotive industry, particularly in the US and European Union, has invested in the transformational shift to electric vehicles, anticipating a near future in which manufacturers will not be allowed to sell vehicles powered by internal combustion engines. And the US government&#39;s Inflation Reduction Act has been described by the World Economic Forum as “ <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/11/how-new-laws-meet-climate-goals/">a compelling nudge</a> ” to the private sector and investors to decarbonize hard-to-abate sectors.</p><p> In the US, the approach has been to rely heavily on incentives — the proverbial carrot — which means that companies&#39; participation is voluntary. This reflects what is politically most feasible in the US: It is hard to impose constraints on business, especially at a federal level, in a culture that reveres free enterprise. Incentives are targeted at strengthening the technology leadership of the US economy, playing to a nationalist and environmental agenda. The problem: The incentives needed to kick-start investment in some industries might be very high and might depend in practice on enabling initiatives that cannot be solved with money alone, such as issuing permits to build new long-distance grids for wind and solar power.</p><p> The EU, in contrast, relies principally on regulation — the proverbial stick. This reflects what is politically most feasible; it is hard to offer incentives at the EU level without favoring national target industries and getting into divisive politics. But regulation is unifying and has been the core of the EU&#39;s supranational toolkit. It uses the EU&#39;s market power, a market too big for global players to miss out on. The problem: It might impose unquantified and hidden costs on industry without first gaining political acceptance of that outcome. That is the background to Germany&#39;s recent wobble about protecting its internal-combustion-based car industry from the forced move to electric vehicles.</p><p></p><h3> The Power of an Industrial Strategy</h3><p> America and Europe have hugely different approaches to climate action that reflect their respective self-image and values. Where politics allow, a more balanced mix of sticks and carrots can provide the most effective incentives for companies to progress along their transition pathway. Building up the initiatives in an advertised sequence can provide strong incentives for early action, if companies are confident of the policy environment to come and motivated to position themselves for it.</p><p> Such an industrial strategy is not about picking winners and losers but about recognizing and accepting the idea of winners and losers and playing to win — or to not lose. The incentives work by creating risk that companies are motivated to avoid. The financial case for Volkswagen&#39;s early investment in the electric vehicle market sprang in part from the opportunity to win share from its biggest rival, Toyota. The financial case for Toyota&#39;s recent investment in electric vehicles is partly based on defending its market share. Both companies are strongly incentivized by the threat from emerging electric car makers in China. Similarly, carbon capture and storage is expensive and still speculative, but the financial case to industrialize it could be strong for a fossil fuel company concerned about future prohibitions against extracting and selling its mineral assets.</p><p> This insight aligns well with the way political power sits largely at the national level (or regional level, in the case of the EU). Governments can stimulate climate action in ways that favor their companies and their economies. The incentives in the Inflation Reduction Act are attracting corporate investment, skilled jobs, and technology innovation to the US Japan&#39;s steelmakers are looking to lead the world in new technology solutions for high-end steel, using hydrogen rather than carbon to reduce iron ore to iron. This battle for competitiveness at both the national and company levels is how we can drive climate action at scale in the short time we have to make an impact.</p><h3> Creating and Destroying</h3><p> The transition we are describing is the creative destruction and value migration that have always fueled innovation and investment in a capitalist economy. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> In this important sense, climate change is not a collective-action problem: For systemwide transformations in which nobody loses, the transition will be practically unaffordable. We need winners and losers — or at least the real prospect of winners and losers — to provide the competitive pressure and financial incentive for companies to act.</p><p> The practical task for policy makers is not just to correct for the externalized costs of pollution but to facilitate the dynamic transition to this new state. As researchers have recently asserted, policy makers need to “simultaneously and successfully navigate two distinct but interrelated dynamics: the creation and mass commodification of new green energy technologies on the one hand, and the destruction of powerful, fossil fuel incumbencies on the other.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> The American and European approaches do not provide this navigation. The carrots of America&#39;s Inflation Reduction Act help to create the new without constraining the old. The sticks of EU&#39;s regulations constrain the old without solving the technological or economic challenge of substituting with the new.</p><p> What would a more balanced and dynamic, sequenced approach look like?</p><h3> Paths to Green Transformation</h3><p> Japan&#39;s approach to green transformation, or GX, involves a mix of carrots and sticks to drive both parts of the creative destruction required, sequenced over time. The <a href="https://www.meti.go.jp/english/press/2023/pdf/0210_003b.pdf">explicit goal</a> is to deliver “both emissions reduction and economic growth,” without sacrificing either. At the highest level, Japanese corporate and government interests are aligned: “The success or failure of GX initiatives is directly linked to the competitiveness of companies and nations.”</p><p> The immediate carrot is the commitment of 20 trillion yen ($140 billion) of government support for upfront investment over the next 10 years and an envisaged 150 trillion yen of public and private investment. The principal stick is an <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/carbon/japans-carbon-pricing-scheme-being-launched-april-2023-03-30/">industrial pricing mechanism</a> for carbon that is in trials now and expected to be phased in starting in 2026. The plan includes both a European-style emissions-trading scheme for high-emissions industries and a surcharge on the supply of fossil fuels.</p><p> Announcing the stick now but phasing it in later in the decade creates the immediate incentive for companies to make the technology investments in their transitions, without penalizing them financially before they have had the opportunity to adapt.</p><p> Japanese companies are partners in this effort as well as counterparties. The intent is not just to reduce Japan&#39;s own emissions, which account for 3% of the world&#39;s total, but to position Japanese companies as service providers helping to reduce other countries&#39; emissions too, through the green technology solutions they will offer.</p><p> Companies worked with METI — or with the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism, in the case of maritime transport and aviation — to develop technology road maps for 10 sectors that collectively cover 80% of Japan&#39;s carbon emissions. In the technology road map for iron and steel, for example, the specialist committee advising METI included representation from the Japan Iron and Steel Federation, credit analysts, and the Development Bank of Japan, as well as professors in engineering and technology. The METI road map illustrates its general framework with a specific example, JFE Steel; JFE Steel in turn presents its corporate road map as an application of the METI framework. This collaboration helps companies commit to ambitious transition plans, with the confidence that the government is doing its part in creating the conditions that will make them viable in terms of R&amp;D, energy infrastructure, finance, carbon pricing, and more. The GX plan is as much about enabling these road maps as it is about mandating them.</p><p></p><p> The plans are not rigid. In the future, different technologies might win out than what today&#39;s plans project. Both government and industry know the technology assumptions that the plans are based on and thus are able to adapt as needed and aren&#39;t locked in. Pluralism is celebrated: The cover image of METI&#39;s strategy document shows multiple paths up a mountain to the 2050 carbon-neutral summit.</p><p> Creating the conditions for corporate investments in this way is the role for governments&#39; industrial strategy, in partnership with sustainable finance. Without such coordinated industrial policies, merely strengthening disclosure requirements on climate-related data and information might increase regulatory burdens unproductively. Government efforts to step up sustainability-related reporting frameworks need to be matched by government actions on the industrial strategy front.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>