<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 16 日星期一 19:08:21 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>为什么薪酬透明度法规是一个战略管理机会</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>塔玛拉·蒙塔格-斯密特 (Tamara Montag-Smit) 是马萨诸塞大学 (UMass) 洛厄尔分校管理学助理教授。卡罗琳·埃文斯 (Karoline Evans) 是麻省大学洛厄尔分校管理学副教授。布兰登·斯密特是本特利大学管理学助理教授。卡森德拉·巴茨-巴巴里奇 (Cassondra Batz-Barbarich) 是森林湖学院 (Lake Forest College) 的商学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">安娜丽莎·格拉萨诺</p></figcaption></figure><p>薪酬透明度法被誉为解决性别工资差距的一种补救措施，美国各地州和地方各级越来越多地推出<a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">薪酬透明度法</a>。截至 9 月份，包括纽约在内的九个州目前正在规范薪酬披露的某些方面。国家妇女法律中心报告称，总共有超过四分之一的美国雇员居住在<a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">薪酬信息受到监管的</a>地区。</p><p>总的来说，薪酬透明度法规强调披露广告职位的薪酬范围和内部晋升机会。这些法律旨在确保同工同酬，有效缩小性别工资差距。逻辑很简单：如果工资过低的员工，包括女性和少数族裔，不知道他们的同事的工资是多少，那么他们在通过诉讼和谈判创造公平竞争环境时就会处于明显的劣势。当不平等现象仍然蒙在鼓里时，如何解决不平等问题呢？如果没有薪酬透明度，现有法律（例如<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">1963 年《同工同酬法案》）</a>的执行就会变得困难。根据<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">最近的案例</a>和已暴露的显着差异（有些跨越多年的少付），更大的透明度似乎可以发挥重要作用。</p><p></p><h3>对不断变化的监管环境的组织反应</h3><p>尽管薪酬透明度法规得到越来越广泛的采用，但许多组织的反应却是抵制、抵制和最低限度的合规性。科罗拉多州于 2021 年成为第一个要求组织披露广告职位薪资范围的州后，在全国范围内招募求职者的组织开始<a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">明确将科罗拉多州居民排除</a>在考虑范围之外，以规避新法律，促使该州劳工部发出 <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">警告和罚款</a>。另一种组织策略是遵守薪资信息要求，薪资范围过大，以至于申请人无法有意义地预测他们可能会得到的薪资。在一个著名的例子中，Netflix 发布了一份薪资范围<a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">为 90,000 美元到 900,000 美元的</a>职位。</p><p>虽然组织层面遵守透明度法律的方法有多种形式，但领导者对薪酬透明度对其业务运营和文化的潜在负面影响表达了一些共同的担忧：</p><ul><li><strong>每个人都会要求更多的钱吗？</strong>更多的薪酬信息可能会引发更多关于薪酬的讨论（以及为什么有人会得到他们的工资）。经理们担心，他们会陷入困境，试图兼顾预算和员工满意度方面的相互竞争的目标。</li><li><strong>如果一些员工发现他们的工资低于其他人，会发生什么？</strong>向老员工解释为什么他们的薪酬与新员工相同可能会让人感到不舒服，并会引发对雇主的严厉批评。</li><li><strong>薪酬透明度会影响我们的合作能力吗？</strong>当个人认为自己得到不公平的回报时，薪酬透明度可能会引起嫉妒和适得其反的竞争。经理们担心，当差异暴露出来时，员工可能会互相争斗并破坏彼此的利益。</li></ul><p></p><h3>管理薪酬透明度的新见解</h3><p>我们的工作为解决组织在透明度方面的一些主要问题提供了新的见解。大多数新法律只专注于通过要求组织披露空缺职位的薪酬范围来创造薪酬透明度。在学术研究中，这种形式的透明度被称为<em>分配透明度</em>，因为它仅披露有关员工工资<em>金额</em>的信息。</p><p>然而，在我们的研究中，我们描述了几种使薪酬信息透明的方法。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a><em>程序透明</em>，重点是共享有关如何制定薪酬<em>决策的</em>信息；在最透明的层面上，这将包括计算薪酬的公式（例如基本工资或基于绩效的加薪）。</p><p>区分分配透明度和程序透明度至关重要，因为正如我们的研究表明，程序透明度可以减轻与分配透明度相关的许多风险和缺点。</p><p>薪酬透明度法规隐含的理念是，工资过低的员工将自行协商<a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">争取更公平的工资</a>。事实上，过去二十年对超过 100,000 名学者进行的一项大规模研究发现，薪酬透明度的变化与男女之间的工资平等程度显着提高有关。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>然而，研究还表明，透明度并不等于<em>每个人都</em>要求更多。</p><p>为了进一步探索这一点，我们进行了一系列四项实验，以更好地了解薪酬透明度<em>如何</em>以及<em>何时</em>可以鼓励员工（尤其是女性）更有效地谈判公平工资。在我们的第一项研究中，实验室参与者在四轮流行的单词搜索游戏后根据他们的表现获得报酬，并有机会谈判以获得更好的报酬。在研究 2、3 和 4 中，在线参与者准备好进行绩效评估，并掌握有关绩效和薪酬的不同程度的信息，以便可能就更好的年度加薪进行谈判。他们被告知预计加薪 3%，但加薪幅度可能在 3% 到 10% 之间。在这些研究中，我们改变了参与者可以获得的信息量，包括其他人的报酬金额以及参与者相对于同龄人的表现。</p><p>这些研究得出了关于分配和程序薪酬透明度的四项重要发现：</p><p> <strong>1.人们进行了更清晰的比较。</strong>我们发现，判断某人是否试图通过谈判争取更高薪酬的最佳预测因素是他们相对于同事的表现。与平均绩效者相比，当高绩效者知道自己相对于其他人的排名时，他们要求更高薪酬的可能性大约高出 50%。值得注意的是，在我们的研究中，参与者看到了其团队成员上一年的绩效和薪酬数据，很明显，绩效的提高与薪酬的提高直接相关。尽管没有一个明确的公式表明基于绩效的薪酬，但这一信息向参与者提供了一个明确的信号：加薪很大程度上取决于绩效。</p><p> <strong>2. 人们公平地进行谈判。</strong>表现一般的员工更有可能接受向他们提供的最低加薪，通常认为根据他们的表现加薪是公平的。正如一位人士所说，“考虑到我这一年只达到了预期，而不是超出预期，要求更高的加薪似乎是徒劳的，也是不劳而获的。”一般来说，表现一般的员工很少要求最高加薪，部分原因是他们考虑到自己的表现低于某些同事。不过，只有当他们掌握了所有信息时，这才是真的。当他们不知道自己的表现时，85％的人要求最高工资金额。由于缺乏绩效信息，表现一般的员工要求薪资范围内的最高加薪。</p><p> <strong>3.女性<em>确实</em>要求更高的工资。</strong>与普遍的假设相反，女性似乎不需要太多鼓励来进行谈判。事实上，当考虑参加谈判的参与者的百分比时，女性往往比男性更有可能进行谈判（尽管这在统计上并不存在显着差异）。这些发现对以下观点提出了一些质疑：性别工资差距的原因之一是女性谈判的频率低于男性。最近的研究结合了数十项谈判研究的信息得出了相同的结论：近年来，男性和女性之间的许多谈判差距已基本消失。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>虽然这是个好消息，但它对于缩小目前的性别工资差距几乎没有作用。</p><p> <strong>4.人们有动力去表现得更好。</strong>表现一般的员工表达了更加努力工作、表现更好的动机，以便在下一个审核周期中获得更高的加薪。当被问及为什么不通过谈判争取更多的钱时，一位参与者表示：“我的数据并没有表明我应该得到更高的加薪。如果第二年的数字更好，就有理由提高加薪。”另一位则表示，“我知道自己的工作表现一般，所以我希望未来能做得更好，并希望明年能得到更好的加薪。”</p><p>我们的研究结果复制并扩展了管理研究中一个古老但强大的概念：<em>公平过程效应</em>。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>如果员工相信不利的结果是由公平的系统产生的，他们就会接受这些结果。换句话说，如果人们知道<em>为什么</em>他们的工资较低（换句话说，程序透明），他们就不会做出消极反应，甚至可能会更加努力地工作。</p><h3>让薪酬透明度为您的组织带来双赢</h3><p>薪酬透明度可以是双赢的机会，而不是合规障碍。但仅仅在招聘启事中列出薪资数据而没有任何符合法规的背景可能是一个很大的错误。这些做法不仅无视法律的精神，而且付出了沉重的代价并丧失了重要的机会。领导者的思考应该超越合规性，并考虑如何战略性地利用组织的薪酬透明度，以提高申请人的吸引力和员工的保留率。我们的研究为如何做到这一点提供了一些见解。</p><p><strong>让薪酬只是透明度等式的<em>一部分</em>。</strong>人们普遍担心透明度会增加劳动力成本、引起嫉妒并引发冲突，但事实是，薪酬保密本身也会带来问题。 Payscale 的研究人员发现，大多数员工<a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">不确定自己的薪酬是否公平</a>，许多人认为自己的薪酬过低，而事实并非如此，这导致更大的人员流动和不满。我们的研究表明，如果没有绩效参考点，员工几乎没有基础来判断薪酬是否公平，因此更有可能提出不合理的要求。绩效<em>和</em>薪酬的透明度可以让员工更好地评估其薪酬的公平性并提出更合理的要求。</p><p></p><p><strong>关注薪酬决策过程。</strong>程序透明度有助于管理人员更清楚地与员工沟通薪酬问题，因为工资/奖金是基于绩效而不是基于看似无形的因素，或者更糟糕的是充满偏见的因素。提供有关如何确定薪酬的信息可以帮助现任员工了解为什么他们的薪酬高于或低于同事，更重要的是，了解如何晋升。当薪酬直接由绩效决定时，管理者就不能被指责有偏袒和偏见，这使得他们在薪酬谈判中处于协作角色。这些对话以绩效为重点，可以关注发展并研究员工如何才能表现得更好并获得更高的加薪。</p><p><strong>认识到（分配）薪酬透明度本身并不能解决不平等问题。</strong>有一种假设认为，薪酬分配透明度将缩小薪酬差距；然而，有证据表明，仅靠这一点不足以创造一个公平的工作场所。研究表明，女性和男性<em>要求</em>加薪的<a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">比例相对相等</a>，但女性在实现自己的要求方面仍然不太成功。分配薪酬透明度有助于减少一些模糊性，但绩效和薪酬透明度（程序透明度）共同为员工提供了要求他们应得的东西所需的工具。当人们知道谈判会带来什么（即谈判范围是什么以及合理的要求）时，性别差异就会最小化。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>例如，<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">有色人种女性</a>通常不会利用机会协商角色、责任或灵活的工作安排，从而造成长期不平等，从而解释了起薪以外的薪酬差距。更广泛的透明度有助于减少模糊性，这种模糊性常常使妇女和其他少数群体成员在谈判时犹豫不决，即使她们知道自己可以。</p><p><strong>考虑对现有员工<em>和</em>申请人的好处。</strong>简单地公布薪资范围只是问题的一小部分。申请人对过大的薪酬范围有负面反应，因为他们没有提供有用的信息。在这种情况下，薪酬本质上仍然是秘密的。正如我们在研究中发现的那样，如果没有有意义的信息，人们倾向于要求最大金额，看看有什么可能。这给招聘经理带来了另一个头痛的问题。更好的方法是利用程序透明度来清楚地概述确定薪资报价时使用的因素，甚至可能包括这些因素的权重。例如，营销公司 Buffer 在创建一个<a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">薪酬系统方面</a>做得非常出色，该系统通过使用制定薪酬决策的标准公式来平衡简单性（为了更好地理解）和复杂性（为了捕捉细微差别）：薪水 = 工作类型 x 资历x 经验 + 地点 + 10,000 美元或股权。</p><p></p><p></p><p>尽管组织对实施有关薪酬透明度的政府法规存在担忧和犹豫，但此类政策继续受到关注，并且只是对薪酬披露的期望不断提高的推动力之一。在人力资源技术公司 Visier 2022 年的一份报告中，79% 的受访员工表示他们希望<a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">薪酬透明</a>； Z 世代员工是最强烈的支持者。</p><p>我们的研究强调了程序透明度的潜力，可以战略性地减轻感知的组织风险，同时满足法律要求和社会期望。虽然变化显然正在发生，但我们希望企业领导者能够更深入、更具创造性地思考<em>如何</em>以既支持组织目标又满足员工需求的方式实现薪酬透明。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>挑战上级的微妙动态</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>本杰明·莱克 ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) 是雷丁大学亨利商学院的领导力教授。</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>挑战上级的行为不仅仅需要提高声音，还需要更多的努力。它涉及理解、驾驭和参与权力动态、外交和相互尊重的微妙而复杂的舞蹈。接近职业等级中比你高的人需要微妙的平衡以及对这个人和情况的深刻理解。</p><p>对于那些热衷于保持职业礼仪并不断成长的人来说，本指南可以帮助确保您的富有挑战性的对话既具有建设性又充满尊重。</p><p></p><p><strong>明智地选择你的战斗。</strong>工作场所是充满活力的观点、流程和方法的生态系统。解决一个人遇到的每一个观点差异或分歧可能很诱人，但智慧在于辨别哪些战斗值得打。每次出现潜在分歧时，请考虑：这个问题是否如此重要以至于需要对抗？意见上的微小分歧可以通过被动渠道更有效地解决，甚至应该被忽视。但更大的问题，尤其是那些影响团队动力、公司文化或更广泛业务目标的问题，需要采取更直接的方法。</p><p><strong>了解时机的重要性。</strong>在专业沟通的世界中，时机就是一切。选择正确的时机可以决定是否真正考虑某个问题或仓促地驳回某个问题。在考虑挑战上级之前，暂停并从整体角度评估情况至关重要。您的担忧是否如此紧迫以至于需要立即解决？或者，是否最好将其指定为稍后进行详细的私人讨论？明智的做法是避免在高压情况下或公共论坛上与上级对抗，因为这可能会被误解为试图破坏或炫耀。通过选择最佳时间，您可以为建设性对话创造更顺畅的路径。</p><p></p><p><strong>优先考虑私人讨论。</strong>您选择表达担忧的环境对于如何接受这些担忧起着关键作用。参与公开分歧或冲突可能会导致多种不可预见的并发症，包括被视为具有攻击性或对抗性。通过选择私人环境进行这些讨论，您可以为自己和上级提供有利于公开和真诚对话的氛围。这种方法不仅可以最大限度地减少干扰和潜在的偏见，而且还强化了这样一种观念：其意图是建设性反馈，而不是公众批评。</p><p><strong>掌握“我”陈述的艺术。</strong>有效的沟通不仅关乎内容，也关乎交付。我们选择的措辞和表达担忧的方式会极大地影响我们信息的接收。不要采用潜在的对抗性语气，而是使用“我”的陈述来表达观察、感受和建议。例如，与其直言不讳地说“你忽略了这个关键方面”，更具协作性的方法是“我认为这个特定方面可以从进一步的关注中受益”。这种方法确保焦点仍然集中在当前的问题上，而不是个人偏见或对抗上。</p><p></p><p><strong>拥抱反馈过程。</strong>挑战上级或表达担忧的过程本质上是双边的。这不仅是您表达想法的途径，也是了解他人观点的机会。即使反馈与您的观点相矛盾，也要表现出真正的开放态度，这一点至关重要。这种方法不仅为相互尊重铺平了道路，而且在组织内培育了持续学习和协作的文化。</p><p><strong>与志同道合的同事结盟，但要巧妙。</strong>虽然个人的担忧有其道理，但不可否认的是，数量的力量。寻找与您观点相同的盟友或同事可以进一步减轻您的担忧。然而，这种联盟必须不被视为拉帮结派或分裂。主要关注点应始终放在组织的集体利益上，而不是在团队内形成派系。</p><p><strong>将组织的目标放在首位。</strong>您提出的任何疑虑或挑战都应该与组织更广泛的目标和目标产生内在的共鸣。通过始终将您的反馈和建议与公司的使命和价值观保持一致，您可以向上级保证您对组织集体成功的承诺而不是个人愿望。</p><p><strong>为一系列结果做好准备。</strong>虽然我们都希望我们的分歧能取得积极和建设性的成果，但有必要为各种反应做好准备。你的上级可能会乐于接受、漠不关心，甚至是防御性的。通过预测这些潜在的反应并相应地规划您的策略，您可以确保无论即时反馈如何，您都保持平衡、建设性和专业。</p><h3>后果：反思、适应和发展</h3><p></p><p>每一次职业互动，尤其是那些涉及挑战或对抗的互动，都为个人和职业成长提供了丰富的机会。讨论结束后，花时间评估对话的有效性、所采用的策略以及取得的成果。这些反思将为您带来宝贵的经验教训，并帮助您不断完善和增强您的沟通技巧，以应对未来的挑战。</p><p>最终，虽然挑战上级的任务似乎充满了潜在的陷阱，但只要采取正确的策略并注重相互成长和尊重，就可以通过机智和专业精神来完成它。鼓励公开对话和反馈文化是创新和前瞻性组织的基石。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>幽灵情景如何困扰战略执行</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang 是牛津大学赛德商学院管理实践高级研究员，也是牛津协作战略实验室主任。拉斐尔·拉米雷斯 (Rafael Ramírez) 是赛德商学院的实践教授，也是牛津情景项目的主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">帕特里克·乔治/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>从事战略规划的高管通常存在盲点。他们几乎只关注可能的行动方针，很少关注这些行动将在未来的社会经济和环境背景下发挥作用。在我们 70 年的研究、实践和教学过程中，我们以及其他人观察到，企业领导者及其组织的配置倾向于仅以一种对未来的隐含观点开展工作。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这种观点通常深深植根于他们的战略中，作为对未来环境的一组毫无疑问的假设。我们将这些未经检验的假设称为<em>“幽灵情景”</em> ，因为它们是无形的，而且可能会以意想不到和不受欢迎的方式再次困扰高管和公司。</p><p></p><p>每一个幽灵情景的基础都是一小部分隐含的趋势，领导者在不怀疑这些趋势是否会改变的情况下预测了未来。想想气候的剧烈变化是如何影响英国铁路服务的。 2022 年 7 月，该国首次记录到超过 40 摄氏度（104 华氏度）的气温。这些高温将铁轨加热到略高于 62 摄氏度（143 华氏度），导致它们弯曲。结果，许多火车行程被取消，其他路线的服务速度减慢至 60 英里/小时。铁轨专为未来气温不超过 27 摄氏度（80 华氏度）而设计。简而言之，英国铁路网的设计和建造并不是为了 2022 年的情景，而是为了隐含地假设历史气候趋势将继续保持不变。</p><h3>假设隐藏在众目睽睽之下</h3><p>对人类感知的研究表明，人们通过将视觉焦点的物体置于他们注意力的最前面，而其他一切都后退，从而将其视觉焦点的物体与其背景区分开来。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>人类可以将注意力集中在人物或背景上，但不能同时关注两者。</p><p><a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">鲁宾花瓶错觉</a>是这种图形-背景（或背景）感知挑战的一个众所周知的例子。根据您观察图片的方式，您会看到一个花瓶或两张脸的侧面。然而，重要的是，你不能同时看到两者：其中一个在感知上会后退，成为你所看到的人物的背景。要看到这两个数字，您必须在它们之间交替显示。</p><p>重要的是，高管们必须认识到人们的专注能力也会让他们忽视重要的背景信息，因为领导者常常看不到他们的战略将发挥的背景以及他们的战略所依赖的背景。他们可能认为硬基础设施（例如铁路轨道）是一个相对静态的背景问题，并将注意力集中在对业务规划似乎更重要的趋势上，例如客户偏好和习惯的变化。但这可能会导致高管们实施一项战略，而该战略可能会因与背景问题交织在一起的未经审查的假设而出乎意料地受到干扰。</p><p></p><p>特别是在今天，鉴于变化速度快、不确定性飙升和动荡程度高，未能将战略规划中内置的假设浮出水面是有风险的，就像未能通过<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">情景规划</a>考虑多种可能的替代未来一样。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>情景规划练习可以帮助管理人员探索他们的策略在不同的业务环境和条件下如何发挥作用，并着眼于磨练这些策略以使其更加有效。</p><p>为了了解情景规划如何防止高管受到幽灵情景的困扰，让我们看看我们最近在牛津情景计划中合作的两个全球组织。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA 审查其 ESG 假设</h3><p>保险公司<a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a>为 50 多个国家的 9500 万客户提供财产伤亡保险、人寿保险和储蓄以及资产管理领域的产品和服务。该公司的关键战略目标之一是维持其气候领导地位。 AXA 的高管明智地决定在有限的时间内将该目标的未来背景作为他们关注的焦点，以便他们可以探索它可能会如何变化，以及如果发生变化，他们可能需要如何适应。</p><p>该公司特别有兴趣了解未来的环境、社会和治理 (ESG) 趋势可能如何影响其既定目标。例如，美国一些州拟议的立法将惩罚奉行 ESG 投资策略的金融机构，这可能会产生什么影响？或者，如果公司被视为洗绿或歪曲其 ESG 资质，公众会如何反应？因此，该公司并没有像目前所理解的那样，让 ESG 要求成为幻影，而是提出了有关 ESG 未来的问题，更广泛地说，提出了有关企业新兴可持续发展环境的问题。</p><p>情景规划练习的参与者和协调者以团队形式合作，着眼于未来的环境。一种设想是，独立保险公司被占主导地位的科技平台吞并，而这些平台的 ESG 优先事项取代了保险公司的优先事项。在另一种情况下，政府制定了有关 ESG 问题的严格法规，这对公司的战略选择具有合规性影响。在另一个想象中的未来，气候变化的加速速度超出预期，导致企业将优先事项转向紧急解决气候相关危机，或者只专注于减少二氧化碳排放，放弃社会和治理议程。</p><p>通过明确参与幽灵情景及其同样合理的替代方案，AXA 开始认识到，继续努力提供目前所理解的卓越 ESG 绩效可能并不是它应该为的唯一未来做好准备。在 AXA 内部，这些见解已被用来为有关未来 ESG 挑战及其对可能发布的公告和承诺的影响（包括何时发布和与谁发布）的对话提供信息。他们促使 AXA 开始准备替代策略，以防根据当前 ESG 预期提供出色的业绩变得无关紧要。</p><p></p><h3> Swift 期待数字货币</h3><p>Swift（全球银行间金融电信协会）是一家会员制合作社，为全球跨境支付提供金融消息传递和相关服务。目前，它每天为 200 多个国家和地区的 11,000 多家机构发送超过 3000 万条消息。它由 15 个国家的 239 家银行于 20 世纪 70 年代初创建，旨在通过新技术平台解决跨境支付通信笨重、缓慢且成本高昂的日益严重的问题。颠覆是 Swift 起源故事的一部分，因此它积极主动地应对其环境中的潜在变化。</p><p> 2021 年，Swift 高管有兴趣了解数字货币（包括央行发行的货币）在未来几年可能会如何发展。 2021 年，该类别的加密货币数量增加了一倍多，达到 9,000 多种。</p><p> Swift 的高管并没有假设数字货币的这种展开和快速增长是唯一可能的情况，而是停下来更好地了解可能发生的其他发展、它们将如何塑造未来的数字货币生态系统以及 Swift 可能会受到怎样的影响。例如，经济学家和其他专家指出许多数字货币缺乏内在价值，以及<a href="https://concerned.tech/">对其底层技术的安全性和可靠性的</a>担忧。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>通用战略规划流程中的幽灵隐藏在哪里</h4><p><strong>在 SWOT 分析中，</strong>领导者仅根据当前情况以及已知的竞争对手、供应商、客户、监管规则等来考虑其组织的优势、劣势、机会和威胁。在识别和分析风险时，高管们隐含地假设只有一种情况。然而，在另一种情况下（不同的场景），风险可能会消失，新的机会可能会出现。</p><p><strong>在利益相关者绘图中，</strong>领导者对利益相关者现在和预期未来的注意力和权力进行评估。隐含的场景是本次评估的背景。但如果环境发生意外变化，利益相关者的重要性可能会发生重大变化。</p><p><strong>在博弈论和兵棋推演中，</strong>竞争对手的举动是在幽灵场景的背景下考虑的，而兵棋推演通常不会考虑与正在进行的未来不同的未来。然而，不断变化的场景可能需要新的战术并暴露出不可预见的未来战斗人员。<br /></article></aside></div><p>斯威夫特本人对数字货币的立场是开放和中立的。如果它们得到适当的监管并为其服务的经济、企业和社区增加价值，它将有可能为它们提供支持。</p><p>为 Swift 高管开发的场景探索了对技术的信任可能演变的不同方式。在其中一些国家中，随着数字货币所基于的不透明技术和算法变得可疑，与数字货币相关的信任将会消失。 In other scenarios, digital currencies could be manipulated, and thus the authenticity of what was being exchanged could no longer be guaranteed. And in another scenario, a more generalized lack of trust in for-profit financial institutions would spread to providers of digital currencies, leading some segments of society to hesitate to engage with either, with related consequences.</p><p> For the Oxford participants envisioning these scenarios, it was not clear that the values held by those promoting the technology, or the values that the technology supposedly enabled, would be accepted by governmental regulators or by those in society at large in all imaginable future contexts. Swift&#39;s executives have since explored those sets of scenarios, which provided rich and divergent insights about the ways digital currencies might pan out. Those insights have helped them avoid relying on overly simplistic views of the future — and being swayed by hype.</p><h3> How to See a Ghost Before It Haunts You</h3><p> Based on our experience leading scenario planning exercises for AXA, Swift, and many other organizations, we have developed the following suggestions for executives who want to bring their ghost scenarios into view and make the figure-ground reversal a key part of their strategy practice.</p><p> <strong>Use scenario planning to acknowledge implicit assumptions.</strong> Recognize that every organization&#39;s strategy presumes a future scenario that often remains unquestioned. That is, every executive engages in a form of implicit scenario planning, whether they are conscious of it or not. Making scenario planning a regular part of the strategy-making process achieves two important goals: It alerts leaders to how turbulent conditions could change the context within which they work and compete, and it acknowledges the reality that current conditions themselves present a hypothetical future scenario, not a fixed reality.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize the figure-ground dilemma.</strong> Acknowledge that the figure that is attended to (most often, the organization&#39;s strategy) and the background that is so often ignored (the unexamined ghost scenario) cannot successfully be the focus of attention at the same time. Instead, executives need to flexibly and sequentially shift between the two to investigate each fully and avoid the trap of making implicit assumptions about the other. AXA took the time to deliberately explore the future of ESG rather than assuming there would be no changes to how it is currently used and understood. Swift purposefully focused on understanding the potential future contexts of digital currencies rather than just implicitly assuming subsequent options from the existing trends.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Dedicate executive time and resources to the problem.</strong> Organizations must intentionally create a time and space for leaders to explore how relevant economic, political, technological, social, and environmental factors might be changing. Contrast a small set of future scenarios with the ghost scenario to pinpoint where current strategy might need to be adapted to be well positioned for the range of ways the context might develop. Some organizations even have dedicated units, such as the <a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">Global Business Environment scenarios team</a> at Shell International. <a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">Policy Horizons Canada</a> plays this role for the Canadian government.</p><p></p><p> For all of these efforts to be truly useful, scenario planning outputs must be fed back into strategic decision-making rather than written up in a report and placed on a shelf. They should also be disseminated more widely in an organization so that people at all levels and functions can consider possible implications from their own perspective — implications that might not occur to leadership. For a strategy to be successful when the context changes, executives need to have a balanced approach — recognizing both figure and ground as important areas for discernment. That is, they must recognize the importance of the background or ground upon which their actions will play out, even as they plan their next move. Savvy executives know that they must both envision and embrace change. The trick is learning to adeptly shift one&#39;s attention between the figure and the ground to see how the context might unfold, so it doesn&#39;t leave your strategy ungrounded.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Fueling Interdisciplinary Innovation With AI: Volvo&#39;s Anders Sjögren</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automotive Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory. On this episode of the Me, Myself, and AI podcast, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Anders joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to explain the ways the carmaker uses data and artificial intelligence to inform manufacturing — ensuring that parts are made consistently and as efficiently as possible — as well as driver experience and safety. He also outlines some specific ways smart technology keeps drivers alert and aware of conditions around them and describes Volvo&#39;s approach to technology-driven innovation. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/MMAI-S8-E1-Sjogren-Volvo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Anders Sjögren"></p><h4> Anders Sjögren, Volvo Cars</h4><p> Anders Sjögren is senior technical leader for Volvo Cars. He focuses on strategy, research, innovation, and transformation, with the key objective of ensuring that the automaker understands and executes within the continuously emerging areas of data, analytics, and artificial intelligence. Application areas include creating AI-enabled intelligent customer functionality and using AI to reform Volvo&#39;s operations and development activities. Sjögren has an academic background in mathematical statistics (large-scale and computational aspects) and an industrial background in data-centric methods development and software product development.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one carmaker use AI to bring together all of the complex systems required to engineer a safe and high-performing vehicle? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m Anders Sjögren from Volvo Cars, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Today, Sam and I are delighted to be joined by Anders Sjögren, senior technical leader, data, analytics, and AI-enabled engineering, at Volvo Cars.让我们开始吧。 Anders, welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So tell us a little bit about your role at Volvo Cars.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m a technical leader in data, analytics, and AI in the engineering part [of the organization], so that&#39;s the R&amp;D. So, essentially, what comes in is a wish for a car, and what comes out is drawings and code. In that area, there are, of course, a lot of possibilities for data analytics and AI, both during the development process and also as part of the actual functions in the car — so intelligent functions and personalized functions and so on.</p><p> So my purpose here is really to make sure that we get the value that we can through data, analytics, and AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is [your focus] the AI and data analytics that go into the car — like the sensors and all kinds of intelligent devices in the car that make driving safer and more interactive, and things like that? Or is it also customer acquisition and dealer networks and all kinds of data analytics to run a business of making and selling cars?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yes. So, I mean, all of those apply to Volvo Cars, but the part I&#39;m really active in is more in the part of the making of the car.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think that&#39;s a great point because when most people think about cars and artificial intelligence, I think they immediately jump to this idea of fully self-driving cars. And what you&#39;re pointing out is how much other stuff that there is going on, even in the production of cars, that can benefit from artificial intelligence. You know, I think perhaps everyone&#39;s frustrated that we don&#39;t have fully automated cars now, but there&#39;s so much going on behind the scenes that people don&#39;t get a chance to see. What are some of the examples of the ways that you&#39;re using artificial intelligence in the production process?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we take a little bit of a step back, the goal of Volvo Cars is really to give people the freedom to move in a personal and sustainable and a safe way.</p><p> If we start with “personal,” then it&#39;s really critical that we understand you and make you feel special as a customer or as someone in the car. And there, of course, it has to do with starting with the sensors and then really interpreting those values. That can be cameras, different types of steering input …</p><p> Another area is definitely sustainability. AI is being used there to make sure that we have as many lightweight parts as possible. So using AI, one can, for example, get mechanical parts with the same strength and those kind of properties, but with much lower weight and less material that&#39;s being used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In the design process, you&#39;re talking about, right? As engineers consider all the different permutations of parts, yeah?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> In the design process — yes, exactly. That&#39;s really the essence of AI, I think, in lots of engineering activities, is that we go from manually deciding first what we want to do, but then actually performing all the different steps. That&#39;s the current way of doing it, while in the AI era, it&#39;s much more about deciding and describing what are the aspects I want to reach to? What are things I want optimized, and what are maybe the boundary conditions? And then the AI helps you get there.</p><p> So in the context of the mechanical parts, you might say, “These are the attachment points. These are the strength and stiffness properties I want. Give me the part with those properties but [make it] as light as possible and also, of course, possible to produce.”</p><p> That could be one area. And also, it is super important for sustainability that we use as little material as possible and also have as low a rate as possible.</p><p> And then, of course, the third point was about [safety]. And, of course, we have autonomous cars, but also, even before that, there are other types of functionality being used. For example, understanding the driver: Is the driver aware or not? Should we maybe nudge him to take a cup of coffee or something if he seems to be tired?</p><p> In the later versions of our cars, we understand if there are some pets or children left in the car, maybe on a hot day, and then preventing them [from getting] hurt in such a situation and so on.</p><p> I&#39;d say that those are some of the areas where AI can really be a core technology in bringing us toward our purpose.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s really interesting because lots of times organizations tell us they start with a problem they&#39;re trying to solve and then find a technology to solve it, and that makes sense, because otherwise you&#39;re trying to find a problem to fit a solution, which seems backward. You mentioned that your cars can sense … if a person or a pet is accidentally left in the car. How did Volvo make the decision to focus on that particular problem to solve?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> A lot of what we do is really created by real-world safety in that we actually see what are the actual causes of people getting injured. I mean, if we take the analogy with crashes and that type of safety, we have teams that go out to sites when there has been a crash to really see what actually happened in reality and not just on certification [from] that type of crash test and so on.</p><p> And, going back to this example, if we look here, pets and kids do get hurt — hopefully not in a Volvo car, but that&#39;s reality, right?</p><p> But what you mentioned there is really super interesting because then it also goes the other way around: Like, now that we have these sensors, what are the other really valuable functionalities that we can provide our customers with through this, of course, taking privacy into account and so on?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is quite intriguing because Volvo … I remember as a child that my uncle used to say, “You want a safe car, you get a Volvo.” And it&#39;s always been synonymous with safety, and it&#39;s really amazing to step back and think about ... for a company who has put one of its main goals for safe experience, now, with the availability of this amount of data and all of this massive amount of processing, I could imagine there are so many use cases that, to Sam&#39;s point, are being thought about. So that&#39;s really, really encouraging.</p><p> What [does] the road map here look like? I mean, is this a constant sort of innovation ideation approach going on to say, “What else could we do in these three pillars of personal, safe, and sustainable?” What is the process for coming up with these ideas and picking up the good ones and pursuing them or not?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think that those ideas can either come from the technology side and be really inspired by that, or it could come from the analytics side. And often it&#39;s when the new technology and the really customer-centric needs … where they meet, and also, of course, where we have the agility in the organization to execute on it. That&#39;s really where we have something that&#39;s really fruitful. It&#39;s typically a mix of different sources of this: innovations and new directions, I would say.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And there&#39;s a mechanism to create this interdisciplinary inspiration in the company?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I would say so. I would say that there are both formal mechanisms but also informal mechanisms. [As] a car company, Volvo Cars is not super big. Of course there are also smaller ones, but I think it&#39;s also an advantage that, I mean, pretty much all the different steps, from product strategy, design, the R&amp;D, engineering, and then the later stages …</p><p> The headquarters is in Gothenburg [in Sweden], within walking distance. The US department is literally 50 meters from where I&#39;m sitting right now, while 50 meters in the other direction, there are the crash test facilities and the safety center.</p><p> So, what I want to say with that is that it&#39;s more easy to get connections and to create this kind of — how should I put it? — informal innovation activities.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is where relatively smaller size and colocation really, really helps. To have teams that close to each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s funny to talk about it being small, because it&#39;s certainly not a small company.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, I guess. As we&#39;re chatting, I&#39;m thinking about some of the people we&#39;ve talked to before, and one of the recurring themes that people have mentioned is, oh, this idea [of] starting with a business problem: “You don&#39;t have AI and find a place to use it. You start with a business problem and then solve it.” But this is kind of a nice mix on that — that it sounds like there&#39;s a lot that starts with a business problem, but then, interestingly, once these processes are in place, and once these technologies are in place, then there becomes a grassroots innovation to say, “All right; how can we use that?” And that&#39;s an interesting perspective that, I think, hasn&#39;t come through strongly — or maybe I&#39;m forgetting something — but it seems like that hasn&#39;t come through as strongly. This is a nice mix of that, that maybe works in this size organization … this colocated organization.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, and not least in the prototyping and ideation stages. But, then, of course, before it actually goes into the product, it needs to go through a more thorough review and so on.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> There&#39;s been quite a few investments and acquisitions of smaller AI startups and firms by Volvo. Tell us a bit about the overall ecosystem of internal and vendor and partner companies that come together to bring to life some of these AI-enabled ideas that you&#39;re talking about. Is it internal? Is it external? Is it a mix? How do you think about the ecosystem?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I would definitely say that it&#39;s a mix. Some of the things … we need to do it ourselves to get the full understanding or where we really want to be in the forefront, and [in] some other areas, we definitely want to partner with other companies that are strong in those areas. Traditionally speaking, a car is a super complex product. It has hundreds or thousands of different parts that all need to come together. And, of course, it is a space where there is traditionally a lot of suppliers supplying different parts.</p><p> Lately, we are moving more toward bringing software implementation in-house to increase the speed and agility in the development process.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That seems particularly complicated in auto manufacturing because if I think about how cars got started, they were independent systems. There was a braking system, and a power train system, and an air conditioner, and an infotainment system, and all these were separate. And that&#39;s kind of nice because then we have a certain, different standard than we would have for the infotainment system than we would have for the braking system — or at least I hope that there would be. But what you&#39;re pointing out is, each one of these may be using sensors that come from a different area, and how the whole car has become more complicated independently, but it&#39;s also become more complicated cohesively, trying to connect all these parts and have them work together.</p><p> And that seems, on the one hand, an opportunity for artificial intelligence but, at the same time, a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah. It&#39;s 100% true. It&#39;s both a really big opportunity, but that also means that&#39;s really one of the core challenges — I mean, how to build the cohesive understanding of both the inside and the outside of the car.</p><p> We speak about the customer digital twin and vehicle digital twin and so on, and in some sense, those aspects can mean a lot of different things. But, of course, these different systems that you speak about, they are traditionally in different parts of the company, so that also means that there is a lot of cross-functional collaboration that is needed. But we really need to bridge those kind of organizational borders.</p><p> I think that that&#39;s really one of the key points — that is, in order to get successful adoption of the analytics and AI, it really means that different parts of the company need to work together to make it happen. Because otherwise, it will just become a silo. Some people will not really have the benefits of it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You know, it&#39;s very true. It&#39;s a common theme, and in our work at BCG, we have this rule of thumb — the 10:20:70 — where we say 10% is the data and algorithms, and 20% is the technology and the digital platform, but 70% of it is the business integration and implementation and bringing different parts of the organization together. This, perhaps, is nowhere more true than at a car company, where you have, as you said, Sam, seemingly disparate systems that are coming together to create a bigger system, but each one of these units has been perfected individually, and now you want the collective perfection as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we talked a lot about Volvo. How did you personally get interested in artificial intelligence, in data, in technology and analytics? What&#39;s your origin story?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think I&#39;ve always been interested in computers. My father was really an addict, so I kind of grew up with that.</p><p> I started out as an engineering student [and got a] master&#39;s in computer science. And then I started off as a research engineer in the medical area, at the university hospital in Gothenburg, then found out fairly quickly that in order to really make use of data — conclusions and so on come from data … so I then went into the area of mathematical statistics.</p><p> So I did a Ph.D. in that, then went back to software product development. After some time, I went back to academia for a couple of years, did a postdoc, and then was offered a good opportunity at Volvo Cars. So I&#39;ve essentially been here for seven years now. That&#39;s a bit of my history.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Quite inspiring.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we also want to ask you a few rapid-fire questions, and the idea is just to answer it as quickly as you can. These are not particularly Volvo questions.</p><p> What have you been proudest of that you&#39;ve done with artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The problem is that most of the things, I can&#39;t speak about.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer too.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You have to wait and see. OK, well, what worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The worries?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Oh, I think, of course, one is the longer term — the kind of singularity things. But I think a bit closer to now, so to speak, we definitely see that this super-fast progression of large language [models] and what they can do, and also the kind of systems that don&#39;t just take one problem and give one answer but can really produce a series of steps, in sequence. And that is a super-powerful technology, but a super-powerful technology can be used both for good and for bad.</p><p> That&#39;s both something that makes me super excited but also a little bit worried. What will the world look like in 20 years?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Motorcycling, but obviously using technology. But it&#39;s more of a … yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Technology&#39;s involved. Everything&#39;s involved in technology in some way.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, pretty much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were a kid? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Medical doctor.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, that ties with your first career in working in the medical company, then.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I think so, but then I found mathematics and those things to be super exciting, so I went into that area.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What do you hope that we can gain from the advent of these technologies?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we say the greatest wish, I think it is that we find a way to use it in a way for our common good. We need to find a way to integrate it into society, and I think that that is really my biggest wish for it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In a relatively short time, we learned so much about various uses of data, AI, and technology, in just what it takes to build a car in new ways, and all the different ways that AI and tech are helping and serving the people who are driving them. It&#39;s been really enlightening, Anders. Thank you for joining.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thanks for having me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Ways Leaders Can Turn Pushback Into Progress</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phillip G. Clampitt and Bob DeKoch. <p>Phillip G. Clampitt is the Blair Endowed Chair in Communication at the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay. Bob DeKoch is the founder of leadership consulting firm Limitless and former president of the Boldt Co. They are the coauthors of <cite>Leading with Care in a Tough World</cite> (Rodin Books, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it’s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Clampitt-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it&#39;s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns and raising questions to active opposition and sabotage. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> Effective leaders think of pushback as an opportunity to boost their team&#39;s learning while moving their organization forward. The objective should be to increase people&#39;s understanding and build support by tempering both advocate enthusiasm and contrarian pessimism. This deeper level of understanding, while not necessarily satisfying to all in the moment, fosters a climate of candor, humility, adaptation, and trust, thereby subtly steering pushback away from latent disruptive tendencies.</p><p></p><p> Drawing on decades of research, C-suite observations, and interviews, we&#39;ve identified the major mistakes leaders make when encountering pushback and offer five guidelines to help them better respond.</p><h3> What Doesn&#39;t Work</h3><p> Leaders make three primary mistakes when facing ambivalence, disagreement, or resistance:</p><p> <strong>Suppressing uncertainty.</strong> Pushback increases uncertainty when questions are raised that might not have immediate answers or perspectives are introduced that might have recently emerged or been sidelined or overlooked. Some leaders respond to uncertainty-induced pushback by marginalizing concerns, offering placating assurances, or invoking authoritarian voices. Such practices offer false certainty that undermines trust in the long term.</p><p> According to our research, even employees who seek more certainty in their work lives want their organizations to embrace uncertainty. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Effective leaders avoid the temptation to paper over uncertainty, even when they face demands for a level of certainty that simply doesn&#39;t exist. Even if they don&#39;t know the answers now, they can provide an operating level of certainty by discussing how they will find those answers.</p><p> <strong>Ignoring power dynamics.</strong> Leaders with positional or acquired status directly or subtly influence the nature of the pushback. Highly authoritarian power structures tend to drive pushback underground. Likewise, more subtle power signals can suppress open discussion of legitimate concerns. Leaders might then wrongly equate silence with agreement. Some people will feign acceptance while others sow dissent in the “meeting after the meeting,” thereby revealing and often amplifying people&#39;s fears.</p><p></p><p> We had an opportunity to observe one seasoned executive group&#39;s reaction — which consisted of tepid and token feedback — when their CEO proposed a new initiative. The CEO, sensing a lack of candor, probed for more input. One frustrated executive eventually blurted out, “We don&#39;t share our thoughts on this issue because you are going to do what you are going to do, regardless of what we say.” This remarkably candid comment suggested a deeper challenge: How do powerful people with strong views on particular issues encourage candor? Effective leaders take active steps to mitigate disruptive dialogue — discussed below — because they recognize that inherent power dynamics greatly influence the quality of any discussion.</p><p> <strong>Assuming that the loudest voices represent a consensus.</strong> Pushback takes many forms: Some of them are obvious, like complaints or employee petitions, while others are more subtle, like queries in meetings or a lack of engagement. Leaders are often tempted to pay more attention to the most vocal employees, assuming the people with the biggest megaphones represent majority opinion. They may or may not.</p><p> When the loudest or most politically powerful voices dominate the discussion, such dynamics often create an inaccurate impression of the level of support or divisiveness. Effective leaders recognize the peril at either extreme: the enthusiasts glossing over concerning issues or the contrarians undermining potential support.</p><p></p><h3> Recommendations for Engaging With Pushback</h3><p> Effective leaders not only avoid suppressing uncertainty, ignoring power dynamics, and assuming that the most vocal represent consensus opinion — they also take active countermeasures that reflect the following guidelines.</p><p> <strong>1. Set ground rules for the conversation.</strong> Ground rules like the following drive expectations, temper disrespectful advocacy, and increase the value of pushback opportunities for everyone:</p><ul><li> <strong>Seek to understand viewpoints you don&#39;t agree with.</strong> When discussing contentious issues, many people&#39;s first instinct is to offer an instant rebuttal or counterpoint. Resist that temptation by demonstrating a willingness to engage with a differing point of view. Simple tactics like asking questions or rephrasing someone else&#39;s argument — particularly those with which you disagree — can temper the rebuttal and almost magically enhance the conversational tone. Likewise, statements like “Tell me how my idea might be wrong” or “I may have missed something; please say more” signal openness to new ideas.</li><li> <strong>Respectfully disagree with others.</strong> Respectfully framing the disagreements with language such as “Let me offer another perspective” sets the right discussion tone while also encouraging those who are more hesitant to speak up. Reluctance to share differing points of view often signals an underlying trust deficit. Sometimes leaders need to encourage others to share their concerns despite the inherent power differences in the room.</li><li> <strong>Avoid polarizing, stake-in-the-ground assertions.</strong> Advocating with too much certainty may well trigger power-dynamic issues. Indicating probability levels, such as “I&#39;m 95% certain on this fact,” often stimulates more robust debate.</li><li> <strong>Depersonalize pushback.</strong> If a decision is labeled as “the CEO&#39;s program,” many people will self-censor and avoid raising concerns out of fear of offending the person in power. Depersonalizing pushback by recording concerns on a whiteboard, without attribution, mitigates this power dynamic while tempering strong emotions.</li><li> <strong>Shift your opinions and reactions as the discussion evolves.</strong> Employees often need to be reminded that changing their opinion after considering new evidence or gaining a fresh perspective is not a sign of weakness. No one should fear a loss of face for shifting their opinion. In fact, effective leaders highlight when their opinions shift by making a statement such as “I see an issue that wasn&#39;t on my radar screen.” As the dialogue emerges, reframe key issues to underscore new perspectives.</li></ul><p> <strong>2. Orient the team about pushback opportunities.</strong> Many meetings or initiative rollouts conclude with question-and-answer periods without first offering attendees an orientation on expectations around pushback. Absent clarity, people often make a variety of untested and unspoken assumptions that might not be accurate.</p><p> Some employees become disenfranchised by pushback opportunities because they think all of their ideas should be accepted in totality. They don&#39;t expect reasoned debate or pushback to <em>their</em> pushback. That&#39;s why wise leaders carefully orient employees about possible outcomes other than the accept/reject polarized extremes. They introduce other alternatives, such as tweaking the plan, introducing a test period, delaying implementation, modifying a decision, or rethinking the proposal.</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. Select the right forums and settings.</strong> Some settings, like town hall gatherings or online forums, tend to embolden more emotive expressions of opinions, posturing, and venting. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Such situations might discourage useful inquiry and questions from those less inclined to engage in emotive scrums. The right venues and forums maximize the opportunities for insightful queries, deliberative discourse, and respectful debate. Typically, smaller groups of people who are equipped with the proper discussion parameters work best. Likewise, properly monitored online forums for smaller groups can encourage better pushback dynamics.</p><p> Leaders also need to be mindful that some people are reluctant to share concerns in front of others because they fear being viewed as poor team players or they lack confidence in how to express concerns or defend their views. To encourage people who are more reluctant to speak up, it&#39;s often helpful to provide them with the meeting&#39;s discussion points in advance and encourage them to write down their concerns and queries.</p><p> <strong>4. Focus on educating before advocating.</strong> Skilled educators soon learn to jettison the idea that a single good explanation will suffice to build understanding. Typically, they discuss their methods for arriving at their conclusions, including the opposing viewpoints and extant questions. This approach bakes uncertainty into conclusions, making room for further discussion and contrary views.</p><p> In contrast, advocates rarely discuss evidence or approaches that might contradict their firmly held viewpoints. They often trivialize or deride opposing views when they do entertain them. Advocates might short-circuit any criticism, downplaying uncertainty and reasoning that a brief explanation will enlighten others. Even smart executives often fall into this trap, overestimating the degree and depth of their educational efforts.</p><p> Advocating might play a role at some point after educating, but ultimately, effective leaders assume that allowing people to voice concerns reaps benefits. Short term, the pushback might result in tweaks that will increase long-term acceptance and smooth implementation.</p><p> <strong>5. Signpost inflection points.</strong> As decisions, initiatives, and policies evolve, a leader&#39;s level of certainty and openness to pushback shifts. In the absence of leadership clarity about these inflection points, employees apply unspoken rules regarding pushback, such as the following:</p><ul><li> Rule A: If the leader has not made a final decision, then I can speak up and candidly share my perspectives.</li><li> Rule B: If the leader has a strong position or has made a final decision, then I support it or shut up.</li><li> Rule C: If I agitate on an issue long enough, leaders will yield.</li></ul><p> If unspoken rules A and B undergird the pushback dynamics, then leaders might overestimate the degree of support for an initiative or decision.为什么？ Because employees operating under rule B assume that requests for feedback are for theater or designed to manufacture buy-in; they self-censor or offer only token opposition. Consequently, dissenting and potentially valuable voices go silent.</p><p></p><p> Rule C animates pushback dynamics in precisely the opposite direction, with endless debate; this fosters a culture of complaint after decisions have been tweaked, modified, or finalized. Effective leaders know that openness does not provide a license for never-ending discussion; after all, pushback to the pushback can go on forever.</p><p> The best way to inhibit these silent rules from taking root is to clearly signpost inflection points during pushback. Leaders who camouflage their sentiments in the name of openness undermine the candor of the entire conversation. Instead, effective leaders share their level of openness to tweaking proposed plans, proclaiming when their sentiments have shifted, and clearly signaling when the time for pushback has ended.</p><h3> A Pushback Success Story</h3><p> Laurie Butz, the CEO of Capital Credit Union, routinely uses these guidelines to lean into pushback to fully understand what employees believe they are losing as new initiatives roll out. For example, as the COVID-19 threat faded, she sought to restart face-to-face all-employee meetings to enhance inclusiveness and engage in more robust, thoughtful discussions about pending initiatives. She believes that the educational process goes in both directions, which requires more face-to-face forums that encourage adherence to more productive discussion ground rules than screen-enabled venting.</p><p> Yet that announcement was greeted with considerable pushback by employees who faced a long commute to the twice-a-year gatherings. Some used online surveys to voice concerns about the expense and time, while others expressed their discontent directly to their immediate supervisor, arguing that “Zoom meetings worked pretty well during COVID.”</p><p> Butz acknowledged these concerns while respectfully justifying the in-person gathering because, after all, “you could have a Zoom wedding, but something important would be missing.” Similar messaging was echoed in more personal channels by her “ambassadors” (opinion leaders).</p><p></p><p> Over time, the in-person meetings (1) increased employee engagement, (2) renewed employee interest in being a part of the process, and (3) spawned more thoughtful discussions of key issues. Quantitative evidence backed up these observations. For example, participation in all-employee surveys increased from 60% to 91% after the in-person meetings resumed, and 83% of survey respondents reported that they were “highly engaged in their work.” Anecdotal evidence also emerged: Employees often left the in-person meetings inquiring, “When will we have another opportunity to meet like this?”</p><p></p><p> Suppressing pushback by repressing uncertainty, invoking power dynamics, and paying too much attention to the most vocal employees may well induce short-term conformity and compliance at the expense of <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/decision-downloading/">undermining long-term trust</a> . Adroitly and respectfully managing pushback involves an upfront time commitment that engages employees while supplying forward momentum. The bonus: Leaders learn to more subtly influence how employees interpret trends, events, and decisions and develop greater insight into emerging issues.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How ChatGPT Can and Can&#39;t Help Managers Design Better Job Roles</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fangfang Zhang and Sharon K. Parker. <p>Fangfang Zhang, Ph.D., is a research fellow at the Centre for Transformative Work Design at Curtin University. She is also a CEPAR (Centre of Excellence in Population Ageing Research) research fellow. Her research interests include work design, job crafting, future of work, overqualification, and aging. Sharon K. Parker is a John Curtin Distinguished Professor at Curtin University, an Australian Research Council laureate fellow, and director of the Centre for Transformative Work Design. She is a fellow of the Australian Academy of Social Science and the Society for Industrial and Organisational Psychology. She is the creator of the SMART model and cofounder of the Thrive at Work initiative.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Today’s leaders are pushing to increase employee engagement and decrease turnover but face a harsh reality: widespread employee burnout. To fight it, managers need to offer employees more healthy and meaningful work. In surveys conducted in the United States by Gallup in 2022, 40% of employees reported that their [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Parker-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Today&#39;s leaders are pushing to increase employee engagement and decrease turnover but face a harsh reality: widespread employee burnout. To fight it, managers need to offer employees more healthy and meaningful work. In surveys conducted in the United States by Gallup in 2022, 40% of employees reported that their job had a negative impact on their mental health, and around 30% said they frequently experience burnout. Moreover, US employee engagement hit a seven-year low, with only 32% of workers polled by Gallup saying they were engaged and 17% saying they were actively disengaged in 2022. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Globally, employees&#39; lack of engagement has been estimated to cost employers $7.8 trillion — equivalent to 11% of the global gross domestic product. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> The root causes of disengagement and work stress often lie in how an organization has designed people&#39;s jobs. Decades of extensive research consistently link poor work design with negative employee outcomes, including mental strain, high turnover, job dissatisfaction, decreased productivity, and impaired learning. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Many companies are now striving to do better.</p><p></p><p> Unfortunately, our research indicates that many managers lack the necessary understanding to design high-quality jobs. This is where artificial intelligence technologies such as ChatGPT could play a key role, by bridging the manager knowledge gap and helping design high-quality work that benefits both employees and organizations. However, it is important for managers to first understand the pros and cons of using ChatGPT for work design. Let&#39;s explore some takeaways for managers that our research has revealed.</p><h3> Managerial Challenges: Mundane and Unfulfilling Jobs</h3><p> What factors determine whether a job is high quality? The <a href="https://www.futureofworkinstitute.com.au/smart-workdesign">SMART work design model</a> , a framework created by Sharon K. Parker, defines high-quality work as work that is <em>stimulating</em> (jobs with task variety and a chance to develop new skills), incorporates <em>mastery</em> (such as role clarity and job feedback), is <em>agentic</em> (such as job autonomy and change participation), is <em>relational</em> (where social support and positive teamwork are available), and is <em>tolerable</em> (with manageable work hours and reasonable levels of time pressure). <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Despite the benefits of well-designed jobs, poorly designed ones are still prevalent. According to the Gallup 2019 Great Jobs Survey, only 40% of employed Americans are engaged in jobs that possess SMART characteristics. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> On the other hand, 16% find themselves in jobs that lack essential SMART characteristics, and 44% have jobs that possess only some satisfactory SMART attributes. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> A lack of knowledge among today&#39;s managers about job design might explain such findings. A study we recently conducted explored how people design jobs for others. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Participants in an online simulation (Simulation 1) were asked to design an administrative job role. The half-time job was made up entirely of four photocopying and filing tasks. Participants were asked to make the job full time by selecting four additional tasks from a list of 11, including five repetitive photocopying and filing tasks and six more-meaningful and interesting tasks, such as greeting visitors or helping colleagues arrange meetings.</p><p></p><p> Participants were scored on a 0 to 4 range, with a higher score indicating the creation of a more stimulating work design. Almost half (45%) of university-level management students and professionals/managers working in human services industries tended to incorporate repetitive and monotonous work, demonstrating a knowledge gap when it comes to quality work design.</p><p> In a second simulation (Simulation 2), participants were asked to act like a manager and solve workforce problems in four scenarios. In each scenario, the job role design was clearly poor. To fix the problems, participants rated how likely they were to adopt strategies from a list that included both “fixing the worker” approaches, which attributed problems to the employee, and “fixing the poor work design” approaches, which acknowledged the poor-quality job design.</p><p> For example, in one scenario, a warehouse worker consistently failed to meet 50% of the timed deadlines in gathering products and delivering them to dispatch — despite frequently running to pick up goods. While the majority of participants focused on choices that improved the work design (for example, “Involve the employee and their colleagues in a review to identify ways in which their work could be organized better” or “Reorganize the work so that tasks do not need to be timed”), a surprising number of participants (40%) still chose strategies aimed at fixing the worker (such as “Discreetly observe the person&#39;s behavior to see how fast they are moving”). These findings validate our finding that there is a lack of knowledge of work design among managers and staff members.</p><h3> Generative AI Can Suggest Strong Work Design</h3><p> In the study&#39;s next phase, we researched whether an AI-powered tool such as ChatGPT could help managers do better. The short answer: ChatGPT has the potential to enhance decision-making in work design. However, it is important for managers to understand what ChatGPT can and cannot do well.</p><p> We used ChatGPT to make hypothetical work design decisions for the administrative work design simulation (Simulation 1). We ran the simulation task 20 times, using a new, independent chat session with the same prompt each time in ChatGPT. The generative AI model consistently chose enrichment tasks out of the provided list, outperforming both students and professionals/managers in creating interesting and meaningful work. ChatGPT&#39;s performance was similar to that of work design experts. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Work Design Decision Scores in Different Groups</h4><p class="caption"> When participants in Simulation 1 were asked to design an administrative job role, 45% mostly chose to assign the worker repetitive and monotonous tasks (scored from 0 to 4 indicating the number of enriched tasks selected by the participants). When participants in Simulation 2 were asked to address problems in four poorly designed job roles, 40% chose strategies aimed at fixing the worker rather than the poor design (scored from 1 to 5 indicating the extent to which participants will adopt the strategies, 1=extremely unlikely, 5=extremely likely). </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023_1005_Parker_Fig1-1.png" alt="Work Design Decision Scores in Different Groups"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> We then tasked ChatGPT to tackle Simulation 2, addressing the four managerial workforce scenarios (including the theoretical warehouse worker mentioned above), choosing strategies from a list. In each scenario, ChatGPT consistently chose strategies aimed at fixing the work design (good strategies for employee well-being, motivation, and performance) over those focused on fixing the worker. As in Simulation 1, ChatGPT outperformed students, managers, and professionals in its focus on work design to solve the workforce problems.</p><p> However, ChatGPT did not score as well as the work design experts in Simulation 2, suggesting that some caution is warranted. For example, in one session addressing the warehouse worker who was missing deadlines, ChatGPT scored 4 overall but chose the strategy “I would give the employee and her colleagues a bonus when they meet the allocated times,” which ignores the role&#39;s unreasonable time allocation.</p><p></p><h3> One Big Lesson: Specific Prompts Are Key</h3><p> To further assess ChatGPT&#39;s ability to generate suggestions independently, we ran the Simulation 2 work design tasks without providing a multiple-choice solution list. We ran each test in a new account with the chat history function turned off and in independent new chats so that the output of ChatGPT would not be affected by previous inputs.</p><p> To begin with, the outcome was worrying. When we simply instructed the AI model to “provide effective strategies to address the problem” in the missed-deadlines scenario, ChatGPT tended to address problems by trying to fix the worker and creating old-fashioned <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-progressive-roots-of-management-science/">Taylorist approaches to work systems</a> , such as conducting time and motion studies. For example, ChatGPT suggested solutions such as time management skills and additional training to help the warehouse employee, who we named Karen, improve her performance (for example, “Focus on improving Karen&#39;s speed and accuracy in locating and gathering items from the warehouse”). It also recommended providing performance feedback and incentives to motivate Karen to move faster (for instance, “By linking performance with rewards, Karen will be encouraged to focus on improving her speed and efficiency”). Each of these solutions implicitly assumes that the worker&#39;s motivation or ability is the problem rather than the work design.</p><p> After learning that such an open-ended approach was not optimal, we next instructed ChatGPT to address this same scenario using specific prompts: “Consider designing a good-quality job for Karen”; “Consider Karen&#39;s health, well-being, motivation, satisfaction, and work meaningfulness”; and “Consider Karen&#39;s work design.” The AI model then provided solutions related to improving Karen&#39;s work design, including the following:</p><ul><li> Reviewing time allocation and workload to set realistic time goals.</li><li> Involving Karen in the decision-making process and seeking her input on ways to improve her job.</li><li> Offering supportive feedback and recognition to enhance employee satisfaction and motivation.</li><li> Providing adequate training and skill development opportunities to boost confidence and engagement.</li></ul><p> These strategies would boost Karen&#39;s SMART work design characteristics, increasing the tolerability of demands, enhancing agency, boosting mastery, and making the work more stimulating.</p><p> ChatGPT also suggested solutions such as fostering a supportive work environment, encouraging team support and collaboration, offering career advancement opportunities, and promoting work-life balance. These solutions all align well with extensive research on work design and well-being and would make the job “SMART-er” and hence result in a healthier and more productive employee.</p><p> We learned from this particular experiment with ChatGPT that generative AI can make valuable work design decisions, but managers need to provide clear instructions that prioritize outcomes for the worker. For example, asking ChatGPT to “design a high-quality job” rather than simply requesting “good work design” can generate more relevant and effective strategies. Therefore, to enhance the quality of strategy suggestions generated by ChatGPT, managers need to mention specific, desirable goals in their question prompts, such as high-quality jobs; employees&#39; health, well-being, and motivation; and work meaningfulness.</p><p></p><p> One piece of good news: Managers who do not frequently use ChatGPT can learn how to write effective prompts via the ChatGPT tool itself. For example, when asked, “How can one craft a well-structured and clear prompt to effectively address work design challenges?” ChatGPT provided a step-by-step guide on how to write effective prompts. ChatGPT advised us to identify the core issue and be specific — suggestions that could be applied to work design by using prompts such as “Design high-quality work that enhances positive team interaction and collaboration for the sales team” or “Design work that is meaningful to facilitate employee acceptance of technological changes in their work.”</p><p> The experiment also showed that effective prompts need to be reviewed and tested. Managers who struggle to write effective ChatGPT prompts can improve their skills by using a prompt such as “The following is a prompt aimed at asking ChatGPT for advice from a work design expert&#39;s perspective. Please analyze and suggest improvements to get actionable and practical advice from ChatGPT.” In this case, ChatGPT will provide more specific suggestions that drive better-quality outputs.</p><h3> Five Lessons for Managers</h3><p> To address the pervasive issue of poor work role design and its detrimental effects, embracing innovative solutions is crucial. Based on our research, ChatGPT has emerged as a promising AI-powered tool to help managers design healthier and more productive jobs. But it&#39;s not a panacea and needs to be used wisely. Our advice for managers:</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT cannot replace training.</strong> Managers need to be <em>aware</em> that worker problems can emerge from poor work design and that work design, in turn, can affect worker well-being, motivation, and work meaningfulness. This means that before using ChatGPT to design better jobs, managers still need basic training on work design concepts. To get started on this topic, see the related article “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-well-designed-work-makes-us-smarter/">How Well-Designed Work Makes Us Smarter</a> ” and the <a href="https://www.smartworkdesign.com.au/">SMART Work Design site</a> .</p><p> <strong>Managers need to be supported in their goal to create well-designed work.</strong> Managers need to be <em>motivated</em> to create better jobs for their staffs. This means managers themselves need roles in which the creation of healthy employee work roles is seen as a legitimate and important responsibility, versus having their sole focus be the bottom line. For example, if managers get promoted purely on the basis of productivity achievements, they will not have much motivation to design SMART work for their teams.</p><p> <strong>Managers need healthy jobs themselves.</strong> Managers need sufficient time to be able to pay attention to how well their staff members&#39; jobs are designed. This means managers&#39; own jobs need to be <em>tolerable</em> and not excessively time-pressured.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Managers need to learn ChatGPT prompting skills.</strong> Managers should be encouraged to use generative AI to help with work design challenges, but they need clear and comprehensive instructions as to how to use it effectively. For example, managers need to be specific and to mention goals such as employee well-being and motivation when seeking work design recommendations from ChatGPT.</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT will augment, not replace, people in designing better jobs.</strong> Unlike simulations, real-life job design situations are often characterized by their ambiguity and complexity, with numerous variables that can influence outcomes. Real situations require a deep understanding of context, human emotions, social dynamics, and political and ethical considerations, all of which can be challenging for an AI tool like ChatGPT to fully grasp. We recommend using ChatGPT as a <em>complement</em> to human managers rather than as a <em>replacement</em> for them.</p><p> By incorporating ChatGPT&#39;s suggestions alongside human expertise, organizations can foster higher staff engagement, job satisfaction, and overall performance. Achieving such a synergy between managers and AI can pave the way for a better future for work design and employee experience.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Role of Culture in Enabling Change</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonathan Knowles, B. Tom Hunsaker, and Melanie Hughes. <p>Jonathan Knowles is the founder of advisory firm Type 2 Consulting. B. Tom Hunsaker is a clinical professor of strategy and leadership at Arizona State University&#39;s Thunderbird School of Global Management. Melanie Hughes is the former chief HR officer of Moody&#39;s, American Eagle, and Tribune Media.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Culture is often described as “how we do things around here” — a passive reflection of legacy norms and behaviors. It’s more helpful to think of culture as the nervous system of an organization. In biology, the central nervous system is the pathway by which thoughts in our brains are translated into actions by our [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Knowles-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p> Culture is often described as “how we do things around here” — a passive reflection of legacy norms and behaviors. It&#39;s more helpful to think of culture as the nervous system of an organization. In biology, the central nervous system is the pathway by which thoughts in our brains are translated into actions by our muscles, and how our experience of acting in the world updates our brain&#39;s understanding of the world. In organizations, this means thinking of culture as the transmission mechanism by which a company both communicates its intended strategy to the front lines and receives feedback and intelligence from the field about whether the strategy is achieving the intended outcomes in the market.</p><p> This nervous system metaphor illuminates the factors behind two of the most common reasons given for business failure: “We had a great strategy but failed to execute it” (a failure in the communication from the center to the field) or “Our leaders surrounded themselves with people who were afraid to tell them how the business was really performing” (a failure to relay important feedback and intelligence from the field). Both are examples of the failure to create an effective transmission mechanism from thought to action and back again.</p><p></p><p> A strategic approach to culture involves an active effort to create the environment and infrastructure to promote the necessary information flow between strategy and execution — treating them as complementary components of purposeful doing. These tools can include town halls, customer site visits, postmortems on lost bids, employee engagement surveys and any number of other mechanisms that facilitate the exchange of valuable information about what is (or is not) working. These tools nurture a culture of contextual awareness and adaptability that enables the business to perform better in its current environment and to prepare for future success.</p><p></p><p> There are certain aspects of culture that are universally desirable and others whose value is more context-dependent. When Donald Sull and Charles Sull analyzed 1.4 million employee reviews on Glassdoor, they <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/10-things-your-corporate-culture-needs-to-get-right/">identified four key factors</a> that contribute to a positive corporate culture (respect, leadership, compensation/benefits, and job security). But when organizational change is the imperative, this requires deliberately adding context-dependent factors to the culture.</p><p> The importance of adaptation has been the defining theme of our earlier articles about <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">strategy</a> ,<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/effective-innovation-begins-with-strategic-direction/">innovation</a> , and <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-change-means-changing-how-you-lead/">leadership</a> . To illustrate how different change objectives require different choices about culture, we&#39;ll draw on the corporate human resources leadership experiences of one of the authors (Melanie Hughes) across her career. At three different companies, she used three different strategies first to determine the change need and then to identify the characteristics of an effective culture to operationalize this change priority.</p><h3> Identify the Organization&#39;s Change Priority</h3><p> One of the most important — but often overlooked — responsibilities of HR is to analyze what aspects of the corporate culture are enabling the company to perform well in its current environment and what aspects are inhibiting its ability to act in the way and/or with the speed that the context requires.</p><p> The first step in this process is investigating the type of change that the business, unit, or team should be trying to achieve. As we described in “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">The Essence of Strategy Is Now How to Change</a> ,” there are three approaches to making such changes:</p><ul><li> Reinforce magnitude: Refine and deepen the actions that are contributing to high levels of relevance for key stakeholders and distinctiveness from competition.</li><li> Reimagine activity: Refresh the approaches, channels, and tools being used to pursue the current strategy.</li><li> Rethink direction: Reinvent the business model to deliver the levels of relevance and distinctiveness necessary for an economically viable business.</li></ul><p> Based on its understanding of the desired form of change, HR can identify the mechanisms to achieve the desired results, which staff members are best placed to play the role of change agent (those tasked with infusing new elements into the culture), and who can play the role of culture carrier (demonstrating how these new elements can be integrated with the legacy elements of the culture that are being maintained).</p><p> We review each of the change types and what kinds of tools and actions can best enable each one, drawing from <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/melaniehughes/details/experience/">Hughes&#39;s experiences</a> as the chief administrative officer at Gilt Groupe and the chief human resources officer (CHRO) at Moody&#39;s and Tribune Media.</p><p></p><h4> Change Type 1: Reinforce Magnitude</h4><p> Launched in 2007, New York-based Gilt Groupe was a pioneer of the luxury goods flash sale. The company was in hypergrowth mode from 2009 to 2012, when Hughes was the chief administrative officer: expanding from women&#39;s clothing to offering menswear and travel as well, launching operations in Japan, raising capital at a valuation of more than $1 billion in 2011, and actively planning for an initial public offering. With Gilt Groupe as a recognized market leader in the fashion space and a preferred partner of luxury goods manufacturers, the change priority was to reinforce magnitude — that is, expand the actions that were making the company relevant and distinctive — by replicating the successful core business model in new categories.</p><p> The central challenge was determining how to combine the entrepreneurial, growth-focused orientation of the existing culture with the knowledge sharing and repeatable processes necessary to support expansion into multiple new categories and manage their different stages of development. Two of the key enablers of this change were revised messaging by the CEO in the company&#39;s all-hands meetings and adjustments to the incentive schemes for executives and managers.</p><p> In both cases, the prior focus on growth alone was replaced by an emphasis on manageable growth, efficiency, and profitability. The CEO assumed the role of principal change agent, focusing on stories that celebrated costs avoided and efficiencies achieved, not just revenues won. The incentive programs were adjusted, with the focus on the performance of the individual businesses shifting instead to a balance of contributions to “Gilt corporate” and individual business performance. Specific individuals were identified as culture carriers because they had already demonstrated the behaviors of knowledge sharing, mentorship, and effective delegation — three key aspects of the new culture. These individuals were given increased responsibilities and promotions as visible signs of recognition (in addition to nonpublic compensation increases) to underscore the behaviors that the company now valued.</p><p> These actions paved the way for organizational changes that the previous culture would have resisted as bureaucratization infringing on the autonomy of the individual businesses. Instead, the centralization of certain services and infrastructure (such as marketing, development, finance, and recruiting) was accepted as the means to enable the businesses to scale faster.</p><h4> Change Type 2: Reimagine Activity</h4><p> The context of Hughes&#39;s most recent role, as CHRO at Moody&#39;s (2017 to 2021), was, in contrast, one in which reimagining activity was the appropriate stance, given the objective of innovating the approaches and tools being used to pursue the existing strategy. Moody&#39;s comprised a highly successful but mature ratings business and a fast-growing analytics business. There was rising cultural tension as each organization championed the merits of its approach to risk, innovation, customers, and staffing. Recognizing the incompatibility of these modes of operating, the CEO and president of each business worked with HR leadership on a program designed to evolve the corporate culture while also establishing an operating infrastructure and a performance management system specifically designed to support the needs of Moody&#39;s Analytics.</p><p> Several organizational initiatives were developed to support the change. Among them were expanding the corporate values to include elements such as speed and innovation (primarily associated with the analytics business) and to celebrate examples of those values in communications to employees and on investor calls. Leadership development programs were established to cross-train managers on the critical skills for each line of business and identify change agents who could cross-seed desired behaviors into each business. A new talent-planning process called Talent to Value identified the roles with the greatest strategic impact on each business and the skills required to perform those roles. This enabled leaders to understand which internal candidates were truly qualified for roles and where they needed to look for external talent to fill critical roles and support the new culture.</p><p> The CEO explicitly articulated a change from the previous “promote from within” culture, emphasizing the benefits of a broader and more diverse employee base to the performance of both businesses. These communications included LinkedIn posts from the CEO, signaling both internally and externally what was required to progress in the modern Moody&#39;s. This messaging was reinforced by the publicity given to new hires and internal promotions, emphasizing how these employees embodied the desired skills and traits described in the Talent to Value effort.</p><p> Reimagining these activities supported the transition of Moody&#39;s to a multibusiness firm with cultures, structures, and skills sets appropriate for each entity. The stock grew 60% in two years, reflecting a strong profit performance of the legacy Moody&#39;s ratings business combined with a higher multiple attributed to the growth potential of the analytics business.</p><h4> Change Type 3: Rethink Direction</h4><p> Hughes&#39;s time as CHRO at Tribune Media (2013 to 2016) represented an entirely different challenge. Tribune Media had gone through the largest media industry bankruptcy in US history in 2008, and as it emerged from four years of bankruptcy proceedings in 2012, the priority was to rethink its direction by establishing a business based on viable economics. A creative and action-oriented CEO was recruited for this purpose. The company adopted a strategy to spin off the legacy print journalism assets into a separate company (Tribune Publishing), invest heavily to grow the digital media and content-creation capabilities of Tribune Media, and make selective acquisitions in the broadcast business to build the necessary economies of scale.</p><p> For a business that had been beaten down by years in the bankruptcy courts and a relentless focus on cost cutting, the new strategy necessitated a complete cultural reboot. Certain behavioral norms — aversion to risk, a focus on the short term, reluctance to take on additional responsibility — had become ingrained during the bankruptcy years and needed to be reset. The CEO and Hughes recruited a new executive team ready to establish the type of culture required to support the new strategy. They, in turn, brought in new leaders and employees to start to transform their teams. The leadership team worked together to identify “Trib traits” — the set of values and competencies that would encourage new behaviors, which included “curious and courageous,” “competing with passion,” and “exemplifying leadership.”</p><p></p><p> The Trib traits became the blueprint for recruiting new employees and for a new performance evaluation and rewards system. The latter now tied fully 50% of managerial bonuses to the demonstration of competencies, to emphasize that how things got done was as important as the outcome. (Historically, bonuses had been entirely based on financial results.) This shift was reinforced in newly established televised town halls, where the CEO spoke about doing the <em>right</em> thing rather than doing the <em>thing</em> right to give employees the license to venture away from the safe path and experiment with new ways of operating — as was appropriate for a business emerging from bankruptcy and competing in the dynamic environment of digital media and entertainment.</p><p> As the above cases illustrate, the enablers of cultural change vary according to the type of change that an organization is trying to achieve. The table below summarizes how the type of change needed informs a consistent set of culture actions to be taken. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive </h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Culture Impact Area</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reinforce Magnitude</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reimagine Activity</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Rethink Direction</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>Definition of strategic goal</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine and double down on sources of existing advantage</p></td><td><p> Adapt approach to deliver greater value</p></td><td><p> Identify a new basis for a viable business model</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of communication</strong></p></td><td><p> Reaffirm existing beliefs; encourage consistency</p></td><td><p> Evolve core beliefs; encourage experimentation</p></td><td><p> Revisit core beliefs; encourage new ways of thinking</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Performance and risk metrics</strong></p></td><td><p> Reinforce current market position; minimize risk</p></td><td><p> Experiment around the core; be selective in terms of risk tolerance</p></td><td><p> Reinvent; iterate rapidly; have a high risk tolerance</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Changes to organizational structure</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine to optimize efficiency and minimize disturbance</p></td><td><p> Realign to support new products and customer priorities</p></td><td><p> Restructure to focus on areas where a sustainable advantage can be achieved</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Priority for talent acquisition</strong></p></td><td><p> Deepen expertise</p></td><td><p> Expand expertise</p></td><td><p> Redefine expertise</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of learning and development</strong></p></td><td><p> Emphasize skills for leading and delivering operational excellence</p></td><td><p> Make focused investments in leadership and high-demand technical skills</p></td><td><p> Make an enterprisewide investment in culture change</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Basis for rewards and recognition</strong></p></td><td><p> Incentivize growth and efficiency initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize redesign initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize novel and disruptive initiatives/outcomes </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Knowles_Culture_Essay_Table_mobile-fallback-1.png" alt="Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p></p><p></p><p> Culture is the enabler of business strategy. It either facilitates or inhibits the speed and reliability with which information flows within an organization, determining how well the company understands and responds to its environment.</p><p> Businesses are collaborative human endeavors that require the harnessing of the skills and shared beliefs of the individuals within them. Culture is the nervous system that promotes cohesion and integrates strategy and execution into purposeful doing. While certain aspects of a healthy culture might be universal (respect for individuals, ethical leadership, fair rewards for work performed), the effective management of culture is also contextual — involving the deliberate introduction of elements that enable the business to evolve to reflect the need for reinforcing magnitude, reimagining activity, or rethinking direction.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Burden of Proof for Corporate Sustainability Is Too High</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) is a globally recognized expert on how to build resilient, profitable companies that help people and planet thrive. He is coauthor of <cite>Net Positive: How Courageous Companies Thrive by Giving More Than They Take</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people, respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of Fortune magazine asserted that companies were “swapping exuberance for efficiency” and pointed out that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Winston-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce<a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3685936/tech-layoffs-in-2023-a-timeline.html?page=2">cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people</a> , respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> magazine asserted that companies were “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-finance-crypto-making-seismic-110000390.html">swapping exuberance for efficiency</a> ” and pointed out that they had collectively laid off more than 150,000 people since January. (By August, that number was up to <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/09/07/tech-industry-layoffs-2023/">nearly 225,000</a> .)</p><p> An article in that same issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> focused on Salesforce, asking whether there was a conflict between the company&#39;s layoffs and CEO Marc Benioff&#39;s commitment to empathetic leadership and sustainability. That&#39;s a fair question, but the article went further, declaring that Benioff&#39;s dilemma could “serve as a referendum on the whole <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/m-willing-bullets-marc-benioff-153000800.html">model of stakeholder capitalism</a> .” If that&#39;s true, then why aren&#39;t the collective woes across the tech industry, which another article declared “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-150-000-people-let-153000599.html">a confession of bad management</a> ,” a referendum on <em>shareholder</em> capitalism?</p><p></p><p> There&#39;s a serious inconsistency in how the business world sees sustainability. Whenever a company that prioritizes sustainability gets in trouble, people say the leaders took their eye off the ball. But when companies stumble while pursuing the “normal” strategy of maximizing profits above all — which is, by the way, wrongly implied to be the opposite of sustainability — their troubles are rarely blamed on that single-minded focus.</p><p></p><h3> Sustainability as Scapegoat</h3><p> The burden of proof on sustainability became crystal clear when, in 2021, activist investors and the board ousted the CEO of Danone, the French multinational food company, in a dramatic move that made headlines across the world. CEO Emmanuel Faber had faced harsh criticism for the company&#39;s financial performance versus that of its competitors, but here&#39;s how some of the press approached it at the time: The <cite>Financial Times</cite> editorial board&#39;s take: “ <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/668d9544-28db-4ad7-9870-1f6671623ac5">Danone: A Case Study in the Pitfalls of Purpose</a> .” <cite>Forbes</cite> : “ <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/frankvangansbeke/2021/03/20/sustainability-and-the-downfall-of-danone-ceo-faber-12/?sh=7dc8835b16de">Sustainability and the Downfall of Danone CEO Faber</a> .” <cite>Time</cite> : “ <a href="https://time.com/6121684/emmanuel-faber-danone-interview/">A Top CEO Was Ousted After Making His Company More Environmentally Conscious. Now He&#39;s Speaking Out</a> .”</p><p> Unfortunately, this two-year-old story has legs. I was recently speaking to leaders of a big consumer packaged goods company, and one of the execs expressed skepticism about sustainability, pointing to what had happened at Danone (and at Unilever, which has also <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-under-pressure-show-sustainability-focus-is-good-business-2022-02-09/">taken heat about its sustainability focus</a> ).</p><p> The finger-pointing at sustainability is, if anything, accelerating in some circles; to use modern parlance, it just triggers some people. Without diving into the morass of the anti-ESG movement, I think it&#39;s clear that some prominent voices will blame sustainability for <em>any</em> corporate trouble. When Silicon Valley Bank went under, for example, some pundits and politicians hit the airwaves to claim, ludicrously, that it was because the company had <a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/columnist/2023/03/15/silicon-valley-bank-failure-republicans-blame-diversity-woke/11472710002/">mentioned its diversity and inclusion efforts</a> in its proxy statement.</p><p> Blaming sustainability for financial woes just rings true for most execs. But <em>why</em> ?</p><p> I believe it&#39;s about a deeply flawed base assumption: Sustainability, even as companies embrace it like never before, is still generally assumed to be a drag on earnings and to <em>always</em> add to costs. But that&#39;s never been remotely true.</p><p> The idea that sustainability is a trade-off or is incompatible with financial responsibility is false. Some of the companies most famously focused on sustainability, such as Walmart and Ikea, are relentless cost cutters and have fit their environmental and social efforts into that strategy. These companies know that sustainability not only can cut expenses but also slashes risk, drives innovation and revenues, and builds intangible or brand value. It&#39;s not true that running a business in a sustainable fashion always costs more, although new ways of operating don&#39;t always pay off quickly. And, to be fair, the sustainability community — and that includes me — has sometimes implied as much.</p><p></p><p> But let&#39;s go back to the burden on sustainability and try a quick mental exercise. If a focus on sustainability causes failures, then are the companies that focus only on shareholder profits always successful? Of course not. The failure rate for companies is high: Roughly 50% of <a href="https://www.chamberofcommerce.org/small-business-statistics/">small businesses close</a> within about five years. Even among the Fortune 500 giants, failure is the norm. Of the original list in 1955, <a href="https://www.aei.org/carpe-diem/fortune-500-firms-1955-v-2017-only-12-remain-thanks-to-the-creative-destruction-that-fuels-economic-prosperity/">only 60</a> of them survived until the late 2010s. Obsessing over shareholder value didn&#39;t save 88% of the biggest companies.</p><p> All companies, at some point, emphasize a strategic focus. Consider a sample list of core strategies — some fads, some lasting additions to the management arsenal — that companies have embraced across a century: mass production, specialization, product differentiation, quality, safety, customer satisfaction, employee happiness, cost cutting, reengineering, agile and lean development, data-driven decision-making. Companies that embraced these things often outcompeted others, but none of those core strategies was ever the <em>only</em> factor in their success.</p><p> Companies rise and fall for diverse reasons. The most celebrated success stories, like those profiled in the influential book <cite><a href="https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/bhag.html">Built to Last</a></cite> , can also face scrutiny over time. Decline occurs when companies fail to adapt to sectoral transformations (Blockbuster), neglect technological shifts (Kodak), or lose brand relevance when they fail to attract younger consumers as their core audience ages (a fate shared by numerous apparel and consumer packaged goods brands).</p><p> So, in that context, what really happened with Danone? Is it possible that sustainability was the problem?当然。 But perhaps it was something more nuanced. In his book <cite><a href="https://www.harpercollinsleadership.com/books/purpose-profit/ ">Purpose &amp; Profit</a></cite> , Harvard professor George Serafeim analyzed how Danone was doing at the time of the CEO&#39;s ouster and found that the company was underperforming peers not just on financial outcomes but also on <em>sustainability</em> outcomes: The intentions and plans were solid, but the results lagged. Serafeim concluded, “Maybe Danone is underperforming not in spite of its focus on impact but because it&#39;s failing to generate enough impact.” Whether this conclusion is correct is the right debate to be having rather than simply chalking up the company&#39;s problems to sustainability.</p><h3> Stop the Blame Game</h3><p> The good news is that sustainability must now be mainstream or attention-seekers wouldn&#39;t find it worth attacking. It&#39;s becoming core to how business is done, with evidence everywhere — signs like increased regulation and transparency demands from stakeholders, sustainability reports issued by nearly every large company, and countless courses added to business school curricula globally.</p><p></p><p> Given how widespread sustainability efforts are now, perhaps it&#39;s time to do something paradoxical. Could we make sustainability in business more important by lowering the intensity of focus? This does not mean going light on the issues sustainability is grounded in — like climate change and inequality, which are, quite literally, deadly serious — but instead just turning down the heat. Can we normalize sustainability and stop blaming it for anything that goes wrong at companies with a purpose and vision? And can we stop crediting it for being the only factor that drives some companies&#39; success? I&#39;m willing to stipulate, for example, that sustainability darling Patagonia also succeeds because it has <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/travel-backpacks/patagonia-black-hole-mini-mlc-travel-backpack-review-a1476285024/">kick-ass products</a> that last a long time and a culture that <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Overview/Working-at-Patagonia-EI_IE5474.11,20.htm">attracts employees</a> and customers.</p><p> It&#39;s time to truly embed sustainability into business and treat it like any other unquestioned part of operations (think HR, R&amp;D, and safety). Sustainability need not be the scapegoat or the hero. It can just be a powerful way to do business and stay relevant in a fast-changing world … and help society and the planet thrive.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Want More Clarity on Generative AI? Experiment Widely</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) is a professor of management practice at London Business School and founder of HSM Advisory. Her most recent book is <cite>Redesigning Work: How to Transform Your Organization and Make Hybrid Work for Everyone</cite> (MIT Press, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT’s release in November 2022, more than 1 million people (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Gratton-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT&#39;s release in November 2022, <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/12/05/technology/chatgpt-ai-twitter.html">more than 1 million people</a> (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a predictor of growth, then the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.de/~/media/mckinsey/locations/europe%20and%20middle%20east/deutschland/news/presse/2023/2023-06-14%20mgi%20genai%20report%2023/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier-vf.pdf">$12 billion invested in generative AI</a> in the first five months of 2023 shows the depth of commitment.</p><p> To get a sense of current momentum and direction, I ran a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=74OaRCKn92k">research webinar last month on the impact of generative AI</a> on the workplace. Some 260 executives from organizations in Australia, Europe, Japan, and the United States joined me to describe their current use of generative AI in human capital domains. What I heard is that generative AI is a top priority for many CEOs, experiments abound alongside ambiguity, and organizations are already beginning to use artificial intelligence to augment their human capital strategies. I&#39;ll share more details about those findings in a moment.</p><p></p><p> I wanted to hear directly from practitioners because it seems to me that, as with the previous era-defining event — the COVID-19 pandemic — and its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/making-sense-of-the-future/">impact on the workplace</a> , imagining what is ahead with this new technology is a tough call. As with the emergence of hybrid work and work-from-home initiatives in response to the pandemic, figuring out the right approaches to generative AI is a process replete with ambiguity, experiments, and changes of mind. In other words, it is a learning process driven both by the initiative of individuals and the strategies of organizations.</p><p> Like the response to the pandemic, debate and action around gen AI are moving fast.</p><p></p><p> Two facts are emerging. First, this is a rapidly developing technology. The size of investment gives a sense of this. So, too, does the volume of experimentation: One executive told me, “We have created a head of generative AI with a role simply to moderate and make sense of the hundreds of experiments we have running on any day.” Second, unlike previous workplace technologies, generative AI is not being positioned as a substitute for routine tasks — either analytical tasks, like keeping records or providing repetitive customer-oriented services, or manual tasks, like picking and sorting products or performing routine assembly. Instead, it&#39;s a technology with the potential to hit at the heart of nonroutine analytical work. This is knowledge work, such as forming a hypothesis, creating content, recommending medical diagnostics, or making a sales pitch. The source of this impact is generative AI&#39;s growing capacity to understand natural language. Around 25% of the total work time of knowledge workers is spent on the kinds of creative tasks that generative AI is beginning to get good at.</p><p> Yet, like during the early days of the pandemic and hybrid work, much is currently conjecture. There will certainly be pushback, changes of direction, and believers and resisters, just as there has been throughout the ongoing debate about hybrid work. There will be many experiments before leaders begin to develop their own narratives about how best to support their workers in these complex and ambiguous times.</p><p></p><h3> Experiments, Projections, and the Great Ambiguity</h3><p> The potential for generative AI to very quickly have a real impact in the workplace is fueling the attention it&#39;s getting. Consider the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier#key-insights">McKinsey report on generative AI</a> published in June 2023. McKinsey asked a group of technology experts at what point they believed generative AI would substitute for a number of human tasks. It then compared those estimates with pre-gen AI projections made in 2017 about when human performance might be achievable by technology. What is striking is the extent to which their estimated timelines have contracted. For one work task, for example — “coordination with multiple agents” — the experts in 2017 estimated a timeline of substitution that ranged from 2035 to 2058. Today, they estimate that happening from 2023 to 2035. That feels very soon. As important, in 2017, the estimate for when we&#39;d see technology achieve human-level performance for the task of “creativity” was 2030 to 2045; today, the projection is from 2025 to 2030. These dates are for tasks where technology performance is expected to match median human performance. For top-quartile human performance, the timelines are pushed out somewhat.</p><p> How do we make sense of this? What I learned from observing the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-increase-collaborative-productivity-in-a-pandemic/">impact of the pandemic on work</a> is that watching closely and asking questions of people in the field about their current lived reality is a useful practice. So my Sept. 19 webinar was essentially a listening process. Many executives came from human capital functions, so their interest was primarily in the people side of their business.</p><p> I began by asking where generative AI currently sits on the leadership agenda. Over half of attendees (52%) agreed with the statement “It is a CEO priority where leadership teams are discussing impact.” Only 13% said “It is not yet on the agenda in any meaningful way.” This is a topic that is definitely consuming bandwidth at the top levels of organizations across the world.</p><p></p><p> Generative AI is at the top of leaders&#39; agendas — but what about the scope of debate? What issues are coming forward as people talk through its consequences? For the webinar, I focused on a central aspect of this question: machines and creativity. The technologists in the McKinsey panel estimated that human creativity will be achieved by generative AI within the time span of 2025 to 2030, but what did this group of leaders believe? This, for me, is an important question because the McKinsey panelists are technology experts. I have a hunch that people like them will overestimate technological progress, whereas people like me (psychologists) will overestimate human progress.</p><p> What is fascinating is the lack of agreement among webinar attendees about whether they think human creativity at the top quartile will be achieved by gen AI from 2023 to 2030: Just 10% strongly agreed, while 34% agreed, 22% neither agreed or disagreed, 30% disagreed, and 4% strongly disagreed. I ran a Menti (a quick survey at the website Mentimeter) to collect participants&#39; real-time thoughts and asked why they had come to their conclusions. Within seconds, more than 80 comments had emerged: Those who agreed pointed out that creativity can be broken down into logical steps; that creativity sits on a lot of data; that prompts will be more important than AI; and that use cases, such as songs, already demonstrate creativity. Those who disagreed described how generative AI would augment, not substitute for, creative people and asserted that creativity was about empathy and vulnerability, that humans can generate new ideas, while AI pulls from the past, and that governments will provide regulation. Those who did not know said there are simply too many unknown unknowns.</p><p> For me, the takeaway here is the sheer richness of conversation and variance in opinions about generative AI. These are debates we need to be open about and continue to have.</p><p> I wondered, of course, how generative AI is currently being experimented with and used. My interest is in the human capital agenda and how generative AI will impact the everyday experiences of workers. One of the “promises” of AI, according to the McKinsey report, is a productivity boost from the automation of a wide variety of activities. For knowledge workers, this will come by technology either substituting for or augmenting tasks such as creating connections, retrieving stored data, personalizing content, automating activities, increasing the speed of response, and collaborating.</p><p> I asked about the current velocity of the use of generative AI in three human capital domains: talent development (like recruitment, induction, and career management), productivity (like skills training and managing collaboration), and change management (like internal knowledge management). I was interested in the current use of generative AI in each domain and the use cases. Of course, the data set of attendees comprised self-selected people who had an interest in generative AI, but still, what is clear is that there are many, many experiments currently underway.</p><p></p><p> The human capital domain with the greatest reported use of generative AI right now is “internal knowledge management.” Forty-six percent of attendees said they are experimenting in this sphere, with use cases such as creating communications, conducting market research analysis, finding resources and competencies, and engaging in employee listening. Almost as many attendees (44%) reported using gen AI for recruitment, with use cases such as creating job advertisements, developing simple approval flows, and onboarding new hires. About a third of attendees (34%) said they&#39;re using gen AI for skills training, with use cases that include self-directed learning, the creation of learning content, and virtual reality-based training. And 23% said they&#39;re using the technology for assessment and feedback, with use cases such as developing bespoke assessments, improving performance feedback, designing career paths, and creating chatbots for employees.</p><p> I feel that what I captured in this research webinar is a sense of the sheer depth of conversation and experimentation taking place right now across the world. How to think about and use generative AI is being debated in the C-suite as use cases are being created and tough questions (like the relationship between machines and creativity) are being debated. For organizations to be aligned with this emerging narrative, it is imperative that they experiment freely and observe closely.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sound Business: The Promise of Audio Machine Learning Technologies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mark Purdy. <p>Mark Purdy ( <a href="https://twitter.com/mjpurdyecon">@mjpurdyecon</a> ) is managing director of Purdy &amp; Associates, an independent economics and technology research company.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Purdy-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or as engineers testing the safety of a vehicle or machine.</p><p> But until recently, the systematic analysis of sounds in dynamic situations — a busy train station, a shopping mall, or an urban park, for example — has been difficult due to the sheer number of complex acoustic signals interacting at once. But this is now changing, thanks to major advances in sensor technology and deep learning algorithms that can harvest enormous quantities of acoustic input and rapidly extract key information.</p><p></p><p> Two branches of sound-related machine learning are emerging: one focused on the detection and analysis of sounds and the other on the AI-powered creation of sounds. Both have significant potential for business and societal value creation. In fact, according to one estimate, the <a href="https://www.astuteanalytica.com/industry-report/audio-ai-recognition-market">global market for AI audio-recognition technologies</a> is set to more than triple, from $4.1 billion in 2021 to $14.1 billion by 2030.</p><p> Deep learning algorithms are now being used to pioneer innovations across a diverse range of industries and sectors, such as these applications of sound detection and analysis:</p><p> <strong>Commercial and household security.</strong> Every year, US businesses and consumers spend billions of dollars protecting buildings and other physical assets. Smart home devices, such as Amazon&#39;s Echo, already use AI-driven voice recognition technology to authenticate different users and provide personalized entertainment and shopping experiences. But now AI systems&#39; sensors and deep learning algorithms can analyze nonvoice ambient sounds from every part of an office, a factory, or a military facility, distinguishing between innocuous sounds and those that may indicate an emerging threat, such as breaking glass.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Health care.</strong> AI sound technologies could transform many areas of health care, particularly by enabling low-cost, rapid diagnoses of diseases in their early stages. In health care, they could be used to provide real-time measurements for an array of biometric data, such as heart rate, blood pressure, respiration rate, and stress level. Deep learning has been used to extract and classify the <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34433880/">“crackles” and “wheezes”</a> of different lung diseases. <a href="https://www.cochl.ai/">Cochl</a> , a South Korean startup, is pioneering AI applications to rapidly identify health problems based on the coughs and sneezes of patients. Such early-warning systems could prove to be pivotal in the fight against COVID-19 and future virus outbreaks.</p><p> <strong>Hearables.</strong> Acoustic deep learning technologies are being pioneered in the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/03/2681513/0/en/Exploring-the-Global-Hearable-Market-Size-Is-Estimated-to-Exceed-96-53-Billion-by-2030-At-an-Exponential-Growth-Rate-of-16-74-Revenue-and-Market-Share-Projections-from-2022-to-2030.html">“hearables” market</a> — which includes headphones, earphones, and other listening devices — to improve people&#39;s listening experience. Such technologies can <a href="https://edtechmagazine.com/higher/article/2022/01/hearables-combine-machine-learning-and-microchips-smart-listening">screen out unwanted noise</a> or alert users to potential dangers, such as when someone is wearing earphones while jogging near traffic. Machine learning algorithms can be used to curate listening content to different contexts, such as by playing more relaxing or softer sounds when breathing signals indicate signs of stress, or more stirring content when the user is exercising.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Retail and leisure industries.</strong> Machine learning technologies can now recognize individuals through the sounds of their <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1809.08783.pdf">footsteps</a> by isolating these distinctive footfall echoes from background noises and the sounds of other pedestrians. Sound-based gait-recognition technologies offer significant advantages over other surveillance systems, given that they work even in poor lighting conditions and are less intrusive than facial recognition, computer vision, or biometric identification systems.</p><p> One of the biggest potential applications of this technology is in footfall-intensive industries such as retail. Sound-based footfall recognition can be used to recognize returning customers and help identify linger points on the shopper&#39;s journey — places where they pause to compare different products or respond to particular discounts or promotions — or pinpoint the time sensitivity of customers at different times of the day or week, based on the rapidity of footsteps.</p><p> <strong>Predictive maintenance and early-warning systems.</strong> Deep learning algorithms can analyze acoustic signals such as noise pressure and reverberations from machines and engine parts to assess wear and tear and predict when a particular part is likely to need replacing. NASA has used sound-sensing algorithms to monitor the functioning of equipment aboard the <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/research/experiments/explorer/Investigation.html?#id=7860">International Space Station</a> . Deep learning algorithms are being used to classify underwater acoustic signals to potentially develop an early-warning system for <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-021-02483-w">deep-sea earthquakes and tsunamis</a> .</p><p> <strong>Marketing and media content production.</strong> Speech-to-text technologies have been around for some time, but the reverse is now happening with the growth of AI-powered text-to-speech or <a href="https://www.cs.unc.edu/~yipin/pub/cvpr2018.pdf">video-to-sound technologies</a> . <a href="https://audiostack.ai/">AudioStack</a> , a UK-based startup, provides AI-enabled audio creation, drawing on a database of more than 600 voices in more than 60 languages. Use cases include generating audio ads with different regional nuances, music, or voice tones, or generating synthetic or cloned voices for podcasts or narrated news flashes based on textual content. The algorithm that <a href="https://deepzen.io/">DeepZen</a> uses for artificial voice creation from text is able to infer different emotional tones from the content, such as excitement, enthusiasm, or comfort. <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2002.10981.pdf?utm_source=thenewstack&utm_medium=website&utm_campaign=platform">AutoFoley</a> was developed to replicate the role of Foley artists, who add audio effects — such as the gallop of a horse or footsteps on a staircase — to movies. Applications like these have huge potential in industries such as gaming, marketing, and publishing, where <a href="https://speechify.com/blog/what-is-the-voice-over-actor-market-size">global demand for voiceovers</a> is forecast to grow by 9% per year to reach $2.3 billion by 2026.</p><h3> Recommendations for Business Leaders</h3><p> The rise of AI-based sound detection and creation will raise several challenges for businesses, especially in the intellectual property arena. To capitalize on the opportunities and mitigate the risks, business leaders should consider these recommendations:</p><p> <strong>Understand and protect your sonic assets.</strong> Most large companies will trademark or register a well-known jingle or catchphrase associated with their products or services, but in a world of AI-based sonification, businesses will also need to carefully assess the sonic print of their entire product portfolios — the distinctive whir of a washing machine or vacuum cleaner, the signature ignition of a sports car, the pop of a soda can opening. Counterfeiting of sounds will become a growing problem that businesses will need to prepare for.</p><p></p><p> <strong>“Sonify” the product experience.</strong> Businesses will pay increasing attention to the sonic signatures of their products, either to diminish cacophonous elements (such as a noisy clothes dryer) or to enhance aesthetically pleasing sounds (such as the tick-tock of a <a href="https://www.soundoflife.com/blogs/design/product-sonification-elevating-the-consumer-s-experience-via-the-beauty-of-sound-engineering">car&#39;s turn indicator</a> ). In the future, manufacturers could incorporate sonic signatures that track the product life cycle — for example, by varying a sound profile from a consumer durable as its components start to wear out. Businesses of all types will need to make sonic signatures a core part of user interface design, by identifying both the right functional and informational sounds for different uses and contexts, and by combining these with visual and other sensory elements.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prompt for sound.</strong> Generative AI systems — large language models capable of creating and synthesizing text, sounds, speech, images, and code — are increasingly enabling businesses to create completely new sounds and sonic combinations, or to combine audio with video, text or images to create new product campaigns. With a single prompt, marketers will be able to create an advertising tune for a new brand of ice cream, turn a wordy blog or product description into a music video, or alter a product jingle to make it more appealing to younger or older consumers or potential customers in a new market overseas. With “prompt engineering” now becoming a major discipline in the AI and automation fields, businesses will need to train designers, marketers, and product developers to write efficient prompts for sound-based use cases, taking into account factors such as brand values, product tone of voice, intellectual property rules, and ethics.</p><p> As the saying goes, “Wisdom is the reward for a lifetime of listening.” Today, AI-powered acoustic technologies are opening up a world of sounds previously inaccessible to us. They&#39;re providing new insights and opportunities for businesses and policy makers in areas as diverse as consumer behavior, health care, urban planning, commercial security, and infrastructure management. Businesses that choose to listen to this new world, and act upon the insights, will be well positioned for future success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thorny Talent and AI Challenges Now: 5 Experts Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you’ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with MIT Sloan Management Review authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston. This distinguished group of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6uXF_DY4e0k?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you&#39;ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston.</p><p> This distinguished group of management and leadership experts from the MIT Sloan School of Management and other institutions weighed in on two questions:</p><ul><li> What are the top talent management issues for 2024?</li><li> What is a manager&#39;s role in advocating for workers in the age of AI?</li></ul><p> “AI really changes how we work; it changes how we relate to each other and how we can talk to each other,” said Christine Moser, associate professor of organization theory at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, who spoke with <cite>MIT SMR</cite> at the event.</p><p></p><p> How should forward-looking leaders adjust to those new realities? Watch the video, recorded at AOM Boston, to learn what these experts have to say about AI checks and balances, how to motivate workers, and what happens when black-box AI models meet your organizational processes.</p><p> Want to learn more about leading people in the age of AI? Read our related article, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-humans-lose-when-we-let-ai-decide/">What Humans Lose When We Let AI Decide</a> .”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>