<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 6 月 13 日星期二 03:13:18 +0000</lastbuilddate><language>英文</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1个</sy:updatefrequency><generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>我们应该将摩尔定律引入气候行动</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) 是全球公认的专家，擅长如何建立有弹性、盈利的公司来帮助人类和地球繁荣发展。他是<cite>Net Positive 的合著者：勇敢的公司如何通过付出超过索取而蓬勃发展</cite>（哈佛商业评论出版社，2021 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Gordon Moore, cofounder of Intel and a towering figure of the early semiconductor business, died earlier this year at the age of 94. He leaves behind one of the more successful companies in history and, of course, his famous Moore’s law. He predicted in 1965 that the density of transistors on a microchip would double [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Winston-MooresLaw-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>英特尔联合创始人、早期半导体行业的杰出人物戈登摩尔于今年早些时候去世，享年 94 岁。他留下了历史上最成功的公司之一，当然还有他著名的<a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/news/gordon-moore-obituary.html">摩尔定律</a>。他在 1965 年预测微芯片上的晶体管密度每年都会翻一番，并在 1975 年将他的预测调整为“恰好”每两年翻一番。后一种预测已经成立了将近 50 年。</p><p>人们常说，我们手中的手机比 1969 年的阿波罗登月任务的计算能力更强。的确如此，但这也太轻描淡写了——我们的手机实际上 <a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/moon-mars/a25655/nasa-computer-iphone-comparison/">比当时所有的 NASA 都强大</a>，这一事实证明了指数变化的令人震惊的现实。</p><p></p><p>我们人类倾向于以线性方式思考：如果去年增长了一点，今年就会增长更多一点。我们很难理解半导体发生了什么。 1971 年，每个微处理器大约有 2,400 个晶体管。五十年后，一块芯片拥有 580 亿个晶体管，英特尔计划<a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/opinion/moore-law-now-and-in-the-future.html">到 2030 年达到 1 万亿个</a>。如果每两年翻一番，它大约每十年增长 30 倍，20 年增长 1,000 倍，40 年增长 100 万倍。在 60 年内，您将以 10 亿倍的速度获得某些东西。</p><p>很难夸大这种变化速度对世界造成的影响。有趣的是，我十几岁的男孩们对他们几乎可以立即查询几乎任何事实或流式传输任何视频或歌曲完全不感兴趣。与此同时，错误信息传播得更快。至于人工智能？无论是好的还是坏的，它都会迅速变得更好。 （如果你想害怕，请查找“deepfakes”。）</p><p>摩尔定律还导致了商业史上一些最经典的失败。柯达没有为数码照片做好准备。 Blockbuster 也被打了个措手不及，下载电影在短短几年内就从不可能变成了实时下载。一旦流媒体电影变得微不足道，租用视频的模式就死了。</p><p>在所有这一切中，我看到了两个重要的教训。首先，如果我们能够尽早取得成功，相信还有更多的可能，为此疯狂竞争，并进行<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/">必要的投资，</a>我们就能取得显着进步。这里的核心点是，显而易见，摩尔定律不是定律。几十年来，没有人要求大型芯片公司将晶体管的宽度缩小到纳米级。他们之所以这样做，是因为竞争、为建立芯片市场而进行的大量公共和私人支出，以及理论、制造技术、设备设计和营销方面令人印象深刻的创新水平。 （一旦 iPad<em>可行，我们还需要</em>吗？）根据早期经验和成功，摩尔定律被证明是对一个行业可以实现的目标的有力而大胆的预测。</p><p>其次，我们可以将其与我们时代的关键商业挑战相提并论：如何在管理我们的社会和环境影响（尤其是气候变化）的同时实现繁荣和发展。我们可以拥抱快速变化，以可持续或净积极的方式运营。</p><h3>我们可以再次拥抱指数</h3><p>就像在 1960 年代和 70 年代一样，在外部目标的驱动下，我们再次沿着一条我们不确定如何前进的道路前进——最重要的是，科学告诉我们世界应该以多快的速度去碳化。 “基于科学的目标”是应对气候变化的准摩尔定律。跟上这些雄心勃勃的目标是商业价值的重要创造者，是实现卓越创新和绩效的途径，也是与客户、员工和其他利益相关者保持相关性（而不是被 Blockbuster 化）的核心方式。</p><p></p><p>到目前为止，许多清洁技术领域给半导体世界留下了良好的印象。清洁能源和电池存储的成本即使不是每两年减半，也一直在快速下降。根据国际能源署的数据，2000 年至 2020 年间， <a href="https://www.iea.org/data-and-statistics/charts/evolution-of-solar-pv-module-cost-by-data-source-1970-2020">新太阳能模块的每瓦成本</a>下降了 96%。45 年来，太阳能成本暴跌了 500 倍，大约每五年减半。虽然不是摩尔定律的步伐，但它的速度足以撼动整个行业并创造巨大的新机会。清洁技术转型是我们旅行、建造建筑物、制造事物等方式的数万亿美元的转变。</p><p>与半导体一样，清洁技术领域的这种表现来自于创新、投资、政策支持和大规模制造能力的大规模建设（主要在中国）。但也许在这两种情况下最重要的是，变革的步伐需要意志力和新的思维模式。 10 多年前，当我们这些身处可持续商业世界的人开始推动以科学为基础的目标的想法时，阻力是显而易见的。 “我们怎么可能移动得那么快？”很多人会问。 “考虑到它的成本，我们<em>为什么</em>要移动得那么快？”但是，当您跨越成本和心理临界点时，怀疑会转变为热情。</p><p></p><p>尽管摩尔定律一直在推动社会的深刻技术和社会变革，但它仍然是一个人为的目标。竞争、创新和利润动机驱使公司朝着它迈进。这一次，为了实现气候目标，我们正在使用全球行星阈值来确定我们需要实现多快的目标——不仅是碳，还有水的使用、环境中有毒物质或塑料的数量、人权的普遍性供应链中的滥用行为等等。</p><p>如果我们希望我们的世界繁荣昌盛，那么拥有这些可不是一件好事。我们正在努力应对的可持续性“法则”绝对<em>不是</em>理论上的或发明的——它们基于自然和物理法则。聪明的公司会将这些不容谈判的现实视为他们所拥有的难以置信的机会，并开始行动。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>管理您的劳动力生态系统，而不仅仅是您的员工</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth J. Altman, David Kiron, Jeff Schwartz, and Robin Jones. <p>Elizabeth J. Altman 是马萨诸塞大学洛厄尔分校曼宁商学院的管理学副教授。 David Kiron 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的研究编辑部主任。杰夫·施瓦茨 (Jeff Schwartz) 是 Gloat 负责洞察力和影响力的副总裁，也是哥伦比亚商学院的兼职教授。 Robin Jones 是 Deloitte Consulting LLP 的负责人，并担任劳动力转型实践负责人。他们是<cite><a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047777/workforce-ecosystems/">《劳动力生态系统》</a></cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2023 年 4 月）的作者，本文改编自该书。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jon Krause/theispot.com “How do you define your workforce?” We have posed this question to dozens of executives and in multiple global management surveys. The most common answer is also the most surprising. A confident minority of executives say their workforce is just their employees. But the overwhelming majority, especially leaders on the front lines of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM_Altman_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">乔恩·克劳斯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> “你如何定义你的劳动力？”我们已经向数十名高管和多项全球管理调查提出了这个问题。最常见的答案也是最令人惊讶的。</p><p>少数自信的高管表示，他们的员工就是他们的员工。但绝大多数人，尤其是处于组织转型前线的领导者，所持的观点更广泛，不仅仅是员工。他们越来越多地将劳动力描述为参与实现公司业务目标的所有人员和群体。组织的扩展劳动力对其业务、品牌和价值创造方法变得如此重要，以至于他们需要以不同的方式思考并以不同的方式对待他们的整个员工队伍。</p><p>自从我们几年前开始研究劳动力的未来以来，这代表了管理观点的转变。我们正在看到这种跨行业和各种规模的组织发生的变化——领导者需要重新定义他们的员工队伍由谁组成以及由什么组成，并制定新的管理实践和组织结构，这对领导者提出了挑战。</p><p></p><p>等级制、命令与控制、以内部为中心的管理实践不适合跨越内部和外部组织边界的员工队伍。例如，使用孤立的职能来独立管理员工和外部贡献者充满了挑战：不明确的决策权、治理流程和权力动态甚至会破坏最善意的高管。此外，用于管理员工的技术系统通常与用于访问和跟踪外部贡献者的技术系统不同且相互脱节。缺乏整合会导致效率低下，从而阻碍获得和维持具有战略价值的能力的努力。</p><p>我们将<em>劳动力生态系统</em>定义为一个结构，其中包含组织内外的参与者，他们致力于为组织创造价值。在生态系统中，参与者朝着个人和集体目标努力，参与者之间相互依存和互补。</p><p>劳动力生态系统包括员工以及各种外部贡献者和合作伙伴——长期和短期承包商、临时工、应用程序开发人员、服务提供商和众包参与者。生态系统观点明确认识到，获取和聘用劳动力不再是人力资源职能的唯一权限，而是需要涉及最高管理层、IT、采购、财务、法律和其他领域的领导者的跨职能行动。</p><p>有意识地协调劳动力生态系统需要领导者协调整个组织的活动以及与外部贡献者的活动。为了应对这一挑战，公司需要重新评估人力资源、采购和 IT 等职能之间的协调。还需要决定如何管理与外部贡献者的关系，例如应用程序开发人员和分包商。我们开发了<em>集成架构</em>的概念来定义内部协调以及组织如何与其扩展的员工交互。</p><p></p><p>我们的集成架构模型与大多数劳动力生态系统中管理交互的默认、孤立的方法形成鲜明对比。通常，临时工负责采购。合作伙伴和联盟通常由战略处理，人工智能和自动化是技术组织的一部分（但很少被视为更广泛的劳动力生态系统的一部分）。人力资源部通常监督全职和兼职员工。在这种通用方法中，多个小组独立工作以管理他们有任务的贡献者，但整个组织的努力是不协调的。</p><p>不同部门的经理经常在没有任何集中协调的情况下使用外部和内部员工的组合。这些分散的方法在局部层面可能是有效的，每个业务部门和职能经理都保留最大的控制权，但它们在总体层面上并不是最优的。</p><p>事实上，在协调劳动力生态系统时，权力下放可能会有很大的缺点。分散的努力可能与总体战略重点不一致，并可能破坏企业对新战略方向的追求。缺乏集成可能会限制有关谁（和什么）为组织做出贡献的可用数据。这可能会导致成本效率低下，因为临时工是临时寻找的。这可能意味着内部员工和外部贡献者（现有的和潜在的）都不太了解贡献的机会。虽然权力下放是目前管理员工和扩展劳动力的最常见方法，但它几乎总是不协调的。</p><h3>为什么集中式集成架构具有吸引力</h3><p>鉴于分散架构的缺点，许多协调劳动力生态系统的组织正在创建在其设计中更加集中和跨职能的集成架构。在一些组织中，人力资源部门协调劳动力生态系统管理与采购和 IT 职能；在这些情况下，业务领导者和团队与 HR 和其他人合作，主动管理风险。其他公司正在采用更具跨职能的方法来管理所有类型的个体工人和提供者；在这些情况下，人力资源发挥着关键但不太重要的作用，人才市场在支持跨业务部门和职能的劳动力需求方面发挥着更突出的作用。</p><p>例如，瑞士全球医疗保健公司诺华公司成立了一个跨职能指导委员会来管理其大约 100,000 名内部员工和大约 50,000 名外部员工。诺华正在努力为管理人员提供内部和外部人才来源的可见性，这是​​由来自各种合作伙伴和平台的数据驱动的一项努力。这个过程将由称为劳动力战略家的策展人推动，他们将授予管理人员实时访问员工、承包商和技术团队的权限。</p><p>这场大流行病促使我们研究的另一家全球公司的人力资源部门更多地参与监督更广泛的员工队伍，因为它引发了对临时工和员工的远程和现场工作政策、薪酬连续性、缺勤和病假的担忧。该公司人力资源副总裁报告说，在大流行之前，人力资源部门只密切关注全职员工或兼职员工的情况；通常，对于临时工，“人力资源部门根本不参与，”她说。当时，甚至对于公司临时工的组成人员都没有达成共识。大流行病使公司必须更加集中整合和灵活地照顾其临时工的想法变得紧迫。它还强调，公司需要更好地管理更广泛员工的声誉、法律、运营和成本风险，并充分利用全体员工的竞争优势。</p><p>在同一家公司，招聘流程和程序历来因部门而异——而且部门之间往往不相互沟通。人力资源部支持有关雇用长期雇员的决定，而采购则引入临时工。与此同时，人力资源部门不知道的是，管理人员经常将临时工转变为全职员工。一个涉及人力资源、采购和财务的新开发的信息交换平台为公司提供了基于数据的跨职能可见性，以跟踪和批准外部员工。</p><p>根据首席采购官的说法，临时员工的管理一直是公司的一个烫手山芋：“任何处于中心位置的人都将承担所有风险，而没有任何好处。”但他表示，该公司已经转向从战略而非交易的角度考虑与临时工的关系，这涉及跨职能管理临时工。正如人力资源副总裁所解释的那样，“我们的首席财务官、首席法律顾问、首席人力资源官 [chief human resources officer] 和首席运营官都承认他们都参与了这场游戏。”</p><p>人才市场是另一个很好的工具，可以锚定一个集中的、跨职能集成的​​架构。例如，NASA 曾经有六个人才市场平台，分布在多个部门，每个平台都独立地将员工与演出和项目相匹配。现在，航天局使用单一的人才市场——一种协调机制——来协调整个组织对内部人才的访问。将其内部人才市场扩展到外部贡献者是 NASA 的目标。</p><p></p><h3>集成架构挑战</h3><p>虽然集中式和跨职能集成架构使组织能够在其劳动力生态系统中实现更高级别的协调，但这些努力仍处于初期阶段。即使在处于劳动力生态系统转型前沿的公司中，领导者也强调这些努力才刚刚开始获得牵引力。在我们的研究和咨询工作中，我们发现大多数组织仍然采用被动、本地和不协调的方法来招募和留住外部人才和互补贡献者。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1个</a></p><p>领导者意识到，这种分散的努力既没有成本效益，也没有资源效率，并且有可能使内部员工失去积极性。然而，他们努力为劳动力生态系统编排建立一个集中的跨职能集成架构。我们听到了以下担忧：</p><ul><li>您如何确定一组合适的利益相关者来创建用于劳动力生态系统编排的集中集成架构？</li><li>您如何让利益相关者参与本地劳动力生态系统实验，以根据特定情况调整共同目标？</li><li>您如何从本地实验中促进协调学习？</li><li>随着时间的推移，您如何改进您的劳动力生态系统实施流程？</li></ul><p>要打造一个一体化的劳动力生态系统，至少需要解决三类问题：结构设计（涉及分工、目标和激励）、政治（涉及资源、权力和地位）和文化（影响个人对身份和意义的追求）。我们建议对这些问题采取分阶段的方法，这些问题相互交织、重叠并可以相互加强。此过程可能最适合开始采用劳动力生态系统的大型成熟组织，但关键要素应该对中小型企业有所帮助。 （参见“编排集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>协调集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段</h4><p class="caption">下图描述了与协调劳动力生态系统相关的主要挑战以及与解决这些挑战相关的阶段。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Altman_Figure.png" alt="协调集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>在第一阶段，我们建议创建一个编排团队，与相关的本地和中央利益相关者（内部和外部）协商制定工作计划、目标和指标。该团队应关注组织内部的整合考虑（职能角色和职责）以及与外部参与者的关系。通过与组织内已经聘用外部员工的团队合作，团队可以与在协调部分劳动力生态系统方面经验丰富的经理一起抢先一步。从结构设计的角度来看，他们可以快速开始突出并解决之前发现的技能差距。</p><p>为了解决政治问题，团队可以选择当地德高望重和行动导向的冠军来领导转型。此外，该团队可以包括来自外部贡献者的代表，以将他们的观点带入工作中。团队成员应能够酌情代表职能领域、产品组和业务部门发言；关键是获得所有利益攸关方群体的参与。最后，为了应对文化挑战，至少有一名团队成员应该扮演边界扳手的角色，充当中央团队、地方团队和其他受影响群体之间的中间人。</p><p>第二阶段，我们建议推进地方试点。中央编排团队可以引入试点项目来探索劳动力生态系统关系的潜在配置。这些实验可以解决结构性问题，例如为项目配备内部和外部员工、确定必要的技能、确保能力以及衡量结果的质量。他们可以解决政治挑战，例如内部员工抵制外部员工的贡献，以及当地领导因为失去对团队组成的控制而感到紧张。最后，随着员工适应职责的转变，可能会出现文化问题，特别是如果他们需要承担更多的协调角色，协调来自不同来源的参与者。</p><p>在第三阶段，我们强调协调学习和资源配置，跨越由本地团队确定并由中央团队监督的挑战（和成功）。现有政策和程序（例如知识产权许可模型或培训规则）等结构性障碍可能在传统的员工生命周期模型中为组织提供良好服务，但需要对劳动力生态系统进行修改。资源问题可能会出现，因为当地管理人员雇用了更多的外部工人或更容易与分包商合作，但随后拒绝释放员工接受其他机会。即使最高管理层和较低级别的人接受变革，中层管理人员也可能会抵制，因为他们经常肩负管理这些有时具有高度破坏性的转型的日常挑战的任务。</p><p>在第四个也是最后一个阶段，我们考虑劳动力生态系统的扩展。一旦对初始试点进行了分析并且新实践开始制度化，领导者应该考虑哪些其他新系统、工具、目标、指标和流程已被证明足够成功，可以采用。随着组织不断获得知识和经验，应定期审查这些内容。领导者可能希望扩大中央协调团队，以包括来自其他内部团队的代表。他们可能想考虑将他们的劳动力生态系统与其他人联系起来——例如，与客户组织及其生态系统更紧密地合作。在文化上，领导者可以考虑通过讲故事和其他沟通工具更积极地促进分布式学习和劳动力生态系统活动。他们可能希望强调增长机会，同时也开始解决不可避免地伴随此类转型而来的无数担忧。</p><p>这种四阶段方法提供了一种实用的方法来吸引、连接和激活关键利益相关者。从那里开始，组织可以开始塑造自己的战略和路径，方法是尝试新型集成架构，并在了解不同环境下哪些有效和无效时快速迭代。</p><p>与集成架构定义内部职能和业务部门如何协同工作以协调劳动力生态系统的方式相呼应，领导者需要定义如何管理与外部贡献者的关系。领导者面临着关于哪些集成架构适合外部贡献者的几个决定。</p><p>第三方集成架构的选择可能决定合作伙伴愿意花费资源参与（或贡献）劳动力生态系统的程度。例如，关于如何与开发人员生态系统协调的决策对于有效的劳动力生态系统至关重要。 Google Play 是 Google 的应用程序和内容分发市场。与 Apple 分发应用程序和内容的 Apple App Store 相比，Google 的操作更轻松，要求和合规性测试也不那么严格。众所周知，Apple 的政策要严格得多。与外部开发人员的集成架构可能或多或少有些僵化，也可能或多或少受欢迎。</p><p>与第三方构建集成架构引发了关于谁应该在企业内拥有这些关系的问题。例如，视频游戏机制造商通常允许第三方开发者（补充者）开发可在其系统上运行的游戏；通常，正是对这些第三方游戏的需求推动了特定游戏机的销售。开发者关系应该由业务开发或战略小组（也可能处理战略联盟）负责，还是由专门负责开发者生态系统的单独小组负责？集成架构有助于定义职责并裁定具有竞争利益的内部团队之间的潜在冲突。</p><p></p><p>在您的组织中实施集成架构首先要评估您的劳动力生态系统当前的运作方式。您组织的人力资源职能目前对内部和外部贡献者有多大的可见性和控制力？如果这些贡献者当前以分散的方式进行管理，请评估您的组织是否最适合此架构。</p><p></p><p>如果您认识到更集中集成和协调的劳动力生态系统对您的组织来说是更好的方法，请决定哪些团体和个人应该成为协调团队的一部分。是否应该由某人（或某个团体）集中负责监督整个劳动力生态系统？</p><p>在我们的整个研究过程中，我们听到领导者描述了他们在日益复杂和相互联系的劳动力生态系统中聘请对公司成功至关重要的人才的努力。我们一次又一次地观察到，有意识地协调劳动力生态系统的观点可以帮助领导者对他们自己的组织以及他们实现战略目标所依赖的人员、合作伙伴和技术有更丰富、更细致的看法。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>打开职业公平的快速通道</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian 是 Workforce Sciences Institute 的共同负责人和联合创始人，也是 Mercer 的前高级合伙人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com The Research The author conducted the research underlying this article while coleading Mercer’s Workforce Sciences Institute.i The author analyzed results of his research team&#8217;s statistical analyses of three to five years of employee data for 20 large and midsize, mostly global, employers representing manufacturing and services companies in a range of industries, including [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Nalbantian_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者在共同领导美世劳动力科学研究所的同时进行了本文的基础研究。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></li><li>作者分析了他的研究团队对 20 家大中型（大部分是全球性）雇主的三到五年员工数据的统计分析结果，这些雇主代表了一系列行业的制造和服务公司，包括消费品和工业产品、制药、技术、金融服务和专业服务。这些公司总共雇用了超过 700,000 名员工。大约 40% 的员工在美国。</li></ul></aside><p>商业领袖倾向于将他们的多元化、公平和包容 (DEI) 工作重点放在解决偏见和歧视上，因为这些做法很普遍，而且歧视是非法的。但在这个过程中，他们忽视了情境因素，这些情境因素在决定女性和有色人种是否获得晋升以及是否属于高薪人群方面起着主导作用——而且更容易解决。</p><p>职业和薪酬公平有着千丝万缕的联系。女性和有色人种在经理和高管中的比例仍然不足，在高级专业人士中也经常如此。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>虽然这些人口群体的薪酬公平正在改善，但许多公司的原始薪酬差距（女性和男性之间以及有色人种和白人员工之间的平均和中位数差异）仍然很高。这些薪酬差距将持续存在，直到女性和有色人种以合理反映其在劳动力中的代表性的比率占据要求最高薪酬的职业级别和角色。</p><p></p><p>不公平不仅伤害个体员工；它还剥夺了企业被忽视的人才。如果领导者了解情境因素如何影响员工的晋升前景，他们就可以应用<em>积极的职业生涯管理 (PCM)</em> ——识别并消除阻碍员工成功的障碍——使他们的工作场所更加公平和高效。</p><p>为了更好地理解这些职业成果差异背后的因素，我检查了 20 家大中型公司多年晋升、​​保留、绩效和薪酬数据的分析结果，这些公司的员工总数超过 700,000。调查结果证实，女性和有色人种在晋升概率方面存在显着的性别和种族差异，这可归因于四个始终对员工成功产生影响的因素：绩效评级、角色分配、报告关系和灵活的工作安排。</p><p>除了绩效评级外，这些因素与员工的情况有关，而不是他们的知识、技能或行为。例如，如果职业发展需要某些角色的经验，但相对于男性，女性在这些角色中的比例不足，最终结果是晋升的女性人数较少。</p><p>当然，偏见和歧视也在起作用：在大多数组织中，我们发现在晋升的可能性方面存在巨大的、无法解释的性别和种族差异，这无法用任何与业务相关的因素来解释。我们发现绩效评估中存在普遍且相当大的种族差异，有色人种，尤其是黑人员工，不太可能获得高评价。这些是企业多元化、公平和包容性努力的合乎逻辑的重点，因为它们是偏见或歧视的证据。</p><p>但由于解释的差异往往对职业发展和薪酬公平影响最大，因此直接解决这些差异很重要。好消息是这些因素通常最容易成功解决。积极的职业生涯管理是一种数据驱动的方法，可提供有效的解决方案。</p><h3>四大因素推动谁在工作中进步</h3><p>让我们更仔细地看看我确定的四个因素，这些因素可以解释谁在工作中获得晋升、高绩效评级和更大的加薪，以及为什么女性和有色人种往往看不到这些好处。</p><p><strong>绩效评级。</strong>由于绩效评级会影响所有其他结果，例如晋升、保留和薪酬，因此该领域的差异会产生级联效应。在 89% 的研究公司中，黑人员工不太可能获得高绩效评级。差异可能相当大，大多数为 25% 或更高。此外，由于绩效评级往往年复一年地持续存在——一年的高评级预示着下一年高评级的可能性——有色人种获得较低评级的趋势实际上成为他们进步的障碍。 Interestingly, women are generally more likely to be highly rated than otherwise comparable men, but that doesn&#39;t translate into a higher probability of promotion for them.</p><p> <strong>Access to accelerator roles.</strong> In every company, certain roles are career accelerators and others are dead ends, regardless of who occupies them. In this study, having a supervisor role at any level almost universally improved the chance that an employee would be promoted and receive high ratings. However, we almost always found that women and people of color were far less likely to be in such roles than men or White employees, respectively.</p><p> The differences are often stark and steep. For example, in a global financial services company we studied, US-based employees who were supervisors were 50% more likely to be promoted and 55% more likely to receive high performance ratings than those who were not supervisors. Outside the US, supervisors were 89% more likely to be promoted and 37% more likely to get high ratings. These effects were even larger for female supervisors than for male supervisors. But across the company, women were half as likely to be supervisors. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> Further, because women are more likely than men to face career disruption during their child-rearing years, they may take on supervisor roles later. In such cases, they don&#39;t experience the same compounding benefit of being in such roles as their male colleagues.</p><p> <strong>Reporting relationships.</strong> Whom one reports to can have a decisive impact on the trajectory of one&#39;s career. We generally found that people who reported to supervisors with high performance ratings were significantly more likely to receive a high rating as well. The probability that they would be promoted also increased.</p><p> We saw similar effects for employees whose managers were higher up in the corporate hierarchy than the norm for someone at their level and thus had more clout. To the extent that women and people of color are less likely to report to high-performing and higher-level supervisors, they are less likely to receive high ratings or promotions themselves.</p><p> They may also be less likely to benefit from these relationships when they do have them. At a global insurance company, those who reported to a top-rated supervisor were about 50% more likely to be promoted and 30% more likely to receive high performance ratings. Those whose supervisors were at a level higher than the norm were 9% more likely to be promoted and 14% more likely to be highly rated. However, having a high-performing or higher-ranked supervisor did not help women and people of color as much as it helped White men.</p><p> <strong>Flexible working.</strong> Increasingly, organizations view flexible work arrangements as essential to attracting and retaining talent, particularly women and younger employees. Since the COVID-19 pandemic, more companies and employees have embraced such arrangements, but historically, they have been career killers. For example, those who work part time or remotely or take family leave are less likely to be promoted, are paid less, and are more likely to leave their companies.</p><p> At a business I&#39;ll refer to as ConsumerCo, opting for flexible work arrangements hurt both women and people of color. The percentage of women working part time was three times that of men; for people of color, it was two times that of White employees. Overall, working part time reduced promotion probability by 50% and the likelihood of receiving a high rating by 70%. It also increased turnover probability by 25% compared with similarly situated full-time workers.</p><p> Likewise, leaves of absence were disproportionately taken by women and people of color. Those on leave were about 50% less likely to be promoted or receive high ratings and much more likely to turn over — at least 150% more likely in the US and at least 80% more likely globally. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Unless companies do something to mitigate the negative consequences of flexible working on employees, the phenomenon of higher levels of flexible work arrangements risks further undermining career progress for women and people of color.</p><h3> The Case for Proactive Career Management</h3><p> With the exception of performance ratings, these drivers of career progress, or lack thereof, are situational. This is telling. It indicates that whether employees advance is not just a reflection of the talents and skills they bring or what they do, but also of how well their employers position them to succeed. All too often, women and people of color simply aren&#39;t positioned to succeed in the same way their White male counterparts are.</p><p> This is not to say that bias and discrimination are not factors, as mentioned above. However, employers can make measurable progress on DEI when they understand the extent of the positioning issues in their workforce and deal with them in a purposeful, systematic way. This is where PCM comes into play.</p><p></p><p> The idea behind proactive career management for DEI is simple: Identify and rank the factors that most influence career success and retention; if and where they skew significantly against certain demographic groups, intervene to eliminate or reduce the disparities. In other words, work to ensure that demographic characteristics bear no relationship to how well or poorly positioned an employee is to stay and succeed at work.</p><p> Every organization has talent flows that shape their workforce. Employers hire, train, and develop employees. And they value employees by giving them promotions, high ratings, raises, and other forms of compensation for the knowledge, capabilities, behavior, and experience they bring, the effort they deliver, and, ultimately, how they perform. Meanwhile, employees&#39; decisions to stay or leave are influenced by whether their careers are progressing.</p><p> These talent flows and rewards define the internal labor market of an organization and produce the supply of people with the attributes needed to meet the demands of the business. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> But as we have seen, different demographic groups within an organization do not have the same opportunities to acquire these attributes or be rewarded for them.</p><p> By not distributing opportunities equitably, companies effectively restrict their talent supplies. Women and people of color become more likely to leave or, if they stay, become less engaged because their careers are stalled. Knowing how the internal labor market functions for different demographic groups within an organization is thus crucial for a company to execute its DEI strategy.</p><p> To implement PCM, organizations should start by creating a success profile that identifies and ranks the factors that drive who advances. From there, they can examine how each factor influences the probability that employees from different demographic groups get promoted and whether the organization is valuing their capabilities and efforts equitably.</p><p></p><p> Small organizations might rely on the four factors described in the previous section. For them, controlled, statistical analyses of their own internal labor market data are likely infeasible. Such organizations might complement the research with qualitative input about the keys to career progress from their leaders and employees who have successfully risen in the ranks there.</p><p> Large employers with complex organizations will be best served by developing an objective success profile based on empirical evidence that identifies and ranks the critical individual and situational factors that drive success in the organization. The natural place to start is with the factors that drive promotions. But organizations might examine other markers of success as well, like pay, ratings, and retention, to see how well the results align with those from the analysis of promotions.</p><p> After creating the profile, the next step is to examine how the profile plays out for different demographic groups. There are two questions to answer.</p><p> First, are the factors that most influence employee success distributed similarly across demographic groups, or do they tend to be concentrated more in some groups than in others? These are <em>quantity effects</em> , and they reflect the relative frequency of the factors across groups. For instance, are women and people of color as likely as men and White employees to have the prized characteristics or to work in circumstances associated with success?</p><p> Second, when people possess the prized characteristics or work in favored circumstances, do they benefit equally from those attributes, or do some demographic groups benefit more? These are <em>price effects</em> . They reflect whether the employer values the attribute, behavior, or situation in question differently for one group than for another.</p><p> Objectively answering these questions is the foundation of PCM, as illustrated in the case of ConsumerCo.</p><p></p><h3> Positioning Employees for Success at ConsumerCo</h3><p> ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders were committed to improving career and pay equity in both their salaried and front-line workforces.</p><p> The company recognized that having a diverse workforce was not a luxury or a concession to social good; it was essential to its success. With an increasingly diverse customer base and growth occurring mostly in markets outside the US and Europe, having a leadership team and a workforce well attuned to the preferences and norms of local cultures was important to achieving growth targets.</p><p> HR and DEI leaders modeled their workforce data to uncover and assess the success profile for their salaried workforce. They identified 12 factors that were most likely to predict whether someone would be promoted. Situational factors dominated this success profile — a finding that stunned company leaders, who viewed the culture as a meritocracy. Of the top 12, only performance ratings and tenure were specific to the talents or accomplishments of an individual employee. The rest were purely circumstantial.</p><p> Being an expat (working outside one&#39;s home country) was the most positively influential factor. Reporting to a supervisor at a higher level than is typical had the least impact among the top 12 factors, but the effect was statistically significant.</p><p> Other factors included three of the four described earlier: having a high performance rating, being in a supervisory role, and reporting to a highly rated supervisor. In addition, working in certain functions or business lines mattered a lot to how one&#39;s career progressed.</p><p> Similar modeling showed that even the probability of receiving a high rating was inordinately influenced by situational factors. This finding suggested that performance ratings were not accurate measures of individuals&#39; contributions.</p><p> When ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders mapped the success profile to women in the company, they found that when women were positioned in situations conducive to their future progress, they usually fared as well as men. But overall, they were less likely to be so positioned. (See “Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile.”) For instance, women who were expats were more likely to be promoted from those roles than otherwise comparable men, but women were less represented among the expat population.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile</h4><p class="caption"> A global consumer products retailer identified the 12 attributes that most strongly influenced whether an employee would be promoted. It found that in most cases, when women possessed any of these attributes, they were as likely to be helped by it as men were. However, women were less likely than men to possess 9 of the 12 attributes. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.) </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:45%;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Traits Favorable to Promotion<br /> <span class="normal">(in order of impact)</span></th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Likelihood That Women Possess Trait Compared With Men</th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Relative Impact of Trait Compared With Men</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>1. Being an expat</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>2. In Function M</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>3. In Function C</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>4. In Country A</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>5. In Bonus Plan F</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong style="color:crimson;">降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>6. In Function H</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>7. In Function S</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>8. Receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>9. Supervisor receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>10. Being a supervisor</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>11. Longer tenured</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>12. Reporting up</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Nalbantian_Table_1.png" alt="Mapping Women’s Experiences to a Success Profile" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p> Being a supervisor is also an important stepping stone to success at ConsumerCo, but the company learned that women were less represented in supervisor roles. When they did have those roles, it did not help their careers to the same extent as comparable men, for reasons that were not clear. ConsumerCo leaders could see that female employees faced a double whammy of sorts: Not only were they blocked from this accelerator role, but they also didn&#39;t get the same lift to their promotion prospects as their male colleagues when they did have that role.</p><p> When the company looked at people of color, it found that they tended to be both less well positioned and less valued than White employees. ConsumerCo needed to change its internal labor market dynamics to achieve career and pay equity for women and people of color.</p><h3> A Checklist for Change</h3><p> Focusing on situational factors has a distinct advantage: They&#39;re easier to address than individual characteristics. For instance, although tenure is an important driver of success, it is a fact of people&#39;s employment history, not something that ConsumerCo could change overnight.</p><p> Still, ConsumerCo identified several areas where it could act reasonably quickly, such as changing reporting relationships for women and people of color, finding opportunities for them to gain more supervisory experience earlier in their careers, and addressing the disparities in performance ratings for people of color.</p><p> The company had found that taking a leave of absence thwarted career advancement, especially for women, and so it is also developing new leave and career development policies to address imbalances for that group.</p><p> Here&#39;s where the “proactive” part of PCM comes in.</p><p> The analysis of ConsumerCo&#39;s success profile made it possible to create a simple checklist of green lights (career advancers) and red flags (success blockers) that managers could use to evaluate the positioning of individual employees. By considering whether women and people of color on their teams were experiencing more green lights or red flags, line managers and supervisors could identify who was well positioned to stay and thrive, as well as who might be at risk of stalling in their career or leaving the organization. (See “Green Lights, Red Flags.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Green Lights, Red Flags</h4><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> A global consumer products retailer created a checklist of attributes that help or hurt employees&#39; career progress. Managers use the checklist to identify whether women and people of color on their teams are well positioned to advance or might be at risk of stalling in their careers or leaving the organization. They can then take any steps needed to increase access to success drivers and mitigate unintended consequences. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.)</p><h4 style="color:#43BD29;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> GREEN LIGHTS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>FAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceptional” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being more tenured than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceeds” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being younger than comparable peers</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being an expat<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being a supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in function M, C, S, or H<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in bonus plan F or L<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a higher-level supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a top-rated supervisor</p><h4 style="color:crimson;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> RED FLAGS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>UNFAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Having a longer time in grade than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being part time<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Recently on leave<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Receiving a “medium” rating</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working in distribution<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working on the night shift<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Not in top brands<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Experienced a change in supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a female supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being on teams with more older colleagues (reduces promotion likelihood, but increases chances of getting top rating)<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a supervisor with a larger number of direct reports</p></article></aside></div><p> Meanwhile, HR and DEI leaders used the analysis to evaluate at the aggregate level how employees from different demographic groups were positioned to succeed. For each factor, they could effectively evaluate the situational reality of different groups and tailor their interventions to address the most significant gaps.</p><p> For instance, they found that female, Black, and Hispanic employees were less likely to be reporting to highly rated supervisors, while Asian employees were more likely to have this advantage. And although women were less likely to be reporting to a manager one grade higher than usual, there were no such disparities for people of color. Also, while every non-White racial group was significantly underrepresented in one of the core functions that most contributed to advancement, women were more likely to work in that function than men.</p><p> ConsumerCo is in the early stages of rolling out interventions to address its disparities. But other companies I have worked with have pursued a variety of solutions.</p><p> Closing gaps due to flexible work arrangements often requires changing the culture. In many companies, part-time work is looked upon as evidence of lower commitment, and it can be difficult to shake these perceptions. However, companies can make quick progress on pay if they stop factoring leaves of absence into the statistical models that they use to assess pay equity and adjust wages and salaries to close gaps.</p><p> Situation-based racial disparities in performance ratings have been reduced in some companies through the calibration process used to align ratings by different supervisors. Some have also eliminated forced rankings that provide for a very limited percentage of employees to receive top ratings. These tend to favor people with more tenure, whom supervisors have known longer, and presumably better — and who are more likely to be White.</p><p> Some clients have addressed the importance of supervisor roles by expanding training, both to reinforce the importance of these roles and to help supervisors understand the impact they have on employees&#39; prospects. Leaders can offer training to help women and people of color gain the experience they need to advance — and close the gap between women and men in these positions.</p><h3> Proactive Career Management Has Benefits and Risks</h3><p> Because a success profile is built from an organization&#39;s data, it is more likely to reflect reality than the assumptions that leaders make about how employees succeed. Leaders may be prone to thinking that what got them to the top could get anyone else there as well, and they may oversimplify their own path. Further, people tend to generalize based on their own experiences, even if they don&#39;t represent the organizational norm.</p><p> A good empirical model can counter the tendency of people to engage in wishful thinking or to cling to belief. It can also account for the effects of being in different business lines, functions, geographies, and job families. This is something that&#39;s hard to do based on personal observation and experience alone.</p><p></p><p> Another value of PCM is that it is grounded in what creates value for the business. If, for instance, a role becomes critical to growth, one would expect the employer to accord more value to that role and the employees who successfully deliver value in it. And to the extent that an organization&#39;s DEI strategy helps ensure that high-potential women and people of color are able to access these newly valuable roles and perform them ably, it will serve the greater business need.</p><p> If there is a downside to PCM, it relates to the sharing of sensitive data and intelligence. PCM proceeds from objective modeling of the drivers of success and how they affect different groups. Invariably, the models will surface potentially damaging information about the existence of systemic gender or racial disparities in outcomes and opportunities, which creates legal risk.</p><p> PCM works best when managers understand the realities uncovered by the models and the reasons why specific actions are warranted. Thus, it requires a reasonable level of transparency. Corporate legal departments may, however, object to exposing what they may believe to be strong evidence of bias and inequity.</p><p> There&#39;s a delicate balance to be achieved. Most organizations I work with accomplish it by sharing high-level information with business and line leaders, and sometimes employee groups, about the reasons for particular actions while restricting the more granular data to a smaller group of top executives and HR and DEI leaders. Legal counsel almost always presides over such decisions; however, such advisers have become more understanding of the need for data-driven DEI strategies, appreciating that people can&#39;t solve problems they don&#39;t know about or understand.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The unexplained disparities in career opportunity and advancement at many organizations are important to address because they signal the potential influence of bias and discrimination. But doing so should not override attention to differences that can be explained by legitimate, business-relevant factors. The surest, most sustainable way to create career equity and equitable representation across all levels of an organization is to address the organization&#39;s career development practices (or lack thereof) that systemically impede the progress of women and people of color.</p><p> Of course, the work that employees do, their knowledge and skills, and how hard and effectively they work influence whether they will succeed. But success is also determined by how individuals are positioned to succeed — and organizations can do better at ensuring that all high-potential talent can gain experiences that will set them up for growth.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Empower Your Team, Empower Yourself</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Clayton, Andrew Artis, and Dejun Tony Kong. <p>Russell Clayton is an assistant professor of instruction, teaching MBA courses in the Muma College of Business at the University of South Florida. Andrew Artis is an associate professor teaching sales and strategy courses, also in the Muma College of Business. Dejun Tony Kong is an associate professor of organizational leadership at the University of Colorado Boulder&#39;s Leeds School of Business.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s rapidly evolving work environment, professional development is no longer a nice-to-have perk, it’s an imperative. With budgets tightening and workforce disruptions such as layoffs affecting many sectors, now is not the time for organizations to eliminate employee professional development and training. Likewise, individuals should continue to upskill regardless of whether organizational resources are [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Clayton-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> In today&#39;s rapidly evolving work environment, professional development is no longer a nice-to-have perk, it&#39;s an imperative. With budgets tightening and workforce disruptions such as layoffs affecting many sectors, now is not the time for organizations to eliminate employee professional development and training. Likewise, individuals should continue to upskill regardless of whether organizational resources are plentiful. In this article, we explore ways that executives may approach learning and development (L&amp;D) spending, as well as strategies for employees to secure professional development funding.</p><h3> For Managers: How L&amp;D Can Keep Teams Competitive</h3><p> In this first section, we&#39;ll explore three key strategies for managers to effectively allocate resources for L&amp;D, even during difficult economic times. When they better understand the importance of such programs, leaders can make more informed decisions that benefit the organization in the long term.</p><p></p><h4> 1. Assess the risk of cutting L&amp;D budgets.</h4><p> When budgets are tight, L&amp;D is often among the first programs to suffer cutbacks. This frequently happens because training is perceived as the low-hanging fruit when it comes to justifying budget cuts. However, these types of short-term cost-saving measures may not be a wise strategic move for executives. Having well-trained employees is critical to staying competitive, and we encourage executives to assess the risks their organization will be taking should they decide to eliminate employee training dollars.</p><p> For example, organizations that cut L&amp;D spending may fall behind when the economy recovers compared with those that maintain their investments. As a result, workers could lack the critical skills needed for organizational success. Furthermore, investing in L&amp;D helps companies do more with less. The number of skills needed for a single job has increased 10% annually since 2017, according to <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">research conducted by Gartner</a> . Those organizations that continue to prioritize upskilling will have employees who are up to date on the skills needed to accomplish their work, whereas organizations that significantly cut L&amp;D likely will not.</p><p> <a href="https://www.pwc.com/gx/en/ceo-survey/2020/reports/pwc-23rd-global-ceo-survey.pdf">PwC&#39;s annual CEO survey</a> found that companies with advanced L&amp;D programs in place had higher employee engagement and were better at attracting and retaining top talent. Executives must keep this in mind, even in the face of economic downturns, because slashing L&amp;D budgets can increase the risk of losing talented employees. As Josh Felperin, global sales director of Alps Controls, put it, “Investing in employees&#39; personal and professional development on a consistent basis should be any leadership team&#39;s No. 1 priority, not just financial results.”</p><h4> 2. Shift to framing L&amp;D as an investment.</h4><p> Managers need to consider L&amp;D as an investment rather than a cost. Think about how L&amp;D can generate revenue instead of being just another budget line item. For example, upskilling and promoting from within can save organizations money on recruitment and hiring. According to the Society for Human Resource Management, the average hard cost of recruiting a new employee is $4,700, with total costs — including soft costs such as time — amounting to two to three times the position&#39;s salary. Now imagine what your L&amp;D managers could do with just half of that dollar figure in terms of upskilling a current employee instead of hiring a new candidate. Not only are you saving on recruiting costs — you are also helping your organization close the skills gap that is plaguing many industries.</p><p></p><p> Finally, executives should view their <em>own</em> L&amp;D activities as an investment. In a tight economic environment, it might be tempting to cut both L&amp;D funds and the time dedicated to training. However, research has found a significant relationship between <a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/ijtd.12082">executive L&amp;D activities and organizational performance</a> .</p><h4> 3. Strategically prioritize the skills to be developed.</h4><p> When facing economic headwinds, budget reductions across all departments might be unavoidable, and we&#39;re not arguing that L&amp;D budgets should remain completely untouched. However, we do advocate for allocating funds to strategic training priorities. The reality is that some L&amp;D training may be postponed until the economy flourishes again. It might be necessary to prioritize hard skills, like project management or cybersecurity, over soft skills, like time management, in the short term. While we strongly support <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/answer-sheet/wp/2017/12/20/the-surprising-thing-google-learned-about-its-employees-and-what-it-means-for-todays-students/">soft skills training</a> — they play a key role in every business — we understand that L&amp;D funds may need to be spent on immediate hard-skills training needs in order to keep your organization competitive.</p><p> Match your L&amp;D expenditures to your organization&#39;s KPIs. Amazon is a great example of a company that does this. Despite recent major layoffs, it continues to train employees in key areas through its Upskilling 2025 initiative, including hard skills like cloud computing services and machine learning. Regardless of which skills you value most, the imperative is to be sure you&#39;re providing training opportunities. “Organizations that are not investing in the development of their employees are working against themselves and tripping over their own feet,” Jon Sexton, senior vice president of culture and leadership development at Vibrant Credit Union, asserted.</p><p></p><h3> For Employees: Strategies for Securing Professional Development Opportunities</h3><p> Pursuing professional development opportunities in the workplace can be challenging, particularly when budgets are constrained. Instead of passively waiting for workshop and training opportunities to arise, employees need to be proactive in convincing managers of the mutual benefits of L&amp;D investments.</p><p> That said, asking for money when budgets are tight is never an easy conversation, particularly when L&amp;D is perceived as merely nice to have. We recommend the following approaches to prepare your case, shape a productive conversation, and secure funding for your professional development.</p><h4> 1. Align your goals with your organization&#39;s needs.</h4><p> To increase your chances of obtaining approval for professional development opportunities, frame your request by demonstrating how the training will support your team&#39;s objectives. If you can explain how it will move your team forward, you&#39;re more likely to gain your manager&#39;s support (and funding).</p><p></p><p> Take the case of Nick. His employer already had an in-house training team delivering Continuing Professional Education hours for accountants, so he didn&#39;t think it would sign off on an external CPE course that focused on reviewing skills. To justify the expense and need — given his position as a junior accountant at the time — Nick discussed how the course would benefit the firm <em>first</em> and himself <em>second</em> with the managing partner. Nick emphasized that the course would help the company maintain its commitment to providing accurate, reliable information to clients through specific training on how to avoid making common tax accounting errors. By making the compelling argument that the external training would provide critical skills to help the company achieve its mission, Nick was able to convince his manager that the training would be valuable and received the funding.</p><p> Similarly, when Amanda, an insurance professional, asked her manager to pay for her training to earn her claims adjuster license, she took what she described as a “help me, help my team” approach. Amanda made her pitch for professional development during a time when the team she was on was struggling. While her current job function was <em>not</em> that of a claims adjuster, earning the license allowed her to help her organization in an area that really needed assistance.</p><p> During your pitch, ask your manager how they would like you to share the knowledge gained from training. This might involve a one-on-one follow-up, sharing presentation materials or bullet points summarizing the training, or even hosting a workshop to review the material with your team. By being proactive in sharing what you&#39;ve learned, you further solidify the benefits of professional development for the entire team.</p><h4> 2. Bring your manager on board.</h4><p> As <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/learning-for-a-living/">Gianpiero Petriglieri has noted</a> , many organizations “are not as hospitable to learning as their rhetoric suggests.” While employees may be frustrated by managers who overlook learning or prioritize performance over all else, they can educate managers on the benefits that professional development can bring to the company by taking a tactful approach.</p><p> For example, one vice president at a large industrial services company was reluctant to see training as an investment, fearing that employees might demand a raise or even leave after the training. In truth, this belief is a myth, if not irrational. Employees are a greater flight risk when they do <em>not</em> see internal opportunities and have to look elsewhere for personal growth. After all, employees are humans who have the fundamental need to feel competent, and they appreciate arrangements that are <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.obhdp.2015.08.002">customized to their skills and interests</a> . Employees can share third-party sources that emphasize the importance of targeted training to employee retention and engagement. For example, <a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/236438/millennials-jobs-development-opportunities.aspx">research from Gallup</a> suggests that professional development is a top factor in retaining millennials.</p><p> When discussing the topic with your manager, it&#39;s important to embrace a positive tone and remember that there might be resistance along the way. Shape the conversation in a way that focuses on how professional development increases the retention of valued employees. Be prepared to hear “no,” but probe to find out what might make your manager say “yes.” By understanding their concerns, you&#39;re better equipped to overcome those barriers. Consider asking questions like, “What would help you say yes?” or, “Would you worry about our competitor sending employees to this training?” This encourages your manager to consider the potential upsides of your request.</p><p> Three communication touch points are helpful for closing the circle when it comes to getting your manager invested in L&amp;D as a team resource. First, communicate clearly about the training you&#39;re seeking and gain permission to attend the training. Second, update your manager <em>during</em> the training, expressing your enthusiasm and gratitude. For example, you can send your manager a short status update on how the training is going and initial ideas you have to bring back to the team. Lastly, once the training is complete, acknowledge your manager&#39;s support when sharing your newfound knowledge with the team. By showing your excitement, you can inspire coworkers who also desire professional development.</p><h4> 3. Show your commitment to learning.</h4><p> When pitching your professional development request, consider providing several options, ranging from fully funded by the company to partially funded by you. Demonstrating your commitment to learning new skills, even if it means investing your own money, can make your request more persuasive.</p><p> Divya, for example, found a $2,500 training opportunity to develop the soft skills needed to better serve customers at her government agency job. Knowing that funding was limited, she proposed several options to her manager, including 100%, 50%, and 25% company funding. By having some skin in the game, Divya showed that she was serious about the training. In the end, her request was fully funded by the agency, but she was prepared to accept partial funding and cover the rest herself.</p><p> You can also show your commitment by exploring lower-cost or free opportunities before pursuing other options. An effective way to do this is to detail what you have learned so far through training options at no cost to your employer — and what skills or knowledge gaps still exist. Perhaps you want to earn a certification in data visualization. You can begin by completing online courses for free or at minimal cost, which can provide the foundational knowledge needed in this area and demonstrate your time investment. Then, explain to your manager what you&#39;ve learned and why additional, funded training is necessary to further your goals.</p><p></p><p> This collaborative negotiation process allows you to (1) <a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1571-9979.1999.tb00178.x">adopt an interest-based approach</a> , (2) help your manager <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0065-2601(08)60407-4">overcome psychological barriers</a> , and (3) <a href="https://doi.org/10.5465/amj.2012.0461">build trust</a> and mitigate your manager&#39;s perception of risk.</p><p></p><p> Prioritizing learning and development is essential for both managers and employees to help steer their organizations toward sustainable success and maintain a competitive edge. Even during economic uncertainty, strategic L&amp;D investments can boost employee engagement, close skill gaps, and foster growth. By recognizing the value of professional development and adopting a collaborative approach, leaders and employees alike can create a thriving learning culture that promotes individual and organizational success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do You Have a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ane Casajús-Burutaran, Tina C. Ambos, and Gilbert Probst. <p>Ane Casajús-Burutaran is a research assistant and doctoral candidate at the University of Geneva. Tina C. Ambos is a full professor of international management at the University of Geneva. Gilbert Probst is an honorary professor at the University of Geneva and chairman of the Swiss Board Institute.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Reputation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Corporate Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><description><![CDATA[Corporate philanthropy spending reached new heights in 2021, exceeding $21 billion in the U.S. alone and marking a 24% increase over the previous year.1 These contributions, which traditionally focused on supporting galleries, museums, and shiny new buildings, have gained a higher profile in corporate decision-making. While management scholars have long pointed out the importance of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Casajus-Burutaran-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Corporate philanthropy spending reached new heights in 2021, exceeding $21 billion in the US alone and marking a 24% increase over the previous year. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These contributions, which traditionally focused on supporting galleries, museums, and shiny new buildings, have gained a higher profile in corporate decision-making. While management scholars have long pointed out the importance of corporate philanthropy, businesses&#39; approaches to it vary widely, and few have fully integrated it into their corporate strategy. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> This article examines the shifting landscape of corporate giving and the potential implications for businesses and their stakeholders.</p><p> As companies face growing pressures to incorporate purposeful social missions into their core businesses, leaders have gained experience managing initiatives aimed at social impact in addition to profit. While corporate social responsibility (CSR) is part of most companies&#39; business strategies, philanthropy often remains disconnected from core business objectives. This makes it challenging for leaders to discern what types of philanthropic engagement should be prioritized and why.</p><p></p><p> We define <em>strategic corporate philanthropy</em> as voluntary giving that builds on the company&#39;s core competencies to achieve social impact while improving its competitive edge — resulting in a win-win situation. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The scope of corporate philanthropic engagement is vast. (See “Main Types of Corporate Philanthropy Engagement.”) Even though gift matching has led the way for many years in the US, Coca-Cola, Google, and Walt Disney are just a few of the many multinationals that now engage in more than one type of corporate philanthropy. IBM&#39;s Open Source Community Grant program (with annual contributions of $200,000), the Danone Ecosystem (an impact investment fund with over $200 million committed since 2009), and the Ikea Foundation (with unrestricted funding for selected nonprofits working on emergency relief) are examples of the great diversity of corporate philanthropic engagement.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Main Types of Corporate Philanthropy Engagement</h4><p> <strong>Community grants:</strong> The company supports local community efforts or nonprofits with financial or in-kind contributions.</p><p> <strong>Corporate foundations:</strong> The company establishes and funds an independent legal entity to manage its philanthropic projects. These can be directly operated by the foundation or co-led through partnerships or grant giving.</p><p> <strong>Corporate sponsoring:</strong> The company finances the events, projects, or programs of a nonprofit organization.</p><p> <strong>Gift matching:</strong> The company matches the charitable donation of an employee, usually at a 1-1 ratio.</p><p> <strong>Venture philanthropy:</strong> The corporation takes the principles of venture capital financing to select, guide, and support a charitable project. This is often done through a corporate foundation.</p></article></aside></div><p></p><p> Increasingly, companies are establishing corporate foundations, which are legally independent entities that work exclusively on philanthropic activities. This allows them to take a more systematic approach to giving and create a “philanthropic identity.” Examples include the Walmart Foundation (with annual giving of $1.5 billion) and the Chanel Foundation (supporting over 150 charitable organizations since 2011). However, guidance remains limited on what type of philanthropic engagement would best fit a company&#39;s strategy.</p><p> Corporate philanthropy has the potential to create multiple benefits for a business, including enhanced reputation, legitimacy, local integration, network creation, knowledge acquisition, institutional acceptance, and stakeholder trust. But it also bears risks. Thus, companies must think carefully about what, how, and where to engage.</p><p> Our research examines the various strategies companies are testing in the realm of corporate philanthropy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> When building a corporate philanthropy strategy, a business&#39;s most important decisions revolve around three central issues: what topics to engage in, which parts of the company can support these efforts, and how to maximize impact. First, in terms of engagement, companies can either actively engage in the design, implementation, and evaluation of potential projects (operational), or provide the resources for another organization to take the lead (grant giving). This decision should be based on their knowledge and expertise in their respective field. The second decision is whether to house the project in an external entity, like a corporate foundation, or internally under a department like sustainability, HR, public relations, or partnerships. Lastly, the project must be anchored within the community to make a real impact, either through the company&#39;s own networks in the country or through local partners.</p><p></p><p> Our analysis offers a framework to assist managers in their decision-making process, enabling them to ask the right questions to understand the fit of a philanthropic project for their organization. Three dimensions need to be assessed.</p><p> <strong>Cognitive fit:</strong> <em>Does your company have the knowledge and expertise to engage in this social issue?</em> Corporate philanthropy, much like any business activity, demands specialized competencies; thus, companies need to be selective to maximize their impact. Tackling complex issues related to their primary industry is a good starting point because businesses already have expertise in dealing with customers, suppliers, and other stakeholders. Prominent examples include the Loewe Foundation&#39;s commitment to creativity and craftmanship — aligned with its identity as a luxury fashion house — and Adidas&#39; focus on expanding access to sports for all.</p><p> <strong>Structural fit:</strong> <em>Can the project be linked to the internal structure of your organization?</em> Every project needs organizational support to be integrated with the company&#39;s corporate structure and processes, which will potentially involve CSR, HR, or logistics. But one unit or department has to be in charge of providing adequate economic, human, social, and intellectual capital. We find that different corporations develop very different structural solutions to manage their philanthropic activities. Roche decided to create a whole new department, called the Corporate Donations and Philanthropy department, integrated under the CEO&#39;s office. Inditex still carries out its philanthropic activities within its sustainability department, and Visa chose to manage its donations through the Visa Foundation, as an independent entity.</p><p> <strong>Contextual fit:</strong> <em>Is the company well anchored in the local community, and does it have access to it, in order to effectively design and implement the project?</em> Gaining access to the local context is critical for success — it enhances onsite decision-making capabilities and fosters trust among stakeholders. If the organization engages in a familiar context, it can better tailor social solutions to local needs and do so more efficiently. For instance, HSBC&#39;s Hongkong Bank Foundation has distributed over HK$2.4 billion ($305.8 million) to support the Hong Kong community, its home market. Another example is the eBay Foundation, which encourages its employees to volunteer and give within their local communities.</p><p> Answering these questions helps companies craft a corporate philanthropy strategy and determine the implications of alternative pathways. (See “Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy.”) Our assessment framework can be used on individual projects and to systematically manage a portfolio. When planning and defining a potential philanthropic project, managers can answer the questions related to the three dimensions and consider the recommendations given for each option. For example, a US-based fintech company seeking to engage in research projects focused on Alzheimer&#39;s disease would have a low cognitive fit between the philanthropic project and company expertise. It would also have a low structural fit if it did not have an in-house department to support community outreach for medical issues. Additionally, the fintech firm would score low on contextual fit if it were to engage in a program in Somalia — a market in which it doesn&#39;t operate or have specific knowledge. Under these circumstances, a grant-giving strategy through an external body like a foundation would be advisable. As this case reveals, thinking about the three dimensions can help managers establish guiding principles for their corporate philanthropy strategy and set rules regarding what, how, and where to engage. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4 style="line-height:1.5;"> Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy: An Assessment Framework</h4><p class="caption"> Using a structured framework to answer key questions, companies can craft strategies that not only guide the development of potential philanthropic projects but also streamline the management of their philanthropic portfolios. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile" style="width: 100%"><thead><tr><th style="width:23%;" class="white"> Dimension</th><th style="width:30%" class="white">评估</th><th style="width:45%" class="white">Evaluation</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Cognitive Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “What”)</p></td><td><p> <strong>Does your company have the knowledge and expertise to engage in this social issue?</strong> </p></td><td><div style="vertical-align:top"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Take an operational approach based on the company&#39;s knowledge and expertise. A corporate foundation, in-kind donations, or venture philanthropy might be the best solution. </p></div></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> Consider a grant-giving approach. Alternatively, engaging in a partnership with an expert organization can bridge the lack of cognitive fit and allow for more direct participation.</p></div></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Structural Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “How”)</p></td><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><p> <strong>Can the project be linked to the internal structure of your organization?</strong> </p></td><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Pursue this project internally; the CSR, HR, marketing, or communications teams may be suitable departments. You may choose to establish a dedicated unit focused on corporate donations and philanthropy. </p></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> The missing structural fit suggests that establishing an external entity such as a corporate foundation may be a better option to pursue this project.</p></div></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Contextual Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “Where”)</p></td><td><p> <strong>Is the company well anchored in the local community, and does it have access to it, in order to effectively design and implement the project?</strong> </p></td><td><div style="vertical-align:top"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Take an operational approach to the project. Your onsite team will be able to provide support, contextual understanding, and access to the local network for effective implementation. </p></div></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> A grant-giving approach is recommended in this case. Alternatively, engage in a partnership with an expert (local) organization. </p></div></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Casajus-Burutaran-Table.png" alt="Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy: An Assessment Framework" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> Our study of the Adecco Group, a Fortune Global 500 company and leader in HR solutions based in Switzerland, offers a prime example of the strategic decision-making process in corporate philanthropy. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> In 2017, the Adecco Group established a global foundation, and leaders took a proactive approach to create synergies between the company&#39;s social and business strategies.</p><p> The Adecco Group&#39;s foundation has a clear purpose closely aligned to the corporation&#39;s mission: <em>Making the future work for everyone.</em> Initially, many of its social programs were transferred to the foundation. Over time, however, the Adecco Group&#39;s philanthropic portfolio grew and became very diverse, requiring a detailed assessment across the cognitive, structural, and contextual fit of the programs. In 2021, the management team carefully selected the foundation&#39;s priority projects based on the questions provided in our assessment framework. Accordingly, other initiatives were given back to the company (and integrated into the respective departments), and some were entrusted to better-suited nonprofits to take forward. This strategic move allowed the Adecco Group&#39;s foundation, now called the Innovation Foundation, to redefine its corporate philanthropy strategy and develop a decision-making framework rooted in three principles:</p><p> <strong>Industry expertise (cognitive fit).</strong> The foundation now focuses exclusively on the domains of employment, skills, and the future of work — the business&#39;s areas of expertise. In addition to receiving financial support, it benefits from the knowledge, data, experience, and ecosystem of the Adecco Group. This mutually beneficial relationship ensures that the valuable outcomes and insights generated by the foundation are shared back to the company.</p><p> <strong>Tailored social innovation lab methodology (structural fit).</strong> The foundation developed a proprietary operating model that blends data-driven analysis, design thinking, and innovation to deliver user-centric solutions following an acceleratorlike process. Thus, projects that did not align with that format — such as grant giving and fundraising — were given back to the business. These projects were run in the marketing or sustainability department, contingent on their structural fit and their knowledge, personnel, and network needs.</p><p> <strong>Local knowledge (contextual fit).</strong> Because the Innovation Foundation focuses on projects with long-term impact — those that address the source of a problem rather than the symptoms — local partners and end users are involved at every stage. One example is the foundation&#39;s Women Back to Work project in Spain, where the continuous involvement of local organizations and beneficiaries ensures that the program incorporates a deep understanding of the real problems of women reintegrating into the workforce in that context. Once a project has been developed and tested in-house, it is spun off for a local partner organization to scale and create maximum impact.</p><p></p><p> In the year following the foundation&#39;s restructuring, the team pursued three projects aimed at boosting employability for women, young adults, and older employees. These initiatives have provided the company with insights and real-time data on the unmet needs and potential solutions for underserved populations in the labor market.</p><p></p><p> The Adecco Group&#39;s case demonstrates the power of a well-crafted corporate philanthropy strategy that is grounded in guiding principles. As corporate giving becomes increasingly important in today&#39;s business landscape, it&#39;s critical for companies to focus their efforts on maximizing their social impact as well as their competitive position. A well-executed philanthropic strategy not only benefits society but also strengthens an organization&#39;s market position by providing access to new knowledge and expanding the organization&#39;s network.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Making Investments in AI: Samsung&#39;s Hina Dixit</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startup Financing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Venture Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Hina Dixit’s interest in supporting people and solving problems has its roots in her family’s call office business, where she helped people place telephone calls when she was growing up in India. Later, after earning her bachelor’s degree in computer science, she was quickly recruited into the tech space, where her problem-solving and customer service [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Hina Dixit&#39;s interest in supporting people and solving problems has its roots in her family&#39;s call office business, where she helped people place telephone calls when she was growing up in India. Later, after earning her bachelor&#39;s degree in computer science, she was quickly recruited into the tech space, where her problem-solving and customer service skills have served her well as both a software engineer and tech investor. From a developer role at Symantec, to project leader at Apple, to an AI investor role at Samsung Next, Hina continues to leverage her communication and connection skills in seeking out and supporting innovations in artificial intelligence, as well as robotics, Web3, and other tech sectors.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Hina shares the criteria she considers when making investments in new entrepreneurial ventures. She also highlights the focus areas that are of most interest right now, explains why she enjoys mentoring other technologists, and shares her views on what the future of AI looks like. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-s7-e4-Dixit-Instagram-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="希娜迪克西特"></p><h4> Hina Dixit, Samsung Next</h4><p> Hina Dixit is a venture capitalist and software engineering leader with more than 13 years of experience. She is currently an investor at Samsung Next, focusing on the AI, augmented reality, Web3, and infrastructure sectors.</p><p> Before she joined Samsung Next, Dixit led a team at Apple that worked on a variety of projects, including security, iCloud, artificial intelligence, developer tools, and data integrity, for eight years. She is an investor in several companies, including Stability AI, MosaicML, and Space and Time.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-dixit"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one technology leader approach AI investments? Find out her five criteria on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I&#39;m Hina Dixit from Samsung Next, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> On today&#39;s episode, we have Hina Dixit, an investor at Samsung Next. Hina, thanks for joining us.欢迎。</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Thank you so much. It&#39;s a pleasure being here with you.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Most of our listeners are likely familiar with Samsung — giant South Korean multinational, lots of consumer electronics — but people may be less familiar with Samsung Next, so let&#39;s start there. Can you describe what Samsung Next is and what your role is?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. Samsung Next is the private equity or venture capital arm of Samsung. We tend to be stage-agnostic, but at the same time, we have six focus areas where we invest. AI is one of them. We also invest in fintech, blockchain, and infrastructure, and media tech as well, along with health tech.</p><p> Along with these six focus areas, we tend to make more and more learned investments about the ever-changing, dynamic world as well. So if you or anyone has a cool idea, please feel free to reach out.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I should&#39;ve prepared more and had a few pitches ready so that we could&#39;ve put you on the spot here while we were recording and get you on record there. So, what, exactly, do you do, though?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I currently lead the AI investment segment area. If there is any deal which is associated with AI, I tend to lead that deal and also work on the investment strategy for Samsung Next.</p><p> When you head out to these startup demos, to these pitches and expos, you will see thousands of startups. Now, how do you ensure that you are focused on the right areas which matter to Samsung? It should also propel innovation further; [instead of simply] furthering the innovation, it should also be usable. So that&#39;s why having a paradigm will help you make those sound decisions, where you can actually prioritize certain areas ahead of time compared to other investors, and understand which of the current technologies will be booming, say, a few years from now. And accordingly, you tend to segment and understand that, OK, these are my top-priority areas.</p><p> At the same time, I&#39;m very, very passionate about mentoring entrepreneurs, mentoring fellow people in tech. I come from a tech background, so I can always understand the hiccups people face when they are moving from individual-contributor roles or management roles in these big techs and moving forward to a startup entrepreneurial journey. I love connecting with them and helping them out.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s really wonderful, Hina. So I want to talk about both things you said, both the mentoring, but also I want to go back to how you pick an investment. I mean, obviously, where you&#39;re sitting, you are looking at thousands of opportunities probably, right? And so you mentioned there are some guiding principles in terms of how you prioritize where to focus and what fits strategically with Samsung, but tell us more about how you pick an investment once you&#39;ve already gone through that filter, that “OK, it&#39;s the right thing for the company. We want to do it.” Now you&#39;re actually evaluating an AI company. Tell us how you pick. What are the factors you consider?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I tend to focus on very important factors for me personally. Every investor out there has a very different way of investing. Some people are very intuition-driven, and I have seen such investors make really great decisions. Some people are very theory-driven, and some people tend to take it as they go.</p><p> I am a mix of all of them. I tend to make these sound, learned decisions where I&#39;m very comfortable and I know the space very well. One thing that is always very important for me is the team. Is there a right product-team fit here? Are these individuals capable of building these great products that they&#39;re promising? I think that is an essential parameter for me.</p><p> And then, moving on to the problem itself: Is this pain point really [going to be] valid in few years? The pain point has to be there. The next thing is the technical innovation. Now, that is important, because that serves as a mode for you, or mode for these entrepreneurs, right? Otherwise, any big tech [company] can just go in and create what they have created. We want to have a solid mode around these products that they&#39;re building and some sort of novelty.</p><p> And then, moving from technical innovation and the mode, obviously there has to be a decent market size. You might be building an awesome product, but at the same time, the market sizing [might be] very small. It becomes really hard to scale that kind of product. Even if it&#39;s not monetizable, it should be solving a very solid pain point, plus the impact of that particular solution has to be global. And that&#39;s another factor for me, where I tend to make my own decision that, OK, this is something which is going to change everything that we do today.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Tell us more about the team, because technology is one aspect, but how do you suss out both the capability of the team itself and then how well the team works with each other? I mean, a lot of startups have team issues, right?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How do you look into that?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Sure. I think it&#39;s a very deep question, and I think it comes from my days at Apple. Apple has a very startuplike culture in some of their organization, and here I&#39;m speaking about the culture because there were so many learnings from them. When I started, there was a very open culture where people would come on the weekends to support and mentor you and help you. They wouldn&#39;t even ask for any kind of credit. They would help you move forward, and at the same time, they will not just stop there. They will empower you. They will connect you with the right connections across the organization.</p><p> I kind of felt that it is very difficult for people to be that selfless and just focus on making the product great, but I think that&#39;s what the spirit of Apple is, and I tend to see a similar spirit in founders if I know that they&#39;re very, very product-driven, or they&#39;re very, very goal-driven in terms of [their] team. Then I tend to get that sense, OK, these guys will support each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You&#39;ve got some extensive experience in this area. You mentioned Apple a couple of times. Tell us a bit about how you got to where you are now from where you started.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I come from a very humble family background. So while my dad would work very hard, I would help them out with our family business, which was a small public call office, or a PCO, where people [went] and used to make telephone calls. So I used to sit there, and I used to make those calls for people, handle the customers, and enable them to make these phone calls, and that was a very good learning point for me because I learned how to talk to people.</p><p> From being a very introverted child, I became very public-facing, right then and there. … Like, OK, these are my customers. They are top priority. I need to serve them, help them, and that&#39;s where I think some of these qualities that I [espouse] or these passions that I have — that I love helping people, I love solving conflicts — probably arise.</p><p> I did my high school from Kanpur [City in India], which is Mercy Memorial School, and after my high school, I went to a women&#39;s college because my parents were a bit conservative yet. I was the first girl in the entire family of my dad&#39;s side who went outside of the city in order to get an education.</p><p> It was immensely fun. It was a very safe and secure environment. Obviously, it was very competitive — we women tend to be very competitive — and at the same time, I made great friends there, and I learned so much from my classmates at that time. We used to trade on these various ideas, and we used to create these JavaServer Pages-based applications, web applications for online quizzing, test banks, writing educational articles.</p><p> I remember, even buying a Starbucks coffee at that time used to be a very, very far-off thought because it was so expensive for me, and I used to work multiple jobs at the same time. And then I was placed at Symantec six months ahead of graduation. So that took some pressure off of me, and Symantec was a great starting point for me. I was in their data loss prevention team. I learned significantly from all the mentors there. I still share great relationships with all of them. And then Apple happened, and the rest is history.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing that&#39;s fascinating: As you were saying that, I was thinking about how you tied your exposure to customer service through that very early call office job.</p><p> At the same time, much of what we&#39;re talking about with artificial intelligence ... it strikes me that the kind of job that would be suspect or likely to be replaced, and I have to wonder, how does the next Hina Dixit come along without that experience if we don&#39;t have those introductory customer service-oriented jobs to learn those skills?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, I get the question. This has been a grave thought, and a lot of people are coming forward and discussing it. But I think AI is not going to replace people. AI is going to empower people, and that&#39;s the thought process I come from. Just because phones became relevant, it didn&#39;t mean that [the mail was] not relevant anymore. We still order Amazon packages, and we still get our bills in the mail and whatnot, and that&#39;s how I think we will be able to push mankind. That&#39;s how we keep on pushing each and every … mile toward the ultimate goal of humankind&#39;s future, right?</p><p> Moving to the ultimate goal there, I think nobody should blindly trust that, OK, AI is going to replace their job, but they should be able to learn about AI. And that&#39;s one of the things where I&#39;ve been focusing on: finding these really cool technologies which can help people ramp up on AI.</p><p> Like, why do people need to write any single piece of code in order to use AI? Why can&#39;t this be as simple as looking at an Excel sheet? Why can&#39;t this be as accessible [as a] user interface, which is very easily programmable by just any business user out there? So finding that kind of interface between AI and the current users, that is a very critical piece where I think investors should focus on, because the ultimate goal here is to normalize the usage of AI and make that publicly available and at the same time accessible as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I think this is a very, very good point. That vision you painted is actually quite appealing. It used to be, the human element of AI was around making the technology better, faster, cheaper, or [writing] the next-generation algorithm, which of course, we still do, but that&#39;s going to be more and more in the R&amp;D and innovation zone. I think, as you&#39;re saying, the usage of AI will go from humans&#39; role as programmers and writers of code to more working at that interface, of having these building blocks and connecting those building blocks that AI provides to solve existing problems, but more importantly, as you&#39;re saying, thinking about “What else can we do with this? How do you innovate, now that you have all this at your fingertips?”</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah. I kind of think the same way, because anybody ... you know, think of Excel. Anybody can just jump into Excel and make applications out of it. I know there are a bunch of cool apps coming around productivity right now which are backed by AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Share with us a bit your view on the coolest areas of technology that you are looking at right now. What piques your interest these days with everything that&#39;s going on with cyber and Web3 and quantum computing and everything else? Can you share specific investments or areas you&#39;re looking at?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Sure. We are focused a lot on infrastructure pieces of Web3, and at the same time, we are also focusing a lot on the AI aspect of Web3. So can we use these decentralized systems in order to make compute efficient? That&#39;s a question that we are trying to … answer right now. We are also trying to dive in deeper on the health-tech side, where we want to digitize the normal health paradigm, and we want to empower users out there and give them more proper feedback, maybe in their diet, maybe connect them to the right agents or doctors or nurses.</p><p> The focus is on empowering the humans. That&#39;s where I think we are trying to focus. And then obviously there is meta-tech aspect, which is the metaverse. We&#39;re trying to understand, how easy would it be to convert any image into a 3D asset and place it in the metaverse? And then, how do we make this metaverse accessible, just like the real world?</p><p> It seems surreal, but at the same time, there&#39;s so much hard work and research for each and every aspect of this. We are also focusing a lot on the fintech perspective and trying to empower these LatAm [Latin American] countries, finding a way they can build very sustainable and safe credit-scoring systems in Asia, for example, [and in] India, East Asia, and LatAm countries. So building a lot of infrastructure around fintech in LatAm countries and Asian countries is another thing that we are focusing on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah, I think that infrastructure&#39;s particularly interesting because that is an area where artificial intelligence can make a difference, when you can get some scale through an infrastructure. It&#39;s one of those situations that it seems like it opens up new possibilities when the economics change — when things that were no longer possible become possible. Are there other things that you&#39;re working on that are next in the portfolio? What are we going to see from Samsung Next next?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> We are moving into robotics as well. I did invest in one of the companies, called Integral AI, and they are trying to use these large AI models or foundation models [to train] their robots. But at the same time, robotics is another area where we want to focus on the consumer robotics aspect, so any cool startups out there building these cool consumer robots, please feel free to reach out to us, and we&#39;ll be happy to jump in and help out.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Hina, we&#39;ve got a segment where we ask you a series of questions, and these are supposed to be rapid-fire. Just give us the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You&#39;ve got a past career that&#39;s over a decade of being involved in these technologies. What&#39;s your proudest AI moment? What&#39;s the thing in this portfolio that you&#39;re proudest of that involves AI?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I think I&#39;ll have to say Stability AI because before that, there were a lot of research communities around, but at the same time, there was no way that somebody could go and commercialize those research works. And I really value Emad Mostaque&#39;s work there — that he recognized this problem and he got these research facilities together in order to start commercializing and build more solid consumer end products.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We&#39;ve been very positive about artificial intelligence today, but is there anything that worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I think one thing that worries me is that we have seen a recent burst of these large language model-based apps, and that does include ChatGPT. I love their work, but at the same time, there are other pain points. And then, obviously, there are copyright issues that we need to solve, there are security issues. So those are some of the other areas we are trying to focus on, and trying to understand how those pain points can be resolved.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> It&#39;s basically gardening in my house. I just find that very therapeutic, and, secondly, I love playing with my dog, Jimmy. He&#39;s absolutely adorable.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What was the first career you wanted? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I have always wanted to be a startup founder. I was 8 when I manifested that … I would be a founder, I would be building great products, and I would be helping out other people. So ever since I was 8, [I&#39;ve been] chasing that dream.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What are you hoping we can gain from this?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> My biggest wish for AI would be enabling common sense in some way, because these large AI models, they do have some AI capabilities when they can be put together in conjunction. We know from the recent <a href="https://doi.org/10.48550/arXiv.2204.02311">PaLM research paper that Google published</a> that, OK, there is a way of having these multiple multimodels work together in order to create more sensible information and reliable information out there for users to believe in, and they basically used it to train their robots.</p><p> So that&#39;s one application, but a lot can come forward from that particular research work that Google published, including chain-of-thought prompting as well. How do you use these several models to work together in order to perform better in real-world and unstructured environments? So that would be very cool to see.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK, yeah, that seems so exciting to me, too, because we originally had the generative AI adversarial models, where, yes, we learned how to play chess really quickly, or we learned through a game, but the universe that has expanded from the idea that we can have bazillions of these models working kind of with and against each other — that seems very natural to, well, the way that we as humans or current biology works. It seems like there&#39;s a lot of potential for that.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, Hina, thanks for taking the time to talk with us today. I think that there&#39;s lots — actually, particularly from your background — that is inspiring to people. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah, thank you so much.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Thank you so much for having me. It was a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Shervin and I speak with Elizabeth Anne Watkins, research scientist at Intel Labs. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Cashing Out Excellence</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert D. Austin, Robert H. Hayes, and Richard L. Nolan. <p>Robert D. Austin is a professor of information systems at Ivey Business School and an affiliated faculty member at Harvard Medical School. Robert H. Hayes is the Philip Caldwell Professor of Business Administration, Emeritus, at Harvard Business School. Richard L. Nolan is a professor emeritus at Harvard Business School and the University of Washington.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Long-Term Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stakeholder Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com When Southwest Airlines suffered a post-holiday meltdown in December 2022, the trigger was a bout of adverse weather. But the storm hit Southwest harder than it did most airlines. The company’s outdated computer systems collapsed, and years of underinvestment in technology, particularly staff scheduling systems, led to more than 16,700 flight cancellations over [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Austin-1290x860-1.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> When Southwest Airlines suffered a post-holiday meltdown in December 2022, the trigger was a bout of adverse weather. But the storm hit Southwest harder than it did most airlines. The company&#39;s outdated computer systems collapsed, and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/02/18/can-southwest-fix-its-tech-problems-aviation-experts-arent-confident.html">years of underinvestment in technology, particularly staff scheduling systems</a> , led to more than <a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/01/06/1147445280/southwest-airlines-cancellations-costs-825-million">16,700</a> flight cancellations over the holiday travel period. Amid the chaos, an executive&#39;s memo demanding proof of illness for the use of any sick days indicated a lack of trust in employees. The scenario contrasts starkly with what the company was once celebrated for: the pioneering development of an alternative short-haul airline concept, an unrivaled commitment to employees, and a reliance on front-line decision-making, all of which had led to industry-best operational excellence and customer service and the highest profits in the history of the industry.</p><p> Southwest&#39;s troubles are typical of a kind of leadership malaise we see in organizations that struggle to cope with disruptive events — such as the pandemic and its aftermath, which threw airports and airlines into operational turmoil and caused supply chains to collapse. To manage short-term appearances, these leaders and their predecessors had “cashed out” capabilities and allegiances they previously relied on to help them deal with unanticipated changes. It&#39;s a practice that has become too common and too accepted: Values, qualities, and relationships that have been honed over many years and served as the foundation for earlier successes are exchanged for near-term monetary rewards — typically in the form of cost reductions and stock price improvements that prove to be ephemeral.</p><p></p><p> We call this style of short-term leadership <em>performance hacking</em> . Performance hacking is the practice of giving the appearance of effective leadership by delivering on particular metrics, without delivering real performance. It involves companies and their leaders polishing financials through the calculated manipulation of investment planning and cost-cutting measures instead of prioritizing the creation of long-term value. The usual way to hack performance is by focusing on delivering short-term financial results to maintain steady trends that are unrealistic for major companies operating in complex environments but that leaders have come to believe — perhaps rightly — that the markets expect.</p><p> What performance hacking doesn&#39;t deliver is updated facilities and computer systems; investments in product/process research and development; the ability to master or exploit new technologies; or a loyal, capable workforce.</p><p> Performance-hacking leaders might, for example, reduce investments in key organizational capabilities, allow them to atrophy, or even outsource them — in effect, cashing out the less visible products or services that seem less urgent or less cost-effective at the moment, based on the convenient but often mistaken assumption that they can always be reacquired if needed in the future. They might skimp on employee pay and growth, which over time results in their more capable (and more expensive) employees leaving and less capable (and less costly) ones taking their place. Any subsequent external disruption then reveals how much an organization&#39;s know-how, resilience, and commitment have been sacrificed by managers&#39; attempts to improve appearances.</p><p> Organizational leaders can&#39;t hack performance by themselves, of course; boards and investors must acquiesce. They often drive this behavior by rewarding executives for meeting short-term financial targets. Indeed, major investors with no stake in the company&#39;s long-term success and viability often instigate and drive the process, motivated by the potential for short-term earnings.</p><p> Performance hacking is not a new phenomenon. In 1980, one of us (Bob Hayes), with coauthor Bill Abernathy, identified elements of what we now call performance hacking and cautioned against the tendency of corporate leaders to focus too much attention on controls and surface appearances at the expense of the “drive trains” of their companies. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> In many ways, the problem is worse today than when they first wrote about it. Adding to the urgency of this concern is that, as we will soon see, such practices appear to be spreading.</p><p> What is it that distinguishes performance hacking from strategically sound business decisions that may cut losses on bad bets or shift resources to invest in the long-term health of the business? The distinction is not always obvious to outside observers and often becomes clear only in retrospect. That said, examining recent examples where companies have clearly suffered as a result of performance hacking helps us identify warning signs that leaders are engaging in the practice.</p><h3> How Performance Hacking Harms Great Companies</h3><p> In the aftermath of last December&#39;s debacle at Southwest, the pilot union published a letter that contrasted two quotations. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The first was from Southwest&#39;s cofounder, Herb Kelleher, who is often credited with the uniquely successful business model and culture for which the company was known in its early days: “You put your employees first. If you truly treat your employees that way, they will treat your customers well, your customers will come back, and that&#39;s what makes your shareholders happy. So there&#39;s no constituency at war with any other constituency. Ultimately, it&#39;s shareholder value that you&#39;re producing.” <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Gary Kelly, the company&#39;s CEO from 2004 until 2022, was quoted espousing a different philosophy: “Arguably, our shareholders have suffered for a long time when it comes to getting a return and our employees have been very well taken care of.” The pilot union blamed that shift to a greater focus on shareholders for more frequent and severe operational problems.</p><p> The stated intention to take better care of shareholders is a sign that performance-hacking leadership is ascendant, but ironically the evidence suggests that these practices are actually bad for shareholders in the long run. Cashing out vital competitive capabilities might briefly benefit a subset of shareholders, but it destroys long-term value and prospects for other shareholders and stakeholders.</p><p> The corporate leader who arguably made performance hacking a mainstream management practice was Jack Welch, General Electric&#39;s CEO from 1981-2001. By the 1990s, he had perfected ways to manage earnings per share (EPS), using tweaks and tricks to yield a smoothly rising trend that was implausibly regular, always just beating projections. <cite>The Economist</cite> called it “taking money from one pocket and putting it in another.” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> After Welch&#39;s retirement, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ge-sec/ge-to-pay-50-mln-to-settle-sec-fraud-charges-idUSTRE5734G420090804">GE paid $50 million to settle allegations of accounting fraud</a> by the US Securities and Exchange Commission. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p></p><p> Today, many commentators trace GE&#39;s subsequent collapse — its stock plunge in the late 2010s, its removal from the Dow Jones Industrial Average after years of being named America&#39;s Most Admired Company by <cite>Fortune</cite> magazine, and its breakup into three smaller companies — to Welch&#39;s focus on appearance management and what insiders called the “success theater” of his successor, Jeffrey Immelt. But these practices had wider implications: GE&#39;s ability to deliver such unwaveringly positive results, however unrealistic this was for a complex conglomerate, led investors to expect it from other companies as well. Today&#39;s CEOs still feel this pressure.</p><p> Boeing&#39;s safety troubles with the 737 Max airliner, two of which suffered fatal crashes that killed a total of 346 people, can also be traced back to a deliberate decision to supposedly prioritize shareholder interests.</p><p> From 1998 to 2000, Boeing&#39;s leaders, many of them former Welch-era GE executives who came on board through Boeing&#39;s 1997 merger with McDonnell Douglas, became fixated on polishing a financial ratio called return on net assets (RONA). To accomplish this, they expanded outsourcing, slashed R&amp;D investment, and laid off almost 20% of the workforce. The new philosophy at Boeing called for avoiding what leadership described as “moonshot” investments — a focus on developing the kinds of major new platforms and technologies that had made Boeing the unrivaled industry leader over the previous 80 years but involved placing big bets with uncertain outcomes. The decision in 2010 to squeeze more value out of the 50-year-old 737 airframe instead of building an all-new airplane was a direct result of this new way of thinking. But putting new, larger engines on the old airframe and positioning them differently than in the past required additional software to compensate for changes in handling, which contributed significantly to the Max&#39;s crashes.</p><p> Despite the misalignment we see in hindsight between performance hacking and protecting shareholder value, there are indicators that performance-hacking habits are spreading. Lately, large tech companies seem to be falling over one another to lay off employees, something they have historically not done at the current scale. Meta has cut 25% of its workforce over the last year. Salesforce has cut 10%; Amazon, 8%; and Alphabet, 6%, among others. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> These are highly profitable companies with favorable opportunities for further growth in their futures.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Performance Hacking Toolkit</h4><p> <strong>Business leaders, managers, and board members should be aware of these common methods of performance hacking so that they are prepared to intervene and prevent long-term damage.</strong></p><p> <strong>Liquidating non-balance-sheet assets.</strong> Know-how that resides with employees is an invisible asset in the sense that it is valuable to the company but doesn&#39;t appear on the balance sheet. Similarly, a fully depreciated physical asset (a piece of equipment — say, a mainframe computer system) has value even though it no longer appears on the balance sheet. What is tempting to leaders about such assets is that they can be used to generate earnings without any corresponding balance sheet entry. As if by magic, laying off workers, outsourcing, or selling a fully depreciated asset can seem to produce earnings from thin air, without any telltale reduction of on-the-books assets. Wise leaders never forget, though, that unaccounted value is still real value for the company that, once gone, is difficult to get back.</p><p> <strong>Time-shifting cash flows and accounting assumption shifts.</strong> Boeing&#39;s technique of shifting cash flows to manage appearances was described by an anonymous employee in a 2019 <cite>Seattle Times</cite> article: “If the defense side falls short of expectations by hundreds of millions of dollars in a quarter, the call goes out from its Chicago headquarters to the Puget Sound-based Boeing Commercial Airplanes unit with a specific target to close the cash-flow gap: Negotiate with airlines and suppliers to pull money forward, say from January into December, and delay outgoing payments the opposite way. … [It happens] &#39;pretty much every quarter,&#39; said the insider. … &#39;Everyone realizes it&#39;s not a good decision long term.&#39;” <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a> The financial terms of these deals are private, kept between buyer and sellers, so outsiders are none the wiser when they happen.</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p> Changing accounting assumptions can also change financial results, without shifting cash flows. In 2016, GE&#39;s power division was having trouble hitting its earnings targets. It approached customers with new, sweet deals on upgraded equipment and coupled them with extensions on the terms of service contracts, some of them out to 2050 or beyond. The new sales provided an opportunity to shift the assumptions that determined how much of future earnings could be counted in the current year and thus boosted 2016 earnings. The company is still saddled with these long-term bad deals.</p><p> <strong>Drawing down buffers.</strong> One of the most common ways for managers to hack financial performance/cash out invisible assets is to remove buffers — of inventory, production capacity, duplicate groups, or facilities — from their organizations by asserting that they are unnecessary “slack.” Or they outsource those buffers to other organizations, often in distant locations. Those buffers, however, often serve an important purpose: to protect an organization from immediate disruption should it experience widespread disturbances in its competitive environment.</p><p> <strong>Stock buybacks.</strong> When a company uses its cash to purchase its own shares, earnings per share improve even if earnings don&#39;t actually change. If companies have extra cash but can&#39;t find a high-return way to invest it, buybacks can be a legitimate alternative to dividends as a means of returning value to a company&#39;s owners. But as Robert C. Pozen has explained, from 2014 to 2016, the amount spent on buybacks and dividends consistently exceeded the aggregated net income of companies in the S&amp;P 500, which suggests that companies buy back stock instead of using cash to invest in available high-return projects. <a id="reflinkii" class="reflink" href="#refii">ii</a> Pozen also noted that many borrow money to buy back shares. If this tactic resulted in long-term improvements in stock price, that might be a justification, but the evidence suggests that companies that spend more on buybacks actually underperform compared with other companies in the long run in terms of returns. Ironically, over the long term, the markets seem to interpret stock buybacks as a form of financial engineering that signals fundamental weakness. <a id="reflinkiii" class="reflink" href="#refiii">iii</a></p><p> <strong>Kicking risk down the road.</strong> In his 2011 annual letter to shareholders, Boeing&#39;s then-CEO, James McNerney, explained the company&#39;s decision to try to wring more profits out of the 737 rather than develop a new airplane: “With development costs and risks far below an all-new airplane … we reduce our business risk substantially for the next decade.” <a id="reflinkiv" class="reflink" href="#refiv">iv</a> In retrospect, however, this claim seems absurd. The decision led to the need for a new software system that was implicated in the later crashes, so it did not reduce business risk but rather deferred and magnified it. What it probably also did was reduce short-term risk to the stock price. If we read closely, we see that this is what McNerney meant by “business risk” — not the risk of a plane not performing, but the risk of short-term stock devaluation due to the uncertainties inherent in a major investment in a new plane.</p></div></article></aside></div><p></p><p> These layoffs could be warranted, as company announcements have explained, by a need to adjust the workforce to evolving competitive challenges, or to correct for having possibly overhired during the pandemic.</p><p> But they could also be gestures aimed at short-term investors. Amid Alphabet&#39;s layoffs, a major hedge fund investor publicly demanded more, seeking a 20% workforce reduction and the shutdown of some advanced R&amp;D projects. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Layoffs have indeed been accompanied by such project cancellations, including some from the company&#39;s famed X division specifically commissioned to work on moonshots. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> In recent years, tech companies have also embraced another favorite tool of performance hackers, with rising enthusiasm: the stock buyback. It&#39;s a great tool for generating misleading EPS trends; for example, by operating on the denominator of the EPS ratio, stock buybacks enable the interesting trick of increasing EPS while earnings decrease. Such tactics have historically been employed by companies in mature markets whose leaders may be tempted to mislead because they have trouble generating growth. Tech companies, in contrast, appear to have ample growth prospects. Nevertheless, in 2021 and 2022, Alphabet, Apple, Meta, and Microsoft collectively announced almost $300 billion in stock buybacks.</p><h3> Performance Hacking Indicators</h3><p> Discouraging performance hacking begins with recognizing when it&#39;s happening. Signs are often apparent to insiders: As early as 2016, Southwest pilots called for Kelly&#39;s resignation after a computer system failure, citing his “misguided emphasis on cost controls” and spending cash on stock buybacks rather than investing in technology improvements. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Because any individual decision can have a legitimate business rationale, detecting the practice is less about spotting a smoking gun than watching for an accumulation of decisions and actions that add up to a likelihood that leaders have succumbed to temptation. Here are some of the indicators.</p><p> <strong>Sudden, unexplained improvements in performance ratios or key results, or trends that seem unrealistically smooth.</strong> The EPS trends at GE were too smooth. The improvements in RONA at Boeing from 1998 to 2000 happened too fast to signal real operational change in such a large company. We know now what was really being signaled: excellence being cashed out. Sound management requires investing in creating new capabilities — <em>building</em> excellence — which often worsens performance metrics, at least initially. Numbers and trends that only improve should therefore elicit suspicion, not celebration.</p><p> <strong>A degraded customer experience.</strong> Whether it&#39;s flight cancellations, reduced customer support, or lower-quality products, an overt shift toward maximizing shareholder value in the short term might involve “borrowing” that value from customers.</p><p> <strong>Sudden enthusiasm for outsourcing, or a shift to more transactional people management that downplays the importance of employee expertise.</strong> Scholars Gary Pisano and Willy Shih have convincingly argued that outsourcing production based on narrow financial criteria usually also outsources expertise critical to a company&#39;s capacity to innovate. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Leaders engaged in performance hacking often see employee contributions to a company&#39;s products and services as just another fungible resource, interchangeable with what can be easily obtained externally. They dismiss the notion that employees are reservoirs of unique competitive know-how who have been and can be invested in and developed over many years.</p><p> <strong>Decreased leadership emphasis on the operational characteristics of the business, and fewer leaders with industry expertise.</strong> While Southwest founder Kelleher was known for his hands-on involvement in operations, Kelly rose to a leadership position on the strength of his contributions as CFO. During his tenure, he appointed an executive with an accounting background as COO. Late-1990s leaders at Boeing urged employees to avoid getting “overly focused on the box” (the airplane) and to instead conceive of the company as a generic return-making business. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> This type of perspective also tends to play down the importance of leaders&#39; industry-specific expertise. Past research on short-termism has implicated the hiring of leaders with little domain expertise. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> Under Kelly, Southwest board members&#39; airline expertise decreased noticeably. Industry expertise on the board at Boeing also declined after its late-&#39;90s transformation.</p><p> <strong>Abandoning “moonshot” development projects.</strong> Developing new competitive capabilities sometimes requires a company to place big bets. Risk inevitably accompanies such investments. And yet it is hard to imagine a company thriving in the long run if it doesn&#39;t do some of this — and, in industries where competition is very innovation-based, quite a lot of it. Past research on companies afflicted by short-termism points to tendencies to decentralize R&amp;D and shift emphasis from “research” (which has a less obvious return) to “development” (which has a clearer sense of return). <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> When Boeing, the dominant commercial airline innovator at the time, turned away from moonshots, it started down a path to the loss of its industry-leading capabilities (and the 737 Max crashes). Some analysts now doubt whether the company, lately competing with the likes of SpaceX and Blue Origin for aerospace talent, has the ability to create an entirely new plane. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a> Might tech companies be edging toward a similar path?</p><h3> The Role of the Board</h3><p> As noted earlier, boards can be complicit in performance hacking. But at companies with strong, independent governance, boards of directors have a number of tools that allow them to encourage performance that benefits companies and their investors in the long term. They might rework executive compensation packages to incentivize long-term thinking rather than rewarding short-term share price performance. They might also use frameworks, such as the Balanced Scorecard, that offer a wider set of measures intended to better account for the creation and cashing out of capabilities.</p><p> However, we don&#39;t think this problem will be solved purely through the redesign of incentives. It&#39;s preferable that boards stay alert to the possibility of performance hacking; orchestrate ongoing conversations about the relationship between building and maintaining vital competitive capabilities and the movement of short-term financial metrics; and insert themselves into some key decisions that are routinely left to senior management (like decisions about stock buybacks, which, unlike decisions about dividends, are not legally required to involve the board).</p><p> Of course, it&#39;s critical — but hardly a given — that board members themselves take a long-term view, just as some shareholders themselves do. An example of this came in 2021 at ExxonMobil, when the hedge fund Engine No. 1 led a campaign to install, over management objections, three board members who explicitly embraced a philosophy of focusing on long-term value creation. <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> Working with management researchers and consultants at PwC, Engine No. 1 developed a “total value framework” that used multiple data sources to evaluate long-term risks and opportunities, with a goal of making it clear to everyone how actions that might look good in the short term could drag down value over time.</p><p> The harm caused by performance hacking goes beyond companies and their employees, customers, and investors, however. If the only way for the market to correct for performance hacking is to let companies implode, the public at large can bear significant collateral damage. Measures for mitigating and containing risks might include establishing regulations like the Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002, ensuring accurate financial reporting, and requiring stress testing as in industries like banking.</p><p></p><p> Silicon Valley Bank&#39;s recent implosion came just a few years after it successfully lobbied against regulatory safeguards and ultimately resulted in the government having to bail out its depositors (a significant chunk of the American startup ecosystem) to avoid wider economic damage. Leaders intent on lobbying against regulations that seem onerous should keep in mind that those regulations might play an important function in curtailing performance-hacking practices.</p><h3> The Risks of Inaction</h3><p> Performance hacking is so destructive because it often involves irreversible decisions. Organizations made vulnerable through excessive outsourcing may find that they don&#39;t have the ability to bring production back in-house when they need it, for example. Companies can also progressively weaken themselves through a long series of less visible decisions. Each of them might conform to what are considered generally accepted management principles and appear to have little effect on current operations but could be weakening certain expertise or capabilities, discarding a potentially useful technology, or undermining employees&#39; commitment to the company&#39;s success. When those capabilities, technologies, and commitments are needed in times of stress, managers may find that they&#39;ve gone down a one-way street: It&#39;s much harder to replace such invisible assets than it is to cash them out.</p><p> The pandemic, the war in Europe, the attendant disruption of global supply chains, and rising inflation and interest rates vividly illustrate the kinds of sudden stresses that business leaders have had to deal with these past three years. They also provide stark examples of the bad things that can happen to those who become addicted to polishing financial metrics at the expense of their organizations&#39; long-term resilience.</p><p></p><p> If a business leader like Welch could make performance hacking seem desirable, it should be possible for another high-profile leader (or a group of them) to make investing for the long term seem fashionable again. A strong CEO, backed by a highly respected board, can express their intention to invest for the long haul, even if the usual financial metrics might temporarily suffer. If that approach dissuades short-term investors, so much the better. This, of course, will not be easy. It will probably attract activist short-term shareholders and short sellers. But if an influential group of business leaders can prevail and demonstrate the success of this approach, other companies might follow.</p><p> One thing is certain: If this problem is left unfixed and continues to fester and hobble companies, we should resign ourselves to watching a parade of executives retire with lavish compensation packages, leaving behind hollowed-out businesses that are incapable of providing the products, services, and desirable jobs that are desperately needed.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Ask Sanyin: How Can I Field a Winning Team Without All-Star Players?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-field-a-winning-team-without-all-star-players/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-field-a-winning-team-without-all-star-players/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:57 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang is a CEO coach and leads the Fuqua/Coach K Center on Leadership &amp; Ethics (COLE) at Duke University. Need advice? Send an <a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">email to Sanyin</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[My organization urgently needs to execute on a new strategic initiative, but I’m not confident that my current staff members have the skills and drive required. How can I field a championship team when I don’t have any all-star players? It’s easy for managers to succumb to a scarcity mentality and believe that their people [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MITSMR-AskSanyin-featured-column3-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question"> My organization urgently needs to execute on a new strategic initiative, but I&#39;m not confident that my current staff members have the skills and drive required. How can I field a championship team when I don&#39;t have any all-star players?</p><p> It&#39;s easy for managers to succumb to a scarcity mentality and believe that their people aren&#39;t good enough — but it&#39;s important not to nurture this mindset. When we look closely at this problem, we often discover that the existing team&#39;s potential hasn&#39;t yet been fully realized. Building a championship team is almost always a matter of activating untapped potential, not trading for better players.</p><p> Years ago, my friend Sue Gordon, the former principal deputy director of national intelligence, told me that although you don&#39;t always get to choose your team, your team is enough and you must help them believe that it is so. How do we make the most of who we have rather than fixating on their deficiencies?</p><p></p><p> The first step is to get much better at diagnosing the underlying problems when our teams aren&#39;t functioning effectively. I start by assessing where there are skill set issues and where there are behavioral problems. The former is straightforward to address (if not overnight) by investing in training or providing opportunities to gain specific experience.</p><p> Behavioral issues — by which I mean contextually variable behaviors that can diminish an individual&#39;s effectiveness or team dynamic — are a bit tougher. For example, an opinionated, creative person may contribute meaningful new ideas in meetings but dismiss suggestions made by others, demotivating teammates and dampening collaboration. Helping that team member see the effect of their behavior and develop new communication habits can improve team effectiveness.</p><p></p><p> Second, make sure everyone knows why and how they matter. Your team can&#39;t achieve greatness if its members don&#39;t believe that their presence on the team is important, their contributions are appreciated, and their ideas will be considered. Identify each individual&#39;s differentiating contributions (what I call <em>superpowers</em> ), and explicitly share those insights with them. Superpowers are the inimitable strengths we all have — but because they&#39;re so innate to us, we often don&#39;t see them and need others to point them out to us. An important part of good leadership is identifying the superpowers of everyone on your team and encouraging them to share what they see as each other&#39;s unique talents. This has the added benefit of giving you more data about how your team can sync up.</p><p> Finally, focus on the people, not the titles. Notice the capabilities, gifts, and inclinations of the people on your team, and be open-minded about how they might work together in new configurations. The market and operating context are changing rapidly, demanding a fluidity beyond the functional constructs that exist now. Someone&#39;s current title does not comprehensively define their capabilities, and it can often constrain them to a more limited role. Having a more expansive view of each person can help you harness the team&#39;s fullest potential.</p><p> When we&#39;re open to the potential of our existing team members and create opportunities for the team to surface, see, and recognize new strengths, we can come to see that the championship team is the one we already have.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-field-a-winning-team-without-all-star-players/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Building a Winning Workplace Culture: Strategies for Leaders</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/building-a-winning-workplace-culture-strategies-for-leaders/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/building-a-winning-workplace-culture-strategies-for-leaders/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 31 May 2023 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull, Charlie Sull, and Ally MacDonald. <p>Donald Sull is a global expert on strategy and execution in turbulent markets. Don is a cofounder of CultureX and a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management, where he directs the Strategic Agility Project and the Culture 500. Charlie Sull is a cofounder of CultureX. He has advised the senior executive teams of dozens of multinational organizations on cultural management, strategy development, and strategy execution. Ally MacDonald is a former senior editor of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Evaluation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Satisfaction]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Join us for a 60-minute webinar on building a winning organizational culture in today’s workforce. New research from Donald Sull and Charlie Sull has found that toxic workplace culture has been the driving force behind the Great Resignation. Meaning: Understanding and measuring culture has never been more critical for leaders. The authors’ multiyear research series [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Join us for a 60-minute webinar on building a winning organizational culture in today&#39;s workforce. New research from Donald Sull and Charlie Sull has found that toxic workplace culture has been the driving force behind the Great Resignation. Meaning: Understanding and measuring culture has never been more critical for leaders.</p><p> The authors&#39; multiyear research series demonstrates that measuring culture can also help managers identify opportunities for improvement, recognize areas where the organization is excelling, and build a culture that attracts top talent and boosts retention.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> What workplace culture is and why it matters for employee engagement, organizational performance, and external reputation.</li><li> How to measure culture to unlock actionable insights on how to improve it.</li><li> Key research findings with deep-dive examples from leading companies.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/building-a-winning-workplace-culture-strategies-for-leaders/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Three Lessons From Chatting About Strategy With ChatGPT</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 30 May 2023 11:00:20 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Stadler and Martin Reeves. <p>Christian Stadler ( <a href="https://twitter.com/enduringsuccess">@enduringsuccess</a> ) is a professor of strategic management at Warwick Business School at Warwick University and coauthor of several books, including <cite>Open Strategy: Mastering Disruption From Outside the C-Suite</cite> (MIT Press, 2021). Martin Reeves ( <a href="https://twitter.com/MartinKReeves">@martinkreeves</a> ) is a senior managing director and partner at Boston Consulting Group and chair of the BCG Henderson Institute. He is coauthor of several books on strategy, including <cite>The Imagination Machine</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2021) and <cite>Your Strategy Needs a Strategy</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2015).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Geoffrey Hinton, a pioneer of deep learning, quit Google recently, he made it clear that he is worried about the risks of artificial intelligence. He is not alone. Following the launch of ChatGPT-4, thousands of artificial intelligence experts signed a letter calling for a pause in the development of more-powerful AI systems. On the [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Stadler-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> When Geoffrey Hinton, a pioneer of deep learning, quit Google recently, he made it clear that he is worried about the<a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/05/02/1072528/geoffrey-hinton-google-why-scared-ai/">risks of artificial intelligence</a> . He is not alone. Following the launch of ChatGPT-4, thousands of artificial intelligence experts <a href="https://futureoflife.org/open-letter/pause-giant-ai-experiments/">signed a letter</a> calling for a pause in the development of more-powerful AI systems.</p><p> On the other hand, excitement about the opportunities arising from large language models (LLMs) and their speed of adoption is unprecedented. Microsoft was quick to integrate the new technology into its Bing search engine, and the company&#39;s founder, Bill Gates, stated that <a href="https://fortune.com/2023/02/10/bill-gates-chatgpt-jobs-chatbot-microsoft-google-bard-bing/">ChatGPT will “change our world”</a> without necessarily putting jobs at risk.</p><p></p><p> While speculating about the future of AI is irresistible, the more practical question is how we can use it right now. Conversations about this are taking place in classrooms, newsrooms, and workplaces around the world.</p><p> As business strategists, we wanted to see what generative AI could add to our work. We explored this question through a series of experiments on different aspects of the strategy creation process. In each of the experiments, we put a realistic question of strategy to ChatGPT, followed by a lengthy back-and-forth to refine the initial responses. The intention was to understand how the tool can support ideation, experimentation, evaluation, and the building of stories — and where it falls down.</p><p> Three lessons emerged from these experiments.</p><h3> 1. Expect interesting input, not infallible recommendations.</h3><p> In one of our experiments, we asked ChatGPT to suggest some disruptive business ideas for a large European transport provider. The chatbot suggested a personalized planning app, a ride-sharing service, hyperloop transportation, and a smart-luggage delivery service. Coincidently, the first three matched ideas from a recent workshop with a transport provider in another European country. The tool was also able to provide business models and cost estimates for these business ideas.</p><p> On the one hand, this is impressive. At the same time, it highlights that the tool seems unlikely to come up with ideas humans can&#39;t, although it gets results faster and with less effort. Several other experiments confirmed this.</p><p></p><p> In another experiment, it also became obvious that humans are better at translating ideas into actions. For example, when we asked ChatGPT to come up with an idea for a new streaming service, the list of suggestions included a service focused on education. When we asked what it would take to realize such an idea, it proposed a partnership with either a university or an established consulting firm. While that made sense, ChatGPT&#39;s suggestions for how to win over such partners were not sufficiently concrete and realistic. The current iteration of the tool, which is based on training set data in the public domain, isn&#39;t able to capture the nuances of each corporate reality.</p><p> Still, LLMs can be helpful in the strategy process for a few key reasons:</p><p> <strong>They are fast and easy to use.</strong> You can avoid all the logistical effort required to get the right people in the room at the same time.</p><p> <strong>The tendency toward conventional thinking can be mitigated by asking the right follow-up questions.</strong> For example, when we asked for an innovative new concept for a bakery, ChatGPT initially suggested just offering savory products. We then asked for more creative ideas and got a space-themed bakery, with robotic assistants and bakers, zero-gravity dining, and 3D food printers, which was too expensive to realize. In a third attempt, the ideas became more interesting — for example, a bakery that uses artificial intelligence to analyze data about customer preferences and food trends to create and design unique flavor combinations for baked goods. From there, we were able to probe about steps to get started on realizing this idea.</p><p> <strong>It&#39;s easy to generate many ideas.</strong> The most interesting ideas were, however, mixed with implausible, impractical, and untested ones. Only by sifting through them in a discerning manner can you get a better understanding of what might actually work.</p><p></p><h3> 2. Experienced strategists will benefit most from ChatGPT.</h3><p> ChatGPT acts like a worldly wise and persuasive friend who is prone to overconfidence to the point of sometimes asserting fictions as facts, either because errors were present in the initial training set or through some emergent process that experts are still trying to understand.</p><p> While it would be foolish to rely unquestioningly on the advice of such a fallible friend, its suggestions could in fact be very useful in several ways, provided we fully apply our powers of judgment. We could tap into this friend&#39;s extensive knowledge to characterize competitive environments. We could generate ideas upon which to base a strategy. We could simulate how different strategies might perform in different scenarios and highlight the risks and contingencies.</p><p> But extracting insights and avoiding being misled require that we exercise our powers of discretion by asking the right questions in the right sequence, judging the consistency of recommendations with our own knowledge and experience, checking the accuracy of assertions and assumptions, and judging the feasibility of the resulting strategies. In other words, we stand to benefit by applying the very same powers of discrimination that experienced strategists must regularly employ but novices are likely to lack.</p><p> The main attraction of ChatGPT in strategy work is probably its ability to write well, complementing the blind spot of many strategists. Strategists often underestimate the importance of <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/02/your-strategy-needs-a-story"><em>how</em> ideas are communicated</a> , wrongly assuming that <em>what</em> they propose is what matters most. With only 28% of managers being able to correctly name three of<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/no-one-knows-your-strategy-not-even-your-top-leaders/">their organization&#39;s strategic priorities</a> , this points to a misperception of what it takes to create impact in practice. But ChatGPT definitely has something to offer managers for whom creating engaging stories is both time-consuming and challenging. If you provide or refine the proposition, the tool can add style.</p><h3> 3. Strategists use different data and use it differently.</h3><p> ChatGPT processes billions of data points to construct output. This might create the false impression that it exceeds the cognitive capacity of humans. It&#39;s easy to overlook the limitations imposed by the lack of transparency into the exact nature of this data set and its gaps. Strategists often rely heavily on proprietary information, since effective strategies must uniquely reflect the position and capabilities of each company. We know for sure that current tools don&#39;t have access to such inside knowledge. It is, therefore, not surprising that ChatGPT&#39;s answers are somewhat generic — more or less according to the textbook, but lacking spice.</p><p> Most importantly, effective strategy often relies not on what is generally the case or generally effective but rather on <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/07/the-power-of-anomaly">anomalies</a> to create new and unique approaches. Relatedly, as Giovanni Gavetti from the Tuck School of Business and Jan Rivkin from Harvard Business School explain, <a href="https://hbr.org/2005/04/how-strategists-really-think-tapping-the-power-of-analogy">strategists often rely on analogies</a> . This means they are able to make decisions with very little or no data that applies to a specific situation. ChatGPT doesn&#39;t seem to have the capability to infer useful counterfactuals using analogical reasoning.</p><p></p><p> Even if LLMs were to become capable of asserting all of the facts, as opposed to linguistic correlations in a constrained data set, they would still face a limitation. Experienced strategists know to be skeptical of “facts.” What is true most of the time may not be true in a specific case. What was true in the past may not be true in the future. What happens to be true may not be inevitably and persistently so. And even if a statement is robustly true in these senses, there are always alternative ways of framing problems and solutions.</p><p> Strategists know that this <a href="https://framers-book.com/">framing step</a> is often the most subtle and important one in developing a strategy. Strategy is, in one important sense, as much about useful fictions as established facts. By aiming to shape circumstances to bring about a new goal, strategies create <em>new</em> facts. In this regard, strategists are in the business of distinguishing useful fictions from misleading or infeasible ones — again a skill that only experienced strategists are likely to possess.</p><p></p><p> An interesting question is whether this pattern of utilities and limitations is likely to remain stable as the technology progresses. To assess this, we conducted the same experiments with ChatGPT-3 and ChatGPT-4. The substance of the answers remained quite similar. To some extent, the limitations were even more pronounced in the more advanced version of the tool, whose answers were, on average, twice as long. The newer version seemed to be a little more careful, like a slightly older friend who has been caught out before and wants to hedge their opinions. This manifests itself with a taste for pro and con lists and less pronounced judgment — a feature we look for in a strategist.</p><p></p><p> The bottom line: ChatGPT and similar tools are more likely to be useful in particular steps of strategizing (like idea generation and storytelling) and to experienced strategists rather than naive beginners. Such tools are, therefore, no substitute for the cultivation of strategic minds. And just as airline pilots must avoid over-relying on an autopilot, would-be strategists must avoid impeding the development of their own discriminating powers.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Incumbent&#39;s Deep Tech Strategy Playbook</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-incumbents-deep-tech-strategy-playbook/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-incumbents-deep-tech-strategy-playbook/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 25 May 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[François Candelon, Vinit Patel, Max Männig, and John Paschkewitz. <p>François Candelon is a senior partner and managing director at Boston Consulting Group (BCG) and the global director of the BCG Henderson Institute, where his research focuses on the impact of technologies on business and society. Vinit Patel is a project leader at BCG and a former ambassador at the BCG Henderson Institute. Max Männig is a project leader at BCG and an ambassador at the BCG Henderson Institute. John Paschkewitz is a partner and associate director at BCG and a core member of BCG X&#39;s Deep Tech team.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Deep tech — the innovative use of emerging physical technologies enabled by digital technologies to solve large-scale problems — has the potential to create transformative growth opportunities for businesses. By tapping into these advanced technologies, leaders are better positioned to address large-scale problems and reshape entire markets. Consider the impact of synthetic biology; by 2030, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Calendon-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Deep tech — the innovative use of emerging physical technologies enabled by digital technologies to solve large-scale problems — has the potential to create transformative growth opportunities for businesses. By tapping into these advanced technologies, leaders are better positioned to <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2022/ceos-need-to-know-about-deep-technologies">address large-scale problems</a> and reshape entire markets. Consider the impact of <a href="https://fortune.com/2021/08/06/synthetic-biology-plant-based-meats-bioengineering-environmental-impact/">synthetic biology</a> ; by 2030, this rapidly advancing field could affect industries that account for as much as 30% of global gross domestic product.</p><p> In the pharmaceutical industry, the disruptive power of deep tech is evident in the development of mRNA vaccines. Through decades of government-funded research, academic ingenuity, and backing from venture capitalists and accelerators, mRNA technology gradually emerged as a groundbreaking innovation. However, it took medical urgency and the strategic involvement and operational support of established companies such as Pfizer to usher in an mRNA-based vaccine at scale and enable its commercial success. Partnering in 2018 with BioNTech, a spinoff of Mainz University that had been founded a decade earlier, Pfizer played a critical role in developing the record-profit-making COVID-19 vaccine.</p><p></p><p> But the disproportionate coverage of deep-tech successes masks many failed attempts in commercializing them. For every Pfizer, there are cautionary tales from other well-known health care giants. Clearly, the tectonic changes caused by deep tech compel executives across industries to come to grips with the underlying technologies right away and identify the right engagement models. Striking the right balance is critical: Investing in deep tech too early can be counterproductive, but delaying too long or choosing the wrong approach can be detrimental.</p><p> To help executives at incumbent companies identify and execute their deep-tech engagement strategies, we&#39;ve developed a three-step deep-tech playbook. This framework puts a system behind the questions we hear from companies looking to engage with the deep-tech ecosystem. It is based on our experience in deep-tech client work, discussions with executives, observations of industry dynamics, and academic research.</p><p></p><p> Steps 1 and 2 introduce the two key dimensions influencing the choice of deep-tech strategy — urgency to act on challenges, and the innovation momentum of the surrounding ecosystem — along with guidance for executives on assessing those factors in their business context. For steps 1 and 2, we will use the European steel industry as an illustration. This industry serves as a useful example, given the need to address its large carbon footprint and the adoption challenges that its advanced technologies need to overcome, such as high capital intensity.</p><p> In Step 3, executives must identify the company&#39;s unique positioning and strategy based on the assessment of the aforementioned factors. This assessment is not a monolith for a company; it differs for each challenge its specific industry faces. Because our framework can be applied in various industries, the resulting deep-tech strategies will differ by company and industry. We, therefore, illustrate four archetypal engagement strategies with examples from other industries.</p><h3> Step 1: Incumbents must assess the urgency to act on challenges.</h3><p> Given the combination of challenges related to climate change and geopolitics, businesses are waking up to the urgent need, or are being compelled, to develop and deploy deep-tech-based solutions to tackle them and generate novel opportunities. The graphic below provides an overview of the assessment of the following factors through the example of the European steel industry.</p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Deep-Tech Canvas</h4><p class="caption"> Executives can assess the urgency to act on challenges and the innovation momentum of the surrounding ecosystem through a set of concrete questions. The evaluation of the urgency is driven by the challenges an industry or company faces and how limited current solutions are in addressing them. Evaluating innovation momentum starts with identifying new technologies or solutions and assessing technology and stakeholder factors. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023-0525_Candelon-Fig-01-1.png" alt="The Deep-Tech Canvas" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Executives must start by <em>identifying the long-term emerging or aggravating challenges</em> that their business or industry is facing. The European steel industry faces massive pressures to manufacture steel much more sustainably, given that the sector produces approximately 5% of <a href="https://joint-research-centre.ec.europa.eu/jrc-news-and-updates/eu-climate-targets-how-decarbonise-steel-industry-2022-06-15_en">European CO <sub>2</sub> emissions</a> . Current plans to decarbonize the sector are insufficient because they fall short of the industry&#39;s ambitious 2030 target of <a href="https://www.eurofer.eu/issues/climate-and-energy/maps-of-key-low-carbon-steel-projects">reducing emissions by 55%</a> compared with 1990 levels.</p><p> To determine how urgent the need for deep-tech solutions is, executives must next <em>gauge the impact of the challenges</em> . Applied to the European steel industry example, the impact could come from the effect of carbon pricing or the <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2021/eu-carbon-border-tax">EU&#39;s carbon border tax</a> on the industry&#39;s competitiveness. Analysts predict that European <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/_division_assets/images/special-editorial/carbon-pricing-in-various-forms-is-likely-to-spread-in-the-move-to-net-zero/esg_research_-_carbon_pricing_in_various_forms_is_likely_to_spread_in_the_move_to_net_zero.pdf">carbon prices</a> will reach more than 120 euros ($130) per ton of CO <sub>2</sub> by 2030; if their predictions bear out, the cost of supplying European steel through existing technology would increase sharply once free carbon allowances are phased out completely.</p><p> Then, companies must <em>evaluate how constraining existing approaches are</em> in adapting to these challenges. The dependence on carbon-intensive thermochemical reactions for steel production, an inability to fully capture carbon emissions, and limitations in steel scrap availability and quality are exemplary constraints of the current steel manufacturing paradigm that further increase the urgency.</p><p> Lastly, companies must <em>assess the opportunity in <a href="https://fortune.com/2022/08/05/artificial-intelligence-problem-solving-deep-tech/">reimagining the existing paradigm</a></em> . For this, they can apply methodologies such as backcasting — that is, starting with the desired outcome and charting a path backward to the present scenario. In our steelmaking example, an alternative sustainable high-efficiency conversion pathway could be an opportunity to tap into the market for sustainable building materials in Europe. Many leading automotive and consumer durables companies have announced ambitious targets for <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/scope-emissions-climate-greenhouse-business/">Scope 3 emissions</a> reductions, which means major demand disruptions for noncompliant steel producers. Switching to green steel would have limited cost risks while curbing Scope 3 emissions for these steel buyers.</p><p> When we look at the level of urgency for deep-tech innovation in the European steel industry example, it can be considered high.</p><h3> Step 2: Incumbents must evaluate the surrounding innovation momentum.</h3><p> Deep tech is different from digital innovation in several key ways. If digital innovation is about generating economies of scale, network effects, and speed to market to seize first-mover advantage, deep tech&#39;s characteristics are the convergence of multiple rapidly maturing technologies, a need to navigate both tech and market fit, larger investment needs, and longer development times. Deep tech focuses on challenges that span multiple scientific disciplines and sectors, requiring a collaborative approach. For deep tech to thrive, its development relies on innovation ecosystems that encompass everything from R&amp;D to commercialization. Established corporations may find it difficult to work with these ecosystems, which operate with rapidly evolving technical risk and market fit.</p><p></p><p> To evaluate the innovation momentum, incumbents must first <em>identify the solutions or scientific advances</em> that are or will become available to address the business challenges they have identified. Potential solutions within the steel example could be an electrochemical or a green hydrogen-based thermochemical pathway for conversion. We focus our subsequent analysis on the green hydrogen-based reduction technology, as it is relatively advanced in terms of technology readiness and is one of the <a href="https://www.spglobal.com/commodityinsights/en/market-insights/blogs/metals/062222-dri-steel-decarbonization-direct-reduced-iron">most CO <sub>2</sub> -efficient pathways for steel production</a> , with the potential to reduce emissions by more than 75%. Innovation momentum should be evaluated from two angles: technology factors and stakeholder factors. The graphic below provides an overview of the assessment of the following factors through the example of the European steel industry.</p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> European Steel Illustration of the Deep-Tech Canvas</h4><p class="caption"> Determining high, medium, or low urgency and innovation momentum depends on the factors that are being assessed. Although these binary outcomes serve well as an illustration, real-world results may span a spectrum. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023-0525_Candelon-Fig-02-1.png" alt="European Steel Illustration of the Deep-Tech Canvas" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p> On the technological side, incumbents should assess the level of granularity of the technology, dependencies on other innovations, and the technology&#39;s interfaces. To assess granularity, incumbents can evaluate the technology&#39;s physical size, divisibility, capital expenditure (CapEx), complexity, and nonfinancial risk. In the European steel example, increasing the production capacity for direct reduced iron or building greenfield thermoelectric plants will require significant CapEx.</p><p> Unlocking new technologies&#39; full potential will require incumbents to consider <a href="https://hbr.org/2016/11/right-tech-wrong-time">dependencies on the success of other innovations</a> , such as the convergence of technological streams, to make these solutions possible. Beyond determining how to use hydrogen efficiently in steelmaking, the success of the technology will depend on developments and innovation in green hydrogen production and infrastructure.</p><p> Finally, incumbents should evaluate the technological innovation momentum by considering the extent to which the technology&#39;s interfaces are sufficiently stable and mature to facilitate easier co-innovation. The hydrogen-based steelmaking pathway, for instance, demands stable, consistent, and large quantities of low carbon-intensity hydrogen supplies.</p><p> On the stakeholder side, incumbents need to <em>evaluate the ecosystem inertia, stakeholder contributions, and need for stakeholders to adapt</em> . For instance, the European steel industry profits from economies of scale and faces significant inertia to change, due to extensive capital lock-in and low profitability.</p><p> Incumbents further need to <em>ask how stakeholders are aligned to progress on the identified deep-tech solutions</em> . Consider that the risk of being outcompeted by cheaper and less-sustainable imported steel can likely be mitigated only by a steadfast policy commitment to carbon border adjustments and further regulatory support. But such regulation could also create pockets of geographies where momentum is higher. Government funding, such as from the European Innovation Council or the European Investment Fund, plays a role in supporting deep-tech efforts and contributes to de-risking private investment. <a href="https://dealroom.co/uploaded/2023/01/Dealroom-deep-tech-report-2023-europe.pdf">Investors&#39; commitments</a> allowed European deep-tech startups to raise $17.7 billion in 2022.</p><p> Finally, incumbents aiming to leverage the deep-tech ecosystem to support their project&#39;s scale-up can count on facilitators like accelerators, incubators or consortiums, and stakeholders from academia; in fact, many European deep-tech successes have their roots in universities, such as the aforementioned Mainz University spinoff BioNTech and Climeworks from ETH Zurich.</p><p> Lastly, incumbents must ask themselves <em>to what extent stakeholders across the value chain must adapt</em> . Within the European steel industry, energy suppliers need to provide a steady, ample, and cost-effective supply of green hydrogen, requiring a significant expansion of electrolyzer capacity and renewable energy generation. End consumers, however, would not need to adapt much since the quality and form factor of steel from a new process would not be significantly different.</p><p> Despite the good number of incumbent projects and government interest, the momentum for hydrogen-based steel production technology is mellowed significantly by existing technology ecosystem inertia and the need for a transformative but capital-intensive new technology ecosystem. Hence, the innovation momentum in this illustration can be gauged as medium to low.</p><h3> Step 3: Incumbents must define and execute their engagement strategies to manage deep tech.</h3><p> The factors of urgency and innovation momentum offer executives valuable signals regarding the potential impact of deep tech on their various industries. Assessing these aspects is a crucial prerequisite for any business before determining and implementing a strategy to engage with a deep-tech ecosystem. The urgency to change, and the momentum for innovation, will keep evolving as new challenges arise, research breakthroughs occur, investment flows in, and startups emerge and churn. For each emergent challenge your business faces, your approach toward deep tech will differ.</p><p> By assessing the two key factors of urgency and innovation momentum, executives can choose from four archetypal strategies for engaging with deep tech. Below, we provide guidance to incumbent companies across industries looking to execute any one of these four distinct strategies.</p><ul><li> <em>Facilitators</em> focus on maturing deep technologies through significant investments while leveraging ecosystems to share costs and diversify.</li><li> <em>Orchestrators</em> reinvent their core business to embrace deep tech, brace for a large and rapid deep-tech transition, and stay ahead of the curve — thereby orchestrating change toward a new reality.</li><li> <em>Scouts</em> proactively use deep tech to expand into new markets, increasing their value pool and positioning themselves as leaders in their own playground.</li><li> <em>Observers</em> acknowledge deep-tech opportunities and scan the horizon for potential disruptions.</li></ul><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Deep-Tech Archetype Matrix</h4><p class="caption"> Mapping an organization&#39;s market urgency to its innovation momentum determines its deep-tech archetype: Facilitators mature technologies with investments and shared costs, orchestrators embrace deep tech to transform their core business, scouts leverage deep tech for market expansion, and observers keep a watchful eye on potential deep-tech disruptions. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023-0525_Candelon-Fig-03.png" alt="The Deep-Tech Archetype Matrix" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h4> Deep-Tech Facilitators</h4><p> Companies can consider the facilitator engagement strategy when innovation momentum is low but addressing external challenges is critical. Facilitators build and nurture deep-tech building blocks and ecosystems, identifying and developing promising new technologies for real-world impact.</p><p> To evolve technologies at each stage of development, companies must identify constraints, align with complementary organizations to scale promising solutions, and promote systemic adoption. This results in consortia-style collaborations for joint research and/or pilot projects aimed at scaling a specific technology. Companies must focus on solutions for the key issues relevant to their core while leveraging collaborators to drive additional innovations.</p><p> Consider the Swedish steelmaker SSAB, which is developing a path-breaking sustainable hydrogen-based steelmaking process. In Sweden, SSAB leads the <a href="https://www.ssab.com/en/fossil-free-steel/insights/hybrit-a-new-revolutionary-steelmaking-technology">Hybrit project</a> in tandem with Vattenfall, a multinational power company, and LKAB, a state-owned mining company. Together, the consortium members hope to use the new process to produce <a href="https://climate.ec.europa.eu/system/files/2022-07/if_pf_2022_hybrit_en.pdf">1.2 million tons of steel annually</a> by 2027. Because the availability of electrolyzers is a key constraint, SSAB is using its years of operational experience to improve the effectiveness of hydrogen in steel production while relying on partners for complementary techno-commercial capabilities — like Vattenfall for renewable energy and hydrogen production, and LKAB for raw materials.</p><p> Success with technology-oriented solutions that affect large-scale systemic (or systems-of-systems) value-chain transformations would require business model innovation too — either upstream or downstream. For instance, Volvo has committed to purchasing the premium <a href="https://www.media.volvocars.com/global/en-gb/media/pressreleases/301755/volvo-cars-is-first-car-maker-to-join-steelzero-initiative-in-support-of-fossil-free-steel-ambitions">green steel</a> supplied by the SSAB pilot partly because it aspires to introduce a range of carbon-free electromobility solutions. Further, government support, like the EU Innovation Fund&#39;s investment of up to 20 billion euros in <a href="https://single-market-economy.ec.europa.eu/industry/strategy/hydrogen/funding-guide/eu-programmes-funds/innovation-fund_en">low-carbon technologies</a> , often plays a critical role in enabling systemic change for deep-tech facilitators.</p><h4> Deep-Tech Orchestrators</h4><p> Incumbents can become orchestrators when it&#39;s imperative that they react to urgent external challenges and the deep-tech innovation ecosystem offers an effective response. This strategy demands defining an ambitious vision, reinventing the company to tackle it, and committing resources to generate significant revenue and profits from deep-tech solutions.</p><p> Hyundai Motor Group (HMG) exemplifies this approach in the way it addresses the environmentally unfriendly problem of urban mobility, where there&#39;s a business opportunity in rethinking and overhauling the automobile industry. HMG hopes to become a complete mobility solutions provider, offering novel mobility services and developing the infrastructure solutions to deliver them. For some orchestrators, much of the innovation will take place outside the company&#39;s boundaries; <a href="https://www.cradleinc.com/">HMG has invested</a> in several mobility upstarts, such as Metawave for autonomous driving systems and SolidEnergy Systems for fuel cell technology.</p><p> Incumbents must invite and incentivize many stakeholders — such as competitors, suppliers, and distributors — to become complementors in their ecosystems, build deep-tech platforms, or form industry working groups. HMG unveiled open-source platforms for each of its automotive brands, gathering myriad kinds of data from connected automobiles and ultimately making it accessible to its partners via APIs while it develops proprietary solutions.</p><p> Orchestrators can ease bottlenecks and relieve key frictions in their deep-tech ecosystems by using their assets and capabilities, such as giving startups access to manufacturing facilities — ultimately with the goal of scaling solutions or coordinating go-to-market tactics to create a faster path to commercial deployment. HMG, for instance, is testing Boston Dynamic&#39;s Spot robots in a facility in South Korea, where AI developed by HMG&#39;s Robotics Lab has been integrated with the robots to ensure their suitability for factory work.</p><h4> Deep-Tech Scouts</h4><p> Incumbent companies that have high innovation momentum on new technologies but experience lower urgency with external challenges can opt for a deep-tech scout strategy. This approach begins with replacing existing technologies with available deep-tech solutions. Through this approach, companies benefit from their ecosystem&#39;s innovation dynamism and the ease of plug-in solutions, which in turn reduces risks and catalyzes higher returns.</p><p> A plug-in solution is best handled through a corporate venture or incubator arrangement that externalizes technical risk as equity risk. Since true plug-ins are rare, incumbents should have the capability to understand the potential trade-offs and effects of using a new material or component. Incumbents should also have strong investment and technology scouting teams that can identify compelling, technically sound deep-tech plays at attractive valuations.</p><p> When developing a scout strategy, incumbents can use a mix of research and/or development partnerships, corporate venture capital investments, and strategic deals, such as M&amp;As, to foster collaboration. It&#39;s smart for companies and promising startups to strike exclusive deep-tech partnerships for specific applications so the benefits accrue only to them. Companies can either codevelop or license technology exclusively. For instance, Unilever and Geno jointly invested $120 million in 2022 to develop a <a href="https://www.genomatica.com/news-content/genomatica-and-unilever-launch-venture/">plant-based substitute for palm oil</a> that only the former will use in its cleaning and personal care products.</p><h4> Deep-Tech Observers</h4><p> If an incumbent company and its ecosystem are hesitant to adopt new technologies, they can consider remaining deep-tech observers — even though that&#39;s increasingly a risky strategy. Proactive leadership teams will constantly scan the business environment to find opportunities for deploying emerging technologies. This type of monitoring and vigilance will help them anticipate deep-tech-based disruptions and avoid the perils of inaction. By leveraging their ecosystems — academia, incubators, accelerators, vendors, and suppliers — along with their technology teams, they can minimize the cost of developing their own deep-tech “observatory.”</p><p> For example, the fast-food industry has been surrounded by deep-tech innovations in recent times, but none of them have had a significant business impact on quickly delivering affordable, consistent, quality food through a network of retail outlets. Consider that plant-based meats — driven mainly by upstream food and agriculture businesses — or robots specifically designed to automate cooking tasks such as deep-frying can easily be integrated into restaurants. These robots are, for instance, developed by companies such as Miso Robotics and used by companies like <a href="https://misorobotics.com/newsroom/white-castle-expands-partnership-with-miso-robotics-to-install-flippy-2-in-100-new-locations/">White Castle</a> .</p><p> Deep tech may not (yet) usefully address key imperatives for growth, sustainability, or margin that businesses in some sectors may find worth the investment. Sectors like construction, water, and waste management have had limited venture investment, given regulatory barriers, value-chain lock-in, and limited technological choices. Yet even here, changes in regulations or technologies can catalyze investment. For example, urban mining — reclaiming and reusing electronic waste materials — is an emerging area of investment, given strong incentives for electrification and the domestic supply of battery materials. For fast followers, valuations and access to emerging capabilities may be significantly less attractive.</p><p></p><p></p><p> By nature, the deep-tech strategy archetypes described in this article are not one-size-fits-all solutions. Some companies may want to proactively address challenging problems with deep tech, whereas others may focus on other priorities in the short term. Also, few companies will have the bountiful resources needed to execute ambitious deep-tech plays.</p><p> Nonetheless, many incumbents are in a unique position in the innovation ecosystem due to the tangible and intangible <a href="https://fortune.com/2023/02/03/synthetic-biology-startups-incumbents-cooperation/">assets and capabilities</a> they&#39;ve developed over time, such as expertise in scaling manufacturing processes or market access. Unsurprisingly, many have started to recognize this advantage and are exploring the potential to use new technologies to create commercially valuable offerings.</p><p> Deciding which play to make is crucial and will depend on a company&#39;s aspirations, its urgency to change, and the vitality of the innovation ecosystem it is engaging with. By embracing the right deep-tech strategy, incumbent companies can avoid being disrupted, help foster ongoing success, and drive the development of innovative, world-changing solutions.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-incumbents-deep-tech-strategy-playbook/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>