<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 23 日星期三 11:00:36 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>问三阴：为什么我们不能开好会？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang 是一位 CEO 教练，领导杜克大学 Fuqua/Coach K 领导力与道德中心 (COLE)。需要建议吗？发送<a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">电子邮件至三阴</a>。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Building]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[As a senior leader in my company, I find meetings are crucial for keeping tabs on what’s going on and making decisions. But we seem to accomplish little, people are frequently unprepared, and they gripe about the time cost. How can I shift people’s attitudes and run more effective meetings? We’ve all been there: We [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AskSanyin-featured-column4-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question">作为公司的高级领导者，我发现会议对于密切关注正在发生的事情并做出决策至关重要。但我们似乎收效甚微，人们常常毫无准备，并且抱怨时间成本。如何改变人们的态度并召开更有效的会议？</p><p>我们都经历过这样的情况：我们坐下来进行了一个小时的谈话，但不知何故，会议结束时的清晰度不如开始时的清晰。我们走出去，感叹时间的浪费和缺乏进展。</p><p>在生产力超高、待办事项无穷无尽、个人疲惫不堪的时代，您的团队可能将会议视为返回工作的障碍，而不是有目的的事情。将这种态度转变为热情参与意味着重新思考您想要通过会议实现的目标。随着远程工作的广泛普及，与我们的团队实时互动的机会变得更加稀有和更有价值。我们如何利用这段时间加深关系？如果我们将建立信任作为每种类型会议的主要目标怎么办？</p><p></p><p>决策会议通常是关于对一系列行动的承诺。在这里，您还可以讨论决策对员工的情感影响以及沟通变革的最佳方式。对这些问题的深入讨论可以洞察他人的价值观和方法。</p><p>头脑风暴和解决问题的会议从对建立信任的明确考虑中受益匪浅。每个人都需要轻松地分享自己的想法，同时抵制评判的冲动。在这里，你想鼓励脆弱性，因为当我们说“我不知道”时，我们承认我们在更大的团队中的局限性和相互依赖性。</p><p>还有机会将有时例行的信息共享会议转变为更丰富的联系场所。尝试设定这样的期望：这些都是更多地了解彼此的挑战和策略的机会，并鼓励提出问题。这些会议还提供了庆祝胜利或邀请其他部门帮助的机会。利用时间帮助团队成员建立彼此之间的联系（矩阵），而不是以您为中心作为首选问题解决者的轴辐式联系。</p><p></p><p>最后，尝试在定期团队会议中安排集体反思的时间。 elf Beauty 的首席执行官塔朗·阿明 (Tarang Amin) 截至 2023 年 5 月已连续 17 个季度实现增长，每次执行领导团队会议开始时都会有时间公开分享和反思。 “高管们可以在这里谈论他们个人生活中发生的事情……他们的心态、重要举措是什么、他们在组织中听到了什么，”他说。</p><p>请记住，阻碍进展的通常不是缺乏行动项目。阻碍我们前进的往往是对意图的误解、理解上的偏差以及变革带来的情感损失。解决这些问题的是能够实现良好沟通的信任关系。因此，不要深入讨论您计划的下一次会议的<em>内容</em>，而是从<em>谁</em>以及他们之间的关系开始。您的团队可能会重新发现彼此交流所带来的活力和快乐，甚至开始期待会议。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>使用联合机器学习克服 AI 规模劣势</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yannick Bammens and Paul Hünermund. <p>Yannick Bammens 是比利时哈瑟尔特大学战略与创新教授，他是该大学 AI4Business 计划的共同领导者。 Paul Hünermund 是丹麦哥本哈根商学院战略与创新助理教授，他在那里共同组织了一年一度的因果数据科学会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Big Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Deep pockets, access to talent, and massive investments in computing infrastructure only partly explain why most major breakthroughs in artificial intelligence have come from a select group of Big Tech companies that includes Amazon, Google, and Microsoft. What sets the tech giants apart from the many other businesses seeking to gain an [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Bammens_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">宗晶晶/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>雄厚的财力、人才资源以及对计算基础设施的大规模投资只能部分解释为什么人工智能领域的大多数重大突破都来自包括亚马逊、谷歌和微软在内的一批精选的大型科技公司。科技巨头与许多其他寻求从人工智能中获得优势的企业的不同之处在于，他们作为平台运营商收集了大量数据。仅亚马逊每月就在其平台上处理数百万笔交易。所有这些大数据都是丰富的战略资源，可用于开发和训练复杂的机器学习算法，但对于大多数企业来说，这是一种遥不可及的资源。</p><p>访问大数据可以实现更复杂、性能更好的人工智能和机器学习模型，但许多公司必须使用更小的数据集。对于规模较小的公司以及医疗保健、制造或建筑等传统行业的公司来说，缺乏数据是冒险进入人工智能的最大障碍。由于自我强化的数据网络效应，大数据和小数据组织之间的数字鸿沟是一个严重的问题，更多的数据会带来更好的人工智能工具，这有助于吸引更多生成更多数据的客户，等等。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这为大公司提供了强大的人工智能竞争优势，而中小型组织则难以跟上。</p><p></p><p>多个小规模公司将数据集中在一个共同控制的中央存储库中的想法已经存在一段时间了，但对数据隐私的担忧可能会阻止此类举措。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>联合机器学习 (FedML) 是一项最新的创新技术，它通过使用去中心化数据的隐私保护协作人工智能来克服这一问题。 FedML 可能会成为游戏规则的改变者，解决拥有和没有大数据的公司之间的数字鸿沟，并使经济的更大一部分能够从人工智能中获益。这项技术不仅在理论上听起来很有前途，而且已经在工业中成功实施，我们将在下面详细介绍。但首先，我们将解释它是如何工作的。</p><h3>小数据和联合机器学习</h3><p>FedML 是一种允许小数据组织训练和使用复杂的机器学习模型的方法。<em>小数据</em>的定义取决于人工智能所解决问题的复杂性。例如，在制药领域，考虑到广阔的化学空间，获得一百万个带注释的分子用于药物发现相对较小。其他需要考虑的因素包括机器学习技术的复杂性，从简单的逻辑回归到需要更多数据的神经网络，以及应用程序所需的准确性： 对于某些人工智能应用程序（例如进行医疗诊断） ），把事情做好比其他人更重要（例如当有人打字时建议表情符号）。在其他条件相同的情况下，较小的组织和传统非数字行业的组织面临着更严重的数据相关规模劣势。</p><p></p><p>人们已经构思出一些有用的策略和技术来帮助企业解决这个问题，例如跨公司数据池、迁移学习（重新利用以前训练的模型）和自我监督学习（在人工数据集上训练模型） 。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>然而，数据池的集中式方法在某些情况下可能不适合，例如当存在禁止数据传输的法律限制或涉及应保密的敏感数据的战略问题时。同样，只有当公司能够基于执行相关领域任务的机器学习模型的早期见解时，迁移学习和自我监督学习才是可行的方法，而这可能并不总是可行的。 FedML 可以成为小数据公司人工智能工具包中强大的额外工具，并作为其他小数据技术的重要补充。</p><p>在联邦学习设置中，机器学习模型在由不同组织控制的多个分散服务器上进行训练，每个服务器都有自己的本地数据。他们与中央协调器进行通信，该中央协调器聚合各个模型更新并协调训练过程。 （请参阅“联合机器学习概述”。）在最简单的情况下，学习目标是获取数据分布的基本描述性事实，例如均值或方差。例如，每家公司都可以计算其工厂某一制造流程的平均故障率，并将其提交给协调器，然后协调器将结合这些个人的贡献以形成更准确的联合估计。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>联合机器学习概述</h4><p class="caption">在联邦学习设置中，机器学习模型在由不同组织控制的多个分散服务器上进行训练，每个服务器都有自己的本地数据。他们与中央协调器进行通信，该中央协调器聚合各个模型更新并协调训练过程。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Bammens_Fig1.png" alt="联合机器学习概述" /><br /></article></aside></div><p></p><p> FedML 是一种分布式机器学习技术，可用于多种算法。例如，神经网络的权重或梯度可以以类似的方式在组织之间进行平均。协调器负责设置初始模型架构并协调训练过程，该过程通常需要多次迭代。因此，公司可以使用大量参数来训练复杂的机器学习模型，否则这些模型将超出他们的能力范围，因为本地数据的限制将导致模型准确性不佳。</p><p>重要的是，原始公司数据保持私密，并且在应用 FedML 时，只有统计数据（例如估计权重和其他参数）才会被共享和汇总。这样，10 家协作的小数据公司（每家都可以访问<em>x 个</em>数据点）可以通过其 AI/机器学习应用程序实现与一家可以访问 10 倍<em>x</em>数据点的大公司大致相似的预测能力，而不会损害数据隐私。</p><h3>制药行业的 FedML</h3><p>制药创新非常昂贵且耗时。截至 2022 年，将一种新药推向市场的<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/press-releases/deloittes-thirteenth-annual-pharmaceutical-innovation-report-pharma-r-and-d-return-on-investment-falls-in-post-pandemic-market.html">平均成本</a>约为 23 亿美元，而这个过程可能需要 10 多年的时间。药物发现的关键困难之一涉及极其大量的可能分子（数量级为 10 <sup>60</sup> ）以及在广阔的化学空间中寻找具有前景的分子的相关挑战。在如此高昂的成本和大量的分子可能性的背景下，高性能的预测机器学习模型是制药公司人工智能驱动的药物发现议程的基石。随着 Alphabet 等<a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/famga-big-tech-pharma/">大型科技</a>公司利用其在人工智能和机器学习方面深厚的专业知识冒险进入药物发现领域，制药公司也面临着压力。</p><p> Janssen Pharmaceutica 的科学总监 Hugo Ceulemans 认识到人们不愿共享药物发现数据，但也意识到协作人工智能在提高药物发现效率方面的巨大潜力，因此在 2016 年左右开始提出 FedML 想法并与同行展开讨论。最终，10 家制药公司在 2019 年成立了 Melloddy 联盟。Ceulemans 在一篇博文中指出，虽然制药公司之前已经汇集了数据来支持预测工作，但鉴于数据是一种数据，因此合作范围有限。昂贵的竞争性资产。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>他解释说，由于新的 FedML 联盟将允许基础数据贡献保持在各自数据所有者的控制之下而不是共享，因此可能会实现更雄心勃勃的范围。</p><p> Melloddy 是一个以<em>用于药物发现的机器学习账本编排命名</em>的术语，是一个为期三年的试点项目，旨在测试 FedML 的可行性和有效性。该项目由欧盟共同资助；欧盟委员会认为 Melloddy 是一个为制药以外的商业领域提供见解的测试案例。参与公司包括阿斯利康、拜耳、葛兰素史克、杨森制药、默克和诺华等。这些公司得到了技术和学术合作伙伴的支持，包括 Owkin（一家人工智能生物技术企业）和 KU Leuven（一所拥有人工智能驱动药物发现专业知识的大学）。</p><p>通过利用彼此的数据而不实际共享数据，参与的制药公司可以在世界上最大的药物发现数据集上训练他们的机器学习模型，从而能够更准确地预测有前途的分子并提高药物发现过程的效率。 Owkin 首席产品官 Mathieu Galtier 在一篇博客文章中解释说，由于 Mellody 使用联合学习，数据从未离开任何制药合作伙伴的基础设施。机器学习过程在每个参与的制药公司本地进行，并且仅共享模型。 “一项重要的研究工作致力于确保合作伙伴之间只共享统计信息，”他写道。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>于 2022 年结束的 Melloddy 试点项目的结果表明，使用去中心化数据创建用于协作人工智能的安全多方平台是可行的，并且通过使用 FedML 方法确实增强了机器学习模型的性能。</p><h3> FedML 联盟的战略考虑</h3><p>在建立 FedML 联盟时，参与规划过程的人员必须仔细考虑协调技术和激励合作伙伴的最佳方法。选定的协调器在有效管理 FedML 流程方面发挥着关键作用。小数据组织的领导者有时不愿意与大型科技公司合作，因为他们可以保持更大的战略控制，并与平等运营的小型科技合作伙伴建立更紧密的联系。一些人甚至担心大型科技公司自己会进入他们的领域，就像制药行业一样。</p><p>以 Mellody 为例，制药公司选择了初创公司 Owkin 来承担协调该联盟的 FedML 平台的责任。对于许多 FedML 计划来说，这可能是一个好方法，但考虑到初创公司的高失败率，它可能存在风险：如果初创公司失败，联盟可能会崩溃。还有一个潜在的风险是，初创公司可能会从未参加该联盟的竞争对手那里筹集资金；这是一个尴尬的情况，但并非不可能。因此，如果选择一家初创企业作为主要技术协调者，财团合作伙伴应该认真考虑投资企业风险资本（CVC）的选择。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>当合作伙伴在初创公司中拥有相当大的 CVC 联合股份并拥有优先购买权时，他们对科技初创公司的跑道长度及其未来发展轨迹拥有更强的控制力。</p><p></p><p> FedML 可能会引发激励问题，其中一些参与者无法使用所有相关的本地数据或忽视投资必要的数据基础设施以提高本地模型的准确性。他们可能选择不付出努力，而依赖其他联盟合作伙伴提供的数据贡献。这种搭便车行为会破坏善意参与者的积极性和参与性。为了解决这个问题，FedML 联盟可以在所提供数据的数量和覆盖范围方面就适当的合作伙伴承诺达成一致，并在合同协议中预先指定。协调器还可以监控本地模型更新对联合模型整体准确性的贡献，并且可以根据每个合作伙伴对联邦学习过程的贡献按比例支付 FedML 服务费。</p><p></p><p>在迈出组建 FedML 联盟的第一步时，确保合作伙伴的支持至关重要。因此，合作伙伴应参与确定联盟的目标，以换取他们的数据承诺。 AI Canvas 是一种决策工具，可用于识别和讨论机器学习用例和所需的训练数据。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>在与合作伙伴联系时，请记住，大多数 FedML 应用程序中的有效模型更新需要访问所有相关模型变量的本地数据。因此，通常会在同一行业内找到合适的合作伙伴，共享相似的业务流程和数据。与间接竞争对手（例如为其他地理市场提供服务的竞争对手）合作而不是与直接竞争对手合作可能有利于最大限度地减少潜在冲突。对于涉足 FedML 的小数据组织来说，建议从可实现的机器学习项目开始，以建立动力并在合作伙伴之间建立信任，然后再开始更雄心勃勃的项目。</p><p> FedML 仍然是一种年轻的人工智能方法，由一群 Google 工程师于 2016 年开发。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>但该领域的进展速度很快，我们可以预期其在一系列业务领域的采用将会激增。将 FedML 纳入其战略愿景的小数据组织具有前瞻性思维的领导者能够更好地利用人工智能的变革力量来塑造他们未来的成功。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>谁应该为演出定价？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jovana Karanovic, Elizabeth J. Altman, and Carmelo Cennamo. <p>Jovana Karanovic 是伊拉斯姆斯大学鹿特丹管理学院的助理教授，也是重塑工作基金会的创始人。伊丽莎白·J·奥尔特曼 (Elizabeth J. Altman) 是马萨诸塞州洛厄尔大学曼宁商学院管理学副教授； <cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》劳动力未来计划的客座编辑；合著者<cite>《劳动力生态系统：与人员、合作伙伴和技术一起实现战略目标》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2023 年）。 Carmelo Cennamo 是哥本哈根商学院战略与创业学教授、数字市场竞争论坛主任、SDA 博科尼管理学院平台经济与监管监测副教授兼主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Platforms & Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted interviews with platform executives at four platform businesses — Malt, Ring Twice, Temper, and Wolt — that represent different industry sectors and price-setting models. They also conducted archival web-based research studying platform-based businesses in various regions of the world and evaluated their pricing models. They were provided with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Karanovic_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹尼尔·赫茨伯格/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者采访了四家平台企业（Malt、Ring Twice、Temper 和 Wolt）的平台高管，这些企业代表了不同的行业领域和定价模式。</li><li>他们还进行了基于网络的档案研究，研究世界各地基于平台的业务，并评估其定价模型。</li><li>他们获得并分析了来自服务平台的数据，该平台从平台控制的价格设置转变为允许服务提供商设定价格。这些数据是 Jovana Karanovic、Hakan Özalp、Carmelo Cennamo 和 Mark Boons 正在进行的研究项目的一部分。</li></ul></aside><p>经过一段疲惫的旅程抵达波士顿洛根国际机场后，米娅打开优步应用程序寻找回家的车。看到“您的 Uber 司机将在 3 分钟内到达”的消息后，她松了口气，但这种安慰并没有持续太久，因为司机取消了行程。在接下来的 30 分钟内，六名 Uber 司机接受了她的乘车请求，然后取消了，最后一名司机到达了。发生了什么事？</p><p>与许多平台公司一样，Uber 需要高效地匹配服务提供商（司机）和客户（乘客）。为此，它必须确保定价具有足够的竞争力，以便乘客选择服务并让司机有动力提供服务。米娅很难搭车，因为优步已经开始为司机提供更高的收入透明度，允许他们在接载乘客之前查看他们的预期报酬和路线目的地。一项旨在让司机受益的变化对乘客来说有一个重大的缺点：更多的司机开始取消他们认为无利可图的行程。</p><p></p><p>对于平台运营商来说，由谁制定价格以及交易中的其他各方有什么自由裁量权来改变价格以实现互利的结果的问题是复杂而微妙的。就优步而言，该平台设定了乘车价格，尽管司机可以在收入潜力不具吸引力的情况下选择退出，但司机和乘客都没有提出不同定价的灵活性。这是将控制权主要掌握在平台提供商手中的缺点之一。</p><p>虽然平台运营商通过算法确定价格在叫车和送餐服务中很常见，但其他类型的平台业务允许服务提供商或客户设定价格。 Fiverr 是一个在线市场，为高技能服务提供商与客户匹配编程或图形设计等任务，让自由职业者说出他们的费率。相比之下，荷兰酒店、零售和物流领域的轮班工作平台 Temper 让客户（例如餐馆和商店）决定零工的报酬。</p><p>正如 Uber 的例子所示，控制所有定价可能会给平台带来意想不到的后果，但允许其他利益相关者设定价格也可能有缺点。例如，比利时平台企业 Ring Twice 提供园艺和保姆等各种家庭服务，将定价控制权分配给客户。事实证明，客户知道他们想要什么，但不一定知道一项特定任务需要花费多少时间和精力。允许客户设定价格会导致匹配次数减少，因为许多客户提供的付款低于服务提供商愿意接受的价格。成功的工作匹配减少意味着平台的收入损失。</p><p>授予定价控制权是一项重大战略决策，最终决定价值的创造和获取，并建立平台本身、服务提供商和客户之间的权力动态。创建一个让所有三个利益相关者都认为定价模型可持续且有益的场景是平台领导者面临的主要挑战。为了帮助领导者做出这一决定，我们提供了一个框架来理解不同平台定价方法的关键权衡。除了经济考虑之外，我们强调管理者需要预测权力动态并采取混合方法来缓解它们。 （参见“零工平台的定价动态”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>零工平台的定价动态</h4><p class="caption">平台运营商必须了解将定价权交给不同利益相关者的关键权衡；通过混合方法分享这种力量往往是最可持续的选择。 </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%">谁控制定价</th><th style="width:25%">好处</th><th style="width:25%">风险</th><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%">混合解决方案</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p><strong>平台</strong></p></td><td><p>基于捕获市场数据的算法定价可以最大限度地提高标准化服务的市场效率。</p></td><td><p>实时价格调整可能对提供商或客户不利。缺乏可预测性会损害信任。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>设定基本费率，使提供商能够上调价格或让客户提出报价。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>提供与生活工资相符的价格保证。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>供应商</strong></p></td><td><p>服务提供商的定价能力可以激励高质量的提供商加入。平台上更多的可变性满足了长尾需求。</p></td><td><p>定价过低会降低整个平台服务的感知价值。定价过高可能会赶走客户并限制平台的增长。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>允许客户和供应商之间进行价格和合同谈判。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>提供价格建议并与提供商分享市场数据。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>顾客</strong></p></td><td><p>客户可以控制自己的成本，这可能会增加客户对平台的参与度和感知价值。</p></td><td><p>提供太低的薪酬可能会赶走提供商，从而限制平台的增长。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>根据生活工资设定最低价格门槛。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>通过共享市场数据和/或提供价格建议来协助客户。 </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Karanovic_table-1.png" alt="零工平台的定价动态" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><h3>当平台发号施令时</h3><p>通过保留定价控制权，平台可以受益于众多优势，尤其是在某些细分市场。这种做法在叫车、食品配送和包裹递送领域很普遍，这些领域的服务相当标准化，数量很大，而且物流随着规模的扩大而迅速变得复杂。</p><p>通过保留控制权，平台可以优化效率，特别是当它们为大量具有类似需求的客户提供服务时。为了设定最佳价格，平台利用他们收集的大量交易数据。以最近被 DoorDash 收购的芬兰平台 Wolt 为例，该平台提供食品配送等服务。 Wolt 依赖于诸如快递员与餐厅的距离、食物准备时间以及与顾客的距离等参数。利用这些信息，它可以为快递员提供最佳路线建议，并提供相关的额外信息（例如，建筑物入口位置），以确保快速送货并节省时间。正如 Wolt 经理向我们解释的那样，该平台对效率的关注与快递员选择最佳路线的愿望是一致的，因此标准化配送流程和价格是有意义的。</p><p>控制价格还可以让平台根据市场情况快速调整，实现收入最大化：当需求高时，网约车和配送平台通常会实时提高价格。平台还可以尝试不同的定价策略。</p><p></p><p>最后，通过控制价格，平台提供商可以提供折扣和促销来吸引和留住客户。它可以选择根据客户行为、偏好和购买历史提供个性化定价。例如，亚马逊利用此类数据为某些商品设置动态定价。当客户在亚马逊上查看产品时，他们看到的价格可能与其他客户看到的同一产品的价格不同。这是因为亚马逊的定价算法会考虑客户的浏览和购买历史记录、他们的位置以及其他变量，以确定最大化购买可能性的个性化价格。</p><p>然而，平台保留定价控制权是需要权衡的，特别是当涉及到对利益相关者之间权力动态的影响时。特别是，如果平台定的价格太低，服务提供商可能会拒绝接受工作，或者如果价格定得太高，他们可能会难以吸引客户。在这两种情况下，服务提供商参与平台的动力都会减弱。一项研究检查了美国城市 Uber 司机论坛上的帖子，发现他们讨论了故意关闭自己的应用程序，让其显得不可用，以便让算法实施更高的高峰定价，旨在激励司机上路。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>司机本质上必须与系统进行博弈才能获得他们想要的价格，这反映出并加剧了供应商和平台之间缺乏信任。</p><p>平台控制的定价还与可能无法充分满足某些客户需求的标准化服务菜单密切相关。他们可以使用该平台寻找服务提供商，然后在平台外安排后续交互。最近的一项研究确实发现，提供商对平台规则和费用的不满，以及客户对更加个性化服务的渴望，是导致脱媒的主要因素之一。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>当客户和提供商对平台强加的规则不满意时，他们不太可能在平台上进行交易（收入降低），并且平台的声誉可能会在所有不满的利益相关者群体中受到损害。</p><p></p><h3>让服务提供商掌控一切</h3><p>服务提供商控制价格设定也有优势——这是 Upwork、Toptal 和 Malt 等自由职业市场的常见做法。授予这种自主权提供了一个具有竞争力和灵活的定价环境，这对于寻求特定功能以满足独特项目需求的客户来说特别有利。同样，提供者可以更有效地利用他们的技能或非凡才能货币化。</p><p>当提供商为项目设定价格时，他们可以考虑他们的成本、他们愿意付出的努力以及他们可以提供的服务质量——平台没有但需要这些信息才能设定适当的价格。定价还允许服务提供商行使创业自由，并根据无形因素（例如他们对特定项目的个人兴趣）调整价格。例如，欧洲咨询和软件开发服务平台 Malt 的一位经理表示，他们可能会以较低的价格获得一项有助于他们积累宝贵专业知识的任务。</p><p>当服务提供商能够设定自己的定价并提供差异化​​服务时，该平台就可以满足利基产品的长尾需求。 Helpling 是一个在德国、法国、瑞士、英国、爱尔兰、意大利和新加坡提供家庭清洁服务的平台，就是一个很好的例子。该平台最初有一个模型，在给定市场内，它为重复的清洁工作设定每小时的标准价格。 （一次性工作略高的价格也在市场内标准化。）然而，几年后，Helpling 改变了做法，让供应商自行设定价格。我们的研究表明，随着供应商愿意以更高的费用从事不同类型的工作（例如派对后的清理工作），某些工作的价格随后上涨。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>平台的政策变化显然暴露了附加服务需求未得到满足。</p><p>允许服务提供商设定价格还可以改善服务质量更可能因提供商而异的类别的客户体验。类似服务的不同质量水平可能会产生不确定性并降低满意度。质量较低通常是由于当客户支付平台业务设定的标准价格时，提供商缺乏动力付出所需的努力。如果提供商能够自行设定反映其真实价值的价格，他们就可以通过付出更大的努力获得回报并提供更高的客户满意度。</p><p></p><p>这种方法确实有缺点。 When platform operators relinquish price-setting control and providers overcharge, that can lower overall matching and transaction volumes; if providers undercharge, that can leave money on the table. At Malt, where service providers have full control of price setting, they tend to underprice themselves despite deep knowledge of what&#39;s required to perform tasks and their level of expertise. But that can be a vicious circle, according to the Malt manager we interviewed: Clients who are attracted to low-cost providers may be less discerning. Without a way for customers to differentiate between high- and low-quality providers listed on the platform, there&#39;s a risk that low prices will increasingly attract clients looking for more basic, lower-quality services. This drives out high-quality providers and potentially downgrades the brand equity and reputation of the platform. It might also lead to a race to the bottom, with providers consistently lowering prices to outcompete one another, reducing the platform&#39;s margins and providers&#39; earnings (and their willingness to remain on the platform).</p><p> For customers, provider pricing puts other dynamics into play. Providers that choose to focus on lucrative niches may leave some demand unmet. And the greater variability in provider-set pricing makes it more difficult for customers to fairly compare prices and find the best value for their money. If selecting a service provider becomes too time-consuming, customers may abandon the platform altogether.</p><h3> Customers Name Their Price</h3><p> Temper, the Dutch shift-work platform, allows customers to decide what they are willing to pay and matches skilled workers, such as baristas, with venues, such as restaurants. This approach is most appropriate when customers are businesses that have precise requirements for the services they need and the amount they are willing to pay.</p><p> Under this model, customers can set prices that reflect their budget and desired level of service, and service providers can choose to accept or reject offers based on their own pricing policies and cost structures. At Temper, restaurants looking for shift workers have different cost structures — for example, those in a city center pay higher rents. They also vary by service quality (for example, fine dining versus fast-casual), which affects the skills profiles they need and therefore the pay they will offer to attract workers. Customers can control their costs but also have flexibility to adapt to the competitive environment — for example, by offering higher compensation for weekend shifts. The platform exposes the going rate that other businesses are offering for the same services, which can also inform pricing decisions.</p><p> Finally, customers may be more motivated to use a platform if they have greater control over the pricing process. If they are given the power to determine the value they place on the service, they may feel more satisfied as well as invested in the transaction. Being more in control on the platform may deepen a sense of ownership and increase engagement and loyalty.</p><p> Naturally, customer-set pricing has trade-offs that can affect platform operators and providers. If customers set prices too low, service providers may be unwilling to take the task or they may be incentivized to cut corners to maintain profitability. This in turn could lead to a decline in the overall quality of products or services, reducing the platform&#39;s attractiveness and growth potential. Similarly, customers may not have access to complete information about the market dynamics, costs, and competitive landscape, leading to suboptimal outcomes for both providers and customers.</p><h3> Strike a Balance With Hybrid Approaches</h3><p> Whether pricing is controlled by the platform, service provider, or customer, under appropriate circumstances each choice has the potential to maximize value creation and efficiency. Nonetheless, dynamics that unfold among platforms&#39; different stakeholders may outweigh some of these benefits and lead to unintended consequences. To ensure long-term sustainability and enhance a platform business&#39;s financial performance, platform managers may want to share some control over pricing.</p><p> Platform providers can consider hybrid approaches to do this. For instance, TaskRabbit sets standard prices for different types of tasks based on factors such as complexity, duration, and market rates. These standard prices are initially determined by the platform to provide consistency and guidance to both customers and gig workers. However, TaskRabbit also allows service providers to adjust prices based on their own preferences and circumstances, and set a price that can be higher or lower than the platform&#39;s standard prices. The European Union has a proposed platform work directive that considers the right to set one&#39;s own rate a distinguishing factor between freelancers and employees; if adopted, it may push ride-hailing and food delivery platforms, which currently determine prices, to share this control with providers.</p><p> Platforms that control pricing can mitigate the power imbalance by being transparent with service providers about how prices are determined and whether they can do anything to increase earnings. They should also provide a mechanism for hearing providers&#39; concerns and enable them to appeal algorithmically determined decisions that affect their earnings on the platform.</p><p> While allowing service providers to set prices makes sense in some cases, it does not always lead to optimal pricing for them or the platform. For example, providers who have established high ratings and show a high number of completed tasks may have more pricing power compared with new providers. This is not beneficial for platforms, because new service providers quickly disengage if it takes too long to acquire work, limiting platform growth. Malt handles this discrepancy by boosting new providers&#39; visibility in search results.</p><p> Platforms can also assist providers with price setting, especially for offerings that are prone to demand fluctuations. A study of Airbnb found that only professional hosts (those with multiple properties) set prices skillfully; most others set suboptimal prices. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Airbnb introduced price recommendations, alerting hosts to events and time periods when demand is high and prompting them to increase prices. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Moreover, it lets hosts opt for automatic price adjustments, which essentially brings the price-setting power back to the platform, even in this service provider-controlled model.</p><p> When customers set prices, as we have seen, they may make lowball offers to service providers, especially during unfavorable market conditions. Platforms can prevent exploitation of service providers by setting minimum price thresholds that, for example, correspond to minimum or living wages. For instance, Temper sets a minimum price threshold for each service category that is in line with minimum wages, although it is not required to do so under Dutch law. In addition, it allows providers to negotiate. In 2022, 10% of all transactions on Temper were negotiated upward compared with initial prices set by customers, one of the company&#39;s cofounders told us. Such proactive initiatives from platforms may anticipate increasing regulations aimed at curtailing their power. New York City already has imposed a minimum wage for Uber and Lyft drivers and recently announced the same for workers on food delivery apps. The European Union is going a step further: Its proposed directive will presume gig workers are employees of platforms if certain criteria do not apply, such as a worker&#39;s right to adjust platform-determined rates as they see fit. In other words, if a platform sets upper limits for pay, it may be viewed as an employer.</p><p></p><p> As we have noted, customers may not always be fully informed, or they may have very specific preferences, in which case platforms can assist them with making provider selections. For example, on freelance marketplace Upwork, customers post desired tasks they need accomplished such as “logo design” or “report writing,” with detailed descriptions of what they are looking for and the price they are willing to pay. This price-setting model works well when customers have specific preferences and need a specific kind of provider for the job. However, Upwork eventually realized that not all customers have clear preferences; some just want the service done and would rather select it from a menu of offerings. This led to the launch of Upwork&#39;s Project Catalog, a website offering predefined projects that customers can browse and select, such as “A 500-word SEO-optimized blog article in under 24 hours” for $50. Instead of customers detailing the job, providers post what they can offer for a set price. This makes it easier for customers to find the right provider for their needs and gives providers more opportunities to win work.</p><p></p><p> A platform&#39;s need to control its marketplace to maximize returns isn&#39;t going away, but the approach it takes will determine its long-term sustainability. Platform leaders must realize that a platform is not a unilateral, hierarchically managed entity but rather a web of economic and social relationships. To manage it successfully and ensure satisfaction for all parties, they must share some aspects of control with other stakeholders, allow for compromise, and step in to support their workforce when needed. When control is shared more equitably among all parties in the platform relationship, the platform model can cater more beneficially to all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Rethinking Governance for Digital Innovation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David L. Rogers. <p>David L. Rogers is faculty director of Columbia Business School&#39;s executive education programs on digital business strategy and leading digital transformation. He is the author of <cite>The Digital Transformation Roadmap: Rebuild Your Organization for Continuous Change</cite> (Columbia Business School Publishing, 2023), from which this article is adapted, as well as the bestselling <cite>The Digital Transformation Playbook</cite> (2016).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Process]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George When global chemical company BASF launched its Onono lab in São Paulo, Brazil, its mission was to accelerate innovation through rapid collaboration with local partners and startups. But Onono’s director, Antonio Lacerda, faced an immediate hurdle from corporate governance: He was told that his lab would have to follow the same corporate data [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Rogers_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George</p></figcaption></figure><p> When global chemical company BASF launched its Onono lab in São Paulo, Brazil, its mission was to accelerate innovation through rapid collaboration with local partners and startups. But Onono&#39;s director, Antonio Lacerda, faced an immediate hurdle from corporate governance: He was told that his lab would have to follow the same corporate data policies used to secure BASF&#39;s entire cloud infrastructure — which would have made it impossible to partner quickly and nimbly with new startups. Lacerda postponed the launch until he was able, with significant political capital, to arrange an exception: a “sandbox” of separate data for his team, with special permission to share that data through APIs with new partners.</p><p> Lacerda&#39;s experience, and that of so many innovation champions, points to a fundamental problem for digital transformation: In large companies, innovation teams are left to fight for waivers in the face of business rules that contradict their own mandate for change. But innovation will never happen at scale as long as it relies on ad hoc exceptions approved by senior leaders. Instead, we must rethink our approach to governance and design new management practices for innovation at the speed of digital.</p><p></p><p> Designing repeatable processes for innovation is essential for growth in the digital era, yet it is incredibly hard. In too many organizations, new ventures are green-lit based on a single executive sponsor. Once started, ventures move slowly, managed by teams that sit in traditional silos. Resource allocation is slow too, as promising projects wait weeks or months for their next round of approvals. Because each project is backed by an influential executive, no one wants to shut it down, even if it shows little promise.</p><p> Meanwhile, risk aversion leads businesses to fund only their low-hanging fruit — incremental improvements in the core that bring a guaranteed, quick ROI. This path will never lead to transformation. Instead, you need governance that embraces uncertainty and supports growth both within and beyond the core. (See “How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation </h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:50%"> Signs of <em>Poor</em> Governance</th><th style="width:50%"> Signs of <em>Good</em> Governance</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> A top executive must personally approve any new innovation.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Established structures provide resources and governance for innovation.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> New ventures move slowly, led by traditional teams in functional silos.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> New ventures move fast, led by highly independent, multifunctional teams.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Allocating resources to new ventures is slowed by the annual budgeting cycle.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Resource allocation happens quickly through iterative funding.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Innovation is limited to a few big projects, which are hard to shut down once they are started.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> A steady pipeline of innovations is managed with smart shutdowns to free up resources.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> The only ventures to gain support are low-risk innovations in the core business.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Governance supports ventures with low and high uncertainty, both in the core and beyond. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Rogers_table-1.png" alt="How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p> Digital transformation requires that governance be carefully designed to address several issues. The first is <em>oversight</em> . Who approves new projects? To whom do they report? And who shuts them down? Next is <em>funding</em> . How will you allocate resources across a portfolio of ventures to maximize opportunities for success? Equally critical are <em>people</em> . Who will staff new ventures, whether inside or outside your organization? How will teams be formed with the right mix of skills? Governance must also include <em>metrics</em> . How will you measure the progress of new ventures? And, crucially, how can you bring discipline to regularly <em>shutting down</em> ventures, a practice so often neglected at large enterprises?</p><p> In this article, we will discuss how to design governance models to drive digital innovation across any enterprise, by focusing on two critical work groups: the people engaged in building new ventures and those overseeing and assessing their work. We&#39;ll delve into the top governance issues for managing growth at scale, including how venture teams and supervisory boards work together. And we will explore how to manage ongoing decisions to green-light new ventures, grant additional funding to those that merit it, and shut down others to free up resources.</p><h3> Design Teams to Drive Innovation</h3><p> Decades of experience have shown us that, in established businesses and small startups, meaningful new growth always starts in one place: small teams, effectively empowered. These teams do the work of rapid, iterative experimentation, which is at the heart of every modern approach to innovation — whether agile, design thinking, lean startup, or product management. Every innovation team&#39;s job is to take a proposed new venture and rapidly test every facet of its business model to validate what will or will not work in the market.</p><p> Within any established enterprise, the rules governing innovation teams are critical to their success. Many readers will be familiar with the idea of small multifunctional teams. But size and composition are only part of what matters for team success. By studying innovation in digital natives like Amazon and Google, and digital transformers like Walmart and Mastercard, I have identified five essential pillars of team governance. Great innovation teams are:</p><p><strong>小的。</strong> Research has shown that small teams communicate, coordinate, and make decisions much faster than large ones. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Small teams are foundational to agile methods, which use a rapid cadence of short sprints in which every team must deliver new working code, test and learn, and adjust priorities. At Amazon, innovation teams are called two-pizza teams because each one should be small enough to be fed by two pizzas (a maximum of eight people).</p><p> <strong>Multifunctional.</strong> Great innovation teams have diverse members who cut across functional silos (for example, marketing, engineering, and design). The goal is for each team to have members who can provide all the essential skills needed to do its work. Instead of constantly waiting for another department&#39;s input before taking the next step in its project, a multifunctional team is able to push ahead entirely on its own.</p><p> <strong>Single-threaded.</strong> The best innovation teams have all members dedicated full time to the team&#39;s work. At a minimum, the innovation team&#39;s leader must be single-threaded, meaning they cannot be splitting their workweek between the team&#39;s new venture and other projects. Leading the team is their full responsibility.</p><p> <strong>Autonomous.</strong> Successful innovation teams have clear decision rights that give them the authority to work under their own direction. They should not need to get approval on their work from anyone outside the team — whether it is on product design, what tests to run next, or which customers to pursue. Autonomy also means there are no prohibitions on contracting resources from outside the company.</p><p> <strong>Accountable.</strong> Autonomy is possible only if the team is also clearly accountable for the results of its work. Here, good governance demands a clear definition of success, which is defined in terms of outcomes, not deliverables. That definition may include quantitative metrics as well as qualitative principles, and it must be agreed on with leadership before the team&#39;s work begins. Effective accountability also requires transparency: At any time, the team&#39;s results must be visible to anyone inside or outside the team. Every test run, every MVP built, and every metric tracked should be visible to anyone in the company.</p><h3> Establish Oversight With Growth Boards</h3><p> Innovation teams&#39; most critical partners are the managers who will allocate funds and oversee and support their work. In my experience, the most successful model for sponsoring corporate innovation is the board. In the board model, a small group regularly convenes and deliberates to decide whether to sponsor various possible innovation ventures — much like a group of VC investors listening to pitches from startups. One innovation board will sponsor and support multiple teams working in parallel.</p><p> This approach contrasts with what I have found to be all too common: organizations where new ventures are approved by a single sponsor. In these companies, one or more executives may use their clout within the organization to sponsor a new digital venture they deem strategically important and promising. This model is inherently ad hoc, with decisions based on the instincts and judgment of different individuals. And once a sponsor puts their name and reputation behind a project, it is very hard for them to let it die, no matter what market validation shows about its prospects. By contrast, the board model — with its greater diversity and impartiality of decision-making — is inherently better for managing innovation at scale.</p><p> Effective corporate innovation boards — also known variously as growth boards, venture boards, or growth councils — should number no more than eight people. They should include members with topical expertise and knowledge of the market. A board should be able to challenge company orthodoxy, advocate a long-term view, and bring in ideas from outside the industry. The best boards combine internal stakeholders from different divisions and at least one member with an external perspective. Members should be senior enough to have real clout in the organization but not so senior that they can&#39;t make board work a priority.</p><p> The job of the board is to regularly meet to green-light new ventures, provide strategic guidance to teams, decide on each stage of additional funding, and make disciplined decisions about when to shut down ventures. Here again, decision rights are critical. The innovation board must have complete funding authority for each team in its portfolio. Its decisions should be informed by open and lively debate with the team, but the decisions remain with the board. Other senior executives, including the CEO, may advise and provide input on ventures, but they cannot vote on or overrule the board&#39;s investment decisions.</p><p></p><h3> Green-Light New Projects</h3><p> The first process where boards and teams must work together is green-lighting — that is, approving new ventures to start work. When a board green-lights a new venture, it should allocate just enough resources (in the form of time, money, and people) for the team to conduct a first round of testing to validate the initial questions about the business model. The key to effective green-lighting is to <em>minimize</em> the initial investment made in each team and <em>maximize</em> the number of ideas that are approved to be tested.</p><p> This approach may seem counterintuitive — it certainly contrasts with the tendency to try to “pick a winner and bet big,” seen at so many organizations with poor innovation governance. In fact, it is important for boards to resist the urge to try to pick the best ideas among those submitted. First, the board has truly no way of knowing which ideas will work. That knowledge can be gained only through testing and validation. Second, successful ventures often emerge from ideas that are initially flawed but evolve in response to testing, feedback, and iterative design. Instead of trying to evaluate the likelihood of success, I recommend that boards judge new venture pitches based on their problem definition, strategic fit, and team mindset.</p><p></p><p> To green-light many innovation ideas, it is essential to build a fast, cheap, and effective validation process. This means bringing in the voice of the customer to rapidly test whether the venture is focused on solving a genuine problem. At Citibank, new ventures often begin with a two- or three-day workshop in which employees explore a problem/opportunity statement and have a chance to develop their own innovation ideas in a rapid, iterative fashion with actual customers. As you increase the speed and drive down the cost of your first stage of validation, your business can afford to approve more venture teams to test and pursue more possible ideas for growth.</p><h3> Manage Resources With Iterative Funding</h3><p> The next critical process for managing innovation is iterative funding, which is how boards allocate resources to teams after their ventures have been green-lit. Iterative funding is designed to be extremely agile, based on the VC approach to financing startups. At each board review (typically every 30, 60, or 90 days), the board will review each team&#39;s progress, including new data from its tests in the market, and decide whether to release the next tranche of resources to that team.</p><p> Iterative funding is a dramatically different process from traditional budgeting in large enterprises. Here&#39;s why it&#39;s a better approach for managing investments in new innovation:</p><p> <strong>Get off to a faster start.</strong> In a traditional budgeting process, a new project will be granted a large initial sum that reflects commitment to the project. But that happens only after a long period of analysis that strives (misguidedly) to assess the chances of an uncertain new venture through benchmarks and third-party data. Iterative funding, in contrast, gives ventures a small initial budget but allows teams to get started fast, if the opportunity they are pursuing is well defined and strategically relevant.</p><p> <strong>Be more agile with shorter funding cycles.</strong> Corporate budgets are typically set annually, with projects and departments funded through a complex process that takes months. A promising new venture can wind up waiting over a year to get resources for a four-week test. In contrast, when boards meet frequently and funding rounds provide teams with just one to three months of resources, decision-making is much more agile.</p><p> <strong>Invest based on real-world data.</strong> Many leaders will overcommit funds to an untested new venture because they have a personal conviction that the strategy is right or because they are swayed by the persuasive talents of the team. With an iterative funding process, the board decides on each round of resources based entirely on real-world data. Every time they meet, the board and the team must agree on what data the team needs to bring to its next review meeting. Those metrics — typically three to six key variables — will shift over time, depending on the biggest sources of uncertainty still facing the new venture. They capture what the venture team has learned so far and what it needs to learn next.</p><p> <strong>Scale fast to drive exponential growth.</strong> In traditional budgeting, when funding is renewed, any increase is only incremental from the previous budget. With iterative funding, if validation is successful and a venture moves ahead, the size of each investment round should grow exponentially. Allocation of human resources should increase as well. This means that innovation teams that uncover meaningful growth opportunities can scale quickly to make a measurable impact on the company&#39;s bottom line.</p><p> Clearly, iterative funding requires that boards be ready to ramp up investment quickly in ventures that prove themselves in the market. That means the enterprise must fund a pool of resources in advance, for the board to allocate over the course of a year and across a portfolio of projects.</p><p> Within each portfolio, similar innovations (for example, a portfolio of high-risk innovations within a single business unit) should compete for funds. Don&#39;t let apples compete with oranges. First fund the portfolio for a specific class of innovations, and then let the board iteratively fund the various ventures.</p><h3> Make a Habit of Smart Shutdowns</h3><p> Of course, not every team review will conclude with a decision to continue funding. One of the classic problems that bedevil corporate innovation is that companies learn how to start new projects but not how to stop them. For innovation to deliver results, companies must be ready to exit projects that prove unsuccessful or are insufficiently aligned with strategy.</p><p> Shutting down ventures systematically and regularly is a critical job for growth boards. Every time a board meets for an iterative funding review, the question must be, “Do we fund this venture further or shut it down?”</p><p></p><p> At legacy companies, the biggest barrier to shutting down innovation projects is often an aversion to admitting failure and an irrational feeling that any kind of failure poses too much risk. But the cost of failures is minimal when they are shut down early, through iterative funding. In contrast, there are very real costs to the company if your teams do not shut down ventures quickly and smartly. Without this discipline, your innovation will lack focus, your resources will be spread too thin, and you will run out of bandwidth for new experiments. You will be stuck with <em>zombie projects</em> — unsuccessful ventures that never shut down and continue siphoning off resources. At Johnson &amp; Johnson, an entire new series of innovations was funded by evaluating the existing portfolio and shutting down projects that no longer matched the company&#39;s updated strategy. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> Halting projects will become easier only if you make it a routine decision, and here innovation boards with a regular calendar of funding reviews will make a huge difference. In GE&#39;s oil and gas division, projects were rarely shut down before its board was instituted. As soon as the board began, it easily shut down 20% of existing projects in its first 90-day cycle. As the board and teams became focused on aligning to strategy, this rose to 50% of new ventures shutting down within 60 days. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> At media giant Schibsted, the goal is to remove one venture whenever adding something new to the development pipeline. When a project comes up for review, set a high bar for yourself by asking, “Why shouldn&#39;t we shut this venture down?”</p><p> The following five practices are essential to achieving smart shutdowns in any organization:</p><p> <strong>Plan a pipeline with survival rates.</strong> Innovation at scale requires planning for most new ventures to be shut down. Only a third to a half of bright, shiny new ideas typically survive their first funding review after they&#39;ve had contact with real customers. Survival rates typically increase in subsequent rounds. Understanding your survival rates at different stages of validation will allow you to plan a pipeline for the future. For example, if a board is expected to help bring three or four new ventures to market within a year, it needs to plant enough seeds at the start to have good odds for success.</p><p> <strong>Use a venture backlog to reassign swiftly.</strong> An innovation board should maintain a ranked list of ideas for ventures that have been approved but not yet begun. Using this backlog in your review process will make shutdowns much easier. The point is no longer simply to kill a failing idea but to free the team and its resources to work on a more promising idea from the backlog. So, when you shutter a project, quickly reassign members to the best next idea. In many cases, that may just mean refocusing that team on a different solution to the same problem.</p><p> <strong>Extract value from shutdowns.</strong> When you decide to shut down a project, look to extract as much value as possible. In some cases, a company may be able to sell the venture to another business. When Walmart&#39;s Vudu streaming video service was no longer a strong strategic fit, Walmart spun it off to media giant Comcast. Sometimes a venture is promising but not yet workable; by shrinking your investment, you may maintain your future options. After Google Glass failed as a consumer product, the company shrank the project to an enterprise-only device focused on applications on factory floors. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Sometimes only a full shutdown makes sense, and the key value to extract is the learning gained from experimentation. When Amazon shut down its Amazon Auctions and zShops services, it applied the lessons it learned for the subsequent launch of Amazon Marketplace to great success.</p><p> <strong>Share learning widely.</strong> Sharing what you learn from failed ventures is one of the hardest principles to follow. Most companies prefer to look away from projects that didn&#39;t work out. In a 2014 internal report on its early digital transformation efforts, The New York Times Co. admitted, “When we do shut down projects, the decisions are made quietly and rarely discussed, to protect the reputations of the people who ran them. As a result, lessons are forgotten, and the staffers involved become more risk averse.” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Overcoming this reluctance was essential to the ultimate turnaround of The New York Times Co. and its business model. The German affiliate of Fédération Internationale de l&#39;Automobile (FIA) ran an innovation lab where eight of 10 projects were killed in a single year. Its biggest win? Sharing those results with other FIA affiliates around the world that were struggling with the same challenges in their own markets.</p><p> <strong>Distinguish people from projects.</strong> This is a final critical piece to building a culture that accepts and learns from innovation failures. A strong board review process will hold teams accountable for their results. But you should be careful not to associate a failed project with the merit of the individuals who worked on it. Those same team members could achieve tremendous success for you in their next project. Be sure to encourage your innovators to keep working on their next idea.</p><p> If your process for shutdowns is truly working, you will begin to see volunteering. When teams are truly focused on validating growth opportunities through experimentation, they will often suggest their own shutdown to the board, reporting, “Here&#39;s what we have learned and why we recommend shutting down now.” Don&#39;t be surprised when those same employees soon return to their board with another venture idea. It could be your next big breakthrough.</p><p></p><p></p><p> For digital transformation to deliver real growth and value to any organization, it must involve more than isolated pockets of innovation from teams struggling under the yoke of ill-suited management. Without new governance models to manage new ventures, the potential for digital innovation will always fall short.</p><p> Innovation governance requires three key building blocks: (1) Teams must be empowered to move fast and experiment to discover what works in the marketplace; (2) boards must be empowered to oversee and advise portfolios of teams, allocating resources where most needed; and (3) both must follow regular processes for green-lighting new ventures, funding them iteratively, and shutting them down to free up resources for the next emerging opportunity.</p><p> With the right governance in place, established companies of every kind can unlock the potential in their own employees to drive transformation and growth at every level of their business.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Images and Inspiration With AI: Pinterest&#39;s Jeremy King</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jeremy King leads a team of 1,400 passionate engineers working on the continuous improvement of Pinterest’s image-driven platform. With a background that includes heading up a translation team at eBay and overseeing the technology behind Walmart’s U.S. retail stores and e-commerce business, Jeremy is now responsible for technology operations at Pinterest. To support the company’s [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Jeremy King leads a team of 1,400 passionate engineers working on the continuous improvement of Pinterest&#39;s image-driven platform. With a background that includes heading up a translation team at eBay and overseeing the technology behind Walmart&#39;s US retail stores and e-commerce business, Jeremy is now responsible for technology operations at Pinterest. To support the company&#39;s mission to inspire people to “create a life that they love,” he and his team rely on advanced AI, machine learning, and a graph database to index and build a network of images so that users can find inspiration — particularly when they aren&#39;t completely sure what they&#39;re looking for.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Jeremy joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to talk about some recent advances Pinterest has made in the image-recognition space and shares his views on how generative AI will transform image-based content like Pinterest&#39;s. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E6-King-Pinterest-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Jeremy King"></p><h4> Jeremy King, Pinterest</h4><p> Jeremy King is senior vice president of technology at Pinterest, where he leads the company&#39;s technical vision and the engineering organization responsible for building and scaling a visual discovery engine.</p><p> Before joining Pinterest, he was CTO and senior vice president at Walmart, where he led the team responsible for the technology behind US retail stores and e-commerce for Walmart and Jet, and oversaw customer, merchant, and supply chain technologies across cloud and data platforms. King has also held executive-level technology roles at Walmart Labs, LiveOps, and eBay.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does an AI-based platform use generative AI to engage users? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I&#39;m Jeremy King from Pinterest, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome. Our guest today is Jeremy King, head of engineering at Pinterest. Jeremy, thanks for taking the time to talk with us.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> It&#39;s great to be here. Thank you very much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s always good to start with an overview; maybe tell us a bit about what Pinterest does and what you do at Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Pinterest is, we like to say, the destination on the internet for inspiration. We have hundreds of millions of people that come to us every day to figure out what they want to wear, what they want to do this afternoon, or what they want to make for dinner, or how to decorate their kid&#39;s cake or remodel their kitchen. And so we want to build a platform that allows anyone to create a life that they love.</p><p> It&#39;s a great place to work with that kind of mission, and I have a lot of people who, when I tell them where I work, get pretty elated about their own Pinterest boards and what&#39;s going on in the world.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Great. Tell us more about working at Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I&#39;ve been at Pinterest now, the head of engineering, for just over four years. And just like any leader, I&#39;m trying to figure out how to unblock my team and hire great people. I tell people all the time that when I came to Pinterest, I was just so impressed with the level of talent. It&#39;s a relatively small team. We have 4,500 employees in the world and about 1,400 engineers. And as a result, competing against some of the biggest companies in the world, this team has to be extremely high caliber. We have some of the best graph database people in the world; we have the best computer vision people in the world. These people are really fun to work with.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> None of that, so far, mentioned artificial intelligence, so, what role does artificial intelligence play with those 1,400 engineers?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, that&#39;s an excellent point. One of the things that is true at Pinterest and now at many other companies is Pinterest was actually born with machine learning and AI from the base. It doesn&#39;t exist without it. So talking about AI and ML separately from Pinterest is almost like a misnomer; it really doesn&#39;t happen without it. Nearly everything that we do touches our machine learning systems. We do millions of inferences every second. Every single request comes all the way back to the graph and publishes back out a very specific use case to every single person.</p><p> It&#39;s not cached. … Every person has a specific result. I mentioned that we have about 1,400 engineers. We have about 350 machine learning engineers. As a percentage, when I tell other CTOs … they&#39;re like, “That&#39;s a really high percentage of machine learning people compared to my company.” That&#39;s true also on the data platform side; we have a wonderful leader, Dave Burgess, who runs our data platform. And you can imagine our data platform is about as important as any other part of our capabilities. And so I mentioned the graph, but it&#39;s also, you know, the sort of normal SQL databases and the real-time systems that keep this thing running.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Jeremy, you said “graphs” a couple of times. What&#39;s a graph?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Essentially what a graph is, is if you take an entity, an object, and you say, “What&#39;s related to that object?” — so, in this case, we&#39;re using a nearest neighbor graph, which we&#39;ve written lots of documents on, which is saying, “Hey, I have an image, in this case, and I have another image that&#39;s related to this image.” So that allows me to build this sort of network of images. And the reason the graph works at Pinterest is because every pin is essentially added to a board, which essentially makes it a node in a graph, and so it continues to increase the graph.</p><p> So it allows you to … unlike a SQL database or a relational database, where you have to sort of tag indexes and indices, the graph can be indexed. Essentially any image could be indexed to any other image. It allows you to do searches on things that are related incredibly efficiently. That&#39;s the power of Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Jeremy, you mentioned AI has been part and parcel of Pinterest&#39;s journey and has been ingrained in Pinterest&#39;s tech stack from its very early inception, so it must be that generative AI is all over the map for you guys as well, and I&#39;m sure it&#39;s on everybody&#39;s mind these days. So maybe tell us a bit about what you are doing there.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> We have a state-of-the-art machine learning environment that interconnects these data sets across all the surfaces. We call it the “home feed,” the search system, the related things that drive personalization and recommendations and engagement across Pinterest. [And] we&#39;re growing really fast from monthly active users. … Gen Z is growing even the fastest. We added 13 million monthly active users, so we&#39;re really focused on how to increase engagement.</p><p> And not surprisingly, a lot of the improvements in machine learning, even in the last two years, have been driving that engagement. We have, of course, built new features [that] allow Pinterest to become more shoppable. But as we&#39;re seeing the capabilities of the machine learning models getting effectively 10 or a hundred times bigger, which is relatively common today, we&#39;re seeing that give an outsize increase in our results as the result gets more specific.</p><p> And frankly, Pinterest is also about looking at [vastly] different things. So it&#39;s not [that] every single item is about “What do you want to cook for dinner tonight?” It&#39;s also “I know you were looking at birthday cakes last week” or “New Year&#39;s is coming up,” and we&#39;re going to interplay some of that. So we&#39;ve been taking advantage of some of the advanced AI capabilities that have only come to life over the last couple years. And that includes GPU [graphics processing unit] work and all the things that make it cost-effective to do these things.</p><p> So tying back to your question of generative AI, not surprisingly, given that we&#39;re an image platform, generative AI is very interesting to us, and I typically break it up into three buckets. When we&#39;re thinking about large language models — LLMs — we talk about, No. 1, how do I make my team more productive? We&#39;ve got a couple of pilots running. We haven&#39;t decided exactly which way to go yet, but it&#39;s looking really promising, and, like lots of other CTOs, we&#39;re really excited about that.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s interesting. Tell us how generative AI increases efficiency.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I was talking to a number of CTOs, and one thing I thought was really interesting is, this one particular CTO was saying that, in general, it&#39;s increased productivity by 10% to 15%, but there is a small set of users where it&#39;s increased their productivity by 50%.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s fantastic. I was just going to say, it also feels like, if you go back a decade ago, there were lots of images and unstructured text and that kind of stuff that, for AI to train on that data and make sense of it, human intervention was needed, both to tag the content but also to make sure that the outputs made sense. And it feels like now, with gen AI, that a lot of those humanlike judgment calls are going to be made more and more with gen AI, particularly with lots of unstructured text and images and video and that kind of content. Is that right, or am I going too far?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think it&#39;s right. I mean, Pinterest&#39;s system is built on embedding, so you take an image or a piece of text and you essentially tag it — essentially, to your point, this is what Pinterest has really been great at. You take our computer vision technology and effectively build these embeddings to detect people or content or couches or birthday cakes.</p><p> We&#39;ve been really good at that and have really led the industry for a long time on this. And you&#39;re not wrong that what happens is, it just gets better; it gets more accurate, more specific. In the old days, I could say, “Hey, I know this is a lamp, and I know it&#39;s got pendants, and it&#39;s made of crystal, and it&#39;s gold,” and that sort of thing. But now I can say, “I know exactly how many tines it has on it; I know what kind of light bulbs they are; I know probably who manufactured it,” and these sorts of things. I can get way more specific.</p><p> And at Pinterest, we really think about these as two different things. People come to Pinterest because they don&#39;t know exactly what they want. And this is where Pinterest thrives, and I think why we have a long-term differentiation in the market. Because if you know what you want, you can always go to Amazon or Home Depot or Wayfair to go buy it, but if you don&#39;t know what you want, you start with Pinterest or do a million different searches because [you] don&#39;t know how to describe, you know, “classic barnyard kitchen” — [you] don&#39;t know those words.</p><p> So even putting it in something like ChatGPT, I don&#39;t know how to say that — you know what I mean? I&#39;m sure that&#39;ll get better over time, but a lot of it will be image-based, too, as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Are you finding that the foundational models that are available do it for you, or you&#39;re building your own domain-specific models?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Both, I guess, is the answer. What we&#39;re finding — and it&#39;s still relatively early — in sort of the generative imagery, what we&#39;re finding is that the smaller models actually are much more specific, and so I think that&#39;s what&#39;s going to happen. And my CTO friends are saying the same thing, which is, each one of these models is going to be very specific to the use case, and that helps it not only be more accurate but also makes it much, much cheaper to implement as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think it&#39;s interesting that you mentioned cakes several times, because decorating cakes is, I think, practically my only use of Pinterest. And it ties to Shervin&#39;s comment about generative, because I deeply suspect that those cakes that I see there, no human could create. I certainly can&#39;t create them. So to what degree are … people putting [up] images that don&#39;t really exist or products that don&#39;t exist? What&#39;s Pinterest&#39;s perspective on that?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Excellent point. I think, yes, and we see this a lot [in] one of our biggest categories we call “art.” Art includes a whole bunch of things, including things that you would traditionally put on walls, and paintings, and that sort of thing. But it also includes things like body art, and we have tattoos and these sorts of things. And again, lots of those are great cases where people need a little bit of inspiration, and it can be generative, right? It may not exist in the world, but you want to see what it looks like on a human.</p><p> You can see this coming, where you&#39;ll be able to print out something that&#39;s generative. And this is already happening, right?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah. That really aligns with the idea of inspiration.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And things like cakes and that sort of thing are very interesting. One of the harder parts is, I&#39;ve seen lots of work for home and home improvement, but what it&#39;s doing is it&#39;s generating a whole bunch of ideas that can&#39;t be realized, where I can say, “Hey, people have yet to really break out the camera and take a picture of their room.” People do that, but we call it a 1% feature. Like, how do you get people to actually engage the phone or the phone camera?</p><p> But if you can upload an image — I&#39;ve seen some beautiful renderings of, like, “Here&#39;s what my room is. Rearrange the furniture in my room, the furniture I already have,” and things like that become really interesting. Or you say, “I want to replace this couch with this couch from Wayfair. I want to replace this lamp [with] some other lamp,” and here&#39;s 20 different combinations, and you can kind of click through it.</p><p> Those are like you&#39;re taking a virtual experience, almost AR-like [augmented reality-like], but you&#39;re putting real products in there versus them being generated products. But it allows you to build user experiences that are much more enhancing.</p><p> Last year, we built <a href="https://help.pinterest.com/en/article/try-on">AR Try On</a> , which allows you to try on makeup, and what we&#39;re seeing, again, while it doesn&#39;t get a ton of usage, the people that do use it are 60% more likely to buy something. It&#39;s amazingly engaging when people actually get there.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s tough at Pinterest? You mentioned a lot of good use cases, where you&#39;re doing lots of things with these technologies. Certainly, [it] can&#39;t all be wonderful. What&#39;s hard?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> We spend a lot of time on inclusive search and results. In 2021, we launched hair-pattern search. It was kind of this first of technology: When you&#39;re searching for hairstyles, how do you identify hair that looks like yours? This is hugely important in order to refine what you&#39;re looking for.</p><p> We had these same kinds of problems with skin tone, where originally we were trying to use the early models for skin tone detection. And what we found is, it was more on face detection. And so our team had done some great work doing skin detection — it could be a side shot or a back shot or ear shot or a hand shot. You have no idea what kind of skin. So how do I detect what skin is? And then you can detect what kind of tone you&#39;re looking for.</p><p> Same thing had to be applied to hair. And we&#39;ve got all kinds of hair: We have shaved/bald, we have straight, we have wavy, we have curly, we have coily, we have protective, and these kinds of things make the results dramatically better.</p><p> You can save your hair pattern and your skin tone, and then we&#39;ll tailor your results to that. And as you can imagine, this is a complex problem. It&#39;s not just a USA thing; every different country has different types of hair patterns and skin tones and different kinds of fashion, and so these kinds of things are really hard, but they&#39;re the great projects to work on.</p><p> And we&#39;ve had a wonderful team. The advanced technology group here, in particular — we&#39;ve been working on inclusive technology and all these advanced models, and they&#39;re definitely hard, but they&#39;re wonderful when you get them right.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> We have a segment here: five rapid questions. I&#39;ll just ask you a bunch of rapid-fire questions. Just tell me the first thing that comes to your mind. What&#39;s your proudest AI moment?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> The inclusive product feature, and actually, hair pattern was my proudest one, because not only was I involved [with] the product from the beginning, but it&#39;s also first in the industry. And the amount of response that we got from our pinners was incredible. So, yeah, it was a really good one.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What worries you about AI, aside from bias and some of the ethical issues?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> It&#39;s funny. It&#39;s on every single forum. It says, “Hey, are you worried about bias?” Let&#39;s see. What worries me about AI? Hmm. Yeah, I&#39;m not worried. I don&#39;t worry about too many things, but that&#39;s a CTO ...</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s good. That&#39;s a good thing though, right?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> That&#39;s a longtime CTO&#39;s thing. If you worry about too much, you can&#39;t survive in this job.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Mountain biking.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very cool.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I try and go at least two times a week. I go with a crew of Silicon Valley tech [colleagues] on Friday mornings and then usually on the weekends with my brother and a few other people.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think my 5-year-old baby book says fireman, but both my grandfather and my father were engineers, so I actually thought I would build houses, because I loved working with my hands outside. So that&#39;s where I thought I was going to go — architecture or house-building.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What do you wish AI could do that it currently can&#39;t?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Teleportation: Get me through the security line faster! Maybe that&#39;s coming. I&#39;ve always been super excited about translation. I took over the translation team at eBay way back when, and there were some wonderful people that were working on this. And I&#39;ve always thought about a universal translator as something that would just be so amazing. And it&#39;s getting so close, but it still seems like so far away before there&#39;ll be a consumer version of this device.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But why do you think that is? Because we&#39;ve got LLMs now, and we&#39;ve had, for a long time, audio to text. What&#39;s the limiting factor here?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think it&#39;s form factor; like, how do I get out my phone, hit “translate from Spanish to English” — you know, that kind of thing. I don&#39;t know; if I&#39;m walking up to a vendor in the street in San Francisco and I don&#39;t speak the same language, and I want something. … It&#39;s got to be close, but it&#39;s a form factor thing. But I think it&#39;ll come shortly.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Seems solvable.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, solvable.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Jeremy, we really appreciate you taking the time to talk with us. It&#39;s been very interesting to learn, sort of behind the scenes, what&#39;s happening between all those images that we see but maybe didn&#39;t appreciate all that goes into making something that looks as easy as Pinterest work. And it&#39;s been pretty fascinating to see how much artificial intelligence and machine learning is behind that.感谢您加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Of course. It&#39;s been wonderful.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening today. On our next episode, Sam and I meet with Damini Satija and Matt Mahmoudi from Amnesty International. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Identify Critical Roles to Improve Performance</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boris Groysberg, Eric Lin, Abhijit Naik, and Sascha L. Schmidt. <p>Boris Groysberg is the Richard P. Chapman Professor of Business Administration at Harvard Business School. Eric Lin is an associate professor of business at Oberlin College and Conservatory. Abhijit Naik is senior global quantitative researcher at Quent Capital. Sascha L. Schmidt is a professor and director of the Center for Sports and Management at WHU-Otto Beisheim School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Brian Stauffer/theispot.com Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization’s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn’t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Groysberg_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Brian Stauffer/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization&#39;s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn&#39;t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs that aren&#39;t critical is just a waste of talent.</p><p> It&#39;s accepted wisdom in strategy execution that focused application of concentrated strength — identifying, developing, and leveraging critical capabilities — is required for success. Yet until these capabilities are translated into specific roles, with systems in place to ensure that high-quality employees occupy such positions, a strategy is just an intention. Unfortunately, too many organizations build strategy around the people they have at the time and current skill sets — when they should instead be devising the most promising strategy, developing a better understanding of the roles that will be most critical in executing it, and then staffing those roles with the best available talent. As we&#39;ll demonstrate, applying data and analytics to that problem can help you determine exactly where your top talent needs to be placed.</p><p></p><p> There are two ways to figure out which roles have the most influence on key results: using data to deduce this from the bottom up and inferring it from the top down. Where the context is appropriate and the data available, taking the bottom-up approach can yield answers that may be surprising. In such cases, leaders must be prepared to let the insights guide their decisions.</p><h3> Data Reveals the Difference Makers</h3><p> Data can be used to help tease out both who your current stars are and what positions have the greatest influence on organizational outcomes. It can help identify hidden talent in situations where performance is a team effort and point out roles that may be much more important to success than leadership has realized.</p><p> Take soccer: There is much debate around which positions on the field are the most valuable. Forwards, including strikers, are the primary scorers — they capture the limelight as well as the largest salaries by producing goals. The top 50 highest-paid athletes worldwide include six soccer players — and they are all forwards — according to a 2023 <cite>Forbes</cite> report.</p><p> Since soccer is a low-scoring game, every goal matters — so preventing an opponent&#39;s goal is an equally crucial contribution. Thus, some argue that defenders are the most valuable players. Central defenders play a critical role in coordinating the counteroffensive, as failure to stop the ball at key moments can create big opportunities for the opponent to score. It&#39;s no surprise that central defenders have been team captains more often than other position players.</p><p></p><p> Of course, goalkeepers are the last defenders on the line: Their judgment and skills in the face of extreme pressure can mean the difference between victory and defeat. Still others contend that midfielders drive the tempo of the game. Just as controlling the center of the board is critical to winning chess matches, midfielders can magnify the impact of everyone&#39;s contributions by shutting down opponent passing lanes or by initiating drives through well-timed distributions from the defensive players to the offensive strikers. Finally, the grandmaster might be the coach, who makes decisions on rosters, positions, and general strategy.</p><p> To determine each role&#39;s relative contribution, we collected and analyzed five years&#39; worth of data from the Bundesliga, Germany&#39;s top soccer league, and evaluated the importance of individual positions on the soccer field between 2014 and 2019.</p><p> By analyzing the changes in outcomes as players moved among different roles and teams, we isolated contributions by position while observing how fortunes rose and fell following such switches. Building a model of how each position contributes to the outcome, we weighted the importance of positions by measuring how much the model&#39;s win prediction deteriorated when we omitted each role from the model in turn.</p><p> Our analysis indicated that defenders and goalkeepers are the most critical for winning matches; they occupy the top three slots in two different models we developed. Four positions are always present among the top five: left fullback, right fullback, goalkeeper, and offensive left midfielder. Although defenders may not get as much fan adoration, the numbers indicate that they are the biggest difference makers for winning.</p><p> This kind of analysis works regardless of industry. Every organization or function is similarly likely to have its own underappreciated roles. While the sales team may land the account, it could be the service department that keeps that account renewing each year.</p><p> Talent scarcity matters, too. Comparing the left versus right positions for fullback, midfielder, and center defender, the roles on the left side contribute disproportionately more.为什么？ While left-footed soccer players are naturally advantaged for these roles, the number of world-class left-footed players is considerably smaller than right-footed players. In critical roles where exceptional talent is scarce, having performers in such roles is doubly important.</p><p> Organizational leadership and structure also matter. When included in the models, coaches are the third-most-important factor, behind only the fullback positions. Team organization, systems of play, and staffing govern how critical roles are deployed. In the Bundesliga, the 4-5-1 team formation — four defenders, five midfielders, and one striker — is the most successful configuration. It favors the strategy of prioritizing defense positions and is a good example of congruence between strategy and how organizations configure themselves around critical roles.</p><p></p><h3> Use Data to Fill Critical Roles</h3><p> A similar analytical approach can be applied to businesses by combining performance and HR data. For companies with multiunit structures (such as multiple stores, distribution centers, or service teams), the good news is that you don&#39;t need a soccer league&#39;s worth of data — you can do this yourself. Multiunit organizations with common roles offer the opportunity to capture data across the units and isolate difference-making roles.</p><p> First, gather the data that identifies your workers by location, role, and timing. Second, be sure to gain an understanding of contextual factors that influence outcomes but are unrelated to staffing (for example, stores may perform differently due to location, age, format, or season). This allows you to separate an individual&#39;s impact on outcomes from circumstantial factors. Third, collect performance outcome data for the unit; it&#39;s best to obtain multiple types of metrics, since outcomes are multidimensional.</p><p> In work we did with a national retailer, we gathered such data from hundreds of stores over five years. We measured monthly store performance by revenue, profit, growth, employee turnover, and breakage. We found that store managers matter a great deal: Twenty-one percent of revenue performance could be attributed to store managers — over three times more significant than store attributes — and they had an outsize impact on margins. Regional and district managers also produced measurable effects, but they were less influential than store managers. As expected, the impact of district and regional managers differed depending on the metric. While store managers had the strongest influence on revenues, margin performance was more strongly influenced by district and regional managers, who had significant input into purchasing decisions.</p><p> Just as in soccer, structure and systems matter. Our research found that stores that were closer to headquarters performed better, motivating the further exploration of how stores farther afield could be supported. There is also valuable insight to be gained from employee mobility. When people stay in their roles and locations, it is impossible to use data to disentangle the impact of people from their surrounding circumstances. Moving people through different settings not only gives them a chance to develop and grow, it also enhances the data, allowing more precise measurements of the impact of roles and the people performing them.</p><p></p><p> For the retailer we worked with, these insights changed the talent strategy. Originally, the leaders were moving toward creating a training academy program for district and regional managers, having assumed that higher-status managers with a broader scope of responsibilities would matter more to performance. After considering the results of our analysis, they pivoted to explore what behaviors and practices mattered in the critical role of the store manager. They launched a companywide effort to find out, modeling their approach on Google&#39;s internal research called Project Oxygen, to distill the attributes of managers who positively influenced company performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Once they had identified the details of this critical role, they were able to apply focused investment in developing and replicating capabilities for the job at scale.</p><h3> Talent Insights and Sustainable Competitive Advantage</h3><p> Billy Beane of the Oakland Athletics used data to build a high-performing team at a surprisingly low cost. His strategy as a general manager was to use different performance metrics to find undervalued players who contributed more to winning games than players who performed well on traditional measures. The success of this approach was quickly copied throughout the league, dissipating the A&#39;s strategic advantage. Could an advantage from data-driven talent decisions on crucial roles also be so short-lived?</p><p> There is a key difference to note. The Athletics studied measures that identified great players — but these players could be great on any team. The hallmark of a good strategy is one where the sources of competitive advantage are interlocked with other strategic commitments, making it difficult to copy. Finding key roles and building an organization around those roles may be more defensible than finding hidden stars, since the strategic advantage is tied to how organizations support these roles and develop pipelines to fill them.</p><p> The Bundesliga is known not only for its defense game but also for how it sources talent. It lacks the financial muscle of leagues such as the Premier League, with its billionaire owners. However, the German soccer system&#39;s commitment to developing young talent over relying on high-priced transfers of proven stars makes it an attractive option for young players who need to prove themselves with time on the field — including young players from outside Germany. Because other leagues that have paid dearly for high-priced transfers are obligated to play such talent for more minutes, they have diminished value propositions for younger, emerging talent. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Like Beane&#39;s winning Athletics team, there is an advantage in arbitraging on the undervalued, be it defensive players or younger players. However, unlike this Major League Baseball case, imitating the Bundesliga advantage will require a substantial adjustment to strategy — one that many teams and even leagues are not prepared to make.</p><h3> Execute Based on Differentiating Capabilities</h3><p> Strategy is about defining how to win — it requires committing to capabilities that are unambiguously the best in class. But no company can be the best at everything; a winning strategy requires focus and a keen awareness of what roles are disproportionately critical — and investing appropriately. Failing to acknowledge this puts the entire strategy at risk. By translating abstract capabilities into concrete jobs, organizations are much better positioned to make their strategies a reality.</p><p> Leaders can take a page from the soccer playbook and consider the following lessons for their own organizations:</p><p> <strong>Know your critical roles and where you need to invest.</strong> Despite being a less visible role, defenders matter more than other positions for winning soccer games. Insight into where difference-making roles exist should guide attention and investment when it comes to recruiting, developing, and retaining talent. While it is important to know your key contributors, it is just as important to know where you have deficits in critical roles.</p><p> Additionally, critical roles may change over time. As the competitive landscape evolves, difference-making positions can also change. Winning consistently requires monitoring not only what the critical roles are but how they might be shifting.</p><p></p><p> Investing in critical roles is not just about finding amazing talent — it is also about creating the required systems and practices that focus on positions first, and the people who fill them second. It&#39;s tempting to be blinded by the brightness of stars and give in to eagerly absorbing them regardless of what position they take. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Building a system around such stars makes organizations fragile: They become overdependent on them and distracted from the goal of aligning strategy with talent deployment.</p><p> <strong>Use data where you can, and invest in making it informative.</strong> When you have multiunit structures in your organization, you can exploit that to study roles systematically. Many companies have invested in systems that measure the performance of business units, products, regions, or stores. It takes additional investment to connect this information to personnel data, since most organizations do not explicitly link organizational performance and human resource information. Additionally, it&#39;s common to opt for the ease of keeping people in fixed locations instead of rotating them through different settings. But the practice of introducing some variance in how and where people work can create incredible insights into what roles drive performance. Such insights can highlight the contributions of unsung heroes and highlight where investments in training and recruiting can yield the most substantial gains in performance.</p><p> <strong>Hire for and develop based on key skills.</strong> Today, seniority and pedigree are too influential in talent markets; moreover, they have the effect of entrenching common wisdom about what matters within a role. Just as leaders can be misguided about what roles matter most, they can also be led astray about what skills and behaviors within those roles make the difference. By identifying critical capabilities within critical roles, organizations can both reward what matters and develop the blueprint for hiring, retaining, and developing employees with such skills in mind.</p><p> <strong>Align systems and structure.</strong> Talented employees in critical roles need to be supported with systems and structures that play to their strengths. Similar to the way Bundesliga teams have found that prioritizing the defense roles in field positioning increases the odds of success, organizations need to think creatively about what structure frees those in critical jobs to do their best work. These investments both enable more contributions from your critical roles and make your strategy less vulnerable to replication.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize leadership&#39;s critical role.</strong> On soccer teams, coaches are the third-most-important factor to winning games. Leaders set strategy and then build and motivate the team that supports it. Because alignment across the organization is so critical, any meaningful step to identify, invest in, and develop critical roles needs support from the top. This is especially important when a change in strategy requires building up talent in a critical role that has historically been weak. Leaders need to reinforce their commitment to supporting new key roles with their teams and with potential hires.</p><p></p><p> In soccer, winning can hinge on very small differences. While good teamwork is critical, the highly integrated nature of the sport obscures what the critical roles are. The thoughtful use of data can shed light on the critical roles within your team and uncover surprising results that challenge conventional wisdom. Having insight on critical roles may not only inform your strategy — it may be a source of competitive advantage in itself.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thriving in the New World of Work</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriella Rosen Kellerman. <p>Gabriella Rosen Kellerman is chief innovation officer at BetterUp and coauthor of <cite>Tomorrowmind: Thriving at Work With Resilience, Creativity, and Connection ― Now and in an Uncertain Future</cite> (Atria Books, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Wellness]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book Tomorrowmind, have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled. During Work/23, an MIT Sloan [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book <cite>Tomorrowmind</cite> , have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled.</p><p> During <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023, Kellerman and Seligman explained that they use the acronym <em>PRISM</em> to refer to those five skills. It starts with <em>prospection</em> — the ability to imagine our options, plan for the future, and restore our agency — which Kellerman described as “the meta skill of our era.” The others are <em>resilience</em> , <em>innovation</em> , <em>social connection</em> , and <em>mattering</em> . All of them can be learned, the coauthors said, and leaders can help their employees do so.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Kellerman and Seligman&#39;s work builds on seminal research Seligman conducted with the US Army to understand which soldiers are most at risk of experiencing post-traumatic stress disorder. He found that people with extreme pessimism — catastrophizers who believe that when bad events occur, everything will fall apart — are most vulnerable. His research also found that soldiers who demonstrate high positive emotion, low negative emotion, and high optimism on Day One are better positioned to withstand their environments and even go on to be awarded medals for heroism.</p><p> “I&#39;ve worked on resilience my entire 60 years in psychology,” Seligman said. “The people who were invulnerable, who are resilient, are the optimists.”</p><p> Resilience draws on self-awareness and self-compassion, they explained. “Emotional regulation is, in some ways, the foundational skill of maturing as an adult,” noted Kellerman. “It&#39;s our ability to recognize our emotions, to pause in response to them, to reappraise them, and then to choose a response.” That response, she added, ideally comes from a thoughtful, centered place rather than an emotionally reactive one.</p><p> Kellerman and Seligman weren&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the Work/23 event, so Kellerman answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><p></p><h6> Why is it that, in some cases, self-efficacy and confidence are seen as negative traits, irrespective of knowledge or skills?</h6><p> <em>Self-efficacy</em> is our belief in our own ability to act in the ways we need to in order to achieve our goals. We build self-efficacy by witnessing our own successes as we build mastery in specific domains. Many decades of studies have shown the positive relationship between self-efficacy and well-being and accomplishment.</p><p> In contrast, <em>self-esteem</em> — often defined as confidence in our own abilities — is a less robust construct and can be falsely inflated. It may or may not be related to actual accomplishments. As our colleague Roy Baumeister has demonstrated, <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1111/1529-1006.01431">self-esteem does not predict performance or well-being</a> .</p><p> People with high degrees of self-efficacy may not come across as confident to others, and people who do come across as confident may or may not have high degrees of self-efficacy. Confidence becomes a negative trait when it is false or narcissistic, but neither characteristic applies to self-efficacy.</p><h6> Are there studies correlating pessimism, PTSD, and suicide?</h6><p>是的。 Pessimism is a common feature of depression, and a significant risk factor for suicide. See, for example, “ <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/257552463_An_Examination_of_OptimismPessimism_and_Suicide_Risk_in_Primary_Care_Patients_Does_Belief_in_a_Changeable_Future_Make_a_Difference">An Examination of Optimism/Pessimism and Suicide Risk in Primary Care Patients: Does Belief in a Changeable Future Make a Difference?</a> ”</p><p> <em>Catastrophization</em> , an extreme form of pessimism, is predictive of PTSD risk. Catastrophization has also been shown to have a causal relationship with PTSD severity; see “ <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32479704/">The Sequential Relation Between Changes in Catastrophizing and Changes in Posttraumatic Stress Disorder Symptom Severity</a> .”</p><h6> What skill do you recommend that people choose first for growth?</h6><p> This will vary for every person. For those who are low on resilience, start there. Specifically, focus on the five following skills that drive resilience: emotional regulation, self-efficacy, cognitive agility, self-compassion, and optimism. Which of the five do you feel least comfortable with? Learn about it and look for ways to apply it in your day-to-day life.</p><p></p><p> Our book, <cite><a href="https://www.gabriellarosenkellerman.com/book">Tomorrowmind</a></cite> , includes exercises to build each of these in Chapter 4. For those who are already feeling resilient, pick another of the PRISM powers (prospection, resilience, innovation, social support, and mattering) to start with. [ <em>Editor&#39;s note: Kellerman and Seligman also explore the elements of PRISM in their recent</em> MIT SMR <em>article “<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reimagining-hr-for-better-well-being-and-performance/">Reimagining HR for Better Well-Being and Performance</a></em> .”]</p><h6> How can companies train their employees on these skills?</h6><p> All of these skills can be taught and developed. The best forms of training are personalized and longitudinal and include a mix of learning and practice. Human experts, like mentors or coaches, are an ideal resource, where available.</p><p> You can start with large-group experiences, like presentations or workshops, but don&#39;t stop there. Teach these skills to managers, and teach the managers how to teach those skills to the people who report to them. Look for ways to integrate practices that build these skills into your culture. All of them require practice over time in order to be sustained.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Countering the Corporate Diversity Backlash</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Victor Ray and Tsedale M. Melaku. <p>Victor Ray is the F. Wendell Miller Associate Professor in the departments of sociology and criminology and African American Studies at the University of Iowa and the author of <cite>On Critical Race Theory: Why It Matters &amp; Why You Should Care</cite> (Random House, 2022). Tsedale M. Melaku, Ph.D., is an assistant professor of management at the Zicklin School of Business at Baruch College (CUNY) and the author of <cite>You Don&#39;t Look Like a Lawyer: Black Women and Systemic Gendered Racism</cite> (Rowman and Littlefield, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com Corporate diversity is facing a backlash. Target, a company that has carried merchandise celebrating LGBTQ+ pride for over a decade, ordered some stores to remove such products after conservative activists accused the company of sexualizing children and organized a boycott. Anheuser-Busch lost sales in response to a promotion with trans influencer Dylan Mulvaney, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Ray_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Corporate diversity is facing a backlash. Target, a company that has carried merchandise celebrating LGBTQ+ pride for over a decade, ordered some stores to remove such products after conservative activists accused the company of sexualizing children and organized a boycott. Anheuser-Busch lost sales in response to a promotion with trans influencer Dylan Mulvaney, costing Bud Light its spot as America&#39;s bestselling beer. Even Chick-fil-A, perhaps the prototype of corporate conservatism with its opposition to same-sex marriage and policy of closing on Sundays, recently came under attack from conservatives for employing an executive to lead its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) efforts.</p><p> Universities are also facing a diversity backlash. The US Supreme Court recently struck down race-conscious admissions programs at Harvard and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill. Ending race-conscious admissions will likely have ripple effects, as an unclear regulatory environment might discourage organizations from implementing current diversity efforts while spurring some to explicitly exclude Black, Latine, and Indigenous groups.</p><p></p><p> These recent events show that resistance to civil rights progress for members of marginalized or underrepresented groups remains entrenched, and opponents of efforts to improve equity have been emboldened.</p><p> Diversity backlash puts companies in a difficult position. Bowing to pressure from anti-diversity groups may cost them the goodwill they have tried to cultivate among other consumers; Target&#39;s capitulation to conservative pressure earned it blowback from progressive activists. Backing down can also encourage conservative activists to push their demands further. While it might temporarily reduce the pressure on companies, giving in to anti-diversity forces could hurt them over the long term. Demographics are changing, with nonWhites making up an increasing portion of the coveted youth market, and legal protections for LGBTQ+ Americans have broad <a href="https://thehill.com/changing-america/respect/equality/599240-support-for-lgbtq-rights-on-the-rise-poll/">support</a> . Rooting out discrimination and increasing access to opportunity is essential to ensuring a rich talent pipeline. And for many individual managers and employees, anti-discrimination is simply a moral imperative.</p><p> Diversity initiatives are vulnerable to attack because many have been tentative. One-off hours-long training sessions, unsupported new hires, or programs that wither as anti-racist protests recede fall far short of the transformative structural changes needed to make organizational outcomes truly equitable. Leaders who are sincerely committed to diversity must prepare for the cost of defending inclusive organizations and adopt policies that make it difficult to roll back diversity gains.</p><p></p><h3> A Tepid Embrace of Diversity</h3><p> When President Lyndon Johnson signed the 1964 Civil Rights Act, with Martin Luther King Jr. present, he was responding to decades of agitation for full economic inclusion. Under the act&#39;s Title VII, the commonplace racial discrimination foundational to American workplaces became illegal. Most organizations that adopted diversity policies did so because social movements forced their hand, not out of a high-minded commitment to equal opportunity.</p><p> Many organizations retroactively recognized that greater diversity helped <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2019/04/business-case-for-diversity-in-the-workplace/">them</a> exploit niche markets or foster innovation. But arguments that diversity can be good for the bottom line haven&#39;t led to a fundamental transformation of segregated and racially stratified American workplaces. And relying on a business case for diversity lets leaders withdraw support for these initiatives if economic gains don&#39;t materialize.</p><p> While civil rights laws drove real workplace changes, they were largely marginal. Despite early gains in Black and Latine employment, workplace desegregation essentially stopped in the <a href="https://www.russellsage.org/publications/documenting-desegregation">1980s</a> , and hiring discrimination against Black <a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1706255114">men</a> has been relatively constant since. When hired, people of color were often designated to diversity positions cordoned off from the organization&#39;s core functions, limiting opportunities for their career growth and mobility. Enforcement of anti-discrimination laws varied greatly depending on the political winds, typically (but not exclusively) increasing under Democratic presidents and waning under Republicans. As sociologists Frank Dobbin and Alexandra <a href="https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/abs/10.1146/annurev-soc-090820-023615">Kalev</a> have found in their research, attempts to comply with an uncertain regulatory environment led companies to adopt diversity policies with dubious effectiveness. Human resources experts often introduced policies that courts countenanced as good-faith anti-discrimination efforts, despite the policies being ineffective and sometimes counterproductive.</p><p> Diversifying organizations rarely undermined the White norms and the <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0003122418822335">power</a> that shaped them. Homogeneity remained the standard, diversity a deviation. Acknowledging the changes brought to workplaces by the Civil Rights Movement, Kimberlé Crenshaw and <a href="https://thenewpress.com/books/critical-race-theory">colleagues</a> nonetheless highlighted in their 1996 book <cite>Critical Race Theory</cite> the unequal ground on which diversity policies were seeded: “The very same Whites who administered explicit policies of segregation and racial domination kept their jobs as decision makers in employment offices of companies, admissions offices of schools, lending offices of banks, and so on.”</p><p> This history of organizations&#39; tepid embrace of diversity has left them unprepared to deal with the current backlash. Three short years after their collective response to massive protests over the police murder of George Floyd, companies are reneging on their diversity <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/esg/host-of-companies-sued-alleging-unmet-diversity-equity-pledges">pledges</a> . Promises included increasing the representation of marginalized groups and women in senior-level positions and boards; addressing retention, promotion, and pay gaps; and working with senior leaders and managers on upskilling inclusive leadership behaviors. Companies added positions focused on DEI to demonstrate their intentions to tackle injustice, without transforming in ways that would support long-term organizational changes.</p><p></p><p> A slowing economy and, we suspect, a diversity backlash led companies to cut those new DEI positions at a faster <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/diversity-roles-disappear-three-years-george-floyd-protests-inspired-rcna72026">rate</a> than other jobs. Attacks on DEI have led some organizations to backtrack from their commitments to create initiatives centered on addressing organizational policies, practices, and cultures that target groups facing persistent inequities. Attempts to integrate substantive DEI programs also succumbed to the backlash, as evidenced by <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/business-and-practice/coca-cola-scraps-diversity-requirements-for-outside-law-firms">Coca-Cola</a> abandoning its proposed DEI policy for outside law firms. Some activist shareholders have attacked companies&#39; DEI <a href="https://www.mvalaw.com/media/news/15112_WLT_McDowell.pdf">interventions</a> and also targeted the practice of DEI audits, which help mitigate workplace discrimination.</p><h3> Confront the Resistance</h3><p> Although we&#39;ve outlined a pessimistic story, diversity programs can succeed. Research <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/000312240607100404">shows</a> that diversity programs are effective when organizations dedicate specialized positions to manage and monitor equity goals and programs.</p><p> Accountability is <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/02/dei-initiatives-are-futile-without-accountability">key</a> to sustaining effective DEI policies and programs. While equity work should involve all employees, DEI professionals must be empowered to hold the leadership accountable. Organization leaders must take responsibility for designing, modeling, and implementing equity programs that reshape organizational policy. Research shows that strategic DEI initiatives, including establishing mentoring programs that incentivize employees to sponsor marginalized group members, demonstrating transparency in hiring and promotion processes, and holding employees accountable for diversity goals, can work.</p><p> The latest backlash against diversity should prepare organizational leaders for possible resistance to diversity initiatives from internal stakeholders and external anti-diversity activists. Making public statements in support of DEI can help establish accountability goals, but unfortunately, it seems that a growing number of leaders are choosing silence or capitulation in response to anti-diversity activists.</p><p> We see a similar phenomenon in how the right-wing rejection of climate science has led some leaders to downplay sustainability goals, a practice known as <em>greenhushing</em> . A recent <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/0047287520930087">study</a> examining this dynamic in the hospitality industry found that consumers preferred when hotels communicated their corporate social responsibility efforts rather than engaging in greenhushing. Interestingly, the study found that such communications also prompted consumers to consider the ethics of their own choices. Similarly, we believe that openly discussing an organization&#39;s commitment to address systemic issues through accountability reduces resistance to initiatives that can change behaviors and attitudes and lead to progress.</p><p></p><p> Organizations should confront the diversity backlash, along with the empty nature of superficial diversity policies, head-on. With diversity training increasingly criticized and White fatigue derailing serious discussions of racism, racial inclusion in organizations faces an existential threat. Resisting this diversity retreat requires organizational accountability to the broad array of commitments made in response to acknowledged racial injustices.</p><p> For organizations committed to embedding equity within their mission, values, culture, and practices, we recommend taking a strategic planning approach. Expectations for overnight results must be regulated by realistic goals that are results-oriented and measurable, with targeted dates for completion. This process must include a feedback loop design that allows for corrections in planning, implementing, and executing, thus providing managers with openings to check for impact and progress. Recent events give organizations an opportunity to reaffirm and strengthen their commitments to working toward creating an equitable organization by stamping out inequality.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Outlawing Collegiate Affirmative Action Will Impact Corporate America</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Derek R. Avery. <p>Derek R. Avery is the CT Bauer Chair of Inclusive Leadership at the University of Houston&#39;s Bauer College of Business.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Recruiting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equality]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avery-Extension-a4312ir2142-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college admissions, we can draw upon existing data to forecast the impact on corporate America. The evidence clearly points to two key outcomes: First, collegiate patterns of racioethnic diversity will change fairly dramatically; and second, these changes will have considerable downstream consequences for workplace composition as well as patterns of racioethnic inequity across a host of other measures.</p><p> As tempting as it might be to view those conclusions as hyperbolic, research on three decades of state-level affirmative action bans strongly suggests otherwise. In fact, eradicating affirmative action has led to reductions in the proportions of underrepresented (Black and Hispanic) students in undergraduate and graduate programs, particularly in science, technology, engineering, and math; it has also led to fewer underrepresented students enrolled in and graduating from medical and law schools. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These effects tend to be lasting — and, importantly, implementing alternative policies that don&#39;t explicitly consider race and ethnicity has done little to counter them. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p> Extending these state-level findings to the national level suggests that employers will have less racioethnically diverse college-educated talent to draw upon when filling their vacancies, particularly from premier institutions. Alternatively, the Black and Hispanic candidates within their applicant pools are less likely to be selected because they will be less credentialed as a result of having fewer degrees or having graduated from lower-ranked colleges, where they are more likely to apply and be accepted post-affirmative action. A somewhat less-intuitive consequence is that the White (and Asian) graduates of more prestigious colleges and universities will have had less exposure to people of other racioethnic backgrounds. This has implications for their multicultural competence — the ability to relate to those dissimilar from oneself — and may help account for why employers tend to pay higher starting salaries to graduates of more racioethnically diverse business schools and universities. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> The fallout within Black and Hispanic communities stands to be devastating. Most notably, there will be fewer minority professionals to help meet the needs of racioethnically similar minority clientele. Though this might seem to be more a matter of convenience, it is especially troubling in fields like medicine or law (which employs attorneys and members of law enforcement), where minority underrepresentation is often noted as a contributing factor to well-documented racioethnic health care and criminal justice disparities. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Lower odds of graduating from a more prestigious school or graduating at all also have implications for racioethnic inequality within organizations. This begins with underrepresented minorities being less apt to obtain a job or more likely to land a lower-quality one. It goes on to influence outcomes spanning the entire human resources management landscape, from entry to exit, because initial placements have lasting consequences for things like compensation, promotions, training/development, retention/separation, and deployment. For instance, even Black and Hispanic professionals who gain access to employment opportunities may be more likely to find themselves facing the “last hired, first fired” phenomenon. Moreover, a low starting salary can affect the size of raises or competitive offers from other companies and has deleterious compounding effects on one&#39;s retirement savings.</p><p></p><p> Those seeking even more concrete evidence that outlawing collegiate affirmative action can influence diversity in corporate America need look no further than recent research by Harvard Business School professor Letian Zhang. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> He examined affirmative action bans&#39; effect on whether people from different racial backgrounds became managers, using data from the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission on more than 11,000 private-sector US businesses from 1985 to 2015. He anticipated that executives might interpret bans as a sort of license to discriminate and, therefore, be less likely to hire Black managers or promote Black candidates. The results showed that “after a state adopts the affirmative action ban, growth in the proportion of Black managers in establishments with corporate headquarters in that state slows down by more than 50% and this slowdown is mostly concentrated in firms with politically conservative CEOs.”</p><p> By widening the collegiate achievement gap, the ban on affirmative action in colleges actually kicks the proverbial can of equal opportunity further down the road by adding larger higher education differentials to existing racial differences in wealth and access to quality preschool and K-12 education that also disfavor underrepresented minorities. Ironically, this further enhances the need for workplace affirmative action strategies just to maintain the racial status quo. That said, any such efforts will almost certainly be challenged along legal grounds, and the Supreme Court (at least as currently constituted) has shown itself highly unlikely to view such efforts favorably.</p><p></p><p> In fact, in a form of preemptive strike, 13 state attorneys general recently informed companies such as Apple, Microsoft, and Uber that they should expect greater scrutiny of any policies perceived as promoting race-based preferences in employee selection. They went on to promise legal action against “violators,” signaling their intention to extend the parameters of the Supreme Court ruling to US workplaces. This raises the question, what can organizations that remain committed to racial equal employment opportunity do to limit any losses they might suffer in this new, evolving employment landscape? Below, I provide four suggestions to help practitioners, managers, and organizations navigate this challenge.</p><p></p><h3> Don&#39;t Wait on the Sidelines</h3><p> President Theodore Roosevelt is often credited with saying, “In any moment of decision, the best thing you can do is the right thing, the next best thing is the wrong thing, and the worst thing you can do is nothing.” In the wake of the Supreme Court ruling, it is probably tempting to maintain business as usual, wait and see how things proceed, and adopt a reactionary approach as the dust settles. Doing so, however, promises to have considerable consequences. Namely, continuing to source applicants from the same schools while making no adjustments based on the predictable changes to student-body compositions leaves an organization entirely dependent on college admissions staffs to retool their strategies to solve a problem that few have been able to address in the past 30 years.</p><p> Accordingly, continuing to use degrees and degree-granting institutions as proxies for human capital, as many organizations historically have, will likely result in race differentials widening across virtually all employment outcomes, with cascading effects for nonemployment outcomes. For instance, a recent study showed that underrepresented minority youth tend to increase their engagement in risky behaviors (smoking cigarettes, alcohol use, and binge drinking) immediately following an affirmative action ban. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In short, expect to have fewer underrepresented minority employees and greater racial inequity, including larger differentials in earnings and advancement.</p><h3> Question Everything</h3><p> Well, you might not have to question everything, but if an organization wants to get better at something, it will need to do some things differently and examine how they&#39;ve been done in the past. For instance, an HR executive once told me that it was company policy to recruit only from the country&#39;s top 10 engineering programs. An unintended consequence of this practice was that new recruits came from geographic regions that were quite dissimilar to the company&#39;s locale, and new-hire turnover was unusually high for its industry. There was no qualitative difference between the No. 10 program and the No. 12 program, which was located within 100 miles. Why not recruit from the No. 12 program to reduce the chance of a new employee experiencing extreme culture shock and leaving within the first year?</p><p> Applying this logic in the current context, companies might need to broaden their search parameters to attract applicant pools that are demographically consistent with those of their recent past. Recruiting at historically Black colleges and universities and Hispanic-serving institutions is a good way of engaging in targeted recruitment — a strategy that is presently legally permissible. Placing online advertisements in places frequented by underrepresented minorities conveys that your organization is interested in receiving applications from members of these groups. Moreover, when it comes to selection and compensation, companies will need to reevaluate the implicit and explicit weights assigned to degree-granting institutions. The spoils of graduating from a premier institution are already distributed inconsistently, with larger benefits for White graduates than for Black degree holders. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Why not make that benefit smaller for everyone and simultaneously open more employment opportunities to a larger group?</p><h3> Lean Into the Data</h3><p> To address the issues raised by questioning everything, organizations can turn to what their data reveals. For instance, though inertia and benchmarking against competitors may suggest that a job requires a college degree, does the data support that contention? Job requirements that are linked to racial differences, like degree attainment and earning degrees from highly prestigious schools, tend to have an adverse impact on underrepresented groups — a form of statistical discrimination. In the context of selection, adverse impact occurs when a particular decision-making tool advantages members of one racial group (or any other legally protected category) relative to members of another racial group. While such differences are not illegal if the difference is job relevant, data is needed to establish such relevance.</p><p> Requiring degrees, favoring graduates of elite schools, and using minimum GPA cutoffs can adversely impact underrepresented minorities when such requirements are not directly related to job performance. In the past several years, there&#39;s been more discussion of eliminating these types of requirements, not only to enhance racial justice but also to simply tap a larger pool of high-potential candidates in a tight job market. Although some may interpret this as a form of “lowering standards” to enhance diversity, it should be noted that standards unrelated to performance are unnecessary and potentially illegal and may result in employee overqualification, which can have negative implications for hires&#39; attitudes, well-being, and performance. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Use your data (and that of relevant others) to determine job relevance and get rid of barriers that aren&#39;t boosting your bottom line.</p><h3> Select for Potential, and Train for Performance</h3><p> Though colleges invest considerable resources in preparing students for careers, there are inevitable shortfalls in the competency levels that graduates possess and employers desire. For instance, the National Association of Colleges and Employers indicates that employers are nearly unanimous in naming communication as the most important competency, and almost all students know this. Nevertheless, though 80% of students rate themselves extremely proficient at communication, only 47% of employers see students in this same light. The point is that more than half of employers see graduates as lacking the most important competency. Clearly, the 53% of employers that consider college graduates less than extremely proficient communicators are not leaving their vacancies unfilled. If they were, the unemployment rate for 2022 college graduates would not be 4%. Rather, many, if not most, employers recognize that they will need to invest in training to get new hires up to speed.</p><p></p><p> Identifying potential in a race-neutral yet valid way is certainly easier said than done. Generally speaking, the more closely the indicators used to select employees relate to what employees actually do, the better. This suggests that tools like high-fidelity simulations, work samples, and behaviorally anchored structured interviews may be particularly useful. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Selection approaches should also focus on identifying trainability to ensure that organizations are able to maximize returns on their training investments. This could entail giving top candidates an opportunity to demonstrate their trainability by actively learning a new job-relevant competency and subsequently demonstrating their proficiency.</p><p></p><p> Over the past half century, affirmative action and its progeny have helped transform the racioethnic landscape of American colleges, universities, and organizations. These programs have done so by providing opportunities to those who history suggests would otherwise have been unlikely (or at least considerably less likely) to receive them. The choice of word — <em>opportunity</em> — is both intentional and important, as many people often lose sight of the fact that these programs grant beneficiaries only the chance to show that they belong. Although the Supreme Court decision eliminated one means of helping to level the playing field, as Alexander Graham Bell once said, “When one door closes, another opens.” Though the path may seem somewhat less clear, innovative companies will create and maintain competitive advantages by finding, attracting, and selecting the most talented people from <em>all</em> racial and ethnic backgrounds.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Make Your Case for Communication Upskilling</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a> is CEO of <a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a> , a communication company in the Silicon Valley. She&#39;s the author of six books, including <cite>DataStory: Explain Data and Inspire Action Through Story</cite> (Ideapress Publishing, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[ROI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It’s hard to find a job posting that doesn’t mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Duarte-Upskilling-ROI-pie-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It&#39;s hard to find a job posting that <em>doesn&#39;t</em> mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that candidates actually have and those that they&#39;re weak in, hiring managers find themselves making trade-offs, particularly to meet pressing technical needs: <em>This guy can code like there&#39;s no tomorrow, but his communication is a challenge. Let&#39;s get him in here fast. We&#39;ll coach him up. It can wait.</em></p><p> The thing is, communication skills <em>can&#39;t</em> wait. Executives in “people functions” like human resources and learning and development (L&amp;D) understand that communication and persuasion skills are critical in all areas of business — even software development and accounting. Those who design, manage, implement, and track employee development programs already know the business benefits of being adept at influencing colleagues and others in an organization.</p><p></p><p> So how do you also show the deep skeptics in your organization — for instance, data scientists who view the word <em>persuasion</em> with disdain, as a euphemism for <em>manipulation</em> — that a serious investment in communication skills is worth making?</p><p> You do it by making a solid case for the return on that investment. And you can take your cues from those folks in L&amp;D. They&#39;ve thought long and hard about ways to measure the ROI of their training programs and the best ways to communicate the benefits of those talents.</p><h3> A Measurement-Based Case for Better Soft Skills</h3><p> At a recent event for my company&#39;s customers, our executive vice president of customers led a panel discussion on the ways that large technical brands are building soft skills and what the ROI has been for them. Two L&amp;D executives shared what they&#39;ve discovered about conveying that value in their organizations: Catherine (Cat) Lang, who heads up product training and certification for customers and partners at ServiceNow, a digital workflow company based in Santa Clara, Calif.; and Noelle Anderson, the director of enablement at Snap, the parent company for visual messaging app Snapchat. Here are five key insights from their conversation.</p><h4> Collect examples of the ROI you&#39;ve seen from previous training.</h4><p> One way to start is to think back to previous learning efforts in your organization and see what dots you can connect for stakeholders. For instance, did an in-house workshop on presenting data precede a big win for your organization — like landing a lucrative project or winning a major client? Make that correlation explicit and point to others like it. You might already have more of an ROI track record for some of your soft skills training than you realize.</p><p></p><h4> Help identify the value of future training.</h4><p> When you&#39;re considering or developing future training, look for more direct ways to measure upskilling outcomes. At Snap, for instance, the enablement team has developed a pitch-coaching program in which salespeople, account managers, and creative strategists work together to develop pitches for existing clients. Participants receive lots of coaching and developmental feedback from seasoned communicators while formulating, framing, and practicing their pitches — a big incentive to sign up for the program. They also create real, measurable value by workshopping real pitch content.</p><p> The payoff — whether it&#39;s a renewed contract or the sale of a new product or service — is quantifiable. “What we&#39;ve done on the back end,” Anderson said, “is work with our CRM teams to create a check box in Salesforce to denote whether or not each presentation was part of our pitch program.” From there, the team can filter to see which pitches brought in revenue.</p><p> Although Anderson&#39;s group at Snap reports to the sales team rather than to corporate L&amp;D, they collaborate with L&amp;D as a “sister team” to identify and build soft skills needed on the sales side. That&#39;s an approach that can pay dividends in both directions: Teams throughout organizations can report back to L&amp;D with evidence of ROI in their areas, which supports further investment in companywide learning programs. For its part, the learning organization can share broader insights on what types of development drive employee satisfaction and retention. And L&amp;D can hone its skill-building programs in light of where teams are seeing the greatest impact on day-to-day performance and sales.</p><h4> Recognize qualitative impact — including better employee retention.</h4><p> Even with something like a pitch program in place, it&#39;s tough to tally up the costs of soft skills training in cold, hard dollars — especially when the training is conducted internally by HR staff members or informally by managers and colleagues. The benefits can be tricky to gauge, too, since much of the value in upskilling is indirect.</p><p> For instance, consider one of the pitch program&#39;s key benefits for employees: greater visibility with senior leadership. That pays off for both individuals and the organization, but not in a way that shows up immediately on the balance sheet. Anderson said that batches of pitches are developed and presented in rounds, and by the third round, the two groups with the best pitches get to present their ideas to the executive team for more feedback before sharing anything with clients.</p><p> Sure, these interactions with executives make the pitches themselves better. But think about the other benefits: They kick-start mentoring relationships, and they open up more development and growth opportunities and more doors to advancement — all of which can enhance the employee experience, motivation, and loyalty.</p><p> Can you quantify these results? Sometimes you can&#39;t, so you gauge value qualitatively. That can mean soliciting input from managers and team leaders on a training program&#39;s impact on employees&#39; behavior, effectiveness on the job, and approach to teamwork. Considering the qualitative impact from the employee&#39;s perspective is essential, too, because talent retention has major implications for ROI. For proof of why these intangibles matter, consider a <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/03/09/majority-of-workers-who-quit-a-job-in-2021-cite-low-pay-no-opportunities-for-advancement-feeling-disrespected/">Pew Research Center 2022 survey</a> that found a tie between “no opportunities for advancement” and “pay was too low” as the top reasons US workers cited for leaving their jobs. Or consider the findings of LinkedIn&#39;s March 2022 “ <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220506202443/https://business.linkedin.com/glint/resources/employee-well-being-report-march-2022">Employee Well-Being Report</a> ,” which found the No. 1 driver of work culture to be “opportunities to learn and grow.”</p><p> Lang said that at ServiceNow, her team is “looking at employee retention and satisfaction with development” and tying those “very, very closely to our employee voice surveys as well” to get a holistic view of the effects of upskilling on retention. She said she saw “quick uptake as we started piloting new soft skills programs.” People have demonstrated keen interest in this type of upskilling at Snap, too: Anderson said employees view it as evidence that the company values them because it&#39;s “demonstrating [its] belief in an individual by investing in them and their development.” She also noted, “These are the types of skills that can help people internally get their own momentum, their own movement, and get their own thoughts put forth in a way in which folks will actually respond.”</p><h4> Strategize about which kinds of jobs to focus on first.</h4><p> Like any organizational change effort, upskilling a workforce requires strategic planning. To help such an initiative gain traction, it&#39;s useful to identify where you&#39;ll see the greatest immediate payoff and plan to concentrate there before you roll things out more broadly.</p><p></p><p> Lang&#39;s group at ServiceNow focuses first on people at the director and senior director levels because they have such a big say in how work gets done day to day and are responsible for keeping employees&#39; efforts aligned with organizational goals. The sooner they&#39;re communicating those goals clearly and framing performance objectives compellingly, the sooner the company will reap the rewards of hitting those targets. Attending to people at the director and senior director levels first also creates a cascade effect, equipping them to share what they&#39;re learning with their teams through one-on-one coaching, mentoring conversations, and even recommendations for courses or other learning content.</p><p> Snap, on the other hand, prefers to upskill front-line managers first, Anderson said. Because she oversees learning in a sales organization, where employees&#39; communication skills have an immediate impact on client relationships, the front line is where she sees the quickest return on investment.</p><h4> Address the time crunch head-on.</h4><p></p><p> Even if an organization&#39;s stakeholders agree that, in an ideal world, they should prioritize helping employees with soft skills, time constraints can make it tough. In the perennial battle between the important and the urgent, the urgent tends to win leaders&#39; attention and resources. Anderson described how what she calls “the here and now” sometimes gets in the way of broader learning goals at Snap: “There have been many classes where folks are like, &#39;I&#39;m so excited. I can&#39;t wait to go.&#39; And they show up, but then they have to drop out.” Work commitments and deadlines often tear people away.</p><p></p><p> One way to address that challenge culturally is by openly acknowledging it and showing how you can accommodate it in your learning schedule and course design. Create the expectation that it&#39;s more than OK for people to engage only as they&#39;re able. Think about dicing up the content into shorter modules or mini-workshops that busy employees can more easily digest. Set aside time in the workday for skill development. Learners need this type of support in the workplace, and the organization benefits too. If executives balk, remind them that making learning doable increases the ROI <em>and</em> shores up employee commitment to the organization in a tight labor market.</p><p> You might need to adjust project deadlines a bit or give people fewer tasks while they&#39;re doing development work so they don&#39;t feel pressure to do their “real” work after hours. Development <em>is</em> real work. Treat it that way as a manager — and discuss it that way with your stakeholders. It&#39;ll be an easier sell if you&#39;ve taken steps to help them see all of the benefits of the investment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> CEOs Can Make (or Break) an Organization Redesign</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz. <p><a href="https://akordeon.com/who-we-are/">Herman Vantrappen</a> is the managing director of Akordeon, a strategic advisory firm based in Brussels. Frederic Wirtz heads The Little Group, advising companies on organization design issues worldwide. Vantrappen and Wirtz are the authors of <cite>The Organization Design Guide: A Pragmatic Framework for Thoughtful, Efficient and Successful Redesigns</cite> (Routledge, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com The Research This article draws on the dozens of major organization redesign exercises the authors have accompanied in the past 30 years across continents in a wide range of sectors, including B2B (such as payroll services) and B2C (such as fast-food retail), products (such as automotive) and services (such as engineering), and for-profit [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Vantrappen-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Page/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><p> This article draws on the dozens of major organization redesign exercises the authors have accompanied in the past 30 years across continents in a wide range of sectors, including B2B (such as payroll services) and B2C (such as fast-food retail), products (such as automotive) and services (such as engineering), and for-profit and nonprofit.</p></aside><p> One of a CEO&#39;s essential responsibilities is leading the effort to reconfigure their organization after recognizing that its structure is no longer optimal for creating and delivering value. Some redesigns are major companywide overhauls, such as Procter &amp; Gamble&#39;s creation of six industry-based sector business units in 2019, which its CEO described as “the most significant organization change we&#39;ve made in the last 20 years.” <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Other redesign efforts have a narrower scope, focusing on a particular division, function, or issue.</p><p> For a CEO, organization redesign is different from other large-scale change initiatives. In a corporate strategic reorientation, for instance, the CEO is bound by the decisions of the board of directors and follows a strongly analytical approach. In a functional initiative, such as setting the company&#39;s digital strategy, the CEO can delegate the lead to someone on the management team and assume a supervisory role. But in a corporate organization redesign initiative, the CEO must actively take the lead, both because of the profound impact that the resulting changes will have on the culture and employees and because only the CEO has the all-encompassing view required to reduce the risk of serious unintended and undesirable consequences from any particular redesign choice.</p><p></p><p> We have witnessed many redesign initiatives in our work with organizations over the years and have confirmed that the CEO&#39;s leadership of these efforts is key to their success. But we continue to be surprised by how many CEOs still struggle to get to effective outcomes. We&#39;ve found that plans frequently go astray or run into dead ends despite the abundant and often sensible advice in the management literature.这里有些例子：</p><ul><li> The new CEO of a business services provider wants to reconsider the role of the corporate center and the organization more broadly. Each member of the management team has their own pet idea for restructuring: One is under the spell of self-organizing teams, another is adamant about a framework used at their previous employer, and a third thinks the company should simply be a holding of small regional enterprises. It takes a long time to build even minimal alignment.</li><li> The CEO of a multilateral agency launches an exercise to make the organization less siloed. Heated debate and a couple of offsites with the management team lead to a number of major decisions, including plans for sharing resources and broadening the CEO&#39;s span of control. But after some backroom maneuvering, decisions are undone.</li><li> The founder-CEO of a family-owned engineering and construction company retires, handing over the reins to one of his children. The new leader has plans to professionalize the company&#39;s business processes and governance, but the retired founder keeps finding ways to short-circuit the CEO, undermining any effort to improve the company&#39;s functioning.</li></ul><p> When we looked back on the major organization redesigns we&#39;ve accompanied in the past 30 years (see “The Research”) and reflected on why some initiatives were less effective than others, we recognized that CEOs can fall into one of two traps: failing to use an appropriate framework, and, quite simply, failing to maintain sufficient leadership throughout the process. In this article, we&#39;ll present a systematic approach to organization redesign that CEOs can follow, and address specific behaviors that executives must guard against if they are to retain full ownership throughout the organization redesign and implementation processes.</p><h3> A Framework for Tackling Organization Redesign</h3><p> Many scholars and consultants have developed frameworks that support systematic thinking about organization design. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The framework we are presenting here emphasizes two aspects that are often underexposed.</p><p> First, the framework recognizes that managers never start with a blank slate when redesigning their organization. There is always an existing organization in place that heavily informs any redesign. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Even if the existing design has become dysfunctional, there are usually good reasons why it was adopted in the first place, and those reasons shouldn&#39;t be ignored. As a consequence, a good framework needs to incorporate a dynamic link between the past and the future.</p><p> Second, much of the current advice in the management literature focuses on either upstream aspects of an initiative (for instance, identifying the company&#39;s purpose, values, and vision) or downstream aspects (such as execution and change management). Less is said about the midstream core of the discipline — that is, the hard stuff, such as structure, processes, and systems. A good framework should rehabilitate this essential midstream part while integrating it seamlessly with the upstream part (by considering the drivers of change) and the downstream part (by ensuring readiness for the go-live on Day One).</p><p> The framework that we have gradually developed through our work aims to overcome those two shortcomings by respecting the dynamic nature of change and focusing on the hard organization design variables. Starting from the first principle, it brings together the building blocks of organization design thinking into a logical flow, from understanding an organization&#39;s <em>drivers of change</em> to the options for <em>concept design</em> , the operationalization in <em>detail design</em> , the implementation at the <em>transition</em> stage, and the course corrections necessary during the reorganization&#39;s actual <em>performance</em> . (See “The Organization Redesign Guide.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Organization Redesign Guide</h4><p class="caption"> This framework integrates familiar building blocks into a logical process flow to steer reorganization initiatives. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig1.jpg" alt="The Organization Redesign Guide"></p><p class="attribution"> Source: Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p> CEOs at the front end of an organization redesign need to be aware of five overarching principles that stand out in this framework:</p><p> <strong>1. Organization is a means to an end.</strong> Managers change an organization design with the expectation that the new design will better enable the company to achieve its business goals. That expectation is based on the assumption that those goals will be made explicit, embraced by the management team, endorsed by stakeholders, and remain reasonably stable. A company whose goals are vague or fluctuating is likely to cycle through disruptive organizational rearrangements without much improvement in its performance. That&#39;s why our design framework starts with identifying both the external and internal drivers of change.</p><p> <strong>2. The best possible design is unknowable.</strong> Making organization design choices is arguably more difficult than making business strategy choices. A strategy choice comes down to selecting the one of various alternatives that maximizes the defined objective — say, EBITDA growth. With strategy, leaders weigh the available information, the assumptions and uncertainties, resource constraints, and their own appetite for risk. Not so for organizational choices. They do not flow from a mathematical optimization but from a judgment about the weight of the arguments in favor of and against each of a number of design alternatives. That is why the design framework encourages CEOs to consider alternative organizational concepts.</p><p> <strong>3. Concept design precedes detail design — and only the latter is participative.</strong> At the concept stage, the principles for the new design are defined. Those involve fundamental organizational variables, in particular the architecture (for example, what to centralize and what to decentralize). <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> After considering alternative design concepts, one is selected and taken forward for detail design (for example, the roles of various functions in an end-to-end business process). The detail design can and should be done with the broad involvement of the managers and people directly concerned: They know best what works, will have to operate within the design outcome, and can act as change ambassadors. However, such a participative approach is rarely advised for concept design, which tends to require familiarity with the company&#39;s (often still confidential) vision and strategic options, freedom from conflicts of interest concerning the fate of various company functions, and speed.</p><p> <strong>4. An organization design evolves through a pattern of deliberate leaps and emergent hops.</strong> The notions of deliberate and emergent strategy are well entrenched in the discipline of strategy formulation: Guided by the company&#39;s deliberate strategy, managers at all levels in the organization make myriad decisions every day that gradually alter the exact form of that strategy. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> A similar pattern is observed in organization design: Senior management deliberately decides on a major rearrangement (leap) of the organization, after which a series of adjustments (hops) are made to compensate for the inevitable imperfections of the original design. This leap-and-hops pattern is totally normal and even desirable, since the perfect design is elusive and a company&#39;s environment changes all the time. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> That is why the design framework shows loops that feed imperfections back into the design so that they can be addressed.</p><p> <strong>5. The proof of the design is revealed only after Day One.</strong> Day One refers to the moment at which the approved detail design goes live and the redesign starts to have a direct impact on the daily functioning of a large number of people: what they do, how they do it, and with whom. As little as possible should go wrong, for the sake of managerial credibility, respect for people, and impact on the business. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> That is why it is crucial to start a careful change management process well ahead of Day One. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> No employee should be left in the dark about their place in the redesigned organization.</p><p></p><h3> Why the CEO&#39;s Continuous Engagement Matters</h3><p> In strategy formulation exercises, it may be perfectly adequate for the CEO to stay involved through ad hoc interventions spaced over time, such as participating in an executive offsite, leading the steering committee, or presenting to the board of directors. In organization design exercises, on the other hand, we find that the most effective CEOs keep their finger on the pulse of the process on an almost daily basis, from start to finish.</p><p> One reason they do this is that it provides them the opportunity to form their own ideas about a fit-for-purpose design and to possibly shift their mental model quite radically. They take their time to allow their thinking to mature, as there is no single best design and the eventual choice is a largely qualitative judgment about a number of valid alternatives.</p><p> They also consistently engage because they realize that the organization design process is quite unforgiving. Each phase builds on the choices made in the previous phase, gradually involving more and more people. The number of explicit or implicit micro-commitments made along the way — about roles, borders, lines, people, head count, and other factors — keeps growing. Having to backtrack is painful, in part because it is widely visible. If strategy formulation is like planting trees, organization design is like sowing grass: Its effect is immediate, all over the place, and in need of attention.</p><p></p><p> A third reason for daily engagement is to help build buy-in for the new design within the organization. Effective CEOs insist on participating fully in communications about the outcomes of the design exercise, not so much through the proverbial “memo to all staff” as by talking with people in the field. They can only do so credibly and convincingly if they have immersed themselves in the actual design work.</p><p> Most importantly, CEOs involve themselves in the process daily because they recognize that people and interactions will eventually make (or break) the organization. Fully participating in the design process gives CEOs a unique opportunity to observe and influence the people side of the business beyond their direct reports.</p><h3> How Leadership Weakness Can Derail Redesign</h3><p> In situations where we&#39;ve observed a leader&#39;s inability to remain fully in control of the redesign process as laid out above, their weaknesses have tended to reflect one of four characteristics: half-heartedness, appeasement, indecisiveness, or incapacitation. We&#39;ve distilled the following four archetypes from our observations of organization redesign efforts that have faltered:</p><p> <strong>The half-hearted CEO.</strong> Whereas the trigger of a strategy formulation exercise tends to be clear, an organization design exercise may be prompted by lobbying by certain stakeholders rather than a clear business need. In some cases, a member of the management team or the board of directors may raise a concern. The CEO might not initially find that concern important or be inclined to initiate change, but they might want to satisfy that stakeholder to end the debate and thus agree to consider organization redesign — with the private thought that the plans will go nowhere. Or the CEO may be confused, unclear, or cagey about the motivation for a redesign, leaving it to the project team to fill in the blanks. In still other cases, the CEO might be on their way out, voluntarily or involuntarily. In all of those situations, the CEO lacks a full-throated commitment at the inception of the project, getting it off to a bad start.</p><p> <strong>The appeasing CEO.</strong> Every transformation requires careful change management, with deliberate activities to move the company from its present state to the desired future state and help people adopt the changes. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> However, CEOs can go overboard when it comes to inviting people&#39;s involvement, which can result in an excessively complex process with too many steps, participants, and approval points. For example, inviting more comments instead of deciding and freezing the process can drag out the design phase. Appeasing behavior aimed at demonstrating a willingness to listen is often well intentioned and meant to function as stakeholder management — but it can also reflect the CEO&#39;s own uncertainty about the design concept.</p><p> <strong>The indecisive CEO.</strong> The decision-inept CEO who fails to make decisions or stick to firm decisions is rare but not extinct. A typical symptom is the CEO giving in to a late-stage “over my dead body” threat by a manager who disagrees with a well-thought-out executive team decision. CEOs will sometimes compromise in the final stretch out of a fear of negative fallout. In such organizations, things happen in spite of the CEO.</p><p> <strong>The incapacitated CEO.</strong> Defective governance can make it hard for the CEO to keep a grip on the redesign throughout the entire process. In companies where the CEO is not also the chair of the board of directors, the board might interfere with the CEO&#39;s handling of the organization redesign. In privately owned companies, powerful board members such as retired founders can meddle in the design and short-circuit the CEO, protecting old favorites or otherwise disrupting an orderly process. Such impairing of the CEO — whether during the concept design, detail design, or transition phase — is often visible at lower levels and highly damaging.</p><p> CEOs planning an organization redesign would be well advised to consider these patterns of weak leadership. They should assess their own vulnerability in terms of both their own traits and the contextual factors that hamstring their leadership, and then consider how to overcome them.</p><p> They can begin by asking themselves four questions:</p><ol><li> Do I fully believe in this initiative?</li><li> Will I listen to the right people without letting the process go off track?</li><li> Am I prepared to make tough decisions where needed and stick to them?</li><li> Am I in control of all the levers I will need to pull?</li></ol><p> Such soul-searching is important because once CEOs understand where their leadership of this critical change effort may be weak, they can work to mitigate those weaknesses. (See “How CEOs Can Diminish Their Vulnerability.”) Imagine a CEO who knows they tend to be appeasing. They might recognize that during the concept phase, they should consult with a restricted group of senior managers, and during the transition phase, they should adopt a kind of comply-or-explain process (when any deviation from the concept design must be explained and can only be accepted after approval by the governance body that had approved the concept) and freeze the design, reassuring employees that the company will make course corrections after launch as needed. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> How CEOs Can Diminish Their Vulnerability</h4><p class="caption"> CEOs who tend toward any of the four behavioral archetypes that can undermine organization redesign can take action at each stage of the process to strengthen their leadership. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig2.png" alt="How CEOs Can Diminish Their Vulnerability"></p><p class="attribution"> Source: Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p> We worked with the CEO of an industrial company who acknowledged that he had some elements of the incapacitated and indecisive archetypes. He was able to compensate for the tendencies that might have otherwise derailed the process, in a few smart, specific ways:</p><ul><li> Because the CEO traveled almost constantly, he appointed a chief change officer with complementary skills who worked closely with him and took care of day-to-day project matters at the head office. However, the CEO remained in charge of the effort.</li><li> The CEO proposed having the company&#39;s nomination and compensation committee act as a steering committee during the concept design phase. This provided a managed channel to the board chair, whose frequent intervention in operational matters sometimes undermined the CEO.</li><li> After the results of the concept design phase were formally endorsed by the nomination and compensation committee and approved by the board, the CEO was able to more easily implement the comply-or-explain rule during the detail design phase. To avoid concept creep, any deviation from the concept would have to pass through the committee again.</li><li> The CEO encouraged the company&#39;s divisions and functions to each appoint an ambassador for the transition phase. These representatives were on the management team of their respective divisions and functions and had participated in the detail design phase. They met with the chief change officer monthly to share progress information in both directions.</li><li> A simple tracker was used to monitor progress toward a range of specific transition targets in advance of the go-live. The percentage-of-completion statistics were regularly reviewed by the CEO and openly published based on division and function. This generated some healthy peer pressure and helped the process maintain traction.</li></ul><p></p><p> The example demonstrates that it pays for CEOs to do some upfront, explicit, and honest introspection about their visible behavioral tendencies and the actions that can prevent the redesign exercise from derailing.</p><p></p><p> Continual organization redesign is a fact of corporate life. In most cases, there are good business reasons to consider a redesign, despite the significant extra time, resources, and emotional energy it tends to consume. But the CEO&#39;s full-on engagement is needed to make the redesign succeed. Even then, however, redesign exercises often go astray. CEOs may lack an appropriate design framework or simply fail to maintain sufficient leadership throughout the process. They should start with an assessment of their vulnerabilities — both their own behavioral tendencies and governance-related constraints. And they should find ways to demonstrate that they are full-hearted, conclusive, decisive, and, ultimately, in control.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>