<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 30 日星期三 15:37:32 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>万事达卡的生成式人工智能：治理占据中心舞台</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/generative-ai-at-mastercard-governance-takes-center-stage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/generative-ai-at-mastercard-governance-takes-center-stage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 11:00:30 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) 是巴布森学院信息技术与管理学校长杰出教授、牛津大学赛德商学院客座教授以及麻省理工学院数字经济项目研究员。他是<cite>《Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）一书的合著者。 Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) 是一位行业思想领袖、作家、创始人兼首席执行官，目前担任全球咨询公司 Wavestone 的创新研究员、数据战略部门。他是<cite>《快速失败，更快学习：颠覆、大数据和人工智能时代数据驱动领导力的教训》一书</cite>的作者（Wiley，2021 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[If you saw the action-adventure movie Everything Everywhere All at Once, you might have had the same reaction we did. Impressive and exciting? No doubt — that’s one reason why it won seven Academy Awards. A portent of the future? Perhaps — as scientists explore the idea of a multiverse, the film provides one vision [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Davenport-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>如果你看过动作冒险电影<cite>《一切都同时发生》</cite> ，你可能会有和我们一样的反应。令人印象深刻且令人兴奋吗？毫无疑问，这就是它赢得七项奥斯卡奖的原因之一。未来的预兆？也许——当科学家们探索<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2023/03/12/is-the-multiverse-real-the-science-behind-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/?sh=4a4837583475">多元宇宙的想法</a>时，这部电影提供了一种关于它可能是什么样子的愿景。有点奇怪和令人困惑？好吧，无论如何对我们来说。</p><p>直到最近担任万事达卡首席数据官的乔安·斯托尼尔 (JoAnn Stonier) 在<a href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/generative-ai-is-everything-everywhere-all-at-once-in-the-enterprise-says-mastercard-cdo/">最近的一次小组</a>讨论中对这部电影和生成式人工智能进行了恰当的比较。 “一切无处不在”是描述这项技术的好方法——令人兴奋、令人困惑，但同时又很重要。我们之前曾<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2020/04/13/joann-stonier-of-mastercard-a-unique-take-on-the-cdo-role/?sh=4dea1d172ac6">写过有关</a>斯托尼尔的文章，以及她作为少数多年来一直高度关注数据道德的 CDO 之一的不同寻常的地位。我们在她担任 CDO 的最后几天采访了她；此后，她成为了万事达卡会员，但仍将致力于数据和人工智能道德问题。</p><p></p><p>采访结束后，我们如您一样松了一口气，因为我们发现斯托尼尔和万事达卡在生成人工智能方面仍在摸索中。许多公司都是如此。 VentureBeat 最近的一项调查显示，超过一半的受访者表示他们的组织正在试验人工智能，但<a href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/more-than-70-of-companies-are-experimenting-with-generative-ai-but-few-are-willing-to-commit-more-spending/">其中只有 18% 的公司已经开始实施</a>。同样比例的人表示，他们预计明年会在该技术上投入更多资金。</p><p>当然，万事达卡是数据、分析和人工智能方面的老手：我们一年前写过它为成为“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/becoming-an-ai-powerhouse-means-going-all-in/">人工智能强国</a>”所做的努力，斯托尼尔在<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>播客<cite>《我，我自己》</cite>中<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/designing-a-better-future-mastercards-joann-stonier/">讨论了该公司对人工智能的使用</a><cite>和人工智能</cite>。万事达卡涉足人工智能领域已有十多年，最重要的是在网络安全领域。一位在人工智能方面经验丰富的领导者和公司仍在努力制定生成式人工智能战略的细节，这应该会让许多其他公司和管理者感到欣慰。</p><p></p><h3>什么已经清楚</h3><p>万事达卡在以前的人工智能形式方面拥有丰富的经验，这使其建立了强大的方法论和治理流程。在较高层面上，此过程涉及理解数据、理解模型以及审查输出和相关结果。</p><p>这些步骤中的每一个都将进入评估生成模型的过程，但它们可能有不同的风格。当然，万事达卡并不缺乏结构化数字数据，但生成式人工智能处理的数据通常是图像和结构较少的文本。考虑到生成模型的复杂性和规模，准确理解给定的输入如何产生特定的输出是非常具有挑战性的。这使得审查结果的步骤变得更加重要，需要评估结果的事实准确性、偏见或有毒语言、对用户的价值，以及结果可能对个人、组织和生态系统造成的意外后果。操作。</p><p>尽管该技术存在固有的不确定性，但万事达卡已经制定了一些关于生成人工智能的政策。 2022 年 11 月推出 ChatGPT 后不久，公司就制定了指导方针，以确保员工利用新技术进行负责任的创新。这鼓励内部探索其供应商提供的模型，同时保护公司机密信息。</p><p>一些公司甚至禁止员工使用 ChatGPT 和其他大型语言模型，但万事达卡并没有这么做。 “有些用例比其他用例更有创意，但到目前为止我们还没有遇到任何问题，”斯托尼尔说。也许这是因为，正如她所指出的，“公司中的每个人现在都更加了解并参与数字化工作，他们将治理视为每个人工作的一部分。”</p><p>我们认为，几乎每家公司都应该对其高级管理人员和董事会成员进行有关生成式人工智能的教育，而万事达卡在这方面的表现正如预料的那样积极。它为高级管理团队和董事会成员举行了多次会议，讨论该技术的不同方面，包括其提供的机会、其所需的监管以及公司在实施该技术时应遵循的流程。许多外部专家参加了这些简报会，斯托尼尔指出，有几位精通技术的董事会成员已经非常了解这项技术。</p><p>万事达卡成立了一个由来自各个业务领域的人工智能领导者组成的委员会，该委员会在部署人工智能用例之前对其进行评估，并且在经过审查的用例中添加了生成式人工智能用例。迄今为止开发的一些用例涉及欺诈检测、内部知识管理和个性化等领域。更多用例正处于实验阶段，尚未用于生产部署。</p><p></p><p>尽管美国尚未发布针对生成式人工智能的详细政府政策，但斯托尼尔表示，很明显，针对生成式人工智能的许多不同功能将会有不同的政策。例如，由于万事达卡严重依赖可靠的信息系统，因此使用生成式人工智能开发编程代码将与使用它来创建营销文案受到不同的对待。</p><p>很明显，万事达卡需要采用跨学科和跨职能的方法来管理生成人工智能。律师、人力资源专业人员、系统和数据工程师以及架构师已经开始参与开发公司的技术方法。随着用例变得更加以客户为导向（现在主要是内部用例），组织的更多部分可能会参与其中。外部监管机构将希望了解该公司如何构建“黑匣子”模型，其中模型所基于的逻辑和数据源对用户来说不容易可见。斯托尼尔表示，考虑到所涉及的组织的所有可能的用例和方面，生成式人工智能的治理是一个挑战。她预计，与之前的人工智能开发流程一致，治理不仅要解决该技术的用户试图实现的目标，还要解决最可能的结果是什么。</p><h3>仍在发展中的事情</h3><p>斯托尼尔表示，生成式人工智能的许多方面仍在讨论中，这是理所应当的。对于公司及其员工来说，这是一段试验时期，斯托尼尔指出，只要遵循<a href="https://www.mastercard.us/en-us/vision/corp-responsibility/data-responsibility.html">公司的数据责任原则，</a>就没有人愿意阻止它。万事达卡希望利用生成式人工智能作为学习的机会，并最终从中受益，就像在减少欺诈和网络安全举措中从传统人工智能中获得的收益一样。</p><p>目前，实现的主要好处是公司自身流程的内部生产力提高。万事达卡客户（包括接受万事达卡的商家）的用例将在稍后提供。未来有可能为客户提供高度个性化的数据分析和消息。</p><p>万事达卡已经拥有一套明确的流程来推出数据和数据产品，甚至还有一个业务部门（汤姆几年前<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2021/01/13/data-exhaust-turbocharges-mastercard/?sh=451638f887df">写过的</a>数据与服务）来将它们提供给客户。斯托尼尔认为，数据与服务以及公司的网络与智能业务将是未来最有可能实施基于生成式人工智能的产品，从而丰富现有的人工智能解决方案。她相信这些生成式人工智能的使用将采用多种类型的语言模型，并且它们将在循环中广泛使用人类，也许是通过人类反馈的强化学习。她说，将会进行广泛的测试，以确保产品中不存在实质性的幻觉或其他有问题的输出。我们认为这很重要；如果机器学习就像类固醇的分析，那么生成式人工智能就像迷幻剂的机器学习。这抓住了该技术不可预测的方面。</p><p>生成式人工智能模型的具体架构也尚未确定。斯托尼尔认为肯定会有多个模型，但她不确定它们是否会堆叠在一起（组合为一个用例）或排列起来，由前端系统确定哪个模型最适合上下文。</p><p></p><p>我们询问斯托尼尔，她是否认为生成式人工智能是一种增量技术或具有巨大变革性的技术。 “到目前为止，它是渐进式的，但最终可能会带来变革，”她说。 “但任何转变都不会是一个大爆炸时刻——它会随着时间的推移而发生。运营效率的提升会相对较快，但产品和服务的改变则需要更长的时间。”</p><p>如果您的公司正在努力解决如何治理和充分利用生成式人工智能的问题，那么万事达卡的经验应该会让您感到更加轻松。这项技术可能会也可能不会改变您的业务，但它肯定会带来许多新问题和机遇。它们并不需要一夜之间就全部弄清楚。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/generative-ai-at-mastercard-governance-takes-center-stage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>保护社会免受人工智能危害：国际特赦组织的 Matt Mahmoudi 和 Damini Satija（第 1 部分）</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/protecting-society-from-ai-harms-amnesty-internationals-matt-mahmoudi-and-damini-satija-part-1/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/protecting-society-from-ai-harms-amnesty-internationals-matt-mahmoudi-and-damini-satija-part-1/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 11:00:47 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Public Policy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Justice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equality]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Amnesty International brings together more than 10 million staff members and volunteers worldwide to advocate for social justice. Damini Satija and Matt Mahmoudi work with Amnesty Tech, a division of the human rights organization that focuses on the role of government, Big Tech, and technologies like artificial intelligence in areas like surveillance, discrimination, and bias. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>国际特赦组织汇集了全球超过 1000 万员工和志愿者，致力于倡导社会正义。达米尼·萨蒂亚 (Damini Satija) 和马特·马哈茂迪 (Matt Mahmoudi) 与国际特赦组织合作，该组织是人权组织的一个部门，专注于政府、大型科技公司以及人工智能等技术在监视、歧视和偏见等领域的作用。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客中，马特和达米尼与主持人 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 一起重点介绍了人工智能工具可能使人权面临风险的场景，例如当政府和公共部门机构使用面部识别系统时跟踪社会活动家或算法，以做出有关公共住房使用和儿童福利的自动决策。达米尼和马特警告说，人工智能技术无法解决偏见、歧视和不平等等人类问题；这将需要人为干预和公共政策的改变。</p><p>有关组织可以采取哪些措施来应对因使用自动化技术而产生的意外负面后果的更多信息，请收看我们与 Matt 和 Damini 对话的下一集，即 2023 年 9 月 13 日播出的第二部分。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E7-E8-Mahmoudi-Satija-Amnesty-International-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="马特·马哈茂迪和达米尼·萨蒂亚"></p><h4>国际特赦组织的马特·马哈茂迪和达米尼·萨蒂亚</h4><p>马特·马哈茂迪 (Matt Mahmoudi) 是一名讲师、研究员和组织者。他一直在领导国际特赦组织的研究和宣传工作，禁止面部识别技术，并揭露从纽约市到巴勒斯坦被占领土的种族化社区使用这些技术的情况。他是乔·考克斯博士学位的首届获得者。他在剑桥大学获得了奖学金，在那里他研究了数字城市基础设施作为种族资本主义的新领域，并仍然是社会学的附属讲师。他的作品发表在<cite>《社会学评论》</cite>和<cite>《国际政治社会学》</cite>杂志以及<cite>《数字见证》</cite>一书中（牛津大学出版社，2020 年）。他即将出版的书是<cite>《数字外围的移民：控制的新城市前沿》</cite> （加州大学出版社，2023 年）。</p><p>达米尼·萨蒂亚 (Damini Satija) 是一位人权和公共政策专家，致力于数据和人工智能领域，重点关注算法歧视、福利自动化、政府监控和技术公平。她是算法问责实验室的负责人，也是国际特赦组织技术公司的副主任。她此前曾担任英国政府数据和人工智能伦理方面的顾问，并代表英国在欧洲委员会担任人工智能和人权政策专家。她拥有哥伦比亚大学国际与公共事务学院公共管理硕士学位。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我们的许多客人都希望在他们的组织中利用人工智能来造福他人。在今天的节目中，我们采访了两位专注于在使用人工智能工具时保护人权的研究人员。</p><p><strong>达米尼·萨蒂亚：</strong>我是达米尼·萨蒂亚……</p><p><strong>马特·马哈茂迪：</strong> ……我是国际特赦组织的马特·马哈茂迪……</p><p> <strong>Damini Satija：</strong> ……你正在听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的</cite>声音。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p>欢迎。今天，萨姆和我很高兴能与国际特赦组织的马特·马哈茂迪和达米尼·萨蒂亚交谈。马特、达米尼，感谢您今天加入我们。让我们开始吧。马特，请告诉我们一些您在国际特赦组织中的角色。</p><p><strong>马特·马哈茂迪：</strong>当然。是的，非常感谢您邀请我们。我是国际特赦组织科技项目人工智能和人权方面的顾问和研究员。我的职责一直专注于某些人工智能技术，特别是人工智能驱动的监控如何被警务机构采用，并由公司开发，表面上是为了提高效率，但往往会导致歧视性结果、各种形式的不平等，并影响一些人。历史上最边缘化的社区。因此，特别是在过去的几年里，我一直在追踪面部识别的部署、涉及的公司以及警察在哪里使用这些工具。</p><p>我们研究了纽约市、印度海得拉巴市和巴勒斯坦被占领土等地的面部识别技术，并且真正关注这些技术的应用方式，这些技术有望提高效率并变得更加智能将人们从A地转移到B地或确保他们的安全的方式实际上正在导致他们的权利受到侵蚀。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>马特，请告诉我们一些国际特赦组织的工作、结构是什么以及[其]技术实践是如何开始的。</p><p><strong>马特·马哈茂迪：</strong>国际特赦组织是一个由全球超过 1000 万人组成的运动，他们通过志愿服务或研究、宣传和运动等方式共同努力，围绕当今的关键人权问题进行动员。</p><p>就技术和人权计划（也称为“特赦科技”）而言，我们是一个由技术专家、研究人员、倡导者、法律学者等组成的集体，他们共同努力让公司和国家对自己的行为负责。使用和开发真正使这些基本人权面临风险的技术。因此，我们的工作是调查和揭露这些技术配置被用来侵蚀这些权利的方式，并在可能的情况下，倡导更强有力的保障、监管和人权实践，使我们能够在继续发展的同时享受这些权利。生活在一个快速变化的世界中。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Damini，请告诉我们一些关于算法问责实验室的工作。</p><p> <strong>Damini Satija：</strong>是的，非常感谢您今天邀请我们来到这里。我在技术项目工作，领导一个名为“算法问责实验室”的团队，这是国际特赦组织内一个相对较新的团队。我们特别关注自动化和人工智能技术在公共部门中越来越多的使用，特别是在福利领域和社会保护领域。因此，我们研究政府和公共部门机构如何使用自动化来确定谁可以获得基本的基本服务，例如住房、教育、医疗保健福利等。我们特别感兴趣的是调查和了解这些工具如何对已经边缘化的群体产生歧视性影响或不成比例的影响，这是我们已经在公共部门自动化或福利自动化中看到的证据。</p><p>该团队本身是一个由七人组成的多学科团队：数据科学家、人权研究人员、倡导者、法律专业知识——全方位……支持我们以整体视角审视和理解这些系统对社会影响的愿景。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>谢谢你。这很有趣，山姆，因为当我们的大多数客人与我们谈论他们如何使用人工智能时，[它]是为了创造更多利润或更多收入或降低成本或做好事，但一般来说，对吧？看来你的角色是确保我们不会用人工智能做坏事，对吧？</p><p>因此，在这种背景下，考虑到您在人工智能方面的背景和专业知识，您认为一些指导原则是什么？它有何不同？就像，当你寻找坏演员时，我必须想象这与寻找做好事有根本上的不同。我将从你开始，马特。你打算怎样做呢？</p><p><strong>马特·马哈茂迪：</strong>嗯，我们经常了解到一些涉及某个特定人面临某种形式歧视的案件。例如，在纽约市的背景下，我们联系了一位名叫德里克·英格拉姆（Derrick Ingram）的活动家，他创立了一个名为“花园勇士”的团体，同时也是“黑人生命也是命”社区中的一位杰出活动家。他受到了[警察]的骚扰，警察出现在他家门口，有效地骚扰了他四个小时，因为他没有意识到自己做了什么，而且实际上，对于他们为什么这样做，并没有明确的答案。在那里。</p><p>事实证明，鉴于他受到骚扰时某些记者在他家附近，他们发现警方打印了一份面部识别识别报告，该报告在现场——然后，[它]变成了确定他是该特定抗议活动中唯一可识别的抗议者之一，这是一场抗议乔治·弗洛伊德谋杀案的“黑人生命也是命”抗议活动。在这种情况下，我们发现，实际上，警方只是简单地用扩音器认出了一名著名抗议者，并且由于能够识别他的身份，即使没有搜查令，警察也认为这属于他们的职权范围，以表明站在他家门口，试图质问他，并试图骚扰他。</p><p>警方最终提出了一项虚假指控，指控他将扩音器离警官耳朵太近，但这一切都发生在国际特赦组织调查纽约警察局针对的其他社区成员的同时以及谁正在开发[和]提供他们正在使用的软件。纽约警察局也没有特别主动。</p><p>因此，我们的工作通常围绕两种传统方法，例如《信息自由法》请求或<a href=" https://opengovernment.ny.gov/freedom-information-law">《信息自由法》</a>请求，但它也涉及使用，例如，谷歌街景图像来标记由纽约警察局运行的摄像机，以提供例如，我们了解纽约人对网络摄像头系统，特别是具有面部识别功能的网络摄像头系统的接触程度。这让您了解风险的传播范围有多大。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以，当人们谈论人工智能时，让我感到困扰的是这种使用拟人化语言的倾向。人们很容易使用“AI 做 X”或“AI 做 Y”这样的短语，而且在与你们交谈时已经很引人注目，你们都没有使用<em>AI</em>作为演员。这是一个工具，而你似乎非常关注谁是演员。因此，困难在于，如果一个工具可以放大好的一面，也可以放大坏的一面，那么我们如何向实际参与者传达信息呢？如何让演员使用一个<em>可以</em>用来做好事，也<em>可以</em>用来做坏事的工具，用它来做好事还是做坏事？甚至好与坏也很难划清界限。</p><p><strong>达米尼·萨蒂亚：</strong>是的，如果我可以用它来回答你之前问到的关于坏演员的问题，我认为这本身就很能说明问题，因为我们非常关注演员，而不仅仅是人工智能。它还是谁设计了人工智能，人工智能的设计方式，谁在部署它，它被部署在什么环境中。我们必须非常小心，不要把注意力集中在人工智能的问题上，因为这也会导致我们落入“这个问题有技术解决方案”的陷阱。</p><p>但通常情况下，我们正在研究的人工智能工具也在操作我们所关心的特定环境，对吧？因此，举例来说，如果我们正在研究在移民背景下使用的工具，并且盛行的叙述是仇外或反移民的，那么它将实施适合该类别的政策。因此，正如您所说，这不仅与技术有关，还与开发、采购和部署这些技术的环境有关。</p><p>因此，简单地说，这意味着我们并不总是关注不良<em>行为者</em>本身，而是关注不良使用。但我认为这对于我们寻找需要调查的案件来说同样是一个指导因素，正如马特所说，这也是寻找歧视性影响的指导因素。我认为这里浮现的另一个例子是旧金山使用的<a href=" https://www.codastory.com/authoritarian-tech/san-francisco-homeless-algorithm">住房算法，</a>其中没有专门针对负面后果部署工具，但最终产生了负面后果。大约一年前有一个关于这个的故事。</p><p>有一个工具是为社会工作者开发的，用于分配公共住房。开发该工具的目的是提供一些东西，使社会工作者能够与他们正在工作的需要住房援助的个人进行更知情的对话。该工具专门帮助他们对人员进行某种脆弱性或风险评估，然后确定他们需要多少住房援助。该工具旨在帮助促进对话。 [然而，]在它的使用方式中，社会工作者根据该工具对谁应该获得住房援助和谁不应该获得住房援助的信息做出是或否的决定。</p><p>所以……我的意思是你可能会说这是不好的使用，但这也是对该工具的无意使用。因此，我们正在考虑的各种现实并不那么容易——只是很难说问题出在人工智能本身，这并不能回答你最初的问题，而是我想要的一些背景补充一下坏人的问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>它还强调了你所说的——人工智能和人类[互动]的重要性，而不仅仅是一个与另一个，或者一个<em>或</em>另一个。因为在所有这些例子中，都有意外或意外使用的例子，或者可能是因为缺乏培训，或者潜在的叙述并不是你一开始就打算造成伤害；你只是不知道或者没有预料到“哦，我应该只是将它用作输入而不是指示”。</p><p>我有一个问题……你提到了它，但你的方向与我想象的不同，因为你说，“我们不是在谈论技术出了什么问题，因为这意味着技术修复。”但我想挑战这一点，因为为什么修复的一部分不能至少是技术性的呢？</p><p> <strong>Damini Satija：</strong>是的，对于偏见有一些技术解决方案，并且有人已经推出了消除偏见工具的方法。我认为我们不想完全局限于此的原因是因为我所概述的——我们需要采取更全面的方法来理解这些技术的影响，因为正如我们所说，这不仅仅是关于技术的影响方式。工具的设计，虽然，是的，这也非常重要。它还涉及人类与工具的交互以及人类如何使用它们。</p><p>我认为另一个问题是，技术修复路线可能使我们对问题所在采取一种非常孤立的方法。例如，在人工智能伦理算法公平领域，已经提出了很多去偏见解决方案，这意味着算法或人工智能系统中以非常技术性的方式存在偏见是唯一的问题。但我认为我们很有可能从技术角度解决这个问题，但我们正在研究的工具仍然存在无数其他问题。答，即使已经进行了技术修复，它们仍然可以以歧视性的方式使用。存在监视问题；这些是数据密集型技术。</p><p>我们还经常担心这些技术所产生的二阶和三阶影响。因此，举例来说，再次以住房为例，如果使用某种工具拒绝某人提供住房或拒绝某人获得社会保障福利，然后他们无法为家人支付租金或购买食物，那么这些影响就是与工具发生了两到三度的分离，即使您反转或将算法从图片中删除，这种情况仍然会发生。这种影响仍然存在并且仍然发生。</p><p>我认为，从我们的角度来看，重点是保持对社会后果——政治、经济——以及技术的全面理解。我不知道马特是否想对此添加任何内容。</p><p><strong>马特·马哈茂迪：</strong>我希望在此基础上进一步发展，特别是因为住房示例和其他类似示例。此外，儿童保护服务机构还使用风险指示器算法来决定是否将儿童从寄养机构中移出，甚至将其置于寄养机构中。尤其<a href=" https://www.technologyreview.com/2018/01/26/104816/algorithms-are-making-american-inequality-worse/">是 Virginia Eubanks 的工作</a>将概述面对该算法的社会工作者如何根据基于光的指示器做出决定，如果看起来有太多关于儿童福利的主动报告，该指示器会向他们发出红色信号。危险。事实上，这告诉你的是，系统本身，技术本身，并不像你知道的那样容易修复，“哦，好吧，然后摆脱指标并把它们变成现实”。更多的是一种描述性的文本形式。”因为您正在处理的是一种远远超出实际代码本身的技术，这也是达米尼在这里所要达到的目的。这是一个完整的社会技术系统。</p><p>你不能认为人工智能是一个东西，同时也认为存在人机交互，它为系统如何运作和做什么提供了动画。所以，代码中写的内容——我已经采取了这种立场——有点无关紧要。它所做的以及它最终在世界上所做的事情，在这里没有使用太多学术术语，但从现象学角度来看，才是真正重要的，并且告诉我们系统实际上是什么。</p><p>因此，通过摆脱“在人工智能技术方面去偏见是一种美德”的观念，通过摆脱系统存在技术修复的想法，而不是坚持认为，实际上，这些系统都应该经过测试和理解在它们被推出之前，就可能对整个社会和人们的人权产生什么影响——这可能会导致我们应用和部署“更好的技术”。至于我们如何利用技术来识别某些<em>有害</em>技术：我之前提到的一个例子是我们如何使用街道测绘工具来了解摄像头的位置。需要明确的是，我们没有在那里使用图像识别算法。都是人。</p><p>这使我们能够将志愿服务规模扩大到全球约 7,500 人，他们帮助我们用摄像头标记纽约市的每个十字路口。我认为，这是一个非常引人注目的模型，可以说明如何扩展激进主义和工作，在技术方面将杠杆推向某种形式的正义和公平，当然，这是一种可以促进更多尊重的干预措施抗议的权利可能看起来像。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我认为……我的观点是关于技术的。 It wasn&#39;t to say, “Let technology fix the problem it&#39;s created,” because the problem is created by the usage of it, as you said. And, of course, when you&#39;re talking about a powerful technology being used by institutions that have power to make policy, power to make law, power to make arrests or make war … of course the actor and the motivation of the actor and the use takes far more precedence [than] a technological fix. But I also have to believe that AI isn&#39;t going anywhere and the technology will only get improved.</p><p> And so I wonder … all of the deficiencies that your teams are finding, in terms of … I mean, in your example, you did not rely on image recognition to identify cameras, because you thought humans would be more accurate. Well, that is feedback to the algorithms and to the instrumentation that does image recognition. And in the example, Damini, that you talked about with housing, I wonder if there could be safeguards or additional prompts or additional data feeds that would actually make it almost impossible for that technology that was making the choice on what to do for a human to rely on the technological choice. So I must believe that as users and as agencies that are monitoring the use, that there is some feedback to the developer community that is building these tools. Not to say bias is the central problem, but that … I mean, you&#39;ve highlighted so many different areas where technological artifacts could help advance the very cause that you&#39;re talking about.</p><p> <strong>Damini Satija:</strong> Yeah. I mean, in terms of safeguards, there are many we could go into in terms of what we call for as a human rights community in regulation. I think Matt has already alluded to the No. 1 safeguard, which is clear questioning at the outset in the very conceptualization of these technologies as to whether they are required and whether automation is actually necessary in a certain context, and in doing that interrogating and scrutinizing, what that rights-violating or disproportionate impact could be of this technology. And I think in doing that, and what comes up for us again and again in our work is, which voices are being heard? Whose articulation of problems that need to be solved using technology are heard in that conceptualization phase?</p><p> And what we&#39;re often up against in our work is that there are certain sets of pretty powerful voices, which you&#39;ve just mentioned yourself as well. You know, policy makers, big technology companies, those who have funding to develop new technology, those who are funding new technology. Those who have the power to really dictate the trajectory of AI are the ones whose voices are also heard in what AI is being developed and then deployed, whereas those who are then impacted by the use of these systems, and especially the communities that we look at, often say … We&#39;ve mentioned racialized impacts. Often, Black and Brown communities are really negatively impacted and harmed by these systems. Those are not the voices that are then feeding into what the problems are that need to be solved through this technology, which, as you say, is here and the development of AI is happening very quickly. But it&#39;s that power imbalance that really concerns us in terms of whose voice is being heard [and] what should be conceptualized. And that is an intangible safeguard but a very, very important one for us in our work.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s interesting you mentioned the social work example. My mother was a social worker and in [the] foster care [field]. And that is a highly understaffed, overworked world. And so when you gave that example, I have to say, part of me still finds it appealing that we could help those people improve. It may not be perfectly correct, it may not perfectly do prediction, but given so much of what else goes on, it may be a better solution. So how do we get a better solution in place without opening up this Pandora&#39;s box of difficulties to a point that we can improve it and can get experience over time? How does that happen?</p><p> <strong>Matt Mahmoudi:</strong> So if I could jump in here, Sam, I think staying with the social worker example and just staying with a particular program that Virginia Eubanks looks at, it&#39;s an interesting one because the state ends up spending more money on trying to hold up a failed technology than it would have spent just trying to equip the social workers with more resources, to be able to hire more social workers to be able to carry out their work more adequately and in line with the demand.</p><p> So I think, just drawing from the page of a piece of reading that I like to always assign to a class I&#39;m teaching on science and technology studies, which is sort of a drawing from Chellis Glendinning&#39;s “ <a href=" https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chellis-glendinning-notes-toward-a-neo-luddite-manifesto">Notes Toward a Neo-Luddite Manifesto</a> ,” I will say I&#39;m not anti-technology, and neo-Luddites aren&#39;t either, and I think that&#39;s kind of the crucial point here: that, A, neo-Luddites aren&#39;t anti-technology; they&#39;re worried about the ways in which technology creates numbers out of people and leads toward a hyperrationality that takes out these important questions of harm.</p><p> And then, secondly — and this is a really important one — all technologies are political. We have to understand, what are the forms of politics and policies that are undergirding the particular deployment of a technology instead of, say, investing in the particular social programs that are required? So the kinds of examples that Damini has been bringing up all along and that we&#39;ve been talking through really show that there is an insistence on investing in the tool of technology under the auspices that it&#39;s going to lead to some cost saving in the future, when the reality is that oftentimes states end up having to spend much more money either trying to hold the companies to account on what they promised but couldn&#39;t deliver or facing lawsuits by individuals, whether they&#39;re class action suits or whatever, given the harms that they would&#39;ve incurred on people who have been subject to these mass forms of idealized technologies. Which I think goes to the point of, try and uncover what the politics that underlie it is and see if there is a social-political-economic fix that might actually be more sustainable than trying to get out of our way and go into this fantasy land of “AI will solve everything” — sort of technochauvinistic ideology that <a href=" https://www.publicbooks.org/letting-go-of-technochauvinism/">Meredith Broussard talks about</a> — and get away from that a little bit, and thinking about what kinds of investment our society needs outside of these technologies.</p><p> I think, importantly, with tools such as your GPT-based chatbot models and what have you, you&#39;re dealing with systems that appear to be in perpetual beta, and so they can constantly make the claim that they&#39;re not working the way they should just quite [yet] and they may have unintended consequences because they haven&#39;t crunched enough data or quite gotten the model right. And you can sit on that narrative for a very, very, very long time.</p><p> But the question is, when do we, as a civil society, and when do we, as people who form a constituency on lawmakers that can speak on our behalf and regulate on our behalf, pump the brakes and say, “No, these are products that are out in the open. They&#39;re having an impact, and, therefore, they should be subject to regulation.” It doesn&#39;t matter how large the language model is. It doesn&#39;t matter how much larger it needs to be to reach a saturation point at which it&#39;ll operate according to some prescribed fantasy of efficiency.</p><p> We have to get to a point — and that point, I think, was yesterday — in which we say, “We need regulation.” I think [the European Union&#39;s] AI Act, which Damini is working on extensively as well, is a really good first attempt at trying to create a regional-level legislation that has an understanding of the kinds of consequences we&#39;re dealing with and the kinds of impacts that these technologies can have on our rights and our ability to engage in the kinds of liberties that we have today.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Damini, Matt, thank you so much for a very enlightening discussion.</p><p> <strong>Damini Satija:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. Please join us next time, when we bring Matt and Damini back to continue the discussion about AI regulation, including what others can do to help limit harms stemming from the use of technology tools.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/protecting-society-from-ai-harms-amnesty-internationals-matt-mahmoudi-and-damini-satija-part-1/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why the Power of Technology Rarely Goes to the People</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-the-power-of-technology-rarely-goes-to-the-people/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-the-power-of-technology-rarely-goes-to-the-people/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Daron Acemoglu and Simon Johnson, interviewed by Kaushik Viswanath. <p>Daron Acemoglu is an economist and an MIT Institute Professor, the university&#39;s highest faculty honor. Simon Johnson is the Kurtz Professor of Entrepreneurship at MIT and a former chief economist to the International Monetary Fund. They are the authors of <cite>Power and Progress: Our 1,000-Year Struggle Over Technology and Prosperity</cite> (PublicAffairs, 2023). Kaushik Viswanath is features editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Taylor Callery/theispot.com In a new book, economists Daron Acemoglu and Simon Johnson provide a sweeping historical overview of just how unevenly the spoils and costs of technological change have been distributed. Power and Progress: Our 1,000-Year Struggle Over Technology and Prosperity reminds us that technology is not itself a force but rather a tool that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Acemoglu_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Taylor Callery/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> In a new book, economists Daron Acemoglu and Simon Johnson provide a sweeping historical overview of just how unevenly the spoils and costs of technological change have been distributed. <cite>Power and Progress: Our 1,000-Year Struggle Over Technology and Prosperity</cite> reminds us that technology is not itself a force but rather a tool that is developed to support the agendas of the people and institutions who hold power in society. Claiming a fair share of technology&#39;s benefits for the rest of society — that is, for most of humanity — requires that that power be challenged. Acemoglu and Johnson chatted with features editor Kaushik Viswanath about what lessons the past holds for how we should develop and implement technology today and in the future. This conversation has been edited for length and clarity.</p><p></p><h6> Kaushik Viswanath: What&#39;s the central argument you&#39;re making in <cite>Power and Progress</cite> , and what motivated you to write it?</h6><p> <strong>Daron Acemoglu:</strong> This is a critical time to be thinking about the future of technology. A lot of decisions of great import are being hampered by the fact that there is “techno-optimism” in academia, the tech world, and the policy world. Techno-optimism is the notion that impressive technological change will automatically lead to better outcomes for society, especially for workers via the labor market, even if there are some transition costs.</p><p> Our understanding of the relevant economic theory and history has led us to believe this isn&#39;t right. Throughout history, deliberate decisions have had a bearing on who gained and lost from a particular technology, whether it brought anything approaching shared prosperity, or even whether it helped or destroyed democracy. So our purpose in writing <cite>Power and Progress</cite> was to dispel the notion that in the history of technology, everything has always worked out OK. There are similar choices and struggles over technology today as we&#39;ve had in the past.</p><p></p><h6> One of the key concepts you discuss is the productivity bandwagon. What is this, and how does it create winners and losers whenever we have technological change?</h6><p> <strong>Simon Johnson:</strong> The productivity bandwagon is the notion that when technology improves, you get higher wages, more opportunity, and better health, and everybody gains from it eventually. Our key problem with that notion is the “eventually.” “Eventually,” from the beginning of the Industrial Revolution, was 120 years. The 1720s to the 1840s saw a lot of new technology, but we know that in the 1840s, children as young as 6 were still pushing coal carts deep underground with their heads. Conditions improved for more people in the second half of the 19th century but as a result of a lot of effort, not through any kind of automatic economic or political process.</p><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> The perspective that Simon and I bring to the British Industrial Revolution is that it was really a revolution of vision. A new class of ambitious people emerged who wanted to apply technology to improve how people control their environment and the production process. They weren&#39;t doing it out of altruism; they were preoccupied with making money, wanted to rise within the British hierarchy, and didn&#39;t have much sympathy for the people who were below them in that hierarchy, whether in Britain or the rest of the world.</p><p> This is an illustration of what ambition does unless it is countered by institutions and other groups that have alternative visions of how society should be organized. It also illustrates the weaknesses of the productivity bandwagon. People were left behind in the early phases of the Industrial Revolution for two reasons. First, most of the technology was used for automation, not increasing workers&#39; productivity contributions. When technology displaces workers, it doesn&#39;t increase their contribution to production or create a powerful reason for employers to go out and pay higher wages to workers. Second, this was all embedded in an institutional setup, both because of the vision of the entrepreneurs and because trade unions were banned and heavily prosecuted, and Britain was very far from a democracy at the time.</p><p> The working class did not have any rights or protections. That&#39;s why, even as many people made fabulous amounts of money, workers&#39; real incomes stagnated or even declined. Sharing the gains of technology required a complete change in the institutional fabric of British society, which the elites and upper middle classes resisted. It required a change in the direction of technology, too — for example, it was necessary to invest in urban infrastructure to improve sanitation and bring infectious diseases under control. Until then, urban life was horrible for working people.</p><p></p><h6> Fast-forwarding to post-World War II in the US, you describe how this period saw a more equitable distribution of the productivity gains from technology. How did this happen?</h6><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> That episode illustrates how the factors that worked against shared prosperity during the Industrial Revolution were turned in favor of shared prosperity in the 20th century, especially in the decades that followed World War II.</p><p> Its origins can be traced to the American system of manufacturing, because this was a key part of a general effort to make unskilled labor more productive using machinery. That, in turn, was critical for less-skilled workers to earn a high and rising wage. In this period, workers&#39; contributions to the production process could be bolstered by training. This was facilitated by a combination of technologies that didn&#39;t simply automate work but created new and more technical tasks, more maintenance tasks, and more advanced machining tasks for workers. And it was in the context of institutions that provided countervailing powers to the most powerful firms — in particular, a secure democracy by historical standards, a labor movement that had become much stronger after the New Deal and during World War II, and a supportive regulatory environment by the US government that encouraged technological change but also brought limits to what the largest companies could do, for example, through antitrust enforcement.</p><h6> You also write that the US labor movement during this period actually encouraged the mechanization of the industries in which they worked. Why did they do this?</h6><p> <strong>Johnson:</strong> The key was in their insistence that their workers get trained to use the machines. They realized that mechanization was coming whether they liked it or not. They couldn&#39;t simply ask for higher wages, because that would lead to more automation. So [labor unions] asked for their workers to acquire the necessary skills and be compensated appropriately. Unions are much weaker today, so that kind of countervailing power is missing, which means the benefits of automation will go to whoever has social power — which means relatively few people.</p><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> We are not against automation. Blocking automation would not just be infeasible, but to the extent that it&#39;s tried, would be hugely costly. In its best moments, the labor movement, both in the United States and in Europe, encouraged the introduction of advanced automated machinery but at the same time negotiated the creation of better, more advanced tasks for workers to operate and inspect these machines. Where workers didn&#39;t have those skills, employers would have to train them. So it was the combination of new tasks and training that unions advocated for. Today the question is, can we still encourage the right type of automation?</p><p></p><h6> What is the role of business leaders in determining the direction of technological advancement and distributing its gains?</h6><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> The future of technology is inseparable from the vision of powerful actors. It&#39;s not something we can all democratically vote on. The same is true of how CEOs decide to split profits between different stakeholders. Do they see labor as one of those stakeholders? That is a question that is entangled with the future of technology.</p><p> Over time, business leaders have shifted toward just serving the interests of the shareholders. Labor is viewed as troublesome and costly, so they try to eliminate it as much as possible. And that has synergized with the vision of the tech community to develop machines that can automate as much as possible.</p><p> But nothing in the laws of capitalism makes that necessary. During other periods, in other contexts, businesses have prioritized increasing worker productivity. They have found ways of rewarding their shareholders while giving raises to their workers when the company is doing well, and investing in technologies that increase worker productivity. A new vision among business leaders would be feasible and highly useful for the kinds of futures of work that we&#39;re talking about. But that won&#39;t emerge by itself. It will require pressure from institutions, civil society, and the media, as well as some amount of organized labor.</p><h6> You describe how the doctrine of maximizing shareholder value became consensus in management schools and then management consultancies, ending an era of widely shared gains from technology. Do you see that changing?</h6><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> I have a <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w29874">paper with Alex He and Daniel le Maire</a> where we find that CEOs with business degrees from the top MBA programs in the United States don&#39;t increase productivity, exports, or investment, but they reduce wage growth and labor share. But the CEOs in our sample are all from the 1970s, &#39;80s, and &#39;90s. Today, the same schools have a somewhat different air. Students seem to care much more about broader aspects of business. Faculty don&#39;t just talk about increasing shareholder value and creating lean corporations by eliminating labor. So I already sense some change in that direction. How effective it is, we don&#39;t know yet.</p><p> <strong>Johnson:</strong> There&#39;s a lot more progress to be made. The curriculum and the core ideas that are imprinted on students still lean a lot more toward <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/strategy-forum/has-strategic-management-overlooked-the-role-of-purpose-what-experts-say/">Milton Friedman</a> than toward Acemoglu-Johnson or any other view.</p><p> If you consider the pressure from financial markets and look at the language used by analysts, it reinforces that narrow view, which is, I think, not ultimately good for business.</p><h6> Turning to the tech that&#39;s on everyone&#39;s minds these days: Where do you think AI — and generative AI, specifically — is headed?</h6><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> These are phenomenally interesting and impressive technologies. That only raises the stakes of getting the direction of this technology right and setting up the right regulatory structure.</p><p> But the two polar views that are most loudly heard in the media are both unhelpful: On one end are techno-optimists, who say, “Everybody will benefit. Yes, a few people might lose their jobs. But you&#39;ll get more massage therapists, even if you don&#39;t have enough white-collar workers.” On the other end is the view that killer robots are coming and we have to worry about existential risk.</p><p> Neither of these views addresses the right concerns. AI can do a lot to help workers and society. It could go along the lines of the platforms that Taiwan introduced, for example, to facilitate more democratic participation; those have worked reasonably well. Or it can go in the direction of automation that deepens inequalities, delivers more misinformation, disinformation, manipulation of users — what we&#39;ve seen with social media, especially platforms like Facebook.</p><p> We really worry about that direction, and that&#39;s where our leaders are asleep at the wheel. Society is not worrying enough about these things. There isn&#39;t even the right set of aspirations that have been articulated about what we should want from this technology.</p><p> <strong>Johnson:</strong> I&#39;ve heard the view that people are complaining now because it&#39;s cognitive tasks that are being replaced by a machine, whereas before it was manual work. What we say in our book is that what&#39;s actually vulnerable here are all routine cognitive tasks. Wendy&#39;s, for example, has said it&#39;s going to use chatbots to take orders at drive-throughs. They&#39;ll still use humans to flip the burgers. Is your ordering of a burger going to be any better with this machine? Are they going to be paying the burger flipper any more money? No, they&#39;re just doing this so they can have fewer workers.</p><p></p><p> We call it <em>so-so automation</em> . It&#39;s a way to tilt power against the workers. You&#39;re replacing people who are quirky and sometimes difficult to manage with machines that are designed for mediocrity. Where&#39;s the productivity breakthrough? Where&#39;s the big positive benefit?</p><p> <strong>Acemoglu:</strong> In productivity revolutions of the past, like at the Ford Motor Company, automation was critical, but only when combined with new products, new tasks, new ways of using machinery, new creativity. The Ford factory would not have done anything of note if it took exactly the cars that other companies were producing and made them with a bit more automation.</p><p> This is why we prefer to emphasize machine usefulness rather than machine intelligence. We should be using machines to make humans better. Generative AI is so promising because it has that capability. It could help with the retrieval and filtering of information so that human decision makers make better decisions. But that&#39;s very different from automating a few more McDonald&#39;s kiosks.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-the-power-of-technology-rarely-goes-to-the-people/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Deliver Career Development for All</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[George Westerman and Tony Gigliotti. <p>George Westerman is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and founder of MIT&#39;s Global Opportunity Forum (formerly known as the Global Opportunity Initiative). Tony Gigliotti is the senior director of talent management and organizational development at UPMC, a health care provider and insurer based in Pittsburgh.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Career Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To be competitive in today’s tough labor markets, companies need to expand career development beyond those employees who are considered “high potential.” Helping all workers build rewarding job paths benefits both individuals and organizations. But broadening the reach of career development is not simple. Traditional development programs don’t easily scale, and most managers aren’t equipped [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA05_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> To be competitive in today&#39;s tough labor markets, companies need to expand career development beyond those employees who are considered “high potential.” Helping all workers build rewarding job paths benefits both individuals and organizations. But broadening the reach of career development is not simple. Traditional development programs don&#39;t easily scale, and most managers aren&#39;t equipped to be good career counselors.</p><p> Forward-leaning companies understand the imperative. During <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023, MIT Sloan&#39;s George Westerman noted that in a <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-companies-should-help-every-employee-chart-a-career-path/">survey of 1,016 employees</a> , two-thirds said they want to advance — but “half of them said they were being held back by lack of good career advice.” A majority of those who changed jobs in 2021 cited a lack of advancement opportunities as the cause.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Westerman said managers can&#39;t be fully responsible for developing employees&#39; careers; many leaders don&#39;t want or know how to help, and many don&#39;t have the incentive to. But organizations shouldn&#39;t think that employees can completely own their career paths. “If you believe this story, then when an employee doesn&#39;t advance, you tend to blame the employee and not the system,” he said.</p><p> Instead, companies that are successfully broadening who gets career help are making opportunities and pathways visible, providing opportunities to learn and practice new skills, and delivering rich feedback and coaching. Providing autonomous routes to this information is especially important because not all employees have the psychological safety to discuss job options with their managers.</p><p> Lani Montoya, the chief human resources officer at Pernod Ricard North America and a presenter on the panel with Westerman, said that at the premium spirits and wine company, a global job-rating process allows all 18,500 employees to see positions at their level as well as above and below it. “They can see how teams are structured, and if they&#39;re interested in a role, they can see how it sits within what team,” she said.</p><p></p><p> Tony Gigliotti, the senior director of talent management and organizational development at UPMC, who was also on the panel, said that his organization is working toward similar transparency around career paths and job opportunities. The Pittsburgh-based health care provider and insurer has 95,000 employees in its hospitals and outpatient offices. A career resource site on UPMC&#39;s intranet offers access to assessments and skill-building opportunities, and a feature within its human capital management system shows job postings, job descriptions, and career paths within and outside an employee&#39;s job family.</p><p> “Now they have at their fingertips a lot of information,” Gigliotti said. “That will empower more employees.”</p><p> Below, Westerman and Gigliotti answer some of the questions from Work/23 attendees that they weren&#39;t able to get to during the event. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> How do you see career development working for employees who really enjoy their jobs, are individual contributors, and don&#39;t want to become managers?</h6><p> <strong>George Westerman:</strong> Many workers don&#39;t want to advance in their careers but can still benefit from development opportunities. Take teachers, for example. Very few want to become principals, but all can benefit from professional development opportunities. Most doctors may not want to move into management, but it&#39;s good for them (and their patients) that they engage in continuing medical education every year.</p><p> <strong>Tony Gigliotti:</strong> It is important to define career development beyond vertical promotion into leadership positions. Otherwise, a portion of your productive and reliable employee population might feel that they do not have opportunities for professional growth, and this may lead to their disengagement.</p><p> Our resources for leaders at UPMC take a more holistic approach to career development by referencing the many interventions that support professional growth and development. These include training and learning paths, mentoring, coaching, job enhancement/enrichment, stretch assignments, cross-functional work teams and committees, conferences, and community involvement.</p><p></p><p> Additionally, our talent-review programs normalize situations where solid performers are content in their current role. Part of that consideration must include the employees&#39; own intentions. In these cases, we explore ways to develop the employee in place.</p><p> Finally, we remind leaders that career aspirations can and often do change over time, so they must seek feedback and listen to their employees as their career needs and preferences evolve.</p><h6> What criteria work best when considering people for internal transfers for their career development? It seems like transfers could be a problem when the needs of the company and the needs of the individual conflict.</h6><p> <strong>Westerman:</strong> If you decide that the needs of the company outweigh an employee&#39;s desire to move to a new role, you&#39;re inviting them to leave the company. They&#39;ll move to another employer instead, leaving you without an employee and with less chance to conduct a smooth transition.</p><p></p><p> To encourage hiring from within, you may not need special criteria or incentives. Just make the opportunities known to internal candidates, and make the candidates known to the hiring manager. However, you can also try other changes to improve incentives, such as opening a position to internal candidates before listing it externally, or asking the manager to share in the costs of external hiring.</p><h6> How can companies manage talent hoarding and deal with managers who are resistant to sharing career paths openly?</h6><p> <strong>Gigliotti:</strong> There are several ways that our organization addresses leaders who hoard talent and do not focus on their employees&#39; career growth within the organization. Our organization transparently shares all career paths, including job descriptions, with all employees. So despite some leaders&#39; penchant for talent hoarding, employees still have access to the resources needed to understand their own (and others&#39;) career paths. This approach is consumer-driven — that is, our employees have expressed a need for this information so that they can navigate their own careers within the organization.</p><p></p><p> In addition, our organizational talent reviews are designed to identify emerging talent and ready-now talent. The outcomes from talent-review discussions across the organization are compiled and then transparently shared with HR leaders. This information empowers HR to identify potential internal talent who may be interested in and ready for available positions within the organization.</p><p> And growth is a key dimension in our employee engagement model. If a leader is not developing their employees, sharing career resources with them, or encouraging their career growth within the organization, then that leader&#39;s employee engagement scores (particularly in the growth dimension) will suffer. Low scores raise a red flag to that leader&#39;s supervisor and the local HR team, who then may intervene. Part of that intervention is to align the leader to our organizational values of responsibility and integrity, which, in part, expect leaders to “support their staff&#39;s … professional growth and development.”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Ask Sanyin: Why Can&#39;t We Get Meetings Right?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang is a CEO coach and leads the Fuqua/Coach K Center on Leadership &amp; Ethics (COLE) at Duke University. Need advice? Send an <a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">email to Sanyin</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Building]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[As a senior leader in my company, I find meetings are crucial for keeping tabs on what’s going on and making decisions. But we seem to accomplish little, people are frequently unprepared, and they gripe about the time cost. How can I shift people’s attitudes and run more effective meetings? We’ve all been there: We [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AskSanyin-featured-column4-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question"> As a senior leader in my company, I find meetings are crucial for keeping tabs on what&#39;s going on and making decisions. But we seem to accomplish little, people are frequently unprepared, and they gripe about the time cost. How can I shift people&#39;s attitudes and run more effective meetings?</p><p> We&#39;ve all been there: We sit through an hour of conversation, and somehow, there&#39;s less clarity at the end of the meeting than there was at the beginning. We walk out, lamenting the wasted time and lack of progress.</p><p> In an era of hyperproductivity, an endless list of to-do items, and personal exhaustion, your team probably sees meetings as an obstacle to getting back to their work rather than something purposeful. Shifting that attitude toward one of enthusiastic engagement means rethinking what you&#39;re trying to accomplish with meetings. With the widespread move to remote work, opportunities to engage with our teams in real time have become rarer and more valuable. How can we use this time to deepen relationships? What if we make trust-building a key aim of every type of meeting?</p><p></p><p> The decision-making meeting is usually about a commitment to a course of action. Here, you can also discuss the emotional consequences of the decisions for your people and the best ways to communicate a change. A deep discussion of these questions provides insight into others&#39; values and approaches.</p><p> Brainstorming and problem-solving meetings benefit enormously from explicit consideration of trust-building. Everyone needs to feel comfortable sharing their ideas while resisting the urge to judge. Here, you want to encourage vulnerability, because when we say “I don&#39;t know,” we acknowledge our limits and interdependencies within the greater team.</p><p> There&#39;s also an opportunity to transform the sometimes-routine information-sharing meeting into a richer venue for connection. Try setting the expectation that these are opportunities to learn more about one another&#39;s challenges and strategies, and encourage questions. These meetings also provide the opportunity to celebrate wins or invite help from another department. Use the time to help team members build connections with one another — a matrix — instead of hub-and-spoke connections with you at the center as the go-to problem solver.</p><p></p><p> Finally, try to include a time for collective reflection in a regular team meeting. Tarang Amin, CEO of elf Beauty, which posted 17 quarters of consecutive growth as of May 2023, begins every executive leadership team meeting with time for open sharing and reflection. “It&#39;s where execs can talk about what&#39;s going on in their personal lives, … their state of mind, what are important initiatives, what are things they&#39;re hearing in the organization,” he says.</p><p> Remember, it&#39;s typically not a lack of action items that hinders progress. It&#39;s more often misinterpretation of intent, misalignment of understanding, and the emotional toll of change that holds us back. And what solves those problems are trusting relationships that enable good communication. So instead of diving into the <em>what</em> of the next meeting you plan, begin with the <em>who</em> and the relationships among them. Your team just might rediscover the energy and joy that come with engaging with one another — and even begin to look forward to meetings.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Using Federated Machine Learning to Overcome the AI Scale Disadvantage</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yannick Bammens and Paul Hünermund. <p>Yannick Bammens is professor of strategy and innovation at Hasselt University in Belgium, where he coleads the AI4Business initiative. Paul Hünermund is assistant professor of strategy and innovation at Copenhagen Business School in Denmark, where he co-organizes the yearly Causal Data Science Meeting.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Big Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Deep pockets, access to talent, and massive investments in computing infrastructure only partly explain why most major breakthroughs in artificial intelligence have come from a select group of Big Tech companies that includes Amazon, Google, and Microsoft. What sets the tech giants apart from the many other businesses seeking to gain an [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Bammens_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Deep pockets, access to talent, and massive investments in computing infrastructure only partly explain why most major breakthroughs in artificial intelligence have come from a select group of Big Tech companies that includes Amazon, Google, and Microsoft. What sets the tech giants apart from the many other businesses seeking to gain an edge from AI are the vast amounts of data they collect as platform operators. Amazon alone processes millions of transactions each month on its platform. All of that big data is a rich strategic resource that can be used to develop and train complex machine learning algorithms — but it&#39;s a resource that is out of reach for most enterprises.</p><p> Access to big data allows for more sophisticated and better-performing AI and machine learning models, but many companies must make do with much smaller data sets. For smaller companies and those operating in traditional sectors like health care, manufacturing, or construction, a lack of data is the biggest impediment to venturing into AI. The digital divide between big and small-data organizations is a serious concern due to self-reinforcing data network effects, where more data leads to better AI tools, which help attract more customers who generate more data, and so forth. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This gives bigger companies a strong competitive AI advantage, with small and midsize organizations struggling to keep up.</p><p></p><p> The idea of multiple small-scale companies pooling their data in a jointly controlled central repository has been around for a while, but concerns about data privacy may quash such initiatives. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Federated machine learning (FedML) is a recent innovative technology that overcomes this problem by means of privacy-preserving collaborative AI that uses decentralized data. FedML might turn out to be a game changer in addressing the digital divide between companies with and without big data and enabling a larger part of the economy to reap the benefits of AI. It&#39;s a technology that doesn&#39;t just sound promising in theory — it has already been successfully implemented in industry, as we&#39;ll detail below. But first, we&#39;ll explain how it works.</p><h3> Small Data and Federated Machine Learning</h3><p> FedML is an approach that allows small-data organizations to train and use sophisticated machine learning models. The definition of <em>small data</em> depends on the complexity of the problem being addressed by AI. In pharma, for example, having access to a million annotated molecules for drug discovery is relatively small in view of the vast chemical space. Other factors to consider include the sophistication of the machine learning technique, ranging from a simple logistic regression to a much more data-hungry neural network, as well as the accuracy needed for an application: For some AI applications (such as making a medical diagnosis), getting things right is simply more critical than for others (such as suggesting emojis when someone is typing). All else being equal, smaller organizations and those operating in traditional nondigital sectors are confronted with more serious data-related scale disadvantages.</p><p></p><p> A few useful tactics and techniques have already been conceived to help companies struggling with this problem, such as cross-firm data pooling, transfer learning (repurposing previously trained models), and self-supervised learning (training a model on an artificial data set). <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Yet the centralized approach of data pooling may not be suitable in several situations, such as when there are legal constraints prohibiting data transfers or strategic concerns regarding sensitive data that should be kept private. Likewise, transfer learning and self-supervised learning are viable approaches only when a company can build on earlier insights from machine learning models performing tasks in related domains, which may not always be feasible. FedML can be a powerful extra instrument in a small-data company&#39;s AI toolkit and serve as a critical complement to other small-data techniques.</p><p> In a federated learning setup, a machine learning model is trained on multiple decentralized servers controlled by different organizations, each with its own local data. They communicate with a central orchestrator that aggregates the individual model updates and coordinates the training process. (See “An Overview of Federated Machine Learning.”) In the simplest case, the learning objective would be to obtain basic descriptive facts of the data distribution, such as means or variances. Each company could, for example, compute the average failure rate of a certain manufacturing process at one of its plants and submit it to the orchestrator, which would then combine those individual contributions to form a more accurate joint estimate.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> An Overview of Federated Machine Learning</h4><p class="caption"> In a federated learning setup, a machine learning model is trained on multiple decentralized servers controlled by different organizations, each with its own local data. They communicate with a central orchestrator that aggregates the individual model updates and coordinates the training process. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Bammens_Fig1.png" alt="An Overview of Federated Machine Learning" /><br /></article></aside></div><p></p><p> FedML is a distributed machine learning technique that can be used for a variety of algorithms. For example, the weights or gradients of a neural network can be averaged across organizations in a similar manner. The orchestrator is responsible for setting up the initial model architecture and coordinating the training process, which typically takes place over multiple iterations. As a result, companies can train complex machine learning models with a large number of parameters that would otherwise be beyond their reach, given that the constraints of their local data would lead to suboptimal model accuracy.</p><p> Importantly, raw company data stays private, and only statistical data, like estimated weights and other parameters, are shared and aggregated when FedML is applied. This way, 10 collaborating small-data companies that each have access to <em>x</em> data points could achieve roughly similar predictive power with their AI/machine learning applications as one much bigger company with access to 10 times <em>x</em> data points, without compromising data privacy.</p><h3> FedML in Pharma</h3><p> Innovation in pharma is very expensive and time consuming. The <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/press-releases/deloittes-thirteenth-annual-pharmaceutical-innovation-report-pharma-r-and-d-return-on-investment-falls-in-post-pandemic-market.html">average cost</a> to bring a new drug to market is around $2.3 billion as of 2022, and the process can take more than 10 years. One of the key difficulties in drug discovery involves the extremely high number of possible molecules (an order of magnitude of 10 <sup>60</sup> ) and the associated challenge of finding molecules with promising qualities in that vast chemical space. Against the backdrop of such steep costs and the sheer number of molecular possibilities, high-performing predictive machine learning models are the keystone of pharma&#39;s AI-driven drug-discovery agenda. Pharma companies are also facing pressure as <a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/famga-big-tech-pharma/">Big Tech</a> players like Alphabet use their profound expertise in AI and machine learning to venture into drug discovery.</p><p> Cognizant of the reluctance to share drug discovery data, but also of the great potential of collaborative AI to boost efficiencies in drug discovery, Hugo Ceulemans, the scientific director at Janssen Pharmaceutica, began floating the FedML idea and initiating talks with peers around 2016. His efforts eventually contributed to the formation of the Melloddy consortium by 10 pharma companies in 2019. In a blog post, Ceulemans noted that while pharmaceutical companies had previously pooled data to support predictive efforts, the scope of collaboration had been limited, given that data is an expensive competitive asset. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Because the new FedML consortium would allow the underlying data contributions to remain under the control of the respective data owners and not be shared, a much more ambitious scope would be possible, he explained.</p><p> Melloddy, a term named for <em>machine learning ledger orchestration for drug discovery</em> , was a three-year pilot project aimed at testing FedML for feasibility and effectiveness. The project was cofunded by the European Union; the European Commission considered Melloddy to be a test case for generating insights for business sectors beyond pharma. Participating companies included AstraZeneca, Bayer, GSK, Janssen Pharmaceutica, Merck, and Novartis, among others. These companies were supported by technology and academic partners, including Owkin (an AI biotech venture) and KU Leuven (a university with expertise in AI-driven drug discovery).</p><p> By leveraging one another&#39;s data without actually sharing it, the participating pharma companies could train their machine learning models on the world&#39;s largest drug-discovery data set, which enabled more accurate predictions on promising molecules and boosted efficiencies in the drug discovery process. In a blog post, Mathieu Galtier, chief product officer at Owkin, explained that thanks to Melloddy&#39;s use of federated learning, data never left the infrastructure of any pharma partner. The machine learning process occurred locally at each participating pharmaceutical company, and only the models were shared. “An important research effort is devoted to guaranteeing that only statistical information is shared between partners,” he wrote. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> The results of the Melloddy pilot project, which concluded in 2022, revealed that creating a secure multiparty platform for collaborative AI using decentralized data is feasible and that the performance of machine learning models is indeed enhanced by using a FedML approach.</p><h3> Strategic Considerations for FedML Consortia</h3><p> When setting up a FedML consortium, those involved in the planning process must carefully consider the optimal approach for orchestrating the technology and incentivizing partners. The selected orchestrator assumes a pivotal role in effectively managing the FedML process. Leaders of small-data organizations are sometimes reluctant to team up with Big Tech companies because they can maintain greater strategic control and build closer ties with smaller tech partners that operate on an equal footing. And some even fear that Big Tech companies will themselves move into their sector, as is happening in pharma.</p><p> In the case of Melloddy, pharma companies chose Owkin, a startup, to take on the responsibility of orchestrating the consortium&#39;s FedML platform. This may be a good approach for many FedML initiatives, but it can be risky, given the high failure rate of startups: A consortium might crumble if the startup fails. There is also a potential risk that the startup might raise funding from a competitor that is not participating in the consortium; it&#39;s an awkward situation, but not unlikely. Therefore, if a startup venture is chosen as the prime technology orchestrator, the consortium partners should seriously consider the option of investing corporate venture capital (CVC). <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> When the partners have a sizable joint CVC stake in the startup, with rights of first refusal, they have much stronger control over the length of the tech startup&#39;s runway and its future trajectory.</p><p></p><p> FedML can give rise to an incentive problem, wherein some participants fail to use all relevant local data or neglect to invest in the necessary data infrastructure to improve the accuracy of their local models. They may choose not to put in the effort while relying on the data contributions made by other consortium partners. This free-riding behavior then undermines the motivation and participation of well-intentioned participants. To preempt this problem, the FedML consortium can agree on appropriate partner commitments in terms of the quantity and coverage of data contributed and specify them upfront in a contractual agreement. Local model updates can also be monitored by the orchestrator in terms of their contribution to the overall accuracy of the joint model, and the payment of a FedML service fee can be made proportionate to each partner&#39;s contribution to the federated learning process.</p><p></p><p> When taking first steps toward assembling a FedML consortium, securing partner buy-in is vital. Partners should therefore be involved in defining the consortium&#39;s objectives in exchange for their data commitments. The AI Canvas is a decision-making tool that can be useful in identifying and discussing machine learning use cases and required training data. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> When approaching partners, keep in mind that effective model updates in most FedML applications require access to local data on all relevant model variables. As a result, suitable partners are often found within the same industry, sharing similar business processes and data. Working with indirect competitors, such as those serving other geographic markets, instead of with direct competitors could be advantageous here to minimize potential conflicts. For small-data organizations venturing into FedML, it&#39;s advisable to start with achievable machine learning projects to establish momentum and build trust among partners before embarking on more ambitious projects.</p><p> FedML is still a young AI approach, developed in 2016 by a group of Google engineers. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> But progress in this field is fast paced, and we can expect a surge in its adoption across a range of business sectors. Forward-thinking leaders of small-data organizations who incorporate FedML into their strategic visions are better positioned to harness the transformative power of AI to shape their future success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Who Should Price a Gig?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jovana Karanovic, Elizabeth J. Altman, and Carmelo Cennamo. <p>Jovana Karanovic is an assistant professor at the Rotterdam School of Management at Erasmus University and the founder of the Reshaping Work foundation. Elizabeth J. Altman is an associate professor of management at the Manning School of Business at the University of Massachusetts Lowell; guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Future of the Workforce initiative; and coauthor of <cite>Workforce Ecosystems: Reaching Strategic Goals With People, Partners, and Technologies</cite> (MIT Press, 2023). Carmelo Cennamo is a professor of strategy and entrepreneurship at Copenhagen Business School, director of the Digital Markets Competition Forum, and affiliate professor and director of the Platform Economy &amp; Regulation Monitor at SDA Bocconi School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Platforms & Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted interviews with platform executives at four platform businesses — Malt, Ring Twice, Temper, and Wolt — that represent different industry sectors and price-setting models. They also conducted archival web-based research studying platform-based businesses in various regions of the world and evaluated their pricing models. They were provided with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Karanovic_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><ul><li> The authors conducted interviews with platform executives at four platform businesses — Malt, Ring Twice, Temper, and Wolt — that represent different industry sectors and price-setting models.</li><li> They also conducted archival web-based research studying platform-based businesses in various regions of the world and evaluated their pricing models.</li><li> They were provided with and analyzed data from a service platform that switched from a platform-controlled price setting to allowing service providers to set prices. This data is part of an ongoing research project by Jovana Karanovic, Hakan Özalp, Carmelo Cennamo, and Mark Boons.</li></ul></aside><p> Arriving at Boston&#39;s Logan International Airport after a tiring journey, Mia opened the Uber app to find a ride home. Her relief at seeing the message “Your Uber driver is arriving in 3 minutes” was short-lived because the driver canceled. In the next 30 minutes, half a dozen Uber drivers accepted her ride request, then canceled, before one eventually arrived. What was happening?</p><p> Uber, like many platform companies, needs to efficiently match service providers (drivers) and customers (riders). To do so, it must ensure that pricing is competitive enough for riders to choose the service and for drivers to have the incentive to deliver it. Mia struggled to get a ride because Uber had started providing more earnings transparency for drivers by allowing them to see their expected compensation and route destinations before picking up riders. A change intended to benefit drivers had a significant downside for riders: More drivers began canceling rides they deemed unprofitable.</p><p></p><p> The question of who sets prices, and what discretion other parties in the transaction have to alter them in order to achieve mutually beneficial outcomes, is complex and nuanced for platform operators. In the case of Uber, the platform sets the price for the ride, and though drivers can opt out if their earning potential is unattractive, both drivers and riders have no flexibility for proposing different pricing. It&#39;s one of the drawbacks to having the locus of control primarily in the hands of the platform provider.</p><p> While algorithmically determined prices set by the platform operator are common among ride-hailing and food delivery services, other kinds of platform businesses allow service providers or customers to set prices. Fiverr, an online marketplace that matches high-skilled service providers with customers for tasks such as programming or graphic design, lets freelancers name their rates. In contrast, Temper, a Dutch platform for shift work in hospitality, retail, and logistics, lets customers (such as restaurants and shops) determine what the gig pays.</p><p> Controlling all pricing can lead to unintended consequences for a platform, as the Uber example shows, but allowing other stakeholders to set prices can also have drawbacks. For example, Ring Twice, a Belgian platform business that offers a variety of household services, such as gardening and babysitting, assigned pricing control to customers. It turned out that customers knew what they wanted — but not necessarily how much time and effort a specific task would take. Allowing customers to set prices resulted in fewer matches because many customers offered lower payments than service providers were willing to accept. Fewer successful job matches meant lost revenue for the platform.</p><p> Granting price-setting control is a major strategic decision that ultimately determines value creation and capture and establishes the power dynamics between the platforms themselves, service providers, and customers. Creating a scenario where all three stakeholders find the pricing model sustainable and beneficial is the key challenge that platform leaders face. To help leaders work through this decision, we offer a framework for understanding the key trade-offs of different platform price-setting approaches. Beyond economic considerations, we emphasize the need for managers to anticipate power dynamics and adopt hybrid approaches to mitigate them. (See “Pricing Dynamics on Gig Platforms.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Pricing Dynamics on Gig Platforms</h4><p class="caption"> Platform operators must understand the key trade-offs of handing pricing power to different stakeholders; sharing that power through hybrid approaches is often the most sustainable option. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%"> Who Controls Pricing</th><th style="width:25%"> Benefits</th><th style="width:25%"> Risks</th><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%"> Hybrid Solution</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>PLATFORM</strong></p></td><td><p> Algorithmic pricing based on capturing market data can maximize efficiency in markets for standardized services.</p></td><td><p> Real-time price adjustments can disadvantage either providers or customers. Lack of predictability can damage trust.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Set a base rate and enable providers to adjust prices upward or customers to make offers.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Provide price guarantees in line with living wages.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>PROVIDER</strong></p></td><td><p> The service provider&#39;s ability to set prices incentivizes high-quality providers to join. More variability on a platform serves long-tail demand.</p></td><td><p> Underpricing can drive down the perceived value of services across the platform. Overpricing can drive away customers and limit platform growth.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Allow for price and contractual negotiations between customers and providers.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Give price recommendations and share market data with providers.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>CUSTOMER</strong></p></td><td><p> Customers can control their own costs, which may increase engagement with and perceived value of the platform to customers.</p></td><td><p> Offering pay rates that are too low can drive away providers, thus limiting platform growth.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Set minimum price thresholds in line with living wages.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Assist customers by sharing market data and/or giving price recommendations. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Karanovic_table-1.png" alt="Pricing Dynamics on Gig Platforms" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><h3> When Platforms Call the Shots</h3><p> A platform can benefit from numerous advantages by retaining price-setting control, especially in certain segments. The practice is prevalent in ride-hailing, food delivery, and parcel delivery, where services are fairly standardized, volume is high, and logistics rapidly gain complexity with scale.</p><p> By retaining control, platforms can optimize for efficiency, particularly when they serve a large number of customers with similar needs. To set optimal prices, platforms leverage the large amount of transaction data they collect. Consider the Finnish platform Wolt, recently acquired by DoorDash, which offers food delivery, among other services. Wolt relies on parameters such as a courier&#39;s distance from the restaurant, food preparation time, and distance from the customer. Using this information, it advises couriers on the best routes to take and provides relevant extra information (for example, building entrance locations) to ensure swift delivery — and time savings. As a Wolt manager explained to us, the platform&#39;s interest in efficiency aligns with the couriers&#39; desire to take the optimal route, hence standardizing the delivery process as well as prices makes sense.</p><p> Controlling prices also allows the platform to maximize revenue by making quick adjustments based on market conditions: When demand is high, ride-hailing and delivery platforms commonly increase prices in real time. Platforms can also experiment with different pricing strategies.</p><p></p><p> Finally, by controlling the price, a platform provider can offer discounts and promotions to attract and retain customers. It may choose to offer personalized pricing based on customer behavior, preferences, and purchase history. Amazon, for example, utilizes such data to set dynamic pricing for certain items. When a customer views a product on Amazon, they may see a price that is different from what another customer might see for the same product. This is because Amazon&#39;s pricing algorithms take into account the customer&#39;s browsing and purchasing history, their location, and other variables to determine an individualized price that maximizes the likelihood of a purchase.</p><p> However, there are trade-offs to platforms retaining pricing control, particularly when it comes to the impact on power dynamics between stakeholders. In particular, service providers may decline to accept jobs if prices are set too low by the platform, or they may struggle to attract customers if their prices are set too high. In both cases, the service provider has less incentive to engage with the platform. A study examining posts to a forum for Uber drivers in US cities found that they discussed intentionally turning off their apps to appear unavailable in order to get the algorithm to implement higher surge pricing designed to incentivize drivers to get on the road. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> The drivers essentially had to game the system to get the prices they wanted, reflecting — and exacerbating — a lack of trust between providers and the platform.</p><p> Platform-controlled pricing also goes hand in hand with a standardized menu of services that might not adequately meet some customers&#39; needs. They may use the platform for finding a service provider and then arrange subsequent interactions off the platform. A recent study indeed found that providers&#39; dissatisfaction with platform rules and fees, as well as customers&#39; desires for more personalized services, are among the main factors contributing to disintermediation. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> When customers and providers are dissatisfied with platform-imposed rules, they are less likely to transact on the platform (lowering revenues), and the platform&#39;s reputation may suffer among all disaffected stakeholder groups.</p><p></p><h3> Putting Service Providers in Control</h3><p> There are also advantages when service providers are in control of price setting — common practice on freelance marketplaces such as Upwork, Toptal, and Malt. Granting this autonomy provides a competitive and flexible pricing environment, which is particularly advantageous for customers seeking specific capabilities for unique project needs. Similarly, providers can more effectively monetize their skills or unusual talents.</p><p> When providers set prices for a project, they can account for their costs, the effort they are willing to exert, and the service quality they can offer — information that the platform doesn&#39;t have but needs in order to set an adequate price. Price setting also lets service providers exercise their entrepreneurial freedom and adjust prices based on intangible factors such as their personal interest in a particular project. For example, they might charge less to land an assignment that will help them build valuable expertise, according to a manager at Malt, a European platform for services such as consulting and software development.</p><p> When service providers are able to set their own pricing and offer differentiated services, the platform can meet long-tail demand for niche offerings. Helpling, a platform for housecleaning services in Germany, France, Switzerland, England, Ireland, Italy, and Singapore, provides a case in point. The platform initially had a model where, within a given market, it set a standard price per hour for recurring cleaning jobs. (The slightly higher price for one-off jobs was also standardized within markets.) However, after a few years, Helpling changed its approach to let providers set their own prices. Our research shows that prices for some jobs subsequently increased as providers became willing to do different kinds of jobs (for example, after-party cleanups) for a higher fee. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The platform&#39;s policy change apparently revealed unmet demand for additional services.</p><p> Allowing service providers to set prices also improves the customer experience in categories where the quality of service is more likely to vary by provider. Different quality levels for comparable services can create uncertainty and diminish satisfaction. Lower quality is often due to providers lacking incentive to exert the required effort when customers pay a standard price set by the platform business. If providers get to set their own prices that reflect their true value, they can reap the rewards of their greater efforts and deliver higher customer satisfaction.</p><p></p><p> This approach does have downsides. When platform operators relinquish price-setting control and providers overcharge, that can lower overall matching and transaction volumes; if providers undercharge, that can leave money on the table. At Malt, where service providers have full control of price setting, they tend to underprice themselves despite deep knowledge of what&#39;s required to perform tasks and their level of expertise. But that can be a vicious circle, according to the Malt manager we interviewed: Clients who are attracted to low-cost providers may be less discerning. Without a way for customers to differentiate between high- and low-quality providers listed on the platform, there&#39;s a risk that low prices will increasingly attract clients looking for more basic, lower-quality services. This drives out high-quality providers and potentially downgrades the brand equity and reputation of the platform. It might also lead to a race to the bottom, with providers consistently lowering prices to outcompete one another, reducing the platform&#39;s margins and providers&#39; earnings (and their willingness to remain on the platform).</p><p> For customers, provider pricing puts other dynamics into play. Providers that choose to focus on lucrative niches may leave some demand unmet. And the greater variability in provider-set pricing makes it more difficult for customers to fairly compare prices and find the best value for their money. If selecting a service provider becomes too time-consuming, customers may abandon the platform altogether.</p><h3> Customers Name Their Price</h3><p> Temper, the Dutch shift-work platform, allows customers to decide what they are willing to pay and matches skilled workers, such as baristas, with venues, such as restaurants. This approach is most appropriate when customers are businesses that have precise requirements for the services they need and the amount they are willing to pay.</p><p> Under this model, customers can set prices that reflect their budget and desired level of service, and service providers can choose to accept or reject offers based on their own pricing policies and cost structures. At Temper, restaurants looking for shift workers have different cost structures — for example, those in a city center pay higher rents. They also vary by service quality (for example, fine dining versus fast-casual), which affects the skills profiles they need and therefore the pay they will offer to attract workers. Customers can control their costs but also have flexibility to adapt to the competitive environment — for example, by offering higher compensation for weekend shifts. The platform exposes the going rate that other businesses are offering for the same services, which can also inform pricing decisions.</p><p> Finally, customers may be more motivated to use a platform if they have greater control over the pricing process. If they are given the power to determine the value they place on the service, they may feel more satisfied as well as invested in the transaction. Being more in control on the platform may deepen a sense of ownership and increase engagement and loyalty.</p><p> Naturally, customer-set pricing has trade-offs that can affect platform operators and providers. If customers set prices too low, service providers may be unwilling to take the task or they may be incentivized to cut corners to maintain profitability. This in turn could lead to a decline in the overall quality of products or services, reducing the platform&#39;s attractiveness and growth potential. Similarly, customers may not have access to complete information about the market dynamics, costs, and competitive landscape, leading to suboptimal outcomes for both providers and customers.</p><h3> Strike a Balance With Hybrid Approaches</h3><p> Whether pricing is controlled by the platform, service provider, or customer, under appropriate circumstances each choice has the potential to maximize value creation and efficiency. Nonetheless, dynamics that unfold among platforms&#39; different stakeholders may outweigh some of these benefits and lead to unintended consequences. To ensure long-term sustainability and enhance a platform business&#39;s financial performance, platform managers may want to share some control over pricing.</p><p> Platform providers can consider hybrid approaches to do this. For instance, TaskRabbit sets standard prices for different types of tasks based on factors such as complexity, duration, and market rates. These standard prices are initially determined by the platform to provide consistency and guidance to both customers and gig workers. However, TaskRabbit also allows service providers to adjust prices based on their own preferences and circumstances, and set a price that can be higher or lower than the platform&#39;s standard prices. The European Union has a proposed platform work directive that considers the right to set one&#39;s own rate a distinguishing factor between freelancers and employees; if adopted, it may push ride-hailing and food delivery platforms, which currently determine prices, to share this control with providers.</p><p> Platforms that control pricing can mitigate the power imbalance by being transparent with service providers about how prices are determined and whether they can do anything to increase earnings. They should also provide a mechanism for hearing providers&#39; concerns and enable them to appeal algorithmically determined decisions that affect their earnings on the platform.</p><p> While allowing service providers to set prices makes sense in some cases, it does not always lead to optimal pricing for them or the platform. For example, providers who have established high ratings and show a high number of completed tasks may have more pricing power compared with new providers. This is not beneficial for platforms, because new service providers quickly disengage if it takes too long to acquire work, limiting platform growth. Malt handles this discrepancy by boosting new providers&#39; visibility in search results.</p><p> Platforms can also assist providers with price setting, especially for offerings that are prone to demand fluctuations. A study of Airbnb found that only professional hosts (those with multiple properties) set prices skillfully; most others set suboptimal prices. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Airbnb introduced price recommendations, alerting hosts to events and time periods when demand is high and prompting them to increase prices. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Moreover, it lets hosts opt for automatic price adjustments, which essentially brings the price-setting power back to the platform, even in this service provider-controlled model.</p><p> When customers set prices, as we have seen, they may make lowball offers to service providers, especially during unfavorable market conditions. Platforms can prevent exploitation of service providers by setting minimum price thresholds that, for example, correspond to minimum or living wages. For instance, Temper sets a minimum price threshold for each service category that is in line with minimum wages, although it is not required to do so under Dutch law. In addition, it allows providers to negotiate. In 2022, 10% of all transactions on Temper were negotiated upward compared with initial prices set by customers, one of the company&#39;s cofounders told us. Such proactive initiatives from platforms may anticipate increasing regulations aimed at curtailing their power. New York City already has imposed a minimum wage for Uber and Lyft drivers and recently announced the same for workers on food delivery apps. The European Union is going a step further: Its proposed directive will presume gig workers are employees of platforms if certain criteria do not apply, such as a worker&#39;s right to adjust platform-determined rates as they see fit. In other words, if a platform sets upper limits for pay, it may be viewed as an employer.</p><p></p><p> As we have noted, customers may not always be fully informed, or they may have very specific preferences, in which case platforms can assist them with making provider selections. For example, on freelance marketplace Upwork, customers post desired tasks they need accomplished such as “logo design” or “report writing,” with detailed descriptions of what they are looking for and the price they are willing to pay. This price-setting model works well when customers have specific preferences and need a specific kind of provider for the job. However, Upwork eventually realized that not all customers have clear preferences; some just want the service done and would rather select it from a menu of offerings. This led to the launch of Upwork&#39;s Project Catalog, a website offering predefined projects that customers can browse and select, such as “A 500-word SEO-optimized blog article in under 24 hours” for $50. Instead of customers detailing the job, providers post what they can offer for a set price. This makes it easier for customers to find the right provider for their needs and gives providers more opportunities to win work.</p><p></p><p> A platform&#39;s need to control its marketplace to maximize returns isn&#39;t going away, but the approach it takes will determine its long-term sustainability. Platform leaders must realize that a platform is not a unilateral, hierarchically managed entity but rather a web of economic and social relationships. To manage it successfully and ensure satisfaction for all parties, they must share some aspects of control with other stakeholders, allow for compromise, and step in to support their workforce when needed. When control is shared more equitably among all parties in the platform relationship, the platform model can cater more beneficially to all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Rethinking Governance for Digital Innovation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David L. Rogers. <p>David L. Rogers is faculty director of Columbia Business School&#39;s executive education programs on digital business strategy and leading digital transformation. He is the author of <cite>The Digital Transformation Roadmap: Rebuild Your Organization for Continuous Change</cite> (Columbia Business School Publishing, 2023), from which this article is adapted, as well as the bestselling <cite>The Digital Transformation Playbook</cite> (2016).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Process]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George When global chemical company BASF launched its Onono lab in São Paulo, Brazil, its mission was to accelerate innovation through rapid collaboration with local partners and startups. But Onono’s director, Antonio Lacerda, faced an immediate hurdle from corporate governance: He was told that his lab would have to follow the same corporate data [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Rogers_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George</p></figcaption></figure><p> When global chemical company BASF launched its Onono lab in São Paulo, Brazil, its mission was to accelerate innovation through rapid collaboration with local partners and startups. But Onono&#39;s director, Antonio Lacerda, faced an immediate hurdle from corporate governance: He was told that his lab would have to follow the same corporate data policies used to secure BASF&#39;s entire cloud infrastructure — which would have made it impossible to partner quickly and nimbly with new startups. Lacerda postponed the launch until he was able, with significant political capital, to arrange an exception: a “sandbox” of separate data for his team, with special permission to share that data through APIs with new partners.</p><p> Lacerda&#39;s experience, and that of so many innovation champions, points to a fundamental problem for digital transformation: In large companies, innovation teams are left to fight for waivers in the face of business rules that contradict their own mandate for change. But innovation will never happen at scale as long as it relies on ad hoc exceptions approved by senior leaders. Instead, we must rethink our approach to governance and design new management practices for innovation at the speed of digital.</p><p></p><p> Designing repeatable processes for innovation is essential for growth in the digital era, yet it is incredibly hard. In too many organizations, new ventures are green-lit based on a single executive sponsor. Once started, ventures move slowly, managed by teams that sit in traditional silos. Resource allocation is slow too, as promising projects wait weeks or months for their next round of approvals. Because each project is backed by an influential executive, no one wants to shut it down, even if it shows little promise.</p><p> Meanwhile, risk aversion leads businesses to fund only their low-hanging fruit — incremental improvements in the core that bring a guaranteed, quick ROI. This path will never lead to transformation. Instead, you need governance that embraces uncertainty and supports growth both within and beyond the core. (See “How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation </h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:50%"> Signs of <em>Poor</em> Governance</th><th style="width:50%"> Signs of <em>Good</em> Governance</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> A top executive must personally approve any new innovation.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Established structures provide resources and governance for innovation.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> New ventures move slowly, led by traditional teams in functional silos.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> New ventures move fast, led by highly independent, multifunctional teams.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Allocating resources to new ventures is slowed by the annual budgeting cycle.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Resource allocation happens quickly through iterative funding.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Innovation is limited to a few big projects, which are hard to shut down once they are started.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> A steady pipeline of innovations is managed with smart shutdowns to free up resources.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> The only ventures to gain support are low-risk innovations in the core business.</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Governance supports ventures with low and high uncertainty, both in the core and beyond. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Rogers_table-1.png" alt="How Governance Helps or Hinders Innovation" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p> Digital transformation requires that governance be carefully designed to address several issues. The first is <em>oversight</em> . Who approves new projects? To whom do they report? And who shuts them down? Next is <em>funding</em> . How will you allocate resources across a portfolio of ventures to maximize opportunities for success? Equally critical are <em>people</em> . Who will staff new ventures, whether inside or outside your organization? How will teams be formed with the right mix of skills? Governance must also include <em>metrics</em> . How will you measure the progress of new ventures? And, crucially, how can you bring discipline to regularly <em>shutting down</em> ventures, a practice so often neglected at large enterprises?</p><p> In this article, we will discuss how to design governance models to drive digital innovation across any enterprise, by focusing on two critical work groups: the people engaged in building new ventures and those overseeing and assessing their work. We&#39;ll delve into the top governance issues for managing growth at scale, including how venture teams and supervisory boards work together. And we will explore how to manage ongoing decisions to green-light new ventures, grant additional funding to those that merit it, and shut down others to free up resources.</p><h3> Design Teams to Drive Innovation</h3><p> Decades of experience have shown us that, in established businesses and small startups, meaningful new growth always starts in one place: small teams, effectively empowered. These teams do the work of rapid, iterative experimentation, which is at the heart of every modern approach to innovation — whether agile, design thinking, lean startup, or product management. Every innovation team&#39;s job is to take a proposed new venture and rapidly test every facet of its business model to validate what will or will not work in the market.</p><p> Within any established enterprise, the rules governing innovation teams are critical to their success. Many readers will be familiar with the idea of small multifunctional teams. But size and composition are only part of what matters for team success. By studying innovation in digital natives like Amazon and Google, and digital transformers like Walmart and Mastercard, I have identified five essential pillars of team governance. Great innovation teams are:</p><p> <strong>Small.</strong> Research has shown that small teams communicate, coordinate, and make decisions much faster than large ones. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Small teams are foundational to agile methods, which use a rapid cadence of short sprints in which every team must deliver new working code, test and learn, and adjust priorities. At Amazon, innovation teams are called two-pizza teams because each one should be small enough to be fed by two pizzas (a maximum of eight people).</p><p> <strong>Multifunctional.</strong> Great innovation teams have diverse members who cut across functional silos (for example, marketing, engineering, and design). The goal is for each team to have members who can provide all the essential skills needed to do its work. Instead of constantly waiting for another department&#39;s input before taking the next step in its project, a multifunctional team is able to push ahead entirely on its own.</p><p> <strong>Single-threaded.</strong> The best innovation teams have all members dedicated full time to the team&#39;s work. At a minimum, the innovation team&#39;s leader must be single-threaded, meaning they cannot be splitting their workweek between the team&#39;s new venture and other projects. Leading the team is their full responsibility.</p><p> <strong>Autonomous.</strong> Successful innovation teams have clear decision rights that give them the authority to work under their own direction. They should not need to get approval on their work from anyone outside the team — whether it is on product design, what tests to run next, or which customers to pursue. Autonomy also means there are no prohibitions on contracting resources from outside the company.</p><p> <strong>Accountable.</strong> Autonomy is possible only if the team is also clearly accountable for the results of its work. Here, good governance demands a clear definition of success, which is defined in terms of outcomes, not deliverables. That definition may include quantitative metrics as well as qualitative principles, and it must be agreed on with leadership before the team&#39;s work begins. Effective accountability also requires transparency: At any time, the team&#39;s results must be visible to anyone inside or outside the team. Every test run, every MVP built, and every metric tracked should be visible to anyone in the company.</p><h3> Establish Oversight With Growth Boards</h3><p> Innovation teams&#39; most critical partners are the managers who will allocate funds and oversee and support their work. In my experience, the most successful model for sponsoring corporate innovation is the board. In the board model, a small group regularly convenes and deliberates to decide whether to sponsor various possible innovation ventures — much like a group of VC investors listening to pitches from startups. One innovation board will sponsor and support multiple teams working in parallel.</p><p> This approach contrasts with what I have found to be all too common: organizations where new ventures are approved by a single sponsor. In these companies, one or more executives may use their clout within the organization to sponsor a new digital venture they deem strategically important and promising. This model is inherently ad hoc, with decisions based on the instincts and judgment of different individuals. And once a sponsor puts their name and reputation behind a project, it is very hard for them to let it die, no matter what market validation shows about its prospects. By contrast, the board model — with its greater diversity and impartiality of decision-making — is inherently better for managing innovation at scale.</p><p> Effective corporate innovation boards — also known variously as growth boards, venture boards, or growth councils — should number no more than eight people. They should include members with topical expertise and knowledge of the market. A board should be able to challenge company orthodoxy, advocate a long-term view, and bring in ideas from outside the industry. The best boards combine internal stakeholders from different divisions and at least one member with an external perspective. Members should be senior enough to have real clout in the organization but not so senior that they can&#39;t make board work a priority.</p><p> The job of the board is to regularly meet to green-light new ventures, provide strategic guidance to teams, decide on each stage of additional funding, and make disciplined decisions about when to shut down ventures. Here again, decision rights are critical. The innovation board must have complete funding authority for each team in its portfolio. Its decisions should be informed by open and lively debate with the team, but the decisions remain with the board. Other senior executives, including the CEO, may advise and provide input on ventures, but they cannot vote on or overrule the board&#39;s investment decisions.</p><p></p><h3> Green-Light New Projects</h3><p> The first process where boards and teams must work together is green-lighting — that is, approving new ventures to start work. When a board green-lights a new venture, it should allocate just enough resources (in the form of time, money, and people) for the team to conduct a first round of testing to validate the initial questions about the business model. The key to effective green-lighting is to <em>minimize</em> the initial investment made in each team and <em>maximize</em> the number of ideas that are approved to be tested.</p><p> This approach may seem counterintuitive — it certainly contrasts with the tendency to try to “pick a winner and bet big,” seen at so many organizations with poor innovation governance. In fact, it is important for boards to resist the urge to try to pick the best ideas among those submitted. First, the board has truly no way of knowing which ideas will work. That knowledge can be gained only through testing and validation. Second, successful ventures often emerge from ideas that are initially flawed but evolve in response to testing, feedback, and iterative design. Instead of trying to evaluate the likelihood of success, I recommend that boards judge new venture pitches based on their problem definition, strategic fit, and team mindset.</p><p></p><p> To green-light many innovation ideas, it is essential to build a fast, cheap, and effective validation process. This means bringing in the voice of the customer to rapidly test whether the venture is focused on solving a genuine problem. At Citibank, new ventures often begin with a two- or three-day workshop in which employees explore a problem/opportunity statement and have a chance to develop their own innovation ideas in a rapid, iterative fashion with actual customers. As you increase the speed and drive down the cost of your first stage of validation, your business can afford to approve more venture teams to test and pursue more possible ideas for growth.</p><h3> Manage Resources With Iterative Funding</h3><p> The next critical process for managing innovation is iterative funding, which is how boards allocate resources to teams after their ventures have been green-lit. Iterative funding is designed to be extremely agile, based on the VC approach to financing startups. At each board review (typically every 30, 60, or 90 days), the board will review each team&#39;s progress, including new data from its tests in the market, and decide whether to release the next tranche of resources to that team.</p><p> Iterative funding is a dramatically different process from traditional budgeting in large enterprises. Here&#39;s why it&#39;s a better approach for managing investments in new innovation:</p><p> <strong>Get off to a faster start.</strong> In a traditional budgeting process, a new project will be granted a large initial sum that reflects commitment to the project. But that happens only after a long period of analysis that strives (misguidedly) to assess the chances of an uncertain new venture through benchmarks and third-party data. Iterative funding, in contrast, gives ventures a small initial budget but allows teams to get started fast, if the opportunity they are pursuing is well defined and strategically relevant.</p><p> <strong>Be more agile with shorter funding cycles.</strong> Corporate budgets are typically set annually, with projects and departments funded through a complex process that takes months. A promising new venture can wind up waiting over a year to get resources for a four-week test. In contrast, when boards meet frequently and funding rounds provide teams with just one to three months of resources, decision-making is much more agile.</p><p> <strong>Invest based on real-world data.</strong> Many leaders will overcommit funds to an untested new venture because they have a personal conviction that the strategy is right or because they are swayed by the persuasive talents of the team. With an iterative funding process, the board decides on each round of resources based entirely on real-world data. Every time they meet, the board and the team must agree on what data the team needs to bring to its next review meeting. Those metrics — typically three to six key variables — will shift over time, depending on the biggest sources of uncertainty still facing the new venture. They capture what the venture team has learned so far and what it needs to learn next.</p><p> <strong>Scale fast to drive exponential growth.</strong> In traditional budgeting, when funding is renewed, any increase is only incremental from the previous budget. With iterative funding, if validation is successful and a venture moves ahead, the size of each investment round should grow exponentially. Allocation of human resources should increase as well. This means that innovation teams that uncover meaningful growth opportunities can scale quickly to make a measurable impact on the company&#39;s bottom line.</p><p> Clearly, iterative funding requires that boards be ready to ramp up investment quickly in ventures that prove themselves in the market. That means the enterprise must fund a pool of resources in advance, for the board to allocate over the course of a year and across a portfolio of projects.</p><p> Within each portfolio, similar innovations (for example, a portfolio of high-risk innovations within a single business unit) should compete for funds. Don&#39;t let apples compete with oranges. First fund the portfolio for a specific class of innovations, and then let the board iteratively fund the various ventures.</p><h3> Make a Habit of Smart Shutdowns</h3><p> Of course, not every team review will conclude with a decision to continue funding. One of the classic problems that bedevil corporate innovation is that companies learn how to start new projects but not how to stop them. For innovation to deliver results, companies must be ready to exit projects that prove unsuccessful or are insufficiently aligned with strategy.</p><p> Shutting down ventures systematically and regularly is a critical job for growth boards. Every time a board meets for an iterative funding review, the question must be, “Do we fund this venture further or shut it down?”</p><p></p><p> At legacy companies, the biggest barrier to shutting down innovation projects is often an aversion to admitting failure and an irrational feeling that any kind of failure poses too much risk. But the cost of failures is minimal when they are shut down early, through iterative funding. In contrast, there are very real costs to the company if your teams do not shut down ventures quickly and smartly. Without this discipline, your innovation will lack focus, your resources will be spread too thin, and you will run out of bandwidth for new experiments. You will be stuck with <em>zombie projects</em> — unsuccessful ventures that never shut down and continue siphoning off resources. At Johnson &amp; Johnson, an entire new series of innovations was funded by evaluating the existing portfolio and shutting down projects that no longer matched the company&#39;s updated strategy. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> Halting projects will become easier only if you make it a routine decision, and here innovation boards with a regular calendar of funding reviews will make a huge difference. In GE&#39;s oil and gas division, projects were rarely shut down before its board was instituted. As soon as the board began, it easily shut down 20% of existing projects in its first 90-day cycle. As the board and teams became focused on aligning to strategy, this rose to 50% of new ventures shutting down within 60 days. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> At media giant Schibsted, the goal is to remove one venture whenever adding something new to the development pipeline. When a project comes up for review, set a high bar for yourself by asking, “Why shouldn&#39;t we shut this venture down?”</p><p> The following five practices are essential to achieving smart shutdowns in any organization:</p><p> <strong>Plan a pipeline with survival rates.</strong> Innovation at scale requires planning for most new ventures to be shut down. Only a third to a half of bright, shiny new ideas typically survive their first funding review after they&#39;ve had contact with real customers. Survival rates typically increase in subsequent rounds. Understanding your survival rates at different stages of validation will allow you to plan a pipeline for the future. For example, if a board is expected to help bring three or four new ventures to market within a year, it needs to plant enough seeds at the start to have good odds for success.</p><p> <strong>Use a venture backlog to reassign swiftly.</strong> An innovation board should maintain a ranked list of ideas for ventures that have been approved but not yet begun. Using this backlog in your review process will make shutdowns much easier. The point is no longer simply to kill a failing idea but to free the team and its resources to work on a more promising idea from the backlog. So, when you shutter a project, quickly reassign members to the best next idea. In many cases, that may just mean refocusing that team on a different solution to the same problem.</p><p> <strong>Extract value from shutdowns.</strong> When you decide to shut down a project, look to extract as much value as possible. In some cases, a company may be able to sell the venture to another business. When Walmart&#39;s Vudu streaming video service was no longer a strong strategic fit, Walmart spun it off to media giant Comcast. Sometimes a venture is promising but not yet workable; by shrinking your investment, you may maintain your future options. After Google Glass failed as a consumer product, the company shrank the project to an enterprise-only device focused on applications on factory floors. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Sometimes only a full shutdown makes sense, and the key value to extract is the learning gained from experimentation. When Amazon shut down its Amazon Auctions and zShops services, it applied the lessons it learned for the subsequent launch of Amazon Marketplace to great success.</p><p> <strong>Share learning widely.</strong> Sharing what you learn from failed ventures is one of the hardest principles to follow. Most companies prefer to look away from projects that didn&#39;t work out. In a 2014 internal report on its early digital transformation efforts, The New York Times Co. admitted, “When we do shut down projects, the decisions are made quietly and rarely discussed, to protect the reputations of the people who ran them. As a result, lessons are forgotten, and the staffers involved become more risk averse.” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Overcoming this reluctance was essential to the ultimate turnaround of The New York Times Co. and its business model. The German affiliate of Fédération Internationale de l&#39;Automobile (FIA) ran an innovation lab where eight of 10 projects were killed in a single year. Its biggest win? Sharing those results with other FIA affiliates around the world that were struggling with the same challenges in their own markets.</p><p> <strong>Distinguish people from projects.</strong> This is a final critical piece to building a culture that accepts and learns from innovation failures. A strong board review process will hold teams accountable for their results. But you should be careful not to associate a failed project with the merit of the individuals who worked on it. Those same team members could achieve tremendous success for you in their next project. Be sure to encourage your innovators to keep working on their next idea.</p><p> If your process for shutdowns is truly working, you will begin to see volunteering. When teams are truly focused on validating growth opportunities through experimentation, they will often suggest their own shutdown to the board, reporting, “Here&#39;s what we have learned and why we recommend shutting down now.” Don&#39;t be surprised when those same employees soon return to their board with another venture idea. It could be your next big breakthrough.</p><p></p><p></p><p> For digital transformation to deliver real growth and value to any organization, it must involve more than isolated pockets of innovation from teams struggling under the yoke of ill-suited management. Without new governance models to manage new ventures, the potential for digital innovation will always fall short.</p><p> Innovation governance requires three key building blocks: (1) Teams must be empowered to move fast and experiment to discover what works in the marketplace; (2) boards must be empowered to oversee and advise portfolios of teams, allocating resources where most needed; and (3) both must follow regular processes for green-lighting new ventures, funding them iteratively, and shutting them down to free up resources for the next emerging opportunity.</p><p> With the right governance in place, established companies of every kind can unlock the potential in their own employees to drive transformation and growth at every level of their business.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Images and Inspiration With AI: Pinterest&#39;s Jeremy King</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jeremy King leads a team of 1,400 passionate engineers working on the continuous improvement of Pinterest’s image-driven platform. With a background that includes heading up a translation team at eBay and overseeing the technology behind Walmart’s U.S. retail stores and e-commerce business, Jeremy is now responsible for technology operations at Pinterest. To support the company’s [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Jeremy King leads a team of 1,400 passionate engineers working on the continuous improvement of Pinterest&#39;s image-driven platform. With a background that includes heading up a translation team at eBay and overseeing the technology behind Walmart&#39;s US retail stores and e-commerce business, Jeremy is now responsible for technology operations at Pinterest. To support the company&#39;s mission to inspire people to “create a life that they love,” he and his team rely on advanced AI, machine learning, and a graph database to index and build a network of images so that users can find inspiration — particularly when they aren&#39;t completely sure what they&#39;re looking for.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Jeremy joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to talk about some recent advances Pinterest has made in the image-recognition space and shares his views on how generative AI will transform image-based content like Pinterest&#39;s. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E6-King-Pinterest-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="杰里米·金"></p><h4> Jeremy King, Pinterest</h4><p> Jeremy King is senior vice president of technology at Pinterest, where he leads the company&#39;s technical vision and the engineering organization responsible for building and scaling a visual discovery engine.</p><p> Before joining Pinterest, he was CTO and senior vice president at Walmart, where he led the team responsible for the technology behind US retail stores and e-commerce for Walmart and Jet, and oversaw customer, merchant, and supply chain technologies across cloud and data platforms. King has also held executive-level technology roles at Walmart Labs, LiveOps, and eBay.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does an AI-based platform use generative AI to engage users? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I&#39;m Jeremy King from Pinterest, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome. Our guest today is Jeremy King, head of engineering at Pinterest. Jeremy, thanks for taking the time to talk with us.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> It&#39;s great to be here.非常感谢。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s always good to start with an overview; maybe tell us a bit about what Pinterest does and what you do at Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Pinterest is, we like to say, the destination on the internet for inspiration. We have hundreds of millions of people that come to us every day to figure out what they want to wear, what they want to do this afternoon, or what they want to make for dinner, or how to decorate their kid&#39;s cake or remodel their kitchen. And so we want to build a platform that allows anyone to create a life that they love.</p><p> It&#39;s a great place to work with that kind of mission, and I have a lot of people who, when I tell them where I work, get pretty elated about their own Pinterest boards and what&#39;s going on in the world.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Great. Tell us more about working at Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I&#39;ve been at Pinterest now, the head of engineering, for just over four years. And just like any leader, I&#39;m trying to figure out how to unblock my team and hire great people. I tell people all the time that when I came to Pinterest, I was just so impressed with the level of talent. It&#39;s a relatively small team. We have 4,500 employees in the world and about 1,400 engineers. And as a result, competing against some of the biggest companies in the world, this team has to be extremely high caliber. We have some of the best graph database people in the world; we have the best computer vision people in the world. These people are really fun to work with.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> None of that, so far, mentioned artificial intelligence, so, what role does artificial intelligence play with those 1,400 engineers?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, that&#39;s an excellent point. One of the things that is true at Pinterest and now at many other companies is Pinterest was actually born with machine learning and AI from the base. It doesn&#39;t exist without it. So talking about AI and ML separately from Pinterest is almost like a misnomer; it really doesn&#39;t happen without it. Nearly everything that we do touches our machine learning systems. We do millions of inferences every second. Every single request comes all the way back to the graph and publishes back out a very specific use case to every single person.</p><p> It&#39;s not cached. … Every person has a specific result. I mentioned that we have about 1,400 engineers. We have about 350 machine learning engineers. As a percentage, when I tell other CTOs … they&#39;re like, “That&#39;s a really high percentage of machine learning people compared to my company.” That&#39;s true also on the data platform side; we have a wonderful leader, Dave Burgess, who runs our data platform. And you can imagine our data platform is about as important as any other part of our capabilities. And so I mentioned the graph, but it&#39;s also, you know, the sort of normal SQL databases and the real-time systems that keep this thing running.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Jeremy, you said “graphs” a couple of times. What&#39;s a graph?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Essentially what a graph is, is if you take an entity, an object, and you say, “What&#39;s related to that object?” — so, in this case, we&#39;re using a nearest neighbor graph, which we&#39;ve written lots of documents on, which is saying, “Hey, I have an image, in this case, and I have another image that&#39;s related to this image.” So that allows me to build this sort of network of images. And the reason the graph works at Pinterest is because every pin is essentially added to a board, which essentially makes it a node in a graph, and so it continues to increase the graph.</p><p> So it allows you to … unlike a SQL database or a relational database, where you have to sort of tag indexes and indices, the graph can be indexed. Essentially any image could be indexed to any other image. It allows you to do searches on things that are related incredibly efficiently. That&#39;s the power of Pinterest.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Jeremy, you mentioned AI has been part and parcel of Pinterest&#39;s journey and has been ingrained in Pinterest&#39;s tech stack from its very early inception, so it must be that generative AI is all over the map for you guys as well, and I&#39;m sure it&#39;s on everybody&#39;s mind these days. So maybe tell us a bit about what you are doing there.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> We have a state-of-the-art machine learning environment that interconnects these data sets across all the surfaces. We call it the “home feed,” the search system, the related things that drive personalization and recommendations and engagement across Pinterest. [And] we&#39;re growing really fast from monthly active users. … Gen Z is growing even the fastest. We added 13 million monthly active users, so we&#39;re really focused on how to increase engagement.</p><p> And not surprisingly, a lot of the improvements in machine learning, even in the last two years, have been driving that engagement. We have, of course, built new features [that] allow Pinterest to become more shoppable. But as we&#39;re seeing the capabilities of the machine learning models getting effectively 10 or a hundred times bigger, which is relatively common today, we&#39;re seeing that give an outsize increase in our results as the result gets more specific.</p><p> And frankly, Pinterest is also about looking at [vastly] different things. So it&#39;s not [that] every single item is about “What do you want to cook for dinner tonight?” It&#39;s also “I know you were looking at birthday cakes last week” or “New Year&#39;s is coming up,” and we&#39;re going to interplay some of that. So we&#39;ve been taking advantage of some of the advanced AI capabilities that have only come to life over the last couple years. And that includes GPU [graphics processing unit] work and all the things that make it cost-effective to do these things.</p><p> So tying back to your question of generative AI, not surprisingly, given that we&#39;re an image platform, generative AI is very interesting to us, and I typically break it up into three buckets. When we&#39;re thinking about large language models — LLMs — we talk about, No. 1, how do I make my team more productive? We&#39;ve got a couple of pilots running. We haven&#39;t decided exactly which way to go yet, but it&#39;s looking really promising, and, like lots of other CTOs, we&#39;re really excited about that.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s interesting. Tell us how generative AI increases efficiency.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I was talking to a number of CTOs, and one thing I thought was really interesting is, this one particular CTO was saying that, in general, it&#39;s increased productivity by 10% to 15%, but there is a small set of users where it&#39;s increased their productivity by 50%.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s fantastic. I was just going to say, it also feels like, if you go back a decade ago, there were lots of images and unstructured text and that kind of stuff that, for AI to train on that data and make sense of it, human intervention was needed, both to tag the content but also to make sure that the outputs made sense. And it feels like now, with gen AI, that a lot of those humanlike judgment calls are going to be made more and more with gen AI, particularly with lots of unstructured text and images and video and that kind of content. Is that right, or am I going too far?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think it&#39;s right. I mean, Pinterest&#39;s system is built on embedding, so you take an image or a piece of text and you essentially tag it — essentially, to your point, this is what Pinterest has really been great at. You take our computer vision technology and effectively build these embeddings to detect people or content or couches or birthday cakes.</p><p> We&#39;ve been really good at that and have really led the industry for a long time on this. And you&#39;re not wrong that what happens is, it just gets better; it gets more accurate, more specific. In the old days, I could say, “Hey, I know this is a lamp, and I know it&#39;s got pendants, and it&#39;s made of crystal, and it&#39;s gold,” and that sort of thing. But now I can say, “I know exactly how many tines it has on it; I know what kind of light bulbs they are; I know probably who manufactured it,” and these sorts of things. I can get way more specific.</p><p> And at Pinterest, we really think about these as two different things. People come to Pinterest because they don&#39;t know exactly what they want. And this is where Pinterest thrives, and I think why we have a long-term differentiation in the market. Because if you know what you want, you can always go to Amazon or Home Depot or Wayfair to go buy it, but if you don&#39;t know what you want, you start with Pinterest or do a million different searches because [you] don&#39;t know how to describe, you know, “classic barnyard kitchen” — [you] don&#39;t know those words.</p><p> So even putting it in something like ChatGPT, I don&#39;t know how to say that — you know what I mean? I&#39;m sure that&#39;ll get better over time, but a lot of it will be image-based, too, as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Are you finding that the foundational models that are available do it for you, or you&#39;re building your own domain-specific models?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Both, I guess, is the answer. What we&#39;re finding — and it&#39;s still relatively early — in sort of the generative imagery, what we&#39;re finding is that the smaller models actually are much more specific, and so I think that&#39;s what&#39;s going to happen. And my CTO friends are saying the same thing, which is, each one of these models is going to be very specific to the use case, and that helps it not only be more accurate but also makes it much, much cheaper to implement as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think it&#39;s interesting that you mentioned cakes several times, because decorating cakes is, I think, practically my only use of Pinterest. And it ties to Shervin&#39;s comment about generative, because I deeply suspect that those cakes that I see there, no human could create. I certainly can&#39;t create them. So to what degree are … people putting [up] images that don&#39;t really exist or products that don&#39;t exist? What&#39;s Pinterest&#39;s perspective on that?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Excellent point. I think, yes, and we see this a lot [in] one of our biggest categories we call “art.” Art includes a whole bunch of things, including things that you would traditionally put on walls, and paintings, and that sort of thing. But it also includes things like body art, and we have tattoos and these sorts of things. And again, lots of those are great cases where people need a little bit of inspiration, and it can be generative, right? It may not exist in the world, but you want to see what it looks like on a human.</p><p> You can see this coming, where you&#39;ll be able to print out something that&#39;s generative. And this is already happening, right?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah. That really aligns with the idea of inspiration.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And things like cakes and that sort of thing are very interesting. One of the harder parts is, I&#39;ve seen lots of work for home and home improvement, but what it&#39;s doing is it&#39;s generating a whole bunch of ideas that can&#39;t be realized, where I can say, “Hey, people have yet to really break out the camera and take a picture of their room.” People do that, but we call it a 1% feature. Like, how do you get people to actually engage the phone or the phone camera?</p><p> But if you can upload an image — I&#39;ve seen some beautiful renderings of, like, “Here&#39;s what my room is. Rearrange the furniture in my room, the furniture I already have,” and things like that become really interesting. Or you say, “I want to replace this couch with this couch from Wayfair. I want to replace this lamp [with] some other lamp,” and here&#39;s 20 different combinations, and you can kind of click through it.</p><p> Those are like you&#39;re taking a virtual experience, almost AR-like [augmented reality-like], but you&#39;re putting real products in there versus them being generated products. But it allows you to build user experiences that are much more enhancing.</p><p> Last year, we built <a href="https://help.pinterest.com/en/article/try-on">AR Try On</a> , which allows you to try on makeup, and what we&#39;re seeing, again, while it doesn&#39;t get a ton of usage, the people that do use it are 60% more likely to buy something. It&#39;s amazingly engaging when people actually get there.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s tough at Pinterest? You mentioned a lot of good use cases, where you&#39;re doing lots of things with these technologies. Certainly, [it] can&#39;t all be wonderful. What&#39;s hard?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> We spend a lot of time on inclusive search and results. In 2021, we launched hair-pattern search. It was kind of this first of technology: When you&#39;re searching for hairstyles, how do you identify hair that looks like yours? This is hugely important in order to refine what you&#39;re looking for.</p><p> We had these same kinds of problems with skin tone, where originally we were trying to use the early models for skin tone detection. And what we found is, it was more on face detection. And so our team had done some great work doing skin detection — it could be a side shot or a back shot or ear shot or a hand shot. You have no idea what kind of skin. So how do I detect what skin is? And then you can detect what kind of tone you&#39;re looking for.</p><p> Same thing had to be applied to hair. And we&#39;ve got all kinds of hair: We have shaved/bald, we have straight, we have wavy, we have curly, we have coily, we have protective, and these kinds of things make the results dramatically better.</p><p> You can save your hair pattern and your skin tone, and then we&#39;ll tailor your results to that. And as you can imagine, this is a complex problem. It&#39;s not just a USA thing; every different country has different types of hair patterns and skin tones and different kinds of fashion, and so these kinds of things are really hard, but they&#39;re the great projects to work on.</p><p> And we&#39;ve had a wonderful team. The advanced technology group here, in particular — we&#39;ve been working on inclusive technology and all these advanced models, and they&#39;re definitely hard, but they&#39;re wonderful when you get them right.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> We have a segment here: five rapid questions. I&#39;ll just ask you a bunch of rapid-fire questions. Just tell me the first thing that comes to your mind. What&#39;s your proudest AI moment?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> The inclusive product feature, and actually, hair pattern was my proudest one, because not only was I involved [with] the product from the beginning, but it&#39;s also first in the industry. And the amount of response that we got from our pinners was incredible. So, yeah, it was a really good one.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What worries you about AI, aside from bias and some of the ethical issues?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> It&#39;s funny. It&#39;s on every single forum. It says, “Hey, are you worried about bias?” Let&#39;s see. What worries me about AI? Hmm. Yeah, I&#39;m not worried. I don&#39;t worry about too many things, but that&#39;s a CTO ...</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s good. That&#39;s a good thing though, right?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> That&#39;s a longtime CTO&#39;s thing. If you worry about too much, you can&#39;t survive in this job.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Mountain biking.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very cool.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I try and go at least two times a week. I go with a crew of Silicon Valley tech [colleagues] on Friday mornings and then usually on the weekends with my brother and a few other people.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think my 5-year-old baby book says fireman, but both my grandfather and my father were engineers, so I actually thought I would build houses, because I loved working with my hands outside. So that&#39;s where I thought I was going to go — architecture or house-building.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What do you wish AI could do that it currently can&#39;t?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Teleportation: Get me through the security line faster! Maybe that&#39;s coming. I&#39;ve always been super excited about translation. I took over the translation team at eBay way back when, and there were some wonderful people that were working on this. And I&#39;ve always thought about a universal translator as something that would just be so amazing. And it&#39;s getting so close, but it still seems like so far away before there&#39;ll be a consumer version of this device.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But why do you think that is? Because we&#39;ve got LLMs now, and we&#39;ve had, for a long time, audio to text. What&#39;s the limiting factor here?</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> I think it&#39;s form factor; like, how do I get out my phone, hit “translate from Spanish to English” — you know, that kind of thing. I don&#39;t know; if I&#39;m walking up to a vendor in the street in San Francisco and I don&#39;t speak the same language, and I want something. … It&#39;s got to be close, but it&#39;s a form factor thing. But I think it&#39;ll come shortly.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Seems solvable.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Yeah, solvable.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Jeremy, we really appreciate you taking the time to talk with us. It&#39;s been very interesting to learn, sort of behind the scenes, what&#39;s happening between all those images that we see but maybe didn&#39;t appreciate all that goes into making something that looks as easy as Pinterest work. And it&#39;s been pretty fascinating to see how much artificial intelligence and machine learning is behind that. Thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Of course. It&#39;s been wonderful.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening today. On our next episode, Sam and I meet with Damini Satija and Matt Mahmoudi from Amnesty International. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Identify Critical Roles to Improve Performance</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boris Groysberg, Eric Lin, Abhijit Naik, and Sascha L. Schmidt. <p>Boris Groysberg is the Richard P. Chapman Professor of Business Administration at Harvard Business School. Eric Lin is an associate professor of business at Oberlin College and Conservatory. Abhijit Naik is senior global quantitative researcher at Quent Capital. Sascha L. Schmidt is a professor and director of the Center for Sports and Management at WHU-Otto Beisheim School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Brian Stauffer/theispot.com Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization’s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn’t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Groysberg_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Brian Stauffer/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization&#39;s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn&#39;t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs that aren&#39;t critical is just a waste of talent.</p><p> It&#39;s accepted wisdom in strategy execution that focused application of concentrated strength — identifying, developing, and leveraging critical capabilities — is required for success. Yet until these capabilities are translated into specific roles, with systems in place to ensure that high-quality employees occupy such positions, a strategy is just an intention. Unfortunately, too many organizations build strategy around the people they have at the time and current skill sets — when they should instead be devising the most promising strategy, developing a better understanding of the roles that will be most critical in executing it, and then staffing those roles with the best available talent. As we&#39;ll demonstrate, applying data and analytics to that problem can help you determine exactly where your top talent needs to be placed.</p><p></p><p> There are two ways to figure out which roles have the most influence on key results: using data to deduce this from the bottom up and inferring it from the top down. Where the context is appropriate and the data available, taking the bottom-up approach can yield answers that may be surprising. In such cases, leaders must be prepared to let the insights guide their decisions.</p><h3> Data Reveals the Difference Makers</h3><p> Data can be used to help tease out both who your current stars are and what positions have the greatest influence on organizational outcomes. It can help identify hidden talent in situations where performance is a team effort and point out roles that may be much more important to success than leadership has realized.</p><p> Take soccer: There is much debate around which positions on the field are the most valuable. Forwards, including strikers, are the primary scorers — they capture the limelight as well as the largest salaries by producing goals. The top 50 highest-paid athletes worldwide include six soccer players — and they are all forwards — according to a 2023 <cite>Forbes</cite> report.</p><p> Since soccer is a low-scoring game, every goal matters — so preventing an opponent&#39;s goal is an equally crucial contribution. Thus, some argue that defenders are the most valuable players. Central defenders play a critical role in coordinating the counteroffensive, as failure to stop the ball at key moments can create big opportunities for the opponent to score. It&#39;s no surprise that central defenders have been team captains more often than other position players.</p><p></p><p> Of course, goalkeepers are the last defenders on the line: Their judgment and skills in the face of extreme pressure can mean the difference between victory and defeat. Still others contend that midfielders drive the tempo of the game. Just as controlling the center of the board is critical to winning chess matches, midfielders can magnify the impact of everyone&#39;s contributions by shutting down opponent passing lanes or by initiating drives through well-timed distributions from the defensive players to the offensive strikers. Finally, the grandmaster might be the coach, who makes decisions on rosters, positions, and general strategy.</p><p> To determine each role&#39;s relative contribution, we collected and analyzed five years&#39; worth of data from the Bundesliga, Germany&#39;s top soccer league, and evaluated the importance of individual positions on the soccer field between 2014 and 2019.</p><p> By analyzing the changes in outcomes as players moved among different roles and teams, we isolated contributions by position while observing how fortunes rose and fell following such switches. Building a model of how each position contributes to the outcome, we weighted the importance of positions by measuring how much the model&#39;s win prediction deteriorated when we omitted each role from the model in turn.</p><p> Our analysis indicated that defenders and goalkeepers are the most critical for winning matches; they occupy the top three slots in two different models we developed. Four positions are always present among the top five: left fullback, right fullback, goalkeeper, and offensive left midfielder. Although defenders may not get as much fan adoration, the numbers indicate that they are the biggest difference makers for winning.</p><p> This kind of analysis works regardless of industry. Every organization or function is similarly likely to have its own underappreciated roles. While the sales team may land the account, it could be the service department that keeps that account renewing each year.</p><p> Talent scarcity matters, too. Comparing the left versus right positions for fullback, midfielder, and center defender, the roles on the left side contribute disproportionately more.为什么？ While left-footed soccer players are naturally advantaged for these roles, the number of world-class left-footed players is considerably smaller than right-footed players. In critical roles where exceptional talent is scarce, having performers in such roles is doubly important.</p><p> Organizational leadership and structure also matter. When included in the models, coaches are the third-most-important factor, behind only the fullback positions. Team organization, systems of play, and staffing govern how critical roles are deployed. In the Bundesliga, the 4-5-1 team formation — four defenders, five midfielders, and one striker — is the most successful configuration. It favors the strategy of prioritizing defense positions and is a good example of congruence between strategy and how organizations configure themselves around critical roles.</p><p></p><h3> Use Data to Fill Critical Roles</h3><p> A similar analytical approach can be applied to businesses by combining performance and HR data. For companies with multiunit structures (such as multiple stores, distribution centers, or service teams), the good news is that you don&#39;t need a soccer league&#39;s worth of data — you can do this yourself. Multiunit organizations with common roles offer the opportunity to capture data across the units and isolate difference-making roles.</p><p> First, gather the data that identifies your workers by location, role, and timing. Second, be sure to gain an understanding of contextual factors that influence outcomes but are unrelated to staffing (for example, stores may perform differently due to location, age, format, or season). This allows you to separate an individual&#39;s impact on outcomes from circumstantial factors. Third, collect performance outcome data for the unit; it&#39;s best to obtain multiple types of metrics, since outcomes are multidimensional.</p><p> In work we did with a national retailer, we gathered such data from hundreds of stores over five years. We measured monthly store performance by revenue, profit, growth, employee turnover, and breakage. We found that store managers matter a great deal: Twenty-one percent of revenue performance could be attributed to store managers — over three times more significant than store attributes — and they had an outsize impact on margins. Regional and district managers also produced measurable effects, but they were less influential than store managers. As expected, the impact of district and regional managers differed depending on the metric. While store managers had the strongest influence on revenues, margin performance was more strongly influenced by district and regional managers, who had significant input into purchasing decisions.</p><p> Just as in soccer, structure and systems matter. Our research found that stores that were closer to headquarters performed better, motivating the further exploration of how stores farther afield could be supported. There is also valuable insight to be gained from employee mobility. When people stay in their roles and locations, it is impossible to use data to disentangle the impact of people from their surrounding circumstances. Moving people through different settings not only gives them a chance to develop and grow, it also enhances the data, allowing more precise measurements of the impact of roles and the people performing them.</p><p></p><p> For the retailer we worked with, these insights changed the talent strategy. Originally, the leaders were moving toward creating a training academy program for district and regional managers, having assumed that higher-status managers with a broader scope of responsibilities would matter more to performance. After considering the results of our analysis, they pivoted to explore what behaviors and practices mattered in the critical role of the store manager. They launched a companywide effort to find out, modeling their approach on Google&#39;s internal research called Project Oxygen, to distill the attributes of managers who positively influenced company performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Once they had identified the details of this critical role, they were able to apply focused investment in developing and replicating capabilities for the job at scale.</p><h3> Talent Insights and Sustainable Competitive Advantage</h3><p> Billy Beane of the Oakland Athletics used data to build a high-performing team at a surprisingly low cost. His strategy as a general manager was to use different performance metrics to find undervalued players who contributed more to winning games than players who performed well on traditional measures. The success of this approach was quickly copied throughout the league, dissipating the A&#39;s strategic advantage. Could an advantage from data-driven talent decisions on crucial roles also be so short-lived?</p><p> There is a key difference to note. The Athletics studied measures that identified great players — but these players could be great on any team. The hallmark of a good strategy is one where the sources of competitive advantage are interlocked with other strategic commitments, making it difficult to copy. Finding key roles and building an organization around those roles may be more defensible than finding hidden stars, since the strategic advantage is tied to how organizations support these roles and develop pipelines to fill them.</p><p> The Bundesliga is known not only for its defense game but also for how it sources talent. It lacks the financial muscle of leagues such as the Premier League, with its billionaire owners. However, the German soccer system&#39;s commitment to developing young talent over relying on high-priced transfers of proven stars makes it an attractive option for young players who need to prove themselves with time on the field — including young players from outside Germany. Because other leagues that have paid dearly for high-priced transfers are obligated to play such talent for more minutes, they have diminished value propositions for younger, emerging talent. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Like Beane&#39;s winning Athletics team, there is an advantage in arbitraging on the undervalued, be it defensive players or younger players. However, unlike this Major League Baseball case, imitating the Bundesliga advantage will require a substantial adjustment to strategy — one that many teams and even leagues are not prepared to make.</p><h3> Execute Based on Differentiating Capabilities</h3><p> Strategy is about defining how to win — it requires committing to capabilities that are unambiguously the best in class. But no company can be the best at everything; a winning strategy requires focus and a keen awareness of what roles are disproportionately critical — and investing appropriately. Failing to acknowledge this puts the entire strategy at risk. By translating abstract capabilities into concrete jobs, organizations are much better positioned to make their strategies a reality.</p><p> Leaders can take a page from the soccer playbook and consider the following lessons for their own organizations:</p><p> <strong>Know your critical roles and where you need to invest.</strong> Despite being a less visible role, defenders matter more than other positions for winning soccer games. Insight into where difference-making roles exist should guide attention and investment when it comes to recruiting, developing, and retaining talent. While it is important to know your key contributors, it is just as important to know where you have deficits in critical roles.</p><p> Additionally, critical roles may change over time. As the competitive landscape evolves, difference-making positions can also change. Winning consistently requires monitoring not only what the critical roles are but how they might be shifting.</p><p></p><p> Investing in critical roles is not just about finding amazing talent — it is also about creating the required systems and practices that focus on positions first, and the people who fill them second. It&#39;s tempting to be blinded by the brightness of stars and give in to eagerly absorbing them regardless of what position they take. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Building a system around such stars makes organizations fragile: They become overdependent on them and distracted from the goal of aligning strategy with talent deployment.</p><p> <strong>Use data where you can, and invest in making it informative.</strong> When you have multiunit structures in your organization, you can exploit that to study roles systematically. Many companies have invested in systems that measure the performance of business units, products, regions, or stores. It takes additional investment to connect this information to personnel data, since most organizations do not explicitly link organizational performance and human resource information. Additionally, it&#39;s common to opt for the ease of keeping people in fixed locations instead of rotating them through different settings. But the practice of introducing some variance in how and where people work can create incredible insights into what roles drive performance. Such insights can highlight the contributions of unsung heroes and highlight where investments in training and recruiting can yield the most substantial gains in performance.</p><p> <strong>Hire for and develop based on key skills.</strong> Today, seniority and pedigree are too influential in talent markets; moreover, they have the effect of entrenching common wisdom about what matters within a role. Just as leaders can be misguided about what roles matter most, they can also be led astray about what skills and behaviors within those roles make the difference. By identifying critical capabilities within critical roles, organizations can both reward what matters and develop the blueprint for hiring, retaining, and developing employees with such skills in mind.</p><p> <strong>Align systems and structure.</strong> Talented employees in critical roles need to be supported with systems and structures that play to their strengths. Similar to the way Bundesliga teams have found that prioritizing the defense roles in field positioning increases the odds of success, organizations need to think creatively about what structure frees those in critical jobs to do their best work. These investments both enable more contributions from your critical roles and make your strategy less vulnerable to replication.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize leadership&#39;s critical role.</strong> On soccer teams, coaches are the third-most-important factor to winning games. Leaders set strategy and then build and motivate the team that supports it. Because alignment across the organization is so critical, any meaningful step to identify, invest in, and develop critical roles needs support from the top. This is especially important when a change in strategy requires building up talent in a critical role that has historically been weak. Leaders need to reinforce their commitment to supporting new key roles with their teams and with potential hires.</p><p></p><p> In soccer, winning can hinge on very small differences. While good teamwork is critical, the highly integrated nature of the sport obscures what the critical roles are. The thoughtful use of data can shed light on the critical roles within your team and uncover surprising results that challenge conventional wisdom. Having insight on critical roles may not only inform your strategy — it may be a source of competitive advantage in itself.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thriving in the New World of Work</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriella Rosen Kellerman. <p>Gabriella Rosen Kellerman is chief innovation officer at BetterUp and coauthor of <cite>Tomorrowmind: Thriving at Work With Resilience, Creativity, and Connection ― Now and in an Uncertain Future</cite> (Atria Books, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Wellness]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book Tomorrowmind, have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled. During Work/23, an MIT Sloan [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book <cite>Tomorrowmind</cite> , have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled.</p><p> During <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023, Kellerman and Seligman explained that they use the acronym <em>PRISM</em> to refer to those five skills. It starts with <em>prospection</em> — the ability to imagine our options, plan for the future, and restore our agency — which Kellerman described as “the meta skill of our era.” The others are <em>resilience</em> , <em>innovation</em> , <em>social connection</em> , and <em>mattering</em> . All of them can be learned, the coauthors said, and leaders can help their employees do so.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Kellerman and Seligman&#39;s work builds on seminal research Seligman conducted with the US Army to understand which soldiers are most at risk of experiencing post-traumatic stress disorder. He found that people with extreme pessimism — catastrophizers who believe that when bad events occur, everything will fall apart — are most vulnerable. His research also found that soldiers who demonstrate high positive emotion, low negative emotion, and high optimism on Day One are better positioned to withstand their environments and even go on to be awarded medals for heroism.</p><p> “I&#39;ve worked on resilience my entire 60 years in psychology,” Seligman said. “The people who were invulnerable, who are resilient, are the optimists.”</p><p> Resilience draws on self-awareness and self-compassion, they explained. “Emotional regulation is, in some ways, the foundational skill of maturing as an adult,” noted Kellerman. “It&#39;s our ability to recognize our emotions, to pause in response to them, to reappraise them, and then to choose a response.” That response, she added, ideally comes from a thoughtful, centered place rather than an emotionally reactive one.</p><p> Kellerman and Seligman weren&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the Work/23 event, so Kellerman answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><p></p><h6> Why is it that, in some cases, self-efficacy and confidence are seen as negative traits, irrespective of knowledge or skills?</h6><p> <em>Self-efficacy</em> is our belief in our own ability to act in the ways we need to in order to achieve our goals. We build self-efficacy by witnessing our own successes as we build mastery in specific domains. Many decades of studies have shown the positive relationship between self-efficacy and well-being and accomplishment.</p><p> In contrast, <em>self-esteem</em> — often defined as confidence in our own abilities — is a less robust construct and can be falsely inflated. It may or may not be related to actual accomplishments. As our colleague Roy Baumeister has demonstrated, <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1111/1529-1006.01431">self-esteem does not predict performance or well-being</a> .</p><p> People with high degrees of self-efficacy may not come across as confident to others, and people who do come across as confident may or may not have high degrees of self-efficacy. Confidence becomes a negative trait when it is false or narcissistic, but neither characteristic applies to self-efficacy.</p><h6> Are there studies correlating pessimism, PTSD, and suicide?</h6><p>是的。 Pessimism is a common feature of depression, and a significant risk factor for suicide. See, for example, “ <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/257552463_An_Examination_of_OptimismPessimism_and_Suicide_Risk_in_Primary_Care_Patients_Does_Belief_in_a_Changeable_Future_Make_a_Difference">An Examination of Optimism/Pessimism and Suicide Risk in Primary Care Patients: Does Belief in a Changeable Future Make a Difference?</a> ”</p><p> <em>Catastrophization</em> , an extreme form of pessimism, is predictive of PTSD risk. Catastrophization has also been shown to have a causal relationship with PTSD severity; see “ <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32479704/">The Sequential Relation Between Changes in Catastrophizing and Changes in Posttraumatic Stress Disorder Symptom Severity</a> .”</p><h6> What skill do you recommend that people choose first for growth?</h6><p> This will vary for every person. For those who are low on resilience, start there. Specifically, focus on the five following skills that drive resilience: emotional regulation, self-efficacy, cognitive agility, self-compassion, and optimism. Which of the five do you feel least comfortable with? Learn about it and look for ways to apply it in your day-to-day life.</p><p></p><p> Our book, <cite><a href="https://www.gabriellarosenkellerman.com/book">Tomorrowmind</a></cite> , includes exercises to build each of these in Chapter 4. For those who are already feeling resilient, pick another of the PRISM powers (prospection, resilience, innovation, social support, and mattering) to start with. [ <em>Editor&#39;s note: Kellerman and Seligman also explore the elements of PRISM in their recent</em> MIT SMR <em>article “<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reimagining-hr-for-better-well-being-and-performance/">Reimagining HR for Better Well-Being and Performance</a></em> .”]</p><h6> How can companies train their employees on these skills?</h6><p> All of these skills can be taught and developed. The best forms of training are personalized and longitudinal and include a mix of learning and practice. Human experts, like mentors or coaches, are an ideal resource, where available.</p><p> You can start with large-group experiences, like presentations or workshops, but don&#39;t stop there. Teach these skills to managers, and teach the managers how to teach those skills to the people who report to them. Look for ways to integrate practices that build these skills into your culture. All of them require practice over time in order to be sustained.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>