<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 11 月 7 日，星期二 17:10:01 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>利用生成式人工智能进行营销：哈佛商学院的 Ayelet Israel</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Market Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[As an assistant professor at Harvard Business School and cofounder of the Customer Intelligence Lab at the school’s Digital Data Design Institute, Ayelet Israeli’s work is focused on how data and technology can inform marketing strategy, as well as how generative AI can be a useful tool in eliminating algorithmic bias. One of the products [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>作为哈佛商学院的助理教授和该校数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的联合创始人，Ayelet Israel 的工作重点是数据和技术如何为营销策略提供信息，以及生成式人工智能如何成为营销策略中的有用工具。消除算法偏差。她最近的工作成果之一是她与两位微软经济学家和研究人员合着的一篇<a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4395751">论文</a>，内容涉及如何使用生成式人工智能来模拟焦点小组和调查以确定客户偏好。</p><p> Ayelet 加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，讨论生成式人工智能在市场研究中的机遇和局限性。她详细介绍了研究的进行方式以及人工智能技术如何帮助营销人员减少与传统客户研究方法相关的时间、成本和复杂性。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E3-Israeli-HBS-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="阿耶莱特·以色列"></p><h4>阿耶莱特·以色列，哈佛商学院</h4><p>阿耶莱特·以色列 (Ayelet Israel) 是哈佛商学院营销部门工商管理学马文·鲍尔 (Marvin Bower) 副教授。她也是该校数字数据设计学院客户智能实验室的联合创始人。她的研究重点是数据驱动的营销，重点是企业如何利用内部数据、客户数据和市场数据来改善结果。她的研究兴趣包括零售、定价策略、渠道管理、营销分析和算法偏差。以色列拥有博士学位。西北大学凯洛格管理学院营销学博士。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>使用生成式人工智能如何帮助我们了解消费者的偏好？在今天的节目中，听听一位教授讲述她的市场研究。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我是哈佛商学院的阿耶莱特·以色列，你们正在听的是<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>大家好。今天，谢尔文和我很高兴阿耶莱特·以色列加入。她是哈佛商学院数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的副教授和联合创始人。 Ayelet，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>非常感谢您邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通常，我们首先会询问客人的职业。但作为一名教授的好处在于人们知道这意味着什么。但我仍然认为很高兴听到一些关于你的背景和简历的信息。那么您能花一点时间介绍一下自己并告诉我们您对什么感兴趣吗？</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>好的。我是哈佛商学院的营销学教授。我真正感兴趣的是我们如何更好地利用数据和人工智能来获得更好的结果，如果这对公司、客户和整个社会都有好处的话。我正在进行的一些工作是围绕人工智能以及企业如何利用它来更好地获取消费者信息和偏好。在我所做的其他工作中，我思考如何消除决策中的算法偏差。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>几个月前我看到了您关于使用生成式人工智能的演讲，这真的让我觉得很有趣，因为很多人都在谈论生成式人工智能，但我们还没有很多证据。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>证据……并不是说它不存在，而是即将到来。但你开始通过你正在进行的这项研究获得一些证据。我们可以在市场研究中使用 GPT 和生成式做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我和我在 Microsoft 的两位同事 Donald Ngwe 和 James Brand 开始思考，我们真的可以使用 GPT 进行市场研究吗？这个想法是，有些人已经证明，你可以通过向 GPT 提出问题来复制非常著名的实验，包括著名的 Milgram 实验。我们在想，“我们作为研究人员和实践者所做的工作就是为了更好地了解客户的偏好；也许我们可以使用 GPT 来实际提取这些类型的偏好。”</p><p>对于大型语言模型，其想法是它们将为您提供最有可能的下一个单词。语言就是这样产生的。我们在想，“也许如果我们要求 GPT 或诱导它在两件事之间做出选择，也许答案（最有可能的下一个词）实际上会反映人群中最可能的反应。从这个意义上说，我们本质上会查询 GPT，但会得到我们在人群中看到的偏好的潜在分布。”我们开始尝试这个想法。我们专注于消费产品——因为我们假设 GPT 所了解的数据主要围绕消费产品，可能来自评论网站或类似的东西——看看这个想法是否真的可行？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>有点！</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>那太棒了。请告诉我们更多信息。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我们的第一反应是，“好吧，让我们看看它是否能产生我们对经济学的期望的非常基本的东西。例如，当价格较高时，它是否知道拒绝报价？它知道在价格和选择之间进行权衡吗？”我们确实看到了一条向下倾斜的需求曲线，这正是我们在查询 GPT 数千次以获得答案时所期望看到的。我们还看到这样的事情，“哦，我们可以告诉它一些关于它的收入的信息，它会对此做出反应。”当它的收入较高时，它对价格的敏感度就会降低，这是有道理的——这也是我们对人们的期望。</p><p>我们还看到，它可以对有关自身的信息做出反应：“哦，上次您在这个类别中购买时，您购买了这个特定品牌”，这使得它将来更有可能选择这个品牌。所以这些是我们对“它是否真的以人类在调查中的方式做出反应？”的测试。然后我们更进一步，我们试图让人们愿意为产品或某些属性付费。然后我们基本上将价格分布与我们在市场上看到的价格分布进行比较，这非常一致。</p><p>对我们来说，真正有趣和令人兴奋的事情是能够了解为属性付费的意愿，因为这是我们作为营销人员都希望找到的东西。在我们的例子中，它是牙膏，我们试图弄清楚有多少人愿意为氟化物支付多少钱，这是我们很难考虑的事情。如果有人问你——“我不知道。”我确实知道我更喜欢买这款牙膏，但我不知道编号是多少。所以这让我们更好奇，GPT 是否可以像我们询问消费者的方式一样为我们提供这个数字。研究人员多年来已经表明，提出这些问题的最佳方法是通过联合研究。本质上，您为人们提供 10 到 15 个选择，通过他们的不同选择，您能够了解他们正在做出的权衡，并实际量化他们愿意支付的差异。</p><p>我们基本上就是这样做的。我们使用 GPT 进行了联合类型分析，并将结果与​​即将发表的论文刚刚运行的人体研究进行了比较，并得到了非常相似的结果，所以我们对此感到非常兴奋。当然，结果并不相同。我们需要做更多的工作来弄清楚一些问题出在哪里，以及这在多大程度上具有普遍性，但我们能够解决这个问题的事实就令人难以置信地令人兴奋。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这对公司来说似乎很令人兴奋，因为我猜测对很多人进行市场研究的成本比仅仅通过 ChatGPT 进行一堆 API 调用要高得多。这一定是吸引力。还有其他上诉吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>基本上，这些类型的研究非常耗时、昂贵且复杂。理想情况下，您希望要求人们做出很多权衡，但您受到人类这样做的能力的限制。使用GPT，您可以多次查询。但在这一点上，我不会告诉任何人，“用 GPT 或另一个法学硕士取代你所有的人体研究”，因为要弄清楚如何正确地做到这一点，还有很多工作要做。</p><p> GPT 的特点之一是它是经过预训练的。它会给我偏好，但这些偏好与其预训练的时间段相关。一家公司想知道“客户现在对什么感兴趣？”所以这是一种限制。</p><p>我们现在正在测试的是，也许我们仍然需要询问人员，但询问的人数比平时要少。因此，通常当您进行这些研究时，您需要数千名用户才能获得从学术或统计角度来看稳健且具有统计显着性的结果。我们正在尝试看看，也许我可以从更少的人那里收集信息，并通过微调将其与 LLM 结合起来，并生成一些有用的东西。但实际上，一个很大的优势是节省成本和时间。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个重要的时刻。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。到目前为止，我们讨论的是消费品，但您可以考虑企业对企业类型的调查，这种调查成本更高，也更难进行。所以也许那里也有潜力。我们还没有测试过。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我喜欢这个主意。我的意思是，当你考虑生成式人工智能的大多数用例时，你会发现很多关于消除工作中的苦差事或创建图像和内容以及总结文本的事情。然后还有围绕计划和库存管理的更高级的内容。但你所说的实际上是用这个取代人类，对吗？我的意思是，基本上就是这样。</p><p>这是一个可能非常有趣的事情的开始，因为你至少证明了它是合理的，对吗？我的意思是，你问了所有这些问题，我想这在经济上是合理的。但是，作为一名营销人员，你就是你自己，并非所有营销策略都基于理性。事实上，其中许多都是基于完全非理性的欲望。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您对许多人做出的非理性选择有何看法，这些选择创造了这些大品牌和 20,000 美元的手袋以及诸如此类的东西？你如何利用这一点？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>在回答你的问题之前，作为一名学者，我首先感到紧张的是当你使用“<em>已证明”</em>这个词时。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>证明——我听到了！</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我看到山姆是……</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我说这话的时候笑了。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我想说我们展示了与此相符的证据。我们也知道这些模型仍在不断发展，也许我们一个月前展示的东西在一个月后就不再相关，这也是为什么你不应该在没有测试的情况下就去实现它的原因。所以我想对此小心。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>所以你知道，对于什么是产品，人们有更理性的看法，但品牌所创造的价值对我们来说是无法衡量和难以量化的。但这几乎就像我用氟化物给出的例子一样。就像，我们不知道如何量化氟化物。如果我问你，“哦，你愿意花多少钱购买像高露洁这样的品牌，而不是我刚配制的牙膏？”我们可能会觉得很困难。</p><p>实际上，相同的联合研究模型将能够推断出这些差异。例如，我们可以看到 Mac 相对于其他计算机类型的偏好。所以它已经以某种方式嵌入其中。</p><p>现在它有多准确——这是一个经验问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，不，你说得很对，因为当我听到你回答这个问题时，我也意识到我的假设，即你所展示的一些证据，相对于已被证明的，不一定是合理的。而是它有能力概括大多数人所做的事情——或者很多人所做的事情——并将其嵌入到它所训练的内容中。那么我的第二个问题是，如何让它更细分、更具体或更细致？因为当您进行焦点小组讨论时，您可能正在寻找特定的风味/特定的细微差别组合。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，而且，当 GPT 和其他法学硕士刚刚推出时，我们看到了很多用途，很多令人兴奋的是，“我是一名工程师。我只能问它一个问题。它给了我最常见的东西。这正是我想要的。”事实上，我们正在做的是另一面。我们不想要最常见的东西。我们想了解分布。</p><p>这就是为什么当我们查询 GPT 时，我们会多次询问每个问题 - 因为我们希望获得很多很多不同的消费者。在我们的分析中，我们仅改变了收入和您之前购买的商品。但我们可以以同样的方式改变性别、种族、任何你想要的东西……年龄。我已经看到其他研究人员这样做了。 ……</p><p>哥伦比亚大学和伯克利分校的同事发表了一篇非常有趣的论文，其中使用 GPT 来创建感知图——两个品牌彼此之间的接近程度。他们还表现出性别、年龄以及汽车等方面的差异，我们预计在汽车市场上会看到这些差异。所以你也绝对可以以类似的方式做到这一点。这也体现在政治学的政治学中。我可以给某人一种意识形态，他们的投票行为是有意义的，他们在不同主题上生成的文本是有意义的。作为一个关心异质性并了解不同消费者之间差异的营销人员，这也是非常令人兴奋的。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。如果我们能将其用于临床试验就好了。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我看到了一些关于法学硕士相对于医生更好的临床态度的论文，所以也许仍然有一些东西。 [笑。]</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>也许这就是 GPT-5。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>不过，正如你所说，我认为这些工作方式是对最有可能的下一个单词、最有可能的下一个单词进行概率估计……并且你已经细分出了“鉴于你的收入较低” ，高收入，鉴于你是这个属性，那个属性……”这很有趣，但是我们从哪里想到奇怪的地方呢？如果一切都基于“最有可能”，特别是预定义的[参数]——并不是说你不擅长想出一个好的搜索空间，而是我们如何找到我们不知道的东西，那么？这不是市场研究和焦点小组得出的结果吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>当然，这是挑战的一部分。显然，GPT 学习某种分布，但有些人，你知道……可以说它学习的所有内容都是来自评论。可能有很多非常极端的消费者，他们不会在网上写评论或无法访问互联网，但有这些有趣的极端想法。即使我告诉 GPT，“我想要尽可能多的随机性，非常高的变化”，我也不会去找那些人。所以这肯定会是一个问题。</p><p>我已经知道一些初创公司正在尝试解决这个问题并识别这些极端消费者，然后通过使用法学硕士来预测他们在另一种情况下会做什么，从而将他们提升到一个新的水平。但与此同时，已经有一些关于 GPT 创造力的工作，它创造了非常有创意的想法，你知道，这并不完全是你所要求的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>其中一些创意不受现实的限制。我想我们都见过其中的一些，[比如]它下棋的方式，并认为该规则有点过于限制。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。所以这也是幻觉的问题，应该在不同的环境下进行测试。但我认为我们诱导它做出选择的方式不太容易出现幻觉问题，因为它提供了一种选择，并且你不需要询问事实或类似的东西。我并不是想说 GPT 的表现会优于任何客户调查或类似的调查。我只想看看它是否和人类一样优秀。</p><p>即使是与我们交谈的人类客户，我们也必须非常努力地找到人来进行这些调查，有时我们会错过他们。我们也许能够得到一些人的分布，但仍然必须在没有人工智能而只有人类对话的极端情况下努力工作。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我发现真正有趣的是，你说过“这不如消费者调查”，现在我想挑战这一点。因为我发现你的这个想法有趣的是，当你考虑其他人工智能或一代人工智能用例时，你会说，“好吧，所以我是一个人。我是个工程师。我有一个任务。让我们问问 GPT”或任何生成式人工智能系统，它是否属于知识类工作，是否能像人类一样做得好。太好了。或者它能比人类编码得更好吗？或者它可以创建一个视频、文档或其他东西，让您阅读后会说：“哇，这太棒了。那么<em>你</em>就可以做到。我不需要这么做。”正确的？所以这种举证责任是非常明确的。</p><p>在这一点上，我不太确定你<em>是否需要</em>承担举证责任，因为在很多方面，我们假设一个由 500 人或 1000 人组成的焦点小组，或任何调查 - 我的意思是，没有焦点据我所知，有这么大的一个群体——但这种调查在某种程度上是福音，或者，就像 GPT 或其他人，无论什么——</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>您能和我们论文的审稿人谈谈吗？ [笑。]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>因为事实是，如果你仔细想想，那就是如果唯一知道的方法......那就回去吧。因为，你看：你的前提是，“我们将通过增强这个来在所有市场研究上节省很多钱”，这是一个真实的前提，而且肯定是这样。但我也发现负担减轻了。即使您不停止任何一项基于人类的市场研究或调查，您仍然可以通过扩大反应和选择范围来增加大量价值。</p><p>因为我会争论，你怎么知道 1,000 人或 2,000 人具有<em>代表性</em>，或者他们有所有这些细微差别？所以这件事实际上带来了事实存在的信号，否则你就不会在那里。我发现这实际上对营销人员很有启发。我很高兴与您的审稿人交谈。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为作为学者，我们习惯于一定程度的严谨性和稳健性，以及能够说，哦，实际证明事物的能力，而且这个工具可以提供某些东西的模拟这一事实很好，但是“它真的能取代人类吗？”是一个更高的负担，因为这个问题，它实际上给了我有意义的、更新的答案吗？它会匹配某些东西吗？你会说，“好吧，也许人类一开始就没有那么伟大，那么我们为什么要尝试……？”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>不，我实际上是在表达不同的观点。我接受过科学家培训，在科学界和学术界，我承担的举证责任要高得多。我并不是想争辩说你已经证明它可以取代人类。我不认为它会取代人类。但我想说的是，这样做的价值在于，它极大地增强了营销人员可用的信号、见解和想法，因为根据定义，没有任何调查或焦点小组是不受限制的，这不是有限，因为它拥有那里的一切。所以我的观点并不是证明举证责任已经得到满足，而是我什至不知道是否应该有这种举证责任，因为它正在解决焦点小组和传统研究的局限性。所以不一定需要更换。它们一开始就并不完美。没有人会反对这一点。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。我认为，至少，我可以放心地说，我们表明它可以提供有关偏好和正在发生的事情的非常丰富的信息，至少在它所训练的数据范围内。考虑到研究的类型以及市场研究和接触人员等方面的问题，这可能已经对很多公司产生了很大的改变。一定。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这里有多种不同的信号，我认为我们首先从以下想法解决了这个问题：这个信号是否取代了焦点小组的其他信号？但这里的因变量可能是，人们真的购买产品吗？人们买氟化物吗？他们购买[假货]产品吗？</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果这个信号为该预测添加了一些信息，那么我们就有了一个新的信息源。如果它完全取代了它，那么我们就有了不同的东西。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。现在我们要解决的问题是，对陈述的偏好与实际上基于人们行为的显露偏好进行调查。现在，我认为 GPT 的问题可能比人类少，因为它不受实验者偏见或试图安抚我等因素的影响。因此，它可能会给我一些更接近的东西，但如果它带来来自评论网站或市场研究的数据，但它仍然给我一些可能更接近所陈述的偏好的东西，而不一定[给我]人们实际会购买什么。但焦点小组和调查也是如此。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以我们认为这是一种新的信号源——那里有很多不同的信号，并且它可能与一个信号有一些重叠。而且我认为这本身就很有趣，但它也可能有一个新的信号。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我发现的另一件令人着迷的事情是，人工智能解决方案已经过数据训练，然后，当它们投入生产时，它们会接受数据训练，或者从生产中的数据中获得反馈，然后它们得到更好的。对于生成式人工智能，很多反馈也需要由人类驱动而不是数据驱动，对吗？就像，这就是它告诉你要做的事情。它引起你的共鸣吗？是的，不是，等等。所以感觉就像是一种技术，生成式人工智能可以成为另一个生成式人工智能输出的用户。</p><p>因此，让我们看一下这样的范式，看，它正在取代焦点小组中的人员，或者我们也可以替换公司中的人员，该公司是一个营销人员，负责处理生成式人工智能的响应，例如“你如何设计一个营销活动”为了这？”</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以这个想法可能是多个生成式人工智能代理相互竞争以提高整体质量——你对此有何看法？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为这是一个有趣的想法。但我也认为，到目前为止的证据表明，在某些时候，你仍然需要至少一个人参与其中……</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>当然。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong> ……因为所有这些幻觉，不切实际的事情出现了。但当然，如果这些模型变得越来越好、效率越来越高、质量越来越高，那为什么不呢？当我们在组织中实施这些类型的事情时，我们还需要考虑如何——我不知道这个词是否完全是<em>“验证”</em> ，但我们如何确保该过程仍然有意义并且我们不这样做这些特工互相交谈只是浪费大家的时间吗？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>不，当然。你是100%正确的。你需要人类参与其中，而且可能至少需要几十年。但您可能不需要那么多。你知道，如果你有某种输出应该对 20,000 名客户服务代表有所帮助，并且根据反馈、根据他们在试点中的使用情况，它会变得更好，让我们比如说，三个月，也许你不需要向 5,000 人进行试点。也许你可以将其试点给一百个人加上两到三个不同的人工智能代理，这样你就可以大大加快采用时间。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，那很酷。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>虽然我不得不说，当我听到你这么说时，Shervin，它让我想到的是当人们将麦克风距离扬声器太近时，我们会得到这些反馈循环 - 放大反馈循环。我确实担心，如果这两个数据源过于一致，我们就会被压制。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>确实如此。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们不会变得疯狂。跳到本章后面：给我们答案。人们正在听这个，他们在公司工作，他们现在就可以使用这些工具，而不是 20 年后，就像我们作为学者所想的那样。人们现在应该使用这些工具做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>和他们一起玩。弄清楚……您想了解客户的哪些信息？我们在论文中提供了完整的提示列表，详细说明了如何提示这些类型的事情并开始获取这些信息。正如谢尔文之前所说，它到底是什么？我们不确定，但这是一个信号。那里有我们可以开始查找的信息，对吧？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通过使用它，可以帮助人们发现其中包含哪些信息？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为是测试和发现。但从一个具体的问题开始确实很有帮助，因为你会陷入很多兔子洞。您可以永远进行这些对话。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Ayelet Israel，您是我们接待的唯一一位带有“AI”缩写的客人，这非常适合“<em>我”、“我自己”和“Ayelet Israel”</em> ，即<em>“我、我自己和我自己”</em> 。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong> [笑]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>请告诉我们更多有关您自己和您的背景的信息，以及您如何最终达到现在的位置以及是什么让您对所有这些东西感兴趣。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>当然。正如我的姓氏所示，我最初来自以色列。以色列被誉为“<a href="https://www.cfr.org/book/start-nation">创业国家</a>”。当我开始思考我想在大学学习什么时，有一个特殊的项目旨在通过为人们提供某种管理工具来改善创业国家。因此，这是一个为期五年的计算机科学学士学位和 MBA 联合课程。</p><p>我开始这样做，我喜欢计算机科学。我实际上主修金融和营销，但我对营销特别感兴趣，特别是在这种背景下理解大量数据，这些数据非常有趣且实用。然后我决定获得博士学位。在营销方面。</p><p>多年来，我认为消费品或围绕客户和交易的事物对我来说很有趣。这只是一个迷人的世界。你有很多关于这方面的数据，因为随着我们更多地转向在线和数字化，我们可以看到越来越多的数据。接下来的问题是，“我们如何才能更有效、更负责任地利用这些数据？”我的研究的一部分也是关于这一点的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以我们有一个环节，我们会问您一系列快速问题，让您了解情况。只需回答您想到的第一件事即可。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>好的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>目前人工智能最大的机会是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>最大的机会。这并不快。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>下一个问题。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，下一个问题。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>哦，好的。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我会考虑一下。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>通过。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>通过。您认为目前人们对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我周围的人往往从事这方面的工作，并且了解这一点，这只是一个模型，但很多人仍然不明白，仍然想象着机器人和发生的这种神奇的事情。这就是为什么我喜欢非常清楚地解释，“哦，它是预测下一个单词的可能性并在分布上选择它们，这就是所发生的一切。”所以我认为我们的情况可能仍然不像十年前那么糟糕，但仍然是这种神奇的、人为的事情发生，但事实并非如此。我想它仍然很神奇。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这真是太神奇了——或者说可以。您想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我不知道。在以色列，你参军。我在军队；我是一名情报中尉。我不认为这是我必然想要的职业。这是我做的事。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>关于人工智能有很多讨论和兴奋。人们在哪里过度使用它？人们在哪里使用它而不适用它？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为我看到的挑战之一实际上是用它来问事实问题，因为这不是它的目的。这不是一种真相发现机制，这只是一种错误的用法。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>好的。有没有什么事情是你希望人工智能现在就能做到但它却做不到的？接下来令人兴奋的事情是什么？明天的什么公告会让你高兴？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我对这个问题的回答略有不同。我认为，就负责任地使用数据和算法偏差的研究而言，人工智能让我兴奋的是，是的，很多人已经表明人工智能可以产生有偏见的结果。多年来我们也知道人类会产生有偏见的结果。 And what excites me about AI is that it&#39;s much easier to fix biased outcomes by a machine and to generate processes that will eliminate bias, and it&#39;s so much more difficult with humans. And that&#39;s something that I&#39;m really excited about.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I love that point because we&#39;ve got all this bias and misogyny in our world, not by the machines. The machines are not the people who put us in this situation in the first place. And the fact that they maybe do a little bit of that at the beginning, before we&#39;ve trained them, we shouldn&#39;t just throw them out for starting down that path, because we can adjust the weights in models. We can give feedback to models to improve those in a way that we can&#39;t with bazillions of people.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Right.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So I think that&#39;s a huge point.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> And we&#39;ve seen the first models of gen AI images. If you say “doctor,” we&#39;re only [seeing] photos of men or things like that. And over time, this has improved a lot. So that&#39;s really exciting, right? We can try to think about how we fix some societal problems using these things because, yes, machines can be manipulated more easily than humans. Of course, that&#39;s a risk, but that&#39;s for some sci-fi podcast, not for this one.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> The example of the doctor in the image is spot-on because I think so many people were fascinated by how accurate these models are because they felt right. They confirmed our stereotypes. You ask for this image, and it gives you exactly what you think of as that image, but that&#39;s just feeding into the problem again. And that&#39;s going to perpetuate it if we don&#39;t [stop it]. But, like you say, there has been improvement there.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ayelet, thank you so much. This has been really insightful and quite interesting. Thank you for being on the show.</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israeli:</strong> Thank you so much for having me. This was fun.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for joining us today. On our next episode, Shervin and I speak with Miqdad Jaffer, chief product officer at Shopify. Before you do your holiday shopping, please join us to learn how little bits of AI everywhere can add up to big value for all of us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>更智能的 KPI 治理</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron, Michael Schrage, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>David Kiron</strong>是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>研究部编辑主任，也是其<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">“大创意”研究计划的</a>项目负责人。</p><p class="mt20"><strong>迈克尔·施拉格 (Michael Schrage)</strong>是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院数字经济倡议的研究员。他的研究、写作和咨询工作重点关注数字媒体、模型和指标的行为经济学，作为管理创新机会和风险的战略资源。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong>是波士顿咨询集团 (BCG) 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 亨德森研究所的全球总监，他的研究重点是技术对商业和社会的影响。您可以通过<a href= "mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong>是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 北美人工智能业务的联席领导者。他是 BCG X 的领导者，在推动人工智能和数字化业务影响方面拥有 20 多年的经验。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong>是 BCG 合伙人兼副总监，专注于将人工智能和机器学习应用于商业职能中的业务问题，包括优化定价、促销、销售和营销。您可以通过<a href= "mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In spring 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>关于研究</h4><p>本系列文章介绍了<em>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</em>和波士顿咨询集团第七次年度人工智能和商业战略全球研究的结果。 2023 年春季，我们开展了一项全球调查，随后分析了来自 25 个行业和 100 个国家/地区的 3,043 名受访者的记录。我们还采访了 17 名在金融服务、媒体和娱乐、零售、旅游和运输以及生命科学等众多公司和行业领导人工智能计划的高管。</p><p>我们的研究探讨了管理者和领导者如何使用人工智能来增强战略衡量，以推进战略成果。它探讨了组织如何利用人工智能调整甚至生成新的 KPI 来定义和提供可衡量的更好绩效。</p></aside><p>如果不进行调整和细化，静态业务指标会产生两种类型的战略风险。一是鼓励在错误的措施上表现。例如，2008 年全球经济危机的部分原因是银行对当时广泛使用的指标的依赖：风险价值，该指标衡量正常市场条件下单个时间点的潜在投资组合损失。金融机构没有调整这一措施，因为风险较高的次级抵押贷款和证券化违约掉期已成为其投资组合的较大部分。在严重低估潜在损失的指标（在某些情况下，低估了几个数量级）的指导下，许多金融机构破产或遭受重大损失。</p><p></p><p>机会成本是静态关键绩效指标带来的另一个风险。我们的研究令人信服地表明，有意使用人工智能来设计和创建更具动态的 KPI 的公司可以享有更强的态势感知能力、运营与战略成果之间更紧密的联系以及整体业绩的改善。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>与未经人工智能通知的类似 KPI 相比，这些<em>智能</em>KPI 反映了对绩效驱动因素的更深入理解，并对未来结果产生更可靠的预测。 （请参阅“三种类型的智能 KPI”。）在波动和快速变化的市场中，“设定后忘记它们”的关键指标方法既不可取，也不可持续。</p><div class="callout-highlight callout-simple"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>三种类型的智能 KPI</h4><p class="caption"><table id="chart1" class="chart-grouped-rows"><thead><tr><th>关键绩效指标类型</th><th>Description</th><th>好处</th><th>例子</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能描述性 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>综合历史和当前数据以提供有关<em>已发生</em>或<em>正在发生的事情</em>的见解。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>更深入地了解绩效差距及其原因。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>赛诺菲的“零食人工智能”工具通过揭示不同 KPI 之间的关键相互依赖性来增强态势感知。</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能预测 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>预测未来表现，产生可靠的领先指标。提供潜在结果的可见性。识别其他技术或人类无法识别的模式，使他们能够利用更丰富的潜在违反直觉的模式。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>采取先发制人的行动，以减轻风险或利用机会。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>通用电气已将其 KPI 转变为关注领先指标，并使用人工智能通过将订单与产品和服务的安装基础进行比较来分析订单渠道，帮助准确识别增加未来订单并推动更强劲的收入和利润的机会。</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能规定 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>使用 AI 推荐可优化性能的操作。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>指出绩效差距并建议纠正措施。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>赛诺菲的智能 KPI 根据供应链绩效建议对销售 KPI 进行调整，从而使运营和销售保持一致。 </ul></p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_Table.png" alt="三种类型的智能 KPI" class="no-desktop" /></p><p class="attribution">资料来源：D. Kiron、M. Schrage、F. Candelon 等人，“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/strategic-alignment-with-ai-and-smart-kpis/">人工智能和智能 KPI 的战略调整</a>”， <span style="font-style:normal">《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</span>》，2023 年 9 月 5 日。</p></article></aside></div><p>需要有效的治理来确保 KPI 不断发展、与战略愿景保持一致，并受到员工和管理者的信任。随着人工智能注入的工作流程和流程殖民并扩展业务能力，领导者需要更新和升级其关键绩效指标以跟上。从施耐德电气到沃尔玛再到马士基，我们看到战略家、技术专家和商业领袖共同努力完善和增强 KPI，以确保其与不断变化的组织目标保持一致。</p><p>在这些公司中，使 KPI 更具预测性、动态性和洞察力的责任超出了战略家和业务领导者的范围。他们鼓励技术人员为 KPI 的制定、组织和优先级排序做出实质性贡献。与公司传统上建立和更新 KPI 的方式相比，这是一个巨大的变化。</p><p>正如施耐德电气首席治理官兼秘书长 Hervé Coureil 所观察到的那样，“当流程数字化时，它们开始产生‘废气数据’，这些数据可以转化为相关的遥测指标，提供有关流程行为、缺陷等的见解。其次，数字化转型引发重大决策和投资——投资组合和投资选择、业务模式实施、新系统和基础设施——因此，有必要衡量这些决策的影响以及构成转型的各种计划的有效性。”</p><p></p><p>制定此类措施不仅仅取决于执行判断、直觉和经验。将静态的传统绩效指标转变为更智能、更动态的 KPI，需要数据、分析和人工智能发挥更大的作用。我们建议领导者采用三管齐下的方法来管理人工智能驱动的 KPI 以及更广泛的战略衡量系统的开发和使用。这种治理方法取决于三个因素：</p><ol><li>坚实的数据基础以及负责任的数据和分析实践。</li><li>对不断变化的 KPI 负有责任和问责的组织结构。</li><li>相信 KPI 能够适应环境变化并从中学习。</li></ol><h3>智能 KPI 开发治理：让您的数据井井有条</h3><p>有效的 KPI 治理需要有效的数据治理。参与我们研究的每个组织都强调数据质量和纪律作为其人工智能驱动的 KPI 计划的技术推动者。然而，大多数遗留 IT 和数据库系统并未配置为生成或提供测量或定义智能 KPI 所需的质量数据。</p><p>保乐力加 (Pernod Ricard) 首席数字官 Pierre-Yves Calloc&#39;h 回忆道，这家烈酒巨头意识到需要三年的每周消费者销售数据才能实现有意义的人工智能干预。初步审查发现存在巨大差距。 “刚开始时，我们几乎没有数据治理，”Calloc&#39;h 说。 “我们需要的数据中几乎 80% 不存在，因为主要是外部数据。我们的统计经验是，您需要每周的数据；如果您有每月数据，则不起作用，因此您需要手动获取信息。我们甚至将其称为“考古学”，因为需要付出很大的努力，甚至要深入邮箱中的旧 PowerPoint 和 Excel 文件。此外，您需要为该项目提供强有力的商业案例，因为如果没有明确的利益，人们就不会投入时间。”从本质上讲，如果没有技术上可靠和强大的治理将数据<em>考古学</em>转变为数据<em>架构</em>，就无法制定人工智能驱动的 KPI 的业务案例。</p><p>通用汽车首席数据和分析官乔恩·弗朗西斯（Jon Francis）曾负责星巴克的数字化转型，他也赞同卡洛克的观点。 “由于潜在的数据挑战，创建 KPI 实际上非常困难，”他说。 “通常，创建 KPI 并报告它需要您付出所有的努力。”糟糕的数据和元数据治理会削弱组织开发正确指标的能力。弗朗西斯指出，技术系统通常只是“假脱机未定义或未使用的数据”，因此，“最终会出现这些数据倾倒场”。他坦率地观察到，对于大多数组织来说，从生产系统生成数据是事后才想到的。</p><p>有效的 KPI 治理仍然取决于公司利用数据的技术能力：它需要勤奋的数据治理、结构化的分析管理方法，以及技术人员和业务部门领导者持续协作开发最佳 KPI 的路径。</p><p></p><h3>将治理嵌入团队或职能中</h3><p>我们的研究发现，高层管理人员正在重新思考如何制定并持续改进其关键绩效指标和指标。虽然方法各不相同，但受访高管的一个共同主题是选择将 KPI 转型的责任归于特定团队或团队组。</p><p>在施耐德电气，领导层逐渐认识到，公司的传统指标可能与其与全球客户进行战略合作和创新的愿望不相容。 Coureil 帮助发起在公司数据团队内创建绩效管理办公室，以监督绩效衡量。该办公室被有意安排在治理团队中，以确保中立的跨职能视角。</p><p>绩效管理办公室帮助高层管理人员转变其 KPI 组合并使其与运营保持一致。它还推动企业变得更加数据驱动，并意识到针对给定绩效指标的改进与增强成果之间的联系。 “测量对我们来说非常核心，”Coureil 补充道。 “我们实际上试图让指标成为我们数字化转型中完整、不可或缺的一部分，而不是事后才想到的。”</p><p>给定 KPI 的预期结果是什么？ “在某种程度上，这是一个本体论或分类学问题：你在寻找什么行为？”库雷问道。 “我认为人们在 KPI 篮子里放了很多东西，我们花了很多时间试图非常清楚我们所关注的是什么：期望的结果是什么？它看起来很简单，但实际上并没有那么简单……对给定 KPI 的预期结果非常敏锐。” Coureil 表示，这就是为什么事实证明，设立绩效管理办公室对于战略上连贯一致的 KPI 治理至关重要。</p><p>星展银行没有使用绩效管理办公室，而是通过跨职能团队来管理 KPI 开发，这些团队创建将客户旅程与期望结果联系起来的价值图。这家总部位于新加坡的金融服务领导者重新审视了其运营模式，以反映这样一个事实：使用更智能的 KPI 可以显着改善企业及其客户的成果。 “在过去的三年里，我们转向了数据驱动的运营模式，”集团首席分析官兼董事总经理 Sameer Gupta 说道。</p><p>该模型的核心是跨职能小队。古普塔解释说，来自产品、风险、数据、营销、呼叫中心和人力资源等不同职能部门的代表组成了一个小队。然后，每个团队成员都会根据映射到四个类别的同一组结果进行协调：客户体验、员工体验、盈利能力和风险。</p><p>每个结果的绩效驱动因素都以价值图表示，该价值图将绩效指标与四种类型的结果联系起来。每个小组负责识别和优化这些因素。 “车队正在考虑优化这些车手，”古普塔说。 “我们会考虑很多因素来优化这些驱动因素：实验、数据、客户沉浸、人工智能、机器学习——尝试与控制塔和管理仪表板协调和协商的各种工具，不断优化。”</p><p> Gupta 指出，其结果不仅是提高了数据驱动的运营效率和效益，而且还扩大了星展银行客户和客户体验界限的关键绩效指标 (KPI)。重新审视 KPI 治理流程带来了更好的 KPI 和更好的 KPI 结果。</p><p>虽然具体方法各不相同，但我们采访过的大多数领导者都处于构建治理结构的早期阶段，以帮助他们的 KPI 更加智能、详细和可预测。</p><h3>有效的 KPI 治理基于信任</h3><p>虽然 KPI 治理中的这些技术和组织投资对于提高 KPI 至关重要，但我们的研究表明，它们对团队的实际价值取决于人们信任它们的意愿。在施耐德电气的数字化转型过程中，Coureil 认识到“与更传统的开展业务方式相比，其中一个变化是您不再构建仪表板。别人帮你做。所以你必须相信这些指标。”</p><p>轶事证据表明，建立对人工智能来源指标的信任可能具有挑战性。</p><p>例如，在马士基，长期以来的假设是，让一艘船尽快离开港口并开往下一艘是理想的。然而，数字孪生模拟表明，准时比早到要好：由于端到端连接的时间表（商业航空公司的情况也是如此），船舶下一个前往的港口无法调整其时间表立即适应较早到达的人。换句话说，“越快并不越好”是数据团队违反直觉的说法，只有在准时方法付诸实践后，一线操作人员——甚至是最高层管理人员整个航站楼——终于被说服了。</p><p>培养开发和使用动态的、人工智能增强的 KPI 所需的信任是一项关键的领导力和治理挑战。培养精通数据、愿意制定和采用人工智能驱动的 KPI 的管理者是这一挑战的重要组成部分。在一家媒体组织，一位接受采访的高管指出，她很难说服上级查看 KPI 并根据数据做出决策。他们通常的反驳是，高管们“因为他们的直觉而获得了数百万美元的报酬”——换句话说，经验和直觉比数据驱动的洞察力更有价值。</p><p></p><p>建立面向数据的管理社区是使用增强的 KPI 在领导者之间建立信任的一种方法。在赛诺菲，代表不同职能和业务的 150 名最高级领导者正在训练营接受培训，以变得更加以数据为中心，并在做出决策之前寻求更多信息。正如首席数字官 Emmanuel Frenehard 所说：“作为我们文化变革的一部分，我们的目标是，这 150 人在离开训练营时，更倾向于采用以数据为中心的观点，并更好地了解人工智能对我们的潜力。我们确保我们的领导核心接受过如何使用下一代人工智能驱动的 KPI 的培训。”</p><h3>进一步的考虑</h3><p>为了确保人工智能支持的智能 KPI 能够帮助他们取得战略成功，领导者必须优先考虑上述 KPI 治理的技术、组织和文化层面。当他们开始这样做时，这些相关的考虑因素应该是首要考虑的。</p><p><strong>建立指导委员会来指导持续改进。</strong>将传统 KPI 转变为增强型 KPI 需要定期进行试验，以确保关键绩效集中在正确的结果上。确定实验在哪里进行、由谁进行以及频率是关键的领导和治理决策点。是在一个中央团队中，比如绩效办公室，还是分布更广泛？某些 KPI 是否应该比其他 KPI 更频繁地重新审视和审查？当改变 KPI 改变责任时，谁拥有决策权？这些问题没有一刀切的答案。领导者需要灵活的流程来有效管理可能孤立或跨职能的 KPI。我们建议建立一个具有业务和技术专业知识的跨职能 KPI 指导委员会，以征求相关利益相关者的必要意见和支持。</p><p><strong>监督对优化 KPI 组的能力的投资。</strong>贵公司是否有能力评估其 KPI 是否足够好或完全优化？我们的研究表明，人工智能可以在评估 KPI 质量、确定 KPI 优先级以及解决它们之间的权衡方面发挥重要作用。例如，人工智能可以帮助确定在什么情况下以客户为中心的要求应优先于提高运营效率，或者何时应优先考虑收入而不是市场份额投资。对于习惯于自己做出这些决策的管理者来说，将人工智能集成到制定、设置和确定 KPI 优先级的流程中可能会带来颠覆性的变化。为了预防或解决此类破坏需要组织、技术和文化投资。</p><p><strong>像管理资产一样管理 KPI，而不是跟踪工具。</strong>增强的 KPI 可以重新定义关键绩效，而不仅仅是跟踪它：这使得 KPI 以及增强 KPI 的能力成为宝贵的资产。与其他资产一样，KPI 可能会随着时间的推移或疏忽而贬值。像资产一样管理 KPI，而不是跟踪工具，可以确保它们随着时间的推移变得更有价值、更有洞察力和更具预测性。鉴于资产管理框架多种多样，有效的治理意味着为 KPI 资产（包括相关的基础数据资产）选择适当的资产管理框架。一些公司已经开始探索使用 KPI 来衡量 KPI，以确保其 KPI 资产的价值不断提高。</p><p><strong>加强KPI监督。</strong>随着 KPI 变得更加智能、更有效地代表公司战略，董事会参与管理 KPI 的开发和使用变得更加重要。诚然，制定和使用 KPI 属于管理职能。然而，董事会签署的战略既体现了关键绩效指标，又传达了关键绩效指标的信息。只批准战略而不批准公司制定 KPI 的方法是短视的行为，可能会破坏战略抱负。直接让董事会参与发展组织能力以提高 KPI 的工作。投资于增强的 KPI 与投资于提高绩效本身具有同样的战略意义。</p><p></p><h3> Conclusion</h3><p>我们管理 KPI 开发和使用的三管齐下的方法扩展了这样的理念：人工智能可以将 KPI 转化为战略资产，而不仅仅是跟踪绩效。它们充当组织的 GPS，提供更大的远见并更深入地了解关键绩效驱动因素之间的相互依赖性。</p><p>向人工智能增强型 KPI 的过渡并不是渐进式的转变。这是一个巨大的变化，从完全由人类、自上而下的方法来设置和完善 KPI。实现这一转变的组织正在将技术纳入（KPI 开发）循环。</p><p>未来，KPI将不再是被动的衡量工具，而是主动赋能决策者。使用生成式人工智能的持续创新有望扩大智能 KPI 的目的、力量和潜力。例如，与支持聊天的智能 KPI 进行对话已经成为我们采访的几位高管的目标。通过适当的治理，赋予智能关键绩效指标将赋予战略家和管理者同样的权力。</p><p><em>编者注：作者衷心感谢 Gaurav Jha、David Zuluaga Martínez、Allison Ryder 和 Barbara Spindel 对本文的贡献。</em></p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何让数据货币化成为每个人的事</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, Leslie Owens, and Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Barbara H. Wixom 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院信息系统研究中心的首席研究科学家，也是该中心数据研究顾问委员会的主席。辛西娅·M·比思 (Cynthia M. Beath) 是德克萨斯大学奥斯汀分校麦库姆斯商学院的名誉教授，也是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院信息系统研究中心的研究员。莱斯利·欧文斯（Leslie Owens）是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院信息系统研究中心的前执行主任，也是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师。此前，她曾担任 Forrester Research 的副总裁兼研究总监，以及 Abbott 的经理。伊丽莎白·海克勒 (Elizabeth Heichler) 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>杂志的编辑总监。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading B.H. Wixom, C.M. Beath, and L. Owens, &#8220;How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Sept. 27, 2023. Most leaders see their organization’s data as an important asset, but few have robust strategies for converting that asset into financial returns. In their new book, Data Is Everybody&#8217;s Business, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>BH Wixom、CM Beath 和 L. Owens，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">如何就数据货币化进行更好的战略对话</a>”，《<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite> ，2023 年 9 月 27 日。</p></aside><p>大多数领导者将其组织的数据视为重要资产，但很少有人拥有将该资产转化为财务回报的稳健策略。 Barbara H. Wixom、Cynthia M. Beath 和 Leslie Owens 在他们的新书《<cite>数据是每个人的事》</cite>中指出，领导者必须将数据货币化作为核心业务活动。</p><p>这需要对三种关键数据货币化方法形成广泛和共同的理解：改进数据工作、用数据包装产品以及销售信息产品。它还需要对整个组织中各个级别和职能的员工进行教育和参与。</p><p>在本次网络研讨会中，您将学习如何：</p><ul><li>实施五组实践，将组织最重要的数据转换为可重用的数据资产。</li><li>建立通用语言，以便每个人都可以参与构建和/或利用数据资产。</li><li>通过衡量实现的财务价值，将业务纪律引入数据投资。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>回流复兴正在进行中</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Erin McLaughlin and Dana M. Peterson. <p>艾琳·麦克劳克林 (Erin McLaughlin) 是世界大型企业联合会的高级经济学家。达纳·彼得森 (Dana M. Peterson) 是世界大型企业联合会的首席经济学家。</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Offshoring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Kevin Foley/MIT SMR; Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Companies are building manufacturing facilities in the U.S. at a pace not seen in decades. A confluence of factors is driving this trend: Amid supply chain bottlenecks, rising labor and transportation costs, U.S. tariffs on China, and geopolitical tensions, companies recognize the value of reshoring production. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/McLaughlin-Reshoring1-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Kevin Foley/麻省理工学院 SMR；卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>公司正在美国以数十年来未见的速度建设制造设施。多种因素共同推动了这一趋势：在供应链瓶颈、劳动力和运输成本上升、美国对中国加征关税以及地缘政治紧张局势的背景下，企业认识到生产回流的价值。美国有利于国内制造业的产业政策也为这些决策提供了信息，包括寻求解决国家安全威胁、经济混乱和关键技术组件获取机会减少的新法律。其结果是美国回流复兴的早期阶段。</p><p>高管们面临的问题是他们的公司是否应该遵循这一趋势。但首先，了解这一趋势的范围及其驱动因素非常重要。</p><p></p><p>自 20 世纪 70 年代末制造业开始急剧下滑以来，一直有人呼吁回流，但新冠肺炎 (COVID-19) 标志着企业高管的转折点。根据世界大型企业联合会的分析，在 2020 年第一季度至 2023 年第三季度之间，高管们在财报电话会议和会议上开始比以前更频繁地谈论在岸、回流和近岸外包。</p><p>随着疫情在全球范围内蔓延，此类言论在 2020 年第二季度开始显着增加。 2022年第二季度，供应链压力再次激增，俄罗斯入侵乌克兰，新联邦产业政策出台。总体而言，短短三年内，高管提及这些想法的次数增加了近 3,000%。</p><p>新法律也有助于推动这种本土化复苏，包括 2021 年《两党基础设施​​法》、2022 年《CHIPS 和科学法案》以及 2022 年《通胀削减法案》。每一项都包含有关美国制造的产品和零部件的生产和采购的规定，这有利于国内制造的公司。</p><p>回流正在推动制造业建筑活动急剧增加。公司在美国建造制造设施的速度高于任何其他房地产类型。根据美国人口普查局的数据，到 2022 年，此类支出的年增长率将达到 1147 亿美元，同比增长 40%，比过去五年增长 62%。</p><p>这使得制造业成为 2022 年增长最快的资产类别，因为<em>所有</em>非住宅建筑和基础设施的平均增长率与 2021 年相比仅增长了 7.4%。而且这种趋势还在继续：2023 年 7 月的制造业支出比同月高出 74%前一年。</p><p></p><p>回流复兴并不普遍适用。需要大量体力劳动的行业，包括鞋服、家具和家居装饰品， <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/05/business/economy/supply-chain-reshoring-us-manufacturing.html">回流的可能性较小</a>。产品更复杂、更昂贵的行业，以及那些可以在制造中使用自动化和机器人技术的行业，正在引领美国的复兴。由于回流和直接投资，美国就业增长最快的<a href="https://reshorenow.org/content/pdf/2022_Data_Report.pdf">五个行业</a>是电气设备、家用电器和零部件；计算机及电子产品；化学品；运输设备；以及医疗设备和用品。</p><p>我们的分析表明，北美（美国、加拿大和墨西哥）现有的供应商基础可以支持比目前更多的制造业活动。事实上，就电气设备而言，北美拥有全球15%的供应商基础和全球7%的产量。根据世界大型企业<a href="https://www.conference-board.org/publications/TCB-Global-Supplier-Index">联合会全球供应商指数，</a>制药行业 21% 的全球供应商基地位于北美，但其在全球产出中所占的份额仅为 18%。</p><p></p><h3>回流适合您的公司吗？</h3><p>高管和高级管理人员将供应链弹性、可持续性和地缘政治稳定性等因素置于廉价外国劳动力之上，从“低成本”转向“最佳成本”供应链战略，从而实现了回流。尽管在岸外包可能会因建设新设施和支付更高的工资而带来更高的成本，但最大限度地减少外部风险和创造长期效率的好处可能比保持短期成本低更重要。</p><p>企业领导者在决定是否采用这种模式时应考虑六个关键因素。</p><p> <strong>1、人工成本。</strong>全球劳动力短缺和成本上升（包括工资上涨的中国）使得在美国设立制造业比以前相对更便宜。根据国际劳工组织《2022 <a href="https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---ed_protect/---protrav/---travail/documents/publication/wcms_862569.pdf">-2023年全球工资报告》</a> ，2008年至2022年，中国的实际工资增长超过了G20国家。 2022年中国的实际月工资相当于2008年实际值的约2.6倍。</p><p> <strong>2.先进制造。</strong>新的自动化“智能工厂”需要更多的工程师和熟练的技术人员，但总体上通常要少得多的工人，包括传统的装配线工人，这使得美国劳动力池因其受过良好教育的劳动力而具有吸引力。对机器人技术和支持智能设施的先进技术的需求也在激增。根据自动化推进协会<a href="https://www.automate.org/news/robot-sales-in-north-america-have-strongest-year-ever-in-2021">的数据，2021 年北美机器人销量创下纪录</a>，售出 39,708 台，销售额达 20 亿美元，比 2017 年的历史高点增长 14%，比 2020 年的销量增长 28%。 Plex 的《 <a href="https://www.plex.com/sites/default/files/2022-05/10292_7th_State-of-Smart-Manufacturing_Supply-Chain.pdf">第七届年度智能制造状况报告</a>》指出，2022 年智能制造采用率同比增长 50%，83% 的制造商表示智能工厂是其未来成功的关键。</p><p> <strong>3. 风险缓解。</strong>供应链越长、越复杂，面临的风险就越大，特别是在潜在的地缘政治不稳定方面。联邦政府还重新审视其对其他经济体在关键公共卫生和国防供应及零部件方面的依赖，例如个人防护设备以及军用车辆和武器中使用的半导体。</p><p> <strong>4. 可持续性</strong>随着公司越来越需要实现可持续发展目标并减少碳足迹，本地化制造提供了多种好处。在国内建设新的绿色设施可以大大减少公司自有设施和车辆的范围 1 运营排放。美国拥有世界上最大的可持续建筑市场，超过 5.11 亿平方英尺<a href="https://www.usgbc.org/articles/top-10-countries-leed-demonstrate-green-building-truly-global-movement">获得能源与环境设计领先评级体系认证</a>，而中国只有 1.8 亿平方英尺。此外，制造离最终客户更近的产品可以减少运输过程中的排放。</p><p> <strong>5. 利益相关者的情绪。</strong>许多公司的利益相关者——包括员工、公司董事会、行业组织、政府官员和供应链内的其他公司——希望高管考虑<a href="https://www.kearney.com/industry/consumer-retail/article/-/insights/the-2021-reshoring-index-the-tides-are-turning">将制造业务本地化</a>。例如，美国最大的零售商沃尔玛在 2021 年承诺，到 2030 年将额外花费 3500 亿美元购买在美国制造、种植或组装的商品。</p><p> <strong>6、运输费用。</strong>在决定是否进行陆上制造业务时，高管们应该权衡较低的国际劳动力和运营成本的好处与较高的海运成本。 2021 年，跨太平洋运输成本比 2020 年 1 月的水平增加了 15 倍，尽管运输成本随着经济放缓而下降，但过去几年的供应链波动是管理者首先要考虑的问题。</p><p> The growth in US manufacturing-facility construction will continue as businesses see value in focusing on aspects of risk mitigation, using automation to offset labor challenges, and even building new facilities that emit less carbon. This reshoring renaissance is just beginning; it takes a few years to plan, permit, and acquire property for new-facility construction.</p><p></p><p> Now is the time for manufacturing executives to understand how their businesses fit into this renaissance and determine whether reshoring is right for them. Using the factors above as a framework, executives should consider these five key questions:</p><ol><li> Can a new facility for my products that uses advanced automation offset higher labor costs?</li><li> Does my current supply chain involve countries that present uncertainty due to geopolitics?</li><li> Will the carbon emissions from my company&#39;s current supply chain improve significantly if we build a new facility powered by renewable energy and localize production?</li><li> Are my stakeholders, especially customers, asking for domestically manufactured products?</li><li> Is the cost savings that comes with eliminating transoceanic shipping enough to balance out a likely increase in labor and new-facility construction costs?</li></ol><p> By seeking answers to questions such as these, the C-suite can better navigate their company&#39;s operations through a changing global production landscape.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Managers Everywhere Must Know About Caste</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hari Bapuji, Kamini Gupta, Snehanjali Chrispal, and Thomas Roulet. <p>Hari Bapuji ( <a href="https://twitter.com/haribapuji">@haribapuji</a> ) is a professor of management at the University of Melbourne, Australia, and a cofounder of <a href="https://air-collective.com/">Action to Improve Representation</a> . Kamini Gupta is a lecturer of management at King&#39;s College London, where she also hosts the <a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/events/series/kings-business-school-nisau-india-series">India Series</a> , fireside chats focused on topics of urgent relevance to India&#39;s growth and place in the world. Snehanjali Chrispal is a lecturer of management at Deakin University in Australia, and researches inequality and organizations, particularly human rights issues like gender and caste. Thomas Roulet is a professor of organizational sociology and leadership at the Judge Business School and a fellow of King&#39;s College, both at the University of Cambridge.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Cultural Differences]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Justice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Grundini/Ikon Images As globalization and workforce mobility make many organizations more multicultural, managers find themselves having to broaden their understanding of workplace discrimination’s possible forms. In particular, issues of bias related to caste identity are making headlines around the world more frequently, and maintaining a healthy and productive culture will require leaders to be able [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bapuji_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Grundini/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> As globalization and workforce mobility make many organizations more multicultural, managers find themselves having to broaden their understanding of workplace discrimination&#39;s possible forms. In particular, issues of bias related to caste identity are making headlines around the world more frequently, and maintaining a healthy and productive culture will require leaders to be able to identify, prevent, and mitigate caste-based discrimination.</p><p> The caste system is a sociocultural-economic hierarchy that is pervasive in South Asia and the sizable South Asian diaspora all over the world. An individual&#39;s caste, inherited from their father, is determined solely by their birth and is unchangeable.</p><p> Numerous incidents of caste-based bias in Silicon Valley and elsewhere have been documented in the media. Studies conducted by academics, governments, and advocacy organizations have found that caste discrimination is prevalent in countries with significant South Asian populations, including the US, the UK, Canada, and Australia. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p> Within South Asia, which is home to a quarter of the world&#39;s population, caste bias can have disastrous consequences for individuals and organizations. For example, in June 2023, Vivek Raj, an employee of Indian fashion retailer Lifestyle International, died by suicide after recording a statement alleging <a href="https://www.thequint.com/south-india/vivek-raj-dalit-bengaluru-employee-lifestyle-dies-caste-discrimination">workplace caste discrimination</a> . In another case, Indian food delivery company Zomato faced public backlash for <a href="https://www.thequint.com/opinion/zomato-ad-kachra-lagaan-caste-marketing-teaching-moment">a 2023 advertisement</a> that reinforced derogatory caste stereotypes.</p><p> Multinational companies, such as Alphabet, Amazon, Apple, Dell, and X (formerly Twitter), have recognized the importance of this issue by addressing caste-based discrimination in their corporate policies. Over 20 US universities have also included caste as a protected category in their policies, alongside race, gender, religion, and others.</p><p> In February 2023, the city of Seattle passed a law to outlaw caste discrimination. A similar bill was passed by California&#39;s legislature but was vetoed in October 2023 by its governor, who said that caste-based discrimination was already prohibited under the state&#39;s existing laws. These legislative efforts are in line with laws in countries that have caste systems, such as India, whose constitution outlaws caste discrimination and guarantees affirmative action for low-caste individuals in public education, employment, and political offices.</p><p> Managers everywhere need to understand these issues to help protect employees of South Asian origin from caste-based discrimination, bullying, incivility, and harassment, and to avoid the legal jeopardy that can result from such acts in the workplace. Managers could also improve the well-being and performance of individuals and their organizations by addressing the influence of caste on activities such as hiring, corporate social responsibility, information sharing, and networking. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><h3> What Is Caste, and Why Is It Relevant?</h3><p> The fundamental assumption underlying the caste system is the notion that humans are created as unequal groups. This inequality is manifested by arbitrarily assigning different levels of purity and value to groups of people on an artificially defined hierarchy that gives some of them socially enforced rights and privileges, including the right to practice certain sets of occupations.</p><p></p><p> Caste is a complex system comprising thousands of groups and subgroups across religions. Broadly speaking, among those who practice Hinduism, Brahmins are at the top of the hierarchy. Their occupations have traditionally included religious duties and knowledge professions like recordkeeping, science, and education. Next in the hierarchy are Kshatriyas (who have traditionally occupied military roles), followed by Vysyas (businesspeople and traders) and Shudras (workers and laborers). Similar groups and subgroups are found among those practicing other religions. For instance, <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4357934">among South Asian Muslims</a> , there are high castes (Ashraf, consisting of the Saiads, Sheikhs, Pathans, and Mughals) and low castes (Ajlaf, consisting of artisans and other workers). Among those who practice Sikhism, there are high-caste groups like the Jatts and Khatris. Similarly, <a href="https://scroll.in/article/876000/is-the-caste-system-deep-rooted-among-christians-in-india-a-kerala-bishop-stirs-up-a-hornets-nest">South Asian Christian congregations</a> have formed around distinct caste-based identities.</p><p> Dalits are outside of, and well below, the above groups. They are considered by those following the norms of the caste system as inferior and impure to the point of being subhuman and are relegated to occupations that involve activities like cleaning up excrement and disposing of the dead. Dalits, found across religions, are stigmatized as “ <a href="https://baws.in/books/baws/EN/Volume_05/pdf/14">untouchable</a> ” due to the historic, and still prevalent, practice of other castes avoiding physical contact and spatial proximity with them.</p><p> Adivasis (meaning first inhabitants or, more generally, indigenous peoples) are another group outside the caste system who have historically lived in forest or hill areas remote from urban locations and have often been <a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/02757206.2023.2204866">stigmatized as outlaws</a> .</p><p> Although individuals from each group today engage in occupations other than those assigned to them by caste, an individual&#39;s caste remains a significant determinant of the social and professional opportunities available to them. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><h3> How Caste Shapes Organizations</h3><p> Caste can shape an organization&#39;s internal environment in a few different ways. The talent pool from which a company hires might not have caste diversity due partly to differences in access to education and other resources that have persisted for generations. Caste determines access to capital and valuable business connections. Research has shown that family firms rely on caste-based networks to share knowledge and resources and exert control over markets and industries. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Value chains that pass through South Asia replicate caste hierarchies such that high-caste individuals control important activities in the chain (such as design, research, and marketing) while low-caste individuals are relegated to activities valued less (such as product assembly and manufacturing). <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> The disproportionate control of institutions like educational, regulatory, legislative, and industry bodies by high-caste individuals also shapes the environment in which organizations operate.</p><p> Caste impacts the functioning of organizations as well. Recruiters and managers are likely to introduce biases into decisions about hiring and promotion, even at the level of the C-suite. Such biases might be explicit, such as through stereotyping individuals of certain caste backgrounds; or implicit, in the weight placed on markers such as speaking English with a familiar accent or observing certain social etiquette, even when they&#39;re not relevant to the job. Caste stereotypes can also affect the assignment of jobs, such as when high-caste individuals get promoted to managerial roles while low-caste individuals are relegated to low-end jobs, like data entry and coding in the <a href="https://scholarcommons.scu.edu/soc/67/">IT sector</a> or cleaning jobs across sectors.</p><p> Caste also tends to impact workplace interactions; for example, low-caste individuals might experience harassment, bullying, and incivility through behaviors like name-calling or exclusion, or be subjected to unsafe or demeaning work conditions. In one study on caste-based discrimination in the US, 25% of Dalit respondents reported having faced physical or verbal assault; 67% said they had been treated unfairly at work, and 60% reported experiencing caste-based derogatory comments and jokes. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><h3> Why Caste Poses Unique Challenges</h3><p> Caste predominantly operates indirectly, in the form of <em>identity</em> , <em>resources</em> , <em>networks</em> , and <em>culture</em> . A person&#39;s caste is not evident from their physiological features but can be inferred based on those four dimensions and shape their perceived merit. That perception of merit, rather than their caste, can then be claimed as the basis for decisions and actions affecting them. (See “The Indirect Markers of Caste.”) Here&#39;s how caste manifests in each of these dimensions.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> The Indirect Markers of Caste</h4><p class="caption"> Caste is often not directly apparent but can be ascertained based on an individual&#39;s identity, resources, networks, and culture. Together, these dimensions shape the perception of an individual&#39;s merit. Caste discrimination in workplaces is therefore not always explicit but can manifest as biases, stereotyping, and exclusionary practices that are difficult to recognize and address. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Bapuji_RF_Winter_2024_Figure-1.png" alt="The Indirect Markers of Caste" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p> <strong>Identity.</strong> For many people from South Asia, caste is an inalienable part of one&#39;s identity. Inherited by birth, caste is seen as a symbol of one&#39;s ancestry. Caste identity is further reinforced through practices such as endogamy (marrying within one&#39;s caste), which is intended to maintain caste purity. Nearly 95% of marriages among Indians, including Indian-origin people in the US, occur within the same caste. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Even a <a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2021-02-11/caste-system-of-india-and-south-asia-in-australia-dalit-rights/13135622">dating app for South Asians</a> that a US company developed allows users to filter for high-caste groups to find matches. Several other matchmaking service providers also facilitate marriages within castes.</p><p> An individual&#39;s caste identity is often reflected in their name. Many South Asian surnames (such as Bhatia, Kamble, Khan, Sharma, and Yadav) can be markers of caste. South Asians who do not have a caste-revealing name can face probing questions and exclusion, because caste identity shapes resource availability, networks, and cultural affinity.</p><p> <strong>Resources.</strong> Tangible resources, such as cash, assets, and investments, are unequally distributed along caste lines. Due to historical differences in rights and opportunities to own and accumulate assets among castes, such inequalities have compounded over generations. Research has found that in India, high-caste individuals are overly represented among the top 50% of wealthy individuals, accounting for 90% of the total wealth, while low-caste individuals have a much higher representation in the bottom 50% of individuals in terms of wealth. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> Members of high-caste communities often have systemically greater access to economic capital and the advantages that come with it, such as the ability to attend elite private schools, which affords them greater access to knowledge professions. For instance, <a href="https://theprint.in/india/education/diversity-deficit-in-iims-iits-just-23-sts-and-157-scs-in-9640-faculty-posts/191246/">only 6% of the faculty at the Indian Institutes of Management</a> (premier business schools established by the Indian government) are from the low castes that account for <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/decoded/2021/06/29/measuring-caste-in-india/">the vast majority</a> (69%, according to one estimate) of the Indian population. A similar situation exists in other higher education institutions.</p><p> These differences in resources also affect who can emigrate from South Asia, with high-caste individuals finding it easier to migrate to and get settled in their host countries. For example, nearly 90% of US residents of Indian origin are from high castes. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> <strong>Networks.</strong> Caste forms the basis of formal and informal social networks that facilitate economic transactions. Members of one caste are more likely to hire, do business with, and lend financial and nonfinancial support to people from similar caste backgrounds. The long-standing practice of marrying within a caste is one way these networks are formed.</p><p> Caste also shapes networks via other forms of spatial and social segregation. Studies have shown the existence of caste-based segregation in many cities in India due in part to historic factors that allowed each caste to reside in a specific part of the city or town and partly due to individuals&#39; preference to live next to people of their own caste. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Social segregation occurs because of how caste norms shape interactions between castes. For instance, high-caste individuals adhering to such norms might avoid sharing space or a meal with Dalits.</p><p> Formal and informal caste-based associations exist both within South Asia and globally. Such associations can be explicitly caste-based, such as the Brahman Samaj of North America, which is open to all Brahmins, and Pravara Vedika, open only to certain Brahmin subgroups. Some associations represent themselves as broader “community” or linguistic/cultural organizations but are dominated by certain high castes. For example, the Telugu Association of North America is dominated by the Kamma, a high-caste group that actively supports its caste kin; the North American Telugu Association is dominated by the Reddy high-caste group; and the NRI Vasavi Association predominantly comprises members of the Vysya community. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> <strong>Culture.</strong> The dominant culture and norms of a particular South Asian religion or region are often defined in terms of the high-caste culture, even when it is practiced by a numerical minority of the population. These are most often reflected in people&#39;s religious and cultural practices, diets, and spoken languages, which vary by caste. For example, high-caste groups have a hegemony on certain forms of “classical” music and dance because low-caste groups have been excluded from practicing them. These arts are considered superior to folk music and dances practiced by low-caste individuals. Because high-caste individuals have migrated abroad at a higher rate than those from low castes, these cultural artifacts are often perceived as typical of South Asian culture.</p><p> The common misconception in high-income countries that <a href="https://www.livemint.com/Politics/dWUqT4epdPTHNAYuKYVThK/No-vegetarianism-is-not-growing-in-India.html">most Indians are vegetarian</a> is another example of high-caste culture defining the norm abroad. Several organizations and <a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/0963662520903690">higher education institutions</a> in India adhere to vegetarian menus or have separate kitchens and dining spaces for vegetarians, leading to the segregation, stigmatization, and exclusion of low-caste individuals. Perceptions of South Asian culture are reinforced by the widespread representation of high-caste culture in popular media, including film, TV, and music. Because low-caste individuals do not always fit these profiles, non-South Asian managers might unwittingly treat lower-caste individuals differently as well.</p><h3> What Managers Can Do About Caste Discrimination</h3><p> Caste can be inferred from how it manifests as identity, resources, networks, and culture. For managers of South Asian origin, many signals are visible (such as last names or diet) or can be learned through social interactions (such as location of residence or ancestral occupations) and used in organizational decision-making. For example, research has shown that when the resumes of two candidates of the same profile are presented, high-caste individuals are selected over low-caste individuals based only on the status associated with their last names. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p> However, non-South Asian managers can have difficulty discerning cultural cues to caste identity, and since it is a sensitive topic, inquiring about a person&#39;s caste is not appropriate. Low-caste individuals might choose to hide their caste to fit in and avoid exclusion. What, then, can managers do to create a caste-inclusive environment in their organizations?</p><p> To successfully address the challenges of caste, managers need to take a holistic approach that includes making caste a part of organizational diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) policies and practices, raising awareness through training, and addressing caste inequalities in societies where they are systemic. (See “How Organizations Can Address Caste.”) Managers should also take steps to preempt resistance as these efforts get underway.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> How Organizations Can Address Caste</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations can employ four approaches to creating a more caste-inclusive working environment for South Asian employees and partners. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Employee Policies and Codes of Conduct</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Make caste a protected category alongside race, gender, and other aspects of identity.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Include caste in codes of conduct, such as those for suppliers and communication.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Employ equitable procedures for hiring, job assignments, and promotion.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Put protocols in place to address complaints based on caste.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Training and Awareness</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Provide diversity, equity, and inclusion training to identify caste discrimination, and support employees facing such discrimination.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Coach managers on how to manage teams with employees of different castes, create inclusivity in teams, and handle caste-sensitive issues.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Raise awareness of caste privilege and oppression and how they affect individual attitudes and behaviors.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Corporate Social Initiatives</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Provide scholarships, coaching, and training for low-caste individuals where the company has operations, to overcome caste disadvantages and increase access opportunities.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Create opportunities for low-caste individuals and groups to work as suppliers for the company.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Make philanthropic support conditional on nongovernmental organizations and charities having caste-inclusive operations.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left; vertical-align:middle;"><p> <strong>Preempting Resistance</strong></p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Understand the sources of resistance and the stakeholders involved.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Address resistance through thoughtful and tactful communications to secure buy-in/participation from employees and other stakeholders.</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span> Design external communications to create broad-based support for caste inclusion. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Bapuji_RF_Winter_2024_Table-1.png" alt="How Organizations Can Address Caste" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Explicitly identify caste as a protected category.</strong> DEI policies aim to promote inclusion for people of all identities, and a first step is to explicitly identify caste as a protected category. This recognition should cover all relevant company policies, including those related to the conduct of employees and suppliers, corporate communications, and employee hiring. Companies can explicitly state in their employee conduct policies that caste discrimination will not be tolerated, as <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/caste-california-tech-giants-confront-ancient-indian-hierarchy-2022-08-15/">Apple</a> and <a href="https://www.cisco.com/c/dam/en_us/about/cobc/2021/fy22-code-of-business-conduct-english.pdf">Cisco</a> have done, and implement protocols to comprehensively address reports of caste discrimination in the workplace. Companies can also include caste in their supplier code of conduct (as Canadian retailer <a href="https://www.loblaw.ca/en/supplier-code-of-conduct/">Loblaw</a> has done) to ensure that caste is a protected category throughout their value chains and that suppliers do not alienate or discriminate against low-caste individuals.</p><p></p><p> Policies around company communications and social media messaging should also include guidance on caste-inclusive language. For example, <a href="https://www.dell.com/en-in/dt/policies/social-media-policy.htm">Dell Technologies&#39;</a> global social media policy notes that caste-based hate speech is not tolerated. Companies that host user-generated content should expand their terms of service to prohibit caste-related discriminatory language and slurs, as <a href="https://transparency.fb.com/en-gb/policies/community-standards/hate-speech/">Meta</a> , X, and <a href="https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2801939?hl=en-GB#:~:text=We%20remove%20content%20promoting%20violence,Disability">YouTube</a> have done, and moderate content that promotes caste indirectly. To develop such policies, organizations can partner with advocacy groups such as the International Dalit Solidarity Network, which has released <a href="https://idsn.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Caste-hate-speech-report-IDSN-2021.pdf">studies</a> on caste-based hate speech.</p><p> Existing practices for inclusive hiring can be adapted for caste with relative ease. Anonymizing applicants&#39; resumes can eliminate some signals of caste from the recruitment process. Employers can instruct hiring managers to disregard candidate characteristics that are not salient to the job, such as accent, etiquette, status of educational institutions attended, and family background. Companies, especially those with subsidiaries in South Asia, must proactively diversify their pool of applicants through targeted referrals or recruiting drives directed at low-caste candidates. These individuals account for the vast majority of the population, and failing to reach them means overlooking a huge talent pool. Structured and standardized interviews that more accurately evaluate candidates based on job-relevant skills can minimize bias at the interview stage and combat caste prejudices in hiring.</p><p> <strong>Increase awareness and training.</strong> Given that caste is an invisible inequality, raising awareness about it is one of the most important aspects of addressing caste discrimination. This training should be aimed at preventing caste discrimination, creating a caste-inclusive environment, and understanding the effects of caste privilege and oppression.</p><p></p><p> Training on caste needs to address the forms of discrimination that low-caste individuals commonly experience, including <a href="https://youtu.be/wJwkIxOpqZA?si=N67lxr5AWEEF2wRQ">slurs</a> , jokes, and <a href="https://dalitdiscrimination.tumblr.com/">derogatory comments</a> about them and their leaders. For example, low-caste individuals from India, which has caste-based affirmative action policies, are often at the receiving end of derogatory remarks, such as “quota candidate” or “reservation people,” that demean the use of these policies. The training should also extend to supporting employees who face such discrimination.</p><aside class="callout-info"><h4>其他资源</h4><ul><li>BR Ambedkar, <cite>Annihilation of Caste: The Annotated Critical Edition</cite> (New Delhi: Navayana, 2014).</li><li> “Testimonies of Practice of Caste in the USA,” Ambedkar King Study Circle, accessed Sept. 14, 2023, <a href="https://akscusa.org">https://akscusa.org</a> .</li><li> <cite>Blocked by Caste: Economic Discrimination in Modern India</cite> , eds. S. Thorat and KS Newman (New Delhi: Oxford University Press, 2012).</li><li> I. Wilkerson, <cite>Caste: The Origins of Our Discontents</cite> (New York: Random House, 2020).</li><li> S. Yengde, <cite>Caste Matters</cite> (New Delhi: Penguin Random House India, 2019).</li></ul></aside><p> Managers should be coached on creating a caste-inclusive environment in their teams. This could include raising awareness about the many ways in which caste discrimination might appear and signaling the inappropriateness of caste-sensitive topics in workplace discussions. Further, without violating the privacy of individuals, companies can collect self-disclosed data on individuals&#39; caste or conduct caste audits (for example, using last names as caste indicators) to understand the caste homogeneity/diversity in their organizations and make employees aware of its implications for organizational functioning and performance.</p><p> <strong>Tackle caste discrimination at its root.</strong> Organizations can work on addressing caste not just internally but within the countries where the caste system is prevalent. Directly funding education and development initiatives in India, Nepal, or Pakistan, for example, can improve access to education for individuals from low-caste backgrounds. Mentoring individuals and groups from lower castes can also help minimize the barriers they face to enter an industry or a profession. Companies can make their support of nongovernmental organizations and charitable organizations (including community and cultural organizations) conditional on their being caste-inclusive in their operations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Preempt resistance to addressing caste.</strong> Organizations that attempt to address caste are likely to face resistance. Google <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2022/06/02/google-caste-equality-labs-tanuja-gupta/">canceled a talk on caste</a> by Thenmozhi Soundararajan of Equality Labs in 2022 after some of its employees objected to it, and legislative efforts to address caste in the US have faced stiff resistance from <a href="https://www.fairobserver.com/world-news/us-news/caste-is-now-weaponized-against-indian-americans/">some Hindu lobbying groups</a> . These groups often argue that caste is an issue of the past or not an issue outside of South Asia and that policies protecting caste could be misused to discriminate against people of Hindu faith or Indian ethnicity. Understanding these sources of resistance to addressing caste can help organizations design ways to overcome them and secure buy-in from all employees and other stakeholders, including via external communications that encourage broad-based support for caste equity.</p><p> Caste is a complex and difficult issue, but addressing it is both an instrumental and moral imperative for organizations around the world. Doing so contributes to more equitable outcomes for individuals and affirms organizational commitment to cocreating a fairer and more equal society for all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Economic Incentives Are Key to Driving Sustainability at Scale</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Satoshi Ikeda and Simon Glynn. <p>Satoshi Ikeda is chief sustainable finance officer of the Financial Services Agency of Japan. Simon Glynn is founder of Zero Ideas.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Business Case]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR When it comes to mobilizing the economy for climate action, most recent progress has been incremental. To come close to achieving the goals of the Paris Agreement, the pace and scale of change must be much more radical. The scaling up we need is not simply a matter of dialing up what [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Ikeda-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> When it comes to mobilizing the economy for climate action, most recent progress has been incremental. To come close to achieving the goals of the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-paris-agreement-its-down-to-business/">Paris Agreement</a> , the pace and scale of change must be much more radical. The scaling up we need is not simply a matter of dialing up what we have already begun. What we now need is qualitatively different, and today&#39;s approach won&#39;t get us there.</p><p> Merely strengthening disclosure requirements on climate-related data and information could increase regulatory burdens without having a significant productive impact. Regulation needs to be partnered with industrial strategy to create the commercial demand for climate action at scale and for the sustainable finance that is increasingly available. Japan is seeking to do this with a balanced mix of sticks and carrots that is in marked contrast to the approaches of both the United States (mostly carrots) and the European Union (mostly sticks).</p><p></p><p> Today we expect companies to act on climate change without a financial case for doing so. Their nonfinancial rationales might be to do the morally right thing, to satisfy the ESG (environmental, social, and governance) interests of investors, to instill pride and a sense of commitment among workers, or to keep their options open in the face of uncertainty. These are all sound motivations, but they rarely add up to a solid financial case in which cash investments predictably generate surplus cash returns. As a result, they drive incremental commitments but can&#39;t drive action at scale.</p><p> Take, for example, the steel industry, which currently accounts for around 8% of global greenhouse gas emissions. There are multiple technological approaches to decarbonizing steel production, but they are all difficult, speculative, and hugely expensive. As Japan&#39;s Ministry of Economy, Trade, and Industry (METI) observes in its <a href="https://www.meti.go.jp/english/press/2021/pdf/1027_002a.pdf">technology road map for the iron and steel industry</a> , “Replacing the existing process with a new one … will require a huge amount of capital investment, resulting in large capital and operating costs. But these additional costs are only for decarbonization and contribute neither to improving the performance of steel nor increasing its productivity.”</p><p></p><p> In Europe, the “green premium” for low-carbon steel is expected to be above 250 euros ($265) per ton — a premium of upward of 25% on today&#39;s cost. How many customers would choose to pay this added cost for a product that offers no improvement in performance? Some carmakers and construction companies will pay a bit more for the ESG benefit of using green steel, but they can&#39;t afford to pay much because the consumers at the end of the value chain are not choosing to pay more for green steel. And if customers won&#39;t choose to pay the premium, how can the steelmakers afford the huge investment required? The availability of sustainable finance doesn&#39;t solve that problem if steelmakers have no financial case for making the investment.</p><p> Driving climate action at the scale that is needed will require more than nonfinancial incentives for businesses. A reliance on such incentives will limit us to nonmaterial, incremental outcomes and also leave the whole climate effort vulnerable to changes in sentiment — a real risk we&#39;re already seeing in the backlash against ESG in the United States. For material, transformational outcomes, companies need financial incentives to act, with financial returns that justify the costs and risks involved. That is the only way that enough companies will choose to invest at scale.</p><h3> Creating Demand for Sustainable Finance</h3><p> Where will these financial incentives come from? Today, to shape the availability and focus of sustainable finance, we use scenarios for how different industries need to transition. The International Energy Agency, the Transition Pathway Initiative, the Science-Based Targets initiative, the Glasgow Financial Alliance for Net Zero, and others all set out such sectoral pathways. These scenarios illustrate what is needed, but they don&#39;t make it happen. They are descriptive, not prescriptive. Using these scenarios, we can see what changes an industry needs to make and what an optimal path might be — but describing this path does not move an industry along it.</p><p> The challenge is not about finding the money. The supply of sustainable finance is impressive. The challenge is to create the demand for that finance, in step with the growing supply. Today, providers of sustainable finance lament that take-up of the money they have to offer is low because potential borrowers don&#39;t have the risk appetite; in other words, they are not sufficiently confident of a return.</p><p> For governments, directly paying the green premium through subsidies would be hugely expensive. Fortunately, that is not necessary. What is needed is to create conditions in which companies are motivated to invest the money themselves and are rewarded for doing so.</p><p> There are good examples of this happening. The automotive industry, particularly in the US and European Union, has invested in the transformational shift to electric vehicles, anticipating a near future in which manufacturers will not be allowed to sell vehicles powered by internal combustion engines. And the US government&#39;s Inflation Reduction Act has been described by the World Economic Forum as “ <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/11/how-new-laws-meet-climate-goals/">a compelling nudge</a> ” to the private sector and investors to decarbonize hard-to-abate sectors.</p><p> In the US, the approach has been to rely heavily on incentives — the proverbial carrot — which means that companies&#39; participation is voluntary. This reflects what is politically most feasible in the US: It is hard to impose constraints on business, especially at a federal level, in a culture that reveres free enterprise. Incentives are targeted at strengthening the technology leadership of the US economy, playing to a nationalist and environmental agenda. The problem: The incentives needed to kick-start investment in some industries might be very high and might depend in practice on enabling initiatives that cannot be solved with money alone, such as issuing permits to build new long-distance grids for wind and solar power.</p><p> The EU, in contrast, relies principally on regulation — the proverbial stick. This reflects what is politically most feasible; it is hard to offer incentives at the EU level without favoring national target industries and getting into divisive politics. But regulation is unifying and has been the core of the EU&#39;s supranational toolkit. It uses the EU&#39;s market power, a market too big for global players to miss out on. The problem: It might impose unquantified and hidden costs on industry without first gaining political acceptance of that outcome. That is the background to Germany&#39;s recent wobble about protecting its internal-combustion-based car industry from the forced move to electric vehicles.</p><p></p><h3> The Power of an Industrial Strategy</h3><p> America and Europe have hugely different approaches to climate action that reflect their respective self-image and values. Where politics allow, a more balanced mix of sticks and carrots can provide the most effective incentives for companies to progress along their transition pathway. Building up the initiatives in an advertised sequence can provide strong incentives for early action, if companies are confident of the policy environment to come and motivated to position themselves for it.</p><p> Such an industrial strategy is not about picking winners and losers but about recognizing and accepting the idea of winners and losers and playing to win — or to not lose. The incentives work by creating risk that companies are motivated to avoid. The financial case for Volkswagen&#39;s early investment in the electric vehicle market sprang in part from the opportunity to win share from its biggest rival, Toyota. The financial case for Toyota&#39;s recent investment in electric vehicles is partly based on defending its market share. Both companies are strongly incentivized by the threat from emerging electric car makers in China. Similarly, carbon capture and storage is expensive and still speculative, but the financial case to industrialize it could be strong for a fossil fuel company concerned about future prohibitions against extracting and selling its mineral assets.</p><p> This insight aligns well with the way political power sits largely at the national level (or regional level, in the case of the EU). Governments can stimulate climate action in ways that favor their companies and their economies. The incentives in the Inflation Reduction Act are attracting corporate investment, skilled jobs, and technology innovation to the US Japan&#39;s steelmakers are looking to lead the world in new technology solutions for high-end steel, using hydrogen rather than carbon to reduce iron ore to iron. This battle for competitiveness at both the national and company levels is how we can drive climate action at scale in the short time we have to make an impact.</p><h3> Creating and Destroying</h3><p> The transition we are describing is the creative destruction and value migration that have always fueled innovation and investment in a capitalist economy. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> In this important sense, climate change is not a collective-action problem: For systemwide transformations in which nobody loses, the transition will be practically unaffordable. We need winners and losers — or at least the real prospect of winners and losers — to provide the competitive pressure and financial incentive for companies to act.</p><p> The practical task for policy makers is not just to correct for the externalized costs of pollution but to facilitate the dynamic transition to this new state. As researchers have recently asserted, policy makers need to “simultaneously and successfully navigate two distinct but interrelated dynamics: the creation and mass commodification of new green energy technologies on the one hand, and the destruction of powerful, fossil fuel incumbencies on the other.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> The American and European approaches do not provide this navigation. The carrots of America&#39;s Inflation Reduction Act help to create the new without constraining the old. The sticks of EU&#39;s regulations constrain the old without solving the technological or economic challenge of substituting with the new.</p><p> What would a more balanced and dynamic, sequenced approach look like?</p><h3> Paths to Green Transformation</h3><p> Japan&#39;s approach to green transformation, or GX, involves a mix of carrots and sticks to drive both parts of the creative destruction required, sequenced over time. The <a href="https://www.meti.go.jp/english/press/2023/pdf/0210_003b.pdf">explicit goal</a> is to deliver “both emissions reduction and economic growth,” without sacrificing either. At the highest level, Japanese corporate and government interests are aligned: “The success or failure of GX initiatives is directly linked to the competitiveness of companies and nations.”</p><p> The immediate carrot is the commitment of 20 trillion yen ($140 billion) of government support for upfront investment over the next 10 years and an envisaged 150 trillion yen of public and private investment. The principal stick is an <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/carbon/japans-carbon-pricing-scheme-being-launched-april-2023-03-30/">industrial pricing mechanism</a> for carbon that is in trials now and expected to be phased in starting in 2026. The plan includes both a European-style emissions-trading scheme for high-emissions industries and a surcharge on the supply of fossil fuels.</p><p> Announcing the stick now but phasing it in later in the decade creates the immediate incentive for companies to make the technology investments in their transitions, without penalizing them financially before they have had the opportunity to adapt.</p><p> Japanese companies are partners in this effort as well as counterparties. The intent is not just to reduce Japan&#39;s own emissions, which account for 3% of the world&#39;s total, but to position Japanese companies as service providers helping to reduce other countries&#39; emissions too, through the green technology solutions they will offer.</p><p> Companies worked with METI — or with the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism, in the case of maritime transport and aviation — to develop technology road maps for 10 sectors that collectively cover 80% of Japan&#39;s carbon emissions. In the technology road map for iron and steel, for example, the specialist committee advising METI included representation from the Japan Iron and Steel Federation, credit analysts, and the Development Bank of Japan, as well as professors in engineering and technology. The METI road map illustrates its general framework with a specific example, JFE Steel; JFE Steel in turn presents its corporate road map as an application of the METI framework. This collaboration helps companies commit to ambitious transition plans, with the confidence that the government is doing its part in creating the conditions that will make them viable in terms of R&amp;D, energy infrastructure, finance, carbon pricing, and more. The GX plan is as much about enabling these road maps as it is about mandating them.</p><p></p><p> The plans are not rigid. In the future, different technologies might win out than what today&#39;s plans project. Both government and industry know the technology assumptions that the plans are based on and thus are able to adapt as needed and aren&#39;t locked in. Pluralism is celebrated: The cover image of METI&#39;s strategy document shows multiple paths up a mountain to the 2050 carbon-neutral summit.</p><p> Creating the conditions for corporate investments in this way is the role for governments&#39; industrial strategy, in partnership with sustainable finance. Without such coordinated industrial policies, merely strengthening disclosure requirements on climate-related data and information might increase regulatory burdens unproductively. Government efforts to step up sustainability-related reporting frameworks need to be matched by government actions on the industrial strategy front.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/economic-incentives-are-key-to-driving-sustainability-at-scale/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> R&amp;D Leaders Must Play a Key Role in the Journey to Net Zero</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Edwards and Michael Zeitlyn. <p>Dan Edwards is group managing director and CEO at Science Group, a science, engineering, and technology consultancy. Michael Zeitlyn is president of advisory services at Science Group.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint]]></category><category><![CDATA[R&D]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com Major companies worldwide have pledged to reach net-zero emissions, but pledges are one thing, and action is another. Momentum can, of course, be difficult to sustain. Carbon reduction may be imperative for the good of the planet, but it requires businesses to think and operate in new ways, to collaborate with more outside [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Edwards_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Page/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Major companies worldwide have pledged to reach net-zero emissions, but pledges are one thing, and action is another. Momentum can, of course, be difficult to sustain. Carbon reduction may be imperative for the good of the planet, but it requires businesses to think and operate in new ways, to collaborate with more outside entities, to trust data-gathering processes that are new and developing — and to put R&amp;D and innovation leaders at the center of the process.</p><p> Science Group convened a forum of R&amp;D leaders and CTOs — including executives from Amcor, Bayer, Mars, PepsiCo, Procter &amp; Gamble, Solvay, and Stepan — to identify ways in which companies can translate net-zero ambitions into material progress. In particular, we wanted to help define the pivotal role that innovation teams can play in the journey. Here, we highlight insights that emerged from this forum about practices that help build a <a href="https://sustainability.sciencegroup.com/net-zero-playbook/ ">pathway</a> for both industry and the planet to thrive.</p><p></p><h3> A Mandate for Action</h3><p> If companies want their net-zero pledges to be more than well-intended aspirations, they have to make carbon reduction a core business value: Management must lose sleep over it, the way they have historically lost sleep over safety, quality, and profits. Acting on net zero is a cross-functional initiative, and the division of labor can be murky. Marketing, distribution, and other business functions will contribute to the company&#39;s greenhouse gas (GHG) reduction target on their own timelines. Procurement, for instance, might be able to reduce emissions in short order, whereas R&amp;D — which is, by definition, forward-looking — might be working three, five, or even 10 years out. The key, of course, is that all functions are working in concert toward clearly stated goals. R&amp;D should swiftly and explicitly map out how its own role vis-à-vis carbon reduction differs from that of colleagues in other parts of the business. R&amp;D leaders&#39; capacity to present scientific arguments to other executives can be a valuable assist to colleagues who must shape a similar plan.</p><p> Mapping out a companywide collaboration can be a process of self-discovery — one that reveals interdependencies and potential alliances. As R&amp;D digs into its targets, its leaders should also consider how entities outside their own company — suppliers, customers, regulators, nonprofit advisers, and even competitors — can be recruited for what is, after all, as universal a mission as they&#39;re likely to encounter in their lifetimes. Companies may well have other worthy sustainability initiatives in the works, and leaders must be conversant with all of them and understand the interplay between them.</p><p> But it&#39;s also critical that companies give their R&amp;D leaders and CTOs a clear mandate to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. Once they have it, they will be well placed to instigate changes to ensure that future products and services have lower associated GHG emissions. The R&amp;D and innovation teams will be on the front lines, reducing GHGs by using alternative raw materials, reimagined product designs, and more climate-friendly technologies. To succeed, net zero must be embedded into each project from its earliest days so that a product&#39;s likely GHG footprint is evaluated early and often. Every R&amp;D conversation should now take GHG into account. And lest anyone think this is a half-hearted exercise in virtue signaling, the team should be judged on how well it executes.</p><p></p><h3> Manage the R&amp;D Portfolio to Deliver Net Zero</h3><p> R&amp;D leaders should now evaluate the “carbon health” of their existing project portfolio to see how well it aligns with their targets. Reaching the goal means knowing exactly where and by when the reductions will happen, and not trusting it to luck or to future technologies that are only barely visible on the horizon.</p><p> To date, sustainability has often been the focus of special projects. Such an approach might help secure investment, demonstrate ambition, create momentum, and burnish a company&#39;s image — and those are undeniably heady inducements. Still, we would argue that integrating carbon reduction into the day-to-day fabric of R&amp;D is more vital. Net-zero success depends on the performance of the portfolio as a whole, not the rise or fall of individual projects. There&#39;s nothing wrong with a few big, speculative longer-term opportunities, but placing smart bets across the entire R&amp;D portfolio is a savvier strategy. Not every project is likely to advance the cause of net zero. And, frankly, R&amp;D can let a particular project underperform in terms of reducing GHG emissions — if commercial needs are simply too urgent, for instance, or if another department can offset the deficit by some other means — as long as the wider portfolio stays on track.</p><p></p><p> Choosing which initiatives to prioritize means identifying the most promising battlegrounds. There will be wins that R&amp;D can instigate and move forward. A product might be a prime candidate for R&amp;D to focus on immediately because rethinking its design or manufacture even minimally could have a significant impact on emissions, or because those changes could be made in the R&amp;D kitchen without creating a ripple effect along the whole supply chain. But many of the big wins will require R&amp;D to work with other partners inside and outside the organization, and although they may be harder and take longer to achieve, the outcome may merit the commitment and investment.</p><p> R&amp;D leaders should expect to provide forecasts of their portfolio&#39;s impact on GHG emissions. Measuring the net contribution (even using a simplistic order-of-magnitude estimate of future impact) will allow the company to balance commercial needs and climate-change intent. Environmental, social, and governance reporting will become more prevalent over time as customers and stakeholders insist on knowing which companies have robust sustainability strategies, and the companies themselves realize that those strategies can reduce costs, spur growth, and minimize issues with regulators. Data on GHG emissions is not yet as accurate as the moment demands, but it will inevitably improve. In the meantime, R&amp;D teams will need to get comfortable with using the available data and accepting approximations.</p><h3> The Commercial Reality</h3><p> It&#39;s often said that corporations have a choice: They can get “green” or they can make money. No one is pretending that there&#39;s no truth in this. But as consumers change, the regulatory environment evolves, stories about reputational damage proliferate, and considerations of carbon impacts become more ubiquitous, a different set of commercial realities will prevail. For now, R&amp;D can build momentum by identifying the customers, products, and brands with a preexisting affinity for net-zero messaging. This is low-hanging fruit. It&#39;s here that carbon-friendly products can command a “green premium” or provide a competitive advantage. In arenas where regulation or standards favor — or even require — carbon-reduced products, the marketplace will likely accept a performance compromise or accept a price premium. Wherever the door is already open, innovators can capitalize on the market value of a climate-friendly product. Elsewhere, they will need to get creative and continually hunt for synergies and flywheels, where innovating for net zero brings other advantages.</p><p> Ideally, innovating to serve the needs of the market — that is, delivering on conventional value parameters — will create collateral opportunities to reduce carbon outputs. No one&#39;s going to object to lowering emissions if it seems to be a happy coincidence. There are manufacturing processes, that, in reducing carbon emissions, may also reduce either upfront capital costs or ongoing energy costs. Projects that can make use of them should be prioritized, and R&amp;D leaders should articulate the benefits of carbon reduction, even if the top priority is cutting expenses.</p><p></p><p></p><p> This next proposal may seem counterintuitive in the extreme, but R&amp;D leaders should also consider trading off on price and/or performance if a reduced-carbon product would enable a different kind of win. The words “new” and “improved” have been fused together in the advertising lexicon for more than a century, so companies won&#39;t be thrilled to announce that they&#39;ve made a less-effective product because they wanted to cut GHG emissions at the plant. But regulation, as well as customer and stakeholder intent, have begun to will it.</p><p> “Accomplishing net-zero goals takes courage,” said Robert Reiter, head of R&amp;D in the Crop Science division of Bayer. “There are going to be tensions, and at some point there will need to be trade-offs when the low-hanging-fruit opportunities are gone. I guess one can wait for regulation to level the competitive playing field, but sometimes a company just needs to lead the way.”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why Text-to-Image AI Requires a New Branding Mindset</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrés Gvirtz and Oguz A. Acar. <p>Andrés Gvirtz is an assistant professor of marketing technology and innovation at King&#39;s Business School and a research affiliate at the King&#39;s Institute for Artificial Intelligence, both at King&#39;s College London. He has worked on AI and machine learning projects with Nokia, Bell Labs, and McKinsey. Oguz A. Acar is a professor of marketing and innovation at King&#39;s Business School and a research affiliate at Harvard University&#39;s Laboratory for Innovation Science. His research focuses on collective innovation, particularly on digital platforms, and the psychology of AI.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images In the world of marketing, brand identity is the castle that guards a company’s reputation, with a moat that keeps the competition at bay. One doesn’t need to look any further than T-Mobile’s signature magenta hue (226 red, 0 green, 116 blue) to realize how fiercely this castle is [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Gvirtz-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>In the world of marketing, brand identity is the castle that guards a company&#39;s reputation, with a moat that keeps the competition at bay. One doesn&#39;t need to look any further than T-Mobile&#39;s signature magenta hue (226 red, 0 green, 116 blue) to realize how fiercely this castle is protected. Use a similar shade, and you might find a cease-and-desist letter in your mailbox. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> But what if the very ramparts that have protected brands could hinder their future in the age of generative AI?</p><p> In one notable advertising campaign, Heinz turned to OpenAI&#39;s DALL-E generator to create ketchup-inspired images. The images weren&#39;t perfect in terms of the dimensions or colors, but they were undeniably Heinz. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> This shows that even AI models recognize that the Heinz brand has top-of-mind awareness. An old-school brand purist might have raised an eyebrow at the way the brand was represented, but the campaign <a href=" https://www.oneclub.org/awards/theoneshow/-award/49451/ketchup-ai">created undeniable buzz</a> , with 850 million earned impressions around the world.</p><p></p><p> We&#39;ve experienced the transformative potential of generative AI on branding in our own classrooms. Generative AI breathed life into King&#39;s College London&#39;s mascot, a fiery-red <a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/ioppn-welcomes-new-students-and-kings-mascot-reggie-the-lion">lion named Reggie</a> , as part of the school&#39;s centennial celebration. Thanks to AI tools, the mascot became more than just a static brand symbol: In classroom sessions, Reggie became animated and “alive,” leading some discussions and even sorting through clothes and adjusting prices as we discussed merchandise management. The result: Bland stock images gave way to a beloved mascot that resonated with our students and elicited overwhelmingly positive reactions. But this is just the beginning of these tools&#39; potential for brands.</p><h3> Creativity Versus Control: Choose Wisely</h3><p> Brands ready to shake off the old, protective mindset will find that generative AI opens new doors to cocreation. Text-to-image AI models, such as OpenAI&#39;s DALL-E, eliminate the barriers for everyday consumers to generate visual designs, allowing unprecedented levels of personal connection and customization.</p><p> In Coca-Cola&#39;s groundbreaking initiative “Create Real Magic,” consumers were invited to unleash their creativity by designing advertisements using ChatGPT and DALL-E. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The winning entries won&#39;t merely be lauded; they will soon light up the billboards of some of the world&#39;s most iconic advertising stages, including New York&#39;s Times Square and London&#39;s Piccadilly Circus.</p><p> Our research, as well as that of others, shows that these enriched connections don&#39;t just affect the people directly involved; they ripple outward, strengthening relationships and enhancing purchase intentions across the broader market. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p></p><p> Despite these exciting prospects, many brands are reluctant to leave the sidelines, likely held back by fears of losing control. The age-old approach of strictly safeguarding brand identity and symbols could make them lagging adopters of text-to-image models.</p><p> Today&#39;s reality is that absolute control over AI technology remains a pipe dream. While generative AI will get better at rendering consistent styles, it is unable to adhere to the rigid guidelines demanded by many brands today. As seen in Heinz&#39;s campaign, while the technology replicated the familiar bottle shape and color, it fell short of reproducing the exact logo or brand name. Brands banking on a “ready” version of this technology might be in for a long wait. Perhaps more importantly, a myopic focus on control could prevent brands from fully unlocking the doors to consumer engagement that generative AI offers.</p><p></p><h3> Brand Managers Need to Be Enablers</h3><p> The path forward requires a mindset shift: Brand managers must evolve from enforcers and guardians to enablers. It is about focusing on broader innovation and connection opportunities instead of obsessing over minutiae like exact color values.</p><p> <a href="https://www.akqa.com/work/gofundme/help-changes-everything/">GoFundMe&#39;s “Help Changes Everything” campaign</a> made new consumer connections by using text-to-image models to engage with donors in the most personalized way possible. Rather than producing typical year-end content, GoFundMe used tools like DALL-E and Stable Diffusion to produce a series of AI-generated street mural-style images showcasing all of the fundraising campaigns and donors of the past year. These individual pieces were then compiled into a captivating video that resonated strongly with audiences and received widespread acclaim. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> Brand managers who are open to such opportunities can leverage text-to-image models to transcend traditional communication boundaries and achieve previously unattainable levels of personalization and authenticity.</p><p> Of course, risk appetites differ. What works for a daring brand like Monster Energy might not for a conservative institution. But even in highly regulated and conservative settings, it is possible to experiment in a way that constrains risks and costs. The risks and potential negative consequences of one-off campaigns or small-scale projects are limited and thus are ideal opportunities for brand exploration. Our endeavor to animate our university&#39;s mascot serves as a case in point.</p><h3> Experiment Safely: Lessons From Coca-Cola</h3><p> This isn&#39;t a call for anarchy. Brands can explore the possibilities of generative AI while keeping within their comfort zones and established boundaries. Coca-Cola&#39;s protective measures include using its own platform, maintaining oversight over <a href="https://www.createrealmagic.com/">content displayed on its site</a> , and providing participants with Coca-Cola-themed templates, all to retain a degree of control over brand portrayal.</p><p> Coca-Cola&#39;s initiative was done in partnership with a text-to-image service alliance of Bain and OpenAI, which helped it switch from a reactive stance to a proactive one. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> Providers that offer brands such as Coca-Cola security and safeguards will likely emerge as preferred partners.</p><p></p><p> Of course, brand managers must guard against potential misuses and walk a tightrope between creative freedom and control. But let&#39;s not forget: Brand perceptions have always been coauthored with consumers and have depended on an intricate two-way relationship between brands&#39; actions and consumers&#39; reactions. Indeed, consumers have long been instrumental in molding brand perceptions, whether it&#39;s through word-of-mouth endorsements or scathing reviews. Generative AI only intensifies this dynamic, empowering the consumer to wear various hats: They can play the role of designer, cinematographer, or even software developer. In the age of generative AI, active listening, consistent monitoring of consumer sentiments, and an agile approach to recalibrate strategies based on real-time feedback and emerging trends become even more important.</p><p> While brands cannot control every narrative twist, they can guide the dialogue more proactively. One effective approach is to cultivate environments where consumers can connect with one another and the brand and contribute to the brand story within a framework of transparent rules, incentives, and recognition. Coca-Cola&#39;s generative AI campaign, for example, clearly communicates the value it places on consumer input — by rewarding top contributions with highly visible advertising placements, as well as a chance to be selected for a trip to the Coca-Cola headquarters to participate in a content-creation workshop. The brand has invested in a specialized digital platform tailored to promote innovation and deepen consumer relationships while at the same time mitigating risks and maintaining alignment with its core values and identity.</p><h3> Addressing Ethical and Legal Concerns</h3><p> Brand managers also need to be vigilant about ethical and legal issues surrounding text-to-image models. As lawsuits entangle key AI tool companies, staying abreast of these developments around ownership and intellectual property (IP) rights becomes essential. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Brands are legitimately concerned about legal implications, but where challenges arise, innovation follows.</p><p> Adobe offers one innovative example of how to ease customer concerns regarding IP issues. For its Firefly generative AI tool, which lets people create or enhance images using simple prompts, Adobe trained the AI models on stock images, openly licensed content, and public-domain materials free from copyright constraints. That&#39;s a forward-thinking approach aimed at addressing customers&#39; concerns.</p><p></p><p> Another promising approach is collaborative IP creation agreements that focus on mutually beneficial relationships between AI developers, creators, and brands. A case in point is Shutterstock&#39;s Contributor Fund, which compensates creators when their images are employed in training generative AI models. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> Brand managers should opt for partnerships with platforms that have effectively mitigated IP risks. Brand managers could also consider adding specific protections in their contracts, where the platforms confirm that they have properly licensed training data and provide guarantees for any potential IP infringement cases against the brand. For generative AI developers, this serves as a compelling incentive to develop models that respect the copyrights of creators and positions them as desirable collaborators for brands.</p><p> All in all, text-to-image generative AI models are tearing down the walls of the traditional branding castle, creating a new reality ripe with opportunities, risks, and challenges. As we navigate this transformation, every brand manager must confront a vital question: Will your brand be a builder of bridges or barricades in this new era?</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> There Actually Is an &#39;I&#39; in Team</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elad N. Sherf, Subra Tangirala, and Alex Ning Li. <p>Elad N. Sherf is an associate professor of organizational behavior and the Sarah Graham Kenan Scholar at the Kenan-Flagler Business School at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill. Subra Tangirala is the Dean&#39;s Professor of Management at the University of Maryland&#39;s Robert H. Smith School of Business. Alex Ning Li is an assistant professor at the Naveen Jindal School of Management, University of Texas at Dallas.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Teamwork]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Imagine running a factory that assembles electronic devices. Your operators work in highly interdependent teams on the assembly lines, and they’re dealing with a fundamental technological change that you recently implemented. Robotic arms and automated machines were put in place to streamline the assembly process, replacing several tasks previously performed by hand. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Sherf_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Imagine running a factory that assembles electronic devices. Your operators work in highly interdependent teams on the assembly lines, and they&#39;re dealing with a fundamental technological change that you recently implemented. Robotic arms and automated machines were put in place to streamline the assembly process, replacing several tasks previously performed by hand.</p><p> Now, the robotic arms handle repetitive and precision movements, such as screwing components together and applying adhesives. This change relieves your operators of mundane work and lets them focus on more complex aspects of the assembly process, such as quality control, troubleshooting, and process optimization. However, they must adjust to the new work environment: They need to individually learn how to operate and maintain the automated systems while also learning how to coordinate differently as a group.</p><p></p><p> This kind of fundamental change to how members of a team relate to their individual roles and to one another plays out in all kinds of workplaces. Whether it&#39;s triggered by organizational decisions to adopt new technology, new regulations, or structural transformations, it requires adaptation on both an individual and team level.</p><p> Members of an accounting team grappling with changes in disclosure laws, for example, may need to individually master new reporting rules as well as rethink collaboration within the team to establish new internal control systems. Employees of an organization transitioning from a functional structure to a divisional structure may need to individually acquire knowledge about the products and services offered by each division in addition to learning how to effectively coordinate with colleagues in the new cross-functional environment.</p><p> Overcoming these dual learning and adaptation challenges is key to successful change management, but as we note in <a href="https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2022.1621">our recent paper in <cite>Organization Science</cite></a> , leaders often don&#39;t pay adequate attention to whether, when, or how individuals on their team reskill — and when they do, their focus is often on the team as a whole. Our research shows that there may be benefits to making individual reskilling a priority. Our study of how teams and individuals adapted to change in a manufacturing company revealed that when individual learning happens first, teams adapt more easily to fundamental change.</p><p></p><h3> Reskill the Individual Before the Team</h3><p> Successful teaming requires skills at two different levels: Team members need to become proficient in their own tasks, and they need to work well together. Until team members master their individual skills, we argue, it is difficult for a team to master and maximize collective coordination. This is because collective mastery can often be built only on individual skills. To best deal with fundamental change, individual skill development should occur first.</p><p> These ideas are supported by our study of fundamental change as it unfolded in a division of a large electronics manufacturing company in eastern China that employs more than 10,000 workers. We followed 116 production teams over several months. These teams had just begun adapting to a series of radical technological advances that required the use of novel tools and production processes. To gauge team performance before and after the change, we used the company&#39;s own metric, yield, which is the percentage of products that are manufactured correctly to technical specifications.</p><p></p><p> As we expected, the need to adjust to the change did negatively affect yield. About two weeks before the change, the average yield was 99.15%; about four weeks after the change, the average yield had dropped to 93.82%. But the drop was not distributed equally across all teams. We attributed some differences among teams to variations in the intensity of the change the team faced: Some teams had much more to relearn at both the individual and collective levels.</p><p> However, after accounting for the intensity of the change, we found that the teams that had initially focused on individual reskilling performed 12% better than the teams that, right off the bat, had focused on improving collective coordination. Reward systems played a critical role: Team members who were given more individual-focused rewards (compared with team-focused rewards) at this initial phase excelled early on in recovering from the change.</p><p> When we explored yield again two months later, in a later phase of the change, the average yield across all teams had climbed back to 96.95%. Yet, there was a high variance in team performance compared with pre-change team performance.</p><p> At this point, teams that had built on individual reskilling and were now focused on collective coordination were performing 11% better than teams that had not made that switch. That change in focus was enabled by a more collectively oriented reward system. Teams that emphasized team rewards at this later phase of change more easily shifted their focus from individual reskilling to collective coordination.</p><h3> Manage Change in Two Phases</h3><p> Our research demonstrates how managing fundamental organizational changes requires a two-phased, sequential response.</p><p> In the early periods following a fundamental change, leaders should encourage individual task reskilling. Such reskilling means not only providing relevant training but also giving members time to experiment and master their tasks alone, before making any attempts to improve the team as a whole. In the context of our study, teams that succeeded early on gave members more time to experiment with new ways to complete their own tasks and adapt the standardized equipment to their own needs.</p><p> The reward system should support such individual reskilling in this phase. When rewards reflect individual contributions, team members focus on improving individual skills. Such rewards promote self-focus and the pursuit of personal goals.</p><p></p><p> In the later periods following a fundamental change, once team members have mastered their individual tasks, they can begin experimenting with coordination and task flow and identifying redundancies in their collective processes. For our study, once members had mastered their new tasks individually, it became clear that some of them could complete their tasks faster than before. This outcome implied that the teams had to change how tasks were assigned to maximize workflow efficiency. This is the phase in which a greater emphasis should be placed on team rewards. When rewards are team-focused and the pay differences between members are minimized, team members focus on learning collective skills. These rewards promote a focus on others, collaboration, and the pursuit of team goals.</p><p> The sequencing of rewards is critical to ensuring that team members focus on the right priority in the right order, by moving from an initial focus on individual reskilling to only later practicing collective coordination. Providing only team-oriented rewards right from the beginning fails to incentivize the individual reskilling that forms the basis of team action.</p><h3> Timing Matters</h3><p> While our research provides some empirical evidence to support the idea of building individual skills before team skills to improve adaptation to change in a business environment, we can observe how this principle applies equally in other domains.</p><p> In the early 1990s, a new rule was introduced in soccer that disallowed goalkeepers from using their hands to pick up balls that the defenders had kicked back to them. This represented <a href="https://99percentinvisible.org/episode/unsure-footing/">a fundamental change</a> in the way the sport was played, because it required new skills and new types of coordination.</p><p> At first, teams struggled to perform under the new rule. Defenders, by habit, would kick the ball back to the goalkeeper. Because the goalkeepers could not touch the ball with their hands and were less skilled at footwork, teams made mistakes.</p><p> Many soccer coaches initially focused on the handoffs between the goalkeepers and defenders, to improve how this set of players coordinated with each other. Such approaches were not very successful. They put the horse before the cart by asking players to focus on collaboration before both goalkeepers and defenders had developed their new individual skills.</p><p></p><p> In contrast, other coaches focused on helping the goalkeepers and defenders first become proficient on their own dribbling and passing skills without making them work with each other. Only later, once the players had individually acquired those skills, did these teams get them together to coordinate their defense and offense in new and creative ways. This strategy was much more successful and led to a reimagining of how the game as a whole was played.</p><p></p><p> Collective capabilities can grow only on a foundation of strong individual skills. Leaders often forget that and, in times of change, try to rally the team to work better together before members have mastered their individual tasks. Leaders managing change should remember to provide enough space and incentives for individuals to experiment and learn new technologies and knowledge on their own before coming to the team to chart out how best to collectively collaborate.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Entrepreneurial AI in the Enterprise: LG Nova&#39;s Shilpa Prasad</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America.您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[A former startup employee herself, Shilpa Prasad knows the level of commitment and effort required to begin a new venture. That’s what led her to join LG Nova, electronics manufacturer LG’s innovation incubator, as an entrepreneur in residence. In her role, Shilpa identifies promising startups — particularly those working with AI — and coaches and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> A former startup employee herself, Shilpa Prasad knows the level of commitment and effort required to begin a new venture. That&#39;s what led her to join LG Nova, electronics manufacturer LG&#39;s innovation incubator, as an entrepreneur in residence. In her role, Shilpa identifies promising startups — particularly those working with AI — and coaches and nurtures entrepreneurs while keeping a close eye on the products that might one day find their way into LG&#39;s ecosystem.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Shilpa explains how keeping a finger on the pulse of startups helps LG Electronics stay open to innovation and new business opportunities. She also discusses why artificial intelligence is at the forefront of her work with startups, and the promising future she sees for using augmented reality and AI technologies to change how skills training is delivered. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MMAI-S8-E2-Shilpa-Prasad-LG-Nova-headshot-3000-1x-scaled.jpg" alt="希尔帕·普拉萨德"></p><h4> Shilpa Prasad, LG Nova</h4><p> Shilpa Prasad is an experienced leader in the startup ecosystem with a strong passion for entrepreneurship and corporate startup engagement/innovation. She brings over 15 years of global experience in corporate startup strategy and venture-building to her role as entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova, where she is helping the company identify market trends and build partnerships.</p><p> Prasad has been instrumental in driving innovation for various open innovation projects across corporations, governments, and accelerators and in establishing new partnerships across the global startup ecosystem. An experienced founder, she has also contributed her time to mentoring and advising startups.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> How can an entrepreneur in residence kick-start new, AI-based businesses in a large incumbent organization? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m Shilpa Prasad from LG Nova, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> Hello everyone. Today Sam and I are excited to be joined by Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova. Hi, Shilpa. Welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Thank you, Shervin. Excited to be here.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Tell us about LG Nova and your role there.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I get asked this a lot. LG Nova is the innovation center of LG Electronics, based here in Silicon Valley. Our mandate is very simple: We&#39;re tasked with finding new business opportunities for LG Electronics that are not core to their bread-and-butter business. LG Electronics is a consumer electronics manufacturer traditionally, looking to make forays into solution-driven businesses. And so [it&#39;s] constantly identifying new technologies and areas that can be interesting for them to build upon and hopefully launch billion-dollar businesses out of it.</p><p> That&#39;s what LG Nova is. My role at LG Nova is entrepreneur in residence, and what that entails is I have many different hats that I wear, one of them being a plain consultant for the corporation. And by consultant, I don&#39;t mean traditional consulting but more in the context of, what are some of the trends to look out for, what new technology areas could be interesting, [and] how can we combine a multitude of technologies, maybe, for a business opportunity? That&#39;s one part of it.</p><p> The second part of it is very much focused on outside-in innovation. Our roots are set on the fact that we don&#39;t want to do what somebody else has already done, and startups are a great example of how quickly they innovate. And we want to bring that innovation into the enterprise that we are and leverage some of that capability to chart out a path together.</p><p> So collaboration with startups is key, and that&#39;s where the entrepreneur side of me kicks in — where you&#39;ve got to be able to understand the mindset of the entrepreneur, the speed at which they function, what drives them, what makes them do the stuff that they do — and convey that to the corporation in an effective way. And then, of course, there&#39;s the reverse role, where the entrepreneurs don&#39;t necessarily — outside of the corporation — understand the workings of the big corporation, and how you bridge that gap, I think, is very crucial to the role. It sounds very simple, but there are a lot of balls in the air in that sense, and you&#39;ve got to be able to juggle all of that at the same time while keeping your eyes on the goal of building new business.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;re talking about a large, global, multibillion-dollar company that&#39;s operating at a given speed, and you also want this group to operate at a much faster, I would assume, entrepreneurial speed. So I could imagine why it&#39;s juggling a lot of balls.</p><p> I wanted to ask you, is it identification of these technologies or innovation opportunities/disruptors, or is it an addition — incubation and building — of these as well?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. So there is the ideation piece, but there is also the venture-building piece, and part of venture-building is incubation. So you have maybe six months to identify an opportunity, build toward something, and then demonstrate that capability both on the product side [and] on the business side to senior stakeholders and investors wherever necessary, and then drive that to new business. So that definitely is a big part of what I do there.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Maybe it&#39;s just what Shervin and I hear a lot of, but there&#39;s a lot of artificial intelligence with startups, and you haven&#39;t mentioned artificial intelligence yet. So how does artificial intelligence intersect with your role?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> AI is not intersecting. It&#39;s at the forefront of what I&#39;m doing. If you remember like a year, year-and-a-half ago, Sam, there was a big hype around the metaverse, and technologies come and go. My focus is to identify real-world problems that can be solved using and leveraging some of these technologies. So AI is definitely at the forefront. There&#39;s a lot of AI-related work that goes on inside of the enterprise which focuses on servicing the existing business units, and that&#39;s not what I&#39;m put in place to do. My role is to look at AI as a technology and identify areas that could be interesting to solve as a problem in this ginormous world and build a business around it.</p><p> I can&#39;t speak too much of exactly what I&#39;m building, but I can talk to the fact that there is an intersection of augmented reality and artificial intelligence that I personally am charting internally here, which will possibly change the way skilled-training transference, upskilling, reskilling, and content around that is going to play out.</p><p> I&#39;m sure you already know this — that with AI in the mix now, so much of this can be so intuitive, with a feedback loop that can be generated for both the trainee and the reviewer and essentially allow workforce development or skill training in particular to move forward at a much faster pace.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It seems like AI is going to be more of a key ingredient of the mix, not just an additive, and so keeping humans in the mix is going to be even more key. I hear thematically in what you&#39;re talking about a focus on that. So tell us a bit about AI that&#39;s happening. You said you can&#39;t speak much, but I still want to tease some information out of you. So talk about AI that&#39;s happening within this innovation center, or contrast it with AI that&#39;s happening at the enterprise.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m sure both of you are very familiar with a large enterprise and the channels one has to navigate in order to get anything to market. And what I mean by “get anything to market,” it&#39;s also about releasing something which impacts a lot more inside the enterprise, right? So when you look at the traditional sort of research that happens around AI within the enterprise, and particularly LG Electronics, my understanding thus far has been that the appetite for risk-taking is limited because it disrupts a lot of their existing work, [whereas] something like this that I&#39;m charting out is leveraging some existing technologies that are out there, and when we launch something like this into the market, none of the existing pieces are impacted — in fact, they&#39;re benefited.</p><p> So LG, for example, has 85,000-plus workers across the globe working in factory environments. Everybody understands today that there is a gap in the labor that&#39;s available in the factories from a front-line worker perspective. There are productivity-related asks constantly within the enterprise to make sure that the entire … capacity is being met. These are all real problems that the AI research within the enterprise is not addressing.</p><p> You asked about the time to market. My mandate is six months to figure out whether a business can go to market or not. I think on the enterprise side, it&#39;s a few years, if not more, right? Anywhere between two to five years.</p><p> It has always been a topic of conversation, saying, “Corporate is slow; the startup is fast.” So I&#39;m essentially building a startup inside corporate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So, what I&#39;m hearing is sort of unshackled from a lot of the sort of legacy scale — with which comes inertia — and much faster sort of as new ventures that are going out. And, of course, some of that innovation then helps some of the existing enterprise AI that&#39;s going on, right?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah.绝对地。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful. You talked about upskilling, reskilling, and possibly reimagining the role of humans in this whole mix with AI — in the mix you talked about. Tell us about generative AI and where you see that play out in this.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think the possibilities are humongous, just like with any other opportunity in AI. One of the aspects of, for example, intersecting augmented reality technology with AI means that we&#39;re not only focusing on voice and text with respect to AI but also computer vision-related data streams that are being captured and processed in order for skill transference to happen as effectively as possible.</p><p> So think about a nurse training environment. We&#39;re not practicing on real patients but on the dummy. If you have to teach trainee nurses how to position the patient on the bed in order to do a specific procedure, then there is a multitude of value in capturing the data stream from the head trainer nurse in order to see how to do that and, when you&#39;re actually practicing it, to get real-time feedback, right?</p><p> So we&#39;re looking at multiple data streams here. So not just NLP [natural language processing], but we would be looking at computer vision-based technologies and bringing in AI to almost superpower that process and that trainee and training experience on both sides, right? So that&#39;s an example of how we&#39;re doing it differently.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Normally, I&#39;m pretty excited about the applications of artificial intelligence we talk about, but I get a little threatened here [for] a second. I mean I&#39;m an educator here, and I hear you talking about all sorts of different ways of reskilling and retraining. Where do I go? You mentioned a model before with nurses, where the experienced nurse would teach the less-experienced nurse. Maybe a lot of that gets replaced. What&#39;s the role for that experienced nurse now in this new model?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. Well, actually, Sam, I think your fear is maybe misplaced here, and let me explain this. We&#39;re not trying to replace the trainer. What we&#39;re doing is actually empowering the trainer with more opportunity to do the stuff that they should be doing. So in the training-of-the-nurses example, a head nurse has to actually physically stand next to the trainee nurses, possibly multiple times during the day, and teach them how they&#39;re doing their specific tasks. Now imagine a scenario where we&#39;ve eliminated at least two levels of feedback, review, and assessment before the head trainer can actually come into the mix and take a look at what&#39;s going on.</p><p> So the certification, I think, is still very, very important, right? Whether it be manufacturing, whether it be health care — the two examples that we&#39;re talking about — the certification is still important, and that certification comes from the trainer, who is the expert. So we&#39;re not removing the expert. It&#39;s actually empowering the expert to also be able to train effectively and not have to monitor 100 screens of trainee nurses that are doing their job. So you see the difference, hopefully.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. Sam&#39;s a tenured professor, so I don&#39;t think he&#39;s going anywhere. But, Sam, it&#39;s a little bit like the full professor, ie, yourself, sort of not being bogged down with the things that a graduate student can take care of, and you only do the tough ones and the ones that really tease your brain.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That sounds glorious to me.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think it&#39;s an assistant, right? You&#39;d have an AI assistant that could actually do a lot of the grunt work that otherwise you have to sit and do. So I think there is value in it. At least we&#39;re seeing some inferences of value that we&#39;re able to generate in the very early conversations we&#39;re having.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful. Shilpa, tell us a little bit about your background, how you ended up in this role.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> My career is a zigzag line, Shervin; it&#39;s not a straight line to what I&#39;m doing today. Over the years, I think there&#39;s always been a lot of value and joy that I have found in creating something [from the] ground up. The energy, the momentum, and the rigor it requires to scoop something up from nothing and create something out of it has been at the core of everything I&#39;ve done.</p><p> So very early on in my career, I had the opportunity to partner with someone to start [up] a graphic design studio. And there, I learned the mechanics of what it takes to actually create a business. It taught me a lot of the pieces that went into it.</p><p> From there, I&#39;ve always landed myself in roles that were actually entrepreneurial in nature or servicing the entrepreneurial ecosystem. I&#39;d like to mention a company called YouNoodle Inc. that I worked with here when I first came to Silicon Valley. There, I learned the power of selecting the right startups or innovations to work with in order to move innovation forward, whether in the context of corporations, governments, universities even, and large-scale accelerator programs.</p><p> That led me to my own entrepreneurial journey again, during COVID. It was really difficult. I launched a startup called LongPlay and built a team of about 10 people. It was focused around changing the way corporate innovation happens. And one of the things I think there is, when you&#39;re outside of the corporate, there is just no way to understand all of the different moving parts that go on. So we couldn&#39;t prove product-market fit there, which is where Nova came into the mix. I got the opportunity again to try to do a product-market fit in an industry and an environment that was a little different from what I was used to, but I think the nuts and bolts are the same. So that&#39;s just a quick background on me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s super exciting — very multidisciplinary. And it brings me to my next question: There is no one-size-fits-all when it comes to AI, and it&#39;s of course a full ecosystem of engineers and software engineers and prompt engineers and AI engineers and data scientists, etc. But I&#39;ve been noticing a gradual evolution of the skills over the past, I would say, 10, 12, 15 years or so, from hard-core technical-only to also more multidisciplinary, and that “multidisciplinary” could be in a variety of areas. It could be in social sciences or it could be in human-AI interaction, or it could be in philosophy or whatever. But are you seeing the same thing, and what is your perspective on talent of the future in this space of AI?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> It&#39;s an interesting question. I have to say I&#39;m not seeing the same thing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m not seeing the width as much as I&#39;m seeing the depth. There is still, I think, a tremendous gap in the workforce with respect to being able to be multidisciplinary. There&#39;s a lot of, to your point, deep tech work that happens, especially around AI.</p><p> I think that&#39;s [something that] over the next few years, a lot of the folks like myself that are responsible for how this technology unfolds are going to have to carry with them.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That comes to measurement too. I mean — Shervin, I know that&#39;s a <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">hot topic for you right now</a> — but when you&#39;re talking about impact, you&#39;ve got to figure out how to measure it. There&#39;s going to have to be some measure of “Is this working? Is this not working?” And these seem like some difficult problems, particularly with the newness of the technology, the freshness of the timelines that you&#39;re talking about. It seems very difficult to figure out if this is working or not working in your role.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. I mean, I can give it a little bit of a personal take. My style of building projects has always alluded to testing it as much as possible with the customer who has the problem.</p><p> And that&#39;s where the product focus sort of is very front and center for me, and that&#39;s why venture-building is exciting. When we talk about measurement, there are definitely different ways in which the impact of what we&#39;re creating or what we&#39;re trying to create can be measured. There is a market validation aspect here, right? There is definitely an investor validation aspect, meaning our investors ... It&#39;s not just about my project, right? It&#39;s not just about the project that I&#39;m creating or building. It&#39;s actually more about where the money is going. And, of course, a little bit of it is hype, but a little bit of it is also taking the chance on the next thing that is likely to change the way AI is going to be used in day-to-day environments or contexts.</p><p> I think the third part here is also just about empowering the users, ultimately, of whatever solution we&#39;re creating and whatever we are building, in order for the business opportunity … Ultimately [it] has to add value to the humans — that is, you and I, who are actually going to use that technology to make our lives better. Today, we&#39;re doing the work in the exact same way that we are taught or we&#39;re used to or we have learned how to, and we&#39;re going to have to change that or adapt that and pivot to a new way of doing things.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And is AI enabling you to have better data and information on that? Is AI enabling you to know something that maybe 20 years ago would&#39;ve taken you a lot longer to know?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Absolutely, but I think “Is AI enabling me? Only <em>it</em> will do that,” I think, is perhaps a lot of weight on AI and less relevant to what has been done in the past 10, 15 years in a specific industry. I think AI also has a flip side to it, which is, sometimes it&#39;s putting too much in front of you, where then you have to actually go through the top layers to really figure out where this data can be used and how this data can be applied. So there&#39;s the pro and the con of AI as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned cons. What kinds of cons are you seeing from these startups you&#39;re working with? What are people struggling with here?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think the startups, in particular, are still looking for ways in which whatever they have developed can be applied. The application of AI in effective ways is still to be determined. And so startups are creating all these LLMs [large language models] that can be relevant to the project, but they don&#39;t know <em>how</em> it&#39;s going to actually translate.</p><p> So I&#39;d say there&#39;s still a little bit of a journey there for the startup to be able to understand it. And in the context of the role that I have today, for example, I&#39;m also enabling the startup to understand how they can use the technology that they&#39;ve created and translate it over to a meaningful problem, but … that&#39;s why I said consulting before. It&#39;s consulting for the startup as well: to give them some real-[world] scenarios where you can apply something that we&#39;ve built together and then see how it translates into value. So I think the startups are still learning for sure, Sam.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So those things actually tie back to maybe some of Shervin&#39;s comments about breadth and breadth of knowledge and multidisciplinary, because you didn&#39;t specifically mention that they&#39;re struggling with technology. I heard lots of things there that were not particularly technology-oriented.</p><p> Let&#39;s transition here. One of the things that we do at the end of the episode is we ask you five questions. We&#39;re going to ask them fast. We just want your first reaction from them. What do you see as the biggest opportunity for AI right now?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Health care.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK. What&#39;s the biggest misconception that people have about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> That it&#39;s going to replace them. That it&#39;s going to replace us as humans. That&#39;s not going to happen, I think. We&#39;re a ways away from that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Ways away. Good. What&#39;s the first career that you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> To be an entrepreneur. I think it was always in my DNA.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Good. Did you have a lemonade stand when you were growing up?</p><p> When is there too much artificial intelligence? Where are we trying to make a square peg fit in a round hole?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I don&#39;t think I have a concrete answer for you, Sam, there. So if you&#39;re going to switch the question out …</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ask it this way: Can it be too much?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Can you put too much artificial intelligence into a product?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. I think an area that comes to mind is cobots — collaborative robots. It could work, it may not work, and then it&#39;s very heavily AI-driven. So automation is key there, but how much of that could be relevant, I think, is questionable for me personally.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> If you were fantasizing, what&#39;s one thing you wish artificial intelligence could do right now that it can&#39;t currently do?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Make me sound as good as I possibly can.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Shilpa, thank you so much. This has been illuminating and wonderful. Thanks for being on the show.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening today. On our next episode, we&#39;ll hear how Harvard Business School professor Ayelet Israeli suggests augmenting corporate market research with generative AI. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Can Friction Improve Your Customers&#39; Experiences?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli. <p>Marco Bertini is a professor of marketing at Esade and Ramon Llull University in Barcelona and a senior adviser to Globalpraxis. Diego Aparicio is an assistant professor of marketing at IESE Business School in Barcelona. Aylin Aydinli is an associate professor of marketing at Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Journey]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bertini_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; after all, competitor websites are but a few clicks away.</p><p> Most business leaders we know prioritize eliminating friction at the “moment of truth,” when displaying prices and taking payment, because beyond wanting to make life easier for eager customers, they fear giving customers reason to pause and reconsider their decisions. But as we will demonstrate, it is precisely in giving customers time to consider their purchase decisions when money is on the line that longer-term benefits and cost savings can accrue to the firm.</p><p></p><h3> Friction and the Fickle Online Shopper</h3><p> It&#39;s easy to see why making shopping as seamless as possible is so urgent for e-commerce companies, when the average global cart abandonment rate for the last 12 months stood at a staggering 71.7% overall — 60.7% among people using desktop or laptop computers, 65.1% among those using tablets, and 77.4% for those using mobile phones. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This last figure is perhaps the most troubling, given that mobile shopping in the US grew by more than $200 billion in three years to reach $431 billion in 2022. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> According to the Baymard Institute, the average large e-commerce site could increase conversion by 35% by streamlining and simplifying the checkout process. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Not surprisingly, e-commerce titans such as Amazon and Alibaba are investing heavily in quickly ushering consumers through their moments of truth by making prices and payments nearly invisible. Amazon pioneered one-click shopping back in 1999. Today, the attention is on its Just Walk Out technology, which blends computer vision, weight sensors, and deep learning to bring some of the ease of online shopping to physical stores: Patrons tap a credit card when entering a retail location to open a virtual cart, select items from the shelves, and leave without stopping at the cashier. At Alibaba, digital payments and self-service checkout stations are the norm across its 300 Freshippo supermarkets. People can even leverage its Alipay affiliate&#39;s facial recognition technology to “pay by face.”</p><p> Companies with fewer resources are making changes to their purchase processes that are more incremental but no less significant. Consider, for example, the recent popularity of “buy now, pay later” installment financing or of automatic-renewal clauses for subscription-based services, which allow companies to avoid the annual reckoning of customers reconsidering whether they still want the service. Online businesses have embraced these and other opportunities to make spending money less painful simply by allowing customers not to think about it.</p><p> However, it is simplistic to think of friction as having strictly negative effects, such as annoying customers or depressing sales. While it is true that too much resistance in the purchase journey can easily crowd out the desire to buy, too little resistance dumbs down decision-making and leads to missed opportunities to better connect with customers. The question we suggest that business leaders ask themselves, then, is whether they really want their customers to purchase on autopilot.</p><p> In this article, we explain how a little friction in the buying process can help companies engage customers and offer guidance on how to leverage these effects to build stronger customer relationships.</p><h3> No Pain, No Gain</h3><p> Some friction in the purchase journey can protect consumers from fraud, privacy violations, or their own unintended actions. For example, requiring two-step verification and asking the customer to confirm that they want to complete the purchase are two commonsense inconveniences that ultimately ensure that customers are safeguarded from threats and mistakes.</p><p> But either too much or too little friction around a purchase decision can have negative effects. Having too many steps in the purchase journey can distract shoppers, leaving them without the cognitive bandwidth to carefully consider their decisions. This fuels cart abandonment rates and removes opportunities to engage customers with the company through reviews, referrals, recommendations, or other interactions. Too little friction, and people don&#39;t think enough about their decisions, giving in to the human inclination to economize on mental effort. This absence of friction is numbing, and the less connected shoppers are with a purchase, the more ambivalent they become. That lack of commitment can in turn prompt product returns, weaken brands, and reduce satisfaction in the long run.</p><p> A purchase journey that is sufficiently challenging, however, is engaging. Because the transaction is neither stressful nor straightforward, people have an incentive to invest mental effort in the task. In other words, the right amount of friction can prompt customers to refine and consolidate their preferences and can lead to three benefits for companies.</p><p></p><p> <strong>1. Friction helps sellers select the right customers.</strong> Companies that prioritize the long-term profitability of their customer bases over the immediate gain from making a sale must take a holistic and equally long-term perspective on developing relationships with their target audiences. This involves investing in acquisition, retention, and growth. With that idea in mind, the question is whether hurdles that increase the psychological pain of considering an expense will disproportionately deter would-be customers who are more costly to acquire, less likely to purchase again on future occasions, or less likely to increase their spending on the brand over time or recommend the brand. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Friction to weed out the wrong customers or select the right ones is a familiar technique in luxury goods markets and in any context where a company wants prospective customers to demonstrate commitment. Ferrari, for example, is known for making it difficult to buy special-edition cars. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Similarly, luxury fashion brands don&#39;t mind fostering queues, whether virtual or real, or complicating the purchase process by temporarily withholding prices, lengthening the checkout process, or using other approaches. The simple logic behind these tactics is that only the customers who are most interested in the company&#39;s products or most invested in the brand will find working through these inconveniences and complications acceptable in the shopping journey.</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. When friction enables better decisions, customer satisfaction improves.</strong> Using friction to give consumers a moment to pause and consider the implications of their purchases can forestall buyer&#39;s remorse and encourage shoppers to choose the most appropriate option among the available alternatives.</p><p> Making the trade-off between what the potential buyer will pay and what they will receive sufficiently obvious can help prevent mindless purchasing decisions made in the heat of the moment. For example, social media may pitch “buy now, pay later” financing as a savvy way to buy on a budget, but the ease and convenience of such services, now available in many e-commerce sites&#39; checkout processes, can encourage households to overspend, leading to financial strain and debt accumulation. One survey found that 42% of Americans who took out such a loan made at least one late payment on it. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In addition, research shows that payments made either long before or long after the natural moment of consumption can reduce people&#39;s attention to cost. Proponents of buy now, pay later assert that this “separates the fun experience of buying from the tedious process of paying,” when in fact such “transaction decoupling” has been shown to reduce the likelihood that the consumer will use the item purchased. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> The advantage of avoiding bad decisions is relatively clear from a public policy perspective: Most people would agree that overspending and chronic underutilization of purchased goods are not desirable qualities in a society. But encouraging more thoughtful engagement by customers via friction in the purchase process can pay off for businesses, too.</p><p> One immediate benefit is a drop in return rates. In many sectors, online returns are a considerable drag on financial performance — adding up to as much as 15 to 30 cents per dollar of the price of returned merchandise. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> According to a study by Appriss Retail and the National Retail Federation, close to $220 billion worth of merchandise was returned to US digital retailers in 2021, or approximately 21% of total online sales. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> And this drag, of course, is not just financial — it&#39;s also environmental. Returned products might not be resalable due to wear and tear or other issues and thus end up being sent to landfills or destroyed. According to one report, online returns in the US alone create 5 billion pounds of landfill waste and 15 million tons of carbon emissions annually. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Adding friction also provides customers with time to consider the purchase and become more invested in it. Brands such as Chanel, Louis Vuitton, and Balenciaga delay the communication of prices in a variety of ways — for example, by introducing personalized experiences with salespeople — not only to select better customers, as discussed above, but to put the product center stage and help customers internalize its quality and meaning. Research at the intersection of marketing and neuroscience reports that revealing prices after product information focuses evaluations on attractiveness and desirability (people ask themselves, “Do I like this?”), while doing the opposite focuses evaluations on monetary worth (people ask themselves, “Is it worth it?”). <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> In a Gartner study, B2B and B2C customers agreed that if they “realized something new about their needs or their own goals,” they were 1.73 times more likely to buy more. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p> Using friction to stimulate thinking that results in a decision to purchase can foster a sense of ownership of the product. This can trigger a stronger bond between company and customers and increase customers&#39; willingness to invest additional resources in the relationship. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> As customers put more thought into the purchase decision, they tend to feel more emotionally attached to the product they ultimately choose. And there&#39;s evidence that connecting with customers at the emotional level is a valid route to maximizing customer value. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Finally, research also shows that people tend to value products more when they are obtained through effort — the aptly named “Ikea effect,” in reference to the retailer&#39;s policy of outsourcing the assembly of its furniture to customers. <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> The experience of effort can influence how people perceive the value and quality of a product or service, and adding effort to the online purchase process can trigger this effect.</p><p></p><p> Overall, we see that friction is successful at triggering engagement, and we know that engaged customers are generally more satisfied with their interactions and experiences with brands and retailers. Engaged customers become advocates, increasing visibility and credibility for companies. They are likely to engage in positive word of mouth, which can lead to new-customer acquisition and elevated brand reputation. They are also likely to have better customer service experiences, feel valued by the company, and provide meaningful feedback and suggestions. Such feedback is valuable for understanding evolving customer needs and making the right improvements to products or services over time.</p><p> <strong>3. Friction creates space for companies to communicate with customers.</strong> Retaining some friction exactly when people face prices and payment, especially when this friction is unexpected, gains attention. This is an opportunity for companies to advertise what they stand for and the merits of their offerings.</p><p> There are several ways to use friction for promotion. First, companies can involve customers in the payment process to evoke positive emotions. For example, one common practice is to give customers the option to round up the transaction amount to the next highest dollar, with the difference being donated to charity. Another possibility is to introduce pay-what-you-want campaigns, where customers choose the price they will pay for the product. While these initiatives do not expedite payment (it is surprisingly effortful to consider how much one wants to pay for something), they can lead to greater emotional connections.</p><p> Companies can also express prices in ways that are intentionally unconventional to force customers to think harder about the underlying message. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> For instance, an advertisement from Ikea uses cans of soda to playfully quantify the prices of its products. Of course, the retailer won&#39;t accept soda as payment for furniture. And although it takes a moment of cognitive effort to understand the “exchange rate,” the message that the furniture is as affordable as a number of small-ticket purchases, such as soda, is conveyed to customers.</p><p> Another example is Stella Artois&#39;s award-winning “reassuringly expensive” campaign. The brand attempted to signal the high quality of its beer by introducing the dependency between price and quality into its price communication. Stella upended consumer expectations by playfully offering a coupon that increased the price of the product (“Bring this coupon and pay an extra $1.25 on your next Stella Artois”). By presenting a seemingly confusing and illogical “deal,” it nudged customers to conclude that the product is far superior to that of its competitors (and worth the cost).</p><p> Friction in the payment process can also be used to communicate the brand&#39;s values. For example, in 2014, the relief organization Misereor increased donation rates by deploying interactive screens in locations such as airports that asked passersby to donate 2 euros by swiping their credit cards over the screen. The swipe activated an engaging interactive sequence, such as depicting the credit card slicing a piece of bread to feed the hungry or freeing an imprisoned child.</p><p> Finally, in a bold example of extreme friction, outdoor retailer REI closed its physical stores and stopped processing online payments on Black Friday, the biggest shopping day of the year in the US Its goal was to take a stand against consumerism and encourage would-be shoppers to spend time outdoors instead — a message that underscores the company&#39;s dedication to accessible exploration. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a></p><h3> The Friction Sweet Spot</h3><p> Better customer selection, consumer decisions, and promotion are three good reasons to abandon the simplistic goal of zero friction. Given the drawbacks of encouraging customers to purchase on autopilot, business leaders should seek to determine the right degree of friction for their companies&#39; purchase processes. In our experience, there are at least five factors to consider. We&#39;ll review them and introduce a scorecard that brings them together and helps to guide decision-making. (See “What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?</h4><p class="caption"> Use this scorecard to help you determine the optimal amount of friction to help you<br /> cultivate enduring customer relationships.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> The first step for every company is to adopt a more accurate definition of what friction is. At the moment, all friction is viewed negatively, which reduces organizations&#39; sense of needing to specify what it actually is. By most accounts, friction is operationalized in terms of time saved. But not all time is created equal. In fact, companies should view negative friction as anything that blocks or distracts customers from the purchase decision, and positive friction as anything that optimizes deliberation.</p><p> The second step is to understand what contexts benefit from positive friction — because this need is not universal. What&#39;s at stake in a particular purchase decision, and does it typically require high or low customer involvement? The two often go together, such that high-stakes decisions also require high involvement, but this is not necessarily the case. For instance, a consumer who is financially secure might not engage more with a purchase decision simply because the item is expensive. And it is exactly when this relation breaks down that you want to step in to proactively manage friction. High-stakes decisions might be such because of the significance of the product or service in question, the scale of the financial outlay, or the personal or social consequences of the purchase. In this spirit, using a technology like Amazon&#39;s Just Walk Out in stadiums might not be good for people who are no longer dissuaded from buying unhealthy snacks by excessively long lines at the concession stand.</p><p> Third, think about your commercial objective. If you care about highlighting cost savings relative to competitors&#39; prices, then, yes — reducing friction by posting your almost-too-good-to-be-true price upfront is worthwhile. However, if you compete on the basis of innovation, quality, or customer service, then perhaps retaining a little friction by delaying when the price is presented is best, because this gets customers to think about and crystallize their preferences. Some friction allows businesses to shift the conversation from “Is it worth it?” to “Do I like it?” And if the goal is to strengthen one&#39;s brand, then adding friction is the right way to go.</p><p> Fourth, consider the makeup of your customer base and the relative closeness of customer relationships. Different customer demographics might require more or less friction, depending on expectations around their understanding of a product or service or their ability to pay. Likewise, relationship stage is important. You might want to include more friction in transactions with new customers versus returning customers, in particular those who might be less familiar with your products or product category. You might want to make it harder for a prospective customer to make a purchase, add a bit of friction for a returning customer, and present a frictionless experience to a loyal customer who fully understands the product or service. A company should maximize enduring relationships with clients — because that is the only path to increase customer value.</p><p> Fifth, think about your choice of route to market. All retail environments could potentially benefit from some friction, but their application will be different. In a brick-and-mortar store, adding pain points that incentivize interaction between a salesperson and the customer might be the right type of friction. In an online store, however, adding steps to foster deliberation can reduce returns and increase subsequent satisfaction with the company. On social media, a company could look to balance content that engages customer interaction and not just click-through rates, thereby helping to dissuade users from mindlessly or impulsively shopping.</p><p></p><p> In fact, for a business selling the same product in brick-and-mortar stores and online, more (positive) friction might be needed in the online or mobile channel, given that product returns tend to be greatest in those channels. One interesting technique that some fashion brands have recently introduced is imposing a fee for online returns. Companies like Anthropologie, H&amp;M, and Zara are charging for returning items online (but not for making in-store returns). <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a> Yes, charging for returns can antagonize some customers. But, again, this point can be key to retaining the most relevant customers and strengthening relationships with those who persist and make a purchase.</p><p></p><p> “How can we make our prices a little less conspicuous and easier to pay?” is among the most common questions asked of user experience teams and experts. But business leaders should embrace the customer moment of truth rather than work to eliminate it. They should not buy into the popular idea that friction is the ultimate conversion killer.</p><p> Without a doubt, when used poorly, friction can derail the customer experience. But a frictionless world is just as dangerous. This is a lesson most of us learned years ago from our high school physics teacher: Too much friction prevents progress toward a goal, but too little friction can throw everything into chaos.</p><p> Indeed, many business leaders are already telling us that they want customers to spend more productive time on their purchase decisions. This sounds like the perfect job for friction. If thinking leads shoppers to make safer, better choices, and in turn these choices impact companies through lower product returns, more sustainable consumer behavior, higher customer satisfaction, and higher loyalty, then let&#39;s all accept and embrace some hassles and hurdles as yet another — albeit surprising — tool at the disposal of customer centricity.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>