<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 16 日星期一 21:09:06 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>为什么薪酬透明度法规是一个战略管理机会</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>塔玛拉·蒙塔格-斯密特 (Tamara Montag-Smit) 是马萨诸塞大学 (UMass) 洛厄尔分校管理学助理教授。卡罗琳·埃文斯 (Karoline Evans) 是麻省大学洛厄尔分校管理学副教授。布兰登·斯密特是本特利大学管理学助理教授。卡森德拉·巴茨-巴巴里奇 (Cassondra Batz-Barbarich) 是森林湖学院 (Lake Forest College) 的商学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">安娜丽莎·格拉萨诺</p></figcaption></figure><p>薪酬透明度法被誉为解决性别工资差距的一种补救措施，美国各地州和地方各级越来越多地推出<a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">薪酬透明度法</a>。截至 9 月份，包括纽约在内的九个州目前正在规范薪酬披露的某些方面。国家妇女法律中心报告称，总共有超过四分之一的美国雇员居住在<a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">薪酬信息受到监管的</a>地区。</p><p>总的来说，薪酬透明度法规强调披露广告职位的薪酬范围和内部晋升机会。这些法律旨在确保同工同酬，有效缩小性别工资差距。逻辑很简单：如果工资过低的员工，包括女性和少数族裔，不知道他们的同事的工资是多少，那么他们在通过诉讼和谈判创造公平竞争环境时就会处于明显的劣势。当不平等现象仍然蒙在鼓里时，如何解决不平等问题呢？如果没有薪酬透明度，现有法律（例如<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">1963 年《同工同酬法案》）</a>的执行就会变得困难。根据<a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">最近的案例</a>和已暴露的显着差异（有些跨越多年的少付），更大的透明度似乎可以发挥重要作用。</p><p></p><h3>对不断变化的监管环境的组织反应</h3><p>尽管薪酬透明度法规得到越来越广泛的采用，但许多组织的反应却是抵制、抵制和最低限度的合规性。科罗拉多州于 2021 年成为第一个要求组织披露广告职位薪资范围的州后，在全国范围内招募求职者的组织开始<a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">明确将科罗拉多州居民排除</a>在考虑范围之外，以规避新法律，促使该州劳工部发出 <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">警告和罚款</a>。另一种组织策略是遵守薪资信息要求，薪资范围过大，以至于申请人无法有意义地预测他们可能会得到的薪资。在一个著名的例子中，Netflix 发布了一份薪资范围<a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">为 90,000 美元到 900,000 美元的</a>职位。</p><p>虽然组织层面遵守透明度法律的方法有多种形式，但领导者对薪酬透明度对其业务运营和文化的潜在负面影响表达了一些共同的担忧：</p><ul><li><strong>每个人都会要求更多的钱吗？</strong>更多的薪酬信息可能会引发更多关于薪酬的讨论（以及为什么有人会得到他们的工资）。经理们担心，他们会陷入困境，试图兼顾预算和员工满意度方面的相互竞争的目标。</li><li><strong>如果一些员工发现他们的工资低于其他人，会发生什么？</strong>向老员工解释为什么他们的薪酬与新员工相同可能会让人感到不舒服，并会引发对雇主的严厉批评。</li><li><strong>薪酬透明度会影响我们的合作能力吗？</strong>当个人认为自己得到不公平的回报时，薪酬透明度可能会引起嫉妒和适得其反的竞争。经理们担心，当差异暴露出来时，员工可能会互相争斗并破坏彼此的利益。</li></ul><p></p><h3>管理薪酬透明度的新见解</h3><p>我们的工作为解决组织在透明度方面的一些主要问题提供了新的见解。大多数新法律只专注于通过要求组织披露空缺职位的薪酬范围来创造薪酬透明度。在学术研究中，这种形式的透明度被称为<em>分配透明度</em>，因为它仅披露有关员工工资<em>金额</em>的信息。</p><p>然而，在我们的研究中，我们描述了几种使薪酬信息透明的方法。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a><em>程序透明</em>，重点是共享有关如何制定薪酬<em>决策的</em>信息；在最透明的层面上，这将包括计算薪酬的公式（例如基本工资或基于绩效的加薪）。</p><p>区分分配透明度和程序透明度至关重要，因为正如我们的研究表明，程序透明度可以减轻与分配透明度相关的许多风险和缺点。</p><p>薪酬透明度法规隐含的理念是，工资过低的员工将自行协商<a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">争取更公平的工资</a>。事实上，过去二十年对超过 100,000 名学者进行的一项大规模研究发现，薪酬透明度的变化与男女之间的工资平等程度显着提高有关。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>然而，研究还表明，透明度并不等于<em>每个人都</em>要求更多。</p><p>为了进一步探索这一点，我们进行了一系列四项实验，以更好地了解薪酬透明度<em>如何</em>以及<em>何时</em>可以鼓励员工（尤其是女性）更有效地谈判公平工资。在我们的第一项研究中，实验室参与者在四轮流行的单词搜索游戏后根据他们的表现获得报酬，并有机会谈判以获得更好的报酬。在研究 2、3 和 4 中，在线参与者准备好进行绩效评估，并掌握有关绩效和薪酬的不同程度的信息，以便可能就更好的年度加薪进行谈判。他们被告知预计加薪 3%，但加薪幅度可能在 3% 到 10% 之间。在这些研究中，我们改变了参与者可以获得的信息量，包括其他人的报酬金额以及参与者相对于同龄人的表现。</p><p>这些研究得出了关于分配和程序薪酬透明度的四项重要发现：</p><p> <strong>1.人们进行了更清晰的比较。</strong>我们发现，判断某人是否试图通过谈判争取更高薪酬的最佳预测因素是他们相对于同事的表现。与平均绩效者相比，当高绩效者知道自己相对于其他人的排名时，他们要求更高薪酬的可能性大约高出 50%。值得注意的是，在我们的研究中，参与者看到了其团队成员上一年的绩效和薪酬数据，很明显，绩效的提高与薪酬的提高直接相关。尽管没有一个明确的公式表明基于绩效的薪酬，但这一信息向参与者提供了一个明确的信号：加薪很大程度上取决于绩效。</p><p> <strong>2. 人们公平地进行谈判。</strong>表现一般的员工更有可能接受向他们提供的最低加薪，通常认为根据他们的表现加薪是公平的。正如一位人士所说，“考虑到我这一年只达到了预期，而不是超出预期，要求更高的加薪似乎是徒劳的，也是不劳而获的。”一般来说，表现一般的员工很少要求最高加薪，部分原因是他们考虑到自己的表现低于某些同事。不过，只有当他们掌握了所有信息时，这才是真的。当他们不知道自己的表现时，85％的人要求最高工资金额。由于缺乏绩效信息，表现一般的员工要求薪资范围内的最高加薪。</p><p> <strong>3.女性<em>确实</em>要求更高的工资。</strong>与普遍的假设相反，女性似乎不需要太多鼓励来进行谈判。事实上，当考虑参加谈判的参与者的百分比时，女性往往比男性更有可能进行谈判（尽管这在统计上并不存在显着差异）。这些发现对以下观点提出了一些质疑：性别工资差距的原因之一是女性谈判的频率低于男性。最近的研究结合了数十项谈判研究的信息得出了相同的结论：近年来，男性和女性之间的许多谈判差距已基本消失。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>虽然这是个好消息，但它对于缩小目前的性别工资差距几乎没有作用。</p><p> <strong>4.人们有动力去表现得更好。</strong>表现一般的员工表达了更加努力工作、表现更好的动机，以便在下一个审核周期中获得更高的加薪。当被问及为什么不通过谈判争取更多的钱时，一位参与者表示：“我的数据并没有表明我应该得到更高的加薪。如果第二年的数字更好，就有理由提高加薪。”另一位则表示，“我知道自己的工作表现一般，所以我希望未来能做得更好，并希望明年能得到更好的加薪。”</p><p>我们的研究结果复制并扩展了管理研究中一个古老但强大的概念：<em>公平过程效应</em>。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>如果员工相信不利的结果是由公平的系统产生的，他们就会接受这些结果。换句话说，如果人们知道<em>为什么</em>他们的工资较低（换句话说，程序透明），他们就不会做出消极反应，甚至可能会更加努力地工作。</p><h3>让薪酬透明度为您的组织带来双赢</h3><p>薪酬透明度可以是双赢的机会，而不是合规障碍。但仅仅在招聘启事中列出薪资数据而没有任何符合法规的背景可能是一个很大的错误。这些做法不仅无视法律的精神，而且付出了沉重的代价并丧失了重要的机会。领导者的思考应该超越合规性，并考虑如何战略性地利用组织的薪酬透明度，以提高申请人的吸引力和员工的保留率。我们的研究为如何做到这一点提供了一些见解。</p><p><strong>让薪酬只是透明度等式的<em>一部分</em>。</strong>人们普遍担心透明度会增加劳动力成本、引起嫉妒并引发冲突，但事实是，薪酬保密本身也会带来问题。 Payscale 的研究人员发现，大多数员工<a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">不确定自己的薪酬是否公平</a>，许多人认为自己的薪酬过低，而事实并非如此，这导致更大的人员流动和不满。我们的研究表明，如果没有绩效参考点，员工几乎没有基础来判断薪酬是否公平，因此更有可能提出不合理的要求。绩效<em>和</em>薪酬的透明度可以让员工更好地评估其薪酬的公平性并提出更合理的要求。</p><p></p><p><strong>关注薪酬决策过程。</strong>程序透明度有助于管理人员更清楚地与员工沟通薪酬问题，因为工资/奖金是基于绩效而不是基于看似无形的因素，或者更糟糕的是充满偏见的因素。提供有关如何确定薪酬的信息可以帮助现任员工了解为什么他们的薪酬高于或低于同事，更重要的是，了解如何晋升。当薪酬直接由绩效决定时，管理者就不能被指责有偏袒和偏见，这使得他们在薪酬谈判中处于协作角色。这些对话以绩效为重点，可以关注发展并研究员工如何才能表现得更好并获得更高的加薪。</p><p><strong>认识到（分配）薪酬透明度本身并不能解决不平等问题。</strong>有一种假设认为，薪酬分配透明度将缩小薪酬差距；然而，有证据表明，仅靠这一点不足以创造一个公平的工作场所。研究表明，女性和男性<em>要求</em>加薪的<a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">比例相对相等</a>，但女性在实现自己的要求方面仍然不太成功。分配薪酬透明度有助于减少一些模糊性，但绩效和薪酬透明度（程序透明度）共同为员工提供了要求他们应得的东西所需的工具。当人们知道谈判会带来什么（即谈判范围是什么以及合理的要求）时，性别差异就会最小化。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>例如，<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">有色人种女性</a>通常不会利用机会协商角色、责任或灵活的工作安排，从而造成长期不平等，从而解释了起薪以外的薪酬差距。更广泛的透明度有助于减少模糊性，这种模糊性常常使妇女和其他少数群体成员在谈判时犹豫不决，即使她们知道自己可以。</p><p><strong>考虑对现有员工<em>和</em>申请人的好处。</strong>简单地公布薪资范围只是问题的一小部分。申请人对过大的薪酬范围有负面反应，因为他们没有提供有用的信息。在这种情况下，薪酬本质上仍然是秘密的。正如我们在研究中发现的那样，如果没有有意义的信息，人们倾向于要求最大金额，看看有什么可能。这给招聘经理带来了另一个头痛的问题。更好的方法是利用程序透明度来清楚地概述确定薪资报价时使用的因素，甚至可能包括这些因素的权重。例如，营销公司 Buffer 在创建一个<a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">薪酬系统方面</a>做得非常出色，该系统通过使用制定薪酬决策的标准公式来平衡简单性（为了更好地理解）和复杂性（为了捕捉细微差别）：薪水 = 工作类型 x 资历x 经验 + 地点 + 10,000 美元或股权。</p><p></p><p></p><p>尽管组织对实施有关薪酬透明度的政府法规存在担忧和犹豫，但此类政策继续受到关注，并且只是对薪酬披露的期望不断提高的推动力之一。在人力资源技术公司 Visier 2022 年的一份报告中，79% 的受访员工表示他们希望<a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">薪酬透明</a>； Z 世代员工是最强烈的支持者。</p><p>我们的研究强调了程序透明度的潜力，可以战略性地减轻感知的组织风险，同时满足法律要求和社会期望。虽然变化显然正在发生，但我们希望企业领导者能够更深入、更具创造性地思考<em>如何</em>以既支持组织目标又满足员工需求的方式实现薪酬透明。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>挑战上级的微妙动态</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>本杰明·莱克 ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) 是雷丁大学亨利商学院的领导力教授。</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>挑战上级的行为不仅仅需要提高声音，还需要更多的努力。它涉及理解、驾驭和参与权力动态、外交和相互尊重的微妙而复杂的舞蹈。接近职业等级中比你高的人需要微妙的平衡以及对这个人和情况的深刻理解。</p><p>对于那些热衷于保持职业礼仪并不断成长的人来说，本指南可以帮助确保您的富有挑战性的对话既具有建设性又充满尊重。</p><p></p><p><strong>明智地选择你的战斗。</strong>工作场所是充满活力的观点、流程和方法的生态系统。解决一个人遇到的每一个观点差异或分歧可能很诱人，但智慧在于辨别哪些战斗值得打。每次出现潜在分歧时，请考虑：这个问题是否如此重要以至于需要对抗？意见上的微小分歧可以通过被动渠道更有效地解决，甚至应该被忽视。但更大的问题，尤其是那些影响团队动力、公司文化或更广泛业务目标的问题，需要采取更直接的方法。</p><p><strong>了解时机的重要性。</strong>在专业沟通的世界中，时机就是一切。选择正确的时机可以决定是否真正考虑某个问题或仓促地驳回某个问题。在考虑挑战上级之前，暂停并从整体角度评估情况至关重要。您的担忧是否如此紧迫以至于需要立即解决？或者，是否最好将其指定为稍后进行详细的私人讨论？明智的做法是避免在高压情况下或公共论坛上与上级对抗，因为这可能会被误解为试图破坏或炫耀。通过选择最佳时间，您可以为建设性对话创造更顺畅的路径。</p><p></p><p><strong>优先考虑私人讨论。</strong>您选择表达担忧的环境对于如何接受这些担忧起着关键作用。参与公开分歧或冲突可能会导致多种不可预见的并发症，包括被视为具有攻击性或对抗性。通过选择私人环境进行这些讨论，您可以为自己和上级提供有利于公开和真诚对话的氛围。这种方法不仅可以最大限度地减少干扰和潜在的偏见，而且还强化了这样一种观念：其意图是建设性反馈，而不是公众批评。</p><p><strong>掌握“我”陈述的艺术。</strong>有效的沟通不仅关乎内容，也关乎交付。我们选择的措辞和表达担忧的方式会极大地影响我们信息的接收。不要采用潜在的对抗性语气，而是使用“我”的陈述来表达观察、感受和建议。例如，与其直言不讳地说“你忽略了这个关键方面”，更具协作性的方法是“我认为这个特定方面可以从进一步的关注中受益”。这种方法确保焦点仍然集中在当前的问题上，而不是个人偏见或对抗上。</p><p></p><p><strong>拥抱反馈过程。</strong>挑战上级或表达担忧的过程本质上是双边的。这不仅是您表达想法的途径，也是了解他人观点的机会。即使反馈与您的观点相矛盾，也要表现出真正的开放态度，这一点至关重要。这种方法不仅为相互尊重铺平了道路，而且在组织内培育了持续学习和协作的文化。</p><p><strong>与志同道合的同事结盟，但要巧妙。</strong>虽然个人的担忧有其道理，但不可否认的是，数量的力量。寻找与您观点相同的盟友或同事可以进一步减轻您的担忧。然而，这种联盟必须不被视为拉帮结派或分裂。主要关注点应始终放在组织的集体利益上，而不是在团队内形成派系。</p><p><strong>将组织的目标放在首位。</strong>您提出的任何疑虑或挑战都应该与组织更广泛的目标和目标产生内在的共鸣。通过始终将您的反馈和建议与公司的使命和价值观保持一致，您可以向上级保证您对组织集体成功的承诺而不是个人愿望。</p><p><strong>为一系列结果做好准备。</strong>虽然我们都希望我们的分歧能取得积极和建设性的成果，但有必要为各种反应做好准备。你的上级可能会乐于接受、漠不关心，甚至是防御性的。通过预测这些潜在的反应并相应地规划您的策略，您可以确保无论即时反馈如何，您都保持平衡、建设性和专业。</p><h3>后果：反思、适应和发展</h3><p></p><p>每一次职业互动，尤其是那些涉及挑战或对抗的互动，都为个人和职业成长提供了丰富的机会。讨论结束后，花时间评估对话的有效性、所采用的策略以及取得的成果。这些反思将为您带来宝贵的经验教训，并帮助您不断完善和增强您的沟通技巧，以应对未来的挑战。</p><p>最终，虽然挑战上级的任务似乎充满了潜在的陷阱，但只要采取正确的策略并注重相互成长和尊重，就可以通过机智和专业精神来完成它。鼓励公开对话和反馈文化是创新和前瞻性组织的基石。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>幽灵情景如何困扰战略执行</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang 是牛津大学赛德商学院管理实践高级研究员，也是牛津协作战略实验室主任。拉斐尔·拉米雷斯 (Rafael Ramírez) 是赛德商学院的实践教授，也是牛津情景项目的主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">帕特里克·乔治/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>从事战略规划的高管通常存在盲点。他们几乎只关注可能的行动方案，而很少关注这些行动将在未来的社会经济和环境背景下发挥作用。在我们 70 年的研究、实践和教学过程中，我们以及其他人观察到，企业领导者及其组织的配置倾向于仅以一种对未来的隐含观点开展工作。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这种观点通常深深植根于他们的战略中，作为对未来环境的一组毫无疑问的假设。我们将这些未经检验的假设称为<em>“幽灵情景”</em> ，因为它们是无形的，而且可能会以意想不到和不受欢迎的方式再次困扰高管和公司。</p><p></p><p>每一个幽灵情景的基础都是一小部分隐含的趋势，领导者在不怀疑这些趋势是否会改变的情况下预测了未来。想想气候的剧烈变化是如何影响英国铁路服务的。 2022 年 7 月，该国首次记录到超过 40 摄氏度（104 华氏度）的气温。这些高温将铁轨加热到略高于 62 摄氏度（143 华氏度），导致它们弯曲。结果，许多火车行程被取消，其他路线的服务速度减慢至 60 英里/小时。铁轨专为未来气温不超过 27 摄氏度（80 华氏度）而设计。简而言之，英国铁路网的设计和建造并不是为了 2022 年的情景，而是为了隐含地假设历史气候趋势将继续保持不变。</p><h3>假设隐藏在众目睽睽之下</h3><p>对人类感知的研究表明，人们通过将视觉焦点的物体置于他们注意力的最前面，而其他一切都后退，从而将其视觉焦点的物体与其背景区分开来。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>人类可以将注意力集中在人物或背景上，但不能同时关注两者。</p><p><a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">鲁宾花瓶错觉</a>是这种图形-背景（或背景）感知挑战的一个众所周知的例子。根据您观察图片的方式，您会看到一个花瓶或两张脸的侧面。然而，重要的是，你不能同时看到两者：其中一个在感知上会后退，成为你所看到的人物的背景。要看到这两个数字，您必须在它们之间交替显示。</p><p>重要的是，高管们必须认识到人们的专注能力也会让他们忽视重要的背景信息，因为领导者常常看不到他们的战略将发挥的背景以及他们的战略所依赖的背景。他们可能认为硬基础设施（例如铁路轨道）是一个相对静态的背景问题，并将注意力集中在对业务规划似乎更重要的趋势上，例如客户偏好和习惯的变化。但这可能会导致高管们实施一项战略，而该战略可能会因与背景问题交织在一起的未经审查的假设而出乎意料地受到干扰。</p><p></p><p>特别是在今天，鉴于变化速度快、不确定性飙升和动荡程度高，未能将战略规划中内置的假设浮出水面是有风险的，就像未能通过<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">情景规划</a>考虑多种可能的替代未来一样。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>情景规划练习可以帮助管理人员探索他们的策略在不同的业务环境和条件下如何发挥作用，并着眼于磨练这些策略以使其更加有效。</p><p>为了了解情景规划如何防止高管受到幽灵情景的困扰，让我们看看我们最近在牛津情景计划中合作的两个全球组织。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA 审查其 ESG 假设</h3><p>保险公司<a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a>为 50 多个国家的 9500 万客户提供财产伤亡保险、人寿保险和储蓄以及资产管理领域的产品和服务。该公司的关键战略目标之一是维持其气候领导地位。 AXA 的高管明智地决定在有限的时间内将该目标的未来背景作为他们关注的焦点，以便他们可以探索它可能会如何变化，以及如果发生变化，他们可能需要如何适应。</p><p>该公司特别有兴趣了解未来的环境、社会和治理 (ESG) 趋势可能如何影响其既定目标。例如，美国一些州拟议的立法将惩罚奉行 ESG 投资策略的金融机构，这可能会产生什么影响？或者，如果公司被视为洗绿或歪曲其 ESG 资质，公众会如何反应？因此，该公司并没有像目前所理解的那样，让 ESG 要求成为幻影，而是提出了有关 ESG 未来的问题，更广泛地说，提出了有关企业新兴可持续发展环境的问题。</p><p>情景规划练习的参与者和协调者以团队形式合作，着眼于未来的环境。一种设想是，独立保险公司被占主导地位的科技平台吞并，而这些平台的 ESG 优先事项取代了保险公司的优先事项。在另一种情况下，政府制定了有关 ESG 问题的严格法规，这对公司的战略选择具有合规性影响。在另一个想象中的未来，气候变化的加速速度超出预期，导致企业将优先事项转向紧急解决气候相关危机，或者只专注于减少二氧化碳排放，放弃社会和治理议程。</p><p>通过明确参与幽灵情景及其同样合理的替代方案，AXA 开始认识到，继续努力提供目前所理解的卓越 ESG 绩效可能并不是它应该为的唯一未来做好准备。在 AXA 内部，这些见解已被用来为有关未来 ESG 挑战及其对可能发布的公告和承诺的影响（包括何时发布和与谁发布）的对话提供信息。他们促使 AXA 开始准备替代策略，以防根据当前 ESG 预期提供出色的业绩变得无关紧要。</p><p></p><h3> Swift 期待数字货币</h3><p>Swift（全球银行间金融电信协会）是一家会员制合作社，为全球跨境支付提供金融消息传递和相关服务。目前，它每天为 200 多个国家和地区的 11,000 多家机构发送超过 3000 万条消息。它由 15 个国家的 239 家银行于 20 世纪 70 年代初创建，旨在通过新技术平台解决跨境支付通信笨重、缓慢且成本高昂的日益严重的问题。颠覆是 Swift 起源故事的一部分，因此它积极主动地应对其环境中的潜在变化。</p><p> 2021 年，Swift 高管有兴趣了解数字货币（包括央行发行的货币）在未来几年可能会如何发展。 2021 年，该类别的加密货币数量增加了一倍多，达到 9,000 多种。</p><p> Swift 的高管并没有假设数字货币的这种展开和快速增长是唯一可能的情况，而是停下来更好地了解可能发生的其他发展、它们将如何塑造未来的数字货币生态系统以及 Swift 可能会受到怎样的影响。例如，经济学家和其他专家指出许多数字货币缺乏内在价值，以及<a href="https://concerned.tech/">对其底层技术的安全性和可靠性的</a>担忧。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>通用战略规划流程中的幽灵隐藏在哪里</h4><p><strong>在 SWOT 分析中，</strong>领导者仅根据当前情况以及已知的竞争对手、供应商、客户、监管规则等来考虑其组织的优势、劣势、机会和威胁。在识别和分析风险时，高管们隐含地假设只有一种情况。然而，在另一种情况下（不同的场景），风险可能会消失，新的机会可能会出现。</p><p><strong>在利益相关者绘图中，</strong>领导者对利益相关者现在和预期未来的注意力和权力进行评估。隐含的场景是本次评估的背景。但如果环境发生意外变化，利益相关者的重要性可能会发生重大变化。</p><p><strong>在博弈论和兵棋推演中，</strong>竞争对手的举动是在幽灵场景的背景下考虑的，而兵棋推演通常不会考虑与正在进行的未来不同的未来。然而，不断变化的场景可能需要新的战术并暴露出不可预见的未来战斗人员。<br /></article></aside></div><p>斯威夫特本人对数字货币的立场是开放和中立的。如果它们得到适当的监管并为其服务的经济、企业和社区增加价值，它将有可能为它们提供支持。</p><p>为 Swift 高管开发的场景探索了对技术的信任可能演变的不同方式。在其中一些国家中，随着数字货币所基于的不透明技术和算法变得可疑，与数字货币相关的信任将会消失。在其他情况下，数字货币可能被操纵，因此无法再保证所交换内容的真实性。在另一种情况下，对营利性金融机构更普遍的缺乏信任将蔓延到数字货币的提供商，导致社会的某些群体犹豫是否参与其中任何一个，从而产生相关后果。</p><p>对于设想这些场景的牛津参与者来说，尚不清楚那些推广该技术的人所持有的价值观，或者该技术据称实现的价值观，是否会被政府监管机构或整个社会在所有可以想象的未来背景下所接受。此后，斯威夫特的高管们探索了这些场景，为数字货币的发展方式提供了丰富而不同的见解。这些见解帮助他们避免依赖对未来过于简单化的看法，并避免被炒作所左右。</p><h3>如何在鬼魂困扰你之前看到它</h3><p>根据我们为 AXA、Swift 和许多其他组织领导情景规划练习的经验，我们为那些希望将幽灵情景纳入视野并使图地反转成为其战略实践的关键部分的高管制定了以下建议。</p><p><strong>使用情景规划来确认隐含的假设。</strong>认识到每个组织的战略都假定了一个通常不容置疑的未来场景。也就是说，每位高管都会参与某种形式的隐性情景规划，无论他们是否意识到这一点。将情景规划作为战略制定过程的常规部分可以实现两个重要目标：它提醒领导者，动荡的环境可能会如何改变他们的工作和竞争环境，并承认当前条件本身呈现出假设的未来情景，不是一个固定的现实。</p><p></p><p><strong>认识图形与背景的困境。</strong>承认被关注的人物（最常见的是组织的战略）和经常被忽视的背景（未经审查的幽灵场景）不能同时成功地成为关注的焦点。相反，高管们需要灵活地、顺序地在两者之间切换，以充分调查每一方，避免陷入对另一方做出隐含假设的陷阱。 AXA 花时间刻意探索 ESG 的未来，而不是假设目前的使用和理解方式不会发生变化。斯威夫特有目的地专注于了解数字货币的潜在未来环境，而不是仅仅隐含地从现有趋势中假设后续选择。</p><p></p><p><strong>投入执行时间和资源来解决问题。</strong>组织必须有意识地为领导者创造时间和空间，以探索相关的经济、政治、技术、社会和环境因素可能发生的变化。将一小组未来情景与幽灵情景进行对比，以查明当前策略可能需要在哪些方面进行调整，以适应环境可能发展的各种方式。有些组织甚至设有专门的部门，例如壳牌国际公司的<a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">全球商业环境情景团队</a>。加拿大<a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">政策视野 (Policy Horizo​​ns Canada)</a>为加拿大政府扮演这一角色。</p><p></p><p>为了使所有这些努力真正有用，情景规划的输出必须反馈到战略决策中，而不是写在报告中并束之高阁。它们还应该在组织中更广泛地传播，以便各个级别和职能的人员都可以从自己的角度考虑可能的影响——领导层可能不会想到的影响。为了使策略在环境发生变化时取得成功，高管需要采取平衡的方法——将数字和背景视为重要的洞察领域。也就是说，即使在他们计划下一步行动时，他们也必须认识到他们的行动将发生的背景或基础的重要性。精明的高管知道他们必须预见并拥抱变革。诀窍是学会熟练地在人物和地面之间转移注意力，以了解上下文如何展开，这样你的策略就不会毫无根据。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>用人工智能推动跨学科创新：沃尔沃的 Anders Sjögren</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interciplin-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-intersubject-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automotive Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory. On this episode of the Me, Myself, and AI podcast, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>怀着成为一名医生的雄心开始职业生涯，最终成为一家大型汽车制造商的技术领导者，这似乎是一条不太可能的道路，但对于领导沃尔沃汽车数据和人工智能创新项目的 Anders Sjögren 来说，这是一条完美的轨迹。</p><p>在<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客的这一集中，安德斯与主持人 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 一起解释了汽车制造商如何使用数据和人工智能为制造提供信息，确保零件的制造一致且尽可能高效。作为驾驶员体验和安全。他还概述了智能技术让驾驶员保持警惕并了解周围状况的一些具体方法，并描述了沃尔沃的技术驱动创新方法。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/MMAI-S8-E1-Sjogren-Volvo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="安德斯·舍格伦"></p><h4>安德斯·舍格伦，沃尔沃汽车</h4><p>Anders Sjögren 是沃尔沃汽车公司的高级技术主管。他专注于战略、研究、创新和转型，主要目标是确保汽车制造商理解并执行不断涌现的数据、分析和人工智能领域。应用领域包括创建人工智能支持的智能客户功能以及使用人工智能改革沃尔沃的运营和开发活动。 Sjögren 拥有数理统计（大规模和计算方面）的学术背景以及以数据为中心的方法开发和软件产品开发的工业背景。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>汽车制造商如何使用人工智能将设计安全、高性能车辆所需的所有复杂系统整合在一起？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p><strong>安德斯·舍格伦：</strong>我是沃尔沃汽车公司的安德斯·舍格伦，你们正在听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能</cite>。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>今天，Sam 和我很高兴能够与沃尔沃汽车公司数据、分析和人工智能工程高级技术主管 Anders Sjögren 一起加入。让我们开始吧。安德斯，欢迎来到这个节目。</p><p><strong>安德斯·舍格伦：</strong>谢谢。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>请告诉我们一些您在沃尔沃汽车的角色。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>我是[组织]工程部分的数据、分析和人工智能方面的技术领导者，这就是研发。所以，本质上，进来的是对汽车的愿望，出来的是图纸和代码。当然，在这个领域，数据分析和人工智能有很多可能性，无论是在开发过程中还是作为汽车实际功能的一部分——智能功能和个性化功能等等。</p><p>因此，我的目的实际上是确保我们通过数据、分析和人工智能获得尽可能多的价值。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> [您关注的焦点]是汽车中的人工智能和数据分析——比如汽车中的传感器和各种智能设备，它们使驾驶更安全、更具互动性，诸如此类？还是也需要客户获取、经销商网络以及各种数据分析来运营汽车制造和销售业务？</p><p><strong>安德斯·舍格伦：</strong>是的。所以，我的意思是，所有这些都适用于沃尔沃汽车，但我真正积极参与的部分更多是汽车的制造部分。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为这是一个很好的观点，因为当大多数人想到汽车和人工智能时，我认为他们会立即跳到完全自动驾驶汽车的想法。你所指出的是，还有多少其他事情可以从人工智能中受益，即使是在汽车生产中。你知道，我想也许每个人都对我们现在没有全自动汽车感到沮丧，但幕后发生的事情太多了，人们没有机会看到。您在生产过程中使用人工智能的方式有哪些示例？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>如果我们退一步说，沃尔沃汽车的目标实际上是让人们以个性化、可持续且安全的方式自由出行。</p><p>如果我们从“个人”开始，那么了解您并让您作为客户或车内人员感到特别就非常重要。当然，这与从传感器开始然后真正解释这些值有关。这可以是摄像头、不同类型的转向输入……</p><p>另一个领域肯定是可持续性。那里使用人工智能来确保我们拥有尽可能多的轻质部件。因此，例如，使用人工智能，人们可以获得具有相同强度和此类特性的机械零件，但重量要轻得多，所使用的材料也更少。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>在设计过程中，你说的是吧？当工程师考虑零件的所有不同排列时，是吗？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>在设计过程中——是的，没错。我认为，在许多工程活动中，这确实是人工智能的本质，那就是我们首先手动决定我们想要做什么，然后实际执行所有不同的步骤。这是目前的做法，而在人工智能时代，更多的是决定和描述我想要达到的方面是什么？我想要优化哪些内容？边界条件可能是什么？然后人工智能会帮助你实现这一目标。</p><p>因此，在机械零件方面，您可能会说，“这些是连接点。这些是我想要的强度和刚度特性。给我具有这些特性的零件，但[使其]尽可能轻，当然也可以生产。”</p><p>那可能是一个区域。此外，对于可持续发展来说，我们使用尽可能少的材料并尽可能降低使用率，这一点非常重要。</p><p>当然，第三点是关于[安全]。当然，我们有自动驾驶汽车，但甚至在此之前，还有其他类型的功能正在使用。例如，了解驾驶员：驾驶员是否意识到？如果他看起来很累，我们是否应该劝他喝杯咖啡或其他什么？</p><p>在我们汽车的后续版本中，我们了解车内是否有宠物或儿童（也许是在炎热的天气），然后防止他们在这种情况下受伤等等。</p><p>我想说，在这些领域，人工智能确实可以成为引领我们实现目标的核心技术。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这真的很有趣，因为很多时候组织告诉我们他们从试图解决的问题开始，然后找到一种技术来解决它，这是有道理的，因为否则你就是在试图找到一个适合的问题一个看似落后的解决方案。您提到您的汽车可以感知……如果有人或宠物不小心留在车内。沃尔沃是如何决定专注于解决这个特定问题的？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>我们所做的很多事情实际上都是基于现实世界的安全，因为我们实际上看到了人们受伤的真正原因。我的意思是，如果我们用碰撞和此类安全进行类比，我们的团队会在发生碰撞时前往现场，以真正了解现实中实际发生的情况，而不仅仅是根据此类碰撞的认证测试等。</p><p>而且，回到这个例子，如果我们看这里，宠物和孩子确实会受伤 - 希望不是在沃尔沃汽车中，但这是现实，对吗？</p><p>但你提到的确实非常有趣，因为它也反过来了：就像，现在我们有了这些传感器，我们可以通过这个为客户提供哪些其他真正有价值的功能，当然，保护隐私考虑到等等？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这非常有趣，因为沃尔沃……我记得小时候我叔叔常说，“你想要一辆安全的汽车，你就买一辆沃尔沃。”它一直是安全的代名词，对于一家将安全体验作为主要目标之一的公司来说，退后一步想想，现在有了如此大量的数据和所有这些，真是太神奇了大量的处理，我可以想象有如此多的用例，对于 Sam 来说，正在被考虑。所以这真的非常令人鼓舞。</p><p>这里的路线图是什么样的？我的意思是，这是一种持续不断的创新构思方法，它会说：“在个人、安全和可持续这三大支柱上，我们还能做些什么？”提出这些想法并挑选好的想法并实施或不实施的过程是怎样的？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>我认为这些想法要么来自技术方面并从中真正受到启发，要么来自分析方面。通常，当新技术和真正以客户为中心的需求……它们相遇时，当然，我们的组织也具有执行这些需求的敏捷性。这确实是我们取得丰硕成果的地方。它通常是不同来源的混合：我想说的是创新和新方向。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>公司中有一种机制可以创造这种跨学科的灵感吗？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>是的，我会这么说。我想说，既有正式的机制，也有非正式的机制。作为一家汽车公司，沃尔沃汽车并不是超级大。当然也有较小的，但我认为这也是一个优势，我的意思是，几乎所有不同的步骤，从产品战略、设计、研发、工程，然后是后期阶段……</p><p>总部位于[瑞典]哥德堡，步行即可到达。美国部门距离我现在坐的地方实际上是50米，而另一个方向50米是碰撞测试设施和安全中心。</p><p>所以，我想说的是，建立联系和创建这种联系更容易——我该怎么说呢？ ——非正式创新活动。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这就是相对较小的尺寸和托管确实非常有帮助的地方。拥有彼此接近的团队。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>谈论它很小很有趣，因为它肯定不是一家小公司。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>一切都是相对的，是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我想一切都是相对的。当我们聊天时，我想到了我们之前交谈过的一些人，人们提到的反复出现的主题之一是，哦，从业务问题开始的想法：“你不没有人工智能并找到使用它的地方。你从一个业务问题开始，然后解决它。”但这是一个很好的组合——听起来有很多事情都是从业务问题开始的，但有趣的是，一旦这些流程到位，一旦这些技术到位，就会出现一个草根问题创新说：“好吧；我们如何使用它？我认为这是一个有趣的观点，但它并没有得到强烈的体现——或者也许我忘记了一些事情——但似乎并没有那么强烈地得到体现。这是一个很好的组合，也许适用于这种规模的组织……这个位于同一地点的组织。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>是的，尤其是在原型设计和构思阶段。但是，当然，在实际进入产品之前，需要经过更彻底的审查等等。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>沃尔沃对小型人工智能初创公司和公司进行了相当多的投资和收购。请告诉我们一些关于内部、供应商和合作伙伴公司的整体生态系统的信息，这些公司共同将您正在谈论的一些人工智能创意变为现实。是内部的吗？是外在的吗？是混合的吗？您如何看待生态系统？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>我肯定会说这是一个混合体。有些事情……我们需要自己做才能获得充分的理解，或者我们真正想在哪些领域处于领先地位，而在其他一些领域，我们肯定希望与在这些领域实力雄厚的其他公司合作。传统上来说，汽车是一种超级复杂的产品。它有数百或数千个不同的部分，所有这些部分都需要组装在一起。当然，这个领域传统上有很多供应商提供不同的零件。</p><p>最近，我们更多地致力于将软件实施引入内部，以提高开发过程的速度和敏捷性。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这在汽车制造中似乎特别复杂，因为如果我思考汽车是如何开始的，它们是独立的系统。有制动系统、动力传动系统、空调和信息娱乐系统，所有这些都是独立的。这很好，因为这样我们就拥有了与信息娱乐系统和制动系统不同的特定标准——或者至少我希望会有这样的标准。但你要指出的是，其中每一个都可能使用来自不同区域的传感器，整个汽车如何独立变得更加复杂，但它也变得更加复杂，试图连接所有这些部件和让他们一起工作。</p><p>一方面，这似乎是人工智能的机遇，但同时也是挑战。</p><p><strong>安德斯·舍格伦：</strong>是的。这是100%真实的。这既是一个非常大的机会，但这也意味着这确实是核心挑战之一——我的意思是，如何建立对汽车内部和外部的统一理解。</p><p>我们谈论客户数字孪生和车辆数字孪生等等，从某种意义上说，这些方面可能意味着很多不同的事情。但是，当然，您所说的这些不同的系统传统上位于公司的不同部门，因此这也意味着需要大量的跨职能协作。但我们确实需要弥合这些组织边界。</p><p>我认为这确实是关键点之一，也就是说，为了成功采用分析和人工智能，这确实意味着公司的不同部门需要共同努力才能实现这一目标。因为否则，它就会变成一个筒仓。有些人并不会真正从中受益。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>你知道，这是真的。这是一个常见的主题，在 BCG 的工作中，我们有这样的经验法则 - 10:20:70 - 我们说 10% 是数据和算法，20% 是技术和数字平台，但 70% 是其中 % 是业务集成和实施，以及将组织的不同部分整合在一起。也许这在汽车公司是最真实的，正如你所说，山姆，在那里，看似不同的系统正在组合在一起创建一个更大的系统，但这些单元中的每一个都已单独完善，现在你也想要集体的完美。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>安德斯，我们谈论了很多关于沃尔沃的事情。您个人是如何对人工智能、数据、技术和分析产生兴趣的？你的起源故事是什么？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>我想我一直对计算机感兴趣。我的父亲确实是个瘾君子，所以我就是伴随着这个瘾君子长大的。</p><p>我最初是一名工程专业的学生，​​并获得了计算机科学硕士学位。然后我开始在哥德堡大学医院担任医学领域的研究工程师，然后很快发现为了真正利用数据——结论等来自数据……所以我然后进入了数理统计领域。</p><p>所以我读了博士学位。然后回到软件产品开发。一段时间后，我回到学术界工作了几年，做了博士后，然后在沃尔沃汽车公司获得了一个很好的机会。所以我基本上已经在这里呆了七年了。这就是我的一点历史。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>非常鼓舞人心。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Anders，我们还想问您一些快速问题，我们的想法是尽快回答。这些并不是沃尔沃特有的问题。</p><p>您对人工智能所做的最自豪的事情是什么？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>问题是大多数事情我都无法谈论。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这也是一个很好的答案。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你必须拭目以待。好吧，那么你对人工智能担心什么？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>担心吗？</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>哦，我想，当然，一个是长期的——那种奇点的东西。但我认为，距离现在更近了，可以这么说，我们确实看到了大型语言[模型]的超快速发展及其可以做的事情，以及那种不仅仅解决一个问题并给出解决方案的系统一个答案，但实际上可以按顺序产生一系列步骤。这是一种超级强大的技术，但超级强大的技术既可以用来做好事，也可以用来做坏事。</p><p>这既让我超级兴奋，又有点担心。 20年后的世界会是什么样子？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动是什么？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>骑摩托车，但显然使用了技术。但它更像是……是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>涉及技术。一切事物都以某种方式涉及技术。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>是的，差不多。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您小时候想要的第一个职业是什么？你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>安德斯·舍格伦：</strong>医生。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，这与您在医疗公司工作的第一份职业有关。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>是的，我这么认为，但后来我发现数学和那些东西非常令人兴奋，所以我进入了那个领域。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>未来您对人工智能最大的愿望是什么？您希望我们能从这些技术的出现中获得什么？</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>如果说我们最大的愿望，我认为就是我们找到一种方法来利用它来实现我们的共同利益。我们需要找到一种方式让它融入社会，我想这确实是我最大的愿望。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>在相对较短的时间内，我们了解了数据、人工智能和技术的各种用途，了解了如何以新的方式制造汽车，以及人工智能和技术提供帮助和服务的所有不同方式驾驶它们的人。这真的很有启发，安德斯。感谢您的加入。</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren：</strong>谢谢你邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您的聆听。在我们的下一集中，Sam 和我采访了 LG Nova 的常驻企业家 Shilpa Prasad。请加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interciplin-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>领导者将阻力转化为进步的五种方法</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phillip G. Clampitt and Bob DeKoch. <p>菲利普·G·克兰皮特 (Phillip G. Clampitt) 是威斯康星大学绿湾分校布莱尔传播学教授。 Bob DeKoch 是领导力咨询公司 Limitless 的创始人，也是 Boldt Co 的前总裁。他们是<cite>《Leading with Care in a Tough World</cite> 》（罗丹图书，2022 年）的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it’s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Clampitt-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>有效应对阻力很可能是领导者可以拥有的最重要的能力之一，在过渡时期尤其重要，比如在大流行后重返办公室。这种对组织政策、指令或决定的抵制可以采取多种形式，从表达担忧和提出问题到积极反对和破坏。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>高效的领导者将阻力视为促进团队学习、同时推动组织向前发展的机会。目标应该是通过调和倡导热情和逆向悲观情绪来增加人们的理解和支持。这种更深层次的理解虽然不一定能让所有人满意，但会营造一种坦诚、谦逊、适应和信任的氛围，从而巧妙地消除潜在的破坏性倾向。</p><p></p><p>根据数十年的研究、高管观察和访谈，我们确定了领导者在遇到阻力时所犯的主要错误，并提供了五项指导方针来帮助他们更好地应对。</p><h3>什么不起作用</h3><p>领导者在面对矛盾、分歧或阻力时会犯三个主要错误：</p><p><strong>抑制不确定性。</strong>当提出的问题可能无法立即得到答案或引入最近可能出现或被搁置或忽视的观点时，阻力会增加不确定性。一些领导人通过边缘化担忧、提供安抚保证或援引独裁声音来应对不确定性引发的阻力。这种做法提供了虚假的确定性，从长远来看会损害信任。</p><p>根据我们的研究，即使是那些在工作生活中寻求更多确定性的员工也希望他们的组织能够拥抱不确定性。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>高效的领导者会避免掩盖不确定性，即使他们面临着根本不存在的确定性要求。即使他们现在不知道答案，他们也可以通过讨论如何找到这些答案来提供操作层面的确定性。</p><p><strong>忽略权力动态。</strong>拥有职位或后天地位的领导者会直接或微妙地影响阻力的性质。高度专制的权力结构往往会将阻力推向地下。同样，更微妙的权力信号可能会压制对合理关切的公开讨论。领导人可能会错误地将沉默等同于同意。有些人会假装接受，而另一些人会在“一次又一次的会议”中散播异议，从而暴露并往往放大人们的恐惧。</p><p></p><p>当一个经验丰富的高管团队的首席执行官提出一项新举措时，我们有机会观察他们的反应——包括不温不火和象征性的反馈。首席执行官意识到缺乏坦诚，因此寻求更多意见。一位沮丧的高管最终脱口而出：“我们不会在这个问题上分享我们的想法，因为无论我们说什么，你都会做你要做的事情。”这一极其坦诚的评论提出了一个更深层次的挑战：对特定问题持有强烈观点的有权势的人如何鼓励坦诚？有效的领导者会采取积极措施来减少破坏性对话（如下所述），因为他们认识到固有的权力动态极大地影响任何讨论的质量。</p><p><strong>假设声音最大代表共识。</strong>抵制有多种形式：其中一些是显而易见的，例如投诉或员工请愿，而另一些则更为微妙，例如会议中的询问或缺乏参与。领导者常常倾向于更多地关注最敢于发声的员工，认为拥有最大扩音器的人代表了大多数人的意见。他们可能会也可能不会。</p><p>当最响亮或最具政治影响力的声音主导讨论时，这种动态往往会造成对支持或分歧程度的不准确印象。有效的领导者认识到两种极端的危险：狂热者掩盖相关问题，或者逆向者破坏潜在的支持。</p><p></p><h3>参与抵制的建议</h3><p>有效的领导者不仅避免压制不确定性，忽视权力动态，并假设最直言不讳的人代表共识，他们还采取反映以下指导方针的积极对策。</p><p> <strong>1. 设定对话的基本规则。</strong>以下基本规则可以提高期望，缓和不尊重的宣传，并增加每个人抵制机会的价值：</p><ul><li><strong>寻求理解您不同意的观点。</strong>在讨论有争议的问题时，许多人的第一本能是立即反驳或反驳。通过表现出接受不同观点的意愿来抵制这种诱惑。提出问题或重新表述别人的论点（尤其是那些你不同意的论点）等简单的策略可以缓和反驳，并且几乎神奇地增强对话语气。同样，诸如“告诉我我的想法可能是错误的”或“我可能错过了一些东西；我可能错过了一些东西”之类的陈述。请说更多”表明对新想法持开放态度。</li><li><strong>尊重地不同意别人的观点。</strong>用诸如“让我提供另一个观点”之类的语言尊重地表达分歧，可以设定正确的讨论基调，同时也鼓励那些比较犹豫的人大声说出来。不愿分享不同观点通常表明存在潜在的信任缺陷。有时，尽管房间里存在固有的权力差异，领导者仍需要鼓励其他人分享他们的担忧。</li><li><strong>避免两极分化、扎根的断言。</strong>过于确定地倡导很可能会引发权力动态问题。表明概率水平，例如“我对这个事实有 95% 的把握”，通常会引发更激烈的辩论。</li><li><strong>消除阻力的个性化。</strong>如果一项决定被贴上“首席执行官计划”的标签，许多人会进行自我审查，并因为害怕冒犯当权者而避免提出担忧。通过在白板上记录问题而不进行归因来消除个性化的阻力，可以减轻这种权力动态，同时缓和强烈的情绪。</li><li><strong>随着讨论的进展改变你的观点和反应。</strong>经常需要提醒员工，在考虑新证据或获得新观点后改变观点并不是软弱的表现。没有人应该担心因为改变观点而丢脸。事实上，有效的领导者会在他们的观点发生转变时通过发表诸如“我看到一个不在我的雷达屏幕上的问题”之类的声明来强调。随着对话的出现，重新构建关键问题以强调新的观点。</li></ul><p> <strong>2. 引导团队了解阻力机会。</strong>许多会议或倡议的推出都以问答期结束，而没有首先向与会者提供有关阻力的期望的方向。由于缺乏清晰度，人们常常会做出各种未经检验和未言明的假设，这些假设可能并不准确。</p><p>一些员工因抵制机会而被剥夺了权利，因为他们认为自己的所有想法都应该被完全接受。他们不期望发生合理的辩论或对<em>他们的</em>抵制进行反击。这就是为什么明智的领导者会仔细地引导员工了解可能的结果，而不是接受/拒绝极端的情况。他们提出了其他替代方案，例如调整计划、引入测试期、推迟实施、修改决定或重新考虑提案。</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. 选择正确的论坛和设置。</strong>有些场合，比如市政厅聚会或在线论坛，往往会鼓励更情绪化的观点表达、姿态和发泄。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>这种情况可能会阻碍那些不太愿意进行情绪化争论的人进行有用的询问和提问。合适的场所和论坛可以最大限度地增加富有洞察力的提问、深思熟虑的讨论和相互尊重的辩论的机会。通常，配备适当讨论参数的小团体效果最好。同样，对较小群体的在线论坛进行适当监控可以鼓励更好的抵制动力。</p><p>领导者还需要注意，有些人不愿意在别人面前分享担忧，因为他们担心被视为团队合作能力差，或者他们对如何表达担忧或捍卫自己的观点缺乏信心。为了鼓励那些不太愿意发言的人，提前向他们提供会议的讨论要点并鼓励他们写下他们的担忧和疑问通常会有所帮助。</p><p> <strong>4.先教育后倡导。</strong>熟练的教育工作者很快就会放弃这样的想法：一个好的解释就足以建立理解。通常，他们会讨论得出结论的方法，包括相反的观点和现有的问题。这种方法将不确定性融入结论，为进一步讨论和相反观点腾出空间。</p><p>相比之下，倡导者很少讨论可能与他们坚定的观点相矛盾的证据或方法。当他们确实接受相反的观点时，他们常常会轻视或嘲笑这些观点。支持者可能会回避任何批评，淡化不确定性，并认为简短的解释会启发其他人。即使是聪明的高管也常常陷入这个陷阱，高估了他们教育工作的程度和深度。</p><p>在教育之后的某个时候，倡导可能会发挥作用，但最终，有效的领导者认为允许人们表达担忧会带来好处。短期来看，阻力可能会导致调整，从而提高长期接受度和顺利实施。</p><p> <strong>5.路标拐点。</strong>随着决策、举措和政策的发展，领导者对阻力的确定性和开放程度也会发生变化。在领导层对这些拐点缺乏明确说明的情况下，员工会采用有关抵制的潜规则，例如以下内容：</p><ul><li>规则A：如果领导还没有做出最终决定，那么我可以大声说出我的观点。</li><li>规则B：如果领导者有很强的立场或者已经做出了最终决定，那么我支持它或者闭嘴。</li><li>规则 C：如果我在一个问题上争论足够长的时间，领导者就会屈服。</li></ul><p>如果潜规则 A 和 B 强化了阻力动态，那么领导者可能会高估某项举措或决策的支持程度。为什么？因为按照规则 B 运作的员工认为反馈请求是为了剧院或旨在制造支持；他们进行自我审查或仅提出象征性的反对。结果，不同意见和潜在有价值的声音都消失了。</p><p></p><p>规则 C 恰恰相反，引发了无穷无尽的争论。这会在决策被调整、修改或最终确定后滋生抱怨文化。高效的领导者知道，开放并不意味着可以进行无休止的讨论。毕竟，反推反推可以永远持续下去。</p><p>阻止这些无声规则扎根的最佳方法是在抵制期间明确指出拐点。以开放之名掩饰自己情绪的领导人破坏了整个对话的坦诚。相反，有效的领导者会分享他们对调整拟议计划的开放程度，宣布他们的情绪何时发生变化，并明确表明抵制的时间何时结束。</p><h3>一个成功的反击故事</h3><p>Capital Credit Union 首席执行官劳里·布茨 (Laurie Butz) 经常使用这些指导方针来进行抵制，以充分了解员工认为随着新举措的推出，他们正在失去什么。例如，随着 COVID-19 威胁的消退，她试图重新启动面对面的全体员工会议，以增强包容性，并就悬而未决的举措进行更强有力、深思熟虑的讨论。她认为教育过程是双向的，这需要更多的面对面论坛，鼓励遵守比屏幕发泄更富有成效的讨论基本规则。</p><p>然而，这一消息遭到了员工的强烈抵制，因为他们需要长途跋涉才能参加一年两次的聚会。一些人通过在线调查表达了对费用和时间的担忧，而另一些人则直接向直接主管表达了不满，认为“Zoom 会议在新冠疫情期间效果很好”。</p><p>巴茨承认了这些担忧，同时恭敬地为现场聚会辩护，因为毕竟，“你可以举办一场 Zoom 婚礼，但会缺少一些重要的东西。”类似的信息在她的“大使”（意见领袖）的更个人渠道中得到了回应。</p><p></p><p>随着时间的推移，面对面的会议 (1) 提高了员工参与度，(2) 重新激发了员工参与流程的兴趣，(3) 引发了对关键问题更深入的讨论。定量证据支持了这些观察结果。例如，在恢复面对面会议后，全员调查的参与率从 60% 增加到 91%，83% 的调查受访者表示他们“高度投入工作”。轶事证据也出现了：员工在离开现场会议时经常询问，“我们什么时候还有机会像这样见面？”</p><p></p><p>通过抑制不确定性、引发权力动态以及过多关注最敢于表达的员工来抑制阻力，很可能会导致短期的顺从和服从，但代价是<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/decision-downloading/">破坏长期信任</a>。巧妙而尊重地管理阻力需要预先投入时间，让员工参与进来，同时提供前进的动力。好处是：领导者学会更巧妙地影响员工如何解释趋势、事件和决策，并对新出现的问题有更深入的洞察。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> ChatGPT 如何帮助经理设计更好的工作角色？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fangfang Zhang and Sharon K. Parker. <p>张芳芳博士是科廷大学变革性工作设计中心的研究员。她还是 CEPAR（人口老龄化研究卓越中心）研究员。她的研究兴趣包括工作设计、工作重塑、工作未来、资历过高和老龄化。莎伦·K·帕克 (Sharon K. Parker) 是科廷大学约翰·科廷杰出教授、澳大利亚研究委员会获奖者、变革性工作设计中心主任。她是澳大利亚社会科学院和工业与组织心理学会的院士。她是 SMART 模型的创建者和 Thrive at Work 计划的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Today’s leaders are pushing to increase employee engagement and decrease turnover but face a harsh reality: widespread employee burnout. To fight it, managers need to offer employees more healthy and meaningful work. In surveys conducted in the United States by Gallup in 2022, 40% of employees reported that their [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Parker-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>当今的领导者正在努力提高员工敬业度并减少人员流动，但面临着严峻的现实：员工普遍倦怠。为了应对这一问题，管理者需要为员工提供更健康、更有意义的工作。盖洛普 2022 年在美国进行的调查显示，40% 的员工表示，他们的工作对他们的心理健康产生了负面影响，约 30% 的员工表示，他们经常感到倦怠。此外，到 2022 年，美国员工敬业度创下七年来的最低点，盖洛普调查显示，只有 32% 的员工表示自己敬业度很高，17% 的员工表示自己在 2022 年积极脱离敬业度<a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">。1</a>在全球范围内，员工缺乏敬业度估计会给雇主带来损失7.8 万亿美元——相当于全球国内生产总值的 11%。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>脱离和工作压力的根本原因往往在于组织如何设计人们的工作。数十年的广泛研究一致认为，糟糕的工作设计与员工的负面结果有关，包括精神紧张、高流动率、工作不满、生产力下降和学习障碍。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>现在许多公司都在努力做得更好。</p><p></p><p>不幸的是，我们的研究表明，许多管理者缺乏设计高质量工作的必要理解。这就是 ChatGPT 等人工智能技术可以发挥关键作用的地方，它可以弥合管理者的知识差距并帮助设计对员工和组织都有利的高质量工作。然而，对于管理者来说，首先了解使用 ChatGPT 进行工作设计的利弊非常重要。让我们来探讨一下我们的研究为管理者带来的一些启示。</p><h3>管理挑战：平凡且没有成就感的工作</h3><p>哪些因素决定了一份工作是否高质量？ <a href="https://www.futureofworkinstitute.com.au/smart-workdesign">SMART 工作设计模型</a>是 Sharon K. Parker 创建的一个框架，它将高质量工作定义为具有<em>刺激性的</em>工作（具有任务多样性和发展新技能的机会的工作），并融合了<em>掌握</em>（例如角色清晰度和工作反馈） ，是<em>代理性的</em>（例如工作自主性和变革参与），是<em>关系性的</em>（可以获得社会支持和积极的团队合作），并且是<em>可容忍的</em>（具有可管理的工作时间和合理的时间压力水平）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>尽管设计良好的工作有很多好处，但设计​​不当的工作仍然普遍存在。根据盖洛普 2019 年优秀就业调查，只有 40% 的美国人从事具有 SMART 特征的工作。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>另一方面，16% 的人发现自己的工作缺乏基本的 SMART 特征，44% 的人的工作只具备一些令人满意的 SMART 特征。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>当今的管理者缺乏对工作设计的了解可能可以解释这一发现。我们最近进行的一项研究探讨了人们如何为他人设计工作。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>在线模拟（模拟 1）的参与者被要求设计一个行政工作角色。半职工作全部由四项复印和归档任务组成。参与者被要求从 11 项任务列表中选择 4 项额外任务来全职完成这项工作，其中包括 5 项重复性复印和归档任务以及 6 项更有意义和有趣的任务，例如问候访客或帮助同事安排会议。</p><p></p><p>参与者的评分范围为 0 到 4，分数越高表明创造了更具刺激性的工作设计。近一半（45%）的大学管理专业学生和从事公共服务行业的专业人士/经理倾向于从事重复性和单调的工作，这表明在高质量工作设计方面存在知识差距。</p><p>在第二次模拟（模拟 2）中，参与者被要求扮演经理的角色并解决四种场景中的劳动力问题。在每种情况下，工作角色设计显然都很糟糕。为了解决这些问题，参与者评估了他们采取策略的可能性，其中包括“修复工人”方法（将问题归咎于员工）和“修复糟糕的工作设计”方法（承认质量差）。工作设计。</p><p>例如，在一种情况下，一名仓库工作人员尽管经常跑去取货，但在收集产品并将其运送到调度方面始终未能满足 50% 的规定期限。虽然大多数参与者关注的是改进工作设计的选择（例如，“让员工及其同事参与审查，以确定可以更好地组织他们的工作的方式”或“重新组织工作，以便任务不需要”），令人惊讶的是，数量惊人的参与者（40％）仍然选择了旨在固定工人的策略（例如“谨慎观察该人的行为，看看他们移动的速度有多快”）。这些发现证实了我们的发现，即管理者和员工缺乏工作设计知识。</p><h3>生成式人工智能可以提出强有力的工作设计</h3><p>在研究的下一阶段，我们研究了 ChatGPT 等人工智能驱动的工具是否可以帮助管理者做得更好。简短的回答是：ChatGPT 有潜力增强工作设计中的决策。然而，对于管理者来说，了解 ChatGPT 能做什么、不能做什么很重要。</p><p>我们使用 ChatGPT 为行政工作设计模拟（模拟 1）做出假设的工作设计决策。我们运行模拟任务 20 次，每次都在 ChatGPT 中使用新的独立聊天会话并提供相同的提示。生成式人工智能模型始终从提供的列表中选择丰富任务，在创造有趣且有意义的工作方面优于学生和专业人士/经理。 ChatGPT 的表现与工作设计专家的表现相似。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>不同组的工作设计决策得分</h4><p class="caption">当模拟 1 的参与者被要求设计行政工作角色时，45% 的参与者大多选择为工人分配重复且单调的任务（评分从 0 到 4 表示参与者选择的丰富任务的数量）。当模拟 2 的参与者被要求解决四个设计不良的工作角色中的问题时，40% 的人选择了旨在修复工人而不是不良设计的策略（得分从 1 到 5 表示参与者将采用这些策略的程度，1=极不可能，5=极有可能）。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023_1005_Parker_Fig1-1.png" alt="不同组的工作设计决策得分"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>然后，我们要求 ChatGPT 处理模拟 2，解决四种管理人员场景（包括上面提到的理论仓库工人），从列表中选择策略。在每种情况下，ChatGPT 始终选择旨在修复工作设计的策略（有利于员工福祉、积极性和绩效的良好策略），而不是专注于修复员工的策略。与模拟 1 一样，ChatGPT 在专注于解决劳动力问题的工作设计方面优于学生、经理和专业人士。</p><p>然而，ChatGPT 在模拟 2 中的得分不如工作设计专家，这表明需要谨慎对待。例如，在一次针对错过最后期限的仓库工人的会议中，ChatGPT 总体得分为 4，但选择了“当员工和她的同事按时完成任务时，我会给他们奖金”的策略，这忽略了该角色的不合理时间分配。</p><p></p><h3>一大教训：具体提示是关键</h3><p>为了进一步评估 ChatGPT 独立生成建议的能力，我们运行了模拟 2 工作设计任务，但没有提供多项选择解决方案列表。我们在关闭聊天记录功能的新帐户和独立的新聊天中运行每个测试，以便 ChatGPT 的输出不会受到之前输入的影响。</p><p>首先，结果令人担忧。当我们简单地指示人工智能模型在错过最后期限的情况下“提供有效的策略来解决问题”时，ChatGPT 倾向于通过尝试修复工人并创建老式的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-progressive-roots-of-management-science/">泰勒主义工作系统方法来</a>解决问题，例如进行计时和运动研究。例如，ChatGPT 提出了时间管理技能和额外培训等解决方案，以帮助我们命名为 Karen 的仓库员工提高绩效（例如，“重点提高 Karen 在仓库中查找和收集物品的速度和准确性”） 。它还建议提供绩效反馈和激励措施，以激励凯伦更快地行动（例如，“通过将绩效与奖励联系起来，将鼓励凯伦专注于提高速度和效率”）。这些解决方案中的每一个都隐含地假设问题是工人的动机或能力而不是工作设计。</p><p>在得知这种开放式方法并非最佳选择后，我们接下来指示 ChatGPT 使用特定提示来解决相同的场景：“考虑为 Karen 设计一份高质量的工作”； “考虑凯伦的健康、幸福、动力、满意度和工作意义”；和“考虑凯伦的工作设计。”然后，AI 模型提供了与改进 Karen 的工作设计相关的解决方案，包括以下内容：</p><ul><li>审查时间分配和工作量以设定切合实际的时间目标。</li><li>让凯伦参与决策过程，并寻求她对改善工作的意见。</li><li>提供支持性反馈和认可，以提高员工满意度和积极性。</li><li>提供充足的培训和技能发展机会，以增强信心和参与度。</li></ul><p>这些策略将提升凯伦的 SMART 工作设计特征，提高需求的容忍度，增强能动性，提高掌握程度，并使工作更具刺激性。</p><p> ChatGPT 还提出了一些解决方案，例如营造支持性的工作环境、鼓励团队支持和协作、提供职业发展机会以及促进工作与生活的平衡。这些解决方案都与工作设计和幸福感的广泛研究相吻合，将使工作变得“更智能”，从而培养出更健康、更有生产力的员工。</p><p>我们从 ChatGPT 的这个特殊实验中了解到，生成式人工智能可以做出有价值的工作设计决策，但管理者需要提供明确的指示，优先考虑员工的结果。例如，要求ChatGPT“设计高质量的工作”而不是简单地要求“良好的工作设计”可以产生更相关和有效的策略。因此，为了提高ChatGPT生成的策略建议的质量，管理者需要在问题提示中提及具体的、理想的目标，例如高质量的工作；员工的健康、福祉和积极性；和工作的意义。</p><p></p><p>好消息是：不经常使用 ChatGPT 的经理可以学习如何通过 ChatGPT 工具本身编写有效的提示。例如，当被问及“如何制作结构良好且清晰的提示来有效应对工作设计挑战时？” ChatGPT 提供了有关如何编写有效提示的分步指南。 ChatGPT 建议我们确定核心问题并具体化——可以通过使用提示将建议应用于工作设计，例如“设计高质量的工作，增强销售团队的积极团队互动和协作”或“设计有意义的工作”促进员工接受工作中的技术变革。”</p><p>实验还表明，有效的提示需要进行审查和测试。难以编写有效的 ChatGPT 提示的经理可以通过使用诸如“以下提示旨在从工作设计专家的角度向 ChatGPT 寻求建议的提示”来提高自己的技能。请分析并提出改进建议，以便从 ChatGPT 获得可行且实用的建议。”在这种情况下，ChatGPT 将提供更具体的建议，以推动更高质量的输出。</p><h3>给管理者的五个教训</h3><p>为了解决工作角色设计不佳及其有害影响这一普遍问题，采用创新解决方案至关重要。根据我们的研究，ChatGPT 已成为一种很有前途的人工智能工具，可以帮助管理者设计更健康、更高效的工作。但它不是万能药，需要明智地使用。我们对管理者的建议：</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 无法替代培训。</strong>管理者需要<em>意识到</em>，糟糕的工作设计可能会产生员工问题，而工作设计反过来又会影响员工的福祉、积极性和工作意义。这意味着，在使用ChatGPT设计更好的工作之前，管理者仍然需要进行工作设计理念的基础培训。要开始了解此主题，请参阅相关文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-well-designed-work-makes-us-smarter/">精心设计的工作如何让我们变得更聪明</a>”和<a href="https://www.smartworkdesign.com.au/">SMART 工作设计网站</a>。</p><p><strong>管理者需要获得支持，以实现创建精心设计的工作的目标。</strong>管理者需要有<em>动力</em>为员工创造更好的就业机会。这意味着管理者本身需要将创建健康的员工工作角色视为合法且重要的责任，而不是只关注底线。例如，如果管理者纯粹根据生产力成就获得晋升，他们就没有太多动力为团队设计 SMART 工作。</p><p><strong>管理者本身也需要健康的工作。</strong>管理者需要足够的时间来关注员工的工作设计得如何。这意味着管理者自己的工作必须是<em>可以忍受的</em>，并且没有过多的时间压力。</p><p></p><p><strong>管理者需要学习ChatGPT提示技巧。</strong>应鼓励管理者使用生成式人工智能来帮助应对工作设计挑战，但他们需要关于如何有效使用它的清晰而全面的指导。例如，管理者在向 ChatGPT 寻求工作设计建议时需要具体并提及员工福祉和动机等目标。</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 将增强而不是取代人们设计更好的工作。</strong>与模拟不同，现实生活中的工作设计情况通常具有模糊性和复杂性，并且存在许多可能影响结果的变量。真实情况需要对背景、人类情感、社会动态以及政治和道德考虑因素有深入的了解，所有这些对于像 ChatGPT 这样的人工智能工具来说要完全掌握都是具有挑战性的。我们建议使用 ChatGPT 作为人类管理者的<em>补充</em>，而不是<em>替代</em>它们。</p><p>通过将 ChatGPT 的建议与人类专业知识相结合，组织可以提高员工敬业度、工作满意度和整体绩效。在管理者和人工智能之间实现这种协同作用可以为工作设计和员工体验的更美好未来铺平道路。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>文化在推动变革中的作用</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonathan Knowles, B. Tom Hunsaker, and Melanie Hughes. <p>乔纳森·诺尔斯 (Jonathan Knowles) 是咨询公司 Type 2 Consulting 的创始人。 B. Tom Hunsaker 是亚利桑那州立大学雷鸟全球管理学院战略与领导力临床教授。梅兰妮·休斯 (Melanie Hughes) 是穆迪、American Eagle 和 Tribune Media 的前首席人力资源官。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Culture is often described as “how we do things around here” — a passive reflection of legacy norms and behaviors. It’s more helpful to think of culture as the nervous system of an organization. In biology, the central nervous system is the pathway by which thoughts in our brains are translated into actions by our [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Knowles-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p>文化通常被描述为“我们在这里做事的方式”——传统规范和行为的被动反映。将文化视为组织的神经系统更有帮助。在生物学中，中枢神经系统是我们大脑中的思想被肌肉转化为行动的途径，也是我们在世界上的行动经验如何更新我们的大脑对世界的理解的途径。在组织中，这意味着将文化视为一种传播机制，通过该机制，公司既可以将其预期战略传达给一线人员，又可以从现场接收有关该战略是否在市场上实现预期结果的反馈和情报。</p><p>这个神经系统的比喻阐明了企业失败的两个最常见原因背后的因素：“我们有一个伟大的战略，但未能执行它”（从中心到现场的沟通失败）或“我们的领导者包围了自己”人们害怕告诉他们业务的实际表现如何”（未能传达来自现场的重要反馈和情报）。两者都是未能建立从思想到行动再返回的有效传导机制的例子。</p><p></p><p>文化的战略方法涉及积极努力创造环境和基础设施，以促进战略和执行之间必要的信息流——将它们视为有目的的行动的补充组成部分。这些工具可以包括市政厅、客户现场访问、投标失败的事后分析、员工敬业度调查以及任何其他有助于交换有关有效（或无效）的有价值信息的机制。这些工具培育了一种情境意识和适应性的文化，使企业能够在当前环境中表现更好，并为未来的成功做好准备。</p><p></p><p>文化的某些方面是普遍受欢迎的，而另一些方面的价值则更加取决于具体情况。当 Donald Sull 和 Charles Sull 分析了 Glassdoor 上的 140 万条员工评论时，他们 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/10-things-your-corporate-culture-needs-to-get-right/">发现了有助于形成积极的企业文化的四个关键因素</a>（尊重、领导力、薪酬/福利和工作保障）。但是，当组织变革势在必行时，就需要刻意在文化中添加与环境相关的因素。</p><p>适应的重要性一直是我们之前有关<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">战略</a>、<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/effective-innovation-begins-with-strategic-direction/">创新</a>和<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-change-means-changing-how-you-lead/">领导力</a>的文章的主题。为了说明不同的变革目标如何需要不同的文化选择，我们将借鉴作者之一（梅兰妮·休斯）在其职业生涯中的企业人力资源领导经验。在三个不同的公司，她首先使用三种不同的策略来确定变革需求，然后确定有效文化的特征来实施这一变革优先事项。</p><h3>确定组织的变革优先事项</h3><p>人力资源最重要但经常被忽视的职责之一是分析企业文化的哪些方面使公司能够在当前环境中表现良好，以及哪些方面抑制了公司按照公司的方式和/或按照公司的方式行事的能力。上下文所需的速度。</p><p>此过程的第一步是调查业务、部门或团队应尝试实现的变革类型。正如我们在“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">战略的本质现在是如何改变</a>”中所描述的，可以通过三种方法来进行这种改变：</p><ul><li>强化规模：细化和深化有助于提高关键利益相关者的高度相关性和竞争独特性的行动。</li><li>重新构想活动：更新用于实施当前战略的方法、渠道和工具。</li><li>重新思考方向：重新发明业务模式，以提供经济上可行的业务所需的相关性和独特性水平。</li></ul><p>基于对期望变革形式的理解，人力资源部门可以确定实现期望结果的机制，哪些员工最适合扮演变革推动者的角色（那些负责向文化注入新元素的人），以及谁可以发挥文化载体的作用（展示这些新元素如何与正在维护的文化的遗留元素相结合）。</p><p>我们借鉴<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/melaniehughes/details/experience/">Hughes 担任 Gilt Groupe 首席行政官以及 Moody&#39;s 和 Tribune Media 首席人力资源官 (CHRO) 的经验</a>，回顾了每种变革类型以及哪种工具和行动最能实现每种变革类型。</p><p></p><h4>变革类型 1：加强规模</h4><p>总部位于纽约的 Gilt Groupe 成立于 2007 年，是奢侈品闪购的先驱。 2009 年至 2012 年，休斯 (Hughes) 担任首席行政官期间，该公司处于高速增长模式：从女装扩展到男装和旅行，在日本开展业务，2011 年筹集资金估值超过 10 亿美元，积极筹划首次公开募股。 Gilt Groupe 是时尚领域公认的市场领导者和奢侈品制造商的首选合作伙伴，变革的首要任务是通过复制成功的核心业务来加强规模，即扩大使公司具有相关性和独特性的行动新类别中的模型。</p><p>核心挑战是确定如何将现有文化的创业、以增长为中心的导向与知识共享和可重复的流程结合起来，以支持扩展到多个新类别并管理其不同的发展阶段。 Two of the key enablers of this change were revised messaging by the CEO in the company&#39;s all-hands meetings and adjustments to the incentive schemes for executives and managers.</p><p> In both cases, the prior focus on growth alone was replaced by an emphasis on manageable growth, efficiency, and profitability. The CEO assumed the role of principal change agent, focusing on stories that celebrated costs avoided and efficiencies achieved, not just revenues won. The incentive programs were adjusted, with the focus on the performance of the individual businesses shifting instead to a balance of contributions to “Gilt corporate” and individual business performance. Specific individuals were identified as culture carriers because they had already demonstrated the behaviors of knowledge sharing, mentorship, and effective delegation — three key aspects of the new culture. These individuals were given increased responsibilities and promotions as visible signs of recognition (in addition to nonpublic compensation increases) to underscore the behaviors that the company now valued.</p><p> These actions paved the way for organizational changes that the previous culture would have resisted as bureaucratization infringing on the autonomy of the individual businesses. Instead, the centralization of certain services and infrastructure (such as marketing, development, finance, and recruiting) was accepted as the means to enable the businesses to scale faster.</p><h4> Change Type 2: Reimagine Activity</h4><p> The context of Hughes&#39;s most recent role, as CHRO at Moody&#39;s (2017 to 2021), was, in contrast, one in which reimagining activity was the appropriate stance, given the objective of innovating the approaches and tools being used to pursue the existing strategy. Moody&#39;s comprised a highly successful but mature ratings business and a fast-growing analytics business. There was rising cultural tension as each organization championed the merits of its approach to risk, innovation, customers, and staffing. Recognizing the incompatibility of these modes of operating, the CEO and president of each business worked with HR leadership on a program designed to evolve the corporate culture while also establishing an operating infrastructure and a performance management system specifically designed to support the needs of Moody&#39;s Analytics.</p><p> Several organizational initiatives were developed to support the change. Among them were expanding the corporate values to include elements such as speed and innovation (primarily associated with the analytics business) and to celebrate examples of those values in communications to employees and on investor calls. Leadership development programs were established to cross-train managers on the critical skills for each line of business and identify change agents who could cross-seed desired behaviors into each business. A new talent-planning process called Talent to Value identified the roles with the greatest strategic impact on each business and the skills required to perform those roles. This enabled leaders to understand which internal candidates were truly qualified for roles and where they needed to look for external talent to fill critical roles and support the new culture.</p><p> The CEO explicitly articulated a change from the previous “promote from within” culture, emphasizing the benefits of a broader and more diverse employee base to the performance of both businesses. These communications included LinkedIn posts from the CEO, signaling both internally and externally what was required to progress in the modern Moody&#39;s. This messaging was reinforced by the publicity given to new hires and internal promotions, emphasizing how these employees embodied the desired skills and traits described in the Talent to Value effort.</p><p> Reimagining these activities supported the transition of Moody&#39;s to a multibusiness firm with cultures, structures, and skills sets appropriate for each entity. The stock grew 60% in two years, reflecting a strong profit performance of the legacy Moody&#39;s ratings business combined with a higher multiple attributed to the growth potential of the analytics business.</p><h4> Change Type 3: Rethink Direction</h4><p> Hughes&#39;s time as CHRO at Tribune Media (2013 to 2016) represented an entirely different challenge. Tribune Media had gone through the largest media industry bankruptcy in US history in 2008, and as it emerged from four years of bankruptcy proceedings in 2012, the priority was to rethink its direction by establishing a business based on viable economics. A creative and action-oriented CEO was recruited for this purpose. The company adopted a strategy to spin off the legacy print journalism assets into a separate company (Tribune Publishing), invest heavily to grow the digital media and content-creation capabilities of Tribune Media, and make selective acquisitions in the broadcast business to build the necessary economies of scale.</p><p> For a business that had been beaten down by years in the bankruptcy courts and a relentless focus on cost cutting, the new strategy necessitated a complete cultural reboot. Certain behavioral norms — aversion to risk, a focus on the short term, reluctance to take on additional responsibility — had become ingrained during the bankruptcy years and needed to be reset. The CEO and Hughes recruited a new executive team ready to establish the type of culture required to support the new strategy. They, in turn, brought in new leaders and employees to start to transform their teams. The leadership team worked together to identify “Trib traits” — the set of values and competencies that would encourage new behaviors, which included “curious and courageous,” “competing with passion,” and “exemplifying leadership.”</p><p></p><p> The Trib traits became the blueprint for recruiting new employees and for a new performance evaluation and rewards system. The latter now tied fully 50% of managerial bonuses to the demonstration of competencies, to emphasize that how things got done was as important as the outcome. (Historically, bonuses had been entirely based on financial results.) This shift was reinforced in newly established televised town halls, where the CEO spoke about doing the <em>right</em> thing rather than doing the <em>thing</em> right to give employees the license to venture away from the safe path and experiment with new ways of operating — as was appropriate for a business emerging from bankruptcy and competing in the dynamic environment of digital media and entertainment.</p><p> As the above cases illustrate, the enablers of cultural change vary according to the type of change that an organization is trying to achieve. The table below summarizes how the type of change needed informs a consistent set of culture actions to be taken. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive </h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Culture Impact Area</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reinforce Magnitude</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reimagine Activity</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Rethink Direction</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>Definition of strategic goal</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine and double down on sources of existing advantage</p></td><td><p> Adapt approach to deliver greater value</p></td><td><p> Identify a new basis for a viable business model</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of communication</strong></p></td><td><p> Reaffirm existing beliefs; encourage consistency</p></td><td><p> Evolve core beliefs; encourage experimentation</p></td><td><p> Revisit core beliefs; encourage new ways of thinking</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Performance and risk metrics</strong></p></td><td><p> Reinforce current market position; minimize risk</p></td><td><p> Experiment around the core; be selective in terms of risk tolerance</p></td><td><p> Reinvent; iterate rapidly; have a high risk tolerance</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Changes to organizational structure</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine to optimize efficiency and minimize disturbance</p></td><td><p> Realign to support new products and customer priorities</p></td><td><p> Restructure to focus on areas where a sustainable advantage can be achieved</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Priority for talent acquisition</strong></p></td><td><p> Deepen expertise</p></td><td><p> Expand expertise</p></td><td><p> Redefine expertise</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of learning and development</strong></p></td><td><p> Emphasize skills for leading and delivering operational excellence</p></td><td><p> Make focused investments in leadership and high-demand technical skills</p></td><td><p> Make an enterprisewide investment in culture change</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Basis for rewards and recognition</strong></p></td><td><p> Incentivize growth and efficiency initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize redesign initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize novel and disruptive initiatives/outcomes </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Knowles_Culture_Essay_Table_mobile-fallback-1.png" alt="Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p></p><p></p><p> Culture is the enabler of business strategy. It either facilitates or inhibits the speed and reliability with which information flows within an organization, determining how well the company understands and responds to its environment.</p><p> Businesses are collaborative human endeavors that require the harnessing of the skills and shared beliefs of the individuals within them. Culture is the nervous system that promotes cohesion and integrates strategy and execution into purposeful doing. While certain aspects of a healthy culture might be universal (respect for individuals, ethical leadership, fair rewards for work performed), the effective management of culture is also contextual — involving the deliberate introduction of elements that enable the business to evolve to reflect the need for reinforcing magnitude, reimagining activity, or rethinking direction.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Burden of Proof for Corporate Sustainability Is Too High</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) is a globally recognized expert on how to build resilient, profitable companies that help people and planet thrive. He is coauthor of <cite>Net Positive: How Courageous Companies Thrive by Giving More Than They Take</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people, respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of Fortune magazine asserted that companies were “swapping exuberance for efficiency” and pointed out that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Winston-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce<a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3685936/tech-layoffs-in-2023-a-timeline.html?page=2">cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people</a> , respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> magazine asserted that companies were “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-finance-crypto-making-seismic-110000390.html">swapping exuberance for efficiency</a> ” and pointed out that they had collectively laid off more than 150,000 people since January. (By August, that number was up to <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/09/07/tech-industry-layoffs-2023/">nearly 225,000</a> .)</p><p> An article in that same issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> focused on Salesforce, asking whether there was a conflict between the company&#39;s layoffs and CEO Marc Benioff&#39;s commitment to empathetic leadership and sustainability. That&#39;s a fair question, but the article went further, declaring that Benioff&#39;s dilemma could “serve as a referendum on the whole <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/m-willing-bullets-marc-benioff-153000800.html">model of stakeholder capitalism</a> .” If that&#39;s true, then why aren&#39;t the collective woes across the tech industry, which another article declared “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-150-000-people-let-153000599.html">a confession of bad management</a> ,” a referendum on <em>shareholder</em> capitalism?</p><p></p><p> There&#39;s a serious inconsistency in how the business world sees sustainability. Whenever a company that prioritizes sustainability gets in trouble, people say the leaders took their eye off the ball. But when companies stumble while pursuing the “normal” strategy of maximizing profits above all — which is, by the way, wrongly implied to be the opposite of sustainability — their troubles are rarely blamed on that single-minded focus.</p><p></p><h3> Sustainability as Scapegoat</h3><p> The burden of proof on sustainability became crystal clear when, in 2021, activist investors and the board ousted the CEO of Danone, the French multinational food company, in a dramatic move that made headlines across the world. CEO Emmanuel Faber had faced harsh criticism for the company&#39;s financial performance versus that of its competitors, but here&#39;s how some of the press approached it at the time: The <cite>Financial Times</cite> editorial board&#39;s take: “ <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/668d9544-28db-4ad7-9870-1f6671623ac5">Danone: A Case Study in the Pitfalls of Purpose</a> .” <cite>Forbes</cite> : “ <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/frankvangansbeke/2021/03/20/sustainability-and-the-downfall-of-danone-ceo-faber-12/?sh=7dc8835b16de">Sustainability and the Downfall of Danone CEO Faber</a> .” <cite>Time</cite> : “ <a href="https://time.com/6121684/emmanuel-faber-danone-interview/">A Top CEO Was Ousted After Making His Company More Environmentally Conscious. Now He&#39;s Speaking Out</a> .”</p><p> Unfortunately, this two-year-old story has legs. I was recently speaking to leaders of a big consumer packaged goods company, and one of the execs expressed skepticism about sustainability, pointing to what had happened at Danone (and at Unilever, which has also <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-under-pressure-show-sustainability-focus-is-good-business-2022-02-09/">taken heat about its sustainability focus</a> ).</p><p> The finger-pointing at sustainability is, if anything, accelerating in some circles; to use modern parlance, it just triggers some people. Without diving into the morass of the anti-ESG movement, I think it&#39;s clear that some prominent voices will blame sustainability for <em>any</em> corporate trouble. When Silicon Valley Bank went under, for example, some pundits and politicians hit the airwaves to claim, ludicrously, that it was because the company had <a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/columnist/2023/03/15/silicon-valley-bank-failure-republicans-blame-diversity-woke/11472710002/">mentioned its diversity and inclusion efforts</a> in its proxy statement.</p><p> Blaming sustainability for financial woes just rings true for most execs. But <em>why</em> ?</p><p> I believe it&#39;s about a deeply flawed base assumption: Sustainability, even as companies embrace it like never before, is still generally assumed to be a drag on earnings and to <em>always</em> add to costs. But that&#39;s never been remotely true.</p><p> The idea that sustainability is a trade-off or is incompatible with financial responsibility is false. Some of the companies most famously focused on sustainability, such as Walmart and Ikea, are relentless cost cutters and have fit their environmental and social efforts into that strategy. These companies know that sustainability not only can cut expenses but also slashes risk, drives innovation and revenues, and builds intangible or brand value. It&#39;s not true that running a business in a sustainable fashion always costs more, although new ways of operating don&#39;t always pay off quickly. And, to be fair, the sustainability community — and that includes me — has sometimes implied as much.</p><p></p><p> But let&#39;s go back to the burden on sustainability and try a quick mental exercise. If a focus on sustainability causes failures, then are the companies that focus only on shareholder profits always successful? Of course not. The failure rate for companies is high: Roughly 50% of <a href="https://www.chamberofcommerce.org/small-business-statistics/">small businesses close</a> within about five years. Even among the Fortune 500 giants, failure is the norm. Of the original list in 1955, <a href="https://www.aei.org/carpe-diem/fortune-500-firms-1955-v-2017-only-12-remain-thanks-to-the-creative-destruction-that-fuels-economic-prosperity/">only 60</a> of them survived until the late 2010s. Obsessing over shareholder value didn&#39;t save 88% of the biggest companies.</p><p> All companies, at some point, emphasize a strategic focus. Consider a sample list of core strategies — some fads, some lasting additions to the management arsenal — that companies have embraced across a century: mass production, specialization, product differentiation, quality, safety, customer satisfaction, employee happiness, cost cutting, reengineering, agile and lean development, data-driven decision-making. Companies that embraced these things often outcompeted others, but none of those core strategies was ever the <em>only</em> factor in their success.</p><p> Companies rise and fall for diverse reasons. The most celebrated success stories, like those profiled in the influential book <cite><a href="https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/bhag.html">Built to Last</a></cite> , can also face scrutiny over time. Decline occurs when companies fail to adapt to sectoral transformations (Blockbuster), neglect technological shifts (Kodak), or lose brand relevance when they fail to attract younger consumers as their core audience ages (a fate shared by numerous apparel and consumer packaged goods brands).</p><p> So, in that context, what really happened with Danone? Is it possible that sustainability was the problem?当然。 But perhaps it was something more nuanced. In his book <cite><a href="https://www.harpercollinsleadership.com/books/purpose-profit/ ">Purpose &amp; Profit</a></cite> , Harvard professor George Serafeim analyzed how Danone was doing at the time of the CEO&#39;s ouster and found that the company was underperforming peers not just on financial outcomes but also on <em>sustainability</em> outcomes: The intentions and plans were solid, but the results lagged. Serafeim concluded, “Maybe Danone is underperforming not in spite of its focus on impact but because it&#39;s failing to generate enough impact.” Whether this conclusion is correct is the right debate to be having rather than simply chalking up the company&#39;s problems to sustainability.</p><h3> Stop the Blame Game</h3><p> The good news is that sustainability must now be mainstream or attention-seekers wouldn&#39;t find it worth attacking. It&#39;s becoming core to how business is done, with evidence everywhere — signs like increased regulation and transparency demands from stakeholders, sustainability reports issued by nearly every large company, and countless courses added to business school curricula globally.</p><p></p><p> Given how widespread sustainability efforts are now, perhaps it&#39;s time to do something paradoxical. Could we make sustainability in business more important by lowering the intensity of focus? This does not mean going light on the issues sustainability is grounded in — like climate change and inequality, which are, quite literally, deadly serious — but instead just turning down the heat. Can we normalize sustainability and stop blaming it for anything that goes wrong at companies with a purpose and vision? And can we stop crediting it for being the only factor that drives some companies&#39; success? I&#39;m willing to stipulate, for example, that sustainability darling Patagonia also succeeds because it has <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/travel-backpacks/patagonia-black-hole-mini-mlc-travel-backpack-review-a1476285024/">kick-ass products</a> that last a long time and a culture that <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Overview/Working-at-Patagonia-EI_IE5474.11,20.htm">attracts employees</a> and customers.</p><p> It&#39;s time to truly embed sustainability into business and treat it like any other unquestioned part of operations (think HR, R&amp;D, and safety). Sustainability need not be the scapegoat or the hero. It can just be a powerful way to do business and stay relevant in a fast-changing world … and help society and the planet thrive.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Want More Clarity on Generative AI? Experiment Widely</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) is a professor of management practice at London Business School and founder of HSM Advisory. Her most recent book is <cite>Redesigning Work: How to Transform Your Organization and Make Hybrid Work for Everyone</cite> (MIT Press, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT’s release in November 2022, more than 1 million people (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Gratton-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT&#39;s release in November 2022, <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/12/05/technology/chatgpt-ai-twitter.html">more than 1 million people</a> (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a predictor of growth, then the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.de/~/media/mckinsey/locations/europe%20and%20middle%20east/deutschland/news/presse/2023/2023-06-14%20mgi%20genai%20report%2023/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier-vf.pdf">$12 billion invested in generative AI</a> in the first five months of 2023 shows the depth of commitment.</p><p> To get a sense of current momentum and direction, I ran a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=74OaRCKn92k">research webinar last month on the impact of generative AI</a> on the workplace. Some 260 executives from organizations in Australia, Europe, Japan, and the United States joined me to describe their current use of generative AI in human capital domains. What I heard is that generative AI is a top priority for many CEOs, experiments abound alongside ambiguity, and organizations are already beginning to use artificial intelligence to augment their human capital strategies. I&#39;ll share more details about those findings in a moment.</p><p></p><p> I wanted to hear directly from practitioners because it seems to me that, as with the previous era-defining event — the COVID-19 pandemic — and its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/making-sense-of-the-future/">impact on the workplace</a> , imagining what is ahead with this new technology is a tough call. As with the emergence of hybrid work and work-from-home initiatives in response to the pandemic, figuring out the right approaches to generative AI is a process replete with ambiguity, experiments, and changes of mind. In other words, it is a learning process driven both by the initiative of individuals and the strategies of organizations.</p><p> Like the response to the pandemic, debate and action around gen AI are moving fast.</p><p></p><p> Two facts are emerging. First, this is a rapidly developing technology. The size of investment gives a sense of this. So, too, does the volume of experimentation: One executive told me, “We have created a head of generative AI with a role simply to moderate and make sense of the hundreds of experiments we have running on any day.” Second, unlike previous workplace technologies, generative AI is not being positioned as a substitute for routine tasks — either analytical tasks, like keeping records or providing repetitive customer-oriented services, or manual tasks, like picking and sorting products or performing routine assembly. Instead, it&#39;s a technology with the potential to hit at the heart of nonroutine analytical work. This is knowledge work, such as forming a hypothesis, creating content, recommending medical diagnostics, or making a sales pitch. The source of this impact is generative AI&#39;s growing capacity to understand natural language. Around 25% of the total work time of knowledge workers is spent on the kinds of creative tasks that generative AI is beginning to get good at.</p><p> Yet, like during the early days of the pandemic and hybrid work, much is currently conjecture. There will certainly be pushback, changes of direction, and believers and resisters, just as there has been throughout the ongoing debate about hybrid work. There will be many experiments before leaders begin to develop their own narratives about how best to support their workers in these complex and ambiguous times.</p><p></p><h3> Experiments, Projections, and the Great Ambiguity</h3><p> The potential for generative AI to very quickly have a real impact in the workplace is fueling the attention it&#39;s getting. Consider the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier#key-insights">McKinsey report on generative AI</a> published in June 2023. McKinsey asked a group of technology experts at what point they believed generative AI would substitute for a number of human tasks. It then compared those estimates with pre-gen AI projections made in 2017 about when human performance might be achievable by technology. What is striking is the extent to which their estimated timelines have contracted. For one work task, for example — “coordination with multiple agents” — the experts in 2017 estimated a timeline of substitution that ranged from 2035 to 2058. Today, they estimate that happening from 2023 to 2035. That feels very soon. As important, in 2017, the estimate for when we&#39;d see technology achieve human-level performance for the task of “creativity” was 2030 to 2045; today, the projection is from 2025 to 2030. These dates are for tasks where technology performance is expected to match median human performance. For top-quartile human performance, the timelines are pushed out somewhat.</p><p> How do we make sense of this? What I learned from observing the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-increase-collaborative-productivity-in-a-pandemic/">impact of the pandemic on work</a> is that watching closely and asking questions of people in the field about their current lived reality is a useful practice. So my Sept. 19 webinar was essentially a listening process. Many executives came from human capital functions, so their interest was primarily in the people side of their business.</p><p> I began by asking where generative AI currently sits on the leadership agenda. Over half of attendees (52%) agreed with the statement “It is a CEO priority where leadership teams are discussing impact.” Only 13% said “It is not yet on the agenda in any meaningful way.” This is a topic that is definitely consuming bandwidth at the top levels of organizations across the world.</p><p></p><p> Generative AI is at the top of leaders&#39; agendas — but what about the scope of debate? What issues are coming forward as people talk through its consequences? For the webinar, I focused on a central aspect of this question: machines and creativity. The technologists in the McKinsey panel estimated that human creativity will be achieved by generative AI within the time span of 2025 to 2030, but what did this group of leaders believe? This, for me, is an important question because the McKinsey panelists are technology experts. I have a hunch that people like them will overestimate technological progress, whereas people like me (psychologists) will overestimate human progress.</p><p> What is fascinating is the lack of agreement among webinar attendees about whether they think human creativity at the top quartile will be achieved by gen AI from 2023 to 2030: Just 10% strongly agreed, while 34% agreed, 22% neither agreed or disagreed, 30% disagreed, and 4% strongly disagreed. I ran a Menti (a quick survey at the website Mentimeter) to collect participants&#39; real-time thoughts and asked why they had come to their conclusions. Within seconds, more than 80 comments had emerged: Those who agreed pointed out that creativity can be broken down into logical steps; that creativity sits on a lot of data; that prompts will be more important than AI; and that use cases, such as songs, already demonstrate creativity. Those who disagreed described how generative AI would augment, not substitute for, creative people and asserted that creativity was about empathy and vulnerability, that humans can generate new ideas, while AI pulls from the past, and that governments will provide regulation. Those who did not know said there are simply too many unknown unknowns.</p><p> For me, the takeaway here is the sheer richness of conversation and variance in opinions about generative AI. These are debates we need to be open about and continue to have.</p><p> I wondered, of course, how generative AI is currently being experimented with and used. My interest is in the human capital agenda and how generative AI will impact the everyday experiences of workers. One of the “promises” of AI, according to the McKinsey report, is a productivity boost from the automation of a wide variety of activities. For knowledge workers, this will come by technology either substituting for or augmenting tasks such as creating connections, retrieving stored data, personalizing content, automating activities, increasing the speed of response, and collaborating.</p><p> I asked about the current velocity of the use of generative AI in three human capital domains: talent development (like recruitment, induction, and career management), productivity (like skills training and managing collaboration), and change management (like internal knowledge management). I was interested in the current use of generative AI in each domain and the use cases. Of course, the data set of attendees comprised self-selected people who had an interest in generative AI, but still, what is clear is that there are many, many experiments currently underway.</p><p></p><p> The human capital domain with the greatest reported use of generative AI right now is “internal knowledge management.” Forty-six percent of attendees said they are experimenting in this sphere, with use cases such as creating communications, conducting market research analysis, finding resources and competencies, and engaging in employee listening. Almost as many attendees (44%) reported using gen AI for recruitment, with use cases such as creating job advertisements, developing simple approval flows, and onboarding new hires. About a third of attendees (34%) said they&#39;re using gen AI for skills training, with use cases that include self-directed learning, the creation of learning content, and virtual reality-based training. And 23% said they&#39;re using the technology for assessment and feedback, with use cases such as developing bespoke assessments, improving performance feedback, designing career paths, and creating chatbots for employees.</p><p> I feel that what I captured in this research webinar is a sense of the sheer depth of conversation and experimentation taking place right now across the world. How to think about and use generative AI is being debated in the C-suite as use cases are being created and tough questions (like the relationship between machines and creativity) are being debated. For organizations to be aligned with this emerging narrative, it is imperative that they experiment freely and observe closely.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sound Business: The Promise of Audio Machine Learning Technologies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mark Purdy. <p>Mark Purdy ( <a href="https://twitter.com/mjpurdyecon">@mjpurdyecon</a> ) is managing director of Purdy &amp; Associates, an independent economics and technology research company.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Purdy-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or as engineers testing the safety of a vehicle or machine.</p><p> But until recently, the systematic analysis of sounds in dynamic situations — a busy train station, a shopping mall, or an urban park, for example — has been difficult due to the sheer number of complex acoustic signals interacting at once. But this is now changing, thanks to major advances in sensor technology and deep learning algorithms that can harvest enormous quantities of acoustic input and rapidly extract key information.</p><p></p><p> Two branches of sound-related machine learning are emerging: one focused on the detection and analysis of sounds and the other on the AI-powered creation of sounds. Both have significant potential for business and societal value creation. In fact, according to one estimate, the <a href="https://www.astuteanalytica.com/industry-report/audio-ai-recognition-market">global market for AI audio-recognition technologies</a> is set to more than triple, from $4.1 billion in 2021 to $14.1 billion by 2030.</p><p> Deep learning algorithms are now being used to pioneer innovations across a diverse range of industries and sectors, such as these applications of sound detection and analysis:</p><p> <strong>Commercial and household security.</strong> Every year, US businesses and consumers spend billions of dollars protecting buildings and other physical assets. Smart home devices, such as Amazon&#39;s Echo, already use AI-driven voice recognition technology to authenticate different users and provide personalized entertainment and shopping experiences. But now AI systems&#39; sensors and deep learning algorithms can analyze nonvoice ambient sounds from every part of an office, a factory, or a military facility, distinguishing between innocuous sounds and those that may indicate an emerging threat, such as breaking glass.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Health care.</strong> AI sound technologies could transform many areas of health care, particularly by enabling low-cost, rapid diagnoses of diseases in their early stages. In health care, they could be used to provide real-time measurements for an array of biometric data, such as heart rate, blood pressure, respiration rate, and stress level. Deep learning has been used to extract and classify the <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34433880/">“crackles” and “wheezes”</a> of different lung diseases. <a href="https://www.cochl.ai/">Cochl</a> , a South Korean startup, is pioneering AI applications to rapidly identify health problems based on the coughs and sneezes of patients. Such early-warning systems could prove to be pivotal in the fight against COVID-19 and future virus outbreaks.</p><p> <strong>Hearables.</strong> Acoustic deep learning technologies are being pioneered in the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/03/2681513/0/en/Exploring-the-Global-Hearable-Market-Size-Is-Estimated-to-Exceed-96-53-Billion-by-2030-At-an-Exponential-Growth-Rate-of-16-74-Revenue-and-Market-Share-Projections-from-2022-to-2030.html">“hearables” market</a> — which includes headphones, earphones, and other listening devices — to improve people&#39;s listening experience. Such technologies can <a href="https://edtechmagazine.com/higher/article/2022/01/hearables-combine-machine-learning-and-microchips-smart-listening">screen out unwanted noise</a> or alert users to potential dangers, such as when someone is wearing earphones while jogging near traffic. Machine learning algorithms can be used to curate listening content to different contexts, such as by playing more relaxing or softer sounds when breathing signals indicate signs of stress, or more stirring content when the user is exercising.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Retail and leisure industries.</strong> Machine learning technologies can now recognize individuals through the sounds of their <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1809.08783.pdf">footsteps</a> by isolating these distinctive footfall echoes from background noises and the sounds of other pedestrians. Sound-based gait-recognition technologies offer significant advantages over other surveillance systems, given that they work even in poor lighting conditions and are less intrusive than facial recognition, computer vision, or biometric identification systems.</p><p> One of the biggest potential applications of this technology is in footfall-intensive industries such as retail. Sound-based footfall recognition can be used to recognize returning customers and help identify linger points on the shopper&#39;s journey — places where they pause to compare different products or respond to particular discounts or promotions — or pinpoint the time sensitivity of customers at different times of the day or week, based on the rapidity of footsteps.</p><p> <strong>Predictive maintenance and early-warning systems.</strong> Deep learning algorithms can analyze acoustic signals such as noise pressure and reverberations from machines and engine parts to assess wear and tear and predict when a particular part is likely to need replacing. NASA has used sound-sensing algorithms to monitor the functioning of equipment aboard the <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/research/experiments/explorer/Investigation.html?#id=7860">International Space Station</a> . Deep learning algorithms are being used to classify underwater acoustic signals to potentially develop an early-warning system for <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-021-02483-w">deep-sea earthquakes and tsunamis</a> .</p><p> <strong>Marketing and media content production.</strong> Speech-to-text technologies have been around for some time, but the reverse is now happening with the growth of AI-powered text-to-speech or <a href="https://www.cs.unc.edu/~yipin/pub/cvpr2018.pdf">video-to-sound technologies</a> . <a href="https://audiostack.ai/">AudioStack</a> , a UK-based startup, provides AI-enabled audio creation, drawing on a database of more than 600 voices in more than 60 languages. Use cases include generating audio ads with different regional nuances, music, or voice tones, or generating synthetic or cloned voices for podcasts or narrated news flashes based on textual content. The algorithm that <a href="https://deepzen.io/">DeepZen</a> uses for artificial voice creation from text is able to infer different emotional tones from the content, such as excitement, enthusiasm, or comfort. <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2002.10981.pdf?utm_source=thenewstack&utm_medium=website&utm_campaign=platform">AutoFoley</a> was developed to replicate the role of Foley artists, who add audio effects — such as the gallop of a horse or footsteps on a staircase — to movies. Applications like these have huge potential in industries such as gaming, marketing, and publishing, where <a href="https://speechify.com/blog/what-is-the-voice-over-actor-market-size">global demand for voiceovers</a> is forecast to grow by 9% per year to reach $2.3 billion by 2026.</p><h3> Recommendations for Business Leaders</h3><p> The rise of AI-based sound detection and creation will raise several challenges for businesses, especially in the intellectual property arena. To capitalize on the opportunities and mitigate the risks, business leaders should consider these recommendations:</p><p> <strong>Understand and protect your sonic assets.</strong> Most large companies will trademark or register a well-known jingle or catchphrase associated with their products or services, but in a world of AI-based sonification, businesses will also need to carefully assess the sonic print of their entire product portfolios — the distinctive whir of a washing machine or vacuum cleaner, the signature ignition of a sports car, the pop of a soda can opening. Counterfeiting of sounds will become a growing problem that businesses will need to prepare for.</p><p></p><p> <strong>“Sonify” the product experience.</strong> Businesses will pay increasing attention to the sonic signatures of their products, either to diminish cacophonous elements (such as a noisy clothes dryer) or to enhance aesthetically pleasing sounds (such as the tick-tock of a <a href="https://www.soundoflife.com/blogs/design/product-sonification-elevating-the-consumer-s-experience-via-the-beauty-of-sound-engineering">car&#39;s turn indicator</a> ). In the future, manufacturers could incorporate sonic signatures that track the product life cycle — for example, by varying a sound profile from a consumer durable as its components start to wear out. Businesses of all types will need to make sonic signatures a core part of user interface design, by identifying both the right functional and informational sounds for different uses and contexts, and by combining these with visual and other sensory elements.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prompt for sound.</strong> Generative AI systems — large language models capable of creating and synthesizing text, sounds, speech, images, and code — are increasingly enabling businesses to create completely new sounds and sonic combinations, or to combine audio with video, text or images to create new product campaigns. With a single prompt, marketers will be able to create an advertising tune for a new brand of ice cream, turn a wordy blog or product description into a music video, or alter a product jingle to make it more appealing to younger or older consumers or potential customers in a new market overseas. With “prompt engineering” now becoming a major discipline in the AI and automation fields, businesses will need to train designers, marketers, and product developers to write efficient prompts for sound-based use cases, taking into account factors such as brand values, product tone of voice, intellectual property rules, and ethics.</p><p> As the saying goes, “Wisdom is the reward for a lifetime of listening.” Today, AI-powered acoustic technologies are opening up a world of sounds previously inaccessible to us. They&#39;re providing new insights and opportunities for businesses and policy makers in areas as diverse as consumer behavior, health care, urban planning, commercial security, and infrastructure management. Businesses that choose to listen to this new world, and act upon the insights, will be well positioned for future success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thorny Talent and AI Challenges Now: 5 Experts Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you’ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with MIT Sloan Management Review authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston. This distinguished group of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6uXF_DY4e0k?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you&#39;ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston.</p><p> This distinguished group of management and leadership experts from the MIT Sloan School of Management and other institutions weighed in on two questions:</p><ul><li> What are the top talent management issues for 2024?</li><li> What is a manager&#39;s role in advocating for workers in the age of AI?</li></ul><p> “AI really changes how we work; it changes how we relate to each other and how we can talk to each other,” said Christine Moser, associate professor of organization theory at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, who spoke with <cite>MIT SMR</cite> at the event.</p><p></p><p> How should forward-looking leaders adjust to those new realities? Watch the video, recorded at AOM Boston, to learn what these experts have to say about AI checks and balances, how to motivate workers, and what happens when black-box AI models meet your organizational processes.</p><p> Want to learn more about leading people in the age of AI? Read our related article, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-humans-lose-when-we-let-ai-decide/">What Humans Lose When We Let AI Decide</a> .”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>