<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 17 日星期一 11:42:49 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>反对限制股票回购的理由</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Guest, S.P. Kothari, and Parth Venkat. <p>尼古拉斯·盖斯特 (Nicholas Guest) 是康奈尔大学约翰逊管理研究生院的会计学助理教授。 SP Kothari 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院会计与金融学 Gordon Y. Billard 教授，此前曾担任该学院副院长。帕斯·文卡特 (Parth Venkat) 是阿拉巴马大学卡尔弗豪斯商学院的金融学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com Are stock buybacks as bad as they’re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Kothari-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡罗·詹巴雷西/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>股票回购真的像人们想象的那么糟糕吗？普遍存在的企业回购股票做法一直是许多政治和媒体关注的焦点。 2022 年联邦通胀削减法案包括对回购征收 1% 的消费税（拜登总统提议在 2024 年预算中将其提高至 4%）。此外，民主党高层表示有兴趣禁止高管在回购后三年内出售股票，联邦政府建议放弃回购的公司将获得优惠待遇，证券交易委员会提议大幅提高股票回购利率。回购报告的范围和频率。</p><p>迄今为止，关于股票回购的经济后果的争论往往集中在小样本或精心挑选的例子上。鉴于每年有数千家公司回购其股票，并且过去五年每年回购总额超过 5000 亿美元，我们认为有必要对回购行为进行大样本研究。我们的研究发表在<cite>《财务管理》</cite>杂志上，概述了这种做法的好处，正如其支持者所说，并提供了证据，对其批评者所称的成本提出质疑。</p><p></p><p>回购批评者通常会提出三个反对这种做法的论点。首先，他们声称股票回购使公司能够通过增加对股票的需求（从而提高股票价格）或通过夸大每股收益（EPS）来欺骗天真的投资者来操纵市场。其次，他们声称股票回购使内部人员能够通过补偿合同或以高价出售股票而受益。最后，批评者指责股票回购挤出了投资，从而牺牲了创新和长期经济增长。</p><p>与此同时，那些支持或参与股票回购的人为这种做法提供了一些理由。首先，向股东支付的股息通过减少自由现金流的潜在滥用来协调经理和股东的激励。其次，使用回购代替股息或在股息之外使用回购可以使公司在返还给股东的现金金额方面具有灵活性，能够将回购的股票奖励给员工作为股权补偿，为股东提供适度的税收优惠（自2003年股息税削减以来不太明显） ），以及向市场传达公司良好前景的能力。最后，股票回购代表自愿参与者之间按照当前市场价格进行的公开且受监管的公平交易。</p><p>鉴于监管股票回购的动力，我们希望在公共数据中可以观察到其缺点的证据。为了测试这一点，我们记录了回购趋势，并比较了回购和不回购股票的公司的交易量、股价表现、首席执行官薪酬以及公司财务活动（通过投资和盈利能力证明）。我们以两种方式对回购股票的企业进行了细分：（1）小额正回购与大额正回购（定义为低于中值与高于中值），以及（2）频繁回购者与不频繁回购者（定义为在一两个季度内回购的公司）而不是一年中的三到四个季度）。</p><p>我们对过去三十年数千家美国交易所上市公司的大样本证据表明，回购在美国是一种主流的企业金融活动，每年为股东返还数千亿美元的资本。从总体来看，我们发现这种活动既不会创造也不会破坏太多财富（也就是说，它不会导致股价发生重大变化）。此外，虽然回购与过去较高的盈利能力有关，但与首席执行官薪酬过高或投资不足无关。</p><p>随着时间的推移，回购活动总量的趋势表明，虽然回购价值迅速增长，但增长的大部分可归因于通货膨胀和市值的增加。此外，回购规模目前与股息相似，并且在相当长的一段时间内没有比股息增长得更快。然而，与股息不同，回购在公司面临压力时会急剧（且暂时）下降，这表明回购实际上为公司提供了上述支付灵活性的好处。</p><p></p><h3>仔细看看数据</h3><p>通过我们的分析，我们能够系统地解决针对股票回购的每一项批评。</p><p>首先，公司是否利用股票回购来操纵市场，通过创造过剩需求来推高股价？如果这样做，回购股票的公司的交易量应该比不回购股票的公司更高。但所有上市公司的平均交易量基本上保持相似，无论它们是否回购股票或回购股票的频率如何。事实上，近年来，不回购股票的公司的交易量大大超过了回购公司的交易量，这表明回购带来的超额交易量与其他力量相比相形见绌。</p><p>如果天真的投资者因为每股收益通胀而被诱骗购买进行回购行为的公司的股票，我们应该观察到短期价格上涨，随后长期业绩不佳。然而，无论公司是否回购股票、回购股票的强度和频率如何，我们都没有发现任何证据表明公司在回购股票的季度中表现明显优于大盘。虽然我们确实发现了一些边际证据表明，大量回购的公司在回购后的季度中表现略好，但我们没有发现未来短期或长期逆转的证据。这种表现优异的模式更符合公司利用回购来发出低估信号的情况——这对投资者有利——而不是操纵市场。</p><p></p><p>第二个批评是回购让内部人士获得不公平的利润。如果股票回购作为内部人员的寻租行为是一种普遍的、系统性的滥用行为，那么回购股票的公司的首席执行官将获得异常高的薪酬，包括工资、奖金和股权奖励的价值。使用模型生成的超额薪酬衡量标准（已在早期学术文献中经过审查），我们估计进行大量正回购的公司首席执行官的收入仅比不回购股票的公司首席执行官的收入高出 51,000 美元——从统计角度和经济角度来看，这一数字微不足道。超额工资。当我们将经常回购的公司的首席执行官与不回购的公司的首席执行官进行比较时，差异甚至更小——4,000 美元。与 CEO 数百万美元的平均薪酬相比，这些差异在经济上微不足道。令人惊讶的是，不频繁回购或回购小额正数的公司首席执行官获得的超额薪酬最少，甚至低于不回购公司的首席执行官。所有这些证据都表明公司利用回购来提高首席执行官的薪酬。</p><p>第三个也是最后一个批评是，回购降低了公司利用投资机会的能力，从而牺牲了创新和经济增长。我们发现，不回购股票的公司投资更多，但利润却明显低于回购股票的公司。频繁、大量回购的公司利润丰厚，过去一直稳定投资，并且继续进行大量投资，同时向股东返还资本。这表明盈利的公司在保持稳定的投资水平的同时回购股票，而盈利较低或亏损的公司不会（或可能无法）回购股票，而是更加密集地投资以期实现盈利。虽然可能存在一些管理不善的公司选择避免有利可图的投资，而是将资本返还给愿意的股东的孤立例子，但很难看出鼓励或激励这些经营不善的公司保留现金的指令会如何引导他们做出良好的投资。</p><p>可能受到回购规定影响的潜在利益相关者包括经理、其他员工、股东、政府和整个社会。如果公司盈利，首席执行官可以以回购或股息的形式向股东支付多余的现金，将资金保留在资产负债表上，或投资新项目。对股票回购征收少量税可能不会显着改变企业行为，并可能为政府增加少量收入。但如果税率增长得足够高，公司将选择不回购股票，而是仅通过股息支付或保留现金。在这种情况下，政府不会增加任何收入，但会实施事实上的股票回购禁令。</p><h3>回购禁令如何会适得其反</h3><p>如果公司改为只支付股息，股东将失去选择是否接受现金支付的能力，并可能面临负税收后果，因为股息作为收入征税，而资本利得通常按较低税率征税。并且只有当收益实现时。此外，该公司在困难时期将失去重要的灵活性，因为削减股息比削减回购受到的市场惩罚更大。</p><p></p><p>然而，限制股票回购的举措似乎并不是为了激励公司转向通过股息偿还股东，而是为了增加对业务的投资。有证据表明，保留现金与首席执行官做出破坏价值的决策有关，例如寻求建立帝国的合并、累积个人开支或资助宠物项目。对股票回购的限制会促使治理不善的公司的首席执行官投资于他们本来不会资助的增值项目，这似乎难以置信。</p><p></p><p>从员工的角度来看，有一些证据表明，如果雇主拥有多余的现金，工会能够更成功地进行谈判，但也有大量证据表明，限制公司筹集和分配资本的灵活性对员工不利，尤其是在经济低迷时期。建立帝国的合并也可能对员工不利，因为并购常常导致收购目标的员工被解雇以及收购公司的员工被错误分配。此外，一些回购的股票被重新发行给员工，使得任何对股东不利的行为也对持股员工不利。</p><p>总体而言，我们的结果显示，股票回购与价格操纵、回报逆转、首席执行官薪酬过高和投资不足之间不存在相关性，这使得股票回购在经济上产生重大因果影响仍然是数据背后的基础是非常难以置信的。如果公司只能依赖股息，那么它们就会失去灵活性，而且有证据表明，管理不善的首席执行官保留了现金，经常将其花在破坏价值的合并、支出或宠物项目上。旨在减少回购的政策也将减少被指控但未被观察到的不当行为，而不会给美国上市公司和其他利益相关者带来成本，这是难以置信的。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>您准备好应对下一次供应中断了吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:46:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Johnny Rungtusanatham, David A. Johnston, and Elizabeth Heichler . <p>M. Johnny Rungtusanatham 是约克大学舒立克商学院运营管理和信息系统教授以及加拿大供应链管理（一级）研究主席。 David A. Johnston 是舒立克商学院运营管理和信息系统教授，也是乔治韦斯顿有限公司可持续供应链中心的研究主席和主任。伊丽莎白·海克勒 (Elizabeth Heichler) 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>杂志的编辑总监。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Capabilities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &#8220;Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Nov. 7, 2022. Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &#8220;black swan&#8221; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently. M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>J. Rungtusanatham 和 D. Johnston，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">为下一次供应中断做好准备”</a> ，《<em>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</em> ，2022 年 11 月 7 日。</p></aside><p> COVID-19 大流行引发的供应中断让许多公司措手不及。为了应对供应链未来的“黑天鹅”威胁，管理者必须以不同的方式思考。</p><p> M. Johnny Rungtusanatham 和 David A. Johnston 研究了供应中断的触发因素和绩效后果。他们的 ADDAPT 框架可以帮助领导者更好地管理中断并维持产品流程。</p><p>在本次网络研讨会中，您将了解到：</p><ul><li>为什么传统的风险管理可能不足以为下一次灾难性的供应中断做好准备。</li><li>为什么您需要开发六种功能（预测、检测、诊断、激活、保护和跟踪）来为供应中断做好准备和管理。</li><li>您需要对业务战略、实践、流程和系统做出哪些改变才能提高供应链的弹性。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>灵活有效：混合工作场所的领导策略</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Elliott. <p>Brian Elliott 是未来论坛的执行领导者和联合创始人，这是一个研究驱动的联盟，帮助全球的高级管理人员重新构想如何将人员、流程和工具结合在一起，通过数据和对话改善工作。未来论坛是 Slack、BCG、明天管理领导力和 MillerKnoll 之间的合作伙伴关系。他是<cite>《未来如何运作：带领灵活的团队完成一生中最好的工作》</cite> （Wiley，2022 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Many leaders don’t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it’s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA02_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>许多领导者不知道如何根据结果来管理工作，而不是众所周知的“座位上的流浪者”——跟踪谁在办公室以及在办公室呆了多长时间。但在混合工作场所中，有可能拥有高绩效、健康的工作场所文化，并且人们可以灵活地工作时间和地点。只是需要以不同的方式进行管理。</p><p>这是未来论坛的 Brian Elliott 传达的信息，他在 2023 年 5 月举办的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间与乔治华盛顿大学商学院的 N. Sharon Hill 和 Atlassian 的 Julie Dervin 一起在小组中发表了演讲。</p><p>埃利奥特表示，在他的公司调查的 10,243 名知识工作者中，93% 的人表示他们希望工作时间具有灵活性。他说，那些有选择的人的<a href="https://futureforum.com/research/future-forum-pulse-winter-2022-2023-snapshot/">生产力得分比没有选择的人高出 39%</a> 。那些对工作<em>地点</em>有一定灵活性的人得分也更高（8%）。</p><p></p><p>要在员工对灵活性的渴望和组织的战略目标之间找到平衡，需要重新检查需要亲自完成的工作类型。它还可能需要同一组织内不同群体的不同工作配置，并且肯定需要不同的方法来衡量员工完成的工作。</p><p>与会者向演讲者提出的问题多于时间，埃利奥特同意在活动结束后回答一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>您如何衡量生产力？大多数员工表示，他们按照自己的时间表在家工作效率更高，但事实真是这样吗？</h6><p>这是一种异端观点：我们需要停止尝试衡量知识工作的生产力，而将所有时间和精力集中在衡量结果上。</p><p>生产力指标采用输出（发送的电子邮件、关闭的案例）并将其除以输入（活跃时间），然后根据质量调整更好的结果（重新打开的案例）。这在某种程度上可以适用于死记硬背的日常任务，随着时间的推移，这些任务会变得自动化。而且，这些指标可以被利用，人们也会利用它们——甚至包括购买<a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07VHBQQVG">鼠标摇动器</a>。正如 Atlassian 的 Dominic Price<a href="https://www.atlassian.com/blog/productivity/the-problem-with-productivity-metrics">所写</a>，“生产力一直是衡量机器和资本影响的好方法。这从来都不是衡量<em>人类</em>影响的好方法。”</p><p>在未来论坛上，我们已经涉足这一领域；我们比较了具有灵活性和不具有灵活性的人群，发现具有位置灵活性的人群的生产力得分更高，而具有日程灵活性的人群则具有更大的优势。斯坦福大学的<a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">尼克·布鲁姆（Nick Bloom）</a> 、哈佛商学院的拉杰·<a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">乔杜里（Raj Choudhury</a> ）和其他人的学术研究也表明了同样的情况。</p><p>但这是一个奇怪的问题，因为当人们在办公室时我们没有问这个问题。我们只是假设，因为人们在场，所以他们正在做一些富有成效的事情。我们都知道这不准确。</p><p>相反，让我们跳过整个混乱的过程，花时间弄清楚我们组织的目标和关键结果 (OKR)，并以一种可以按业务部门和职能向下级联到团队级别的方式来实现。从团队层面来看，很多事情都可以延伸到个人层面，以发现个人在他们所做的事情以及他们作为队友的表现方面的影响。</p><p>评估人们对团队目标的影响比较困难，但比安装更多衡量他们的投入和产出的生产力指标会让我们走得更远。</p><h6>随机碰撞似乎是推动创新的关键。在跨团队建立联系方面，您如何促进偶然性？</h6><p>联系是员工敬业度和保留率的重要组成部分，但与创新的联系充其量是虚假的。<a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4093796">多项研究</a><a href="https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=991">表明</a>，真正促成创新的是心理安全。</p><p>在我们于 2021 年进行的研究中，未来论坛发现位置（无论是完全现场、混合还是完全远程）与团队创新几乎没有相关性。相反，重要<em>的</em>是人们是否觉得自己可以提出问题以及团队是否愿意承担风险等因素——也就是说，他们是否感到心理安全。</p><p>建立联系很重要，但我们应该在组织中有意识地这样做，而不是依靠随机机会。您可以通过以下三种方式执行此操作：</p><p> <strong>1. 有意的跨团队联系。</strong>诸如开放式午餐会之类的计划，由内部专家轮流出席或主持“有问题的会议”，将其他职能部门的领导带入您的季度计划周期，并在 Slack 或 Teams 中创建公共渠道，以便根据主题分享见解（如人工智能）可以走很长的路。</p><p> <strong>2. 利用工具建立联系。</strong> Donut（一款适用于 Slack 或 Teams 的应用程序，以编程方式将团队中的个人配对）等产品有助于确保每个人都能保持联系，而不仅仅是那些在同一楼层或同一栋大楼工作的人。</p><p> <strong>3、帮助新员工建立人际网络。</strong>过去几年的一大挑战是，太多公司在雇用人员时没有重新考虑如何建立联系并了解文化。我最喜欢的建议之一来自欧洲的简柏特公司，那里的新员工会被安排在团队之外与六个人会面，无论是面对面还是在虚拟咖啡会上，每个人都应该再提供两到三个联系人。</p><p>投资新工具和流程也可以带来巨大的推动作用。在头脑风暴会议之前，像<a href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/12/using-brainwriting-for-rapid-idea-generation/">头脑风暴</a>一样思考流程：让人们有低头的空间思考一些研究结果或问题，提前写出自己的想法，然后与小组分享，同时带来更多新想法。它还降低了群体思维的可能性。</p><p></p><h6>您如何以一种鼓舞人心和包容性的方式传达这样一种期望，即人们应该每周去办公室一两天，而不是强行和独裁？</h6><p>过去两年，很多公司声称每周需要 3 天亲自办公，而实际情况是平均每周 1.5 天。这掩盖了这样一个事实：通常有一批初级员工每周来两到三天，而更多高级员工来的次数较少。</p><p>重复这一政策是行不通的，威胁要解雇那些不经常来的人也是不现实的，而且会滋生怨恨。领导层知道，一些经验更丰富、更关键的人才的加入频率较低。初级员工也知道这一点。</p><p>相反，我们所看到的工作重点是通过团队级别的协议帮助团队找出自己的节奏。例如，销售团队和工程团队的需求是不同的。销售团队最终可能会规定每周有两天是默认在办公室工作的日子，并将这些日子与更多“抬头”而不是低头的特定活动叠加在一起，例如培训课程、指导时间和一-上一个。另一方面，工程团队最终可能会在每个月中抽出一周的时间亲自进行规划、共进午餐和演示日。</p><p>鼓励高级员工每周至少有一天来参加指导课程、参加培训以及与初级员工一起喝咖啡，这比简单地告诉他们出现要更进一步。</p><p>另一个关键因素是，去办公室工作不会一直比在家工作更糟糕。人们并不总是想要免费的午餐，他们想要一个团队会议的场所，能够找到一个安静的地方来接客户电话，以及有效的 Wi-Fi。对于很多公司来说，这需要重新设计工作空间。</p><h6>管理者应该怎样做才能避免弹性工作制延续甚至夸大工作场所中现有的偏见？ “眼不见心不烦”是一个真正令人担忧的问题。</h6><p>邻近偏见和出勤主义可能带来更好的机会和回报，这是一个真正的风险。我们需要创造一个公平的竞争环境，首先要培训经理和领导者根据他们产生的结果而不是投入（办公室时间、响应速度、始终在线）来评估团队和个人的绩效。领导者及其员工合作伙伴不仅需要关注晋升和奖励周期，还需要关注他们的人才发展渠道以及谁正在获得新的、闪亮的项目。</p><p>我们与 Slack 执行团队合作，制定了一项规则，即所有高级管理人员的定期审核（例如 CMO 对新项目提案的每周审核）都完全以虚拟方式完成。这不仅有助于解决人们听不到房间另一端的谈话的常见挑战，还有助于缓解“在会议发生的房间”参加这些会议的压力，而初级员工可能每年只参加一两次。</p><h6>科技以外的许多公司和行业都存在知识型员工和需要亲自到场工作的员工（例如零售业和制造业）之间的分歧。您如何建议灵活定位，以免造成不公平的双重标准？</h6><p>办公桌（办公室）员工和无办公桌（或一线）员工之间的差异远远超出了远程工作的能力：它们包括工资、福利、设施、培训等。</p><p>无办公桌员工的人才短缺对许多公司来说是一个巨大的挑战。但我不认为答案是强迫办公桌员工回到办公室全职工作。这并不能真正解决无办公桌员工的任何问题。</p><p>这里的答案是投资于无办公桌员工的特定需求。根据<a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2022/why-deskless-workers-are-leaving-and-how-to-win-them-back">波士顿咨询集团的研究</a>，日程灵活性和选择是留住人才的首要因素。领导者正在投资一些项目，例如轮班能力以及为呼叫中心工作人员提供多种类型的日程安排。 Neiman Marcus Group 通过为销售人员提供灵活的商店和部门以及工作时间选择，将营业额减少了 20%。</p><h6>我在一家初创公司。在一家新兴公司中，随着公司的成长，管理层会非常关注工作文化。初创公司或任何企业如何在允许远程或混合模式的同时建立文化？</h6><p>我坚信文化的建立与你身在何处、墙上的标语或欢乐时光的质量无关。文化是根据员工的日常经历和你所做的决定而建立的：你作为公司的优先事项、你如何对待你的客户和员工、你资源的项目以及你奖励的对象。</p><p></p><p>也就是说，我见过一些确实有助于建立坚实基础的实践。以下是其中三个：</p><p></p><p>首先，数字优先并不意味着“永不面对面”。让人们聚集在一起，即使分布广泛，也是建设文化的重要组成部分。对于团队来说，我建议至少每季度花几天时间主要关注团队建设、社交和联系。随着初创公司的发展，这通常从每个人每季度一次变成团队每季度一次，最后每个人每年一次。</p><p>其次，弄清楚你们如何一起工作，并分享更多关于自己的信息。您的<a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/06/23/team-level-agreements/">团队级别协议</a>不应只关注人们在一起的频率，还应该涉及您的沟通方式、决策方式等。共享<a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/07/15/personal-user-manual/">个人用户手册</a>等工具也可以对建立信任文化大有帮助。</p><p>第三，在工作中创造透明度。推动文化的关键因素之一是领导力沟通，随着公司规模的扩大，在设置护栏的同时保持透明度非常重要。哪些主题对您的公司和使命最重要？我们如何彼此互动？将内部沟通从首席执行官“问我任何问题”会议扩展到知识共享的公共论坛需要时间和精力； <a href="https://slack.com/blog/transformation/a-modern-leaders-guide-to-organizational-transparency">其他人的指导</a>会有帮助。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>当不确定性很高时如何支持您的团队</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Liz Fosslien. <p>Liz Fosslien ( <a href="https://twitter.com/fosslien">@fosslien</a> ) 是工作情绪方面的专家，也是<cite>《华尔街日报》</cite>畅销书<cite>《No Hard Feelings: The Secret Power of Embracing Emotion at Work》</cite> （作品集，2019 年）和<cite>《Big Feelings: How to Be OK When》</cite>的合著者和插画家。<cite>事情不太好</cite>（作品集，2022）。她还是 Atlassian Team Anywhere 的领导团队成员，此前曾担任 Humu 的内容和传播主管。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[“My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don’t really know what’s going to happen in six months either. What can I do?” If you’ve found [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fosslien-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> “我的团队看起来真的很焦虑，”一位经理最近告诉我。 “我们刚刚经历了一次重组，对未来有很多担忧。我想给每个人某种保证，但我也不知道六个月后会发生什么。我能做些什么？”</p><p>如果您最近发现自己遇到类似的情况，那么您并不孤单。过去一年里我见过的几乎每一位人民领袖都问过我这个问题的某个版本。在最近的一项研究中，89% 的人力资源领导者表示，他们的团队表达了对<a href="https://www.humu.com/blog/the-toll-of-workplace-anxiety-and-what-to-do-about-it">工作保障、领导层变动或重组的</a>担忧。</p><p>当不确定性很高时，管理者应该致力于使工作成为一个稳定的场所，而不是另一个压力来源。 “最高效的管理者会清楚地表达出他们关心团队中的成员，”Atlassian Team Anywhere 实践主管 Molly Sands 解释道。 “研究表明，表现最好的团队的管理者一贯采取的不同做法是让他们的报告<a href="https://assets-global.website-files.com/601872ae12d42e2264ff9ac4/62d6d89b1037a1bb82393638_Infographic _ Actions that drive great management.pdf">感到有价值和舒适</a>。”</p><p></p><p>当许多重大决策以及更广泛的经济状况超出您的控制范围时，您如何提供保证？这看起来几乎不可能，但事实并非如此。管理者可以通过以下七种方式在动荡时期为团队提供支持，而不必做出无法兑现的承诺。</p><p><strong>帮助每位员工朝着梦想的工作努力。</strong>你不能总是保证某人升职（或者不幸的是，甚至不能保证工作稳定），但你可以承诺为你的员工提供各种有价值的学习机会，无论接下来发生什么，这些机会都会对他们有所帮助。</p><p>为了展示您的团队成员愿意承担的经历或项目，请他们向您展示一份他们很高兴在三到五年内担任的职位的招聘启事。一起浏览列出的职责，并指出他们认为自己缺乏技能或引人注目的经验的任何职责。然后致力于通过为他们提供相关任务或项目来帮助他们在这些领域成长。</p><p>养成职业聊天的习惯也很有用。每六周，为每份报告安排 30 分钟的时间来提出以下问题：</p><ul><li>您最喜欢什么类型的项目或任务？</li><li>您认为当前职责的哪些部分让您充满活力？</li><li>您觉得自己在角色中不断学习和成长吗？</li><li>您希望在未来发展哪些技能？</li></ul><p>重点是根据这些对话为他们创造或提供相关机会。</p><p><strong>与您的团队共同制定中期任务。</strong>当面临不确定性或频繁改变优先事项时，我们常常会感到陷入困境，或者觉得我们付出的所有努力都没有什么成果。这种无助感可能会导致冷漠和脱离。事实上，我在 Humu 的团队二月份针对持续不确定性的影响进行的研究表明，大约 40% 的<a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/web-assets-humu/eBooks/FY24 Q1 eBook - Uncertainty/eBook_Uncertainty_01.pdf">员工感觉自己的雄心壮志</a>不如一年前。</p><p>为了让您的团队成员重新焕发活力，请将他们聚集在一起，确定并努力实现共同的三个月目标。展望未来三个月可以为您的员工带来长期的稳定感，但这段时间足够短，即使您周围的情况发生变化，您也可能不必改变您的使命。例如，营销团队的目标可能是在下个季度将网站流量增加 25%，或者就如何更快地共享信息和做出决策进行实验。正如 Creativity Partners 创始人杰米·伍尔夫 (Jamie Woolf) 和海蒂·罗森菲尔德 (Heidi Rosenfelder) 建议的那样，“为了更好地让您的团队参与未来的共同创造，请尝试提出诸如‘哪些新的利润来源可以取代日益减少的利润来源？’之类的问题。” or &#39;What can we do to break down silos within our team?&#39;”</p><p></p><p> <strong>Help your team achieve wins within two weeks.</strong> Quickly boost your team members&#39; sense of progress by focusing them on what they <em>can</em> control and giving each of them a specific task they can cross off within a week or two. Start by dividing your medium-term mission or longer-term goals into mini-milestones, and track and celebrate each one as it&#39;s achieved.</p><p> Sarah, an engineering manager, recently split an ambitious product launch into a series of specific features and updates and then assigned her reports individual tasks from the list. She also set up a 15-minute team check-in at the end of each week to celebrate what they had achieved and track the group&#39;s collective progress toward their shared goal.</p><p> <strong>Create clarity when you can.</strong> Thoughtful explanations in tough situations are critical to earning trust and reducing anxiety. The next time you have an update to share, prepare to walk through the story of how the decision was made, and think through any concerns or questions that might come up. Plan how you&#39;ll address each one. If you&#39;re unsure of what to say, ask other leaders or HR for recommendations. When you do share the decision with your team members, encourage them to ask clarifying questions.</p><p> It&#39;s also important for managers to speak to their own emotions — while avoiding emotionally processing news in front of their team. “You should say, &#39;I am disappointed about the results this quarter,&#39; but not, &#39;I am so disappointed by the results. I am so terrified we are all going to lose our jobs. I don&#39;t know what to do,&#39;” Sands suggested. “Transparency doesn&#39;t mean you have to share everything you feel or are concerned about.”</p><p></p><p> You can also run a clarity audit by talking with your team about a recent decision that affected them (such as a new product road map or a change in the expense policy). In your next series of one-on-one meetings, ask the following questions:</p><ul><li> How and when did you learn about this decision?</li><li> Is anything unclear?</li><li> What can I do differently the next time I&#39;m communicating a change with the team?</li></ul><p> These conversations can help you identify how to improve transparency — and make it clear to employees that you&#39;re doing your best to keep them up to date.</p><p> <strong>Provide context when you can&#39;t create clarity.</strong> Managers tend to stay quiet until they can share a concrete decision. But a lack of communication is still a form of communication — and it usually breeds mistrust and gossip.</p><p></p><p> To avoid misunderstandings, explain why you can&#39;t offer more details, and aim to provide a timeline for when you expect to have more information. For example, you might say something along the lines of “I haven&#39;t heard back on what changes will be made to the sales pitch. I&#39;m hoping to have more to share with you in a week or so, but I wanted to be as transparent as possible with where we are right now.”</p><p> <strong>Encourage your team to benefit from benefits.</strong> Studies show that up to 80% of employees are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbeshumanresourcescouncil/2019/07/02/only-half-of-employees-understand-their-benefits-heres-what-hr-leaders-can-do-about-it/?sh=a4a1a578133c">confused about the benefits</a> their company provides. When budgets shrink, it can be an uphill battle to design and fund new ways to support your team. You might be surprised at how much you can boost morale simply by making employees aware of what already exists. For example, though my former employer offered women returning from maternity leave the option to work part time for their first month back, many expectant mothers were unaware of this policy. After Sands, then a product leader at Humu, flagged this option on a companywide Slack channel, several women (including me) took advantage of it and expressed gratitude for the policy.</p><p> Review your company handbook, or schedule a quick meeting with HR for a refresher. In an upcoming team meeting, give a brief overview of your organization&#39;s benefits, and encourage your team members to take full advantage of them. You might want to specifically highlight mental health benefits, vacation policies, or flexible work options. Start by saying something like “I know it&#39;s been a stressful time and uncertainty is high, so I want to highlight a few programs and benefits our company offers that might help you feel better.”</p><p> <strong>Help your team say no.</strong> Preserve your team&#39;s mental health by stepping in to protect their time. Set clear and reasonable expectations, and back your reports when they turn down nonurgent requests.</p><p></p><p> You can also look for ways to get more visibility into everything they&#39;re being asked to do — and aim to set up friendly barriers. For example, when I learned that my team was being overwhelmed with requests from sales, I created a short form and advised my reports to direct all of the requesters to complete it in order to start the process. This served three functions: (1) It allowed me to better understand what my team was being pulled into, (2) I could help my reports prioritize or say no as necessary, and (3) it reduced the number of requests, because few people actually filled out the form.</p><p></p><p> Uncertainty breeds anxiety, and although managers can&#39;t snap their fingers and magically make everything fall perfectly into place, they can take steps to help their teams feel more empowered, supported, and able to succeed. Offering team members personally meaningful growth opportunities and helping them achieve quick wins can restore their sense of control and motivation. Creating transparency around changes and updates — or explaining why a decision has not yet been announced — can restore employee trust. And helping people invest in their well-being and set healthy boundaries can make it easier for them to weather workplace storms.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Improve Key Performance Indicators With AI</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Schrage, David Kiron, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>Michael Schrage</strong> is a research fellow with the MIT Sloan School of Management&#39;s Initiative on the Digital Economy. His research, writing, and advisory work focuses on the behavioral economics of digital media, models, and metrics as strategic resources for managing innovation opportunity and risk.</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>David Kiron</strong> is the editorial director, research, of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and program lead for its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">Big Ideas research initiatives</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at Boston Consulting Group and the global director of the BCG Henderson Institute, where his research focuses on the impact of technologies on business and society. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG&#39;s AI business in North America. He is a leader in BCG X and has over 20 years of experience driving business impact from AI and digital. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong> is a partner and associate director at BCG who focuses on applying AI and machine learning to business problems in commercial functions, including optimizing pricing, promotions, sales, and marketing. He can be reached at <a href="mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a> .</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics and Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Prediction Tools]]></category><category><![CDATA[Smart Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In the spring of 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_1290x860-scaled.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> About the Research</h4><p> This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group. In the spring of 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also interviewed 17 executives leading AI initiatives in a broad range of companies and industries, including financial services, media and entertainment, retail, travel and transportation, and life sciences.</p><p> Our research examines how managers and leaders use AI to enhance strategic measurement to advance strategic outcomes. It explores how organizations have adapted — and even generated new — KPIs with AI to define and deliver measurably better performance.</p></aside><p> Improving key performance indicators is a clear mandate for most organizations. According to our seventh annual <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">global executive AI survey</a> , 7 out of 10 respondents agree that enhancing KPIs — not just improving performance — is critical to their business success. As one executive notes, “We need to evolve our KPIs all the time so we don&#39;t run our business on legacy metrics.”</p><p> A growing number of companies now use AI — in a variety of ways — to accelerate that evolution. “I&#39;m very excited about what machine learning can do in terms of having our senior leaders move away from metrics that look backward to metrics that can look forward,” says Avinash Kaushik, chief strategy officer at digital marketing agency Croud and a former senior director of global strategic analytics at Google.</p><p></p><p> Early on at Lyft, engineers designed an algorithm to maximize revenue by matching driver supply and customer demand. “It looked at all the possible combinations of riders and drivers and picked the combination that — based on the ride being requested, where the driver was located, all of the system dynamics — would maximize revenue,” says Elizabeth Stone, former vice president of science at Lyft. Then, as data scientists began testing other objectives, something interesting emerged. One AI solution discovered that optimizing conversion rates — how often a user ordered a ride after opening the app — would, in turn, deliver more ride requests in the future. More ride requests ultimately mean more revenue. As a result of using AI, Lyft transformed its revenue KPI from one focused on ride and driver combinations to one that also focuses on optimizing conversion rates. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> At Tokopedia (part of GoTo Group), one of Indonesia&#39;s largest marketplaces, AI sifts through petabytes of data to detect signals that are correlated with credibility and reliability. These are key considerations, given that 86.5% of its 14 million merchants — selling 1.8 billion products — are new entrepreneurs. Having more-credible merchants makes the marketplace more appealing, effective, and efficient. “They might have good products to sell, but they don&#39;t know how to manage their stock,” says Herman Widjaja, Tokopedia&#39;s CTO. “With AI, we connect our customers to the right product that is served <em>by the right merchants</em> that they want.” The company synthesized millions of possible signals into a scoring system that represents a new KPI around merchant quality.</p><p> While most respondents understand the need for enhanced KPIs, a clear majority currently rely on inadequate tools and technologies to manage their metrics. Even as machine learning algorithms and generative AI transform enterprise capabilities, human judgment remains the overwhelmingly dominant approach to KPI enhancement. Two-thirds of survey respondents affirm that managers make judgment calls when adjusting their organization&#39;s KPIs. While common, this approach often fails to yield the desired results: Barely a third of survey respondents relying only on human judgment see their KPIs improve.</p><p></p><p> In contrast, companies that use AI to inform their KPIs are far more likely to see improved metrics. Ninety percent of respondents who use AI to create new KPIs say they see their KPIs improve. These AI-informed KPIs offer business benefits and demonstrate new capabilities: They often lead to more efficiency and greater financial benefit and are more detailed, time sensitive, and aligned with organizational objectives. (See “Creating New KPIs With AI.”) We observe a growing awareness among executives that KPIs need to become smarter and more predictive. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Creating New KPIs With AI</h4><p class="caption"> Of the 34% of organizations surveyed that use AI to create new KPIs, 90% see improvements. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig1-final.png" alt="Creating New KPIs With AI" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> All of the leaders we interviewed for our research voiced similar rationales for enhancing KPIs. As legacy metrics become static and outdated, their value as tools for defining and achieving organizational goals diminish. In fact, they become measurably less useful. Both individually and collectively, KPIs need to be updated and enhanced to ensure that they advance desired organizational outcomes. Improving performance without enhancing KPIs creates competitive risk. Companies that focus on — or align around — suboptimal measures are at a competitive disadvantage. Focusing on performance without a commensurate focus on its measure creates an inherent imbalance that can sabotage a company&#39;s efforts to compete effectively.</p><p> Based on our research — which includes results from a global survey of more than 3,000 managers and qualitative analysis of more than a dozen executive interviews — we have identified three ways to enhance strategic metrics with AI:</p><ul><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">I</strong> mprove existing KPIs.</li><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">C</strong> reate new KPIs.</li><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">E</strong> stablish new relationships among KPIs.</li></ul><p> This article explains how this Improve-Create-Establish, or ICE, framework can help leaders and managers repurpose KPIs to make their people, processes, and technologies more effective. Our research shows that AI-enhanced KPIs are associated with strategically valuable business benefits, including increased efficiency, better alignment, and greater financial benefit. Integrating AI into the strategic measurement process has enormous implications for the future of capital allocation, customer engagement, employee experience, EBITDA, and every other executive metric. (See “Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations that create new KPIs using AI are more likely to see stronger alignment, increased collaboration, more accurate forecasts, and more efficiency than organizations that do not create new KPIs using AI. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:25%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:15%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:60%;"></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 5x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Incentive structure is in line with objectives:</strong> 5.13 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (6% → 29%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 4x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Increased collaboration between employees:</strong> 3.97 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (11% → 44%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>More effective at predicting future performance:</strong> 3.37 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (13% → 45%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Greater financial benefit:</strong> 3.27 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (11% → 34%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 2x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Greater efficiency:</strong> 2.31 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (24% → 56%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig2-fallback.png" alt="Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> We offer several practical steps on how to use AI to enhance their KPIs.</p><p></p><h3> Improve Existing KPIs With AI</h3><p> Companies that initially use AI to boost performance numbers tend to find that the technology creates opportunities to revisit and review key performance parameters.</p><h4> The Substitution Effect at Wayfair</h4><p> Wayfair&#39;s AI approach makes that case. While losing a sale may appear to be a straightforward measure, the online furniture retailer used AI to reexamine the fundamentals behind its lost-sales KPI. As CTO Fiona Tan recalls, “We used to think that if you lost the sale on a particular product, like a sofa, it was a loss to the company. But we started looking at the data and realized that 50% to 60% of the time, when we lose a sale it is because the customer bought something else in the same product category.”</p><p> This AI-enabled analysis allowed Wayfair to experiment with substitute offers based on customer concerns such as price points, shipment times, and other factors. Demand for these substitute products provided a new lens on what had been previously measured and interpreted as lost sales. Recognizing this “substitution effect” led Wayfair to adjust pricing across its entire sofa domain, revamp product configurations in its fulfillment centers, and reprioritize legacy KPIs.</p><p></p><p> At one level, Wayfair used AI to transform its legacy lost-sales KPI into a more valuable metric that differentiated truly lost sales from actual sales. But at another level, the AI behind this upgraded KPI also enabled more sweeping changes. Tan&#39;s team used the substitution effect to develop a “profit-awareness framework,” which changed the way the company interacted with customers. Wayfair&#39;s furniture recommendations began to factor in delivery times and shipment costs, as well as product incidents and product profitability, when making next-best offers. Explicitly measuring and incorporating the substitution effect reframed lost sales as sales opportunities and led to pricing shifts. This reframing consequently aligned product placement decisions with the needs and capacities of distribution centers and warehouses, which improved both employee and customer experiences.</p><p> Companies across the industry landscape are finding ways to use AI to improve existing KPIs. Some use AI to deepen their understanding of factors that drive KPI outcomes, whereas others use AI to identify and prioritize which KPIs deliver the most value to the organization. While our survey results suggest that most companies will satisfice around improving KPIs (that is, rely on human judgment), we also see companies recognizing that AI makes possible altogether new KPIs that can achieve, and drive, next-level performance.</p><h3> Create New KPIs</h3><p> In addition to improving existing performance metrics, AI offers the potential for managers to algorithmically discover and generate entirely new KPIs. While our survey shows that only 16% of respondents&#39; organizations use AI to generate new KPIs, 90% agree that their use of AI has measurably improved their KPIs.</p><p> For example, hunting for indicators that can help physicians preempt sudden cardiac death, which afflicts 300,000 people in the US every year, is an ongoing effort for physicians and researchers. These types of deaths come out of nowhere; doctors can&#39;t predict them, since patients don&#39;t present as high risk. It&#39;s an especially frustrating condition because there is a known effective treatment — installing a cardiac defibrillator — if doctors can identify at-risk patients in time. One of the researchers in this hunt, Ziad Obermeyer, a physician and professor at the University of California, Berkeley, is working with Region Halland Health System in Sweden whose electronic health record data can be linked to a variety of government data. He and his collaborators trained an algorithm to predict sudden cardiac death in the year after an electrocardiogram (ECG) is performed, using death certificates, and a variety of other data points taken from government records and electronic health records.</p><p> “The algorithm became quite good at predicting who&#39;s going to succumb to sudden cardiac death in the year after an ECG is taken. Every time someone gets an ECG, it generates a risk score that measures the probability the individual will die from sudden cardiac arrest,” says Obermeyer. That ECG score can also function just like a key performance indicator: With the score in hand, a doctor might observe how it changes if the patient is prescribed a medication such as a beta blocker or an ACE inhibitor. While the research is at a very early stage, it might one day empower doctors and patients to work together to reduce the risk of sudden cardiac death — and identify new interventions that might decrease the risk. “Having the ability to turn these very complicated biological signals into indicators is very powerful,” Obermeyer says, “and I think that&#39;s going to be something that we&#39;ll see a lot more of, not just for sudden cardiac death but for diabetic complications and all sorts of other preventable, high-stakes conditions.”</p><p> Obermeyer&#39;s use of AI to create a new KPI for sudden cardiac death promises to improve patient outcomes, reduce costs, and enhance physicians&#39; sense of their own efficacy. Developing and discerning new key performance indicators with AI is an emergent phenomenon across the business landscape and among large companies we interviewed, such as DBS Bank, General Electric, General Motors, Sanofi, Schneider Electric, and Walmart. These companies are using AI to identify indicators of future performance at earlier and earlier stages of corporate activity. This capability facilitates better situational awareness and a more effective response to changing market conditions, among other benefits.</p><h3> Establish New Relationships Among KPIs</h3><p> No KPI is an island. Many executives we spoke with emphasized that better managing their business requires that they bring local KPIs together into a more integrated set of metrics. Executives across industries explicitly remarked on the inherent organizational and computational tensions between maximizing local KPIs and optimizing higher-level, more macro KPIs. As KPI features and parameters evolve, the importance of anticipating, modeling, and coordinating multiple KPI interactions with AI becomes more critical.</p><h4> DBS Bank Integrates Its KPIs With AI</h4><p> Singapore-based DBS Bank once relied on independent KPIs for each function touching different points along a customer journey. That is, for a given product, marketing would, for instance, have its own customer engagement metrics, product would have its own attrition metrics, finance would have its own revenue metrics, etc. Over the past three years, however, the multinational banking and financial services company has replaced that vertical model with a horizontal one. DBS created a value map that ties the use cases together into a single customer journey with outcomes in four categories: customer experience, employee experience, profitability, and risk. “We call it &#39;managing through journeys,&#39;” says Sameer Gupta, DBS&#39;s chief analytics officer. “Each customer journey would have multiple drivers, and each driver would in turn have multiple metrics to measure. You can imagine how quickly these scale, and it would be humanly impossible to optimize such a large number of drivers and metrics. AI is a force multiplier that gives us the ability to analyze large numbers of drivers and metrics and also identify those that need to be acted on now.”</p><p> In the new model, the outcome data is visible to cross-functional squads, whose members all have a stake in optimizing results in all four categories. “Everyone is looking at the same data, and everyone is accountable for the same outcome,” Gupta notes. The squads use experimentation, data analytics, customer immersion, and AI to continually review the factors driving different outcomes. In addition, they retain a sharp focus on choosing the correct metrics.</p><p> Establishing these interrelationships among their KPIs has been, in Gupta&#39;s words, “a fundamental shift.” He anticipates that AI will have an increasingly prominent role as the organization continues to coordinate its metrics in a drive toward continuous improvement. “We are starting to unpack to ask, &#39;Do we currently make that decision through data and AI enablement? Is there an opportunity to make it through data and AI enablement? If there is, how can we do it?&#39;” Gupta says. Discerning new relationships among KPIs with AI and other analytical techniques can yield new business opportunities, new insights, and a valuable set of data around which to manage organizational behaviors.</p><h3> Leadership Takeaways</h3><p> The future of strategic measurement belongs to smarter KPIs. Our research suggests, however, that few legacy organizations are strategically using AI to improve their KPIs. This makes both AI and KPIs undervalued assets. Leadership needs to invest accordingly. Using AI to improve KPIs, create new KPIs, and establish new relationships among KPIs creates an opportunity to capture measurably greater value. The ICE framework invites executive and boardroom discussions that should lead to management investment in improving strategic measurement.</p><p> Our research also emphasizes the need for leaders to align not only on which KPIs to pursue but, even more fundamentally, on the purpose of those KPIs. Will KPIs be primarily retrospective, or will they predictively lean into the future?</p><p> If the latter, organizations need road maps for improving existing KPIs; a commitment to exploration and experimentation around creating new KPIs; and a recognition that relationships among KPIs may matter as much as, if not more than, the individual KPIs themselves. Intelligent KPIs should not be primarily managed as independent performance silos; rather, their interdependencies and interrelationships must be understood and addressed. As our examples have shown, these shifts represent operational, organizational, and cultural challenges to leadership.</p><p> As has been the case with almost every successful AI initiative, KPIs, like the algorithms that comprise them, must be transparent and explainable. KPIs — organizationally, culturally, and operationally — cannot be seen as black boxes. They should be designed and deployed to be trusted. This cultural component should not be minimized or taken for granted. Otherwise, people at all levels of the organization will seek to game the metrics that guide them, ensuring organizational misalignment.</p><p></p><p> Underlying this new emphasis on AI and KPIs, and on strategic measurement more broadly, is an acknowledgment that quality KPIs depend on quality data. KPIs trained or supervised on biased, incomplete, and flawed data sets are likely to be biased, incomplete, and flawed. Data quality matters more wherever KPIs matter more. We see organizations committed to AI-driven KPIs becoming even more committed to cultivating data as an asset. They see investments in data reflected in KPI improvements.</p><p> Finally, as AI-influenced KPIs become more influential in the enterprise, their own performance will require new levels of monitoring and oversight. Leadership will need to be able to evaluate how well their KPIs are doing, individually and collectively. Are they the right KPIs for sustainable success? Are they appropriately anticipating the future? Are they making the right decisions — and helping humans make the right decisions — for achieving desired and desirable outcomes? Simply put, KPIs will require their own KPIs to help answer those important questions.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The 10 Most Popular Articles in 2023 (So Far)</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Workplace]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Three-plus years after COVID-19 interrupted office-based operations with a sudden transition to remote work, managing hybrid teams remains a pressing issue for leaders. Hybrid culture has its own pitfalls to manage, with risks like feelings of disconnection among employees and “productivity paranoia.” Based on the most-read articles in the first half of 2023, readers of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MostPopular2023-tile-angleREV-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Three-plus years after COVID-19 interrupted office-based operations with a sudden transition to remote work, managing hybrid teams remains a pressing issue for leaders. Hybrid culture has its own pitfalls to manage, with risks like feelings of disconnection among employees and “productivity paranoia.” Based on the most-read articles in the first half of 2023, readers of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> seem keen to address these issues. Tools for improvement can be found in articles on skills-based culture change, effective one-on-one meetings, and intellectual honesty. Readers have also been focused on the bigger-picture issues of ESG, sustainability, and the growing role of AI in performance management and strategy.</p><p> The following are the 10 most popular articles of the year so far. We hope they will continue to help leaders in managing and supporting employees and in building thriving, innovative organizations.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#1</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/work-from-home-regulations-are-coming-companies-arent-ready/" style="border-bottom:none;">Work-From-Home Regulations Are Coming. Companies Aren&#39;t Ready.</a></h4><h6> Jimena Murillo Chávarro</h6><p> A growing web of regulatory minutiae governing flexible working arrangements around the world poses an acute challenge for multinationals. These companies must now contend with different compliance requirements in different jurisdictions, depending on how governments define and interpret terms like <em>remote work</em> , <em>teleworking</em> , and <em>work from home</em> .</p><h4> <span class="blue">#2</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-to-make-your-one-on-one-meetings-more-effective/" style="border-bottom:none;">Five Ways to Make Your One-on-One Meetings More Effective</a></h4><h6> Jessica Wisdom</h6><p> Weekly check-in meetings between managers and their teams or direct reports are key opportunities to build trusting manager-employee relationships. By taking five science-backed steps and asking five key questions, managers can better structure their one-on-ones to make these check-ins more productive.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#3</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-innovation-depends-on-intellectual-honesty" style="border-bottom:none;">Why Innovation Depends on Intellectual Honesty</a></h4><h6> Jeff Dyer, Nathan Furr, Curtis Lefrandt, and Taeya Howell</h6><p> Fostering psychological safety alone isn&#39;t enough to successfully drive innovation; leaders must also create conditions that enable healthy debate. The authors describe the factors most important to establishing the balance between psychological safety and open, honest debate and outline what leaders can do to create a high-performance learning and innovation culture.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#4</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt" style="border-bottom:none;">Three Lessons From Chatting About Strategy With ChatGPT</a></h4><h6> Christian Stadler and Martin Reeves</h6><p> Amid great excitement about the potential use cases of large language models like ChatGPT, a pair of business strategists decided to test whether the tools can support ideation, experimentation, evaluation, and storytelling as part of the strategy creation process. In this article, they share three lessons that emerged when they conducted a series of experiments in which they posed a question of strategy to ChatGPT and followed up with iterative queries.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#5</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-is-helping-companies-redefine-not-just-improve-performance/" style="border-bottom:none;">AI Is Helping Companies Redefine, Not Just Improve, Performance</a></h4><h6> Michael Schrage, David Kiron, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu</h6><p> Research on organizations&#39; use of artificial intelligence offers new perspectives on what drives performance and how best to measure it. Three practical and valuable ways KPIs can redefine strategic measurement include using smart KPIs that learn, measuring the performance of KPIs themselves, and enhancing organizational alignment with KPIs.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#6</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/esg-is-going-to-have-a-rocky-2023-sustainability-will-be-just-fine" style="border-bottom:none;">ESG Is Going to Have a Rocky 2023. Sustainability Will Be Just Fine.</a></h4><h6> Andrew Winston</h6><p> Companies&#39; environmental, social, and governance activities are facing two kinds of backlash: “anti-woke” political theater and noise from the investment community about whether ESG funds will outperform “regular” funds. But while ESG gets buffeted by these winds, the <em>real</em> work of sustainability continues.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#7</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-toxic-culture-gap-shows-companies-are-failing-women" style="border-bottom:none;">The Toxic Culture Gap Shows Companies Are Failing Women</a></h4><h6> Donald Sull and Charles Sull</h6><p> Which elements of corporate culture are most critical to women? And which cultural shortcomings are causing women to head for the exits? In analyzing the language that 3 million US employees used in Glassdoor reviews to describe their employers, the authors found that toxic culture disproportionately affects women, with the widest gender gaps in perceptions of inclusivity and respect.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#8</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-the-cultural-pitfalls-of-hybrid-work" style="border-bottom:none;">Managing the Cultural Pitfalls of Hybrid Work</a></h4><h6> Christine Moorman and Katie Hinkfuss</h6><p> Although the hybrid work model has been widely adopted among many businesses, the complications involving peer relationships and connections that it has introduced linger on. A set of strategies presented here can help leaders navigate organizational culture and the socialization of new employees during this era of digital transformation.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#9</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change" style="border-bottom:none;">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a></h4><h6> Per Hugander</h6><p> Taking a skills-based approach, rather than implementing typical culture-change initiatives, can lead to positive changes in behavior that endure, particularly when it comes to cultivating soft skills like <em>perspective taking</em> and creating psychological safety. The author explains key attributes of the skills-based approach to culture change and how organizations can leverage it to speed the process and improve performance in the long term.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#10</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-ways-to-build-a-culture-of-honesty-and-avoid-productivity-paranoia/" style="border-bottom:none;">Four Ways to Build a Culture of Honesty and Avoid &#39;Productivity Paranoia&#39;</a></h4><h6> Pamela Meyer</h6><p> Remote and hybrid work environments can breed distrust, or productivity paranoia, between managers and employees or between remote and in-person colleagues. The author describes four steps managers can take to foster a culture of trust and honesty when people aren&#39;t able to interact and develop relationships with one another in person.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Regulating AI Innovation: Aboitiz Data Innovation&#39;s David Hardoon</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Chief Executive Officer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[As CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation, David Hardoon oversees the operations of a technology conglomerate focused on using data science and AI to support its businesses in a range of sectors, including banking, financial services, utilities, agriculture, and construction in Singapore and the Philippines. In his role, David is leading some unexpected — but practical [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> As CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation, David Hardoon oversees the operations of a technology conglomerate focused on using data science and AI to support its businesses in a range of sectors, including banking, financial services, utilities, agriculture, and construction in Singapore and the Philippines. In his role, David is leading some unexpected — but practical — uses of artificial intelligence, including using voice and image recognition to detect stress in livestock, and analyzing internet-of-things data to reduce waste and CO <sub>2</sub> emissions in the cement R&amp;D process.</p><p> David joins this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast to discuss the broad scope of the organizations he&#39;s responsible for, the role of AI regulation and governance in helping to spur innovation, humans&#39; sometimes problematic role in shaping AI outputs, and how a high school detention led to a career in artificial intelligence. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MMAI-S7-E3-Hardoon-Aboitiz-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="David Hardoon"></p><h4> David Hardoon, Aboitiz Data Innovation</h4><p> David Hardoon is the CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation and chief data and AI officer of Union Bank of the Philippines. He is concurrently the chief data and innovation officer of the Aboitiz Group and chief data officer of UnionDigital Bank. Previously, he was the Monetary Authority of Singapore&#39;s first appointed chief data officer and head of the Data Analytics Group, as well as a special adviser on AI. Hardoon has a doctorate in computer science (machine learning) from the University of Southampton and a bachelor&#39;s degree from Royal Holloway, University of London, in computer science and AI.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Concrete production? Livestock? The Socratic method? Somehow, we talk about all three. Find out how these connect with AI in today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I&#39;m David Hardoon from Aboitiz Data Innovation, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome. Today, Shervin and I are excited to be joined by David Hardoon, who holds several senior positions at the Aboitiz Group. David, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Thank you very much, Sam, Shervin.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Can you first tell us a bit about the Aboitiz Group? Where do you work?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> The Aboitiz Group is a 100-plus-year-old conglomerate that originated starting in Spain — Catalonia — and relocated to the Philippines. It started in the hemp business but is now quite diversified, from the main business — power generation and distribution across the Philippines — [to] financial services, cement, construction, utilities, [real] estate, airports, food, agriculture. We&#39;re now going through a transformation and becoming — I love this term, by the way — a techglomerate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What is Aboitiz Data Innovation?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> About seven years ago, give or take, the bank started with all digitalization of the banking services. And what that had resulted in, as you would imagine, [was] a tremendous amount of data. The more you engage your consumers digitally, the more you have digital services — well, surprise, surprise — the more data you have.</p><p> And the question came as well, how are we really using it? Are we using it? What&#39;s the best way to put it to good use? And that question kind of also went beyond just the bank into the rest of the businesses, as you can imagine. Power has a lot of data; agriculture, airports, etc., have a lot of data.</p><p> We were born with a very on-point mandate: operationalizing data, operationalizing AI. Really, how do we put it to good use?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What are some of these uses?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I mean, there&#39;s the usual financial side, where we all learn from hyperpersonalization, financial crime. And don&#39;t get me wrong — that stuff … always gets me all excited. I spent a few good years in the financial regulator [space] here in Singapore.</p><p> But let me give you an oddity: cement, an industry that you wouldn&#39;t really associate with data or AI. We sat down with the CEO at the time, and we said, “Look, even in the world of cement, you have a lot of data.”</p><p> How can this work? So let me give you a little tidbit of how the world of cement works. And this is something that was new to me. So basically, it&#39;s like baking. I don&#39;t know if you bake, but it&#39;s like baking. It&#39;s basically, you have mixtures. You have these kind of formulas, and you end up with cement, which will have different types of properties. And these properties [are] what&#39;s absolutely critical depending on what you&#39;re planning to build, whether it&#39;s a mall, a high rise, a low rise, residential, etc., and so forth.</p><p> Having said that, as with baking, you kind of need to do a bit of trial and error. You need to try out these different mixtures to make sure it produces the right one. That results in operational overhead. It results in wastage. I mean, as with baking, you stick this stuff into kilns — literally, it&#39;s a furnace — to bake it. Using data, using the information that&#39;s coming from all the devices, the IoT, using AI, being able to actually tell the bakers or, in this case, the chemical engineers what is going to be the output of this mixture before they even start, while at the same time maintaining that quality control, which is absolutely crucial. Now this is, by the way, not just hypothetical. This is already operational for the past year in all the plants — about six plants in the Philippines — and results in operational efficiency, results in reduction in [the amount] of wastage, resulted in what I like to call quantifiable ESG [environmental, social, and governance]: a 35 kiloton reduction of CO <sub>2</sub> emissions. So that&#39;s a nice unusual example I like to give in terms of how data is used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Well, I could tell you, Sam and I are going to love that. We&#39;re both chemical engineers.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Oh, well, there you go.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Actually, when you said baking, I did my Ph.D. in catalyst synthesis, so I spent a lot of my time baking various aluminosilicates to create catalysts. And you&#39;re completely right: You try all these things. Some work; some don&#39;t work. And had there been the ability for me to know ahead of time, I probably would have gotten my Ph.D. in a tenth of the time.</p><p> But seriously, this is quite interesting. Now, if you go from personalization and cyber and fraud, and you also have this example in baking cements, then we must believe that there is such a wide portfolio of things that you are considering. So tell us more about what makes it into that portfolio, because there is no end to what you could do. What are the kinds of things you get excited about?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> You&#39;re absolutely right. Being fortunate working in a conglomerate, you kind of wake up every day and discover something new. So there are kind of two dimensions to it. On the one hand — and I&#39;m going to go back to this term <em>operationalization</em> , operationalizing data and AI — it&#39;s stuff that has to make sense to the business. So revenue, operational efficiency, risk management. And then we have to look at the things around the corner. We have to experiment. But those may not be things that get immediately deployed. Like, effectively in agricultural builders, we have the animals; we have pigs, swine, and poultry. And as part of that process, we want to make sure that the animals have the best possible care provided to them. On an experimental side, we say, “OK, how can we use technology that&#39;s already available but may not have been put in exactly in this particular context, not in Southeast Asia?” So we&#39;re using voice recognition and image recognition for pigs to help identify stress and detect illnesses, so that could be automatic alerts to the caregivers.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the ground truth on that? That would be interesting to know.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a great question.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the training data?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> So this is the amazing stuff. It&#39;s a very expressive animal. So when you actually go there with the people who take care of them, they can literally point at them and say, “This animal is distressed,” and you&#39;re constantly recording.</p><p> We&#39;re kind of, “OK, is this really something that&#39;s relevant? Does it make sense?” Like, can we have that conversation with the baker, you know, the chemical engineer? Can we have a conversation with the animal keeper, the veterinarian and so forth, or the pole engineer when we&#39;re dealing with electricity cables? It&#39;s extremely important.</p><p> And that&#39;s one of the things that I realized throughout my career of doing data, is where things failed, where you suddenly had this divergence of exploring scientific research — and I came from the world of science, you know, like ex-academic — without really seeing that connectivity. And if we go all the way back, even when radar was invented, the reason things fall apart is whereby the very, very small gaps of “Well, it&#39;s not quite there; oh, it&#39;s not quite usable.” So that&#39;s the first part.</p><p> Then, the second level is seeing, well, is this something that, as much as possible, is truly going to make a difference to either our internal users — because that&#39;s extremely important — and for many of the businesses which are within the group, which are actually B2B, like in power, where, essentially, we provide power and wholesale [electricity]? So it&#39;s our internal users in terms of, let&#39;s say, predictive asset maintenance — critically important.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That is really fantastic. I mean, what you&#39;ve said is inspiring on so many levels. One is, let your imagination be the limit, right, because [of] the question of “Can something be done better, more effectively? Can you see around the corner there?” And there&#39;s data, then, yes. That&#39;s one thing that&#39;s inherent in all these examples that you gave.</p><p> You started with what most would consider quite advanced and interesting things, and we have guests who talk about those all the time: personalization, fraud, cyber. All of those are very important. And then you went to cement. And then you went to pigs. And then you talked about human and AI …</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Which is quite critical too. I just find that very, very energizing.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Well, it&#39;s the nexus between human and AI. There are two critical things that I believe have to go hand in hand — have to. While this may change in the future to some degree or extent — I mean, who knows what&#39;s going to happen around the corner? Things change so rapidly. But I&#39;ll be the first one to admit this: I truly came to this appreciation when I worked [for] the regulator — surprise, surprise — [of the] criticality of combining governance and innovation. And I used to get asked this question repeatedly, of “Oh, but don&#39;t you think governance inhibits innovation? It stifles us.” And I came to the view of, I&#39;m vehemently against that perspective.</p><p> I would argue that not only it does not stifle it — it would result in more and even better innovation. It&#39;s essentially about just simply having, you know, common sense. I was privileged in being in the process and coming up with the FEAT principle. So this was <em>fairness</em> , <em>ethics</em> , <em>accountability</em> , and <em>transparency</em> , back at the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</p><p> I remember that when it came out — and we deliberately kept it very simple — and I showed it to our governor, our managing director, and he was just like, “David, isn&#39;t this just common sense?” And I just smiled, and I was like, “Well, no; even common sense has to ... it&#39;s not always that common. It has to be written down.” But it&#39;s critical. That&#39;s No. 1.</p><p> And No. 2, what you were mentioning is that, yes, while AI and data can do what is seemingly miraculous stuff, it&#39;s critical that this combination with us humans and <em>how</em> we use it is baked in at the very beginning. And even now, obviously, everyone&#39;s talking about ChatGPT, but remember: All the data that it&#39;s trained on is from <em>us</em> to a certain extent.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. You can&#39;t take humans out of the loop, because after a while, they will lose what makes them human.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> But we have examples of that. I mean, that&#39;s OK in some places. I mean, neither of you know how to navigate by the stars, I&#39;m guessing, unless, Shervin, you&#39;ve got some tricks up your sleeve that I haven&#39;t learned yet. I mean, most people don&#39;t drive a manual transmission; that seems to be a skill that&#39;s … well, OK, maybe one or two of us do here. But the point is, we don&#39;t have to retain all possible skills. We just have to be savvy about which ones we hang on to.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> That&#39;s exactly [right], what you said: It&#39;s some, not all. But sometimes you find that you see this trend of like, “Oh, look what it can do. <em>Everything</em> gets automated.” And I remember, if I go to my early days as a consultant — you know, I used to be a consultant doing AI — you would find a lot of times, potential clients and people you spoke to, even if they didn&#39;t say it explicitly, what they were trying to achieve was like, “Oh, just do everything automatically with AI.”</p><p> And you need to have almost this natural inclination by saying, “OK, if it&#39;s contextual, if it makes sense.” Like you said, maybe I want to pick up star navigation because I&#39;m interested in it. I want to learn about astrology or astrophysics or whatnot.伟大的。 But you see it now becomes a niche topic that some people pick up. The general public doesn&#39;t need to know how to do it. But we need to be able to identify that decision point rather than just go [into a] “No, everything now, AI galore” kind of situation.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Well, I mean, what you&#39;re saying is, there&#39;s value in the ongoing dialogue. There&#39;s value in ongoing challenge. And every time there is a dialogue, I mean, even back in Socrates&#39;s time, the dialogue is where it elevates the conversation. And you&#39;re rightly pointing out that the moment you say AI is the be-all and end-all is the moment that you are under-delivering on AI, and then you&#39;re for sure under-delivering on the human potential.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Well you&#39;re losing a potential answer. Let me give you two examples. In the financial section, we have Union Bank of the Philippines, amongst others. While AI governance regulation is not yet — <em>yet</em> — a requirement, let&#39;s say, in the Philippines, we&#39;ve situated a working group, which is an interesting combination of people, from your risk officer, legal, compliance, and then you have marketing, customer engagement, experience. What happens is, while you still have the traditional process of model validation, etc., from a statistical, mathematical, data point of view, the models are presented in this working group for us to have a debate. Because a model may pass all the statistical tests, but if this model goes wrong — even that 10% or 5% — there is a significant reputational risk at play or there&#39;s a potential impact to the consumers. That debate is important because if you just looked at it from that statistical, even a potentially automated process, you would miss it.</p><p> Now, the resolution, interestingly enough — and I honestly tell you, like, maybe eight out of 10 times so far — isn&#39;t data, isn&#39;t AI. The resolution a lot of times is process, which is people. And that makes us actually wiser and understanding, “OK, how do we use it, and how do we engage with it? And when do we allow” — Sam, to your point — “that automation?” And when we go “no,” I retain the veto to overrule, to a certain extent. So that&#39;s one example.</p><p> The other one is if I go back to my cement [example], and in fact, we did this very deliberately at the very beginning because we didn&#39;t want our colleagues and chemical engineers to think, “Oh, great. Why do you need me? You&#39;re just going to automate the whole thing.”</p><p> No. The whole point was, we absolutely need them because there may be new types of mixtures that we haven&#39;t considered. You will still need to have that experimentation. The whole goal is providing information.</p><p> What it has resulted in is efficiency. If I give a swing again to another one — when ChatGPT came out, I got asked straightaway from a few boards, “What does this mean?” And my instinctive reaction, rather than going into this whole lengthy explanation of liberation, I just responded by saying, “It means that every one of us can have the productivity of 10 people.”</p><p> So this is what this stuff means, and that&#39;s what that nexus, the dialogue, the integration, the augmentation means — is that we now have the ability to be far more productive, whatever “productive” means in that context. For some people, they may say, “I just want to work two hours but [appear] as if I work the whole day.” Some may say, “I want to work the whole day.” … It may differ. But that&#39;s what it means because now we&#39;re able to take all this data.</p><p> I&#39;m sure some of you remember, back in 2000, you had these memes online of “getting information off the internet is like drinking from a fire hose.” It&#39;s still true. We&#39;re inundated with information, with data, but it&#39;s like distilling it down to something that&#39;s relevant to me, usable, that I can do something with it and get that gain, essentially.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think one thing that&#39;s coming out of this conversation — Shervin used the word <em>Socratic</em> , and, David, you used the word <em>dialogue</em> . What&#39;s nice about this is it&#39;s dropped this hubris that I feel like I see in a lot of machine learning. Machine learning seems to be about humans teaching machines. So it&#39;s this sort of “We know all. We make the machines emulate us, and if they do, they pass the Turing test, and, yes, everything&#39;s golden.” But then you get pushback, and you say, “Oh, no. The machine can teach <em>us</em> things we&#39;ve never known before.” Well, that just has switched the direction. It still has that same directional hubris, but the things that you&#39;re both talking about are much more [oriented around the] Socratic and dialogue.</p><p> When you think about what that group can form together — and Shervin and I have got some results from last year&#39;s research that said about 60% of the people are thinking about AI as a coworker. And that strikes me as that sort of a relationship, because between the two, yes, you find some new compound that maybe someone wouldn&#39;t have tried. I don&#39;t know what the chemical engineering equivalent of the Fosbury flop is. Do you remember the Fosbury flop, where he learned a different way of jumping over the high bar, and then suddenly everyone else adopted that technique? That sort of idea seems like it could come out of this approach.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> It&#39;s actually really interesting you bring that up. I mean, I&#39;d love to say, “Oh, yeah, we had this all intended in the very beginning,” but I&#39;ll be very honest and say, I think it&#39;s more of a nice consequence that wasn&#39;t fully intended at a point in time.</p><p> But I want to go back to that FEAT principle. One of the principles resulted in a lot of discourse — and I mean a <em>lot</em> — where we had a statement amongst all of them that said that we should hold AI to at least the same standard as human decisions. So AI-based decisions should be held to at least the same standard as human-based decisions. And the debate was phenomenal and [people] said, “Oh, no, we should hold it to a higher one,” etc., and so forth.</p><p> But what the intention of that principle was saying is, if you&#39;re using now … so let me go back again to, let&#39;s say, a financial [example]: loan provisioning. And if [you&#39;re] using an AI algorithm and you&#39;re finding that “oh, we&#39;re discriminating,” OK, yeah, absolutely, that&#39;s something that needs to be addressed, reviewed, and corrected. But hold your horses there. Take a step back. Take the AI out of the equation. Had you been discriminating before the AI? And that&#39;s really the question because ... I remember I had long debates with many regulators. Maybe debate is the wrong word: <em>discussions</em> with many regulators. And I was actually a bit opposed to regulating AI, and I&#39;ll explain what I mean by that.</p><p> I&#39;m not opposing regulation. But when they said “regulating AI,” I got a bit defensive. I said, “What I&#39;m worried about is that we&#39;re like, &#39;OK, well, since AI now is showing me all this stuff that I don&#39;t want to know about, then I&#39;m just not going to use AI.&#39; And we&#39;re going to go back to the same procedures previously, which, guess what — it&#39;s the same problem. You just weren&#39;t paying attention to it because that information, that knowledge, wasn&#39;t bubbled up to the surface.”</p><p> So, what I kept on arguing is that, yes, the regulation has to be in play. And yes, there may be certain scenarios whereby AI requires higher scrutiny. But the regulation is still on the outcome. The regulation is still in the fact that, for example, it&#39;s a case of discrimination. You should not be discriminating; whether you&#39;re using a human-based process or an AI-based process is kind of beside the point. But I just want to emphasize that point, Sam, because it really goes back to what you were saying of, it&#39;s now teaching <em>us</em> things that we may have been, let&#39;s say, sometimes consciously ignorant of, sometimes inadvertently unaware of.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> David, tell us about your background. How did you end up where you are?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> If I roll back all the way to the beginning, and I&#39;m going to say this again with a big smile myself, how did I end up where I am? Detention. That&#39;s how I ended up here.</p><p> I must have been, what, 14, 15, 16 years old, and I got sent to the library because of detention. And, you know, if you&#39;re in a library, you have nothing better to do. I picked up a book on Prolog. Don&#39;t ask me why, from all the books I could have picked up, I picked up one about Prolog. And this is really before knowing anything about the whole world of, well, I guess in that case, it would be expert-based systems. And I started reading, and I just couldn&#39;t put it down. And that kind of triggered this exploration of, how can we better capture knowledge? How can we better learn?</p><p> And that obviously resulted in kind of learning a bit more about neural networks, AI. In fact, I was one of the first two students who took the degree of computer science with artificial intelligence. It was literally brand-new, from that perspective.</p><p> My Ph.D. thesis was about semantic models, so literally the representation and encapsulation of knowledge, effectively, and information; [it] was on learning musical patterns/music, or generating music from brain patterns. And the whole idea about that is essentially providing expert-based systems knowledge, if you think about it in that way, for people who, say, can&#39;t sit in front of a piano and play but are fully capable cognitively.</p><p> So that&#39;s kind of what brought me here. I know it&#39;s a very weird kind of journey. But yeah, I need to thank my literacy teacher: Thank you for sending me to detention.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK, so we&#39;ve got a segment where we&#39;re going to ask you some quick questions. What are you proudest of in terms of artificial intelligence? What have you done that you&#39;re proudest of?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Where to begin? What I&#39;m most proud of is the way we&#39;ve been able to graduate — and I literally mean that — from the academic world to the industrial world.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What worries you about AI? You&#39;ve mentioned some worries today. But what worries you?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> What worries me is I don&#39;t think we&#39;re fully appreciating what we&#39;re creating. I think we need to focus head on with the realization of what we&#39;re creating and what we&#39;re seeding for possibilities, for good and for bad.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> SUP: stand-up paddling. Being on the water and just paddling away. It&#39;s extremely soothing. It&#39;s actually phenomenal exercise, for those who haven&#39;t tried.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I&#39;ve tried and I&#39;ve missed the stand-up part. I&#39;m OK with the paddling, but the stand-up seems to lead to trouble. What&#39;s the first career you wanted while you were sitting in detention? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I wanted to be an astrophysicist.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future? What are you hoping we can gain from this?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I don&#39;t know. Self-actualization? I hope we learn more about ourselves. It&#39;s already giving us capabilities. I mean, for example, I&#39;m dyslexic. Thank heavens for auto spell-checkers!</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, thank you for taking the time. I think that there&#39;s a lot that you&#39;ve mentioned. I think we can go back to even examples of food 100 years ago. We had a terrible food cleanliness [problem], and now we have a supply chain we can trust. Perhaps we can build that same sort of supply chain with data. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. It&#39;s been a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Thank you, Sam, Shervin.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah.谢谢。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> And maybe, if I may just add another note, I think that&#39;s really the critical thing: It&#39;s AI <em>trust</em> . It&#39;s about trust. Thank you very much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, Shervin and I talk with Naba Banerjee, head of trust product and operations at Airbnb, about how the travel platform uses AI and machine learning to make travel experiences safer.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Amid Growing AI, Humanize Communication to Strengthen Relationships</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cole Clark. <p>Cole Clark is president of <a href="https://www.amygdalaunch.com/">AmygdaLaunch</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[AI entered a new era when artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT became available to the public this year. These technologies are taking over more and more aspects of business as they seep into the collective consciousness. As Vox put it, generative AI is “suddenly everywhere,” and it’s poised to profoundly change daily life within organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Clark-Handwritten-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> AI entered a new era when artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT became available to the public this year. These technologies are taking over more and more aspects of business as they seep into the collective consciousness. As Vox put it, generative AI is “ <a href="https://www.vox.com/recode/2023/1/5/23539055/generative-ai-chatgpt-stable-diffusion-lensa-dall-e">suddenly everywhere</a> ,” and it&#39;s poised to profoundly change daily life within organizations in many ways, particularly in the sphere of communication.</p><p> More than ever, when people receive texts, emails, or other digital messages, they have reason to wonder whether an actual human being wrote them. ChatGPT is even being used to write <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/08/chatgpt-is-being-used-to-write-emails-big-companies-are-embracing-it.html">custom messages</a> to individual executives on LinkedIn. In response, tools are being created to help people determine whether a message was really <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90830518/tools-to-detect-ai-generated-text-chatgpt">written by a human</a> . Some of these tools are made by the same companies whose technologies generate such text. But few people are likely to use these detectors in the short term, and even if they do, there will be a continuous cycle of AI-based text generators constantly working to outsmart the detectors.</p><p></p><p> The net result is clear: When it comes to digital communication, we&#39;re unlikely to trust most “personal” digital messages for a while to come. This is why, in working to build authentic relationships, sidestepping technology altogether has newfound power.</p><h3> Handwritten Messages Take on New Value</h3><p> Few people answer calls from unrecognized phone numbers these days. And executives are increasingly aware that AI is also being used to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/11/why-chatgpt-ai-are-taking-over-the-cold-call-salesforce-leader.html">schedule such calls</a> , which can make them feel like just another name on a list.</p><p> In an effort to connect with decision makers, I recently tried going a different route: I wrote notes by hand to several executives and dropped them in the mail. Some of these have led to very positive personal responses and meetings, and even contract discussions. These relationships are being built on <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-susan-mcpherson-on-building-meaningful-relationships-in-business-and-in-life">meaningful foundations</a> that could lead to long-term business growth.</p><p> There have always been people who prefer to write business notes by hand, but it&#39;s never before carried such a significant connotation — that a real person has taken the time to write out a personalized message rather than choosing an easier option. And a recent study shows how powerful that can be: Researchers from business schools at the University of Maryland and Yonsei University in South Korea found that “presenting a <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/10949968221102306?journalCode=jnma">handwritten note</a> has a positive and significant effect on customer spending” and that “warmth underlies the key findings.”</p><h3> Humanizing Communication</h3><p></p><p> A similar principle applies to internal communication as well. Some managers now use technology for things like employee recognition and turn to generative AI to create and send complimentary messages to team members. While this may be helpful for overwhelmed and exhausted managers, it can also reduce the sense of meaning and personalization that employees may be looking for. This is why handwritten notes can be a powerful way for managers to show employees — especially <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-create-belonging-for-remote-workers/">remote workers</a> , who aren&#39;t in the office to receive such recognition face to face — their genuine appreciation.</p><p> Writing notes by hand may not be the right move for everyone — such as if someone&#39;s penmanship is particularly difficult to read. But there are other ways to personalize communication, including creating videos or voice memos tailored to a specific individual, or even leaving a voicemail if a phone call goes unanswered. Some people block off a time in their schedule and say, “I&#39;m going to keep this two-hour block open in hopes that you might want to chat. Reach out anytime within that time frame, and I&#39;ll drop whatever I&#39;m doing.”</p><p> The key is to always be on the lookout for ways to emphasize our humanity in our communications. The more we do that, the less of an interloper AI will be in our relationships — and the more authentic and rewarding they&#39;ll become.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Four-Day Workweek: How to Make It Work in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Barnes. <p>Andrew Barnes is the founder of Perpetual Guardian, New Zealand&#39;s largest corporate trustee company. He is also a cofounder of 4 Day Week Global and the author of <cite>The 4 Day Week</cite> (Piatkus, 2020).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[As cofounder of 4 Day Week Global, Andrew Barnes has a front-row seat to the world’s largest experiment on the effects of scaling back the workweek. It started with Barnes’s own New Zealand company, Perpetual Guardian, when he wondered whether his staff members could do their jobs better if they worked the equivalent of four [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA01_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> As cofounder of 4 Day Week Global, Andrew Barnes has a front-row seat to the world&#39;s largest experiment on the effects of scaling back the workweek.</p><p> It started with Barnes&#39;s own New Zealand company, Perpetual Guardian, when he wondered whether his staff members could do their jobs better if they worked the equivalent of four days instead of five. It would be crucial, he knew, to still deliver the same output, customer service, and profitability. He landed on what he calls the 100-80-100 rule: “We pay 100% income for 80% time, as long as we get 100% output.”</p><p> The trial made global headlines — “We stopped counting when we got over about 14,000” — and Barnes was inundated with requests for advice. He started a not-for-profit organization and began helping companies on their own pilots, providing virtual workshops, mentoring others, and networking opportunities. The results, which now include data from 91 companies and 3,500 workers, have been analyzed by a team of academics.</p><p></p><p> And those results have been universally positive. “Not only are 90%-plus of employees saying they like the four-day week — and, in fact, they really don&#39;t want to go back — but companies are seeing material benefits in productivity,” Barnes said.</p><p></p><p> Barnes talked about the experiments and their findings during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023. He wasn&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the event, so he answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> Is there any research comparing a four-day workweek versus five reduced days (at six hours a day, for example)? Do the results suggest that four days is the better way?</h6><p> Both are viewed by us as four-day weeks! The clickbait is “a four-day week,” but in reality, we talk about <em>reduced hours working</em> — the 100-80-100 rule. The key is that employees get the time off that&#39;s important to <em>them</em> . In my company, we have some people who take a full day off, others who take two half days, and others, often working parents, who work compressed hours five days a week. That schedule helps with child care issues, which a single day off would not address.</p><p></p><h6> How do you measure the success of the four-day workweek from the perspective of employees and teams when it comes to productivity versus company results like revenue?</h6><p> Obviously, it&#39;s easier to see whether there&#39;s improvement in company results such as profitability and revenue. We often find that people ask how we measure employee productivity. This, of course, raises the question of how productivity is <em>currently</em> being measured. All too often, it quickly becomes clear that many organizations use time as a surrogate for productivity.</p><p> Part of our program is helping organizations develop other productivity measures so that improvements can be more clearly assessed. A key part of this is helping employees identify the unproductive parts of their day. Simply eliminating unproductive activity will, by definition, increase productive activity.</p><h6> I find that much of what fills the time outside of tactical work are personal conversations and relationship-building. Do those things diminish when you move to a four-day week?</h6><p> No. In fact, the evidence suggests that these improve. By combining policies such as quiet hours (deep work), fewer and shorter meetings, and better social facilities (in our case, a better staff breakout area), we find that staff cohesion and team-building actually increase. By reinforcing that staff members need to work together to allow everyone to achieve the objective of reduced hours of working, there is often more time for these interactions, not less.</p><h6> Gallup&#39;s US panel data from 2020 shows that employees who work four days per week have higher well-being than those who work five or six days. However, Gallup&#39;s data also shows that the <a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/358346/gallup-workplace-insights-learned-2021.aspx">percentage who are actively disengaged rises</a> among those who work fewer days. Gallup says that employees who already feel disconnected from their employer are likely to drift even further away. What do you advise companies to do to address this?</h6><p> In the context of a society where many employees work from home and are therefore separated from the usual workplace culture, the impact of reduced hours working is actually minimal. It is also necessary to differentiate between the old style of four-day-week working (where only a few worked four days and most worked five, often with the former receiving lower pay) and the new model, where everyone works a reduced schedule with no reduction in pay. Companies in our trials report significant increases in engagement scores. In the case of our own company, scores increased by 40% — to levels the researchers said were the highest they had ever seen in New Zealand.</p><h6> What differences do you see in the effects of the four-day workweek on people doing different kinds of work — say, between software developers and creative workers versus salespeople?</h6><p> Obviously, there are practical differences in how the work is actually done, but the impact on employees across the companies in our various trials appears to be consistent. Employees report being more productive, more rested, less stressed, and happier. It is a thesis of mine that healthier, happier, more rested employees are more productive. Who would have thought!</p><h6> What kind of training and prep do companies do to introduce a four-day week?</h6><p> We encourage organizations to take a couple of months to plan and prepare before initiating the six-month trial. Both the preparation and trial allow organizations to flex the process to find out what works for them. The bulk of the efficiencies and improvements come from empowering staff members and creating a culture where individuals recognize that they have to work together to reduce wasted time. In my own organization and in many others, training was therefore limited and largely unnecessary.</p><h6> How do you build employee trust to successfully achieve the stated goals when implementing a reduced workweek?</h6><p> Put simply, if trust does not exist prior to the implementation of the four-day week, it is unlikely the implementation will be successful.</p><h6> We run a 24-hour operation. Have you seen this done in organizations such as this, and what is the impact on the staffing numbers? Don&#39;t you have to increase the number of employees?</h6><p> In many ways, it is easier to introduce a four-day week into a seven-day, 24-hour operation, as the organization is already running shift patterns. A reduced-hour week simply requires shifts to be reconfigured. Remember that our thesis is that productivity actually increases, so in some operations, each shift can be staffed with fewer employees.</p><p> Alternatively, in people-heavy organizations such as medical facilities, it is likely that more staff will have to be recruited. The savings here, though, come from reduced recruitment time and turnover, fewer sick days (67% fewer, according to the trial data) with reduced impact on productivity, and lower costs for expensive temporary staff. Evidence also suggests that outcomes improve.</p><h6> Have you done this work with clients in consulting industries? What kind of success have you had there? How was billable time affected?</h6><p>是的。 PR firms, legal firms, and consultancies have all moved to the four-day week. Billable hours is often quoted as an impediment, but it is simply a mechanism to allocate costs. The clients pay on value and outcomes. If you can now do the work quicker under the four-day model, just adjust the cost allocation units. The client doesn&#39;t care. A simple example: Two consultants produce an identical piece of work. One takes an hour, one half an hour. Why would the client pay twice as much for the former? In reality, billable hours get adjusted in order to align the bill with the amount the client will pay.</p><p></p><h6> What obstacles did you encounter when making the switch to a four-day workweek?</h6><p> The principal obstacle was that members of my leadership team were highly skeptical, if not hostile, and my board universally hated it. Bringing leadership on the journey and helping them to walk the talk is critical for the project&#39;s success. I have set out the usual obstacles in various papers that are on the <a href="https://www.4dayweek.com/">4dayweek.com</a> website and in my book, <cite>The 4 Day Week</cite> .</p><h6> Can you provide sample policies used by companies?</h6><p> The 4dayweek.com website has lots of helpful material, including the research and a white paper. That white paper includes the policies we introduced at Perpetual Guardian to implement the reduced schedule.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Communication Is at the Heart of Positive Employee Relationships</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Laker. <p>Ben Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School and coauthor of <cite>Too Proud to Lead: How Hubris Can Destroy Effective Leadership and What to Do About It</cite> (Bloomsbury, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment. Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Laker_Communication-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> In today&#39;s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment.</p><p> Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can significantly affect their organization&#39;s reputation as a place where people want to work. After all, having a culture that incorporates transparent and open communication is essential to building trust and loyalty.</p><p></p><h3> The Importance of Communication Skills in Hiring</h3><p> According to research, oral and written <a href="https://newmanu.edu/top-5-skills-employers-look-for">communication skills</a> are among the top five most sought-after attributes in potential new hires: Employers want workers who can effectively convey their ideas, perspectives, and knowledge.</p><p> Employees with strong communication skills are able to express their thoughts and emotions clearly, making them more efficient in the workplace. Additionally, they are better equipped to manage challenging conversations or negotiations with clients or coworkers through their ability to listen attentively, provide accurate feedback, and resolve conflicts.</p><p> Good communication skills also foster a better company culture: Employees create a stronger bond when they are able to effectively communicate with one another. This not only creates a cohesive and productive work environment but also increases their loyalty to the organization.</p><p></p><p> Hiring managers should screen resumes for clear and concise writing abilities and pay attention to how candidates speak during interviews to assess their communication skills. If appropriate, they should request written work samples before an interview to assess candidates&#39; writing capabilities. Candidates who can effectively communicate their qualifications and skills in writing will likely be able to better articulate them orally during the interview.</p><p></p><h3> The Hiring Process: Clear Expectations and Open Dialogue</h3><p> All parties involved in the hiring process need to be clear and concise when conveying information. Hiring managers must clearly define expectations, roles, and responsibilities when talking to potential candidates: One study found that 48% of employees who left a job early did so because their employer&#39;s <a href="https://www.hrdive.com/news/study-48-of-workers-have-left-a-job-because-it-didnt-meet-expectations/551179/">expectations were unclear</a> .</p><p> Establishing an open dialogue with candidates during the hiring process is essential for building trust and gaining insight into their communication styles. By using a combination of open-ended questions, role-playing scenarios, and exercises that focus on communication, employers can better understand each candidate&#39;s approach to their work and create a foundation for a strong working relationship.</p><p> Once a new hire is brought on board, providing feedback on their communication skills can help them understand what they are already doing well and where they can improve.</p><h3> Navigating Layoffs: Transparency, Empathy, and Compliance</h3><p> In an era marked by recession fears and downsizing, how companies handle layoffs can have a profound impact on their reputation and employee morale. To maintain a positive relationship with employees during layoffs, employers should prioritize clear, honest, and timely communication. This means providing as much advance notice as possible to all employees, explaining the rationale behind the decision, and offering support to those affected, such as career counseling, resume preparation, and job search assistance. By treating employees with respect and empathy, companies can minimize negative impacts and maintain a favorable reputation.</p><p> Furthermore, organizations must comply with laws governing layoffs to ensure the fair treatment of employees and avoid legal repercussions. Employers should be aware of their state and local laws to ensure that they meet minimum notice requirements and other regulations. Consider the case of Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, where the initial decision to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bed-bath-beyond-to-pay-out-severance-to-1300-workers-after-initially-bypassing-law/ar-AA1aKgBG">bypass severance laws</a> led to lawsuits — and thus more negative publicity for a company that had recently declared bankruptcy — followed by a reversal of the decision.</p><h3> Creating a Culture of Open Communication</h3><p></p><p> The key to fostering positive relationships with candidates and employees alike lies in creating a culture of open communication. This means valuing transparency, honesty, and empathy, no matter the stage of employment. Companies should also encourage open dialogue among all levels of the organization, providing opportunities for employees to voice their concerns and ideas. This can help to establish a sense of trust, promote a collaborative work environment, and, ultimately, contribute to the company&#39;s overall success.</p><p> In addition to fostering open communication, employers should invest in training and development programs that help employees enhance their communication skills. This benefits the individuals, contributes to a more effective and cohesive work environment, and can, ultimately, lead to greater success for the organization and a more productive work environment overall. By prioritizing communication at every stage of the employee life cycle, managers can foster a positive work culture in which individuals feel valued, supported, and empowered to succeed.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> It&#39;s Time to Face the Three Challenges of Learning</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the-three-challenges-of-learning/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the-three-challenges-of-learning/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) is a professor of management practice at London Business School and founder of the advisory practice HSM. Her most recent book is <cite>Redesigning Work: How to Transform Your Organization and Make Hybrid Work for Everyone</cite> (MIT Press, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Virtual Teams]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Austin/theispot.com Most executives acknowledge that learning is crucial to the performance of their business. But at a recent research workshop that my team and I ran with executives from over 40 companies, it became clear that organizations’ traditional learning models are facing pressure from the emergence of new work models. The participants identified these [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023-0626_Gratton_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Michael Austin/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Most executives acknowledge that learning is crucial to the performance of their business. But at a recent research workshop that my team and I ran with executives from over 40 companies, it became clear that organizations&#39; traditional learning models are facing pressure from the emergence of new work models. The participants identified these three learning challenges as the most acute:</p><p> <strong>1. Increased workloads have reduced learning time.</strong> Eighty-eight percent of executives at our workshop chose workload pressures as one of their top challenges. They said that many employees, particularly those managing others, feel that their workloads have significantly increased in recent years. Some shared sensitive internal data that suggests burnout has increased during that period. The net result of higher workloads is that employees not only lack the headspace for learning but also feel pressured to prioritize work tasks over learning activities. Battling this challenge will require leaders to maximize the value of any available learning time.</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. Hybrid work has increased the complexity of learning.</strong> Two-thirds (66%) of executives said that flexibility in terms of where and when employees work is an important challenge. Executives fretted that employees may not be connected in moments that matter for formal and informal learning. Managers reported that they find it more difficult to identify development opportunities for remote employees and that they fear that remote work is having a negative impact on how people share tacit knowledge. Indeed, research shows that 47% of employees are concerned about <a href="https://newsroom.poly.com/English/press-releases/news-details/2021/Poly-Evolution-of-the-Workplace-Report-Highlights-Need-for-Work-Equity-and-Total-Meeting-Equality-for-Hybrid-Workers/">missing out on informal learning opportunities</a> while working from home. Addressing this challenge will require leaders to build a robust learning strategy in a hybrid business environment.</p><p> <strong>3. A tightening labor market has brought skill shortages.</strong> Sixty-five percent of executives identified finding workers with specialized skills as a major challenge. Many of the executives we spoke with said their companies have historically looked to the external labor market for these specialty hires. However, as the market tightens, particularly for hard-to-find digital skills, the focus has shifted to boosting the skills of internal employees. Reskilling has always been seen as important, but now it&#39;s critical. Tackling this challenge will require leaders to align business strategy with expertly executed upskilling and reskilling initiatives.</p><p> While these are tough challenges to face, executives also acknowledge how important it is to solve them. Skill shortages are one reason, but there is also the significant motivational impact of successful corporate learning.</p><p> In today&#39;s volatile labor market, where employees are quick to move from one job to a more advantageous opportunity, the chance to learn something new that will be valuable in the future is a central reason why they stay. Indeed, studies show that 76% of employees say they would <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work-is-just-work">stay at their jobs longer</a> if they could benefit from learning and development support.</p><p> Moreover, in the face of growing concerns about workplace inequalities, there is a perception that <a href="https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/files/5552_en.pdf">skills-based learning</a> can help to significantly reduce them. This is particularly the case for employees who are not highfliers, who don&#39;t have a college degree or an educational certificate, or who have historically been excluded.</p><p></p><h3> How Companies Are Relearning How to Learn</h3><p> So here is the paradox: At the very time that learning is seen as a crucial part of the business strategy of many companies, those tasked with delivering on a learning agenda describe significant uphill battles.</p><p> Still, I&#39;m seeing experiments by managers who are rising to the occasion by trying out new ways of learning and new ways of delivering learning that can be models for others in similar situations. Here&#39;s how they&#39;re addressing the three essential concerns.</p><h4> 1. They&#39;re using personalization to maximize the value of learning time.</h4><p> One way of making sure every hour devoted to learning counts is by closely aligning learning with the specific needs of the learner. This kind of personalization is typically hard to deliver at scale. But experimentation with virtual and online instruction has opened up routes toward personalizing learning.</p><p> One approach is to develop learning plans, or pathways. At the Dublin-based law firm Matheson, the learning team offers 12 learning pathways (that change annually) from which employees can choose, such as the client experience or environmental, social, and corporate governance issues. Each pathway is a blend of participation in core projects and tutorials delivered by employees who are subject matter experts. One important innovation is that the pathways are available to both lawyers and business service employees. A member of the learning team told me that the approach is designed to break down the traditional siloes between those communities and embed learning into the natural flow of work.</p><p></p><p> Other organizations have approached the task of personalized learning by using AI-driven career diagnostics. Accenture developed an AI tool called Job Buddy to help employees build individual learning plans based on data about themselves, their group, and the external labor market. The tool was designed to use machine learning algorithms to suggest career paths and upskilling opportunities based on an individual&#39;s current job, skills, and experience. Following this individual diagnostic, a learning platform provided resources such as online courses, workshops, and mentoring programs.</p><h4> 2. They&#39;re leaning into the hybrid experience.</h4><p> The pandemic increased the prevalence of hybrid working and set the scene for learning to be as flexible as work is.</p><p></p><p> At global online marketplace Etsy, peer-to-peer learning has always been a priority. Zofia Ciechowska, Etsy&#39;s vice president of strategy and operations, told me that learning is viewed as an opportunity for employees and even vendors to share their knowledge, skills, or craft with the community. Employees have run courses on a vast range of topics as diverse as how to navigate the Tokyo subway system and how to make a candle. The sheer variety of courses is a reflection of Etsy&#39;s culture and mission of keeping commerce “human” by enabling people to showcase their talents and educate one another.</p><p> Crucially, in the spirit of hybrid work, Etsy&#39;s workshops are delivered both face to face and online. Employees, whatever their work schedules, are able to participate fully. This rich community-based learning program has successfully driven informal connections, piqued curiosity, and resulted in robust employee engagement scores.</p><p> The learning team said it has been fascinating to see the benefits of learning flow in both directions — for the person being taught as well as those delivering the courses. Employees get a chance to show off their passions and engage with their peers by sharing knowledge they are proud of.</p><h4> 3. They&#39;re reducing skill shortages by focusing on transferable skills.</h4><p> In the face of tightening labor markets and skill shortages, the most obvious learning strategy is to focus on reskilling current employees rather than recruiting new ones. The challenge, as many executives shared, is that this is fiendishly hard, particularly at scale.</p><p> As an international bank, HSBC is changing constantly, and reskilling is essential to delivering on its strategic plan. The bank is working to ensure that all employees are equipped with the skills and knowledge they need to grow in their careers so they can be successful now and in the future.</p><p> The bank recently rolled out a skills-based development program for internal candidates who want to pursue a career in wealth services. By spending 20% of their working time over a period of three to nine months, participants were able to identify, assess, and develop the transferable skills they needed to move into relationship manager roles in the bank&#39;s wealth and private banking services businesses.</p><p></p><p> “This pioneering program is helping us build a strategic talent pipeline for a very important part of our business,” said Laura Powell, HSBC&#39;s global head of HR for wealth and personal banking and global functions. HSBC plans to extend the program to external candidates later this year.</p><p></p><p> Only 2% of executives who were part of our research workshop on learning said they believe that instructor-led learning will be a priority for their organization going forward. Instead, 39% said that “in the workflow” learning would be more important.</p><p> What has come through crystal clear is that while some of the more traditional forms of learning are diminishing, experiments and new projects are demonstrating how significant challenges can be overcome.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the-three-challenges-of-learning/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>