<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 12 月 21 日星期四 16:09:35 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator><item><title>开放式创新二十年</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/twenty-years-of-open-innovation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/twenty-years-of-open-innovation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Henry Chesbrough. <p>亨利·切斯布鲁 (Henry Chesbrough) 是罗马路易斯·吉多·卡利大学 (Luiss Guido Carli University) 开放创新与可持续发展专业的 Maire Tecnimont 教授，也是加州大学伯克利分校哈斯商学院加伍德企业创新中心的教职主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Innovation Process]]></category><category><![CDATA[Open Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Twenty years ago, I introduced the concept of open innovation in an MIT Sloan Management Review article. Where do we stand two decades later? We’ve seen some companies enjoy great success with this approach and witnessed the difficulties of others. One surprising insight 20 years on is that the biggest barriers to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Chesborough-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡罗琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p>二十年前，我在<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-era-of-open-innovation"><cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的一篇文章</a>中介绍了<em>开放式创新</em>的概念。二十年后，我们现在处于什么位置？我们看到一些公司通过这种方法取得了巨大成功，也目睹了其他公司所面临的困难。 20 年后的一个令人惊讶的见解是，成功开放式创新的最大障碍来自组织内部，而不是组织外部。</p><p>开放式创新强调利用外部资源（例如客户、初创公司、众包平台和大学）来开发新产品和服务的创意。更正式地说，它可以被定义为一个分布式创新过程，涉及跨组织边界的知识流动，无论是出于金钱还是非金钱的原因。为了创新，我们需要将知识从其所在的地方转移到需要它的地方。通常，这意味着调动人员，以便知识渊博的员工可以共同协作创造新事物。在其他时候，可能需要新的工作流程和结构来创建激励措施和程序来转移知识。为了通过开放式创新取得成功，组织需要能够跨所有部门（无论是职能部门、部门还是地理部门）调动和获取知识，以设计、开发和交付客户所需的创新。</p><p></p><p>开放式创新二十年来有很多值得庆祝的事情。许多研究发现证据表明它可以改善财务绩效。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>采用社区创新调查进行的全国性研究发现，在控制其他因素的情况下，拥有更多外部知识来源的组织比那些来源较少的组织取得更好的创新绩效。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>一项针对 125 家大公司的调查还发现，采用开放式创新的组织获得了更好的创新成果。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>尽管取得了这一成功，但仍有许多工作要做。为了使开放式创新取得成功，仅仅确定可能有用的知识来源、访问这些来源、与他们协商可能的合作、然后将新知识融入新的创新产品和服务中是不够的。事实上，更深入的研究发现，组织在使用开放式创新时面临的最大问题往往来自于其内部，而不是外部。在开放式创新中与外部参与者进行协作和协调通常需要改变组织工作流程，并可能引发内部创新者的防御性反应。</p><p></p><p>最近的一篇论文清楚地记录了开放式创新的内部阻力。在 Hila Lifshitz-Assaf 对 NASA 采用开放式创新实践的研究中，她重点关注利用众包来产生新想法。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>一个成功的想法使 NASA 能够显着提高其预测太阳耀斑的能力。然而，在美国宇航局约翰逊航天中心内，工程师们对从该机构外部获得的结果感到不安。他们的身份感和对自己在组织中角色的理解似乎受到开放创新成果的威胁。</p><p>当组织边界导致关键活动更加集中和专业化时，它们可能会成为开放式创新的障碍。有用的知识<em>在筒仓内</em>流动良好，但在筒仓<em>之间</em>（例如不同部门、职能区域或地理位置）却不能很好地流动。</p><p>以企业风险投资 (CVC) 计划为例，该计划投资于新技术和市场，创建初创企业投资组合。如果同一家公司的业务部门通常认为这些年轻企业太不成熟、太遥远、风险太大，不值得给予太多关注和承诺，那么 CVC 团队的知识将无法渗透到任何可以利用和扩展这些知识的业务部门。</p><p></p><p>英特尔在与有前途的初创公司合作时反复遇到这个问题，并创建了一个新的部门——新业务计划（NBI）来解决这个问题。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> NBI 的团队与新的初创企业建立了关系，然后尝试通过金钱和知识这两个要素将这些企业与英特尔业务部门联系起来。这笔资金为业务部门整合项目提供了直接资源；此前，业务部门往往要等到下一个财年才能获得此类资源。与此同时，一旦项目转移到业务部门，开发机会的NBI团队就解散了。接收业务部门开始处理该项目后，经常会提出疑问，但现在分散的团队无法回答这些问题。 NBI 通过部署一名团队成员带着该项目前往新业务部门进行六到九个月的旅行，解决了这一知识问题。该人通常知道业务部门问题的答案，或者知道如何找到答案。</p><p>还有其他方法可以克服内部孤岛带来的障碍。一种简单但有效的方法是让人们在组织内轮换职位，从一个筒仓到另一个筒仓。例如，业务部门的经理可以轮流到 CVC 小组工作 6 到 12 个月，反之亦然。这种轮换可以帮助人们在一个孤岛中建立联系和经验，然后将其带到组织的新部门。随着时间的推移，在三年内轮换 5% 或 10% 员工的组织将发现更容易识别和获取组织大部分部门的有用知识，并且能够很好地进行内部流程更改有效地利用这些知识。</p><p>超越内部孤岛的补充策略是指派高级管理人员对组织的主要客户负责。思科过去经常这样做，每位 C 级高管都被赋予管理自己职能部门的任务<em>，并</em>成为思科与公司一些最大客户之间关系的执行维护者。由于客户的创新需求总是涉及思科内部多个职能部门的变化，这迫使每位高管对公司进行全面思考。如果相关群体不了解他们在创造、开发和交付创新中的作用以及他们需要做出哪些改变来实现创新，这些创新机会就无法推进。为解决一个客户的问题而促进多个部门之间的协作的职能领导者经常会发现其他高管要求她与其他部门合作以获得另一个客户的创新机会。高管奖金部分与特定客户的新产品和服务销售挂钩，进一步促进了跨部门和职能的内部共享和协作。</p><p></p><p>跨组织边界转移知识的另一种机制是，如果内部同行对他们的需求没有反应，则允许每个小组、职能或部门的成员在组织外部进行购买或销售。中国白色家电制造商海尔创建了“人单合一”，这是一个复杂的组织内部和外部承包系统，为未来海尔产品和服务所需的产品和服务的供应和购买创造了内部市场。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>该系统取代了以前限制部门活动的大部分内部组织孤岛。在人单合一的领导下，各部门被转变为公司内部的微型企业，可以自由地与组织内部（有时也包括外部）的任何人签订合同以实现其目标。这一体系加快了海尔内部的创新速度，并在此过程中向更多的外部合作开放。它还使公司能够启动新的业务计划。</p><p>最终，20 年的开放式创新表明，该模型的许多最大挑战在于寻求创新的组织内部，而不是与外部组织进行沟通和谈判。打破孤岛是开放式创新成功的关键，这种方法已经取得了显著成果。如今，在 LinkedIn 上，人们可以找到数十万人在他们的个人资料中标明“开放式创新”。这一概念提出二十年后，我们已经准备好看看开放式创新能走多远。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/twenty-years-of-open-innovation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为您的董事会增添网络安全专业知识</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/adding-cybersecurity-expertise-to-your-board/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/adding-cybersecurity-expertise-to-your-board/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 20 Dec 2023 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Chon Abraham, Sasha Cohen O’Connell, Iria Giuffrida, and Ronald R. Sims. <p>Chon Abraham 是威廉玛丽梅森商学院运营和信息系统管理领域的曼斯菲尔德商学（信息系统）教授。萨莎·科恩·奥康奈尔 (Sasha Cohen O&#39;Connell) 是美利坚大学公共事务学院司法、法律和犯罪学系的高级教授讲师和常驻行政人员。 Iria Giuffrida 是威廉玛丽法学院的法律实践教授兼学术和教职事务副院长。罗纳德·R·西姆斯 (Ronald R. Sims) 是威廉玛丽梅森商学院的弗洛伊德·杜威·戈特瓦尔德 (Floyd Dewey Gottwald) 工商管理名誉教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The Research This article draws on the authors’ experiences consulting with boards and senior cybersecurity personnel, discussions at the 2023 Women in Cybersecurity Conference, and targeted interviews with 15 CISOs serving as board members for public and private organizations across various sectors. Against a backdrop of persistent cyberattacks, and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Abraham-Cybersecurity-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>本文借鉴了作者与董事会和高级网络安全人员进行咨询的经验、2023 年网络安全女性会议上的讨论以及对担任各行业公共和私营组织董事会成员的 15 名 CISO 的有针对性的采访。</p></aside><p>在网络攻击持续存在的背景下，在新法规的推动下，企业董事会正在努力建立更好的能力来监督网络安全风险管理。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>虽然这对于健康的公司治理来说是个好消息，但对于寻求物色和招聘具有适当技能、经验和人脉的新董事的公司来说，它提出了直接的挑战。</p><p>鉴于网络安全风险的重要性，早就应该更多地关注这一领域的董事会技能和组成。普华永道 2023 年年度公司董事调查的受访者将网络安全风险视为对董事会的重大挑战，仅次于战略/破坏性风险，64% 的受访者表示，在过去 12 个月中，他们增加了专门讨论该主题的董事会会议时间。然而，只有 19% 的受访者表示，他们在过去一年中增加了一位具有网络安全经验的新董事会成员。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p>缺乏网络安全战略专业知识的上市公司董事会可能更容易受到网络犯罪分子的攻击，而投资者和进行尽职调查的潜在客户很快就会更加明显地发现这种风险。 2023 年 7 月，美国证券交易委员会通过了新规则，要求及时、全面地披露网络安全信息，从 2023 年 12 月 15 日之后提交的 10-K 表格开始<a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">。3</a>新规则要求披露如何识别和管理网络安全风险、以及管理层在实施网络安全政策和程序中的作用。公司现在需要描述董事会对网络安全威胁风险的监督以及董事会董事的网络安全专业知识水平。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>总体而言，新规则旨在提高投资者对风险管理实践和重大网络安全事件的认识。</p><p>复杂、不断变化的网络安全风险与业务风险交织在一起，需要至少一名具有深厚技术和业务知识和经验的董事会董事的重点关注。例如，在决定使用人工智能等新兴技术来提高运营效率时，需要仔细权衡新安全风险的潜力。</p><p>大型国家卫生组织首席信息安全官 (CISO) 的经验清楚地表明，合格的董事会董事可以在多大程度上帮助推进董事会的网络实践。在接受我们采访时，一位竞争对手的前 CISO 已加入其公司董事会，他表示：“她了解这个行业，看过别人的运作方式，并且拥有丰富的商业经验。她是一个令人难以置信的资源，非常适合。”他赞扬了该董事会成员为非技术人员翻译困难概念的能力，以及她愿意向他（CISO）提出非常尖锐的问题。 “她带来的是理解、翻译和激励的知识。所有这些都确保董事会得到他们需要的东西，而我不会陷入细节之中，”他总结道。</p><p>正如示例所示，具有深厚网络安全专业知识的董事会董事可以与高级管理层和 IT 团队密切合作，并为识别漏洞、评估风险和开发解决方案提供宝贵的见解。他们还可以在监督定期安全审计、确保审查与业务目标相关的合同以了解网络安全影响以及帮助 IT 团队与其他团队（例如法律团队）一起开展事件响应工作方面发挥关键的领导作用。</p><h3>董事会网络安全策略师需要多样化的能力</h3><p>问题在于，虽然许多董事会知道他们需要聘请一位精通网络安全的董事，但他们不太清楚这个角色需要什么或需要什么经验。下面，我们将讨论董事会网络安全专家角色的关键方面以及需要寻找的资格。这些见解应该会对董事会有所帮助，因为董事会正在寻求增加对公司网络安全弹性产生积极影响的人选，并向投资者证明这些重大风险得到了妥善管理。</p><p></p><p>一名优秀的网络战略家不仅仅具备技术能力。他们拥有强大的技术知识和业务理解能力，以及沟通能力和危机管理技能。根据我们的研究，我们编制了有效增强董事会网络监督能力所需的 5 点技能框架。 （请参阅“董事会网络战略家技能星座”。）我们将依次研究其中每一项。对于每个能力领域，我们编制了一份相关资格列表。要将这些作为评估候选人的评分标准，如果候选人非常合格，则奖励 2 分；如果合格，则奖励 1 分；如果缺乏特定资格，则不得分。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>董事会网络战略家技能星座</h4><p class="caption">能够为改善网络安全监督做出有效贡献的董事会董事必须拥有均衡且多样化的技能和经验。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Abraham_CyberSecurity_Fig.png" alt="董事会网络战略家技能星座" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h4> 1. 行业背景丰富的技术专长。</h4><p>专家委员会成员最基本的资格是了解网络安全威胁、漏洞、提高防御和弹性的技术最佳实践的具体细节。这些知识还使他们能够深入了解攻击在特定业务环境中的表现方式：攻击者想要什么，以及他们可能的目标是什么。他们还应该对跨组织边界共享网络威胁情报 (CTI) 有深入的了解。网络战略家了解及时 CTI 所提供的价值，并且应用“如果你看到什么，就说些什么”的原则（即使是对竞争对手）可以减少信息、产品和服务供应链中的连锁反应。 （毕竟，该公司可能既是该供应链中的提供者又是消费者。）</p><p>网络安全不仅涉及应对眼前的威胁，还涉及提前规划并实施以行业标准和法规为指导的预防措施，例如美国国家标准与技术研究院 (NIST)、国际标准化组织 (ISO)、互联网安全中心以及网络安全和基础设施安全局。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>此类框架和法规为创建安全系统提供了全球公认的指南，熟悉它们是该领域技术能力的重要组成部分。网络战略家还应该充分掌握与组织特定行业相关的标准。</p><p>评估候选人的技术经验，以证明他们有能力为战略决策提供建议。查找以下内容：</p><ul><li>需要熟悉基本网络安全技能和工具的职位（例如 CISO、CTO、CIO、首席数据官或安全经理）。</li><li>拥有参与网络安全技术标准、政府政策或咨询工作组（例如 NIST、ISO 27001 或 IANS Research）的经验。</li><li>教育（例如网络安全、计算机科学或信息系统的学士到高级学位）。</li><li>认证技术培训和认证，例如认证信息安全经理 (CISM) 或认证信息系统安全专家 (CISSP)。</li></ul><h4> 2. 商业头脑，包括风险管理。</h4><p>将网络安全目标与更广泛的业务目标保持一致需要对降低实现这些目标的风险进行战略思考。例如，网络战略家可以识别和评估与整合从并购中获得的企业技术相关的前景和风险。</p><p>正如一家科技公司的首席执行官对我们所说：“我们需要一个懂业务的人。 ......他们必须能够了解非网络董事会成员的运营和底线财务风险。”</p><p>网络战略家应该对战略业务目标有透彻的了解，并能够阐明网络安全资产如何帮助实现这些目标。此外，了解和评估潜在网络事件的“爆炸半径”的能力（特别是它们如何波及公司的整个价值链）至关重要。</p><p></p><p>鉴于网络安全专业人士在高管和最高管理层级别上相对占优势，许多候选人可能缺乏更广泛的业务经验。然而，他们可以通过众多重点培训计划之一为晋升为董事做好准备。</p><p>通过寻找以下内容来评估候选人与网络安全相关的商业头脑：</p><ul><li>了解国内外与数据隐私和违规保护相关的法律法规，例如欧盟的《通用数据保护条例》和《加州消费者隐私法》。</li><li>具有管理网络安全投资和预算的能力。</li><li>例如，由全国公司董事协会加速计划或经过认证的学术机构计划提供的董事培训和认证。</li></ul><p></p><h4> 3. 利益相关群体之间的有效沟通。</h4><p>网络战略家的沟通技巧可能对于帮助董事会了解网络风险的重要性及其潜在的财务、法律和声誉后果至关重要。正如一位 CISO 和董事会成员向我们所说的那样，董事会中没有人真正理解拥有 200 多个未修补的漏洞意味着什么，但他们确实理解如果这些漏洞得不到解决，承担 4 亿美元的总责任意味着什么。专家委员会成员应该能够在首席财务官和总法律顾问的帮助下提供此类背景信息。</p><p>有影响力的网络战略家的沟通是双向的——代表技术团队与董事会沟通，以及代表董事会与网络安全人员或其他技术人员沟通。沿着这些思路，网络战略家应该指导 CIO、CISO 和其他人并建立信任，以便他们能够有效地用非技术术语解释相关网络安全问题，并轻松地与董事会共享信息或回答问题。促进这种类型的沟通有助于促进一种文化，使 CISO 有信心向董事会提出明确的要求并提供支持这些要求所需的详细信息。</p><p>通过考虑以下因素来评估候选人与技术和业务利益相关者沟通的能力：</p><ul><li>对跨行业和公司类型的高级管理人员进行网络安全风险教育的经验丰富。</li><li>拥有使用信息风险因素分析等模型来量化网络安全风险以支持战略决策的经验。</li><li>拥有指导安全人员进行管理沟通的经验。</li></ul><h4> 4. 网络安全社区的强大网络。</h4><p>对于董事会中有效的网络安全专家来说，与同样关注这些风险的研究和政府领域的同行和主要利益相关者建立牢固的联系至关重要。维护强大的网络是敏锐扫描不断变化的威胁环境并利用这些见解为战略业务决策提供信息的能力的关键，因为许多有用的信息是由可信联系人共享的。</p><p> “你必须在生态系统中拥有良好的声誉，能够利用你获得的情报并提供良好的情报，”一位 CISO 和资深董事会成员告诉我们。 “我可以去找其他公司的同事，了解他们认为什么是公司的首要任务。我总是了解来自 Google 聊天、博客和专业威胁情报团体的最新信息，而且我与当地的 FBI 有着良好的关系。我积极主动地获取有关可能存在威胁的情报。然后我就可以确定我认为董事会需要听到的内容。”</p><p>网络战略家应该密切关注其紧密的同行圈子，即使是那些被视为竞争对手的人（不过，为了避免引发反垄断担忧，在后一种情况下，网络战略家应该咨询该组织的法律顾问）。他们知道成为第一批向生态系统贡献威胁信息的人的价值，因为它建立了相互共享此类情报的关系。他们还应与相关财团和公共部门当局合作，以预测邪恶活动并及时了解行业标准和报告要求。</p><p>如果董事沉默寡言，董事会的网络安全专家可能需要倡导在公司外部共享信息，并解释共享 CTI 如何使整个社区受益，特别是公司自己对他人 CTI 的访问。</p><p>通过询问以下问题来评估候选人网络的深度和广度：</p><ul><li>参与公共/私人网络威胁情报联盟（例如信息共享和分析中心（ISAC））的经验程度。</li><li>与其他专业网络安全组织的参与程度。</li><li>他们的对等网络的范围。</li><li>他们在执法和威胁研究方面的接触程度。</li></ul><h4> 5、创新思维和新兴技术意识。</h4><p> “作为一名战略家，你必须密切关注行业正在发生的事情——什么是热门的，以及人们为了占领新市场而盲目实施的，”我们的一位 CISO 董事会成员消息人士告诉我们。 “所有新技术都有未知的网络影响，即使你是一家非常有远见、创新的公司的董事会成员，有时你也需要成为控制董事会的人。”他补充说，这可能意味着建议公司的安全专家对新的人工智能工具或系统重新配置进行彻底的风险分析。</p><p>网络战略家应主动了解技术的最新趋势和进步，特别是与组织行业相关的趋势和进步。这包括跟上新兴技术的步伐，以确定潜在的创新机会并了解相关风险，例如，监控量子计算的发展，预计这些发展最终将打破目前使用的数据加密方法。当提出新技术或新项目时，网络战略家应提倡评估潜在的网络安全影响。</p><p>战略家还应与运营团队密切合作，了解他们提出的涉及新兴技术的战略和举措。他们可以提供有关网络安全事务的指导和专业知识，并帮助运营部门评估其提案的潜在风险和影响。他们还了解监管要求，并了解让法律团队了解网络战略的重要性。通过合作，他们可以在创新和风险管理之间取得平衡。</p><p>通过考虑以下因素来评估候选人预测新兴技术的风险和收益的能力：</p><p></p><ul><li>能够通过与公司相关的特定新兴技术和创新领域阐明网络安全问题。</li><li>能够评估组织在运营中安全利用人工智能的能力，向高级管理层描述风险并提出缓解措施。</li><li>了解如何利用新技术来改善网络安全运营。</li><li>能够评估企业级网络架构保护方面的组织工作。</li></ul><p></p><p>通过评估通信、技术知识、业务、网络和创新这五个关键领域的网络战略董事会候选人，董事会增加了任命新董事的可能性，新董事将促进有效的讨论，就关键网络安全问题获得明智的建议，并做出深思熟虑的战略决策。但还有一个更重要的品质是不言而喻的：道德指导和行为应该成为网络战略和决策的基石，一般董事会成员也应该如此。我们在本文中回顾的能力只有在坚定不移的道德原则基础上才能真正有益。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/adding-cybersecurity-expertise-to-your-board/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>关于人工智能模型和数据集，管理者应该询问哪些问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-should-ask-about-ai-models-and-data-sets/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-should-ask-about-ai-models-and-data-sets/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Roger W. Hoerl and Thomas C. Redman. <p>Roger W. Hoerl 是纽约州斯克内克塔迪联合学院的 Brate-Peschel 统计学教授，与 Ronald D. Snee 合着了<a href="https://www.pearson.com/en-us/subject-catalog/p/leading-holistic-improvement-with-lean-six-sigma-20/P200000000618/9780134288888"><cite>《Leading Holistic Improvement With Lean Six Sigma 2.0》</cite></a>第二版。 （皮尔逊金融时报出版社，2018 年）。 Thomas C. Redman 是<a href="http://dataqualitysolutions.com/">Data Quality Solutions</a>总裁，也是<a href="https://www.koganpage.com/hr-learning-development/people-and-data-9781398610828"><cite>《People and Data: Uniteding to Transform Your Organization》</cite></a> （KoganPage，2023 年）一书的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Science]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Alice Mollon/Ikon Images The power of AI and the machine learning models on which it is based continue to reshape the rules of business. However, too many AI projects are failing — often after deployment, which is especially costly and embarrassing. Just ask Amazon about its facial recognition fiascos, or Microsoft about its blunders with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Redman_AI_Model-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">艾丽丝·莫伦/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>人工智能及其所基于的机器学习模型的力量继续重塑商业规则。然而，太多的人工智能项目都失败了——通常是在部署之后，这是特别昂贵和令人尴尬的。只要问问亚马逊关于其<a href="https://www.media.mit.edu/articles/face-recognition-researcher-fights-amazon-over-biased-ai/">面部识别的惨败</a>，或者微软关于其<a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/microsoft-and-the-learnings-from-its-failed-tay-artificial-intelligence-bot/">Tay 聊天机器人</a>的错误即可。数据科学家常常将此类故障视为个体异常，而不去寻找有助于预防未来故障的模式。今天的高级业务经理有权力和责任来防止部署后的失败。但要做到这一点，他们必须更多地了解数据集和数据模型，以便向人工智能模型开发人员提出正确的问题并评估答案。</p><p>也许您在想，“但是数据科学家不是训练有素的吗？”当今数据科学家的绝大多数培训都集中在机器学习的机制上，而不是其局限性。这使得数据科学家无法预防或正确诊断人工智能模型故障。人工智能开发人员必须衡量模型适应未来并超越其训练数据集限制的能力——他们称之为<em>泛化性的</em>概念。如今，这个概念的定义不明确且缺乏严谨性。</p><p></p><p>分析界有句话说，模型开发人员和艺术家都有着同样的坏习惯，那就是爱上他们的模型。另一方面，数据却没有得到它所需要的关注。例如，人工智能模型开发人员很容易满足于现成的数据集，而不是寻找更适合当前问题的数据集。</p><p>高级业务经理缺乏技术学科的高级学位，更没有能力发现与人工智能模型和数据集相关的问题。然而，最终决定是否以及如何广泛部署人工智能模型的是这些企业领导者。我们本文的目标是帮助管理者更好地做到这一点，使用：</p><ul><li>提供所需上下文的框架。我们将特别介绍“正确数据”的概念。正确的数据与人工智能项目中实际使用的数据之间的不匹配可能存在风险。</li><li>在建模工作和部署之前和期间询问组织的 AI 模型开发人员的一组六个问题。</li><li>关于如何评估人工智能模型开发人员对这六个问题的回答的指南。</li></ul><h3>如何识别正确的数据：框架</h3><p>人工智能项目的成功或失败取决于它使用的数据集。为了帮助团队获得正确的数据，我们提供了如下所示的五要素框架。让我们将其分解为各个组成部分。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>正确的数据框架</h4><p class="caption">这个人工智能项目注定会成功吗？该框架将帮助您与人工智能模型开发人员进行更明智的讨论。确认要解决的业务问题后，确定正确的数据至关重要，如下所示。如果没有正确的数据集，您的人工智能项目将会失败。但您还需要评估相关部分：训练数据、AI 模型以及将来将应用于模型的数据。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Redman_AI_Model_Fig.png" alt="正确的数据框架" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> <strong>1. 问题和感兴趣的人群。</strong>所有优秀的数据科学都需要<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/framing-data-science-problems-the-right-way-from-the-start/">对要解决的问题进行清晰的陈述</a>。尽管这看起来很明显，但我们发现人工智能模型开发人员通常没有对此给予足够的思考，或者团队成员对他们试图解决的问题有不同的理解。例如，相对于新的自动信用评分模型，我们的最终业务目标是什么？是为了节省时间吗？是为了取代承销商——还是仅仅为他们提供建议？目标是减少贷款错误，还是减少偏见？答案可能涉及这些目标的某种组合。还有一个细节：这一逻辑必须能够向因信用被拒绝的人解释，还是黑盒模型就足够了？这些业务问题的答案将导致不同的解决方案。</p><p> <strong>2.正确数据的概念。</strong>对数据质量基本面的关键贡献是适合<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/11/bad-data-is-sapping-your-teams-productivity">使用的概念</a>- 是否适合给定的数据或适合给定的决策，操作或分析。根据问题的不同，适合使用的适合度可能有很多，但是两个 - “数据对吗？”和“这是正确的数据吗？” - 总是重要的。</p><p>在这里，我们将重点介绍“这是正确的数据吗？”的问题。因为评估普遍性和防止项目失败至关重要。</p><p>要回答这个问题，管理人员必须专注于六个标准（有时也称为维度，功能，属性，需求或方面）：</p><ul><li>相关/完整性：数据应具有预测能力。在我们的信用评分示例中，诸如年龄，晚期付款历史记录和收入之类的属性可能会产生贡献。理想情况下，所有这些属性都包括在内（即，属性集已完成），并且排除了所有误导，无关或非法属性。</li><li>全面/充分的代表性：两个主要问题是“数据是否充分涵盖了感兴趣的人群？”和“是否有足够的足够训练模型？”重要的是，隐私或其他担忧可能决定必须排除某些数据。</li><li>偏见的自由：许多类型的偏见可以隐藏在数据中，并且该维度需要消除它们。在我们的信用评分示例中，这是一个特别关注的问题，任何时候感兴趣的问题都涉及人类。</li><li>及时性：基本问题是“数据必须是多么新？”对于某些问题，较旧的数据可能包含难以消除的偏差。在某些应用中，（未来）数据在创建后不再相关。</li><li>明确的定义：应明确​​定义所有术语，包括<a href="https://www.wired.com/2010/11/1110mars-climate-observer-report/">测量单位</a>。</li><li>适当的排除：在上面的相关性和全面性的讨论中，我们指出，考虑法律，法规，道德和知识产权的考虑，应排除某些数据。例如，使用邮政编码可以成为信用决策中种族的代孕，并且组织必须避免违反规定如何使用个人身份信息的法律。人们越来越担心接受公共资源培训的AI模型可能侵犯知识产权。经理或其公司的法律团队应尽可能充分地阐明要求。</li></ul><p> <strong>3.培训数据。</strong>这是指实际用于训练模型的数据 - 无论实际上是正确的数据还是更容易获得的替代数据。</p><p> <strong>4.模型/算法。</strong>这是机器学习练习的结果。一旦接受培训，将来可以使用新数据在将来更新该模型。这通常称为“未来数据”。</p><p> <strong>5.未来数据。</strong>这是指您还没有的数据，但将来会适用于AI模型。</p><p></p><p>如图所示，<em>正确数据的概念</em>对所有内容都是核心。我们将其称为正确数据的<em>概念</em>，因为它更常见于人们<em>希望</em>数据满足而不是实际数据集的标准。模型开发人员应首先阐明关注的问题和人群。接下来，他们应定义用于训练模型的数据应满足该问题的标准。第三，他们应该比较他们可以实际获得的培训数据与这些标准。然后，他们应该与未来数据进行类似的比较。越来越大的差距或不匹配会导致麻烦。</p><p>正如我们之前指出的那样，开发人员很容易被他们构建的模型迷恋，并且易于获得的数据和最适合业务问题的数据可能会大不相同。为了解决麻烦，业务领导者必须指导团队清醒地考虑正确的数据，培训数据和未来数据。这是针对过度关注，完全模特的傲慢和令人尴尬的AI项目失败的最佳防御。</p><p></p><h3>提出六个穿透问题</h3><p>在此背景下，我们建议经理根据正确的数据框架在三个关键阶段提出一系列尖锐的问题。询问应从您定义问题并继续部署时开始。顺便说一句，如果您想要在数据科学技术词汇方面的帮助，请寻找可以在与模型开发人员会议上为您翻译的人。一些公司甚至正在建立特定的角色和团体，以弥合<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/">数据科学团队和业务领导者之间的这一差距</a>。</p><h4>问题定义期间要问的问题</h4><p>开发人员应首先询问以下两个问题：</p><p> <strong>1.假设该项目成功，您将如何以及在哪里预期开发的模型将被利用？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中寻找的内容：</em>这个问题旨在确定模型开发人员对企业试图解决的真正问题的理解；关于感兴趣的人群，在范围内有什么和超出范围；以及开发人员打算应用的模型的未来多长时间。</p><p>此外，这个问题为接下来的两个设定了舞台。我们建议管理人员对此查询非常要求。从一开始，太多的数据科学工作就<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/framing-data-science-problems-the-right-way-from-the-start/">无法确定问题陈述</a>。</p><p> <strong>2.您将如何获取符合正确数据标准的培训数据？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中要寻找的是什么：</em>这个问题可能是最关键的。在这一点上，模型开发人员正在期待他们可以获取的数据。确保开发人员已经整理了正确的数据标准（使用上述六个注意事项，从相关性开始）。接下来，检查开发人员是否有可靠的计划来获取符合这些标准的数据。如果他们的答案在此阶段不足，请将它们送回绘图板。</p><h4>在AI模型开发期间要问的问题</h4><p>一旦开发人员完成了问题定义阶段，就该构建AI模型了。专注于以下问题：</p><p> <strong>3.您采取了哪些步骤来了解所获得的培训数据的完整历史，微妙，优势和局限性？与正确的数据标准相比如何？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中要查找的内容：</em>在这里，您要验证模型开发人员<em>实际上</em>获得了他们期望在问题中获取的数据2.正确的数据，评估差距的严重程度，并解释了他们的计划以弥合重要差距。</p><p>重要的是，在教科书之外，没有一个完美的数据集，因此可以期待差距。如果模型开发人员报告没有差距，请非常可疑。</p><p> <strong>4.您将如何检查未来数据符合正确的数据标准？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中查找的内容：</em>当时探测模型开发人员刚刚完成培训数据，以确保他们考虑了未来数据的来源。如果没有，请他们仔细考虑。 （问题5跟进了这一点。）</p><p>请注意，通过“阻止”某些培训数据验证模型<em>不是</em>可接受的解决方案。在Kaggle.com和其他数据科学竞争平台上，培训数据被认为是可以接受的，甚至是原始的，质量。模型开发人员竞争基于与培训数据相同的原始数据集获取的“保持”数据集建立最佳预测。因此，在所有重要方面，保留数据看起来都像培训数据。在现实生活中，这不是发生的事情。例如，在亚马逊的面部识别系统中，培训数据来自当地的地理区域，而算法将更广泛地应用。用<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/1/25/18197137/amazon-rekognition-facial-recognition-bias-race-gender">亚马逊自己的话说</a>，这导致了“算法校准不良”。</p><h4>部署前后要问的问题</h4><p>为什么在部署之前<em>和</em>期间问这些问题？您需要多次问他们，因为团队在部署期间会学习新事物。</p><p> <strong>5.您将如何确保未来的数据满足您的期望？数据和模型的哪些控件都可以确保通过未来数据成功地部署和模型准确性？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中寻找的内容：</em>这是基于问题4对未来数据的讨论。在这里，您要确保开发人员有一个系统可以在模型使用或用于更新模型的系统之前评估未来数据。</p><p>这很重要，因为尽管公司希望通过AI模型部署获得最佳状态，但建议他们为最糟糕的情况做准备。经理应确保模型开发人员制定一个控制计划，该计划将防止或至少提供未来数据变化或模型性能不佳的预警。例如，随着时间的推移，如何逐渐降低模型的准确性？</p><p></p><p>最后，随着未来数据可用，调查开发人员计划更新模型的计划。</p><p> <strong>6.您可以设想模型在部署失败的三大方法是什么？您采取了哪些步骤来减轻它们？</strong></p><p><em>在答案中寻找的是什么：</em>工程师很久以前就了解到，尽管他们尽了最大的努力，但技术系统经常失败。因此，他们开发了<a href="https://asq.org/quality-resources/fmea">故障模式和效果分析或FMEA</a> ，以帮助预测潜在的失败，并制定应急计划以避免或至少检测到它们。</p><p>不幸的是，许多数据科学家尚未接受这种方法。坚持认为模型开发人员投入了同等的工作。迫使他们在与技术，人员，数据质量，环境变化以及其他问题有关的一系列潜在故障上进行广泛思考。</p><h3>艰难但至关重要的对话</h3><p></p><p>我们很清楚，许多数据科学家和AI模型开发人员都不喜欢回答这些问题。但是，鉴于数据科学项目的较高失败率，问：“您将如何阻止您的失败？”只是良好的管理。</p><p>更重要的是，正如一个<a href="https://research.google/pubs/pub49953/">Google研究团队</a>指出的那样，“每个人都想做模型工作，而不是数据工作。”商业领袖没有这种奢侈。要求强调合适的数据，不仅是建立模型，而且要在将来验证和利用它们，也许是管理者可以做的最重要的事情来提高机器学习和AI项目的成功率。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-should-ask-ask-about-ai-models-models-models-and-data-sets/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>火星上的人工智能：NASA 的 Vandi Verma</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham（ <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ）是波士顿学院Carroll管理学院信息系统系的教授，也是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Reviews</cite>的人工智能和商业策略Big Ideas Initiative的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh是BCG的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美BCG Gamma（BCG的AI实践）的coeader。可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>与他联系。</p><p class="mt20"><cite>我，我本人和AI</cite>是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>和Boston Consulting Group的合作播客，由Sam Ransbotham和Shervin Khodabandeh主持。我们的工程师是David Lishansky，协调的制作人是Allison Ryder和SophieRüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Systems]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Vandi Verma saw the Spirit and Opportunity rovers land on Mars while she was working toward a Ph.D. in robotics, it set her on a path toward working at NASA in space exploration. Perhaps unsurprisingly, today, as chief engineer for robotic operations at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL), Vandi sees the biggest opportunities for [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当万迪·维尔玛 (Vandi Verma) 攻读博士学位时，看到勇气号和机遇号火星车登陆火星。在机器人技术领域，这让她走上了在美国宇航局从事太空探索工作的道路。也许毫不奇怪的是，今天，作为NASA的JET推进实验室（JPL）的机器人操作的首席工程师，Vandi看到了机器人和自动化中人工智能的最大机会。</p><p>在<cite>ME，我本人和AI</cite>播客的这一集中，她描述了火星流浪者依赖AI的方式，包括技术在数字双胞胎模拟中的使用，使JPL科学家能够练习他们的驾驶技能，然后才能实际控制火星上的Rovers 。她还与主持人Shervin Khodabandeh和Sam Ransbotham讨论了NASA对AI的使用及其风险方法如何为希望在地球上模拟现实世界情景的组织提供课程。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E6-Verma-NASA-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="万迪·韦尔玛"></p><h4> NASA Vandi Verma</h4><p> Vandi Verma是NASA喷气推进实验室的移动性和机器人部门的首席工程师和副部门经理。她还担任火星2020年毅力漫游者机器人操作的首席工程师。她以前曾是移动与机器人部门的助理部分经理，该部门员工组的主管和可操作的机器人小组的主管。</p><p> Verma致力于新机器人功能，包括研发；任务设计；原型飞行开发，测试和发射；以及着陆和表面操作。自2008年以来，她与火星Exploration Rover Mission的精神和机会，好奇的流浪者，毅力漫游者和Ingenuity直升机一起从事火星的机器人行动。</p><p>在加入JPL之前，她领导了NASA AMES研究中心团队，该团队开发了用于操作自主系统的Plexil（计划执行互换语言），以及已经部署在流浪者和人类航天飞机项目上的技术的开发。</p><p> Verma获得了博士学位。 2005年在卡内基·梅隆大学（Carnegie Mellon University）获得机器人技术。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn领导者的AI<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite>播客，请在LinkedIn上与我们进行对话。今天加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI的AI</a> 。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入»</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple播客</a>， <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google播客</a>上订阅<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我们可以从火星上使用AI中学到什么？找出今天的情节。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我是NASA JPL的Vandi Verma，您正在听<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎<cite>我，我本人和AI</cite> ，这是商业中人工智能的播客。每个情节，我们都会向您介绍与AI创新的人。我是波士顿学院分析教授Sam Ransbotham。我还是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>的AI和业务战略嘉宾编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是BCG的高级合伙人Shervin Khodabandeh，也是我们AI业务的领导者之一。自2017年以来，<cite>麻省理工学院SMR</cite>和BCG一直在研究和发布AI，采访了数百名从业者，并对成千上万的公司进行调查，以建立，部署和扩展AI功能并真正改变组织的运作方式。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嘿，大家，欢迎。今天，我和Shervin与NASA的JET推进实验室的首席工程师Vandi Verma交谈时感到非常兴奋。这真的很酷。范迪（Vandi），从我们进行的偷偷摸摸的预览中，我们很高兴能参加演出。感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>谢谢您让我在这里。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我承认我真的很喜欢您的工作 - 我确定每个人都是 - 但是让我们向所有人提示您的工作。您可以首先对JPL和您的特定角色进行概述？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我是NASA喷气推进实验室的移动性和机器人系统副经理，我也[与Mars 2020 Mass的首席工程师一起工作，该任务由持久漫游者和Ingenenity直升机组成。</p><p> JPL是NASA中心，专门从事用于太空探索的机器人。 NASA的使命是探索，发现和扩大知识，以使人类的利益受益，而我们所做的就是机器人方面的方面。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>当您说“机器人技术”时，我会想到人工智能，但是火星任务似乎是AI等新技术的一个非常具有挑战性的地方。您和JPL在使用机器人技术的工作中如何使用AI？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>对。 AI在一段时间内改变了我们所说的，我们在地面上做了一些事情，并且我们在机器人上做了一些事情，因此我将谈到其中的一些。因此，总的来说，我们更属于自主能力 - 更接近您可能认为自动驾驶汽车使用的东西 - 尽管我们用它来告知它，但其中并不是有可能是经典的机器学习本身我们的很多工作。</p><p>实际上，由于毅力，我们所做的驾驶中有88％是自主驾驶。因此，流动站有相机：它正在拍摄图像；它正在检测地形，并弄清楚障碍物周围是什么危险和导航。这实际上很有趣，因为它在没有人见过的地形上行驶，所以我们甚至无法提供这种信息。因此，这绝对是自动导航的一种形式。</p><p>在驱动器的最后，我们也试图取得很多进步，因为我们处于这个非常严峻的环境中，我们的使命是收集和缓存一定数量的持久样本，因为这是我们的第一次实际上要把它们带回地球。但是我们希望它们来自尽可能不同的地方，因此我们想开很多驾驶。如果您一直停下来，您将不会取得太大的进步。但是，谁知道我们会错过的事情是否真的很令人兴奋？在我们的世界中，我们称其为恐龙骨头。</p><p>我们的AI功能在漫游车上，它将拍摄广角图像，看大片地形，然后尝试找出其中最有趣的功能。我们有大量乐器，但其中一种乐器是<a href="https://mars.nasa.gov/mars2020/spacecraft/instruments/supercam/">超级摄像机仪器</a>，它做得很多。它具有激光，从远处可以在岩石上拍摄激光，并创建等离子，我们使用望远镜镜头进行研究。这是一个如此狭窄的视野 - 您知道是一个Milliradian-因此，如果您要尝试对整个视图做到这一点，那么您将在那里度过几天。</p><p>因此，从本质上讲，我们使用AI来弄清楚“我们应该将最有趣的事情扎根？”然后，您可以将数据寄回并告诉地球上的科学家。那也非常有价值。所以我们这样做。</p><p>然后，您知道，有计划。我们使用了很多资源，例如……主要是在火星上，当您有航天器时，环境就很苛刻。因此，我们正在考虑“如何加热事物 - 将其保持在适当的温度？我们有多少力量？”您需要与地球进行交流；地球在哪里？我们还计划了船上的计划，这在更大的情况下更多地考虑了事情。因此，所有这些事情都是我们做什么的例子。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>那是很多例子。您主要是自主行驶的事实 - 这似乎是一个迷人的世界。您提到找到有趣的东西。那里的目标函数是什么？您如何弄清楚一些有趣的东西？我知道我认为有趣的事，但是告诉我有关让机器找出有趣的过程的过程。</p><p><strong>范迪·维尔玛（Vandi Verma）：</strong>我认为定义有趣的是最有趣的事情之一是它将其放在人类身上。实际上，我们很难告诉机器我们要他们做什么，对吗？为了使我们能够说出有趣的内容，我们有很多不同的参数，科学家可以用来指定“我正在寻找特定尺寸的浅色岩石，特定的反照率和形状，这些岩石在该领域很有趣。 ”我们可以改变这一点。因此，我们有这些不同的模板，具体取决于我们所处的地形，地面上的科学家可以帮助我们确定。我们将其发送给机器人说：“我们正在寻找这种事情。”</p><p>我们也做了一些研究，我们告诉它：“您现在跟踪我们所见过的所有事物”  - 这称为新颖性检测，我们实际上还没有部署过，但是“找到我们尚未看的东西在。”那是另一个。</p><p>但是这里有两件事。当我们进行探索时，我们正在寻找新的事物，但是我们也试图表征使用多种不同工具看到的事物，因为我们正在尝试为我们的假设收集统计学上大量的数据。我们试图弄清楚“生命是否存在于火星上，尤其是古代生活？”</p><p>因此，这个难题……有假设，您正在尝试回答特定的问题，这就是科学家会告诉机器人他们感兴趣的问题。我们实际上使用了超级计算机将其转化为我们可以可以的参数然后上行链路到机器人。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>因此，人们用粗略地描述了他们想要的东西，然后您有一些超级计算机，在地球上的某些东西，试图将其转化为一组参数，然后将其发送给流浪者以找出什么寻找。我正确理解吗？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>是的。我认为，这是AI可以提供很多帮助的领域，因为我们仍处于许多旋钮的许多领域的机器人技术中。我们可以做很多事情，但是艺术在调整这个多变量空间。实际上，您知道，只是在毅力上 - 我们称它们为软件中的参数，[]这甚至没有考虑到硬件设计和其他事项 - 我们拥有超过64,000个显式参数。这些保存在非易失性内存中。这甚至没有考虑到您可以发送的命令的论点。因此，您可以表达出多种方式表达您要说的话，在这里我们可以使用很多能力来了解适合我们打算做的正确组合。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>是的，类似的组合学似乎会爆炸，因此，这似乎是机器学习的好工具，并找出正确的一组最佳参数或下一个可以选择的参数是什么。从中选择。就像您说的那样，您不能激光整个火星表面。好吧，您也不能同时探索64,000个参数。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>是的，您绝对是对的。然而，挑战和美丽 - 使它成为如此有趣的环境 - 错误的余量非常低，因此当很难让航天器成功地降落在火星上时，您不能进行实验。这是一项国家资产。因此，我们说：“您并不是温柔的”，但是您正在做所有的检查，以确保它将成功。您不能将车辆置于危险之中。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> MM嗯。显然，大多数人听的人都不会探索火星，但是当我们考虑您可以创造的类比时，人们现在就决定风险投资组合，关于他们将机器交给机器的数量，在您的情况下，新颖或决定在哪里开车。其他人正在做出相同的风险决策。现在，考虑到资产和在哪里，您似乎对风险的容忍度极低。但是，我觉得像其他人一样，具有人工智能和新技术，也必须做出类似的风险决策。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为您是绝对正确的。实际上，我认为在某些方面，您可能会认为我们有容忍的风险，但是我们必须如此频繁地做出这些决定，如果我们实际上非常规避风险，我们什么也不会做，根本不会动弹。有一个流程来评估它，并且在特定情况下，该阈值在哪里，这是团队中每个人都学会与他们所做的工作一起做的事情。因此，我认为这实际上是可以很好地进入其他领域的事情。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>回到您之前说的话，当您谈论自动驾驶时：您真的不能在从未去过的地方练习驾驶，那么在到达那里之前，您如何练习？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>有两个要素。一个是，我们如何拥有自主能力实践，然后我们如何拥有人类，他们仍然在某种程度上需要指导自主能力，练习？所以我们做了这两个。在为行星体建造机器人方面 - 这是如此不同，对吗？火星上的重力是不同的，压力，温度和所有这些东西 - 我们创建模拟。我在板上持久的某些软件，我帮助了程序，并且实际上，从一开始，我们就开发了软件模拟，因为我们实际上可能没有完整的地球复制品。我们在地球上创建了一个全尺寸模型来测试，但这在任务的早期阶段也在发展。因此，我们正在构建硬件，他们也在尝试：“最好的车轮设计是什么？最好的材料是什么？” - 当我们编写软件时。</p><p> “您如何构建这些仿真，以帮助我们代表我们正确掌握的环境？”但是然后我们也开始剥离某些硬件接口。因此，我们将在更多的商业接口机器人零件上运行真正的飞行软件，但在我们的火星院子中。我们有火星院。它不是火星，但我们试图拥有斜坡，基岩和其他特征。然后，我们构建了运行传感器在火星上使用的实际计算的完整副本，然后对其进行测试。之后，我们进行特定的测试。因此，我们将对某些部位进行热真空室测试，然后用零碎的零件进行。</p><p>当我们进入气氛时，我们必须使用地球上的飞机进行一些测试，因为我们必须研究如何降落在火星上。但是除此之外，一旦我们上火星，我们就会分阶段进行。因此，我们实际上可能会有自主导航告诉我们它将做什么，但实际上没有进行导航。</p><p>实际上，我们会将人类直接驱动器，但实际上，我们实际上让它阴影并说：“让我们看看您将要做什么。”因此，我们分阶段进行。</p><p>我们确实想快速进步，因为如果您这样做太久了……这是在火星上的宝贵时间。因此，这就是我们如何推出自主能力的方式。现在，就人类而言，自2008年以来，我一直在火星上驾驶机器人。您开始了解火星，这需要时间。因此，我们一直在缩短时间。我们有学员，我们有教室会议，所以我们从火星和数据中驱动了驱动器，我们将他们的计划离线计划。然后我们有阴影。因此，现在大多数驱动器现在，我实际上有其他人在键盘上训练，而当您训练他们成为飞行员时，您正在看着他们。因此，我们这样做，实际上仍然需要数年。</p><p>我们中的一些帮助建造机器人的人将从SOL 0开始，这是我们在火星上执行任务的开始。然后，很快，在半年到一年之内，我们开始让下一组人来。因为如果您看任务，它们可以在火星上很长时间，因此您必须接受人们的培训才能做到这一点。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>实际上，就其他人所做的事情而言，有很多有趣的方面。但是您提到了模拟和建造数字双胞胎。您不想在火星上练习。您想在地球上练习，或者您以数字方式练习，尤其是正如您所提到的那样（我不欣赏的），即使您可以练习，硬件甚至都不存在；那是同时发生的。但是，在此过程中，人类也在学习的想法，并且您不会在方向盘后第一天将任何人驾驶的人放松。第一天，您也不会关闭漫游者以自己开车。因此，学习过程也很有趣。</p><p>我还认为这很有趣。 …您在谈论缩短时间 - 随着您获得更多的经验，您可以缩短那个时间。而且，由于世界上有这么多人部署人工智能解决方案来做不同的事情，我猜想一开始很多人都非常仔细地看着他们，但逐渐越来越信任他们。这与我猜想您与键盘上谈论的另一个人一起工作的方式相同 - 可能是在键盘上打字，而现在在键盘上键入的时间更少。因此，我认为有很多类比，即使火星似乎是一个外国环境，也与其他人一起使用人工智能。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>是的，我认为您绝对正确。有趣的事情是，您可以从地球的完全不同的部分（一个完全不同的机器人）中采取什么可能具有不同的移动性特征？但是人类能够很好地提取图案。因此，如果您是一个漫游者任务的漫游者司机，那么您实际上要花费更少的时间，就像您说的那样。但其中的一部分是，我们在用户界面中变得越来越复杂。</p><p>如果您查看界面，我们用来操作和驱动机器人 - 操作机器人臂并实际采样，这在某些方面更为复杂 - 它们也已经显着发展。我们曾经发送指令 - 例如，像您在程序上的函数调用一样，从字面上看命令行说明。现在，我们以图形方式进行操作，从本质上讲，您是在地图上选择航路点。因此，我认为这也非常有帮助，因为我们开始让人类专注于人类直觉和我们积累的丰富经验并可能带来问题的方面。 …因为AI仍然存在，即使它变得非常复杂，我们拥有的功能仍然受到我们创建时的想象力的限制。我们非常意识到这一点是在火星上经营数十年的机器人。我们总是告诉自己：“我们的想象力超出了什么？”因为它发生 - 每次都会发生。我们总是对这些令人惊奇的事情感到惊讶，最终我们以一种我们无意使用的方式使用它。这就像您一直在看到的那样 - 您可能针对其他各种地球应用程序开发的技术。人们还会想出哪些其他内容？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>人们疯了。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我的意思是，我认为它们是创新的！</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>对。这实际上就是您想要的，因为您不仅试图一遍又一遍地做同样的事情。</p><p>您提到了<em>惊喜</em>一词，我认为这是一件有趣的事情。我们谈论的一件事是，您进行所有这些模拟，并且希望工作能够正常工作，但是您不希望它能完全正常工作，因为您试图发现自己没想到的东西。因此，请告诉我们一些有关该过程的工作方式：“嘿，我们希望事情像我们希望它们一样工作，但我们也为发生不期望的事情发生的事情开放吗？”</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>这是您提出的一个很好的观点……模拟并不是事情的执行方式。而且，实际上几乎从来没有。 And partly, the reason we&#39;re driving autonomously is because the detail-level surface information — the imagery that the rover is going to take from its Mars cameras — we cannot simulate it precisely enough. And so any path that we simulate on the ground, it&#39;s sampling terrain. You know, we have an abstraction; we have an orbital map. But it&#39;s doing it at a very coarse level. And if we already had that detail map, we wouldn&#39;t even need autonomous navigation. We would literally just script it to drive.</p><p> As soon as it drives 5 [or] 10 meters, it has far more information about the environment than we had before we sent this command. So at that point, it is far more capable of making decisions and doing the right thing than anything we could [do]. So we have to learn to not over-constrain it. And this is actually one of the things that&#39;s really hard to teach new people: You&#39;ve perfected it in your simulation, but you have to anticipate where your simulation is actually a simulation. It is not reality. And if you don&#39;t leave it enough room to maneuver, you&#39;re actually going to have it fail miserably.</p><p> So we have these things we call “keep in boxes” where, for autonomous capability, we sort of want humans to say, “I have some insight, and I want you to stay within this area.” It can be a hundred meters, right? Like, a really large area. So we create these leashes to leash the behavior, but there&#39;s an art in how long you make the leash.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Vandi, this has been a really fascinating discussion. Can you also share a bit about how you ended up in this role?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I remember watching the Mars Exploration Rovers land. I was in graduate school. I was doing my Ph.D. in robotics, actually at the time because I had already taken a class — and it was a programming class where we were programming mobile robots. And it was just so much fun that I think I spent all my spare time just on this competition we had at the end of the class, where we had to have these robots navigate a maze.</p><p> And it was just fascinating to me that you could apply the theory to an actual machine and see it do something in the environment. I&#39;d been working with AI, actually; my master&#39;s was in AI, and it was fascinating. But here, there&#39;s something so satisfying about a robot that you can actually see operating in a physical world. And I love space exploration; the combination of space and robotics was just a perfect fit. And the robots ended up lasting so long, the mission for the Mars Exploration Rovers spurred an opportunity — it was supposed to be 90 days — that I graduated, and it was still on Mars. So I actually never thought that I would actually get to work on them, and I did.</p><p> And so I think that&#39;s sort of how it came about is, I was fascinated by it, and when I was at university, there are a lot of collaborations that NASA does with universities because a huge part of the mission is education. And so you can get exposed to this. You can work on problems that are interesting to NASA, and my thesis was very much aligned with that, and that&#39;s how I got into it.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Very cool. You have some engineers to thank for the longevity of the mission that let you step in and do it.</p><p> We have a segment where we want to ask you some rapid-fire questions. Just answer the first thing that occurs to you as we do this.</p><p> What do you see as the biggest opportunity for artificial intelligence right now?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I think the biggest opportunity … I think it&#39;s in robotics, actually.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Shockingly.</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK. What&#39;s the biggest misconception people have about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I think the biggest misconception they have is that it can&#39;t extrapolate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Hmm. So, what was the first career that you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I wanted to fly airplanes. My dad was a pilot. I wanted to be a bush pilot.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, since then you have gotten your pilot license, so you&#39;ve achieved that.</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I did, yes.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Do you think there are places that we&#39;re trying too hard to make artificial intelligence fit a solution that it doesn&#39;t fit in? And are we applying this tool in the wrong places anywhere?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> I think that sometimes you could have said that about neural networks, at a certain stage. So I am actually a little bit shy to say, is it the wrong place? It depends on where your bar is to realize whether it&#39;s worth it to do, given the technology at this stage. I think it just depends on your threshold and your horizon.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK, that&#39;s fair. What&#39;s one thing you think that would be really nice if artificial intelligence could do right now that it currently is just not capable of? What&#39;s the one thing you could change?</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> You know, one of the things is that we do have a huge, huge amount of data. And one of the limitations in applying it for some of the space explorations [is], you still need a lot of auditing of the tokens or what it extracts. So I think there&#39;s still just a lot of tweaking. That is the challenge with it, I think. If you could get over that, I think that potential would be unleashed.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Great discussion. I&#39;m guessing that, of course, none of our listeners are driving robots on Mars, but I think there&#39;s lots of things that people can learn from the things that you have learned through this process. People may not be building digital twins for simulating Mars, but they are building digital twins for simulating processes on Earth. We&#39;re all increasingly experiencing the world through these devices and through AI sensing. Even if we don&#39;t work in the space context, I think we can learn a lot from what you and your team have learned. Thanks for taking the time to talk with us today.</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma:</strong> Thank you so much for sharing a little bit of what we do with your audience.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabadenh:</strong> Thanks for listening. Join us next time when Sam and I meet Prem Natarajan, chief scientist and head of enterprise AI at Capital One. Please join us in the new year.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>无处不在的商店是零售业的新面貌吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David R. Bell, Santiago Gallino, and Antonio Moreno. <p>David R. Bell ( <a href="https://twitter.com/davidbnz">@davidbnz</a> ) is the president and cofounder of Idea Farm Ventures, based in New York City. Santiago Gallino is an associate professor of operations, information, and decisions and the Charles W. Evans Distinguished Faculty Scholar at the Wharton School. Antonio Moreno ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tmorenog">@tmorenog</a> ) is the Sicupira Family Associate Professor of Business Administration at the Harvard Business School.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business Models]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Omnichannel Retailing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Retail Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Nearly 30 years ago, a fledgling startup called Amazon made its first online sale, and a retail revolution began. Dubbed “the Everything Store” by Brad Stone in his book of the same name, Amazon leveraged digital technologies to expand the very nature of retail, demonstrating that selling physical goods [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Bell-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Nearly 30 years ago, a fledgling startup called Amazon made its first online sale, and a retail revolution began. Dubbed “the Everything Store” by Brad Stone in his book of the same name, Amazon leveraged digital technologies to expand the very nature of retail, demonstrating that selling physical goods no longer required a physical storefront.</p><p> But today, the cornerstone of retailing — location — has expanded once again, and the advent of what we call <em>everywhere stores</em> is impacting omnichannel strategy and unlocking potential value for new entrants and incumbents alike.</p><p></p><p> Retailing excellence demands optimal engagement with customers through experiences, paired with product fulfillment with minimal friction, and historically both have happened in stores. <em>Everywhere store</em> refers to a new kind of retail experience, in which customer engagement and product fulfillment occur in native environments — that is, they are not dependent on purpose-built stores or warehouses. They allow brands and retailers to think much more expansively about where customer interactions should take place and where inventory should be located.</p><p></p><h3> What Omnichannel Looks Like Now</h3><p> Omnichannel retail comprises four distinct approaches to customer engagement and fulfillment: traditional retail stores; online sales plus physical showrooms where customers can engage with products; online sales with in-store pickup; and pure-play e-commerce, in which both fulfillment and engagement occur online.</p><p> Today, traditional retail through stores still accounts for more than 80% of sales in the US <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Of course, the percentage varies substantially by <a href=" https://www.statista.com/statistics/203043/online-share-of-total-us-retail-revenue-projection/">product type</a> : Less-complex goods that can easily be described online align well with e-commerce, whereas products that consumers prefer to see and touch before buying, such as espresso machines and grills, might benefit from display space and thus lend themselves to some form of offline shopping experience.</p><p> Hybrid models use digital for one function, physical for the other. For traditional retailers that predate the introduction of e-commerce, “buy online, pick up in store” is a must-have — and yields the added benefit that customers who pick up their purchases at a retail location might make incremental purchases of other products when they visit. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> For direct-to-consumer retailers especially, showrooms such as Warby Parker&#39;s stores and Bonobos&#39;s Guideshops increase brand awareness and allow customers to inspect products or try them on before buying. They excel in serving first-time customers and those with more complex needs. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p> The next wave of omnichannel retail is being led by innovators such as Los Angeles-based outdoor furniture brand Outer, which entered the market selling directly to consumers, without establishing physical stores. Outer&#39;s cofounders, Jiake Liu and Terry Lin, saw an opportunity for disaggregated retail: Rather than creating traditional showrooms, they turned customers&#39; backyards into showrooms. Prospective customers visit the homes of existing customers to experience and engage with products and other customers offline. A key advantage of turning customers&#39; yards into showrooms is that other people in the neighborhood might be good sales prospects, given that they are likely to share sociodemographic characteristics.</p><p> This disaggregated approach to retailing can also serve as a model for a stand-alone business. For example, the venture-backed platform Minoan enables the owners of short-term lodging spaces (such as hotels and Airbnb rentals) to purchase from specific brands, furnish their guest quarters with those brands&#39; products, and then invite guests to buy those goods while staying at the property. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Minoan cofounder Marc Hostovsky had a lightbulb moment while staying at an Airbnb, where he admired the comfortable bed, kitchen knives, and other furnishings. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> It occurred to Marc and Minoan cofounder Shobhit Khandelwal that experiencing new products organically, in nonstore environments, was compelling. An alumnus of Walmart.com and Jet.com, Hostovsky told us that “the best product experiences don&#39;t happen on screens.”</p><p> We are also tracking the emergence of everywhere storage, as we described above. Wareclouds, a venture-backed urban logistics startup based in Chile that disaggregates retail for brands by using residential locations to store inventory, aims to launch in the US next year. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> This approach would allow brands to bypass traditional warehouses and tap into homeowners&#39; unused space. The tactic might save costs compared with using traditional warehouse space, allow brands to adapt capacity based on demand fluctuations, and place inventory closer to more customers. The latter enables faster delivery by local drivers, in turn potentially enhancing customer experience and saving brands money by avoiding warehousing expenses.</p><p></p><p></p><p> While it&#39;s still early days for the everywhere store and everywhere storage, retailers should begin to explore the possibilities afforded by these strategies and consider the attendant challenges. How will brands ensure that native spaces present their products as intended? How will a distributed storage system manage inventory across dozens of individual homes? Retailers and brands might choose to partner with specialist businesses such as Minoan and Wareclouds, delegating some elements of execution.</p><p> Retailers must also bear in mind that meeting customers where they are in nontraditional spaces carries some risk: It&#39;s important that customers don&#39;t perceive those initiatives as intrusive, and it remains to be seen whether they&#39;ll be accepted on a wide scale. If brands can do it right, some of the greatest in-person retail innovations will require no stores at all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>技能第一的人才战略</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aneesh Raman, Elyse Rosenblum, and Abbie Lundberg. <p>Aneesh Raman is vice president and head of the Opportunity Project at LinkedIn. The Opportunity Project works with leaders across the private and public sectors to build a more transparent, dynamic, and equitable global labor market in the age of AI. Elyse Rosenblum is the founder and managing director of Grads of Life, a talent strategy consulting firm that works with leading employers to implement skills-first talent practices that deliver both business benefits and social impact. Abbie Lundberg is editor in chief at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Management Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading A. Raman and E. Rosenblum, &#8220;Focus on Skills to Grow Your Workforce,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, June 21, 2023. Skills dominate current conversations about how to spot, foster, and grow talent. A skills-first talent strategy sets your workforce up for long-term resilience in a world where jobs keep changing, and artificial intelligence increasingly [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>A. Raman and E. Rosenblum, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Focus on Skills to Grow Your Workforce</a> ,&quot; <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , June 21, 2023.</p></aside><p> Skills dominate current conversations about how to spot, foster, and grow talent. A skills-first talent strategy sets your workforce up for long-term resilience in a world where jobs keep changing, and artificial intelligence increasingly impacts work. Successful companies have aligned their skills-first practices to the entire employee journey.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why skills-first practices matter now more than ever in the age of AI.</li><li> Three big ideas for how to build a skills-first talent strategy.</li><li> 10 top measurements to focus on in your skills-first efforts.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>好问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:23:35 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Elizabeth Heichler is the editorial director, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko One of the enduring challenges of leadership is avoiding being persuaded that you have all the answers. When anxious employees seek certainty, it might feel like it’s your job to deliver. But numerous articles in this issue of MIT Sloan Management Review remind us how much more important it can be to ask [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-EditLetter_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p> One of the enduring challenges of leadership is avoiding being persuaded that you have all the answers. When anxious employees seek certainty, it might feel like it&#39;s your job to deliver. But numerous articles in this issue of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> remind us how much more important it can be to ask questions.</p><p> Question the conventional wisdom: You could find that what “everybody knows” no longer holds true. That might be the case with one of the truisms of e-commerce: that the online purchase experience should be as free of friction as possible. <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/">Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli</a> ask whether that makes sense in all circumstances — and suggest that the widespread practice of easing customers&#39; paths through the point of sale might actually be one of the culprits behind the high rate of returns for online purchases 。 They explain how introducing the right type of friction can slow buyers down and give them more time to evaluate their purchasing decisions — and increase their loyalty.</p><p></p><p> Question the value you&#39;re getting from routine spending, such as your investment in leadership training. Research by <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/">Hannes Leroy, Moran Anisman-Razin, and Jim Detert</a> found a lack of educational rigor across numerous leadership development programs and a corresponding lack of meaningful outcomes. The onus is on companies buying these programs to ask themselves exactly what skills leaders need to develop in order to advance strategic priorities, and then ask more pointed questions of providers. If customers adopt more exacting criteria for selecting these programs, it might push providers to tighten their curricula and teaching methods, the authors argue.</p><p> Question your workforce about their views on the business and the employee experience. In researching the top 50 public corporations in Germany and their varying approaches to engaging with the employee representatives on their boards, <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/">Ayse Karaevli and Serden Özcan</a> found that those that sought employee input on a wide range of topics did better at managing workforce disputes and gaining employee support for change. The authors point out that the company leaders who used more inclusive decision-making processes, gave employees strategic responsibilities, and identified mutual goals and interests avoided controversy and public conflict with their workforces. All of those strategies require leaders to not only ask questions but be prepared to listen well to the answers.</p><p></p><p> Question what you understand about others&#39; beliefs to establish dialogue on contentious issues. I&#39;ve heard anecdotally that CEOs are concerned about the upcoming 2024 presidential election and the potential for divisiveness along ideological lines within the workplace. <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/">Kenji Yoshino and David Glasgow</a> aim to equip them with strategies and tactics for engaging respectfully with others on tough topics. In an article drawn from their recent book, <cite>Say the Right Thing: How to Talk About Identity, Diversity, and Justice</cite> , they offer a framework for having courageous conversations in the face of deep disagreement. Their approach to locating an appropriate entry point for dialogue can shift how we confront seemingly intractable differences. To prepare for such conversations, it is critical to research the opposing position with an open mind and to ask questions that might offer insight into the experiences, worldviews, and contexts that have formed people&#39;s opinions. This wise advice can not only help leaders model civility for their teams but remind everyone that, often, good leadership begins with asking good questions.</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>我们的 2024 年冬季刊指南</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:22:31 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Decision-Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Set Ambitious but Realistic Environmental Goals Kate Isaacs, Jason Jay, Jeremy Gregory, and Elsa Olivetti Key Insight: Business leaders should judiciously set interim targets to get early wins and build momentum for sustainability goals. Top Takeaways: Companies need to grapple with setting critical goals to reduce carbon emissions while continuing to meet business demands. Moving [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-EXECSUM-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/" class="no-underline">Set Ambitious but Realistic Environmental Goals</a></h4><h6> Kate Isaacs, Jason Jay, Jeremy Gregory, and Elsa Olivetti</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Business leaders should judiciously set interim targets to get early wins and build momentum for sustainability goals.</p><p><strong>主要要点：</strong>公司需要努力设定减少碳排放的关键目标，同时继续满足业务需求。 Moving the needle on addressing major sustainability issues requires setting objectives that are ambitious enough to reflect an organization&#39;s vision but sufficiently realistic as well. The authors walk readers through a five-step process for identifying and setting environmental intentions and for managing the tension between the urgent need for climate action and maintaining business health.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/" class="no-underline">悖论中隐藏的机遇</a></h4><h6>Scott D. Anthony</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Adopting a mindset that views apparently irreconcilable objectives as opportunities boosts creativity and organizational performance.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Business leaders face an endless array of choices. While some decisions are straightforward, others are particularly hard to make because they involve paradoxes — issues that relate to but appear to contradict each other, such as “listen to and ignore your best customers” and “sustain and disrupt your current business model.” Research shows that organizations that tackle and even embrace seemingly contradictory options expand the scope of what&#39;s possible.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/" class="no-underline">为更透明的可持续发展报告做好准备</a></h4><h6>理查德·巴克</h6><p><strong>Key Insight:</strong> Mandatory sustainability reporting will help companies show investors how they intend to manage risk and create value.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> The rigorous sustainability-related financial disclosure requirements on the horizon represent an opportunity, if organizations can think of the coming regulatory revolution as more than simply an exercise in compliance. New reporting will reveal how leaders see the future, how they are planning to meet it, and what value they expect to be able to create for their companies. Focusing on what investors want can provide a useful lens for corporate planning and risk management.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/" class="no-underline">Tackling AI&#39;s Climate Change Problem</a></h4><h6> Niklas Sundberg</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Large AI models are big energy consumers and carbon emitters, but best practices for sustainable AI can reduce their environmental impact.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> The specialized hardware and data centers needed to train and run large language models consume enormous amounts of electricity and generate tons of carbon emissions and e-waste. A single ChatGPT query, for instance, can result in 100 times more carbon than a regular Google search. But there are steps AI leaders can take to make the technology more sustainable, including rightsizing models, choosing more efficient machine learning architectures, and reducing the amount of organizational data that is stored but never used.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/" class="no-underline">Can Friction Improve Your Customers&#39; Experiences?</a></h4><h6> Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> When e-commerce sites make buying products too quick and easy, they can miss out on deepening customer relationships.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Many companies are on a quest to make shopping as hassle-free as possible — especially online, where shoppers are less patient and have short attention spans. But slowing down the purchase process to give customers time to consider their buying decisions can actually produce longer-term benefits. It turns out that when friction enables better decisions, customer satisfaction and loyalty both improve. The authors provide an assessment to help companies determine the degree of friction that will play to these advantages.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/" class="no-underline">Leadership Development Is Failing Us.这是修复方法</a></h4><h6>Hannes Leroy, Moran Anisman-Razin, and Jim Detert</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> An effective leadership development program will have specific goals, use the most appropriate curriculum and teaching methods, and produce outcomes directly relevant to organizational needs.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Leadership development programs are expensive but often fail to produce meaningful results. For that to change, the companies that purchase these programs will have to be more involved upfront. This means asking more relevant questions of providers and demanding better answers. It also means articulating their specific development needs and how they are tied to their organizations&#39; strategic priorities more clearly.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/" class="no-underline">Make Better Allies of Your Workforce</a></h4><h6> Ayse Karaevli and Serden Özcan</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Companies that take deliberate steps to include employees when making decisions experience fewer labor disputes and better manage change.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> The past few years have seen an increase in workforce conflicts, such as strikes and disputes over wages, working conditions, diversity, equal opportunity, and health and safety — along with rising levels of employee disengagement. An analysis of the top public corporations in Germany found that what matters most for reducing conflict is the extent to which C-suite and board leaders actively engage employees in critical strategic decisions. The three approaches leaders can use to include employees are identifying mutual goals and interests, fostering inclusive decision processes, and giving employees strategic responsibilities.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/" class="no-underline">What Managers Everywhere Must Know About Caste</a></h4><h6> Hari Bapuji, Kamini Gupta, Snehanjali Chrispal, and Thomas Roulet</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Caste, a South Asian sociocultural-economic hierarchy, can affect people&#39;s access to capital, business connections, and job opportunities and result in workplace bias and discrimination worldwide.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> The system of socioeconomic stratification known as caste can shape inequities and broader interactions in the workplace — not just in countries such as India and Pakistan but in places with many South Asian residents, including the US, the UK, Canada, and Australia 。 Leaders need to understand how caste works in order to adequately protect employees from its harmful effects. Companies such as Amazon, Apple, and Dell have recognized the importance of this issue by addressing caste-based discrimination in their corporate policies.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/" class="no-underline">How to Productively Disagree on Tough Topics</a></h4><h6> Kenji Yoshino and David Glasgow</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Leaders can apply specific strategies to facilitate thorny workplace conversations about identity, diversity, and justice.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Divisive workplace interactions range from the safest subjects, where disagreement is expected or even celebrated, to controversial subjects, where the conversation is likely to turn ugly. People in positions of power have the greatest opportunity to transform the dynamics of these interactions, by fostering empathy instead of provoking fear and division. Researching another person&#39;s point of view carefully and finding points of commonality outside of the dispute are two of several strategies the authors recommend for bringing respect to conversations and reining in anger and defensiveness.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/" class="no-underline">How Ghost Scenarios Haunt Strategy Execution</a></h4><h6> Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Executives must confront a strategic planning blind spot: assumptions about their organization&#39;s future business context.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Strategic planners often ignore how a business environment&#39;s socioeconomic status quo might change and how that new context might affect their intended outcomes. A scenario-planning mindset that surfaces ghost scenarios acknowledges these implicit assumptions, identifies potential disruptions, and then begins to account for them. Engaging with ghost scenarios could, for instance, mean exploring different ways in which trust in a particular technology might evolve or how regulatory changes might impact specific goals.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/" class="no-underline">The Real Issues Driving the Nursing Crisis</a></h4><h6> Donald Sull and Charles Sull</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Nurses who work for staffing agencies are, on average, more satisfied than other nurses — and health care leaders need to ask why.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> The top problems US hospitals face are staff shortages and burnout, and nursing shortages are a particularly acute pain point. The authors&#39; analysis of employer reviews found that high levels of job dissatisfaction among nurses are driven in part by a view that managers are out of touch with the daily realities of patient care. One bright point is that nurses who work for staffing agencies — who are sometimes referred to as travel nurses — report better working conditions, communication, and trust. The authors&#39; research details the drivers of job satisfaction that other providers can learn from.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><p></p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Tackling AI&#39;s Climate Change Problem</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Niklas Sundberg. <p>Niklas Sundberg is the author of <cite>Sustainable IT Playbook for Technology Leaders</cite> (Packt Publishing, 2022) and a board member of SustainableIT.org, a nonprofit organization dedicated to advancing global sustainability through technology leadership. He is chief digital officer at Kuehne+Nagel, a global transport and logistics company, and was previously CIO and global head of enterprise architecture at Assa Abloy.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko In an era defined by both the promise of technological innovation and the threat of climate change, artificial intelligence has emerged as both a valuable tool and a difficult challenge. As we use AI to tackle tough problems, we must also grapple with its hidden environmental costs and consider solutions that will allow [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Sundberg_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p> In an era defined by both the promise of technological innovation and the threat of climate change, artificial intelligence has emerged as both a valuable tool and a difficult challenge. As we use AI to tackle tough problems, we must also grapple with its hidden environmental costs and consider solutions that will allow us to harness its potential while mitigating its climate impact.</p><p> The success of OpenAI&#39;s ChatGPT language model, which is backed by Microsoft, has sparked a technology arms race, with tech giants making enormous investments in building their own natural language processing systems. But the quest for more intelligent machines is quickly running into a web of sustainability challenges. AI has a fast-growing carbon footprint, stemming from its voracious appetite for energy and the carbon costs of manufacturing the hardware it uses. Since 2012, the most extensive AI training runs have been using exponentially more computing power, doubling every 3.4 months, on average. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><h3> AI&#39;s Environmental Costs</h3><p> The environmental impact of information technology is often overlooked, even though data centers and transmission networks account for 1% to 1.5% of global electricity use. They also account for 0.6% of global carbon emissions, which need to be cut in half to achieve a net-zero emissions scenario by 2050, according to the International Energy Agency. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> A single average data center consumes the equivalent of heating 50,000 homes yearly. Electronic waste is the fastest-growing waste stream in the world, amounting to a staggering 57 million tons generated each year, about the same weight as the Great Wall of China. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Several factors contribute to the carbon footprint of AI systems throughout their life cycles:</p><p> <strong>Large and complex models:</strong> Large language models (LLMs) require tens of thousands of cutting-edge high-performance chips for training and for responding to queries, leading to high energy consumption and carbon emissions. The greater the model&#39;s complexity, the more task times increase, resulting in more energy consumption. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> LLMs like ChatGPT are among the most complex and computationally expensive AI models. The capabilities of OpenAI&#39;s GPT-3 LLM are made possible by its 175 billion-parameter model, one of the largest when it was launched. Its training alone is estimated to have used 1.3 gigawatt-hours of energy (equivalent to 120 average US households&#39; yearly consumption) and generated 552 tons in carbon emissions (equivalent to the yearly emissions of 120 US cars). <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> OpenAI&#39;s latest model, GPT-4, is rumored to be 10 times larger. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> <strong>Data storage and processing:</strong> The data sets required to train and run AI models are large and complex, leading to high energy consumption and carbon emissions. Data storage, CPU operation, and chip operation consume most of the energy in data centers. Furthermore, around 40% of the electricity used in data centers is powering large air conditioners, which are necessary to keep servers cool and operating correctly. Falcon 180B, a recently launched open-access LLM, has 180 billion parameters (similar to GPT-3&#39;s count) and was trained on a 3.5-trillion-token data set (compared with GPT-3&#39;s 499 billion tokens). <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Training this model on such a large data set is estimated to have generated an estimated 1,870 tons of carbon emissions, equivalent to heating 350 US households for a year, assuming a typical US energy mix. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> <strong>Energy sources:</strong> The carbon intensity of the energy sources used to power AI systems determines their carbon footprint. Data centers that can draw on renewable energy sources can have lower carbon footprints than those that do not even if their energy consumption is similar.</p><p> <strong>Water consumption:</strong> The environmental impacts of AI and other information technologies go beyond carbon emissions. Data centers use large amounts of water in cooling towers and HVAC systems to prevent servers and other vital equipment from overheating. The intense computing and data requirements of AI models only increase data centers&#39; water consumption. Microsoft revealed in its most recent environmental report that its global water use increased 34% from 2021 to 2022 (to approximately 1.7 billion gallons, or more than 2,500 Olympic-size swimming pools). Google reported a 20% increase in water use during the same period, an increase that outside experts have linked to its AI development. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> This is a concerning trend for companies that have set ambitious environmental, social, and governance (ESG) targets that include being carbon-negative and water-positive by 2030.</p><p> <strong>Hardware:</strong> The production and disposal of AI hardware contribute to carbon emissions and the growing e-waste problem. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> The global volume of electronic waste is predicted to reach 120 million tons annually by 2050, double what it is today. The material value of the same e-waste — only 20% of which gets formally recycled — is approximately $62.5 billion. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> Recycling these resources and capturing more of that value could open the doors to a more robust, sustainable economy, minimizing the need to mine more of the materials used to manufacture them and keeping them out of landfills.</p><p> This doesn&#39;t mean we should stop the development and use of AI models to protect the climate. Despite these significant environmental costs, AI is also proving to be a vital tool in promoting sustainability and addressing climate change. AI is being used to maximize the utilization of renewable energy sources like wind and solar electricity and to develop intelligent grids that balance energy supply and demand. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> AI-powered solutions are helping farmers increase agricultural yields while applying fewer pesticides and fertilizers, resulting in more environmentally friendly farming methods. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> And AI is being used to optimize logistics and reduce waste in supply chains, to monitor and enforce environmental regulations, and to optimize data center operations through machine learning algorithms that dynamically adjust temperature settings, workload distribution, and server utilization. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p></p><p> AI&#39;s contributions to solving the climate crisis can outweigh its negative climate impacts, but only if the AI industry adopts practices that emphasize ESG sustainability, makes sustainability central to its AI ethics guidelines, and actively seeks opportunities to reduce the environmental footprint of AI technologies. Users of AI must also be aware of the factors that contribute to the environmental impacts of these tools in order to guide their own use of it, and add sustainability to the list of criteria they use to evaluate AI vendors.</p><p> Transparency is critical, and reliable measurements of new models&#39; energy use and carbon emissions must be published to raise awareness of them and encourage AI developers to compete on model sustainability. Much of what we know regarding the carbon emissions and energy use of AI models is through estimates calculated by third parties rather than figures reported by the developers of the models themselves, and this must change. Tools available today, such as the <a href="https://mlco2.github.io/impact/">Machine Learning Emissions Calculator</a> , can help AI engineers simulate carbon emissions on AI models based on variables such as hardware, number of hours, provider, and location. Researchers at Google suggest exploring four technical best practices that they refer to as the 4Ms — model, machine, mechanization, and map optimization — that separately reduce energy and carbon emissions. They claim that following these best practices can reduce machine learning training energy by up to 100x and CO2 emissions by up to 1,000x. <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p></p><h3> Relocate, Rightsize, and Re-Architect</h3><p> While the 4Ms address AI energy use and carbon emissions from a technical standpoint, best practices for sustainable AI can be more broadly expressed as the three R&#39;s: relocate, rightsize, and re-architect.</p><p> <strong>Relocate:</strong> Not all energy is created equal. We can mitigate the carbon emissions associated with AI&#39;s energy consumption by transitioning to renewable energy sources such as solar or wind power. In the past 10 years, the cost of power from solar and wind has decreased by 89% and 70%, respectively, and it is now less expensive than alternatives using fossil fuels like coal and gas. Although the price of wind and solar has decreased dramatically, the biggest constraint remains the need for access to round-the-clock renewable energy sources. Placing computing workload in Quebec, Canada, where the access to renewable energy is almost 100% and the average carbon intensity is 32 grams per kilowatt-hour, can result in a sixteenfold reduction in carbon emissions compared with the US average of 519 grams per kilowatt -小时。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Some cloud vendors use carbon offsets to substantiate their net-zero claims, but this is not the same as running on carbon-free energy; it simply pushes the problem onto someone else.</p><p> Moving from on-premise to cloud-based computing can save on emissions and energy by 1.4x to 2x if it is well architected. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Cloud-based data centers are custom-designed warehouses built for energy efficiency. The flexibility of the cloud also allows considerable freedom in choosing a workload&#39;s location. Compare the PUE (power usage efficiency) values of on-premise and cloud-based data centers: The lower the value, the more efficient the center. One can also choose a data center that runs primarily on renewable energy sources.</p><p> <strong>Rightsize:</strong> Companies often use more computing and storage resources than they need. They can reduce their carbon footprints by rightsizing their AI models and applications and using adequate archiving procedures. Performance and energy efficiency can be increased by 2x to 5x when using processors and systems designed for machine learning training instead of running general-purpose servers not optimized for AI workloads. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a> Optimization involves striking the ideal balance between the scope, model size, model quality, and efficient/sustainable resource use. Graphical processing unit manufacturers offer ways to limit how much power a GPU is allowed to draw, which can reduce energy consumption in exchange for slower performance — something that might be acceptable in many circumstances. <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a> Another strategy to consider is time shifting: performing demanding workloads, such as training periods, at times of day when the carbon intensity tends to be lower.</p><p> <strong>Re-architect:</strong> Building a well-functioning AI model requires a robust software/hardware architecture designed for scaling and fine-tuning the model while maintaining a low-latency response time. Choosing an effective machine learning model architecture, such as a sparse model, can improve machine learning quality while decreasing computation by 3x to 10x. <a id="reflink20" class="reflink" href="#ref20">20</a> Once an AI model has reached production, managing technical debt from a performance, security, and end-user experience perspective is crucial. Mismanaging or ignoring technical debt in favor of functional improvements can cause it to quickly accumulate and pose serious technology risks, including sluggish performance, poor-quality outputs, unanticipated downtime, data loss, or even security breaches. Only some applications or AI models can be redesigned. Still, when the chance arises, it&#39;s critical to investigate more efficient machine learning model architectures to guarantee better quality while reducing computation.</p><h3> Other AI Sustainability Practices</h3><p> In addition to the three R&#39;s, AI leaders must pay attention to the following as avenues to improve sustainability.</p><p> <strong>Data management:</strong> Digital data production is accelerating quickly. In 2022, the world generated an estimated 97 zettabytes, or 97 trillion gigabytes, of data. That figure might almost double, to 181 zettabytes, by 2025. <a id="reflink21" class="reflink" href="#ref21">21</a> Most of this data is generated for onetime use, never to be utilized again, yet gets saved on servers that take up space and use a lot of electricity. Responsible data management practices to reduce the amount of needlessly saved “dark data” are therefore essential for sustainable AI development and deployment. Larger models do not necessarily equate to better models; over time, performance will deteriorate. Energy consumption and environmental impact can be minimized by relocating data storage and processing to data centers that implement more energy-efficient cooling and are powered by renewable energy, and by implementing procedures for data compression, deduplication, and archiving dormant data.</p><p> <strong>Education and awareness:</strong> AI leaders can promote environmentally responsible AI practices by educating employees, partners, customers, and the public about the environmental impacts of AI. These impacts are not widely understood, and the easy availability of tools like ChatGPT can make using them seem equivalent to querying a search engine, even though a single ChatGPT query can generate 100 times more carbon than a regular Google search. <a id="reflink22" class="reflink" href="#ref22">22</a> The more that organizations and decision makers are attuned to the environmental consequences of AI, the more they will seek out solutions with lower environmental impacts and pressure AI providers to adopt more sustainable practices.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Compliance:</strong> Leaders in AI will need to keep an eye on emerging regulations and best practices surrounding things like energy efficiency and e-waste management and their implications for investments in technology. The US-based nonprofit trade association SustainableIT.org has released the first-ever standards tailored to IT&#39;s impact on business sustainability. Both general and AI-focused legislation is emerging, such as the European Union&#39;s Corporate Sustainability Directive and its <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/headlines/society/20230601STO93804/eu-ai-act-first-regulation-on-artificial-intelligence">Artificial Intelligence Act</a> , which is expected to be finalized and go into effect in 2024. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission&#39;s Carbon Disclosure Rule is pending, and California recently passed two laws that will require companies to file annual public reports disclosing their direct, indirect, and supply chain greenhouse gas emissions, and to have them verified by an independent and experienced third-party provider.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The widespread adoption of generative AI models comes with an urgent need for all players in the industry, including managers and users of AI, to take greater responsibility for the environmental and social impacts of this promising technology.</p><p> Following the sustainable AI practices outlined in this article can help build a more sustainable AI ecosystem. By finding ways to minimize the energy and natural resources consumed by our AI development and deployment processes and drawing more attention to sustainability issues in discussions about AI, we can harness the power of this technology while minimizing its negative impact on our planet and society.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为更透明的可持续发展报告做好准备</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:55:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Barker. <p>Richard Barker is a full-time member of the International Sustainability Standards Board, on leave from the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School. This article expresses the personal views of the author, not the official positions of the ISSB.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Reporting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko Rigorous sustainability-related financial disclosure is coming. The era of inconsistent, voluntary disclosure is giving way to mandatory reporting — but don’t treat this regulatory revolution as simply an exercise in compliance. It is instead essential work to gain greater visibility into your business’s exposure to risk and long-term prospects for success — for [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Barker_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p> Rigorous sustainability-related financial disclosure is coming. The era of inconsistent, voluntary disclosure is giving way to mandatory reporting — but don&#39;t treat this regulatory revolution as simply an exercise in compliance. It is instead essential work to gain greater visibility into your business&#39;s exposure to risk and long-term prospects for success — for the benefit of both investors and management.</p><p> Action has been brisk this year on the regulatory front. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plans to issue its climate disclosure rules by the end of 2023. In June, the International Sustainability Standards Board (ISSB) issued its first global standards; the European Union issued its European Sustainability Reporting Standards (ESRS) in August. The ESRS reporting requirements will be mandatory for large European companies starting in 2024 and in due course for international companies with European operations. Corporate reporting hasn&#39;t changed this much since the SEC was created in the wake of the 1929 stock market crash.</p><p></p><p> How should senior executives and boards respond to, and take advantage of, these changes? In this article, I will explain why focusing on what investors want from sustainability reporting is a critical lens for understanding how to act. Through that lens, I examine how best to navigate the evolving landscape of mandatory reporting.</p><h3>投资者需要了解什么</h3><p>Investors seeking gains via either growth or lasting value know that the energy sources that built the global economy are not those that will sustain it. Economic value will therefore be created by serving new and existing markets in different ways. Investors are looking to these different market conditions that lie ahead, where sustainability builds resilience and increases the capacity for growth.</p><p></p><p> Smart investors also know that if global warming is not slowed, and if natural resources continue to be depleted at the current rate, economic activity will suffer. Insurers are experts in anticipating and managing risk, and they are ahead of the game, rethinking where and how they do business. A consequence is that the costs of catastrophes related to climate change will increasingly be borne more directly by businesses and private citizens. The summer of 2023 saw New Yorkers sheltering inside from the smoke of Canadian forest fires; increasing damage from hurricanes in Florida; record high temperatures across the southern US; and dangerous, damaging flooding from summer rains in the Northeast. These are the scouting parties for the effects of climate change; the main forces will be along later.</p><p> In the broader global context, investors want to know how you see the future, how you are planning to meet it, and what value you expect to be able to create. Current financial reporting alone cannot offer this; in a disruptive world, investors cannot evaluate your prospects based on past performance. Investing is making choices. Sustainability informs returns.</p><p> This is not just compliance, any more than accurately tracking revenue and expenses is done purely for the benefit of regulators. Nor is it a PR exercise afforded by selective voluntary disclosures. It is instead the recognition that in a world roiled by wicked, systemic problems, what is material to sound investment decisions is changing; corporate reporting must change as well.</p><h3> How Mandatory Reporting Is Taking Shape</h3><p> For public companies in the US, the primary consideration has to be the <a href="https://www.mwe.com/insights/october-forecast-a-busy-month-for-climate-change-related-regulation-and-insurers/">SEC&#39;s forthcoming rules</a> , which will address investors&#39; demands for climate-related disclosures. At a minimum, the rules will likely require reporting on greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions generated from a company&#39;s directly controlled operations (Scope 1) and from its purchased electricity (Scope 2). More contentious is Scope 3 emissions, which occur as part of the value chain process by which the company makes its money, be that upstream in the production of inputs to the company&#39;s operations or downstream in the use of the company&#39;s products. The significance of these emissions varies enormously by industry. In some cases, where direct operations involve high emissions, Scope 3 might be relatively low. In other cases, Scope 3 might account for more than 90% of a company&#39;s carbon footprint.</p><p> From an investor&#39;s perspective, Scope 3 emissions are a risk factor because a business with a high carbon footprint is relatively vulnerable to transition-related risks. Such potential risks include regulations that restrict sales of carbon-intensive products (or make them more expensive), the loss of business or employees to competitors with stronger sustainability credentials, and the reduced availability of finance or the increased cost of capital. At the same time, a high carbon footprint can be seen as an opportunity for transition that reduces these risks and thus could increase the valuation of a company in relation to its peers. It is hard to make the case that information about significant Scope 3 emissions is not material to investors. It follows that — whether or not the SEC decides to mandate Scope 3 — companies that have Scope 3 in hand are better placed to be resilient than those that do not. It is inevitable that investors will seek this disclosure and that companies will increasingly provide it.</p><p> However, preparation for mandatory disclosure goes beyond keeping track of SEC requirements. This is because other regulators have extraterritorial reach and because sustainability reporting is inherently global, given international supply chains: Data is collected from your suppliers, who will in turn collect it from their suppliers, and so on up the supply chain. For a large corporation, this can easily amount to data from thousands of entities in many different countries. Good luck aggregating this data if it is not all measured in the same way. Meanwhile, your customers will be requiring sustainability data from you (and you from them, in order to understand downstream emissions). These customers will also be spread across different geographies. They might include unlisted and public-sector enterprises, because all are part of the value chain of listed companies. You don&#39;t want each of them to be asking you to measure different things, using different units of measurement.</p><p> It therefore makes sense to align with the global standards of the ISSB, which have been endorsed by the International Organization of Securities Commissions. Fortunately, the SEC climate proposal closely aligns with the ISSB&#39;s, and the agency “recognized the importance of global alignment and of drawing on existing frameworks that have enjoyed significant voluntary market uptake,” according to Allison Herren Lee, former SEC acting chair and commissioner. The widely used standards of the Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB) have been subsumed within the ISSB&#39;s, and both the Task Force on Climate-Related Financial Disclosures (TCFD) and the World Economic Forum have formally announced that they will sunset their guidance on climate disclosure and sustainability metrics, respectively, in favor of the ongoing work of the ISSB. Meanwhile, CDP — the global reporting platform for more than 50% of global market capitalization, formerly known as the Carbon Disclosure Project — will base its future data-capture work on ISSB standards. Overall, there is a clear direction of travel toward having the ISSB set the global baseline of investor-oriented sustainability disclosure standards that can be used across markets.</p><p> In addition — though not immediately obvious — voluntary alignment with global sustainability reporting practice will itself influence the rule-making of the SEC. The role of the SEC is to help ensure that markets are supplied with the material information that investors need and to do so in a way that passes a cost-benefit test. Where consensus has already formed around measurement and reporting, costs of reporting are lower, benefits to investors are greater, and material information is more readily available.</p><p> As noted above, business leaders must also be alert to the extraterritorial reach of some regulations. In early September, California passed legislation to mandate climate-related disclosures by any outside company doing business in the state and generating more than $1 billion in annual revenue. Meanwhile, international attention is currently focused on the EU&#39;s ESRS requirements, which are far deeper and broader than the SEC&#39;s are expected to be. There are 12 standards, covering a range of environmental, social, and governance disclosures in detail. And the scope of ESRS extends to “double materiality,” which means reporting not just to investors but also to all other stakeholders on issues material to them.</p><p></p><h3> Step Up to Meet Demands for Rigorous Sustainability Reporting</h3><p> As mandated corporate reporting expands to include sustainability issues, the following guidance can help you develop a plan to build the necessary capabilities.</p><p> <strong>Don&#39;t stop what you&#39;re already doing.</strong> You might be doing sustainability reporting in some form already, applying SASB, TCFD, or the Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) and/or reporting to CDP. You will need to build on these practices, but you are on the right road already.</p><p> <strong>Don&#39;t let perfect be the enemy of good.</strong> In the realm of voluntary disclosures, what investors want is whatever you can reasonably provide. Keep in mind that sustainability data is only indirectly relevant. Investors don&#39;t want to know your GHG emissions so much as they want to know how their presence affects your financials. For that purpose, reasonable estimation of emissions is typically good enough and, by such means as using industry averages, it is generally not hard to achieve. You should be careful to communicate the basis of your estimation, and you should not overstate the confidence you have in your measurements. Take advantage of safe harbor provisions, as appropriate. What your investors don&#39;t want is nothing, which would convey that you aren&#39;t being transparent, that you don&#39;t have material information about your business, or both. Either would be a good reason for investors not to invest.</p><p> <strong>Align with financial reporting.</strong> If your sustainability report is separate from your financial reports and investor presentations, then you&#39;re missing a trick. Investors want to understand how your sustainability-related position and performance affect your financial prospects. The more you can express your sustainability-related metrics and targets in the language of finance, the better. For example, it is one thing to have a target for net-zero GHG emissions; it&#39;s another to set out a transition plan that quantifies the capital expenditure that will be required and that guides investors in understanding current and prospective income statement effects.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on climate, and be ready for the SEC requirements.</strong> Because climate is the dominant sustainability issue, emissions are appropriately the focus of the SEC&#39;s regulation. If you are not on top of climate-related reporting already, at some point you will need to be, including being prepared to have your data audited externally. Moreover, climate is most likely your best starting point in sustainability reporting. It affects all companies, measurement practices are relatively established, and market understanding is relatively high. And if you can do climate reporting well, you will have built the capabilities needed for most other aspects of sustainability reporting, such as relationships and data systems throughout your value chain, and the art of translating sustainability data into financial implications for evaluation by your investors 。 To have this foundation, you will need to extend your data and control systems beyond your directly controlled operations, because your sustainability performance can be understood only in a value chain context. You should therefore develop your (material) Scope 3 GHG emissions reporting regardless of whether it is mandated by the SEC. This will become easier to do once Scope 1 and 2 disclosure is widespread.</p><p> <strong>Tighten systems and controls throughout your value chain.</strong> You should expect greater influence and control from your finance and legal functions as sustainability reporting evolves from being voluntary to being mandatory, and ownership of sustainability reporting migrates away from existing homes, such as communications, external relations, and dedicated sustainability teams. This migration will come with a higher hurdle for systems and data quality, and so it will almost certainly mean additional costs. But, as ever, focus on the business case, which means thinking about benefits as well as costs.</p><p> A comparison with financial accounting is again helpful. Your finance function is expensive — maybe too expensive. And maybe it could be more efficient. But is anyone suggesting that your company would be better off without it? No doubt there was pushback on cost when the SEC first introduced disclosure requirements. But then the world moved on, and the net benefit from reporting has become well understood.可持续发展报告也是如此。 If you build an authentic sustainability story, the benefits will exceed the costs. In addition, and relatedly, you should stay ahead of the curve. In a world of satellite data and artificial intelligence, your sustainability performance will increasingly be reported <em>to</em> you rather than <em>by</em> you — a scenario in which the best legal and reputational protection is to be in control and transparent. Don&#39;t allow your sustainability story to be an apologetic response to having breached the conditions of your social license to operate.</p><p> <strong>Align with the ISSB global baseline (and require your supply chain to do likewise).</strong> Your regulatory obligation is determined by the SEC. There is little reason to expect the SEC&#39;s investor-oriented focus to diverge from that of the ISSB. Yet there is good reason to expect regulation to become tighter and faster in major jurisdictions elsewhere in the world. You operate in a global economy, where the benefits of investment decisions are greater and the costs of gathering reliable data are lower if everyone shares the same measurement and disclosure standards. Aligning with the ISSB is the most effective way to align with the SEC while also reducing costs and improving data quality.</p><p> <strong>Use ISSB standards as a baseline for ESRS.</strong> The fundamental difference between ISSB and ESRS is that the former requires reporting to investors (consistent with the SEC) while the latter also requires reporting on issues that are material to all other stakeholders. If your operations draw you into the extraterritorial reach of ESRS, your optimal response is simple: Do what you would do anyway to report in the US and globally to your investors, and then separately include the additional disclosures required for ESRS compliance.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Contribute to the development of industry norms.</strong> Sustainability issues vary by industry. Companies are categorized by industry in the capital markets, to better enable like-for-like comparisons and to analyze shared exposures to industry-specific risks and opportunities. This is why the SASB standards are industry-based and why the ISSB has likewise committed to this standard-setting approach. Given that industry expertise sits within the industry and sustainability reporting remains a young practice, companies should participate proactively in discussions on best-practice reporting in their sectors, directly and indirectly helping to shape future standards.</p><p></p><p> Above all, ensure that your sustainability reporting has an authentic connection with value creation. If it feels like an exercise in compliance, then your company is missing opportunities. There should be alignment between information that is valued by your investors and that which is valuable to you in leading the business. Investors might see the company as being at greater risk of being left behind in a rapidly changing and increasingly perilous world, and your reputation in the marketplace could suffer. Consider instead how a willing embrace of tracking and disclosing sustainability performance can not only win support from the market but also, via focus and accountability, help you manage your company through the profound transitions that the planet and society demand of us all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>悖论中隐藏的机遇</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/#comments</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:45:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott D. Anthony. <p>Scott D. Anthony ( <a href="https://www.twitter.com/scottdanthony">@scottdanthony</a> ) is a clinical professor at the Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth College and a managing director and managing partner emeritus at growth strategy consultancy Innosight. He is a coauthor of <cite>Eat, Sleep, Innovate</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2020).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Management Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko The Research The author reviewed relevant academic literature; conducted in-depth interviews with executives, advisers, and intrapreneurs with firsthand experience in organizational paradox; and conducted analysis using systems psychodynamics (a set of tools to study the interaction between structures, norms, and practices of groups and the cognitions, motivations, and emotions of group members) as [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-Anthony_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>The author reviewed relevant academic literature;对具有组织悖论第一手经验的高管、顾问和内部创业者进行了深入访谈； and conducted analysis using systems psychodynamics (a set of tools to study the interaction between structures, norms, and practices of groups and the cognitions, motivations, and emotions of group members) as part of INSEAD&#39;s Executive Master in Change program.</p></aside><p> Leading an organization demands that we confront a constant array of choices. Should we invest in this market or that one? Should we offer luxury products or mass-market goods? Should we provide incentives to individuals or teams? Should we recruit university graduates exclusively or look for nongraduates with specialized skills? While these choices can require careful consideration, they are essentially straightforward. The really hard choices that leaders will face in our increasingly complex world, argue some management thinkers, represent a different kind of problem altogether: the paradox.</p><p> Many of us are likely to have encountered the idea of paradox primarily in the context of art or philosophy. Defined by the <cite>Oxford Pocket Dictionary of Current English</cite> as “a seemingly absurd or self-contradictory statement or proposition that when investigated or explained may prove to be well founded or true,” the word <em>paradox</em> might bring to mind examples like the Socratic statement “I know that I know nothing.” Paradoxes can be interesting to ponder, but we don&#39;t often consider how they might expand our thinking as organizational leaders. That is changing in important ways.</p><p></p><p> In their book <cite>Both/And Thinking</cite> , business scholars Wendy K. Smith and Marianne W. Lewis define paradoxes as “persistent, interdependent contradictions.” <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That means they contain at least two elements that relate to each other but appear to contradict. London Business School professor Herminia Ibarra described the “ <a href="https://hbr.org/2015/01/the-authenticity-paradox">authenticity paradox</a> ”: Leaders are told to be authentic in order to succeed, but an authentic leader can struggle to develop because they get fixated on being true to themself instead of what is required to succeed. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Some scholars assert that the very idea of an organization has a seeming paradox at its heart <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0018726702555001">because</a> “on the one hand it contains free, creative, independent human subjects; on the other hand, the relation between these subjects aspires to be one of organization, order, and control.” <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Innovation seems acutely paradoxical. To resolve Clayton Christensen&#39;s famous innovator&#39;s dilemma, you need to both listen to and ignore your best customers. Sustain and disrupt your current business model. Support and undermine your current value network. More broadly, today&#39;s leaders have to build inclusive and unique cultures that empower and direct employees while striking work-life balances for employees with very diverse desires.</p><p></p><p> Such apparent paradoxes can arise at the level of an individual, team, organization, and even the larger context in which an organization operates, like an industry, a state, or an entire society. But if a paradox is something that is fundamentally unresolvable, does that mean these business challenges are insurmountable?</p><h3> A Paradoxical Industry</h3><p> The energy industry seems to be in a particularly acute moment of paradox. A <a href="https://www.shell.com/business-customers/lubricants-for-business/perspectives/under-pressure-leading-in-paradox-industries.html">report</a> from Royal Dutch Shell called sectors like commercial transport, power, manufacturing, and energy “paradox industries” with “huge pressures to increase their output <em>and</em> reduce their impact on our planet. To grow in size <em>and</em> shrink their footprint. To automate <em>and</em> create jobs.” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> The stakes are high. Activist investors have suggested that these tensions are so intractable that Shell ought to split into three companies. In June 2023, Shell&#39;s newly appointed CEO announced plans to be “ruthless” in capital allocation, cutting some investments in renewable technologies and increasing investment in fossil fuels. “Ultimately what we need to do is to be able to generate long-term value for our shareholders,” said CEO Wael Sawan. “The answer cannot be, &#39;I am going to invest [in clean energy projects] and have poor returns and that&#39;s going to vindicate my conscience.&#39; That&#39;s wrong.” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> What options do Shell and other energy companies have in the face of a seeming unreconcilable paradox? Consider the contrasting approaches taken by two other major energy companies.</p><p> In the late 1990s, oil and gas giant BP attempted (and failed) to rebrand itself as “Beyond Petroleum” and invested billions in wind and solar projects, many of which were later <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bp-solar/bp-turns-out-lights-at-solar-business-idUSTRE7BK1CC20111221">shut down</a> or spun off. In February 2020, BP attempted another push toward clean energy, as CEO Bernard Looney <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/bp-gambles-big-fast-transition-oil-renewables-2021-09-20/">announced</a> plans to slash the company&#39;s oil output by 40%, sell $25 billion in fossil-fuel assets, and boost its capacity to generate electricity from renewable sources twentyfold. It acknowledged that its clean energy business was losing money and would continue to lose money until at least 2025. But when energy prices surged three years later, Looney <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/inside-bps-plan-reset-renewables-oil-gas-boom-2023-03-07/">announced</a> plans to slow the planned cuts and scale back spending on renewables. While BP&#39;s leaders stressed that the company was reviewing, not ending, its commitment to shifting its portfolio, the story seemed eerily reminiscent of its first foray into clean energy. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> BP&#39;s recent history may be said to typify an either/or mindset in action. That is, when you see the apparent tension between two parts of a paradox, you choose one or the other. BP approached renewable energy as fundamentally opposed to fossil fuels, aggressively ramping up (or marketing) the former at the expense of the latter — an approach that was doomed to snap back when circumstances changed.</p><p> In contrast, Danish energy company Ørsted has taken a both/and approach, wading right into the contradictions of a paradox to find a solution that unites parts that seem to be in tension. In 2009, management announced that the company (then known as DONG Energy) would seek to generate 85% of heat and power from renewable sources by 2040. It explored investment in offshore wind and began to wean itself off coal. By 2019, it had become the world&#39;s largest offshore wind-energy producer, achieving its aggressive target 21 years ahead of plan. In 2019, it sold off its coal business and its liquified natural gas unit. While it no longer produces gas, it continues to play in the space as an infrastructure provider and trader, with a spokesperson <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/articles/read/rsted-sells-lng-unit-says-its-natural-gas-business-is-going-nowhere">noting</a> in 2019, “There&#39;ll be a long transition period leading up to a 100% green energy system, during which society can&#39;t do without gas. Gas is the least harmful fossil fuel available to support the transition to green energy, and we&#39;ll continue to trade gas for years to come.” <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Companies should, of course, dynamically adjust their strategies based on market conditions. But, more broadly, they ought to rethink the limiting perception that there is a tension between pursuing short-term returns and longer-term strategic reorientation. A stream of academic research has repeatedly shown that the perceived trade-off between pursuing planet-friendly policies and maximizing financial returns is a false one. In his book <cite>Purpose + Profit</cite> , Harvard Business School professor George Serafeim describes a study that showed purpose-driven companies that took an integrated view of sustainability issues received a risk-adjusted boost of 6% in their share returns. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> A proven path to beating the market. And one that also does good for the planet.很简单，对吧？很不幸的是，不行。</p><p></p><h3> The Polarizing Power of Paradox</h3><p> Paradoxes are complex, adaptive, system-level issues with rampant uncertainty. That&#39;s <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-leaders-delude-themselves-about-disruption">why</a> the innovator&#39;s dilemma has proved to be so stubborn despite two decades of work by practitioners and thought leaders. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Humans suffer from a predictable range of biases and blind spots that make pursuing both/and solutions challenging. Confirmation bias causes leaders to ignore evidence that goes against their existing beliefs. Loss aversion and the status quo bias means people prefer avoiding risks over taking them. Hierarchy and groupthink make it hard for groups to see their way through complexity.</p><p> One recurrent finding from academic research conducted over the past two decades is that paradox produces polarizing reactions. My own research has corroborated this finding. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> I conducted a dozen in-depth interviews with business leaders who found themselves confronting paradoxes that scholars like Smith and Lewis have identified, such as the tension between pursuing profits and purpose, sustaining current operations and driving disruptive growth, and rewarding individual performance and encouraging公平。 (See “The Research.”)</p><p> On the positive side, these kinds of paradoxes produced feelings of curiosity, excitement, and engagement. One of my research subjects, who confronted paradox daily in his role leading an innovation unit within a highly conservative company, described how even <em>discussing</em> paradox makes him feel “stimulated, like in the middle of a great chess game.” An executive who helped launch two billion-dollar businesses within a large consumer goods company described how finding a “point off the line” (data that didn&#39;t conform to expectations) was exciting because it opened up the possibility of a new path to a解决方案。 Another executive described how, as a university president, he confronted the seeming paradox between high-quality, campus-based education and accessible, affordable online programs. The executive formed and led several special-purpose teams. One ensured that both on-campus and online offerings met rigorous academic standards. Another helped on-campus professors learn from online educators and vice versa. Beyond transforming his institute, the executive noted how the effort sparked personal growth: “At an organizational level I&#39;m more effective, and at a personal level I&#39;m either a better person or I&#39;m at least a more self-aware person ”。</p><p> However, <a href="https://journals.aom.org/doi/10.5465/19416520.2016.1162422">research</a> also suggests that paradoxes can foster “anxiety, uncertainty, and ambiguity, leaving individuals feeling threatened and defensive.” <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> A former CEO who drove strategic transformation at two organizations described how confronting paradox raised fundamental questions about the organization&#39;s identity: Having to make choices that invalidate aspects of that identity could have a cascading impact on individuals who connect to the organization&#39;s old identity.</p><p> One practitioner described the paradox of seeking to innovate within a law firm. “The work that I do is paradoxical in nature,” the lawyer said, “because we&#39;re meant to be doing innovation, which by definition is new, but if it&#39;s too new, nobody actually wants to do it because they want to see some proof, or they want some reassurance that it&#39;s going to work.” While a lawyer breaking from the practice of making decisions based on past precedent may seem trivial, such a break would require the lawyer to question a fundamental piece of themselves and their organization. The lost-in-paradox lawyer was left demotivated and frustrated: “I&#39;m stuck in the middle. I&#39;m not in a position to say, &#39;Let&#39;s go and change these structures that are impeding our work&#39; … [or] to say, &#39;Let&#39;s be honest about what we&#39;re doing and clearly state that … we&#39;re not actually doing groundbreaking stuff,&#39; so it feels disempowering.”</p><h3> Is It Really a Paradox?</h3><p> While classic philosophical paradoxes are unsolvable within their logical constraints, paradoxical problems in business can yield to solutions when leaders think beyond apparent constraints — or “out of the <em>para</em> -box,” if you will. Christensen called his first book <cite>The Innovator&#39;s Dilemma</cite> , not <cite>The Innovator&#39;s Paradox</cite> . The challenges of disruptive change are vexing, but like the perceived paradoxes facing modern executives, they are solvable. There&#39;s no law of nature that says law firms have to use past precedent when looking at innovation projects. Individuals can change a group and remain a part of it; individuals can change themselves without losing their sense of self.</p><p> Consider some of the other seemingly irreconcilable tensions that have been resolved:</p><ul><li> It was generally accepted that profitable manufacturing required making trade-offs between cost, quality, and speed — until Toyota showed that those trade-offs were false.</li><li> It was common knowledge that manufacturing had inherent randomness that required extensive quality control — until the Six Sigma movement showed that a tightly designed and managed process could produce highly predictable outputs.</li><li> Leaders believed they naturally had to adopt stricter control mechanisms as organizations grew in order to prevent employee malfeasance — until Netflix showed that “no rules rules.” <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></li><li> Environmental activists and business leaders knew that sustainability and profitability were incompatible goals — until Unilever&#39;s Sustainable Living Plan delivered on its commitment to double revenue while halving the company&#39;s environmental footprint.</li></ul><p> Executives can, of course, choose to follow either/or approaches. Or they can use the following techniques to seek opportunities to find both/and solutions.</p><p> <strong>Shift perspectives.</strong> Consider the concept of work-life balance. In the exact minute that you read this sentence, you can&#39;t be in balance, because you are doing one thing or another. Now, zoom out and imagine that you estimate that your life expectancy is 80 years. That&#39;s about 700,000 living hours. Let&#39;s say you are a <em>really</em> hard worker, averaging 50 hours a week, 50 weeks a year, for 50 years. That&#39;s 125,000 hours. So you work only 18% of your living hours.平衡！ Those extreme answers are not particularly useful, but consider the possibilities opened up by taking a quarterly perspective. That time frame allows rituals such as a weekend family retreat, decision rules such as having no more than 10 days of travel in a quarter, or more rigorous time-boxing, such as dedicating blocks of time for family activities.</p><p> Similarly, a shift in time horizon can reframe the renewable-energy tensions described previously. Consider one <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/43663662">study</a> contrasting five organizations operating in the oil sands of Alberta, Canada. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> All of the companies faced apparent paradoxical tensions in terms of their temporal (short- versus long-term) and philosophical (business versus society) orientations. Some companies viewed these issues as either/or poles that forced a choice. They prioritized practices that favored efficiency, such as quantitative planning, and minimized interactions with stakeholders, which led to what the researchers described as “temporal myopia” that resulted in the “narrowing of the solution space.”</p><p> Those that stepped back, shifted perspectives, and considered the interconnections between issues engaged multiple stakeholders and sought avenues for cross-collaboration. This approach allowed them to develop integrated solutions with greater potential for long-term benefits for all relevant stakeholders — including themselves.</p><p> One way to shift perspectives and find those points off the line that point to novel solutions to a problem is to run a series of thought experiments that play with constraints. That can involve <em>removing</em> a constraint, such as asking how you would approach an apparent paradox differently if you had infinite time or infinite resources, or <em>imposing</em> a constraint, such as imagining what you would do if the government suddenly outlawed the use of a particular raw材料。 While it might feel like imposing constraints would limit creativity, research consistently shows that constraints can focus problem-solving energy and boost creativity. One technique that can help spur these thought experiments is what Hal Gregersen <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/03/better-brainstorming">calls</a> a “question burst,” where you brainstorm not for answers, but for provocative questions. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> <strong>Adopt a paradox mindset.</strong> Adopting a mindset that views apparent paradoxes as opportunities boosts creativity and organizational performance, according to <a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2018-20753-002">research</a> . <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> People who demonstrate a <em>paradox mindset</em> agree with statements such as “Tension between ideas energizes me” and “I am comfortable working on tasks that contradict each other.” The paradox mindset can be approached in three ways. First, leaders can be <em>screened</em> to identify those predisposed to have a paradox mindset by having them complete a short <a href="https://paradox.lerner.udel.edu/">diagnostic</a> . <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Second, the items on the diagnostic can be used as <em>prompts</em> before a group discussion to help people consider multiple possibilities when discussing an apparent paradox. Research shows that simply starting a meeting by stating that tensions create possibilities helps a group adopt more of a paradox mindset.</p><p></p><p> Finally, there can be conscious efforts to help people <em>develop</em> a paradox mindset. Experience in dynamic circumstances or on challenging problems builds what is <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/smj.3415">known</a> as <em>cognitive complexity</em> (the ability to consider multiple possibilities with nuance), a key enabler of a paradox mindset. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Development plans that give high-potential leaders experience launching new products, working in emerging markets, or building new organizational capabilities help to prepare them to confront future paradoxes. More broadly, individuals can consider going on a paradox quest, consciously doing something that would be unusual for them, such as the following:</p><ul><li> Taking an art class, learning a musical instrument, or learning a new language.</li><li> Doing an extreme activity, such as skydiving.</li><li> Volunteering or participating in a socially oriented activity.</li><li> Enrolling in an online program to develop a new skill, like coding.</li></ul><p> <strong>Hold a paradox sparring session.</strong> Boxers use sparring sessions to train. The goal isn&#39;t to knock their opponent out but to practice form and response. A paradox sparring session is a purposeful place to bat around ideas and challenge assumptions. For example, in the early 2000s, a reorganization led to confusion within the iconic Danish toymaker Lego. Managers were being asked to do things that felt contradictory, such as simultaneously focusing on developing people and meeting stringent production targets. Lewis and fellow academic Lotte S. Lüscher led the group through a series of sparring sessions to discuss the apparent tensions. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p> Sparring sessions <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/smj.3415">should</a> challenge participants with four types of questions:</p><ul><li> <em>Linear</em> questions, such as “What are your concerns?” encourage explanation and bring logic to the surface.</li><li> <em>Circular</em> questions, such as “What do you think others think?” explore other perspectives and home in on polarities.</li><li> <em>Reflexive</em> questions, such as “What does what you say imply?” seek opportunities to critique and connect existing options.</li><li> <em>Strategic</em> questions, such as “Is what you say realistic?” motivate more expansive solutions.</li></ul><p> This approach helps to tease a perceived paradox out of a seeming mess, creating opportunities to explore potential novel solutions to transcend it. For example, Lego challenged managers to drive performance and allow teams to be more self-managed. A sparring session devoted to the seemingly paradoxical question of how managers could both let go of and retain control led to specific solutions, such as alignment around goals and degrees of freedom for teams, more regular dialogue between managers and teams, and focused investment to teach teams how to solve problems. Lego ultimately created a list titled “11 Paradoxes of Leadership” to help future leaders develop practical solutions to vexing challenges on their own.</p><p></p><p> Organizational paradoxes are ultimately illusions. They are artificial constructs, sometimes of a system, many times of the mind. They fail to meet the definition of a paradox because they are not irreconcilable. Yet these illusionary obstacles persist as groups and individuals protect themselves from the perceived challenges of addressing them. They demand engagement because the process of engagement reveals the illusion, develops a deeper sense of self, and builds an organization&#39;s capabilities. One of my research subjects, a former Silicon Valley executive researching the human side of transformational change, began our interview by saying, “Continual creativity comes from paradox. … All great meaning comes from grappling with paradox.”</p><p></p><p> Leaders who feel like they are facing a paradox should ask themselves four questions:</p><ol><li> Is the perceived paradox truly a law of nature, or a difficult choice?</li><li> Am I imposing a constraint that is creating the perceived paradox?</li><li> Am I hesitating to act because the perceived paradox is the result of the system I helped to construct, perpetuate, and potentially benefit from?</li><li> Does a different frame reveal the paradox as an illusion?</li></ol><p> There&#39;s no doubt that tackling perceived paradoxes presents challenges and requires work. It may feel easier for leaders to collectively shrug their shoulders and say, “What can I do? It is just too hard.” They can do better. Perceived paradoxes can be dissected and transcended, turning helplessness into empowerment. Make the paradox choice to turn either/ors into both/ands.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>