<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 30 日星期一 14:31:16 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>研发领导者必须在净零之旅中发挥关键作用</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Edwards and Michael Zeitlyn. <p>Dan Edwards 是科学集团（一家科学、工程和技术咨询公司）的集团董事总经理兼首席执行官。 Michael Zeitlyn 是 Science Group 咨询服务部总裁。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint]]></category><category><![CDATA[R&D]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com Major companies worldwide have pledged to reach net-zero emissions, but pledges are one thing, and action is another. Momentum can, of course, be difficult to sustain. Carbon reduction may be imperative for the good of the planet, but it requires businesses to think and operate in new ways, to collaborate with more outside [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Edwards_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>全球各大公司都承诺实现净零排放，但承诺是一回事，行动又是另一回事。当然，这种势头可能很难维持。为了地球的利益，减少碳排放可能势在必行，但它要求企业以新的方式思考和运营，与更多外部实体合作，信任新兴的数据收集流程，并任命研发和创新领导者处于流程的中心。</p><p> Science Group 召集了一次由研发领导者和首席技术官（包括来自 Amcor、拜耳、玛氏、百事可乐、宝洁、索尔维和 Stepan 的高管）参加的论坛，以确定公司如何将净零雄心转化为物质进步。特别是，我们希望帮助定义创新团队在这一过程中可以发挥的关键作用。在这里，我们重点介绍本次论坛中有关有助于为行业和地球繁荣发展<a href="https://sustainability.sciencegroup.com/net-zero-playbook/ ">之路</a>的实践的见解。</p><p></p><h3>行动授权</h3><p>如果公司希望其净零承诺不仅仅是良好的愿望，他们就必须将碳减排作为核心商业价值：管理层必须为此失眠，就像他们历来为安全、质量和利润失眠一样。净零行动是一项跨职能的举措，而且分工可能很模糊。营销、分销和其他业务职能部门将按照自己的时间表为公司的温室气体 (GHG) 减排目标做出贡献。例如，采购可能能够在短期内减少排放，而研发（顾名思义，具有前瞻性）可能需要三年、五年甚至十年才能发挥作用。当然，关键是所有职能部门都在朝着明确规定的目标齐心协力。研发部门应迅速、明确地阐明自己在碳减排方面的作用与企业其他部门的同事有何不同。研发领导者向其他管理人员提出科学论据的能力对于必须制定类似计划的同事来说是一个宝贵的帮助。</p><p>规划全公司的协作可以是一个自我发现的过程——揭示相互依赖性和潜在联盟的过程。当研发部门深入研究其目标时，其领导者还应该考虑如何招募自己公司之外的实体——供应商、客户、监管机构、非营利顾问，甚至竞争对手——来完成他们的普遍使命。有生之年可能会遇到。公司很可能正在制定其他有价值的可持续发展举措，领导者必须熟悉所有这些举措并了解它们之间的相互作用。</p><p>但同样重要的是，公司必须明确授权其研发领导者和首席技术官减少温室气体排放。一旦他们掌握了这一点，他们将能够发起变革，以确保未来的产品和服务具有更低的相关温室气体排放。研发和创新团队将站在第一线，通过使用替代原材料、重新设计的产品设计和更加气候友好的技术来减少温室气体排放。为了取得成功，必须从一开始就将净零融入到每个项目中，以便尽早且经常评估产品可能的温室气体足迹。现在，每次研发对话都应该考虑温室气体。为了避免有人认为这是一种三心二意的美德信号练习，应该根据团队的执行情况来评判团队。</p><p></p><h3>管理研发组合以实现净零排放</h3><p>研发领导者现在应该评估其现有项目组合的“碳健康”，以了解其与目标的契合程度。实现目标意味着确切地知道减排将在何时何地发生，而不是相信运气或仅在地平线上几乎看不见的未来技术。</p><p>迄今为止，可持续性往往是特殊项目的重点。这种方法可能有助于确保投资、展示雄心、创造动力并提升公司形象——这些无疑都是令人陶醉的诱惑。尽管如此，我们认为将碳减排纳入日常研发结构更为重要。净零的成功取决于整个投资组合的表现，而不是单个项目的兴衰。一些大型的、投机性的长期机会并没有错，但在整个研发组合中进行明智的押注是一种更明智的策略。并非每个项目都有可能推动净零排放事业。而且，坦率地说，研发可以让某个特定项目在减少温室气体排放方面表现不佳——例如，如果商业需求太紧迫，或者如果另一个部门可以通过其他方式抵消赤字——只要更广​​泛的投资组合继续存在追踪。</p><p></p><p>选择优先考虑哪些举措意味着确定最有希望的战场。研发可以推动并向前推进，将会取得胜利。某种产品可能是研发部门需要立即关注的主要候选产品，因为重新考虑其设计或制造，即使是最小的可能会对排放产生重大影响，或者因为这些改变可以在研发厨房中进行，而不会在整个供应链中产生连锁反应。但许多重大胜利都需要研发部门与组织内外的其他合作伙伴合作，尽管实现这些目标可能会更困难且需要更长的时间，但结果可能值得承诺和投资。</p><p>研发领导者应该期望提供其投资组合对温室气体排放影响的预测。衡量净贡献（甚至使用对未来影响的简单数量级估计）将使公司能够平衡商业需求和气候变化意图。随着时间的推移，环境、社会和治理报告将变得更加普遍，因为客户和利益相关者坚持了解哪些公司拥有稳健的可持续发展战略，并且公司本身意识到这些战略可以降低成本、刺激增长并最大限度地减少监管机构的问题。温室气体排放数据尚未达到当前要求的准确程度，但它不可避免地会得到改善。与此同时，研发团队需要习惯使用可用数据并接受近似值。</p><h3>商业现实</h3><p>人们常说，企业有一个选择：要么变得“绿色”，要么赚钱。没有人假装这件事没有真相。但随着消费者的变化、监管环境的演变、声誉受损的故事激增、对碳影响的考虑变得更加普遍，一套不同的商业现实将会盛行。目前，研发可以通过识别对净零信息传递有兴趣的客户、产品和品牌来建立动力。这是唾手可得的成果。正是在这里，碳友好型产品才能获得“绿色溢价”或提供竞争优势。在法规或标准青睐（甚至要求）碳减排产品的领域，市场可能会接受性能妥协或接受溢价。无论哪里的大门已经打开，创新者都可以利用气候友好型产品的市场价值。在其他地方，他们需要发挥创造力，不断寻找协同效应和飞轮，其中净零创新带来其他优势。</p><p>理想情况下，通过创新来满足市场需求——即实现传统的价值参数——将为减少碳排放创造附带机会。如果减少排放看起来是一个令人愉快的巧合，那么没有人会反对。有些制造工艺在减少碳排放的同时也可以减少前期资本成本或持续的能源成本。应优先考虑可以利用它们的项目，研发领导者应阐明碳减排的好处，即使首要任务是削减开支。</p><p></p><p></p><p>下一个提议可能看起来极端违反直觉，但如果低碳产品能够带来不同的胜利，研发领导者还应该考虑在价格和/或性能上进行权衡。一个多世纪以来，“新”和“改进”这两个词在广告词典中一直被融合在一起，因此公司不会高兴地宣布他们生产了效率较低的产品，因为他们想减少温室气体排放植物。但监管以及客户和利益相关者的意图已经开始推动这一趋势。</p><p> “实现净零目标需要勇气，”拜耳作物科学部门研发主管 Robert Reiter 表示。 “紧张局势将会存在，在某些时候，当唾手可得的机会消失时，就需要进行权衡。我想人们可以等待监管来创造公平的竞争环境，但有时公司只需要带头。”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rd-leaders-must-step-up-in-the-journey-to-net-zero/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为什么文本到图像的人工智能需要新的品牌思维</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrés Gvirtz and Oguz A. Acar. <p>安德烈斯·格维尔茨 (Andrés Gvirtz) 是伦敦国王学院国王商学院营销技术和创新助理教授，也是国王人工智能研究所的附属研究人员。他曾在诺基亚、贝尔实验室和麦肯锡从事人工智能和机器学习项目。奥古兹·A·阿卡尔 (Oguz A. Acar) 是国王商学院营销与创新教授，也是哈佛大学创新科学实验室的研究人员。他的研究重点是集体创新，特别是数字平台和人工智能心理学。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images In the world of marketing, brand identity is the castle that guards a company’s reputation, with a moat that keeps the competition at bay. One doesn’t need to look any further than T-Mobile’s signature magenta hue (226 red, 0 green, 116 blue) to realize how fiercely this castle is [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Gvirtz-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>在营销领域，品牌形象是保卫公司声誉的城堡，是阻止竞争的护城河。只需看一下 T-Mobile 标志性的洋红色调（226 红、0 绿、116 蓝），人们就能意识到这座城堡受到了多么严格的保护。使用类似的色调，您可能会在邮箱中发现一封停止信。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>但如果保护品牌的壁垒可能会阻碍它们在生成人工智能时代的未来呢？</p><p>在一项著名的广告活动中，Heinz 使用 OpenAI 的 DALL-E 生成器来创建受番茄酱启发的图像。这些图像在尺寸或颜色方面并不完美，但无可否认它们是亨氏的。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>这表明，即使人工智能模型也认识到亨氏品牌具有首要意识。一个老派的品牌纯粹主义者可能会对品牌的表现方式感到惊讶，但该活动<a href=" https://www.oneclub.org/awards/theoneshow/-award/49451/ketchup-ai">无可否认地引起了轰动</a>，在全球赢得了 8.5 亿次展示。</p><p></p><p>我们在自己的课堂上体验到了生成式人工智能对品牌塑造的变革潜力。作为学校百年庆典的一部分，生成式人工智能为伦敦国王学院的吉祥物——一只 <a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/ioppn-welcomes-new-students-and-kings-mascot-reggie-the-lion">名叫雷吉的火红狮子</a>——注入了生命。借助人工智能工具，吉祥物不再只是一个静态的品牌符号：在课堂教学中，雷吉变得生动活泼，引导了一些讨论，甚至在我们讨论商品管理时整理衣服并调整价格。结果是：乏味的库存图片被一个深受学生喜爱的吉祥物所取代，它与我们的学生产生了共鸣，并引起了压倒性的积极反应。但这只是这些工具对品牌潜力的开始。</p><h3>创造力与控制：明智地选择</h3><p>准备摆脱旧的保护心态的品牌会发现生成式人工智能为共同创造打开了新的大门。文本到图像的人工智能模型，例如 OpenAI 的 DALL-E，消除了日常消费者生成视觉设计的障碍，实现了前所未有的个人联系和定制水平。</p><p>在可口可乐的开创性举措“创造真正的魔法”中，消费者被邀请通过使用 ChatGPT 和 DALL-E 设计广告来释放他们的创造力。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>获奖作品不仅会受到赞扬，还会受到赞扬。他们很快就会点亮世界上一些最具标志性的广告舞台的广告牌，包括纽约时代广场和伦敦皮卡迪利广场。</p><p>我们以及其他人的研究表明，这些丰富的联系不仅会影响直接参与的人，还会影响相关人员。它们向外扩散，加强了整个市场的关系并增强了购买意向。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p></p><p>尽管前景令人兴奋，但许多品牌不愿袖手旁观，可能是因为担心失去控制。严格保护品牌标识和符号的古老方法可能会使它们落后于文本到图像模型的采用者。</p><p>今天的现实是，对人工智能技术的绝对控制仍然是一个白日梦。虽然生成式人工智能会更好地呈现一致的风格，但它无法遵守当今许多品牌所要求的严格准则。正如亨氏的活动中所见，虽然该技术复制了熟悉的瓶子形状和颜色，但它未能复制确切的徽标或品牌名称。依赖该技术“现成”版本的品牌可能需要等待很长时间。也许更重要的是，对控制的短视关注可能会阻止品牌完全打开生成人工智能提供的消费者参与的大门。</p><p></p><h3>品牌经理需要成为推动者</h3><p>前进的道路需要转变心态：品牌经理必须从执行者和守护者转变为推动者。它是关于关注更广泛的创新和联系机会，而不是痴迷于精确的颜色值等细节。</p><p> <a href="https://www.akqa.com/work/gofundme/help-changes-everything/">GoFundMe 的“帮助改变一切”活动</a>通过使用文本到图像模型以尽可能个性化的方式与捐助者互动，建立了新的消费者联系。 GoFundMe 没有制作典型的年终内容，而是使用 DALL-E 和 Stable Diffusion 等工具制作了一系列由人工智能生成的街头壁画风格的图像，展示了过去一年的所有筹款活动和捐助者。这些单独的作品随后被汇编成一段引人入胜的视频，引起了观众的强烈共鸣并获得了广泛好评。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>对此类机会持开放态度的品牌经理可以利用文本到图像模型来超越传统的沟通界限，实现以前无法达到的个性化和真实性水平。</p><p>当然，风险偏好不同。对于像 Monster Energy 这样大胆的品牌有效的方法可能不适用于保守的机构。但即使在高度监管和保守的环境中，也可以以限制风险和成本的方式进行试验。一次性活动或小规模项目的风险和潜在负面后果是有限的，因此是品牌探索的理想机会。我们为大学吉祥物制作动画的努力就是一个很好的例子。</p><h3>安全实验：可口可乐的教训</h3><p>这并不是呼吁无政府状态。品牌可以探索生成人工智能的可能性，同时保持在自己的舒适区和既定界限内。可口可乐的保护措施包括使用自己的平台、<a href="https://www.createrealmagic.com/">对其网站上显示的内容</a>进行监督以及为参与者提供可口可乐主题模板，所有这些都是为了保留对品牌形象的一定程度的控制。</p><p>可口可乐的这一举措是与贝恩和 OpenAI 组成的文本到图像服务联盟合作完成的，这帮助其从被动的立场转变为主动的立场。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>提供可口可乐等品牌安全和保障措施的提供商可能会成为首选合作伙伴。</p><p></p><p>当然，品牌经理必须防范潜在的滥用，并在创意自由和控制之间走钢丝。但我们不要忘记：品牌认知一直是与消费者共同创造的，并且取决于品牌行为和消费者反应之间错综复杂的双向关系。事实上，消费者长期以来一直在塑造品牌认知方面发挥着重要作用，无论是通过口碑认可还是严厉的评论。生成式人工智能只会强化这种动力，让消费者能够扮演各种角色：他们可以扮演设计师、电影摄影师甚至软件开发人员的角色。在生成式人工智能时代，积极倾听、持续监控消费者情绪以及根据实时反馈和新兴趋势灵活地重新调整策略变得更加重要。</p><p>虽然品牌无法控制每一个叙事转折，但它们可以更主动地引导对话。一种有效的方法是营造一种环境，使消费者能够相互联系并与品牌建立联系，并在透明的规则、激励和认可的框架内为品牌故事做出贡献。例如，可口可乐的生成式人工智能活动清楚地传达了它对消费者投入的重视——通过高度可见的广告投放来奖励杰出贡献，以及被选中前往可口可乐总部参加活动的机会内容创作研讨会。该品牌投资了一个专门的数字平台，旨在促进创新和加深消费者关系，同时降低风险并保持与其核心价值观和身份的一致性。</p><h3>解决道德和法律问题</h3><p>品牌经理还需要对围绕文本到图像模型的道德和法律问题保持警惕。随着主要人工智能工具公司卷入诉讼，及时了解所有权和知识产权 (IP) 的发展变得至关重要。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>品牌有理由担心法律影响，但只要出现挑战，创新就会随之而来。</p><p> Adobe 提供了一个创新示例，说明如何缓解客户对知识产权问题的担忧。 Adobe 的 Firefly 生成式 AI 工具可以让人们使用简单的提示创建或增强图像，因此 Adob​​e 在不受版权限制的库存图像、公开许可内容和公共领域材料上训练了 AI 模型。这是一种旨在解决客户担忧的前瞻性方法。</p><p></p><p>另一种有前景的方法是协作知识产权创作协议，重点关注人工智能开发者、创作者和品牌之间的互利关系。一个典型的例子是 Shutterstock 的贡献者基金，当创作者的图像被用于训练生成人工智能模型时，该基金会向创作者提供补偿。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p>品牌管理者应选择与能够有效降低知识产权风险的平台合作。品牌经理还可以考虑在合同中添加具体的保护措施，平台确认他们拥有适当许可的培训数据，并为针对该品牌的任何潜在知识产权侵权案件提供保证。对于生成式人工智能开发人员来说，这是开发尊重创作者版权并将其定位为品牌理想合作者的模型的强大动力。</p><p>总而言之，文本到图像生成人工智能模型正在拆除传统品牌城堡的围墙，创造一个充满机遇、风险和挑战的新现实。当我们应对这一转型时，每个品牌经理都必须面对一个至关重要的问题：您的品牌会在这个新时代成为桥梁还是路障的建造者？</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-text-to-image-ai-requires-a-new-branding-mindset/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>团队里其实有一个“我”</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elad N. Sherf, Subra Tangirala, and Alex Ning Li. <p>埃拉德·N·谢尔夫 (Elad N. Sherf) 是北卡罗来纳大学教堂山分校凯南-弗拉格勒商学院组织行为学副教授，也是莎拉·格雷厄姆·凯南学者。 Subra Tangirala 是马里兰大学罗伯特·H·史密斯商学院管理学院长教授。 Alex Ning Li 是德克萨斯大学达拉斯分校纳文金达尔管理学院的助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Teamwork]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Imagine running a factory that assembles electronic devices. Your operators work in highly interdependent teams on the assembly lines, and they’re dealing with a fundamental technological change that you recently implemented. Robotic arms and automated machines were put in place to streamline the assembly process, replacing several tasks previously performed by hand. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Sherf_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">宗晶晶/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>想象一下经营一家组装电子设备的工厂。您的操作员在装配线上高度相互依赖的团队中工作，他们正在处理您最近实施的根本性技术变革。机械臂和自动化机器的安装到位，以简化装配过程，取代了以前由手工执行的多项任务。</p><p>现在，机械臂可以处理重复且精确的运动，例如将组件拧在一起和涂粘合剂。这一变化使操作员摆脱了繁琐的工作，让他们专注于装配过程中更复杂的方面，例如质量控制、故障排除和过程优化。然而，他们必须适应新的工作环境：他们需要单独学习如何操作和维护自动化系统，同时还要学习如何作为一个团队进行不同的协调。</p><p></p><p>这种对团队成员与个人角色以及彼此之间关系的根本性改变在各种工作场所中都会发生。无论是由采用新技术、新法规还是结构转型的组织决策引发的，都需要个人和团队层面的适应。</p><p>例如，会计团队的成员在努力应对披露法的变化时，可能需要单独掌握新的报告规则，并重新考虑团队内部的协作以建立新的内部控制系统。从职能结构过渡到部门结构的组织的员工除了学习如何在新的跨职能环境中与同事有效协调之外，可能还需要单独获取有关每个部门提供的产品和服务的知识。</p><p>克服这些双重学习和适应挑战是成功变革管理的关键，但正如我们在<a href="https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2022.1621"><cite>《组织科学》</cite>最近的论文</a>中指出的那样，领导者往往没有充分关注团队中的个人是否、何时或如何进行再培训，以及何时进行再培训。这样做时，他们的关注点往往是整个团队。我们的研究表明，优先考虑个人再培训可能会带来好处。我们对制造公司的团队和个人如何适应变革的研究表明，当个人学习首先发生时，团队更容易适应根本性变革。</p><p></p><h3>在团队之前重新培训个人</h3><p>成功的团队合作需要两个不同层面的技能：团队成员需要精通自己的任务，并且需要很好地合作。我们认为，在团队成员掌握个人技能之前，团队很难掌握并最大化集体协调。这是因为集体掌握通常只能建立在个人技能的基础上。为了最好地应对根本性的变化，个人技能的发展应该首先发生。</p><p>这些想法得到了我们对中国东部一家拥有 10,000 多名员工的大型电子制造公司的一个部门所发生的根本性变化的研究的支持。我们在几个月内跟踪了 116 个制作团队。这些团队刚刚开始适应一系列激进的技术进步，需要使用新颖的工具和生产流程。为了衡量变革前后的团队绩效，我们使用了公司自己的指标“产量”，即按照技术规格正确制造的产品的百分比。</p><p></p><p>正如我们预期的那样，适应变化的需要确实对产量产生了负面影响。变动前两周左右，平均收益率为99.15%；变化后约4周，平均收益率已降至93.82%。但下降的情况并没有在所有球队中平均分配。我们将团队之间的一些差异归因于团队面临的变革强度的差异：一些团队在个人和集体层面上都有更多需要重新学习的东西。</p><p>然而，考虑到变革的强度后，我们发现最初专注于个人技能再培训的团队比立即专注于改善集体协调的团队表现要好 12%。奖励系统发挥了关键作用：在初始阶段获得更多以个人为中心的奖励（与以团队为中心的奖励相比）的团队成员在从变革中恢复的早期表现出色。</p><p>两个月后，当我们在变革的后期再次探索收益率时，所有团队的平均收益率已回升至 96.95%。然而，与变革前的团队绩效相比，团队绩效存在很大差异。</p><p>此时，以个人再培训为基础、现在专注于集体协调的团队的表现比没有进行这种转变的团队高出 11%。这种焦点的改变是通过更加集体导向的奖励制度实现的。在变革的后期阶段强调团队奖励的团队更容易将注意力从个人重新技能转移到集体协调。</p><h3>分两个阶段管理变革</h3><p>我们的研究表明，管理根本性的组织变革需要两阶段、顺序的响应。</p><p>在发生根本性变革后的早期，领导者应鼓励个人任务重新技能化。这种再培训不仅意味着提供相关培训，还意味着在尝试改进整个团队之前，让成员有时间单独尝试和掌握他们的任务。在我们的研究中，早期成功的团队给了成员更多的时间来尝试新的方法来完成自己的任务，并使标准化设备适应自己的需求。</p><p>奖励制度应该支持这一阶段的个人再培训。当奖励反映个人贡献时，团队成员就会专注于提高个人技能。这种奖励可以促进自我关注和对个人目标的追求。</p><p></p><p>在发生根本性变化之后的后期，一旦团队成员掌握了各自的任务，他们就可以开始尝试协调和任务流程，并确定集体流程中的冗余。在我们的研究中，一旦成员单独掌握了新任务，很明显他们中的一些人可以比以前更快地完成任务。这一结果意味着团队必须改变任务分配方式以最大限度地提高工作流程效率。在这个阶段，应该更加重视团队奖励。当奖励以团队为中心并且成员之间的薪酬差异最小化时，团队成员就会专注于学习集体技能。这些奖励促进对他人的关注、协作和对团队目标的追求。</p><p>奖励的顺序对于确保团队成员以正确的顺序专注于正确的优先事项至关重要，从最初关注个人重新技能转变为后来才练习集体协调。从一开始就只提供以团队为导向的奖励无法激励构成团队行动基础的个人再培训。</p><h3>时机很重要</h3><p>虽然我们的研究提供了一些经验证据来支持在团队技能之前培养个人技能的想法，以提高对商业环境变化的适应能力，但我们可以观察到这一原则如何同样适用于其他领域。</p><p> 20世纪90年代初，足球界引入了一项新规则，禁止守门员用手接住后卫踢回给他们的球。这代表了这项运动的方式发生了<a href="https://99percentinvisible.org/episode/unsure-footing/">根本性的变化</a>，因为它需要新的技能和新的协调类型。</p><p>起初，球队在新规则下表现不佳。防守队员习惯性地将球踢回给守门员。由于守门员无法用手触球，步法不熟练，导致球队出现失误。</p><p>许多足球教练最初关注守门员和后卫之间的交接，以改善这组球员之间的协调方式。这些方法并不是很成功。他们要求球员在守门员和后卫都发展出新的个人技能之前就注重协作，从而本末倒置。</p><p></p><p>相比之下，其他教练则专注于帮助守门员和后卫首先熟练掌握自己的带球和传球技巧，而不是让他们互相配合。直到后来，一旦球员们单独获得了这些技能，这些球队才将他们聚集在一起，以新的、创造性的方式协调他们的防守和进攻。这一策略更加成功，并导致了对整个游戏玩法的重新构想。</p><p></p><p>集体能力只有在强大的个人技能的基础上才能增长。领导者经常忘记这一点，并且在变革时期，在成员掌握各自的任务之前尝试团结团队更好地合作。管理变革的领导者应该记住，在加入团队制定如何最好地进行集体协作之前，为个人提供足够的空间和激励，让他们自己尝试和学习新技术和知识。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>企业中的创业型人工智能：LG Nova 的 Shilpa Prasad</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[A former startup employee herself, Shilpa Prasad knows the level of commitment and effort required to begin a new venture. That’s what led her to join LG Nova, electronics manufacturer LG’s innovation incubator, as an entrepreneur in residence. In her role, Shilpa identifies promising startups — particularly those working with AI — and coaches and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>希尔帕·普拉萨德 (Shilpa Prasad) 本人曾是一家初创公司的员工，她知道创办一家新企业所需的承诺和努力程度。这促使她作为入驻企业家加入电子产品制造商 LG 的创新孵化器 LG Nova。 Shilpa 在她的角色中发现了有前途的初创公司——尤其是那些与人工智能相关的初创公司——并指导和培养企业家，同时密切关注有一天可能会进入 LG 生态系统的产品。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客中，Shilpa 解释了如何把握初创企业的脉搏帮助 LG 电子对创新和新商机保持开放态度。 She also discusses why artificial intelligence is at the forefront of her work with startups, and the promising future she sees for using augmented reality and AI technologies to change how skills training is delivered. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MMAI-S8-E2-Shilpa-Prasad-LG-Nova-headshot-3000-1x-scaled.jpg" alt="希尔帕·普拉萨德"></p><h4> Shilpa Prasad, LG Nova</h4><p> Shilpa Prasad is an experienced leader in the startup ecosystem with a strong passion for entrepreneurship and corporate startup engagement/innovation. She brings over 15 years of global experience in corporate startup strategy and venture-building to her role as entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova, where she is helping the company identify market trends and build partnerships.</p><p> Prasad has been instrumental in driving innovation for various open innovation projects across corporations, governments, and accelerators and in establishing new partnerships across the global startup ecosystem. An experienced founder, she has also contributed her time to mentoring and advising startups.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> How can an entrepreneur in residence kick-start new, AI-based businesses in a large incumbent organization? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m Shilpa Prasad from LG Nova, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p>大家好。 Today Sam and I are excited to be joined by Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova. Hi, Shilpa. Welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Thank you, Shervin. Excited to be here.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Tell us about LG Nova and your role there.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I get asked this a lot. LG Nova is the innovation center of LG Electronics, based here in Silicon Valley. Our mandate is very simple: We&#39;re tasked with finding new business opportunities for LG Electronics that are not core to their bread-and-butter business. LG Electronics is a consumer electronics manufacturer traditionally, looking to make forays into solution-driven businesses. And so [it&#39;s] constantly identifying new technologies and areas that can be interesting for them to build upon and hopefully launch billion-dollar businesses out of it.</p><p> That&#39;s what LG Nova is. My role at LG Nova is entrepreneur in residence, and what that entails is I have many different hats that I wear, one of them being a plain consultant for the corporation. And by consultant, I don&#39;t mean traditional consulting but more in the context of, what are some of the trends to look out for, what new technology areas could be interesting, [and] how can we combine a multitude of technologies, maybe, for a business opportunity? That&#39;s one part of it.</p><p> The second part of it is very much focused on outside-in innovation. Our roots are set on the fact that we don&#39;t want to do what somebody else has already done, and startups are a great example of how quickly they innovate. And we want to bring that innovation into the enterprise that we are and leverage some of that capability to chart out a path together.</p><p> So collaboration with startups is key, and that&#39;s where the entrepreneur side of me kicks in — where you&#39;ve got to be able to understand the mindset of the entrepreneur, the speed at which they function, what drives them, what makes them do the stuff that they do — and convey that to the corporation in an effective way. And then, of course, there&#39;s the reverse role, where the entrepreneurs don&#39;t necessarily — outside of the corporation — understand the workings of the big corporation, and how you bridge that gap, I think, is very crucial to the role. It sounds very simple, but there are a lot of balls in the air in that sense, and you&#39;ve got to be able to juggle all of that at the same time while keeping your eyes on the goal of building new business.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;re talking about a large, global, multibillion-dollar company that&#39;s operating at a given speed, and you also want this group to operate at a much faster, I would assume, entrepreneurial speed. So I could imagine why it&#39;s juggling a lot of balls.</p><p> I wanted to ask you, is it identification of these technologies or innovation opportunities/disruptors, or is it an addition — incubation and building — of these as well?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. So there is the ideation piece, but there is also the venture-building piece, and part of venture-building is incubation. So you have maybe six months to identify an opportunity, build toward something, and then demonstrate that capability both on the product side [and] on the business side to senior stakeholders and investors wherever necessary, and then drive that to new business. So that definitely is a big part of what I do there.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Maybe it&#39;s just what Shervin and I hear a lot of, but there&#39;s a lot of artificial intelligence with startups, and you haven&#39;t mentioned artificial intelligence yet. So how does artificial intelligence intersect with your role?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> AI is not intersecting. It&#39;s at the forefront of what I&#39;m doing. If you remember like a year, year-and-a-half ago, Sam, there was a big hype around the metaverse, and technologies come and go. My focus is to identify real-world problems that can be solved using and leveraging some of these technologies. So AI is definitely at the forefront. There&#39;s a lot of AI-related work that goes on inside of the enterprise which focuses on servicing the existing business units, and that&#39;s not what I&#39;m put in place to do. My role is to look at AI as a technology and identify areas that could be interesting to solve as a problem in this ginormous world and build a business around it.</p><p> I can&#39;t speak too much of exactly what I&#39;m building, but I can talk to the fact that there is an intersection of augmented reality and artificial intelligence that I personally am charting internally here, which will possibly change the way skilled-training transference, upskilling, reskilling, and content around that is going to play out.</p><p> I&#39;m sure you already know this — that with AI in the mix now, so much of this can be so intuitive, with a feedback loop that can be generated for both the trainee and the reviewer and essentially allow workforce development or skill training in particular to move forward at a much faster pace.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It seems like AI is going to be more of a key ingredient of the mix, not just an additive, and so keeping humans in the mix is going to be even more key. I hear thematically in what you&#39;re talking about a focus on that. So tell us a bit about AI that&#39;s happening. You said you can&#39;t speak much, but I still want to tease some information out of you. So talk about AI that&#39;s happening within this innovation center, or contrast it with AI that&#39;s happening at the enterprise.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m sure both of you are very familiar with a large enterprise and the channels one has to navigate in order to get anything to market. And what I mean by “get anything to market,” it&#39;s also about releasing something which impacts a lot more inside the enterprise, right? So when you look at the traditional sort of research that happens around AI within the enterprise, and particularly LG Electronics, my understanding thus far has been that the appetite for risk-taking is limited because it disrupts a lot of their existing work, [whereas] something like this that I&#39;m charting out is leveraging some existing technologies that are out there, and when we launch something like this into the market, none of the existing pieces are impacted — in fact, they&#39;re benefited.</p><p> So LG, for example, has 85,000-plus workers across the globe working in factory environments. Everybody understands today that there is a gap in the labor that&#39;s available in the factories from a front-line worker perspective. There are productivity-related asks constantly within the enterprise to make sure that the entire … capacity is being met. These are all real problems that the AI research within the enterprise is not addressing.</p><p> You asked about the time to market. My mandate is six months to figure out whether a business can go to market or not. I think on the enterprise side, it&#39;s a few years, if not more, right? Anywhere between two to five years.</p><p> It has always been a topic of conversation, saying, “Corporate is slow; the startup is fast.” So I&#39;m essentially building a startup inside corporate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So, what I&#39;m hearing is sort of unshackled from a lot of the sort of legacy scale — with which comes inertia — and much faster sort of as new ventures that are going out. And, of course, some of that innovation then helps some of the existing enterprise AI that&#39;s going on, right?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah.绝对地。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful. You talked about upskilling, reskilling, and possibly reimagining the role of humans in this whole mix with AI — in the mix you talked about. Tell us about generative AI and where you see that play out in this.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think the possibilities are humongous, just like with any other opportunity in AI. One of the aspects of, for example, intersecting augmented reality technology with AI means that we&#39;re not only focusing on voice and text with respect to AI but also computer vision-related data streams that are being captured and processed in order for skill transference to happen as effectively as possible.</p><p> So think about a nurse training environment. We&#39;re not practicing on real patients but on the dummy. If you have to teach trainee nurses how to position the patient on the bed in order to do a specific procedure, then there is a multitude of value in capturing the data stream from the head trainer nurse in order to see how to do that and, when you&#39;re actually practicing it, to get real-time feedback, right?</p><p> So we&#39;re looking at multiple data streams here. So not just NLP [natural language processing], but we would be looking at computer vision-based technologies and bringing in AI to almost superpower that process and that trainee and training experience on both sides, right? So that&#39;s an example of how we&#39;re doing it differently.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Normally, I&#39;m pretty excited about the applications of artificial intelligence we talk about, but I get a little threatened here [for] a second. I mean I&#39;m an educator here, and I hear you talking about all sorts of different ways of reskilling and retraining. Where do I go? You mentioned a model before with nurses, where the experienced nurse would teach the less-experienced nurse. Maybe a lot of that gets replaced. What&#39;s the role for that experienced nurse now in this new model?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. Well, actually, Sam, I think your fear is maybe misplaced here, and let me explain this. We&#39;re not trying to replace the trainer. What we&#39;re doing is actually empowering the trainer with more opportunity to do the stuff that they should be doing. So in the training-of-the-nurses example, a head nurse has to actually physically stand next to the trainee nurses, possibly multiple times during the day, and teach them how they&#39;re doing their specific tasks. Now imagine a scenario where we&#39;ve eliminated at least two levels of feedback, review, and assessment before the head trainer can actually come into the mix and take a look at what&#39;s going on.</p><p> So the certification, I think, is still very, very important, right? Whether it be manufacturing, whether it be health care — the two examples that we&#39;re talking about — the certification is still important, and that certification comes from the trainer, who is the expert. So we&#39;re not removing the expert. It&#39;s actually empowering the expert to also be able to train effectively and not have to monitor 100 screens of trainee nurses that are doing their job. So you see the difference, hopefully.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. Sam&#39;s a tenured professor, so I don&#39;t think he&#39;s going anywhere. But, Sam, it&#39;s a little bit like the full professor, ie, yourself, sort of not being bogged down with the things that a graduate student can take care of, and you only do the tough ones and the ones that really tease your brain.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That sounds glorious to me.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think it&#39;s an assistant, right? You&#39;d have an AI assistant that could actually do a lot of the grunt work that otherwise you have to sit and do. So I think there is value in it. At least we&#39;re seeing some inferences of value that we&#39;re able to generate in the very early conversations we&#39;re having.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful. Shilpa, tell us a little bit about your background, how you ended up in this role.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> My career is a zigzag line, Shervin; it&#39;s not a straight line to what I&#39;m doing today. Over the years, I think there&#39;s always been a lot of value and joy that I have found in creating something [from the] ground up. The energy, the momentum, and the rigor it requires to scoop something up from nothing and create something out of it has been at the core of everything I&#39;ve done.</p><p> So very early on in my career, I had the opportunity to partner with someone to start [up] a graphic design studio. And there, I learned the mechanics of what it takes to actually create a business. It taught me a lot of the pieces that went into it.</p><p> From there, I&#39;ve always landed myself in roles that were actually entrepreneurial in nature or servicing the entrepreneurial ecosystem. I&#39;d like to mention a company called YouNoodle Inc. that I worked with here when I first came to Silicon Valley. There, I learned the power of selecting the right startups or innovations to work with in order to move innovation forward, whether in the context of corporations, governments, universities even, and large-scale accelerator programs.</p><p> That led me to my own entrepreneurial journey again, during COVID. It was really difficult. I launched a startup called LongPlay and built a team of about 10 people. It was focused around changing the way corporate innovation happens. And one of the things I think there is, when you&#39;re outside of the corporate, there is just no way to understand all of the different moving parts that go on. So we couldn&#39;t prove product-market fit there, which is where Nova came into the mix. I got the opportunity again to try to do a product-market fit in an industry and an environment that was a little different from what I was used to, but I think the nuts and bolts are the same. So that&#39;s just a quick background on me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s super exciting — very multidisciplinary. And it brings me to my next question: There is no one-size-fits-all when it comes to AI, and it&#39;s of course a full ecosystem of engineers and software engineers and prompt engineers and AI engineers and data scientists, etc. But I&#39;ve been noticing a gradual evolution of the skills over the past, I would say, 10, 12, 15 years or so, from hard-core technical-only to also more multidisciplinary, and that “multidisciplinary” could be in a variety of areas. It could be in social sciences or it could be in human-AI interaction, or it could be in philosophy or whatever. But are you seeing the same thing, and what is your perspective on talent of the future in this space of AI?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> It&#39;s an interesting question. I have to say I&#39;m not seeing the same thing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I&#39;m not seeing the width as much as I&#39;m seeing the depth. There is still, I think, a tremendous gap in the workforce with respect to being able to be multidisciplinary. There&#39;s a lot of, to your point, deep tech work that happens, especially around AI.</p><p> I think that&#39;s [something that] over the next few years, a lot of the folks like myself that are responsible for how this technology unfolds are going to have to carry with them.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That comes to measurement too. I mean — Shervin, I know that&#39;s a <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">hot topic for you right now</a> — but when you&#39;re talking about impact, you&#39;ve got to figure out how to measure it. There&#39;s going to have to be some measure of “Is this working? Is this not working?” And these seem like some difficult problems, particularly with the newness of the technology, the freshness of the timelines that you&#39;re talking about. It seems very difficult to figure out if this is working or not working in your role.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah. I mean, I can give it a little bit of a personal take. My style of building projects has always alluded to testing it as much as possible with the customer who has the problem.</p><p> And that&#39;s where the product focus sort of is very front and center for me, and that&#39;s why venture-building is exciting. When we talk about measurement, there are definitely different ways in which the impact of what we&#39;re creating or what we&#39;re trying to create can be measured. There is a market validation aspect here, right? There is definitely an investor validation aspect, meaning our investors ... It&#39;s not just about my project, right? It&#39;s not just about the project that I&#39;m creating or building. It&#39;s actually more about where the money is going. And, of course, a little bit of it is hype, but a little bit of it is also taking the chance on the next thing that is likely to change the way AI is going to be used in day-to-day environments or contexts.</p><p> I think the third part here is also just about empowering the users, ultimately, of whatever solution we&#39;re creating and whatever we are building, in order for the business opportunity … Ultimately [it] has to add value to the humans — that is, you and I, who are actually going to use that technology to make our lives better. Today, we&#39;re doing the work in the exact same way that we are taught or we&#39;re used to or we have learned how to, and we&#39;re going to have to change that or adapt that and pivot to a new way of doing things.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And is AI enabling you to have better data and information on that? Is AI enabling you to know something that maybe 20 years ago would&#39;ve taken you a lot longer to know?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Absolutely, but I think “Is AI enabling me? Only <em>it</em> will do that,” I think, is perhaps a lot of weight on AI and less relevant to what has been done in the past 10, 15 years in a specific industry. I think AI also has a flip side to it, which is, sometimes it&#39;s putting too much in front of you, where then you have to actually go through the top layers to really figure out where this data can be used and how this data can be applied. So there&#39;s the pro and the con of AI as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned cons. What kinds of cons are you seeing from these startups you&#39;re working with? What are people struggling with here?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I think the startups, in particular, are still looking for ways in which whatever they have developed can be applied. The application of AI in effective ways is still to be determined. And so startups are creating all these LLMs [large language models] that can be relevant to the project, but they don&#39;t know <em>how</em> it&#39;s going to actually translate.</p><p> So I&#39;d say there&#39;s still a little bit of a journey there for the startup to be able to understand it. And in the context of the role that I have today, for example, I&#39;m also enabling the startup to understand how they can use the technology that they&#39;ve created and translate it over to a meaningful problem, but … that&#39;s why I said consulting before. It&#39;s consulting for the startup as well: to give them some real-[world] scenarios where you can apply something that we&#39;ve built together and then see how it translates into value. So I think the startups are still learning for sure, Sam.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So those things actually tie back to maybe some of Shervin&#39;s comments about breadth and breadth of knowledge and multidisciplinary, because you didn&#39;t specifically mention that they&#39;re struggling with technology. I heard lots of things there that were not particularly technology-oriented.</p><p> Let&#39;s transition here. One of the things that we do at the end of the episode is we ask you five questions. We&#39;re going to ask them fast. We just want your first reaction from them. What do you see as the biggest opportunity for AI right now?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Health care.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK. What&#39;s the biggest misconception that people have about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> That it&#39;s going to replace them. That it&#39;s going to replace us as humans. That&#39;s not going to happen, I think. We&#39;re a ways away from that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Ways away.好的。 What&#39;s the first career that you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> To be an entrepreneur. I think it was always in my DNA.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Good. Did you have a lemonade stand when you were growing up?</p><p> When is there too much artificial intelligence? Where are we trying to make a square peg fit in a round hole?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> I don&#39;t think I have a concrete answer for you, Sam, there. So if you&#39;re going to switch the question out …</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ask it this way: Can it be too much?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Can you put too much artificial intelligence into a product?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. I think an area that comes to mind is cobots — collaborative robots. It could work, it may not work, and then it&#39;s very heavily AI-driven. So automation is key there, but how much of that could be relevant, I think, is questionable for me personally.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> If you were fantasizing, what&#39;s one thing you wish artificial intelligence could do right now that it can&#39;t currently do?</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Make me sound as good as I possibly can.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Shilpa, thank you so much. This has been illuminating and wonderful. Thanks for being on the show.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening today. On our next episode, we&#39;ll hear how Harvard Business School professor Ayelet Israeli suggests augmenting corporate market research with generative AI. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Can Friction Improve Your Customers&#39; Experiences?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli. <p>Marco Bertini is a professor of marketing at Esade and Ramon Llull University in Barcelona and a senior adviser to Globalpraxis. Diego Aparicio is an assistant professor of marketing at IESE Business School in Barcelona. Aylin Aydinli is an associate professor of marketing at Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Journey]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bertini_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; after all, competitor websites are but a few clicks away.</p><p> Most business leaders we know prioritize eliminating friction at the “moment of truth,” when displaying prices and taking payment, because beyond wanting to make life easier for eager customers, they fear giving customers reason to pause and reconsider their decisions. But as we will demonstrate, it is precisely in giving customers time to consider their purchase decisions when money is on the line that longer-term benefits and cost savings can accrue to the firm.</p><p></p><h3> Friction and the Fickle Online Shopper</h3><p> It&#39;s easy to see why making shopping as seamless as possible is so urgent for e-commerce companies, when the average global cart abandonment rate for the last 12 months stood at a staggering 71.7% overall — 60.7% among people using desktop or laptop computers, 65.1% among those using tablets, and 77.4% for those using mobile phones. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This last figure is perhaps the most troubling, given that mobile shopping in the US grew by more than $200 billion in three years to reach $431 billion in 2022. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> According to the Baymard Institute, the average large e-commerce site could increase conversion by 35% by streamlining and simplifying the checkout process. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Not surprisingly, e-commerce titans such as Amazon and Alibaba are investing heavily in quickly ushering consumers through their moments of truth by making prices and payments nearly invisible. Amazon pioneered one-click shopping back in 1999. Today, the attention is on its Just Walk Out technology, which blends computer vision, weight sensors, and deep learning to bring some of the ease of online shopping to physical stores: Patrons tap a credit card when entering a retail location to open a virtual cart, select items from the shelves, and leave without stopping at the cashier. At Alibaba, digital payments and self-service checkout stations are the norm across its 300 Freshippo supermarkets. People can even leverage its Alipay affiliate&#39;s facial recognition technology to “pay by face.”</p><p> Companies with fewer resources are making changes to their purchase processes that are more incremental but no less significant. Consider, for example, the recent popularity of “buy now, pay later” installment financing or of automatic-renewal clauses for subscription-based services, which allow companies to avoid the annual reckoning of customers reconsidering whether they still want the service. Online businesses have embraced these and other opportunities to make spending money less painful simply by allowing customers not to think about it.</p><p> However, it is simplistic to think of friction as having strictly negative effects, such as annoying customers or depressing sales. While it is true that too much resistance in the purchase journey can easily crowd out the desire to buy, too little resistance dumbs down decision-making and leads to missed opportunities to better connect with customers. The question we suggest that business leaders ask themselves, then, is whether they really want their customers to purchase on autopilot.</p><p> In this article, we explain how a little friction in the buying process can help companies engage customers and offer guidance on how to leverage these effects to build stronger customer relationships.</p><h3> No Pain, No Gain</h3><p> Some friction in the purchase journey can protect consumers from fraud, privacy violations, or their own unintended actions. For example, requiring two-step verification and asking the customer to confirm that they want to complete the purchase are two commonsense inconveniences that ultimately ensure that customers are safeguarded from threats and mistakes.</p><p> But either too much or too little friction around a purchase decision can have negative effects. Having too many steps in the purchase journey can distract shoppers, leaving them without the cognitive bandwidth to carefully consider their decisions. This fuels cart abandonment rates and removes opportunities to engage customers with the company through reviews, referrals, recommendations, or other interactions. Too little friction, and people don&#39;t think enough about their decisions, giving in to the human inclination to economize on mental effort. This absence of friction is numbing, and the less connected shoppers are with a purchase, the more ambivalent they become. That lack of commitment can in turn prompt product returns, weaken brands, and reduce satisfaction in the long run.</p><p> A purchase journey that is sufficiently challenging, however, is engaging. Because the transaction is neither stressful nor straightforward, people have an incentive to invest mental effort in the task. In other words, the right amount of friction can prompt customers to refine and consolidate their preferences and can lead to three benefits for companies.</p><p></p><p> <strong>1. Friction helps sellers select the right customers.</strong> Companies that prioritize the long-term profitability of their customer bases over the immediate gain from making a sale must take a holistic and equally long-term perspective on developing relationships with their target audiences. This involves investing in acquisition, retention, and growth. With that idea in mind, the question is whether hurdles that increase the psychological pain of considering an expense will disproportionately deter would-be customers who are more costly to acquire, less likely to purchase again on future occasions, or less likely to increase their spending on the brand over time or recommend the brand. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Friction to weed out the wrong customers or select the right ones is a familiar technique in luxury goods markets and in any context where a company wants prospective customers to demonstrate commitment. Ferrari, for example, is known for making it difficult to buy special-edition cars. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Similarly, luxury fashion brands don&#39;t mind fostering queues, whether virtual or real, or complicating the purchase process by temporarily withholding prices, lengthening the checkout process, or using other approaches. The simple logic behind these tactics is that only the customers who are most interested in the company&#39;s products or most invested in the brand will find working through these inconveniences and complications acceptable in the shopping journey.</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. When friction enables better decisions, customer satisfaction improves.</strong> Using friction to give consumers a moment to pause and consider the implications of their purchases can forestall buyer&#39;s remorse and encourage shoppers to choose the most appropriate option among the available alternatives.</p><p> Making the trade-off between what the potential buyer will pay and what they will receive sufficiently obvious can help prevent mindless purchasing decisions made in the heat of the moment. For example, social media may pitch “buy now, pay later” financing as a savvy way to buy on a budget, but the ease and convenience of such services, now available in many e-commerce sites&#39; checkout processes, can encourage households to overspend, leading to financial strain and debt accumulation. One survey found that 42% of Americans who took out such a loan made at least one late payment on it. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In addition, research shows that payments made either long before or long after the natural moment of consumption can reduce people&#39;s attention to cost. Proponents of buy now, pay later assert that this “separates the fun experience of buying from the tedious process of paying,” when in fact such “transaction decoupling” has been shown to reduce the likelihood that the consumer will use the item purchased. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> The advantage of avoiding bad decisions is relatively clear from a public policy perspective: Most people would agree that overspending and chronic underutilization of purchased goods are not desirable qualities in a society. But encouraging more thoughtful engagement by customers via friction in the purchase process can pay off for businesses, too.</p><p> One immediate benefit is a drop in return rates. In many sectors, online returns are a considerable drag on financial performance — adding up to as much as 15 to 30 cents per dollar of the price of returned merchandise. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> According to a study by Appriss Retail and the National Retail Federation, close to $220 billion worth of merchandise was returned to US digital retailers in 2021, or approximately 21% of total online sales. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> And this drag, of course, is not just financial — it&#39;s also environmental. Returned products might not be resalable due to wear and tear or other issues and thus end up being sent to landfills or destroyed. According to one report, online returns in the US alone create 5 billion pounds of landfill waste and 15 million tons of carbon emissions annually. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Adding friction also provides customers with time to consider the purchase and become more invested in it. Brands such as Chanel, Louis Vuitton, and Balenciaga delay the communication of prices in a variety of ways — for example, by introducing personalized experiences with salespeople — not only to select better customers, as discussed above, but to put the product center stage and help customers internalize its quality and meaning. Research at the intersection of marketing and neuroscience reports that revealing prices after product information focuses evaluations on attractiveness and desirability (people ask themselves, “Do I like this?”), while doing the opposite focuses evaluations on monetary worth (people ask themselves, “Is it worth it?”). <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> In a Gartner study, B2B and B2C customers agreed that if they “realized something new about their needs or their own goals,” they were 1.73 times more likely to buy more. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p> Using friction to stimulate thinking that results in a decision to purchase can foster a sense of ownership of the product. This can trigger a stronger bond between company and customers and increase customers&#39; willingness to invest additional resources in the relationship. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> As customers put more thought into the purchase decision, they tend to feel more emotionally attached to the product they ultimately choose. And there&#39;s evidence that connecting with customers at the emotional level is a valid route to maximizing customer value. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Finally, research also shows that people tend to value products more when they are obtained through effort — the aptly named “Ikea effect,” in reference to the retailer&#39;s policy of outsourcing the assembly of its furniture to customers. <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> The experience of effort can influence how people perceive the value and quality of a product or service, and adding effort to the online purchase process can trigger this effect.</p><p></p><p> Overall, we see that friction is successful at triggering engagement, and we know that engaged customers are generally more satisfied with their interactions and experiences with brands and retailers. Engaged customers become advocates, increasing visibility and credibility for companies. They are likely to engage in positive word of mouth, which can lead to new-customer acquisition and elevated brand reputation. They are also likely to have better customer service experiences, feel valued by the company, and provide meaningful feedback and suggestions. Such feedback is valuable for understanding evolving customer needs and making the right improvements to products or services over time.</p><p> <strong>3. Friction creates space for companies to communicate with customers.</strong> Retaining some friction exactly when people face prices and payment, especially when this friction is unexpected, gains attention. This is an opportunity for companies to advertise what they stand for and the merits of their offerings.</p><p> There are several ways to use friction for promotion. First, companies can involve customers in the payment process to evoke positive emotions. For example, one common practice is to give customers the option to round up the transaction amount to the next highest dollar, with the difference being donated to charity. Another possibility is to introduce pay-what-you-want campaigns, where customers choose the price they will pay for the product. While these initiatives do not expedite payment (it is surprisingly effortful to consider how much one wants to pay for something), they can lead to greater emotional connections.</p><p> Companies can also express prices in ways that are intentionally unconventional to force customers to think harder about the underlying message. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> For instance, an advertisement from Ikea uses cans of soda to playfully quantify the prices of its products. Of course, the retailer won&#39;t accept soda as payment for furniture. And although it takes a moment of cognitive effort to understand the “exchange rate,” the message that the furniture is as affordable as a number of small-ticket purchases, such as soda, is conveyed to customers.</p><p> Another example is Stella Artois&#39;s award-winning “reassuringly expensive” campaign. The brand attempted to signal the high quality of its beer by introducing the dependency between price and quality into its price communication. Stella upended consumer expectations by playfully offering a coupon that increased the price of the product (“Bring this coupon and pay an extra $1.25 on your next Stella Artois”). By presenting a seemingly confusing and illogical “deal,” it nudged customers to conclude that the product is far superior to that of its competitors (and worth the cost).</p><p> Friction in the payment process can also be used to communicate the brand&#39;s values. For example, in 2014, the relief organization Misereor increased donation rates by deploying interactive screens in locations such as airports that asked passersby to donate 2 euros by swiping their credit cards over the screen. The swipe activated an engaging interactive sequence, such as depicting the credit card slicing a piece of bread to feed the hungry or freeing an imprisoned child.</p><p> Finally, in a bold example of extreme friction, outdoor retailer REI closed its physical stores and stopped processing online payments on Black Friday, the biggest shopping day of the year in the US Its goal was to take a stand against consumerism and encourage would-be shoppers to spend time outdoors instead — a message that underscores the company&#39;s dedication to accessible exploration. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17 号</a></p><h3>The Friction Sweet Spot</h3><p> Better customer selection, consumer decisions, and promotion are three good reasons to abandon the simplistic goal of zero friction. Given the drawbacks of encouraging customers to purchase on autopilot, business leaders should seek to determine the right degree of friction for their companies&#39; purchase processes. In our experience, there are at least five factors to consider. We&#39;ll review them and introduce a scorecard that brings them together and helps to guide decision-making. (See “What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?</h4><p class="caption"> Use this scorecard to help you determine the optimal amount of friction to help you<br /> cultivate enduring customer relationships.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> The first step for every company is to adopt a more accurate definition of what friction is. At the moment, all friction is viewed negatively, which reduces organizations&#39; sense of needing to specify what it actually is. By most accounts, friction is operationalized in terms of time saved. But not all time is created equal. In fact, companies should view negative friction as anything that blocks or distracts customers from the purchase decision, and positive friction as anything that optimizes deliberation.</p><p> The second step is to understand what contexts benefit from positive friction — because this need is not universal. What&#39;s at stake in a particular purchase decision, and does it typically require high or low customer involvement? The two often go together, such that high-stakes decisions also require high involvement, but this is not necessarily the case. For instance, a consumer who is financially secure might not engage more with a purchase decision simply because the item is expensive. And it is exactly when this relation breaks down that you want to step in to proactively manage friction. High-stakes decisions might be such because of the significance of the product or service in question, the scale of the financial outlay, or the personal or social consequences of the purchase. In this spirit, using a technology like Amazon&#39;s Just Walk Out in stadiums might not be good for people who are no longer dissuaded from buying unhealthy snacks by excessively long lines at the concession stand.</p><p> Third, think about your commercial objective. If you care about highlighting cost savings relative to competitors&#39; prices, then, yes — reducing friction by posting your almost-too-good-to-be-true price upfront is worthwhile. However, if you compete on the basis of innovation, quality, or customer service, then perhaps retaining a little friction by delaying when the price is presented is best, because this gets customers to think about and crystallize their preferences. Some friction allows businesses to shift the conversation from “Is it worth it?” to “Do I like it?” And if the goal is to strengthen one&#39;s brand, then adding friction is the right way to go.</p><p> Fourth, consider the makeup of your customer base and the relative closeness of customer relationships. Different customer demographics might require more or less friction, depending on expectations around their understanding of a product or service or their ability to pay. Likewise, relationship stage is important. You might want to include more friction in transactions with new customers versus returning customers, in particular those who might be less familiar with your products or product category. You might want to make it harder for a prospective customer to make a purchase, add a bit of friction for a returning customer, and present a frictionless experience to a loyal customer who fully understands the product or service. A company should maximize enduring relationships with clients — because that is the only path to increase customer value.</p><p> Fifth, think about your choice of route to market. All retail environments could potentially benefit from some friction, but their application will be different. In a brick-and-mortar store, adding pain points that incentivize interaction between a salesperson and the customer might be the right type of friction. In an online store, however, adding steps to foster deliberation can reduce returns and increase subsequent satisfaction with the company. On social media, a company could look to balance content that engages customer interaction and not just click-through rates, thereby helping to dissuade users from mindlessly or impulsively shopping.</p><p></p><p> In fact, for a business selling the same product in brick-and-mortar stores and online, more (positive) friction might be needed in the online or mobile channel, given that product returns tend to be greatest in those channels. One interesting technique that some fashion brands have recently introduced is imposing a fee for online returns. Companies like Anthropologie, H&amp;M, and Zara are charging for returning items online (but not for making in-store returns). <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a> Yes, charging for returns can antagonize some customers. But, again, this point can be key to retaining the most relevant customers and strengthening relationships with those who persist and make a purchase.</p><p></p><p> “How can we make our prices a little less conspicuous and easier to pay?” is among the most common questions asked of user experience teams and experts. But business leaders should embrace the customer moment of truth rather than work to eliminate it. They should not buy into the popular idea that friction is the ultimate conversion killer.</p><p> Without a doubt, when used poorly, friction can derail the customer experience. But a frictionless world is just as dangerous. This is a lesson most of us learned years ago from our high school physics teacher: Too much friction prevents progress toward a goal, but too little friction can throw everything into chaos.</p><p> Indeed, many business leaders are already telling us that they want customers to spend more productive time on their purchase decisions. This sounds like the perfect job for friction. If thinking leads shoppers to make safer, better choices, and in turn these choices impact companies through lower product returns, more sustainable consumer behavior, higher customer satisfaction, and higher loyalty, then let&#39;s all accept and embrace some hassles and hurdles as yet another — albeit surprising — tool at the disposal of customer centricity.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Is Your Organization Investing Enough in Responsible AI? &#39;Probably Not,&#39; Says Our Data</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Priorities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year’s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> For the second year in a row, <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year&#39;s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to respond to this provocation: <em>As the business community becomes more aware of AI&#39;s risks, companies are making adequate investments in RAI.</em></p><p> While their reasons vary, most panelists recognize that RAI investments are falling short of what&#39;s needed: Eleven out of 13 were reluctant to agree that organizations&#39; investments in responsible AI are “adequate.” The panelists largely affirmed findings from our <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/building-robust-rai-programs-as-third-party-ai-tools-proliferate/">2023 RAI global survey</a> , in which less than half of respondents said they believe their company is prepared to make adequate investments in RAI. This is a pressing leadership challenge for companies that are prioritizing AI and must manage AI-related risks.</p><p> The need to expand investments in RAI marks a significant shift now that “AI-related risks are impossible to ignore,” observes Linda Leopold, head of responsible AI and data at H&amp;M Group. While making adequate investments in RAI used to be an important but not particularly urgent issue, Leopold suggests that recent advances in generative AI and the proliferation of third-party tools have made the urgency of such investments clear.</p><p> Making adequate investments in RAI is complicated by measurement challenges. There are no industry standards that offer guidance, so how do you know when or if your investments are sufficient? What&#39;s more, rational executives can have different opinions about what constitutes an adequate investment. What&#39;s clear is that epistemic questions should not be a barrier to action, especially when AI risks pose real business threats.</p><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3> The Panelists Respond</p></h3><h2> It is unclear if organizations are making appropriate investments in RAI.</p></h2><p> Most panelists are reluctant to agree that organizations are making “adequate” investments in RAI.</p><p> <a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">Jump to panelists&#39; detailed responses below.</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-Chart.jpg" alt="Chart: 0 strongly agree; 15% agree, 46% neither agree nor disagree; 39% disagree; 0% strongly disagree"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source"> Source: Responsible AI panel of 13 experts in artificial intelligence strategy. </p></p></div><p><path id="Path" d="M0,0,14.067,15.065,28.941,0" transform="translate(1.096 1.054)" fill="none" stroke="#fff" stroke-miterlimit="10" stroke-width="3" /> <a href="" class="callout-chart-add__button"><span class="callout-chart-add__button-text"><strong>Show</strong> Global Survey Results</span></a> </p><div class="callout-chart-add"><div class="callout-chart-add__container"><div class="callout-chart-add__info"><h4></h4><h3> Responses from the 2023 Global Executive Survey<br /></h3><p> “To what extent do you believe that your organization is prepared to invest (reduce revenue, increase costs) to comply with responsible AI initiatives?” </p></p></div><div class="callout-chart-add__chart"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-survey.jpg" alt="Bar chart: To a moderate or great extent: 48%; To some extent: 29%; To a minor extent: 8%; Not at all: 3%; Don't know: 12%" class="mt0"></p><p class="callout-chart-add__source"> Source: Survey data of 1,240 respondents representing organizations reporting at least $100 million in annual revenues. These respondents represented companies in 59 industries and 87 countries. The survey fielded in China was localized.</p></p></div></p></div></p></div></div><h3> Companies Are Investing in RAI, but Not Enough</h3><p> Panelists offered several reasons why companies aren&#39;t making adequate investments in responsible AI. Several panelists suggested that profit motives are a factor. Tshilidzi Marwala, rector of the United Nations University and UN undersecretary general, contends that only “20% of the companies aware of AI risks are investing in RAI programs. The rest are more concerned about how they can use AI to maximize their profits.” Simon Chesterman, the David Marshall Professor and vice provost at the National University of Singapore, adds, “The gold rush around generative AI has led to a downsizing of safety and security teams in tech companies, and a shortened path to market for new products. … Fear of missing out is triumphing — in many organizations, if not all — over risk management.”</p><p> Another reason behind underinvestment is that greater use of AI throughout an enterprise expands the scope of RAI and increases required investments. As Philip Dawson, head of AI policy at Armilla AI, observes, “Investment in AI capabilities continues to vastly outstrip investment in AI safety and tools to operationalize AI risk management. Enterprises are playing catch-up in an uphill battle that is only getting steeper.” Leopold adds that generative AI and an increasing number of possible applications “significantly increases the size of the audience that responsible AI programs have to reach.”</p><p></p><p> A third reason is that growing awareness of AI risks does not always translate into accurate assessments of those risks. Oarabile Mudongo, a policy specialist at the African Observatory on Responsible AI, suggests that some companies might not be investing enough in their RAI programs because they “underestimate the extent of AI risks.”</p><h3> How Do You Know Whether You&#39;re Investing Enough?</h3><p> Other panelists pointed out that although making adequate investments in RAI is important, it&#39;s hard to gauge whether the investment is large enough or effective. How should companies calculate a return on RAI investments? What counts as an “adequate” return? What even counts as an investment? David R. Hardoon, CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation and chief data and AI officer of Union Bank of the Philippines, asks, “How can the investments in RAI be broadly, and generally, considered adequate if (1) all companies are not subjected to the same levels of standards, (2) we have yet to agree on what is &#39;sufficient&#39; or &#39;acceptable,&#39; or (3) we don&#39;t have a mechanism to verify third parties?”</p><p> Triveni Gandhi, responsible AI lead at Dataiku, agrees: “Among those companies that have taken the time to invest in RAI programs, there is wide variation in how these programs are actually designed and implemented. The lack of cohesive or clear expectations on how to implement or operationalize RAI values makes it difficult for organizations to start investing efficiently.”</p><p> “It is difficult to determine the extent to which companies are making adequate investments in responsible AI programs, as there is a large spectrum of awareness and relevance,” asserts Giuseppe Manai, cofounder, chief operating officer, and chief scientist at Stemly. Aisha Naseer, director of research at Huawei Technologies (UK), adds, “It is not evident whether these investments are adequate or enough, as these range from trivial to huge funds being allocated for the control of AI and associated risk mitigation.”</p><p></p><h3>建议</h3><p>For organizations seeking to adequately invest in RAI, we recommend the following:</p><p> <strong>1. Build leadership awareness of AI risks.</strong> Leaders need to be aware that using AI is a double-edged sword that introduces risks as well as benefits. Focusing on investments that increase the benefits of AI without a commensurate focus on managing its risks undermines value creation in two ways. One is that without appropriate guardrails, the benefits from AI might be underwhelming: Our research has found that innovation with AI increases when RAI practices are in place. Second, risks from AI are proliferating as quickly as the tools they are embedded in. A robust awareness of AI&#39;s risks and benefits supports leadership efforts to manage risks and grow the company. Building management awareness can take many forms, including executive education, discussion forums, and RAI programs that have a variety of stakeholders with different types of exposure to (and experience with) AI risks.</p><p> <strong>2. Accept that investing in RAI will be an ongoing process.</strong> As AI development and use increase — with no foreseeable end — RAI practices and implementations need to adapt as well. That requires ongoing RAI investment to continually evolve an RAI program. With the regulatory landscape poised for change in the European Union, the US, and Asia, leaders will face growing pressure to evolve their AI-focused risk management systems. Waiting to invest (or halting investment) in these systems — technologically, culturally, and financially — can undermine business growth. When new regulations and industry standards take effect, rapidly overhauling processes to meet compliance requirements can interfere with AI-related innovation. It&#39;s better to co-evolve RAI programs with AI development so they complement each other rather than create this unnecessary interference. As companies scale their AI investments, so, too, will their RAI investments need to grow. But those companies that are already behind will need to move quickly and invest aggressively in RAI to avoid always lagging behind.</p><p> <strong>3. Develop RAI investment metrics.</strong> Investing in RAI is complex — and what does a return on such an investment even look like? Much like with cybersecurity investments, the best RAI returns might be the sound of silence when AI-related issues are discovered before they create damage to brand reputation, regulatory issues, and increased costs. That said, silence should not be mistaken for adequate investment. As our survey results show, companies making minimal investment might not find issues simply because they aren&#39;t looking for them. Leaders should align on what constitutes an RAI investment, the appropriate metrics to evaluate these investments, and who will decide on investment levels. Metrics that gauge RAI program success are necessary to support RAI programs over time, but they can be a lagging indicator. Metrics should also evaluate forward-looking dimensions such as leadership commitment, program adoption, training and workforce needs, and culture change. Leaders must also determine how RAI funding is related to funding for AI projects. Should every large AI project have a budget set aside for RAI? Or should RAI funding be independent of specific projects or some combination of project-based (decentralized) and institutional (centralized) investments?</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Real Issues Driving the Nursing Crisis</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jack Daly</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><p> We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research on various elements of employees&#39; experiences, including culture, compensation and benefits, work schedules, and perceived organizational support. We clustered related topics together into two dozen broader themes.</p><p> We used the topics as features in an XGBoost model that predicted each nurse&#39;s overall rating of their current or former employer on a 5-point scale. We then calculated SHAP values (which assign an importance value to each feature in a model) to directly compare the relative importance of different topics in predicting job satisfaction (measured by the overall rating each nurse gave their employer). We also used textual analysis to compare how favorably travel nurses spoke about topics compared with nurses on staff at health care systems.</p><p> Using the topics nurses mentioned and their sentiment toward each topic as predictors, our models explain between 29% and 39% of the variance in ratings across nurses — nearly an order of magnitude more than we could account for using ownership, organizational type, and location as predictors. <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a></p></aside><p> Health care leaders face a daunting set of challenges — rising costs, the transition to digital health, and shifting payment models, to name just a few. But according to a recent survey from the American College of Healthcare Executives, the No. 1 problem hospital CEOs face is staff shortages and burnout. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Ninety percent of the CEOs surveyed cited nursing shortages as a particularly acute pain point.</p><p> In 2021, the total number of registered nurses working in the US dropped by the largest amount in 40 years, with younger nurses leading the exodus. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> By 2025, the US health care system could suffer a shortfall of up to 450,000 nurses, or 20% fewer than the nursing workforce required for patient care. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p> High levels of job dissatisfaction and burnout are driving nurses from the profession. The COVID-19 pandemic placed tremendous pressure on all health care workers, but dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses have not improved since the pandemic ended. And by some measures, it might be getting worse: In 2021, nearly two-thirds of registered nurses would have encouraged others to become a nurse, but only half said they would recommend nursing as a profession two years later. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> One of the richest sources of insight on dissatisfaction among nurses is how they describe their job, in their own words, on employment sites like Indeed and Glassdoor. This information is voluminous but difficult to synthesize because most of it takes the form of unstructured free text. To understand the challenges nurses face, we analyzed how 150,000 of them had described their employers in Glassdoor reviews since the beginning of the pandemic. (See “The Research.”) In this article, we share key insights from that analysis and offer advice to health care leaders about how they can address nurses&#39; most pressing issues.</p><h3> Health Care Leaders Are Out of Touch</h3><p> Nurses view their managers as out of touch with the daily realities of patient care. We categorized their comments about managers into nearly 50 leadership traits. The second most frequently cited trait described managers as being unaware of the challenges that nurses struggle with in the workplace. When nurses discussed how managers understood life at the bedside, their comments were negative 9 times out of 10.</p><p></p><p> Nurses are particularly critical of members of the senior executive team for their disconnectedness. The top team was 10 times more likely than front-line supervisors and middle managers to be criticized for being out of touch. Our results reinforce a separate survey in which nearly half of hospital nurses said they believe management does not listen to their concerns. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> To address dissatisfaction and burnout, health care leaders must first understand what&#39;s happening at the bedside. This can be challenging, particularly in large health care systems with thousands of nurses working across multiple sites and specialties.</p><p> Historically, leaders have struggled to systematically analyze the gold mine of insights into nurses&#39; frustrations that can be gleaned from their comments in employee surveys or external reviews. Reading, understanding, and analyzing huge volumes of unstructured textual data has simply not been practical. However, recent advances in artificial intelligence make it possible to identify deep patterns in large bodies of text and understand feedback at scale. Leaders can now mine free text to gain a nuanced understanding of the issues driving dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses and use that insight to improve life at work for their nursing staffs. (See “Getting Started With Text Analytics.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Getting Started With Text Analytics</h4><p> Our research analyzes data from hundreds of organizations and hundreds of thousands of nurses, but you can delve more deeply into your own employees&#39; feedback as well. Regardless of whether you develop AI text analytics capabilities internally, through a workforce analytics function, or with an external partner, you should keep these principles in mind to maximize the effectiveness of the cultural measurement.</p><p> <strong>Precision matters, but so does recall.</strong> Precision — the percentage of text instances that are correctly classified as discussing a topic — is a critical element of free text analysis. So is recall — the percentage of total mentions of the topic in a body of text that are captured by your text analytics platform. If you gauge success solely through precision, you will end up with an analytical platform that is highly accurate but misses most of what employees actually say. A sophisticated AI tool will pick up on slang, idioms, acronyms, cultural references, and organization-specific language to capture the long tail of seldom-mentioned but information-rich terms.</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p> <strong>Keep subject matter experts in the loop.</strong> The heart of text analytics is classifying natural language into meaningful topics. Ideally, the people measuring culture will engage subject matter experts when developing topics for analysis. Subject matter experts can ensure that the cultural and workplace topics selected are clearly defined, linked to existing research, and properly measured.</p><p> <strong>Likert questions have severe drawbacks but, used in moderation, can be very helpful.</strong> Too many Likert-scale questions can lead survey takers to shift into autopilot mode. But Likert questions should not be thrown out altogether. Effective cultural measurement combines Likert-scale outcomes on broad topics (such as engagement, attrition intent, and other important measures) with free-text data to identify which, out of hundreds of free-text topics, have the most powerful impact on outcomes.</p><p> <strong>Transparency matters and will probably matter more going forward.</strong> While it remains to be seen how AI will be regulated, it is likely that legislators or courts will not look kindly on important decisions being made by black-box models with no explanation of how the models are reaching their conclusions. Leaders often rely on culture measurement to make important decisions such as compensation policies, personnel changes, and how to prioritize resources. They should be wary of relying exclusively on models that make decisions that humans cannot understand.</p><p> <strong>Employees hate it when you spy on them — and you won&#39;t learn much about culture.</strong> Leaders should resist the temptation to expand their text analytics efforts to the content of emails, Slack channels, phone messages, and other forms of communication that were not designed to provide employee feedback. Many employees consider listening to their work conversations eavesdropping or worse. Moreover, work emails and Slack messages tend to contain far less cultural information than question prompts that explicitly invite employees to discuss what is working and not working in their organization. Keep employee listening consensual, and keep Big Brother out of the workplace.</p></div></article></aside></div><h3> Identify Relative Strengths and Opportunities Through Benchmarking</h3><p> Nursing satisfaction varies widely across employers. We identified 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies. For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic through June 2023. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> Among large employers, nurses&#39; Glassdoor ratings ran the gamut from poor (2.6) to nearly perfect (4.9) on a 5-point scale. Nurses&#39; assessments of how well senior leadership has performed during and after the pandemic were even more varied, ranging from 2.1 to 4.9 on the same 5-point scale. The wide variance in Glassdoor ratings is consistent with a separate survey in which the percentage of dissatisfied nurses ranged from 2% to 48% across 60 US hospitals. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Employees of the 200 large health care organizations can use our <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">interactive tool</a> to see how their organization ranks against others. The index is sortable by nurses&#39; overall ratings, their assessments of the top leadership, and the four most powerful predictors of nurses&#39; satisfaction: compensation, workload, organizational support, and toxic culture. </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4> How Do Nurses Rate Their Employers?</h4><p class="caption"> Use the Nursing Satisfaction Index to compare how nurses evaluated the employee experience at 200 large health care organizations.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> Nurses who work for staffing agencies (who are sometimes referred to as travel nurses) are, on average, much more satisfied than other nurses. The five highest-ranked employers in our sample (and six of the top 10) are staffing agencies.</p><p> Higher compensation, of course, accounts for part of this difference, but not all of it. We compared how positively nurses working with staffing agencies spoke about 200 topics compared with their counterparts employed by hospitals and health care systems. (See “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors.”) While compensation was viewed more favorably by agency nurses, issues around solving nurses&#39; problems and open, honest communication had a larger sentiment gap between the two groups. By focusing on nurses as clients, staffing agencies excel at practices that improve satisfaction beyond simply paying higher wages. Other health care leaders can learn from their example, and we&#39;ll make some concrete recommendations below.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors</h4><p class="caption"> We analyzed the free text of US Glassdoor reviews by nurses from the start of the pandemic to June 2023 to see how positively they spoke about a variety of topics. We then compared the positive sentiments of nurses working with staffing agencies to those of nurses working in hospitals and health care systems. While staffing agencies rate higher on many key topics — including honest communication, resolving issues efficiently, and building trust — hospitals and health care systems are stronger when it comes to learning and development, benefits, colleagues, and opportunities for promotion. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3> Prioritize Drivers of Job Satisfaction</h3><p> To understand the drivers of job satisfaction among nurses, we analyzed the free text of all reviews that had been written by the nurses in our sample since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into nearly 200 topics. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> We then clustered topics into two dozen broader themes and used those themes to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers. We then compared each theme&#39;s relative importance in predicting ratings. (See “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction.”)</p><p></p><p> Compensation was the top predictor of satisfaction among nurses reviewing their current employer, which is not surprising, given that inflation eroded the purchasing power of take-home pay during the period we analyzed. The importance of workload, the second-most-important driver, jibes with findings from a separate large-scale survey that found insufficient staffing was the strongest predictor of nurses&#39; job dissatisfaction, burnout, and intent to quit. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Workload and compensation are root causes of the nursing crisis that must be addressed, but they are not the only factors influencing nurses&#39; job satisfaction. Our analysis surfaced other aspects of the work environment, including toxic culture, organizational support, work schedules, communication, and learning and development opportunities, that leaders can focus on to improve nurses&#39; work lives.</p><p> This analysis also highlights areas that are unlikely to move the needle in improving the workplace experience for nurses. Perks are nice, but they will not compensate for a punishing workload or wages that fail to keep pace with inflation. Highlighting the corporate mission to promote patient health won&#39;t help much either. Nurses already know that their job serves a higher purpose; that&#39;s why most of them became nurses in the first place.</p><h3> Mine Free Text for Actionable Insights</h3><p> Many health care organizations rely on annual employee surveys, with dozens of items rated on a 5-point scale and a few open-ended questions tacked on as an afterthought. Faced with a long list of multiple-choice questions, employees are prone to switching to autopilot and assigning similar scores to very different items. The choice of questions constrains what employees can discuss, and there is seldom room to expand on why they chose a particular numeric response.</p><p> Open-ended, free-text feedback provides a rich source of nuanced and actionable insights. When nurses can decide which topics to write about, they use their freedom to discuss what matters most to them. Open-ended questions provide nurses with the space to expand on their concerns in their own words, offer crucial context, and propose concrete and actionable fixes to the problems they face. Individual free-text responses can be aggregated into broader themes to prioritize where leaders could focus their attention and limited resources to achieve the largest improvements in nurses&#39; satisfaction.</p><p> While organizational averages are useful, it is important to remember that distinctive subcultures can coexist within the same organization. This is particularly true among large health care systems that have grown through mergers and acquisitions. One national hospital chain, for example, has ratings that range from 1.9 to 3.9 across nearly 50 sites. Rather than relying on organizational averages alone, health care leaders must measure and analyze differences across locations, departments, functions, teams, and individual leaders.</p><p> Women, underrepresented minorities, and older employees can also experience organizational culture very differently from other employees. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> It&#39;s crucial to understand the drivers of job satisfaction and burnout across diverse employee populations.</p><p></p><p> Leaders can mine the free text for detailed insights about the most critical pain points for specific groups and tailor their interventions accordingly. Schedules, for example, have a significant impact on nurses&#39; job satisfaction, but which aspects of scheduling matter most will depend on the specific position. Flexibility in scheduling shifts and the ability to take uninterrupted work breaks is very important for nurses in hospitals and primary care practices, while home health care nurses place a premium on predictable schedules. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Nurses&#39; comments provide a treasure trove of practical suggestions to improve the workplace and patient care. The Glassdoor reviews we studied, for example, include dozens of actionable suggestions for how employers can improve scheduling. Some are easy-to-implement actions, such as using an app to make it easier to pick up or swap shifts, or paying a $20 to $50 bonus to nurses who pick up shifts at the last minute. Others are more systemic changes, like including nurses on a committee established to set schedules or ensuring that employees who receive tuition assistance are able to schedule work around their classes.</p><h3> Listen to Nurses Who Leave Your Organization</h3><p> Most organizations limit their surveys to current employees. Exit interviews are administered haphazardly, if at all, and the feedback from former employees is too often dismissed as the rantings of malcontents. But ignoring feedback from former employees is a big mistake. </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> Interviewing or surveying former employees can surface the reasons for their departure and pinpoint the most effective actions to retain talent. Free of the threat of retaliation, nurses who are leaving (or have left) an organization are more likely to provide candid feedback, even about taboo issues that current employees are reluctant to discuss. By collecting feedback from those who have left, organizations can uncover potential blind spots.</p><p> More than one-third of the Glassdoor reviews in our sample were written by former employees and provide insights on what mattered most to nurses who voted with their feet. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> The bars on the left side of the figure “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction” rank the factors that predict how nurses who quit rank their former employers, and it sheds light on a critical reason nurses might head for the exits.</p><p> In an <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">earlier article</a> , we argued that five behavioral attributes — disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive — mark an organizational culture as toxic. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> Among nurses who quit, toxic culture is more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction than compensation or workload. The importance of toxic workplaces among nurses who quit is consistent with earlier research that found toxicity to be the strongest predictor of industry-adjusted attrition during the first six months of the Great Resignation. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Toxic culture has become more important for nurses in the post-pandemic era. When we compared which factors best predict how nurses rated their employer before and after the pandemic, toxic culture experienced the largest gain in relative importance post-COVID-19 (followed by workload, well-being, and compensation). If your organization suffers from cultural toxicity, another article of ours, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">How to Fix a Toxic Culture</a> ,” presents several evidence-based interventions health care leaders can use to detox their own organization.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction</h4><p class="caption"> We classified the text of over 150,000 nurses&#39; Glassdoor reviews into two dozen themes that affect the employee experience, and we then analyzed which themes best predict how nurses rate their employer. The chart ranks the importance of each theme in predicting these ratings by showing how much each theme contributes to the overall prediction. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses’ Job Satisfaction" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3> Learn From Staffing Agency Practices</h3><p> As the figure “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors” shows, nurses are very positive about the processes staffing agencies have in place to resolve problems quickly and efficiently. Of nurses who mentioned the efficiency of staffing agencies&#39; processes, 75% were positive, compared with 23% expressing positive sentiment for health care systems. For travel nurses, common process issues include onboarding, obtaining required credentials and licenses, contract negotiation, and reimbursement. The best staffing agencies listen to feedback, develop a deep understanding of the typical problems travel nurses face, and optimize their work processes to address these issues.</p><p> Many of the pain points encountered by staff nurses will differ from those of agency nurses. Health care systems, home health agencies, and long-term care providers could, however, adopt a similar approach to capture and analyze nurses&#39; feedback, prioritize the most common and frustrating challenges they face, and work with staff members to address these issues.</p><p> Consistently listening to and acting on feedback can also build trust with the nursing staff. Staffing agency nurses are more positive about having the psychological safety to speak up about difficult issues and be heard than are nurses working in hospitals and health care systems.</p><p> The benefits of psychological safety are blunted, however, if management is slow to respond to issues that nurses raise. Nurses speak highly of how quickly staffing agencies respond to their questions and concerns. In contrast, nurses frequently complain that other types of employers are slow to respond to emails raising issues, if they get a reply at all. Nurses also place a high value on having multiple channels of communication with their supervisors, including text, email, Facebook, Jabber, and a 24/7 hotline.</p><p> Another insight from our research is that nurses value honesty and transparency. They understand the challenges health care faces as well as anyone, and they expect honest communication about what is happening in the organization, how it affects them, and why decisions were made. Triage, a staffing agency and the fourth most highly rated large employer we studied, places honest communication at the center of its value proposition: “We tell it like it is so you won&#39;t be surprised by how it goes.” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p> Health care systems can learn from staffing agencies, but they can also leverage their own distinctive advantages to attract and retain nurses. Nurses in full-time staff positions rate hospitals and health care systems higher than staffing agencies on three important aspects of organizational life: learning and development (including promotion opportunities and reimbursement for training), benefits, and colleagues. Those three factors are among the top 10 predictors of how nurses rate their employers. Health care systems should invest in their comparative advantages and emphasize them when communicating their value proposition to potential and current employees.</p><p></p><h3> Translate Feedback Into Action to Build Trust</h3><p> It&#39;s one thing to collect employee feedback, but it&#39;s another to consistently act on those insights. Employees are less likely to surface issues or propose potential solutions if they believe that managers will not act. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Worse yet, employees are more likely to quit if they believe that management lacks the power, resources, or interest to make changes based on their suggestions. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Nearly half of nurses believe that management will not fix problems that clinical staff members bring to their attention. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p> Organizations need to put in place structures to consistently act on employee feedback. One well-known example is Kaiser Permanente&#39;s unit-based teams (UBTs), which consist of clinical staff members and managers who regularly work together in a specific unit or department. <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a> The teams, which meet at least once per month, are responsible for their unit&#39;s performance and are co-led by a manager, a labor representative, and, typically, a clinical staff member.</p><p> The UBTs identify opportunities to improve along four dimensions: quality (including patient outcomes), patient service, affordability, and employee experience. The teams use employee feedback to identify and prioritize improvement opportunities. Next, the teams develop and test solutions using best practices and evidence-based methods. Once a solution has been deemed effective, it is implemented across the unit, department, or, in some cases, the entire organization. The UBTs then monitor the impact of these changes in terms of patient outcomes, employee satisfaction, and cost reduction.</p><p></p><p> Our study of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses since the onset of COVID-19 reveals wide variation in how nurses rate their employers as a whole, and specifically in terms of compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support — the four factors that most shape nurses&#39; job satisfaction. In our view, this variation offers a message of hope. Despite the structural challenges that all health care organizations face, it <em>is</em> possible to provide an environment where nurses look forward to going to work every day.</p><p> Many organizations, including some of the largest employers of nurses, have significant room for improvement. These rankings are not designed to “name and shame” but rather to make health care leaders aware of the magnitude of the gap between their organization&#39;s performance and what is possible when it comes to providing a healthy workplace for nurses. We also hope that the objective data on how health care organizations rank on factors that matter most to nurses can provide their leaders with the impetus to make improvements and the evidence to convince all stakeholders of the urgent need for change.</p><p></p><p> What leaders should not do is ask nurses to work harder and endure more frustration and stress while failing to understand and address the organizational factors that make life miserable for many of them. Leaders who continue business as usual should not be surprised when staff members quit, workers unionize, and state and federal legislators dictate regulations to protect the interests of nurses.</p><p> To improve the work lives of nurses, and indeed all health care workers, leaders must collect and act on their feedback, recognizing that different parts of the organization and different populations will face distinctive challenges and issues. Listening to nurses demonstrates that there are meaningful steps health care leaders can take to fix the nursing crisis. The single most important step is to listen to them in the first place.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Explore How Nurses Rate Their Employers</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses&#39; own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by US nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers.</p><p> We calculated the relative importance of each theme in predicting nurses&#39; overall satisfaction. Four factors — toxic culture, organizational support, compensation, and workload — emerged as the strongest predictors of how satisfied nurses were with their employer.</p><p></p><p> One significant finding for health care leaders: Among nurses who had quit, toxic culture was more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction compared with compensation or workload.</p><p> Nurses&#39; job satisfaction varies widely among employers. Our interactive Nursing Satisfaction Index shows how nurses evaluate the employee experience at 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies.</p><p> For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. We also report on how positively or negatively nurses spoke about compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support. Each employer&#39;s score on all dimensions is expressed as standard deviations above/(below) the average for all 200 employers.</p><p> <a href="#interactive-launcher">Explore the index above</a> .</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Health Care Leaders Need to Know to Fight the Nursing Shortage: Nurses Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read is multimedia editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What&#39;s driving that burnout? What&#39;s most important to a nurse&#39;s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this video, we talk to five current and former nurses to learn about the reality of working in health care, including the toxic cultures and stressors they&#39;ve experienced, and get advice from them and health care experts on what needs to change.</p><p> Article author and researcher Donald Sull also discusses the truths about job satisfaction revealed by the analysis of 150,000 employer reviews by nurses on job site Glassdoor, and what health care leaders can learn from them.</p><p></p><p> “The key, actionable finding from our research is, nurses are telling you what&#39;s not working for them, often in very granular detail, and they&#39;re offering concrete recommendations to address these issues. They want to help. They want their voices heard, and they want to make a positive impact,” Sull says.</p><p> “One of the most difficult or frustrating things about being a nurse is really not having enough time to spend with the patient,” says Jennie Evans, who served as a pediatric oncology and ICU RN for 18 years. “Those moments where you can sit, talk with the patient, hold their hand, talk with the family, and really get to know them and understand not just the disease but other underlying anxieties or fears that the patient might have.”</p><p> Watch the video to hear more from nurses on what they want health care leaders to know about toxic cultures, mental health, growth opportunities, and other issues that are critical to caregivers.</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Upgrading Culture for Growth and Transformation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander is a strategic adviser and professor of practice at Hult International Business School. His work on decision-making, problem-solving, and culture has been published in <em>Harvard Business Review</em> , <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , and <em>Knowledge at Wharton</em> . Per shares his thoughts and ideas on his blog <a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">leadershipbackbone.com</a> . Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> P. Hugander, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , May 22, 2023.</p></aside><p> Many leaders know that their organization&#39;s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don&#39;t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and growth. But despite ambitious efforts to infuse such skills into their culture, many organizations fail. The secret to success: Shorten the time to reward when people experience the new skills helping teams beat longtime challenges.</p><p> Per Hugander has helped leaders at organizations including Swedish financial services group SEB make progress on complex strategic challenges. His practical approach helps people to link psychological safety to tangible business results.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why many organizations fail at culture change: Just testing the waters can be dangerous.</li><li> How to go deep — not wide — on culture change and win over skeptics.</li><li> How to put the new skills to use quickly on the organization&#39;s toughest problems and create lasting culture benefits.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Steps to Build and Sustain Diversity in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> , Ed.D., is a managing partner and the US practice leader of CEO and Board Services at Boyden, a global executive search firm. He built his career as a turnaround (glass cliff) specialist in corporate America and writes on issues related to diversity, governance, and strategic growth for private and public corporations and boards.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; however, less attention is paid to what happens after the hire. Only when we effectively create a more equitable landscape and support women and people of color in navigating it can we benefit from the full engagement and contributions of all of our people and avoid losing them to turnover or disengagement.</p><p> Occupational minorities — those individuals who are <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">relative rarities</a> in their profession due to their gender or sexual identity, ethnicity, age, or other factors — have accomplished what countless more have only dreamed of: They have broken through the glass ceiling, navigated the often inhospitable <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">corporate jungle</a> , and often successfully negotiated the <a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">glass cliff</a> . Although the executives who represent diverse populations in your organization have successfully overcome these challenges, an important task remains: building a path for others to follow. This is hard, painstaking work that requires many different tools and competencies, yet it is necessary if others are to safely navigate the landscape.</p><p></p><h3> Steps to Sustaining Diversity</h3><p> Although various resources offer suggestions for how professionals from underrepresented populations can navigate and overcome organizational challenges, it is equally essential that organizations identify where <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">persistent systemic bias and racism</a> lurk and take concrete action to address them. Organizations can take the following five steps to begin the process of creating more inclusive environments where all employees have equal opportunities to thrive and advance in their careers.</p><h4> Step 1: Establish leadership commitment to diversity with sponsorship.</h4><p> Leadership throughout the organization must demonstrate a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion. When leaders model these behaviors, employees throughout the organization naturally follow their example. However, this commitment cannot be limited to one-off efforts or statements on corporate values.</p><p> Leaders must consciously exhibit their commitment to hiring people from underrepresented populations by helping to develop and equip these candidates for advancement. Specifically, every leader, regardless of organizational level, should identify at least one such candidate to intentionally sponsor. After getting to know the candidate&#39;s background, career goals, and support needs, the leader should (1) counsel them in navigating the organization, (2) support them in developing the competencies needed to advance in their career, and, critically, (3) help them secure progressive leadership positions.</p><p></p><p> Although formal mentoring, sponsorship, and buddy programs can be helpful in this effort, relationships that develop informally often are equally, if not more, rewarding and beneficial and tend to continue long after one or both individuals have advanced in or moved out of the organization.</p><h4> Step 2: Remove glass ceilings by addressing systemic factors.</h4><p> The metaphor of the glass ceiling depicts the systems of discrimination that prevent certain groups of people (typically women and people of color) from accessing high-level opportunities for career growth and advancement. Clues that glass ceilings exist within your organization include a lack of diversity within the upper-management and executive ranks compared with your overall workforce; pay disparities between individuals with similar roles and qualifications; limited mentorship, sponsorship, development, or advancement for certain groups of people; explicit or implicit biases regarding which groups are a better fit for leadership roles than others; and attrition levels within underrepresented groups that exceed those of other groups.</p><p> To identify and eradicate glass ceilings in your organization, closely scrutinize every aspect of the employee experience. For example, address biased hiring and promotion practices using blind recruitment techniques; review salary ranges and promotion criteria to ensure that equal pay is awarded for equal work; and make clear career paths and development opportunities available to all employees. Diversity goals, inclusion initiatives, and employee education on recognizing and avoiding unconscious biases also can support a diversity-conducive climate. Supporting flexible work arrangements and work-life balance can encourage the full participation of employees who might otherwise be overlooked due to their needs to balance personal and professional responsibilities.</p><p></p><h4> Step 3: Reduce glass cliffs through due diligence.</h4><p> The term <em>glass cliff</em> describes a phenomenon in which women and other minorities are preferentially selected for leadership positions in times of crisis, placing them at increased risk for failure. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This phenomenon occurs across industries and geographies, and for women and ethnic minorities alike. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The problem with giving people from underrepresented populations leadership opportunities only in times of crisis is that those who lead during turbulent times tend to be seen as part of the problem, which perpetuates stereotypes and reduces future opportunities for such candidates. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> To avoid this outcome, care must be taken to recognize and fully examine the situation before assigning a leader to address it. While the temptation to dive in and do something to “stop the bleeding” is overwhelming, taking the appropriate time to first fully understand the problem is a small price to pay for a much-improved chance of success. The diagnosis process should include identifying project parameters (such as performance targets, deadlines, and budget), project stakeholders, past actions taken, the current situation, and desired outcomes — from the perspectives of all stakeholders. My article on the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">glass cliff phenomenon</a> provides more details on the process of due diligence and the questions that can be used to diagnose these situations. Only after diagnosing the problem will it be possible to select the most appropriate candidate to lead the effort.</p><h4> Step 4: Broaden the pathway by changing the conversation.</h4><p> Corporate environments can be fraught with challenges for women and people of color. Many challenges are systemic, such as organizational cultures that <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">disadvantage certain groups</a> versus others, or workloads and behavioral expectations that require long hours in the office and around-the-clock responsiveness. These systemic challenges can make the corporate landscape seem foreign and antagonistic. In turn, occupational minorities might compensate by nursing cognitive biases that result in too much or too little confidence; limiting their social networks to similar peers rather than nurturing<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">vital connections</a> to sponsors, mentors, and career guides; and failing to strike an appropriate work-life balance.</p><p> Although leaders must deliberately sponsor occupational minorities (Step 1), mentors, sponsors, and allies throughout the organization also play important roles in guiding candidates toward success because they, too, have already successfully navigated the organization. Supporting emerging leaders means changing the typical mentoring conversation. Typical conversations involve identifying a mentee&#39;s short- and long-term goals and seeking the mentor&#39;s situational advice, guidance on skill development, and feedback on performance. Mentoring that supports diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging should be adapted to include a clear framework for professional development, an explanation of how various opportunities and positions contribute to the candidate&#39;s career goals, and a discussion of how to navigate the organizational culture — all in light of the glass ceilings, glass cliffs, and systemic challenges they face as occupational minorities.</p><p> Cognitive biases also should be part of the conversation so that candidates can avoid the traps of both being overconfident and overcompensating for perceived shortcomings. Evaluation and adjustment of cognitive biases might be best accomplished by gathering 360-degree feedback regarding the mentee&#39;s performance on key tasks and engaging the mentee to describe their feelings, thoughts, and general experiences related to performing those tasks. Overconfidence might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is at or below average while their own experience of that task reflects strong enthusiasm, satisfaction, and a sense of achievement. In contrast, overcompensation might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is evaluated as or above average yet their described experiences suggest that they are spending too much time on tasks or that they harbor concerns about their performance.</p><h4> Step 5: Measure and track progress.</h4><p> A popular business adage is that we must inspect what we expect. This truism applies equally to any diversity effort. The process begins with defining what success looks like according to key diversity metrics such as hiring, retention, and advancement for various employee populations. It might be tempting to stop there; however, defining the goal is only the beginning. Additionally, it is necessary to measure the organization&#39;s current performance on these KPIs and then examine why that is the current state. Understanding the organization&#39;s current performance requires the following assessments:</p><p> <strong>1. Gauge buy-in.</strong> To what extent do organizational leaders and members understand and agree that the KPIs defined are the right indicators and performance targets?</p><p> <strong>2. Gauge feasibility.</strong> What organizational structures, processes, and other features facilitate the achievement of the KPI? What features threaten or obstruct achievement?</p><p> <strong>3. Gauge support needs.</strong> Leaders are taught to adapt to the needs of individual subordinates based on each person&#39;s skill level. In the same way, leaders throughout the organization need to adjust the amount of oversight, encouragement, and direction they provide as departments and employees across skill levels work to achieve diversity goals. For example, a recruiting department that is relatively inexperienced at hiring professionals from underrepresented groups will need strong, step-by-step guidance and frequent feedback until their competency grows, while a manager who is highly skilled at developing and including such professionals generally should be allowed the autonomy to exercise their talents to their fullest.</p><p></p><p> As initiatives are implemented, continue to regularly assess these metrics to gauge your progress and fine-tune your efforts. As the saying goes, “What gets measured gets done.” Achievement of your diversity goals will happen only if they are deliberately defined and regularly assessed.</p><p></p><p></p><p> I often have been one of few Black leaders in the organizations where I&#39;ve worked. At one point in my career, I was a town hall presenter at two meetings separated by level — one attended by rank-and-file employees, and the other attended by management. Although the Black customer service representatives were pleasantly surprised to see someone who looked like them in an executive role, I was shocked and dismayed to realize that nearly our entire customer service representative force was Black while all of our supervisors and managers were White. This was puzzling because the leadership team seemed to care about diversity from a recruiting standpoint, but it was glaringly obvious that systemic barriers were obstructing the retention and advancement of professionals from underrepresented groups.</p><p> Often, it is only when executives, board members, or the HR team notices a lack of diversity in their organization&#39;s upper levels that problems in the talent management system are noticed — but typically poorly understood and only rarely solved. Such disparities in advancement might be at least partially explained by inhospitable organizational settings and the need to broaden the pathway for these professionals from underrepresented populations to succeed.</p><p> Organizational leaders, coaches, mentors, sponsors, and other potential career enablers all have a part to play in eliminating sources of inequity and equipping occupational minorities to survive and thrive in corporate environments. As more and more diverse groups of professionals travel the pathway to career success, the pathway will become smoother and broader, resulting in an ongoing and cumulative organizational transformation.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>