<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 23 日星期一 20:26:37 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>摩擦可以改善客户体验吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli. <p>Marco Bertini 是巴塞罗那 Esade 和 Ramon Llull 大学的营销学教授，也是 Globalpraxis 的高级顾问。迭戈·阿帕里西奥 (Diego Aparicio) 是巴塞罗那 IESE 商学院营销学助理教授。艾林·艾丁利 (Aylin Aydinli) 是阿姆斯特丹自由大学市场营销学副教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Journey]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bertini_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">奥托·德特默/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>公司的使命是设计尽可能没有挫折和不便的购买旅程。 “摩擦会破坏客户体验！”已成为常识。人们认为，在为在线购物者提供服务时尤其如此，众所周知，在线购物者缺乏耐心且注意力集中时间较短。毕竟，只需点击几下鼠标即可到达竞争对手的网站。</p><p>我们认识的大多数企业领导者在显示价格和收款时都会优先考虑消除“关键时刻”的摩擦，因为除了想让热切的客户生活更轻松之外，他们还担心让客户有理由停下来重新考虑他们的决定。但正如我们将要证明的那样，正是在资金紧张的情况下，让客户有时间考虑他们的购买决定，才能为公司带来长期利益和成本节约。</p><p></p><h3>摩擦与善变的在线购物者</h3><p>很容易理解为什么让购物尽可能无缝对电子商务公司来说如此紧迫，因为过去 12 个月的全球平均购物车放弃率总体高达 71.7%（使用台式机或笔记本电脑的人为 60.7%）。使用平板电脑的比例为 65.1%，使用手机的比例为 77.4%。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>最后一个数字可能是最令人不安的，因为美国的移动购物在三年内增长了 2,000 亿美元以上，到 2022 年将达到 4,310 亿美元。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>根据 Baymard Institute 的数据，大型电子商务网站平均可以提高转化率通过简化结账流程，成本降低了 35%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>毫不奇怪，亚马逊和阿里巴巴等电子商务巨头正在大力投资，通过使价格和支付几乎不可见来快速引导消费者度过关键时刻。亚马逊早在 1999 年就率先推出了一键式购物。如今，人们的注意力集中在其 Just Walk Out 技术上，该技术融合了计算机视觉、重量传感器和深度学习，为实体店带来了在线购物的一些便利：顾客可以利用信用进入零售店时使用卡打开虚拟购物车，从货架上选择商品，然后离开，无需在收银台停留。在阿里巴巴，数字支付和自助结账台已成为其 300 家盒马超市的常态。人们甚至可以利用其支付宝子公司的面部识别技术来“刷脸支付”。</p><p>资源较少的公司正在对其采购流程进行改变，这些改变更加渐进但同样重要。例如，考虑一下最近流行的“立即购买，稍后付款”分期付款融资或基于订阅的服务的自动续订条款，这些条款允许公司避免客户重新考虑是否仍然需要该服务的年度清算。在线企业已经抓住了这些和其他机会，通过让客户不去思考花钱的问题，从而减轻花钱的痛苦。</p><p>然而，将摩擦视为具有严格的负面影响（例如惹恼客户或抑制销售）的想法过于简单化。诚然，购买过程中阻力太大很容易抑制购买欲望，但阻力太小会降低决策效率，导致错失与客户更好联系的机会。那么，我们建议企业领导者问问自己，他们是否真的希望客户自动购买。</p><p>在本文中，我们解释了购买过程中的一些摩擦如何帮助公司吸引客户，并就如何利用这些影响建立更牢固的客户关系提供指导。</p><h3>一分耕耘一分收获</h3><p>购买过程中的一些摩擦可以保护消费者免受欺诈、隐私侵犯或他们自己的意外行为。例如，要求两步验证和要求客户确认他们想要完成购买是两个常识性的不便，但最终确保客户免受威胁和错误。</p><p>但围绕购买决策的摩擦过多或过少都会产生负面影响。购买过程中的步骤过多可能会分散购物者的注意力，使他们没有足够的认知能力来仔细考虑自己的决定。这会提高购物车放弃率，并消除客户通过评论、推荐、推荐或其他互动与公司互动的机会。摩擦太少，人们就不会充分考虑自己的决定，从而屈服于人类节省脑力劳动的倾向。这种没有摩擦的情况令人麻木，购物者与购买的联系越少，他们就会变得越矛盾。从长远来看，缺乏承诺反过来会导致产品退货、削弱品牌并降低满意度。</p><p>然而，具有足够挑战性的购买过程却很有吸引力。由于交易既不紧张也不简单，因此人们有动力在任务中投入脑力。换句话说，适量的摩擦可以促使客户完善和巩固他们的偏好，并可以为公司带来三个好处。</p><p></p><p> <strong>1.摩擦力帮助卖家选择合适的客户。</strong>那些将客户群的长期盈利能力置于销售的直接收益之上的公司必须以全面且同样长远的视角来发展与目标受众的关系。这涉及对收购、保留和增长的投资。考虑到这一点，问题是，增加考虑费用的心理痛苦的障碍是否会不成比例地阻止那些获取成本更高、未来再次购买的可能性较小或不太可能增加支出的潜在客户随着时间的推移对品牌的关注或推荐品牌。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>在奢侈品市场以及公司希望潜在客户表现出承诺的任何情况下，通过摩擦来淘汰错误的客户或选择正确的客户是一种常见的技术。例如，法拉利以难以购买特别版汽车而闻名。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>同样，奢侈时尚品牌并不介意排队（无论是虚拟的还是真实的），也不介意通过暂时扣压价格、延长结账流程或使用其他方法来使购买流程复杂化。这些策略背后的简单逻辑是，只有对公司产品最感​​兴趣或对品牌投入最多的客户才会发现在购物过程中可以接受这些不便和复杂的情况。</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. 当摩擦能够带来更好的决策时，客户满意度就会提高。</strong>利用摩擦让消费者有时间停下来考虑购买的影响，可以防止买家后悔，并鼓励购物者在可用的替代方案中选择最合适的选项。</p><p>充分明确潜在买家将支付的费用和他们将收到的东西之间的权衡，有助于防止一时冲动做出盲目的购买决定。例如，社交媒体可能会宣传“现在购买，稍后付款”融资作为一种精明的预算购买方式，但此类服务的简便性和便利性（现在许多电子商务网站的结账流程中都提供）可以鼓励家庭超支，导致财务紧张和债务积累。一项调查发现，申请此类贷款的美国人中有 42% 至少有过一次逾期付款。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>此外，研究表明，在自然消费时刻之前或之后很久进行支付可以降低人们对成本的关注。 “先买后付”的支持者声称，这“将购买的乐趣体验与繁琐的支付过程分开”，而事实上，这种“交易脱钩”已被证明可以降低消费者使用所购买商品的可能性。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p>从公共政策的角度来看，避免错误决策的好处相对明显：大多数人都会同意，购买商品的过度支出和长期利用不足并不是社会所期望的品质。但通过购买过程中的摩擦鼓励客户进行更周到的参与也可以为企业带来回报。</p><p>一个直接的好处是退货率下降。在许多行业，在线退货对财务业绩造成了相当大的拖累——每美元退货商品的价格加起来高达 15 至 30 美分。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>根据 Appriss Retail 和美国零售联合会的一项研究，2021 年，美国数字零售商退回了价值近 2,200 亿美元的商品，约占在线销售额的 21%。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>当然，这种拖累不仅是财务方面的，也是环境方面的。退回的产品可能由于磨损或其他问题而无法转售，最终被送往垃圾填埋场或销毁。据一份报告称，仅在美国，在线退货每年就会产生 50 亿磅垃圾填埋废物和 1500 万吨碳排放。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>增加摩擦还可以让客户有时间考虑购买并加大投入。香奈儿 (Chanel)、路易威登 (Louis Vuitton) 和巴黎世家 (Balenciaga) 等品牌以各种方式延迟价格沟通——例如，通过向销售人员引入个性化体验——不仅是为了选择更好的客户，如上所述，而且是将产品置于中心舞台，帮助客户内化其品质和意义。市场营销和神经科学交叉点的研究报告显示，在产品信息之后揭示价格的重点是对吸引力和需求的评估（人们问自己，“我喜欢这个吗？”），而相反的做法则侧重于对货币价值的评估（人们问自己，“这值得么？”）。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>在 Gartner 的一项研究中，B2B 和 B2C 客户一致认为，如果他们“意识到自己的需求或自己的目标有新的变化”，他们购买更多产品的可能性就会增加 1.73 倍。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p>利用摩擦来激发思考，从而做出购买决定，可以培养对产品的所有权感。这可以增强公司与客户之间的联系，并增加客户在这种关系中投入额外资源的意愿。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>当顾客在购买决定时投入更多的考虑时，他们往往会对最终选择的产品产生更强烈的情感依恋。有证据表明，在情感层面与客户建立联系是实现客户价值最大化的有效途径。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p>最后，研究还表明，当人们通过努力获得产品时，他们往往会更加看重产品——这恰如其分地命名为“宜家效应”，指的是零售商将家具组装外包给顾客的政策。 <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a>努力的体验会影响人们对产品或服务的价值和质量的看法，而在线购买过程中付出的努力可能会引发这种效应。</p><p></p><p>总体而言，我们发现摩擦能够成功地触发参与度，而且我们知道参与度较高的客户通常对他们与品牌和零售商的互动和体验更加满意。积极参与的客户成为倡导者，提高公司的知名度和可信度。他们可能会产生积极的口碑，从而赢得新客户并提高品牌声誉。他们还可能拥有更好的客户服务体验，感受到公司的重视，并提供有意义的反馈和建议。此类反馈对于了解不断变化的客户需求以及随着时间的推移对产品或服务进行正确的改进非常有价值。</p><p> <strong>3.摩擦为企业与客户的沟通创造了空间。</strong>当人们面临价格和支付时，保留一些摩擦，尤其是当这种摩擦是意外的时候，会引起人们的关注。对于公司来说，这是一个宣传他们的立场和产品优点的机会。</p><p>利用摩擦力进行晋升的方法有多种。首先，公司可以让客户参与支付过程，以唤起积极的情绪。例如，一种常见的做法是让客户可以选择将交易金额四舍五入到下一个最高的美元，并将差额捐赠给慈善机构。另一种可能性是推出按需付费活动，让客户选择他们愿意为产品支付的价格。虽然这些举措并不能加快付款速度（考虑一个人愿意为某样东西支付多少钱是令人惊讶的努力），但它们可以带来更大的情感联系。</p><p>公司还可以故意以非常规的方式表达价格，以迫使客户更深入地思考潜在的信息。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>例如，宜家的一则广告使用罐装苏打水来有趣地量化其产品的价格。当然，零售商不会接受苏打水作为家具付款。尽管需要花点时间来理解“汇率”，但还是向顾客传达了这样的信息：家具与苏打水等小额商品一样便宜。</p><p>另一个例子是时代啤酒 (Stella Artois) 屡获殊荣的“令人放心的昂贵”营销活动。该品牌试图通过将价格与质量之间的依赖关系引入其价格沟通中来表明其啤酒的高品质。 Stella 开玩笑地提供一张提高产品价格的优惠券，颠覆了消费者的期望（“带上这张优惠券，购买下一款 Stella Artois 时需额外支付 1.25 美元”）。通过提出看似令人困惑且不合逻辑的“交易”，它促使客户得出结论：该产品远远优于竞争对手的产品（并且物有所值）。</p><p>支付过程中的摩擦也可以用来传达品牌的价值观。例如，2014年，救援组织Misereor通过在机场等地点部署交互式屏幕，要求路人通过在屏幕上刷信用卡来捐赠2欧元，从而提高了捐款率。刷卡激活了一个引人入胜的互动序列，例如描绘信用卡切一片面包来喂饥饿的人或释放被监禁的孩子。</p><p>最后，举一个极端摩擦的大胆例子，户外零售商 REI 在美国一年中最大的购物日“黑色星期五”关闭了实体店并停止处理在线支付。其目标是反对消费主义并鼓励潜在消费者。购物者应该花时间在户外——这一信息强调了该公司致力于无障碍探索的决心。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17 号</a></p><h3>摩擦最佳点</h3><p>更好的客户选择、消费者决策和促销是放弃零摩擦这一简单化目标的三个充分理由。鉴于鼓励客户自动购买的缺点，企业领导者应设法确定公司购买流程的适当摩擦程度。根据我们的经验，至少有五个因素需要考虑。我们将审查它们并引入一个记分卡，将它们聚集在一起并帮助指导决策。 （请参阅“对于在线客户体验而言，适当的摩擦力是多少？”）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>对于您的在线客户体验来说，适当的摩擦力是多少？</h4><p class="caption">使用此记分卡可帮助您确定最佳摩擦力，以帮助您<br />培养持久的客户关系。</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p>对于每家公司来说，第一步都是对摩擦采用更准确的定义。目前，所有摩擦都被负面看待，这降低了组织需要明确其实际含义的意识。大多数人认为，摩擦是通过节省时间来实现的。但并非所有的时间都是平等的。事实上，公司应该将负面摩擦视为阻碍或分散客户购买决策的任何事物，而将正面摩擦视为优化深思熟虑的任何事物。</p><p>第二步是了解哪些环境可以从积极的摩擦中受益——因为这种需求并不普遍。特定购买决策的利害关系是什么？通常需要高还是低的客户参与？两者经常同时出现，因此高风险的决策也需要高度的参与，但情况并非一定如此。例如，经济上有保障的消费者可能不会仅仅因为商品价格昂贵而更多地参与购买决策。正是当这种关系破裂时，你需要介入并主动管理摩擦。高风险决策可能是由于相关产品或服务的重要性、财务支出的规模或购买的个人或社会后果而做出的。本着这种精神，在体育场馆中使用亚马逊的“Just Walk Out”等技术可能对那些不再因小贩摊前排太长的队伍而劝阻购买不健康零食的人来说可能并不好。</p><p>第三，考虑您的商业目标。如果您关心强调相对于竞争对手的价格节省的成本，那么，是的 - 通过预先发布几乎好得令人难以置信的价格来减少摩擦是值得的。然而，如果你在创新、质量或客户服务的基础上进行竞争，那么最好通过延迟报价来保留一点摩擦，因为这会让客户思考并具体化他们的偏好。一些摩擦可以让企业将话题从“值得吗？”转移过来。到“我喜欢吗？”如果目标是强化品牌，那么增加摩擦是正确的方法。</p><p>第四，考虑客户群的构成以及客户关系的相对紧密程度。不同的客户群体可能需要或多或少的摩擦，具体取决于他们对产品或服务的理解或支付能力的期望。同样，关系阶段也很重要。与回头客相比，您可能希望在与新客户的交易中增加更多的摩擦，特别是那些可能不太熟悉您的产品或产品类别的客户。您可能希望让潜在客户更难购买，为回头客增加一些摩擦，并为完全了解产品或服务的忠实客户提供无摩擦的体验。公司应该最大限度地提高与客户的持久关系——因为这是增加客户价值的唯一途径。</p><p>第五，考虑您选择的市场途径。所有零售环境都可能从一些摩擦中受益，但它们的应用会有所不同。在实体店中，添加痛点来激励销售人员与客户之间的互动可能是正确的摩擦类型。然而，在在线商店中，增加促进深思熟虑的步骤可以减少退货并提高随后对公司的满意度。在社交媒体上，公司可以寻求平衡吸引客户互动的内容，而不仅仅是点击率，从而帮助阻止用户盲目或冲动地购物。</p><p></p><p>事实上，对于在实体店和网上销售相同产品的企业来说，在线或移动渠道可能需要更多（积极的）摩擦，因为这些渠道的产品回报往往是最大的。一些时尚品牌最近推出的一项有趣的技术是对在线退货收取费用。 Anthropologie、H&amp;M 和 Zara 等公司对网上退货收取费用（但店内退货不收取费用）。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a>是的，收取退货费用可能会激怒一些顾客。但同样，这一点可能是留住最相关的客户并加强与那些坚持购买的客户的关系的关键。</p><p></p><p> “我们怎样才能让我们的价格不那么引人注目并且更容易支付呢？”这是用户体验团队和专家最常问的问题之一。但企业领导者应该拥抱客户的关键时刻，而不是努力消除它。他们不应该相信“摩擦是最终转化杀手”这一流行观点。</p><p>毫无疑问，如果使用不当，摩擦会破坏客户体验。但无摩擦的世界也同样危险。这是我们大多数人多年前从高中物理老师那里学到的一课：太多的摩擦会阻碍实现目标的进展，但太少的摩擦会使一切陷入混乱。</p><p>事实上，许多企业领导者已经告诉我们，他们希望客户在购买决策上花费更多富有成效的时间。这听起来像是摩擦力的完美工作。如果思考引导购物者做出更安全、更好的选择，反过来，这些选择通过降低产品退货、更可持续的消费者行为、更高的客户满意度和更高的忠诚度来影响公司，那么让我们都接受并拥抱一些麻烦和障碍——尽管令人惊讶——以客户为中心的工具。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>您的组织在负责任的人工智能方面投资足够吗？我们的数据表明“可能不会”</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Priorities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year’s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团连续第二年组建了一个国际人工智能专家小组，帮助我们了解全球组织如何实施负责任的人工智能 (RAI)。对于今年研究周期的最后一个问题，我们要求学术界和从业者小组成员对这一挑衅做出回应：<em>随着商业界越来越意识到人工智能的风险，企业正在对 RAI 进行足够的投资。</em></p><p>尽管理由各不相同，但大多数小组成员都承认 RAI 投资未能满足需要：13 人中有 11 人不愿意认为组织对负责任的人工智能的投资是“足够的”。小组成员在很大程度上肯定了我们<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/building-robust-rai-programs-as-third-party-ai-tools-proliferate/">2023 年 RAI 全球调查</a>的结果，其中不到一半的受访者表示他们相信他们的公司准备对 RAI 进行足够的投资。对于优先考虑人工智能并必须管理人工智能相关风险的公司来说，这是一个紧迫的领导挑战。</p><p> H&amp;M 集团负责任的人工智能和数据主管 Linda Leopold 表示，扩大 RAI 投资的需要标志着一个重大转变，因为“人工智能相关的风险不容忽视”。虽然对 RAI 进行足够的投资曾经是一个重要但不是特别紧迫的问题，但 Leopold 表示，生成式人工智能的最新进展和第三方工具的激增已经表明此类投资的紧迫性。</p><p>由于衡量方面的挑战，对 RAI 进行充分投资变得复杂。没有提供指导的行业标准，因此您如何知道您的投资何时或是否足够？更重要的是，理性的高管对于什么是充分投资可能有不同的看法。显而易见的是，认知问题不应成为行动的障碍，尤其是当人工智能风险构成真正的业务威胁时。</p><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3>小组成员回应</p></h3><h2>目前尚不清楚组织是否对 RAI 进行了适当的投资。</p></h2><p>大多数小组成员不愿意同意组织正在对 RAI 进行“足够”的投资。</p><p><a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">跳转至下面小组成员的详细回复。</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-Chart.jpg" alt="图：0 强烈同意； 15% 同意，46% 既不同意也不不同意； 39% 不同意； 0% 强烈不同意"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source">资料来源：由 13 名人工智能战略专家组成的 Responsible AI 小组。 </p></p></div><p><path id="Path" d="M0,0,14.067,15.065,28.941,0" transform="translate(1.096 1.054)" fill="none" stroke="#fff" stroke-miterlimit="10" stroke-width="3" /> <a href="" class="callout-chart-add__button"><span class="callout-chart-add__button-text"><strong>显示</strong>全球调查结果</span></a></p><div class="callout-chart-add"><div class="callout-chart-add__container"><div class="callout-chart-add__info"><h4></h4><h3> 2023 年全球高管调查的回复<br /></h3><p>“您认为您的组织在多大程度上准备好投资（减少收入、增加成本）以遵守负责任的人工智能计划？” </p></p></div><div class="callout-chart-add__chart"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-survey.jpg" alt="条形图：中等或较大程度：48%；在某种程度上：29%；较小程度：8%；完全没有：3%；不知道：12%" class="mt0"></p><p class="callout-chart-add__source">资料来源：对代表年收入至少 1 亿美元的组织的 1,240 名受访者进行的调查数据。这些受访者代表了 87 个国家/地区 59 个行业的公司。在中国进行的调查是本地化的。</p></p></div></p></div></p></div></div><h3>公司正在投资 RAI，但还不够</h3><p>小组成员提出了公司没有对负责任的人工智能进行足够投资的几个原因。几位小组成员表示，利润动机是一个因素。联合国大学校长兼联合国副秘书长 Tshilidzi Marwala 认为，“只有 20% 意识到人工智能风险的公司正在投资 RAI 项目。其余的人更关心如何利用人工智能来实现利润最大化。”新加坡国立大学大卫·马歇尔教授兼副教务长西蒙·切斯特曼 (Simon Chesterman) 补充道：“围绕生成式人工智能的淘金热导致科技公司的安全团队规模缩小，新产品的上市路径也缩短了。 ......在许多组织中，即使不是全部，对错过的恐惧正在战胜风险管理。”</p><p>投资不足的另一个原因是，在整个企业中更多地使用人工智能会扩大 RAI 的范围并增加所需的投资。正如 Armilla AI 的人工智能政策主管 Philip Dawson 所观察到的那样，“对人工智能功能的投资继续大大超过对人工智能安全和实施人工智能风险管理的工具的投资。企业正在一场艰苦的战斗中追赶，而且只会变得更加艰难。”利奥波德补充说，生成式人工智能和越来越多的可能应用“显着增加了负责任的人工智能项目必须覆盖的受众规模”。</p><p></p><p>第三个原因是，对人工智能风险的认识不断增强并不总是转化为对这些风险的准确评估。非洲负责任人工智能观察站的政策专家 Oarabile Mudongo 表示，一些公司可能没有对其 RAI 项目进行足够的投资，因为它们“低估了人工智能风险的程度”。</p><h3>您如何知道自己的投资是否足够？</h3><p>其他小组成员指出，尽管对RAI进行足够的投资很重要，但很难衡量投资是否足够大或有效。企业应如何计算 RAI 投资回报？什么才算是“足够”的回报？什么才算投资？ Aboitiz Data Innovation 首席执行官兼菲律宾联合银行首席数据和人工智能官 David R. Hardoon 问道：“如果 (1) 所有公司都不受相同水平的标准，（2）我们尚未就什么是“足够”或“可接受”达成一致，或者（3）我们没有验证第三方的机制？”</p><p> Dataiku 的 AI 负责人 Triveni Gandhi 对此表示同意：“在那些花时间投资 RAI 项目的公司中，这些项目的实际设计和实施方式存在很大差异。对于如何实施或实施 RAI 价值观缺乏一致或明确的期望，使得组织很难开始有效的投资。”</p><p> Stemly 联合创始人、首席运营官兼首席科学家朱塞佩·马奈 (Giuseppe Manai) 表示：“很难确定公司在负责任的人工智能项目上进行了多大程度的投资，因为人们的认知度和相关性非常广泛。”华为技术（英国）研究总监艾莎·纳西尔（Aisha Naseer）补充道：“目前尚不清楚这些投资是否足够，因为这些投资的规模从微不足道到巨额资金都被分配用于控制人工智能和相关风险缓解。”</p><p></p><h3>建议</h3><p>对于寻求充分投资 RAI 的组织，我们建议如下：</p><p> <strong>1. 培养领导层对人工智能风险的认识。</strong>领导者需要意识到，使用人工智能是一把双刃剑，既会带来风险，也会带来好处。专注于增加人工智能收益的投资，而不相应地关注管理其风险，会从两个方面损害价值创造。一是，如果没有适当的护栏，人工智能的好处可能不会令人印象深刻：我们的研究发现，当 RAI 实践到位时，人工智能的创新就会增加。其次，人工智能带来的风险与其所嵌入的工具一样迅速扩散。对人工智能风险和收益的强烈认识支持领导层努力管理风险和发展公司。建立管理意识可以采取多种形式，包括高管教育、讨论论坛和 RAI 计划，这些计划拥有不同类型的人工智能风险暴露（和经验）的利益相关者。</p><p> <strong>2. 接受 RAI 投资将是一个持续的过程。</strong>随着人工智能开发和使用的增加（没有可预见的结束），RAI 实践和实施也需要适应。这需要持续的 RAI 投资来不断发展 RAI 计划。随着欧盟、美国和亚洲的监管格局即将发生变化，领导者将面临越来越大的压力，要求其发展以人工智能为中心的风险管理系统。等待在技术、文化和财务方面对这些系统进行投资（或停止投资）可能会损害业务增长。当新的法规和行业标准生效时，为满足合规性要求而快速调整流程可能会干扰人工智能相关的创新。最好将 RAI 程序与 AI 开发共同发展，这样它们就能相互补充，而不是造成这种不必要的干扰。随着公司扩大人工智能投资，他们的 RAI 投资也需要增长。但那些已经落后的公司需要迅速采取行动，积极投资 RAI，以避免始终落后。</p><p> <strong>3. 制定 RAI 投资指标。</strong>投资 RAI 很复杂——这种投资的回报是什么样的？就像网络安全投资一样，最好的 RAI 回报可能是在人工智能相关问题在品牌声誉受损、监管问题和成本增加之前被发现时保持沉默。 That said, silence should not be mistaken for adequate investment. As our survey results show, companies making minimal investment might not find issues simply because they aren&#39;t looking for them. Leaders should align on what constitutes an RAI investment, the appropriate metrics to evaluate these investments, and who will decide on investment levels. Metrics that gauge RAI program success are necessary to support RAI programs over time, but they can be a lagging indicator. Metrics should also evaluate forward-looking dimensions such as leadership commitment, program adoption, training and workforce needs, and culture change. Leaders must also determine how RAI funding is related to funding for AI projects. Should every large AI project have a budget set aside for RAI? Or should RAI funding be independent of specific projects or some combination of project-based (decentralized) and institutional (centralized) investments?</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Real Issues Driving the Nursing Crisis</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jack Daly</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><p> We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research on various elements of employees&#39; experiences, including culture, compensation and benefits, work schedules, and perceived organizational support. We clustered related topics together into two dozen broader themes.</p><p> We used the topics as features in an XGBoost model that predicted each nurse&#39;s overall rating of their current or former employer on a 5-point scale. We then calculated SHAP values (which assign an importance value to each feature in a model) to directly compare the relative importance of different topics in predicting job satisfaction (measured by the overall rating each nurse gave their employer). We also used textual analysis to compare how favorably travel nurses spoke about topics compared with nurses on staff at health care systems.</p><p> Using the topics nurses mentioned and their sentiment toward each topic as predictors, our models explain between 29% and 39% of the variance in ratings across nurses — nearly an order of magnitude more than we could account for using ownership, organizational type, and location as predictors. <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a></p></aside><p> Health care leaders face a daunting set of challenges — rising costs, the transition to digital health, and shifting payment models, to name just a few. But according to a recent survey from the American College of Healthcare Executives, the No. 1 problem hospital CEOs face is staff shortages and burnout. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Ninety percent of the CEOs surveyed cited nursing shortages as a particularly acute pain point.</p><p> In 2021, the total number of registered nurses working in the US dropped by the largest amount in 40 years, with younger nurses leading the exodus. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> By 2025, the US health care system could suffer a shortfall of up to 450,000 nurses, or 20% fewer than the nursing workforce required for patient care. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p> High levels of job dissatisfaction and burnout are driving nurses from the profession. The COVID-19 pandemic placed tremendous pressure on all health care workers, but dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses have not improved since the pandemic ended. And by some measures, it might be getting worse: In 2021, nearly two-thirds of registered nurses would have encouraged others to become a nurse, but only half said they would recommend nursing as a profession two years later. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> One of the richest sources of insight on dissatisfaction among nurses is how they describe their job, in their own words, on employment sites like Indeed and Glassdoor. This information is voluminous but difficult to synthesize because most of it takes the form of unstructured free text. To understand the challenges nurses face, we analyzed how 150,000 of them had described their employers in Glassdoor reviews since the beginning of the pandemic. (See “The Research.”) In this article, we share key insights from that analysis and offer advice to health care leaders about how they can address nurses&#39; most pressing issues.</p><h3> Health Care Leaders Are Out of Touch</h3><p> Nurses view their managers as out of touch with the daily realities of patient care. We categorized their comments about managers into nearly 50 leadership traits. The second most frequently cited trait described managers as being unaware of the challenges that nurses struggle with in the workplace. When nurses discussed how managers understood life at the bedside, their comments were negative 9 times out of 10.</p><p></p><p> Nurses are particularly critical of members of the senior executive team for their disconnectedness. The top team was 10 times more likely than front-line supervisors and middle managers to be criticized for being out of touch. Our results reinforce a separate survey in which nearly half of hospital nurses said they believe management does not listen to their concerns. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> To address dissatisfaction and burnout, health care leaders must first understand what&#39;s happening at the bedside. This can be challenging, particularly in large health care systems with thousands of nurses working across multiple sites and specialties.</p><p> Historically, leaders have struggled to systematically analyze the gold mine of insights into nurses&#39; frustrations that can be gleaned from their comments in employee surveys or external reviews. Reading, understanding, and analyzing huge volumes of unstructured textual data has simply not been practical. However, recent advances in artificial intelligence make it possible to identify deep patterns in large bodies of text and understand feedback at scale. Leaders can now mine free text to gain a nuanced understanding of the issues driving dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses and use that insight to improve life at work for their nursing staffs. (See “Getting Started With Text Analytics.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Getting Started With Text Analytics</h4><p> Our research analyzes data from hundreds of organizations and hundreds of thousands of nurses, but you can delve more deeply into your own employees&#39; feedback as well. Regardless of whether you develop AI text analytics capabilities internally, through a workforce analytics function, or with an external partner, you should keep these principles in mind to maximize the effectiveness of the cultural measurement.</p><p> <strong>Precision matters, but so does recall.</strong> Precision — the percentage of text instances that are correctly classified as discussing a topic — is a critical element of free text analysis. So is recall — the percentage of total mentions of the topic in a body of text that are captured by your text analytics platform. If you gauge success solely through precision, you will end up with an analytical platform that is highly accurate but misses most of what employees actually say. A sophisticated AI tool will pick up on slang, idioms, acronyms, cultural references, and organization-specific language to capture the long tail of seldom-mentioned but information-rich terms.</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p> <strong>Keep subject matter experts in the loop.</strong> The heart of text analytics is classifying natural language into meaningful topics. Ideally, the people measuring culture will engage subject matter experts when developing topics for analysis. Subject matter experts can ensure that the cultural and workplace topics selected are clearly defined, linked to existing research, and properly measured.</p><p> <strong>Likert questions have severe drawbacks but, used in moderation, can be very helpful.</strong> Too many Likert-scale questions can lead survey takers to shift into autopilot mode. But Likert questions should not be thrown out altogether. Effective cultural measurement combines Likert-scale outcomes on broad topics (such as engagement, attrition intent, and other important measures) with free-text data to identify which, out of hundreds of free-text topics, have the most powerful impact on outcomes.</p><p> <strong>Transparency matters and will probably matter more going forward.</strong> While it remains to be seen how AI will be regulated, it is likely that legislators or courts will not look kindly on important decisions being made by black-box models with no explanation of how the models are reaching their conclusions. Leaders often rely on culture measurement to make important decisions such as compensation policies, personnel changes, and how to prioritize resources. They should be wary of relying exclusively on models that make decisions that humans cannot understand.</p><p> <strong>Employees hate it when you spy on them — and you won&#39;t learn much about culture.</strong> Leaders should resist the temptation to expand their text analytics efforts to the content of emails, Slack channels, phone messages, and other forms of communication that were not designed to provide employee feedback. Many employees consider listening to their work conversations eavesdropping or worse. Moreover, work emails and Slack messages tend to contain far less cultural information than question prompts that explicitly invite employees to discuss what is working and not working in their organization. Keep employee listening consensual, and keep Big Brother out of the workplace.</p></div></article></aside></div><h3> Identify Relative Strengths and Opportunities Through Benchmarking</h3><p> Nursing satisfaction varies widely across employers. We identified 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies. For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic through June 2023. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> Among large employers, nurses&#39; Glassdoor ratings ran the gamut from poor (2.6) to nearly perfect (4.9) on a 5-point scale. Nurses&#39; assessments of how well senior leadership has performed during and after the pandemic were even more varied, ranging from 2.1 to 4.9 on the same 5-point scale. The wide variance in Glassdoor ratings is consistent with a separate survey in which the percentage of dissatisfied nurses ranged from 2% to 48% across 60 US hospitals. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Employees of the 200 large health care organizations can use our <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">interactive tool</a> to see how their organization ranks against others. The index is sortable by nurses&#39; overall ratings, their assessments of the top leadership, and the four most powerful predictors of nurses&#39; satisfaction: compensation, workload, organizational support, and toxic culture. </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4> How Do Nurses Rate Their Employers?</h4><p class="caption"> Use the Nursing Satisfaction Index to compare how nurses evaluated the employee experience at 200 large health care organizations.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> Nurses who work for staffing agencies (who are sometimes referred to as travel nurses) are, on average, much more satisfied than other nurses. The five highest-ranked employers in our sample (and six of the top 10) are staffing agencies.</p><p> Higher compensation, of course, accounts for part of this difference, but not all of it. We compared how positively nurses working with staffing agencies spoke about 200 topics compared with their counterparts employed by hospitals and health care systems. (See “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors.”) While compensation was viewed more favorably by agency nurses, issues around solving nurses&#39; problems and open, honest communication had a larger sentiment gap between the two groups. By focusing on nurses as clients, staffing agencies excel at practices that improve satisfaction beyond simply paying higher wages. Other health care leaders can learn from their example, and we&#39;ll make some concrete recommendations below.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors</h4><p class="caption"> We analyzed the free text of US Glassdoor reviews by nurses from the start of the pandemic to June 2023 to see how positively they spoke about a variety of topics. We then compared the positive sentiments of nurses working with staffing agencies to those of nurses working in hospitals and health care systems. While staffing agencies rate higher on many key topics — including honest communication, resolving issues efficiently, and building trust — hospitals and health care systems are stronger when it comes to learning and development, benefits, colleagues, and opportunities for promotion. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3> Prioritize Drivers of Job Satisfaction</h3><p> To understand the drivers of job satisfaction among nurses, we analyzed the free text of all reviews that had been written by the nurses in our sample since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into nearly 200 topics. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> We then clustered topics into two dozen broader themes and used those themes to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers. We then compared each theme&#39;s relative importance in predicting ratings. (See “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction.”)</p><p></p><p> Compensation was the top predictor of satisfaction among nurses reviewing their current employer, which is not surprising, given that inflation eroded the purchasing power of take-home pay during the period we analyzed. The importance of workload, the second-most-important driver, jibes with findings from a separate large-scale survey that found insufficient staffing was the strongest predictor of nurses&#39; job dissatisfaction, burnout, and intent to quit. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Workload and compensation are root causes of the nursing crisis that must be addressed, but they are not the only factors influencing nurses&#39; job satisfaction. Our analysis surfaced other aspects of the work environment, including toxic culture, organizational support, work schedules, communication, and learning and development opportunities, that leaders can focus on to improve nurses&#39; work lives.</p><p> This analysis also highlights areas that are unlikely to move the needle in improving the workplace experience for nurses. Perks are nice, but they will not compensate for a punishing workload or wages that fail to keep pace with inflation. Highlighting the corporate mission to promote patient health won&#39;t help much either. Nurses already know that their job serves a higher purpose; that&#39;s why most of them became nurses in the first place.</p><h3> Mine Free Text for Actionable Insights</h3><p> Many health care organizations rely on annual employee surveys, with dozens of items rated on a 5-point scale and a few open-ended questions tacked on as an afterthought. Faced with a long list of multiple-choice questions, employees are prone to switching to autopilot and assigning similar scores to very different items. The choice of questions constrains what employees can discuss, and there is seldom room to expand on why they chose a particular numeric response.</p><p> Open-ended, free-text feedback provides a rich source of nuanced and actionable insights. When nurses can decide which topics to write about, they use their freedom to discuss what matters most to them. Open-ended questions provide nurses with the space to expand on their concerns in their own words, offer crucial context, and propose concrete and actionable fixes to the problems they face. Individual free-text responses can be aggregated into broader themes to prioritize where leaders could focus their attention and limited resources to achieve the largest improvements in nurses&#39; satisfaction.</p><p> While organizational averages are useful, it is important to remember that distinctive subcultures can coexist within the same organization. This is particularly true among large health care systems that have grown through mergers and acquisitions. One national hospital chain, for example, has ratings that range from 1.9 to 3.9 across nearly 50 sites. Rather than relying on organizational averages alone, health care leaders must measure and analyze differences across locations, departments, functions, teams, and individual leaders.</p><p> Women, underrepresented minorities, and older employees can also experience organizational culture very differently from other employees. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> It&#39;s crucial to understand the drivers of job satisfaction and burnout across diverse employee populations.</p><p></p><p> Leaders can mine the free text for detailed insights about the most critical pain points for specific groups and tailor their interventions accordingly. Schedules, for example, have a significant impact on nurses&#39; job satisfaction, but which aspects of scheduling matter most will depend on the specific position. Flexibility in scheduling shifts and the ability to take uninterrupted work breaks is very important for nurses in hospitals and primary care practices, while home health care nurses place a premium on predictable schedules. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Nurses&#39; comments provide a treasure trove of practical suggestions to improve the workplace and patient care. The Glassdoor reviews we studied, for example, include dozens of actionable suggestions for how employers can improve scheduling. Some are easy-to-implement actions, such as using an app to make it easier to pick up or swap shifts, or paying a $20 to $50 bonus to nurses who pick up shifts at the last minute. Others are more systemic changes, like including nurses on a committee established to set schedules or ensuring that employees who receive tuition assistance are able to schedule work around their classes.</p><h3> Listen to Nurses Who Leave Your Organization</h3><p> Most organizations limit their surveys to current employees. Exit interviews are administered haphazardly, if at all, and the feedback from former employees is too often dismissed as the rantings of malcontents. But ignoring feedback from former employees is a big mistake. </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> Interviewing or surveying former employees can surface the reasons for their departure and pinpoint the most effective actions to retain talent. Free of the threat of retaliation, nurses who are leaving (or have left) an organization are more likely to provide candid feedback, even about taboo issues that current employees are reluctant to discuss. By collecting feedback from those who have left, organizations can uncover potential blind spots.</p><p> More than one-third of the Glassdoor reviews in our sample were written by former employees and provide insights on what mattered most to nurses who voted with their feet. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> The bars on the left side of the figure “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction” rank the factors that predict how nurses who quit rank their former employers, and it sheds light on a critical reason nurses might head for the exits.</p><p> In an <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">earlier article</a> , we argued that five behavioral attributes — disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive — mark an organizational culture as toxic. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> Among nurses who quit, toxic culture is more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction than compensation or workload. The importance of toxic workplaces among nurses who quit is consistent with earlier research that found toxicity to be the strongest predictor of industry-adjusted attrition during the first six months of the Great Resignation. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Toxic culture has become more important for nurses in the post-pandemic era. When we compared which factors best predict how nurses rated their employer before and after the pandemic, toxic culture experienced the largest gain in relative importance post-COVID-19 (followed by workload, well-being, and compensation). If your organization suffers from cultural toxicity, another article of ours, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">How to Fix a Toxic Culture</a> ,” presents several evidence-based interventions health care leaders can use to detox their own organization.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction</h4><p class="caption"> We classified the text of over 150,000 nurses&#39; Glassdoor reviews into two dozen themes that affect the employee experience, and we then analyzed which themes best predict how nurses rate their employer. The chart ranks the importance of each theme in predicting these ratings by showing how much each theme contributes to the overall prediction. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses’ Job Satisfaction" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3> Learn From Staffing Agency Practices</h3><p> As the figure “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors” shows, nurses are very positive about the processes staffing agencies have in place to resolve problems quickly and efficiently. Of nurses who mentioned the efficiency of staffing agencies&#39; processes, 75% were positive, compared with 23% expressing positive sentiment for health care systems. For travel nurses, common process issues include onboarding, obtaining required credentials and licenses, contract negotiation, and reimbursement. The best staffing agencies listen to feedback, develop a deep understanding of the typical problems travel nurses face, and optimize their work processes to address these issues.</p><p> Many of the pain points encountered by staff nurses will differ from those of agency nurses. Health care systems, home health agencies, and long-term care providers could, however, adopt a similar approach to capture and analyze nurses&#39; feedback, prioritize the most common and frustrating challenges they face, and work with staff members to address these issues.</p><p> Consistently listening to and acting on feedback can also build trust with the nursing staff. Staffing agency nurses are more positive about having the psychological safety to speak up about difficult issues and be heard than are nurses working in hospitals and health care systems.</p><p> The benefits of psychological safety are blunted, however, if management is slow to respond to issues that nurses raise. Nurses speak highly of how quickly staffing agencies respond to their questions and concerns. In contrast, nurses frequently complain that other types of employers are slow to respond to emails raising issues, if they get a reply at all. Nurses also place a high value on having multiple channels of communication with their supervisors, including text, email, Facebook, Jabber, and a 24/7 hotline.</p><p> Another insight from our research is that nurses value honesty and transparency. They understand the challenges health care faces as well as anyone, and they expect honest communication about what is happening in the organization, how it affects them, and why decisions were made. Triage, a staffing agency and the fourth most highly rated large employer we studied, places honest communication at the center of its value proposition: “We tell it like it is so you won&#39;t be surprised by how it goes.” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p> Health care systems can learn from staffing agencies, but they can also leverage their own distinctive advantages to attract and retain nurses. Nurses in full-time staff positions rate hospitals and health care systems higher than staffing agencies on three important aspects of organizational life: learning and development (including promotion opportunities and reimbursement for training), benefits, and colleagues. Those three factors are among the top 10 predictors of how nurses rate their employers. Health care systems should invest in their comparative advantages and emphasize them when communicating their value proposition to potential and current employees.</p><p></p><h3> Translate Feedback Into Action to Build Trust</h3><p> It&#39;s one thing to collect employee feedback, but it&#39;s another to consistently act on those insights. Employees are less likely to surface issues or propose potential solutions if they believe that managers will not act. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Worse yet, employees are more likely to quit if they believe that management lacks the power, resources, or interest to make changes based on their suggestions. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Nearly half of nurses believe that management will not fix problems that clinical staff members bring to their attention. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p> Organizations need to put in place structures to consistently act on employee feedback. One well-known example is Kaiser Permanente&#39;s unit-based teams (UBTs), which consist of clinical staff members and managers who regularly work together in a specific unit or department. <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a> The teams, which meet at least once per month, are responsible for their unit&#39;s performance and are co-led by a manager, a labor representative, and, typically, a clinical staff member.</p><p> The UBTs identify opportunities to improve along four dimensions: quality (including patient outcomes), patient service, affordability, and employee experience. The teams use employee feedback to identify and prioritize improvement opportunities. Next, the teams develop and test solutions using best practices and evidence-based methods. Once a solution has been deemed effective, it is implemented across the unit, department, or, in some cases, the entire organization. The UBTs then monitor the impact of these changes in terms of patient outcomes, employee satisfaction, and cost reduction.</p><p></p><p> Our study of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses since the onset of COVID-19 reveals wide variation in how nurses rate their employers as a whole, and specifically in terms of compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support — the four factors that most shape nurses&#39; job satisfaction. In our view, this variation offers a message of hope. Despite the structural challenges that all health care organizations face, it <em>is</em> possible to provide an environment where nurses look forward to going to work every day.</p><p> Many organizations, including some of the largest employers of nurses, have significant room for improvement. These rankings are not designed to “name and shame” but rather to make health care leaders aware of the magnitude of the gap between their organization&#39;s performance and what is possible when it comes to providing a healthy workplace for nurses. We also hope that the objective data on how health care organizations rank on factors that matter most to nurses can provide their leaders with the impetus to make improvements and the evidence to convince all stakeholders of the urgent need for change.</p><p></p><p> What leaders should not do is ask nurses to work harder and endure more frustration and stress while failing to understand and address the organizational factors that make life miserable for many of them. Leaders who continue business as usual should not be surprised when staff members quit, workers unionize, and state and federal legislators dictate regulations to protect the interests of nurses.</p><p> To improve the work lives of nurses, and indeed all health care workers, leaders must collect and act on their feedback, recognizing that different parts of the organization and different populations will face distinctive challenges and issues. Listening to nurses demonstrates that there are meaningful steps health care leaders can take to fix the nursing crisis. The single most important step is to listen to them in the first place.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Explore How Nurses Rate Their Employers</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses&#39; own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by US nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers.</p><p> We calculated the relative importance of each theme in predicting nurses&#39; overall satisfaction. Four factors — toxic culture, organizational support, compensation, and workload — emerged as the strongest predictors of how satisfied nurses were with their employer.</p><p></p><p> One significant finding for health care leaders: Among nurses who had quit, toxic culture was more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction compared with compensation or workload.</p><p> Nurses&#39; job satisfaction varies widely among employers. Our interactive Nursing Satisfaction Index shows how nurses evaluate the employee experience at 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies.</p><p> For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. We also report on how positively or negatively nurses spoke about compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support. Each employer&#39;s score on all dimensions is expressed as standard deviations above/(below) the average for all 200 employers.</p><p> <a href="#interactive-launcher">Explore the index above</a> .</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Health Care Leaders Need to Know to Fight the Nursing Shortage: Nurses Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read is multimedia editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What&#39;s driving that burnout? What&#39;s most important to a nurse&#39;s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this video, we talk to five current and former nurses to learn about the reality of working in health care, including the toxic cultures and stressors they&#39;ve experienced, and get advice from them and health care experts on what needs to change.</p><p> Article author and researcher Donald Sull also discusses the truths about job satisfaction revealed by the analysis of 150,000 employer reviews by nurses on job site Glassdoor, and what health care leaders can learn from them.</p><p></p><p> “The key, actionable finding from our research is, nurses are telling you what&#39;s not working for them, often in very granular detail, and they&#39;re offering concrete recommendations to address these issues. They want to help. They want their voices heard, and they want to make a positive impact,” Sull says.</p><p> “One of the most difficult or frustrating things about being a nurse is really not having enough time to spend with the patient,” says Jennie Evans, who served as a pediatric oncology and ICU RN for 18 years. “Those moments where you can sit, talk with the patient, hold their hand, talk with the family, and really get to know them and understand not just the disease but other underlying anxieties or fears that the patient might have.”</p><p> Watch the video to hear more from nurses on what they want health care leaders to know about toxic cultures, mental health, growth opportunities, and other issues that are critical to caregivers.</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Upgrading Culture for Growth and Transformation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander is a strategic adviser and professor of practice at Hult International Business School. His work on decision-making, problem-solving, and culture has been published in <em>Harvard Business Review</em> , <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , and <em>Knowledge at Wharton</em> . Per shares his thoughts and ideas on his blog <a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">leadershipbackbone.com</a> . Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> P. Hugander, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , May 22, 2023.</p></aside><p> Many leaders know that their organization&#39;s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don&#39;t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and growth. But despite ambitious efforts to infuse such skills into their culture, many organizations fail. The secret to success: Shorten the time to reward when people experience the new skills helping teams beat longtime challenges.</p><p> Per Hugander has helped leaders at organizations including Swedish financial services group SEB make progress on complex strategic challenges. His practical approach helps people to link psychological safety to tangible business results.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why many organizations fail at culture change: Just testing the waters can be dangerous.</li><li> How to go deep — not wide — on culture change and win over skeptics.</li><li> How to put the new skills to use quickly on the organization&#39;s toughest problems and create lasting culture benefits.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Steps to Build and Sustain Diversity in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> , Ed.D., is a managing partner and the US practice leader of CEO and Board Services at Boyden, a global executive search firm. He built his career as a turnaround (glass cliff) specialist in corporate America and writes on issues related to diversity, governance, and strategic growth for private and public corporations and boards.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; however, less attention is paid to what happens after the hire. Only when we effectively create a more equitable landscape and support women and people of color in navigating it can we benefit from the full engagement and contributions of all of our people and avoid losing them to turnover or disengagement.</p><p> Occupational minorities — those individuals who are <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">relative rarities</a> in their profession due to their gender or sexual identity, ethnicity, age, or other factors — have accomplished what countless more have only dreamed of: They have broken through the glass ceiling, navigated the often inhospitable <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">corporate jungle</a> , and often successfully negotiated the <a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">glass cliff</a> . Although the executives who represent diverse populations in your organization have successfully overcome these challenges, an important task remains: building a path for others to follow. This is hard, painstaking work that requires many different tools and competencies, yet it is necessary if others are to safely navigate the landscape.</p><p></p><h3> Steps to Sustaining Diversity</h3><p> Although various resources offer suggestions for how professionals from underrepresented populations can navigate and overcome organizational challenges, it is equally essential that organizations identify where <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">persistent systemic bias and racism</a> lurk and take concrete action to address them. Organizations can take the following five steps to begin the process of creating more inclusive environments where all employees have equal opportunities to thrive and advance in their careers.</p><h4> Step 1: Establish leadership commitment to diversity with sponsorship.</h4><p> Leadership throughout the organization must demonstrate a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion. When leaders model these behaviors, employees throughout the organization naturally follow their example. However, this commitment cannot be limited to one-off efforts or statements on corporate values.</p><p> Leaders must consciously exhibit their commitment to hiring people from underrepresented populations by helping to develop and equip these candidates for advancement. Specifically, every leader, regardless of organizational level, should identify at least one such candidate to intentionally sponsor. After getting to know the candidate&#39;s background, career goals, and support needs, the leader should (1) counsel them in navigating the organization, (2) support them in developing the competencies needed to advance in their career, and, critically, (3) help them secure progressive leadership positions.</p><p></p><p> Although formal mentoring, sponsorship, and buddy programs can be helpful in this effort, relationships that develop informally often are equally, if not more, rewarding and beneficial and tend to continue long after one or both individuals have advanced in or moved out of the organization.</p><h4> Step 2: Remove glass ceilings by addressing systemic factors.</h4><p> The metaphor of the glass ceiling depicts the systems of discrimination that prevent certain groups of people (typically women and people of color) from accessing high-level opportunities for career growth and advancement. Clues that glass ceilings exist within your organization include a lack of diversity within the upper-management and executive ranks compared with your overall workforce; pay disparities between individuals with similar roles and qualifications; limited mentorship, sponsorship, development, or advancement for certain groups of people; explicit or implicit biases regarding which groups are a better fit for leadership roles than others; and attrition levels within underrepresented groups that exceed those of other groups.</p><p> To identify and eradicate glass ceilings in your organization, closely scrutinize every aspect of the employee experience. For example, address biased hiring and promotion practices using blind recruitment techniques; review salary ranges and promotion criteria to ensure that equal pay is awarded for equal work; and make clear career paths and development opportunities available to all employees. Diversity goals, inclusion initiatives, and employee education on recognizing and avoiding unconscious biases also can support a diversity-conducive climate. Supporting flexible work arrangements and work-life balance can encourage the full participation of employees who might otherwise be overlooked due to their needs to balance personal and professional responsibilities.</p><p></p><h4> Step 3: Reduce glass cliffs through due diligence.</h4><p> The term <em>glass cliff</em> describes a phenomenon in which women and other minorities are preferentially selected for leadership positions in times of crisis, placing them at increased risk for failure. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This phenomenon occurs across industries and geographies, and for women and ethnic minorities alike. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The problem with giving people from underrepresented populations leadership opportunities only in times of crisis is that those who lead during turbulent times tend to be seen as part of the problem, which perpetuates stereotypes and reduces future opportunities for such candidates. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> To avoid this outcome, care must be taken to recognize and fully examine the situation before assigning a leader to address it. While the temptation to dive in and do something to “stop the bleeding” is overwhelming, taking the appropriate time to first fully understand the problem is a small price to pay for a much-improved chance of success. The diagnosis process should include identifying project parameters (such as performance targets, deadlines, and budget), project stakeholders, past actions taken, the current situation, and desired outcomes — from the perspectives of all stakeholders. My article on the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">glass cliff phenomenon</a> provides more details on the process of due diligence and the questions that can be used to diagnose these situations. Only after diagnosing the problem will it be possible to select the most appropriate candidate to lead the effort.</p><h4> Step 4: Broaden the pathway by changing the conversation.</h4><p> Corporate environments can be fraught with challenges for women and people of color. Many challenges are systemic, such as organizational cultures that <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">disadvantage certain groups</a> versus others, or workloads and behavioral expectations that require long hours in the office and around-the-clock responsiveness. These systemic challenges can make the corporate landscape seem foreign and antagonistic. In turn, occupational minorities might compensate by nursing cognitive biases that result in too much or too little confidence; limiting their social networks to similar peers rather than nurturing<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">vital connections</a> to sponsors, mentors, and career guides; and failing to strike an appropriate work-life balance.</p><p> Although leaders must deliberately sponsor occupational minorities (Step 1), mentors, sponsors, and allies throughout the organization also play important roles in guiding candidates toward success because they, too, have already successfully navigated the organization. Supporting emerging leaders means changing the typical mentoring conversation. Typical conversations involve identifying a mentee&#39;s short- and long-term goals and seeking the mentor&#39;s situational advice, guidance on skill development, and feedback on performance. Mentoring that supports diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging should be adapted to include a clear framework for professional development, an explanation of how various opportunities and positions contribute to the candidate&#39;s career goals, and a discussion of how to navigate the organizational culture — all in light of the glass ceilings, glass cliffs, and systemic challenges they face as occupational minorities.</p><p> Cognitive biases also should be part of the conversation so that candidates can avoid the traps of both being overconfident and overcompensating for perceived shortcomings. Evaluation and adjustment of cognitive biases might be best accomplished by gathering 360-degree feedback regarding the mentee&#39;s performance on key tasks and engaging the mentee to describe their feelings, thoughts, and general experiences related to performing those tasks. Overconfidence might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is at or below average while their own experience of that task reflects strong enthusiasm, satisfaction, and a sense of achievement. In contrast, overcompensation might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is evaluated as or above average yet their described experiences suggest that they are spending too much time on tasks or that they harbor concerns about their performance.</p><h4> Step 5: Measure and track progress.</h4><p> A popular business adage is that we must inspect what we expect. This truism applies equally to any diversity effort. The process begins with defining what success looks like according to key diversity metrics such as hiring, retention, and advancement for various employee populations. It might be tempting to stop there; however, defining the goal is only the beginning. Additionally, it is necessary to measure the organization&#39;s current performance on these KPIs and then examine why that is the current state. Understanding the organization&#39;s current performance requires the following assessments:</p><p> <strong>1. Gauge buy-in.</strong> To what extent do organizational leaders and members understand and agree that the KPIs defined are the right indicators and performance targets?</p><p> <strong>2. Gauge feasibility.</strong> What organizational structures, processes, and other features facilitate the achievement of the KPI? What features threaten or obstruct achievement?</p><p> <strong>3. Gauge support needs.</strong> Leaders are taught to adapt to the needs of individual subordinates based on each person&#39;s skill level. In the same way, leaders throughout the organization need to adjust the amount of oversight, encouragement, and direction they provide as departments and employees across skill levels work to achieve diversity goals. For example, a recruiting department that is relatively inexperienced at hiring professionals from underrepresented groups will need strong, step-by-step guidance and frequent feedback until their competency grows, while a manager who is highly skilled at developing and including such professionals generally should be allowed the autonomy to exercise their talents to their fullest.</p><p></p><p> As initiatives are implemented, continue to regularly assess these metrics to gauge your progress and fine-tune your efforts. As the saying goes, “What gets measured gets done.” Achievement of your diversity goals will happen only if they are deliberately defined and regularly assessed.</p><p></p><p></p><p> I often have been one of few Black leaders in the organizations where I&#39;ve worked. At one point in my career, I was a town hall presenter at two meetings separated by level — one attended by rank-and-file employees, and the other attended by management. Although the Black customer service representatives were pleasantly surprised to see someone who looked like them in an executive role, I was shocked and dismayed to realize that nearly our entire customer service representative force was Black while all of our supervisors and managers were White. This was puzzling because the leadership team seemed to care about diversity from a recruiting standpoint, but it was glaringly obvious that systemic barriers were obstructing the retention and advancement of professionals from underrepresented groups.</p><p> Often, it is only when executives, board members, or the HR team notices a lack of diversity in their organization&#39;s upper levels that problems in the talent management system are noticed — but typically poorly understood and only rarely solved. Such disparities in advancement might be at least partially explained by inhospitable organizational settings and the need to broaden the pathway for these professionals from underrepresented populations to succeed.</p><p> Organizational leaders, coaches, mentors, sponsors, and other potential career enablers all have a part to play in eliminating sources of inequity and equipping occupational minorities to survive and thrive in corporate environments. As more and more diverse groups of professionals travel the pathway to career success, the pathway will become smoother and broader, resulting in an ongoing and cumulative organizational transformation.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why Pay Transparency Regulations Are a Strategic Management Opportunity</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>Tamara Montag-Smit is an assistant professor of management at the University of Massachusetts (UMass) Lowell. Karoline Evans is an associate professor of management at UMass Lowell. Brandon Smit is an assistant professor of management at Bentley University. Cassondra Batz-Barbarich is an assistant professor of business at Lake Forest College.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Annalisa Grassano</p></figcaption></figure><p> Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, <a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">pay transparency laws</a> are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women&#39;s Law Center reports that altogether, more than one-quarter of US employees live in a location where <a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">pay information is regulated</a> .</p><p> By and large, pay transparency regulations have emphasized disclosing a salary range for advertised positions and internal opportunities for advancement. These laws are designed to ensure equal pay for equal work and effectively close the gender wage gap. The logic is simple: If underpaid employees, including women and minorities, aren&#39;t aware of what their coworkers are paid, they are at a significant disadvantage in leveling the playing field through litigation and negotiation. How can inequities be addressed when they remain in the dark? Without pay transparency, enforcement of existing laws, such as the <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">Equal Pay Act of 1963</a> , becomes difficult. Based on <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">recent cases</a> and notable discrepancies that have been exposed (some spanning years of underpayment), it seems that greater transparency has an important role to play.</p><p></p><h3> Organizational Responses to the Changing Regulatory Landscape</h3><p> Despite the increasingly widespread adoption of pay transparency regulations, many organizations have responded with pushback, resistance, and minimal compliance. After Colorado became the first state to require organizations to disclose pay ranges in advertised positions in 2021, organizations soliciting applicants from across the country began <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">explicitly excluding Colorado residents</a> from consideration to skirt the new laws, prompting the state&#39;s department of labor to issue <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">warnings and fines</a> . Another organizational tactic is to comply with pay information requirements with pay ranges that are so wide that applicants cannot meaningfully predict what salary they might be offered. In one notable example, Netflix posted a job with a salary range that <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">spanned $90,000 to $900,000</a> .</p><p> While approaches to compliance with transparency laws at the organizational level have taken many forms, leaders have expressed several common concerns regarding the potential negative consequences of pay transparency to their business operations and culture:</p><ul><li> <strong>Will everyone just ask for more money?</strong> More pay information might prompt more conversations about pay (and why someone is receiving what they are). Managers worry that they&#39;ll be caught in the middle trying to juggle competing goals around budgeting and employee satisfaction.</li><li> <strong>What happens if some employees find out that they&#39;re paid less than others?</strong> Explaining to long-standing employees why they are paid the same as a new hire is likely to be uncomfortable and prompt substantial criticism of the employer.</li><li> <strong>Will pay transparency affect our ability to work together?</strong> Pay transparency can elicit jealousy and counterproductive competition when individuals perceive themselves as inequitably rewarded. Managers worry that employees might fight and undermine one another when discrepancies are exposed.</li></ul><p></p><h3> New Insights Into Managing Pay Transparency</h3><p> Our work provides new insights into addressing some of the main questions organizations have about transparency. Most new laws focus exclusively on creating pay transparency by requiring organizations to disclose pay ranges for open positions. In academic research, this form of transparency is referred to as <em>distributive transparency</em> , because it reveals information only regarding the <em>amount</em> of money employees are paid.</p><p> In our research, however, we have delineated several ways in which pay information can be transparent. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> With <em>procedural transparency</em> , the emphasis is on sharing information about how pay <em>decisions</em> are made; at the most transparent level, this would include a formula for calculating compensation (such as base pay or a merit-based raise).</p><p> Distinguishing between distributive versus procedural transparency is crucial because, as our research shows, procedural transparency can mitigate many of the risks and drawbacks associated with distributive transparency.</p><p> Implicit in pay transparency regulations is the idea that underpaid employees will take it upon themselves to <a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">negotiate for a fairer wage</a> . In fact, a large-scale study of over 100,000 academics over the past two decades found that changes in pay transparency were related to significantly more wage parity between men and women. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> However, the research also showed that transparency doesn&#39;t equate to <em>everyone</em> asking for more.</p><p> To explore this further, we conducted a series of four experiments to better understand <em>how</em> and <em>when</em> pay transparency can encourage employees (especially women) to more effectively negotiate for fair wages. In our first study, lab participants were paid for their performance after four rounds of a popular word search game and were given the opportunity to negotiate for better compensation. In studies 2, 3, and 4, online participants prepared themselves to go into a performance review, armed with varying degrees of information regarding performance and pay, to possibly negotiate for a better annual raise. They were told that they were slated for a 3% raise but that raises could range from 3% to 10%. Across these studies, we varied the amount of information participants could access regarding both the amount other people were paid and participants&#39; performance relative to their peers&#39;.</p><p> These studies yielded four important findings regarding distributive and procedural pay transparency:</p><p> <strong>1. People made clearer comparisons.</strong> We found that the best predictor of whether someone tried to negotiate for higher pay was their performance relative to that of peers. Compared with average performers, high performers were approximately 50% more likely to request higher pay when they knew their ranking relative to others. It&#39;s important to note that in our study, participants saw the previous year&#39;s performance and pay data for their team members, and it was clear that increased performance was directly related to increased pay. Although not an explicit formula indicating performance-based pay, this information provided a clear signal to participants that pay raises were largely determined by performance.</p><p> <strong>2. People negotiated fairly.</strong> Average performers were more likely to accept the minimum raise offered to them, often citing the raise as fair based on their performance. As one person stated, “Considering I only met expectations throughout the year rather than exceeded them, asking for a higher raise seems fruitless and unearned.” Generally, average performers rarely asked for the maximum raise, in part because they considered the fact that they were performing at a lower level than some peers. This was true, though, only when they had all of the information. When they were told nothing about their performance, 85% of people requested the maximum pay amount. Lacking performance information, average performers asked for the highest raises available within the pay range.</p><p> <strong>3. Women <em>do</em> ask for higher pay.</strong> Counter to a pervasive assumption, women didn&#39;t seem to need much encouragement to negotiate. In fact, when the percentage of participants who negotiated is considered, women were often more likely than men to negotiate (though this was not a statistically significant difference). These findings cast some doubt on the idea that one reason for the gender wage gap is that women negotiate less often than their male counterparts. Recent research combining information from dozens of negotiation studies has come to the same conclusion: Many of the negotiation gaps between men and women have largely disappeared in recent years. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Although this is good news, it does little to close the gender pay gap as it currently stands.</p><p> <strong>4. People were motivated to perform better.</strong> Average performers expressed motivation to work harder and perform better to earn a higher raise during the next review cycle. When asked why they did not negotiate for more money, one participant stated, “My numbers did not show that I deserved a higher raise. With better numbers the following year, a case would be made for a higher raise.” Another stated, “I knew I&#39;d done an average job, so I hope to do better in the future and hope to get a better raise next year.”</p><p> Our findings replicate and extend an old but powerful notion in management research: the <em>fair process effect</em> . <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Employees will accept unfavorable outcomes if they believe those outcomes were produced by a fair system. Put differently, if people know <em>why</em> they are being paid less (in other words, there is procedural transparency), they will not respond negatively and might even work harder.</p><h3> Make Pay Transparency a Win-Win for Your Organization</h3><p> Pay transparency can be a win-win opportunity rather than a compliance hurdle. But simply listing pay data in job postings without any context in response to regulations might be a big mistake. These practices not only disregard the spirit of the laws but also come at a heavy price and forfeit significant opportunities. Leaders should think beyond compliance and consider ways to strategically leverage pay transparency for their organization to improve applicant attraction and employee retention. Our research offers some insights into how this can be done.</p><p> <strong>Make pay only <em>part</em> of the transparency equation.</strong> Counter to some pervasive fears that transparency will increase labor costs, cause jealousy, and create conflict, the reality is that secrecy around pay creates problems of its own. As researchers at Payscale found, most employees are <a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">unsure whether they are paid fairly</a> , with many believing they are underpaid when they are not, which leads to greater turnover and dissatisfaction. Our research suggests that without a reference point for performance, employees have little to no basis for judging what compensation would be fair and are therefore more likely to make unreasonable requests. Transparency in both performance <em>and</em> pay can enable employees to better assess the fairness of their pay and make more reasonable requests.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on the pay decision-making process.</strong> Procedural transparency helps managers more clearly communicate with employees about pay because salaries/bonuses are based on performance rather than on seemingly intangible or, worse yet, bias-laden factors. Providing information on how pay is determined helps incumbent employees understand why their pay is higher or lower than their peers&#39; and, more importantly, how to move up. Managers can&#39;t be accused of favoritism and bias when pay is directly determined by performance, which puts them in a collaborative role during pay conversations. With a focus on performance, these conversations can focus on development and examine how employees can perform better and earn higher raises.</p><p> <strong>Recognize that (distributive) pay transparency will not fix inequity on its own.</strong> There&#39;s an assumption that distributive pay transparency will close pay gaps; however, evidence suggests that this alone is not enough to create an equitable workplace. Research has shown that women and men are <em>asking</em> for salary increases in <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">relatively equal proportions</a> , but women are still less successful at getting what they ask for. Distributive pay transparency can help reduce some ambiguity, but both performance and pay transparency (procedural transparency) together equip employees with the tools they need to ask for what they deserve. When people know what to expect from negotiations (that is, what the bargaining zone is and what&#39;s reasonable to ask for), gender differences are minimized. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> For example, <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">women of color</a> don&#39;t often take advantage of opportunities to negotiate roles, responsibilities, or flexible work arrangements, creating long-term inequities that explain pay gaps beyond starting salary. Broader transparency helps reduce the ambiguity that often leaves women and members of other minority populations hesitant to negotiate, even when they know they could.</p><p> <strong>Consider the benefits for current employees <em>and</em> applicants.</strong> Simply posting pay ranges is only one piece of the puzzle. Applicants have negative reactions to excessively wide pay ranges because they don&#39;t offer useful information. In this case, pay is still essentially secret. As we found in our study, without meaningful information, individuals are inclined to ask for the maximum amount to see what is possible. This creates yet another headache for hiring managers. A better approach would be to leverage procedural transparency to clearly outline the factors used when determining a salary offer, and perhaps even how heavily those factors are weighted. For example, Buffer, a marketing company, has done a great job of creating a <a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">pay system</a> that balances simplicity (for better understanding) and complexity (for capturing nuance) by using a standard formula for making pay decisions: salary = job type x seniority x experience + location + $10,000 or equity.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Despite organizational concerns and hesitancy to implement government regulations around pay transparency, such policies continue to gain traction and are just one force behind growing expectations around salary disclosures. In a 2022 report from HR technology firm Visier, 79% of surveyed employees said they want <a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">pay transparency</a> ; Gen Z employees were the strongest proponents of it.</p><p> Our research highlights the potential for procedural transparency to strategically mitigate the perceived organizational risks while also meeting legal requirements and social expectations. While changes are clearly happening, we hope business leaders think more deeply and creatively about <em>how</em> to make pay transparent in ways that both support organizational goals and meet employee needs.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Delicate Dynamics of Challenging a Superior</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>Benjamin Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one&#39;s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person and the situation.</p><p> For those keen on maintaining professional decorum and growing in their roles, this guide can help ensure that your challenging conversations are both constructive and respectful.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Choose your battles wisely.</strong> Workplaces are vibrant ecosystems of opinions, processes, and methodologies. It can be enticing to address every single discrepancy or divergence in opinion that one encounters, but wisdom lies in discerning which battles are worth fighting. Every time a potential disagreement arises, consider: Is this issue so significant that it warrants a confrontation? Minor differences in opinion might be addressed more effectively through passive channels or should even be overlooked. But larger concerns, especially those affecting team dynamics, company culture, or broader business objectives, require a more direct approach.</p><p> <strong>Understand the importance of timing.</strong> In the world of professional communication, timing can be everything. Choosing the right moment can make the difference between a concern being genuinely considered or hastily dismissed. Before even considering challenging a superior, it&#39;s crucial to pause and assess the situation from a holistic viewpoint. Is your concern so immediate that it demands to be addressed immediately? Alternatively, would it be better to earmark it for a detailed, private discussion later? It&#39;s wise to avoid confronting superiors during high-pressure situations or public forums because it can be misconstrued as an attempt at disruption or showmanship. By choosing the optimal time, you create a smoother path for constructive dialogue.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prioritize private discussions.</strong> The environment in which you choose to voice your concerns plays a pivotal role in how those concerns are received. Engaging in public disagreements or conflicts can lead to multiple unforeseen complications, including being perceived as aggressive or confrontational. By choosing a private setting for these discussions, you provide both yourself and your superior with an atmosphere conducive to open and genuine dialogue. This approach not only minimizes distractions and potential biases but also reinforces the idea that the intent is constructive feedback, not public criticism.</p><p> <strong>Master the art of “I” statements.</strong> Effective communication is as much about content as it is about delivery. The words we choose and the manner in which we frame our concerns can significantly influence the reception of our message. Instead of adopting a potentially confrontational tone, use “I” statements to express observations, feelings, and suggestions. For instance, instead of bluntly stating, “You&#39;ve overlooked this crucial aspect,” a more collaborative approach would be, “I feel that this particular aspect could benefit from further attention.” This approach ensures that the focus remains on the issue at hand and not on personal biases or confrontations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Embrace the feedback process.</strong> The journey of challenging a superior or expressing concerns is inherently bilateral. It&#39;s not just an avenue for you to voice your thoughts but also an opportunity to understand the other person&#39;s perspective. Demonstrating a genuine openness to feedback, even if it&#39;s contradictory to your viewpoint, is vital. This approach not only paves the way for mutual respect but also fosters a culture of continuous learning and collaboration within the organization.</p><p> <strong>Align with like-minded peers, but tactfully.</strong> While individual concerns have their merit, there&#39;s undeniable strength in numbers. Finding allies or colleagues who share your perspective can provide additional weight to your concerns. However, it&#39;s imperative that this alignment is not perceived as cliquey or divisive. The primary focus should always remain on the collective benefit of the organization rather than on forming factions within the team.</p><p> <strong>Keep the organization&#39;s goals at the forefront.</strong> Any concerns or challenges you raise should inherently resonate with the broader objectives and goals of the organization. By consistently aligning your feedback and suggestions with the company&#39;s mission and values, you reassure your superiors of your commitment to the collective success of the organization over your individual aspirations.</p><p> <strong>Brace for a spectrum of outcomes.</strong> While we all hope for positive and constructive outcomes from our disagreements, it&#39;s essential to be prepared for a variety of reactions. Your superior might be receptive, indifferent, or even defensive. By anticipating these potential responses and planning your strategies accordingly, you ensure that you remain balanced, constructive, and professional, irrespective of the immediate feedback.</p><h3> The Aftermath: Reflect, Adapt, and Evolve</h3><p></p><p> Every professional interaction, especially those involving challenges or confrontations, provides a rich opportunity for personal and professional growth. After the discussion, take the time to evaluate the effectiveness of the conversation, the strategies employed, and the outcomes achieved. These reflections will bring invaluable lessons to light and help you to continuously refine and enhance your communication skills for future challenges.</p><p> Ultimately, while the task of challenging a superior might seem steeped in potential pitfalls, with the right strategies and a focus on mutual growth and respect, it can be navigated with tact and professionalism. Encouraging open dialogue and a culture of feedback is the bedrock of innovative and forward-thinking organizations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Ghost Scenarios Haunt Strategy Execution</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang is a senior fellow in management practice at the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Collaborative Strategy Lab. Rafael Ramírez is professor of practice at Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Scenarios Programme.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, have observed that business leaders are inclined, and their organizations configured, to work with only a single implicit view of the future. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That view is typically deeply embedded within their strategies as a set of unquestioned assumptions about the future context. We call these sets of unexamined assumptions <em>ghost scenarios</em> because they are invisible — and because they may come back to haunt executives and companies in unanticipated and unwelcome ways.</p><p></p><p> Underpinning every ghost scenario is a small set of implicit trends that leaders project into the future without questioning whether they might change. Consider the ways in which dramatic changes in climate have come to haunt rail services in Britain. In July 2022, temperatures above 40 degrees Celsius (104 degrees Fahrenheit) were recorded in the country for the first time. These high temperatures heated the rails to slightly over 62 C (143 F), causing them to bend. As a result, many train trips were canceled and service on other routes slowed to 60 mph. The rail tracks had been engineered for a future in which the air temperature did not exceed 27 C (80 F). In short, the British rail network was designed and built to work not in the scenario in which it found itself in 2022 but in a scenario that made the implicit assumption that historical climate trends would continue unchanged.</p><h3> Assumptions Hide in Plain Sight</h3><p> Research on human perception has demonstrated that people differentiate the object of their visual focus from its background by bringing that object to the forefront of their attention while everything else recedes. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Humans can focus on either the figure or the background but never both at the same time.</p><p> The <a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">Rubin vase illusion</a> is a well-known example of this figure-ground (or background) perception challenge. Depending on how you look at the picture, you will see either a vase or two faces in profile. Importantly, however, you cannot see both at the same time: One or the other perceptually recedes to become the background of the figure you see. To see both figures, you must alternate between them.</p><p> It&#39;s important that executives are able to recognize how people&#39;s ability to focus can also blind them to important contextual information, since leaders often fail to see the background upon which their strategies will play out — and on which their strategies depend. They may consider hard infrastructure — such as rail tracks — to be a relatively static background issue and focus their attention on trends that seem more salient to business planning, such as changes in customer preferences and habits. But that can lead executives to implement a strategy that may be unexpectedly disrupted by the unexamined assumptions about its context that are woven through its background issues.</p><p></p><p> Particularly today, given the fast pace of change, soaring uncertainty, and high levels of turbulence, failing to surface the assumptions built into strategic planning is risky, as is a failure to consider multiple possible alternative futures through <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">scenario planning</a> . <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Scenario planning exercises can help executives explore how their strategies might play out in different business contexts and conditions, with an eye toward honing those strategies to be more effective.</p><p> To understand how scenario planning can keep executives from being haunted by a ghost scenario, let&#39;s look at two global organizations we recently worked with in the Oxford Scenarios Programme. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA Examines Its ESG Assumptions</h3><p> Insurance company <a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a> serves 95 million clients in over 50 countries with products and services in the areas of property-casualty insurance, life insurance and savings, and asset management. One of the company&#39;s key strategic goals is to sustain its climate leadership position. Wisely, executives from AXA decided to make the future context of that goal the focus of their attention for a limited period of time so that they could explore how it might change and how they might need to adapt if it did.</p><p> The company was particularly interested in understanding how future environmental, social, and governance (ESG) trends might affect its stated goal. For example, what might be the impact of some US states&#39; proposed legislation that would penalize financial institutions pursuing ESG investment strategies? Or, how might the public react if companies are seen as greenwashing or misrepresenting their ESG credentials? Thus, instead of letting ESG requirements, as currently understood, be the ghost scenario, the company asked questions about the future of ESG and, more broadly, about the emerging sustainability context for corporations.</p><p> Participants and facilitators in the scenario-planning exercise worked in teams to look at the future environment. One scenario imagined that stand-alone insurance companies had been swallowed up by dominant tech platforms whose own ESG priorities superseded those of the insurers. In another scenario, governments set stringent regulations regarding ESG issues, with compliance implications for companies&#39; strategic choices. In yet another imagined future, climate change accelerated more than expected, causing businesses to shift their priorities to urgently address climate-related crises — or to focus exclusively on reducing CO2 emissions, abandoning social and governance agendas.</p><p> By explicitly engaging with the ghost scenario and its equally plausible alternatives, AXA came to understand that continuing to strive to deliver superior ESG performance as it is currently understood might not be the only future it should be preparing for. Within AXA, these insights have been used to inform a conversation about future ESG challenges and their implications for possible announcements and commitments to be made, including when and with whom. They&#39;ve prompted AXA to start preparing alternative strategies in the event that delivering great performance against current ESG expectations becomes irrelevant.</p><p></p><h3> Swift Anticipates Digital Currencies</h3><p> Swift (the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication) is a member-owned cooperative that enables financial messaging and related services for cross-border payments around the world. It currently delivers over 30 million messages a day for more than 11,000 institutions in over 200 countries and territories. It was created in the early 1970s by 239 banks in 15 countries to solve the growing problem of clunky, slow, and costly cross-border payments communications via a new technology platform. With disruption as part of its origin story, Swift is proactive about potential changes in its context.</p><p> In 2021, Swift executives were interested in understanding how digital currencies, including those issued by central banks, might evolve in the years ahead. The category more than doubled in 2021, to more than 9,000 cryptocurrencies.</p><p> Rather than assuming this unfolding and rapid growth in digital currencies to be the only possible scenario, executives at Swift paused to better understand what other developments might occur, how they might shape the future digital currency ecosystem, and how Swift might be affected. For example, economists and other experts have pointed to the lack of intrinsic value of many digital currencies, as well as concerns about <a href="https://concerned.tech/">the security and reliability of their underlying technologies</a> .</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Where the Ghosts Hide in Common Strategic Planning Processes</h4><p> <strong>In a SWOT analysis,</strong> leaders consider their organization&#39;s strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats in relation to only the current scenario and to known competitors, suppliers, customers, regulatory rules, and the like. When identifying and analyzing risks, executives implicitly assume that there is only one scenario. However, in another context (a different scenario), risks might evaporate and new opportunities might arise.</p><p> <strong>In stakeholder mapping,</strong> leaders make an assessment about the attention and power of stakeholders now and in one expected future. An implicit scenario is the background to this assessment. But the importance of stakeholders could change significantly if the context unexpectedly changes.</p><p> <strong>In game theory and war-gaming,</strong> competitors&#39; moves are considered within the context of a ghost scenario, and war games are typically conducted with no consideration of a different future other than the one that is underway. However, changing scenarios could require new tactics and surface unforeseen future combatants.<br /></article></aside></div><p> Swift&#39;s own stance on digital currencies was open and neutral. It would potentially support them if they were properly regulated and added value to the economies, businesses, and communities it served.</p><p> The scenarios developed for Swift&#39;s executives explored different ways in which trust in the technology might evolve. In some of them, trust associated with digital currencies would disappear as the opaque technology and algorithms upon which they are based became suspect. In other scenarios, digital currencies could be manipulated, and thus the authenticity of what was being exchanged could no longer be guaranteed. And in another scenario, a more generalized lack of trust in for-profit financial institutions would spread to providers of digital currencies, leading some segments of society to hesitate to engage with either, with related consequences.</p><p> For the Oxford participants envisioning these scenarios, it was not clear that the values held by those promoting the technology, or the values that the technology supposedly enabled, would be accepted by governmental regulators or by those in society at large in all imaginable future contexts. Swift&#39;s executives have since explored those sets of scenarios, which provided rich and divergent insights about the ways digital currencies might pan out. Those insights have helped them avoid relying on overly simplistic views of the future — and being swayed by hype.</p><h3> How to See a Ghost Before It Haunts You</h3><p> Based on our experience leading scenario planning exercises for AXA, Swift, and many other organizations, we have developed the following suggestions for executives who want to bring their ghost scenarios into view and make the figure-ground reversal a key part of their strategy practice.</p><p> <strong>Use scenario planning to acknowledge implicit assumptions.</strong> Recognize that every organization&#39;s strategy presumes a future scenario that often remains unquestioned. That is, every executive engages in a form of implicit scenario planning, whether they are conscious of it or not. Making scenario planning a regular part of the strategy-making process achieves two important goals: It alerts leaders to how turbulent conditions could change the context within which they work and compete, and it acknowledges the reality that current conditions themselves present a hypothetical future scenario, not a fixed reality.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize the figure-ground dilemma.</strong> Acknowledge that the figure that is attended to (most often, the organization&#39;s strategy) and the background that is so often ignored (the unexamined ghost scenario) cannot successfully be the focus of attention at the same time. Instead, executives need to flexibly and sequentially shift between the two to investigate each fully and avoid the trap of making implicit assumptions about the other. AXA took the time to deliberately explore the future of ESG rather than assuming there would be no changes to how it is currently used and understood. Swift purposefully focused on understanding the potential future contexts of digital currencies rather than just implicitly assuming subsequent options from the existing trends.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Dedicate executive time and resources to the problem.</strong> Organizations must intentionally create a time and space for leaders to explore how relevant economic, political, technological, social, and environmental factors might be changing. Contrast a small set of future scenarios with the ghost scenario to pinpoint where current strategy might need to be adapted to be well positioned for the range of ways the context might develop. Some organizations even have dedicated units, such as the <a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">Global Business Environment scenarios team</a> at Shell International. <a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">Policy Horizons Canada</a> plays this role for the Canadian government.</p><p></p><p> For all of these efforts to be truly useful, scenario planning outputs must be fed back into strategic decision-making rather than written up in a report and placed on a shelf. They should also be disseminated more widely in an organization so that people at all levels and functions can consider possible implications from their own perspective — implications that might not occur to leadership. For a strategy to be successful when the context changes, executives need to have a balanced approach — recognizing both figure and ground as important areas for discernment. That is, they must recognize the importance of the background or ground upon which their actions will play out, even as they plan their next move. Savvy executives know that they must both envision and embrace change. The trick is learning to adeptly shift one&#39;s attention between the figure and the ground to see how the context might unfold, so it doesn&#39;t leave your strategy ungrounded.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Fueling Interdisciplinary Innovation With AI: Volvo&#39;s Anders Sjögren</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automotive Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory. On this episode of the Me, Myself, and AI podcast, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Starting a career with the ambition of becoming a medical doctor and ending up a technical leader for a major automaker might seem an unlikely path, but for Anders Sjögren, who leads data and AI innovation projects for Volvo Cars, it was a perfect trajectory.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Anders joins hosts Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh to explain the ways the carmaker uses data and artificial intelligence to inform manufacturing — ensuring that parts are made consistently and as efficiently as possible — as well as driver experience and safety. He also outlines some specific ways smart technology keeps drivers alert and aware of conditions around them and describes Volvo&#39;s approach to technology-driven innovation. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/MMAI-S8-E1-Sjogren-Volvo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Anders Sjögren"></p><h4> Anders Sjögren, Volvo Cars</h4><p> Anders Sjögren is senior technical leader for Volvo Cars. He focuses on strategy, research, innovation, and transformation, with the key objective of ensuring that the automaker understands and executes within the continuously emerging areas of data, analytics, and artificial intelligence. Application areas include creating AI-enabled intelligent customer functionality and using AI to reform Volvo&#39;s operations and development activities. Sjögren has an academic background in mathematical statistics (large-scale and computational aspects) and an industrial background in data-centric methods development and software product development.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one carmaker use AI to bring together all of the complex systems required to engineer a safe and high-performing vehicle? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m Anders Sjögren from Volvo Cars, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Today, Sam and I are delighted to be joined by Anders Sjögren, senior technical leader, data, analytics, and AI-enabled engineering, at Volvo Cars. Let&#39;s get started. Anders, welcome to the show.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thank you.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> So tell us a little bit about your role at Volvo Cars.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I&#39;m a technical leader in data, analytics, and AI in the engineering part [of the organization], so that&#39;s the R&amp;D. So, essentially, what comes in is a wish for a car, and what comes out is drawings and code. In that area, there are, of course, a lot of possibilities for data analytics and AI, both during the development process and also as part of the actual functions in the car — so intelligent functions and personalized functions and so on.</p><p> So my purpose here is really to make sure that we get the value that we can through data, analytics, and AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is [your focus] the AI and data analytics that go into the car — like the sensors and all kinds of intelligent devices in the car that make driving safer and more interactive, and things like that? Or is it also customer acquisition and dealer networks and all kinds of data analytics to run a business of making and selling cars?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yes. So, I mean, all of those apply to Volvo Cars, but the part I&#39;m really active in is more in the part of the making of the car.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think that&#39;s a great point because when most people think about cars and artificial intelligence, I think they immediately jump to this idea of fully self-driving cars. And what you&#39;re pointing out is how much other stuff that there is going on, even in the production of cars, that can benefit from artificial intelligence. You know, I think perhaps everyone&#39;s frustrated that we don&#39;t have fully automated cars now, but there&#39;s so much going on behind the scenes that people don&#39;t get a chance to see. What are some of the examples of the ways that you&#39;re using artificial intelligence in the production process?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we take a little bit of a step back, the goal of Volvo Cars is really to give people the freedom to move in a personal and sustainable and a safe way.</p><p> If we start with “personal,” then it&#39;s really critical that we understand you and make you feel special as a customer or as someone in the car. And there, of course, it has to do with starting with the sensors and then really interpreting those values. That can be cameras, different types of steering input …</p><p> Another area is definitely sustainability. AI is being used there to make sure that we have as many lightweight parts as possible. So using AI, one can, for example, get mechanical parts with the same strength and those kind of properties, but with much lower weight and less material that&#39;s being used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In the design process, you&#39;re talking about, right? As engineers consider all the different permutations of parts, yeah?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> In the design process — yes, exactly. That&#39;s really the essence of AI, I think, in lots of engineering activities, is that we go from manually deciding first what we want to do, but then actually performing all the different steps. That&#39;s the current way of doing it, while in the AI era, it&#39;s much more about deciding and describing what are the aspects I want to reach to? What are things I want optimized, and what are maybe the boundary conditions? And then the AI helps you get there.</p><p> So in the context of the mechanical parts, you might say, “These are the attachment points. These are the strength and stiffness properties I want. Give me the part with those properties but [make it] as light as possible and also, of course, possible to produce.”</p><p> That could be one area. And also, it is super important for sustainability that we use as little material as possible and also have as low a rate as possible.</p><p> And then, of course, the third point was about [safety]. And, of course, we have autonomous cars, but also, even before that, there are other types of functionality being used. For example, understanding the driver: Is the driver aware or not? Should we maybe nudge him to take a cup of coffee or something if he seems to be tired?</p><p> In the later versions of our cars, we understand if there are some pets or children left in the car, maybe on a hot day, and then preventing them [from getting] hurt in such a situation and so on.</p><p> I&#39;d say that those are some of the areas where AI can really be a core technology in bringing us toward our purpose.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s really interesting because lots of times organizations tell us they start with a problem they&#39;re trying to solve and then find a technology to solve it, and that makes sense, because otherwise you&#39;re trying to find a problem to fit a solution, which seems backward. You mentioned that your cars can sense … if a person or a pet is accidentally left in the car. How did Volvo make the decision to focus on that particular problem to solve?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> A lot of what we do is really created by real-world safety in that we actually see what are the actual causes of people getting injured. I mean, if we take the analogy with crashes and that type of safety, we have teams that go out to sites when there has been a crash to really see what actually happened in reality and not just on certification [from] that type of crash test and so on.</p><p> And, going back to this example, if we look here, pets and kids do get hurt — hopefully not in a Volvo car, but that&#39;s reality, right?</p><p> But what you mentioned there is really super interesting because then it also goes the other way around: Like, now that we have these sensors, what are the other really valuable functionalities that we can provide our customers with through this, of course, taking privacy into account and so on?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is quite intriguing because Volvo … I remember as a child that my uncle used to say, “You want a safe car, you get a Volvo.” And it&#39;s always been synonymous with safety, and it&#39;s really amazing to step back and think about ... for a company who has put one of its main goals for safe experience, now, with the availability of this amount of data and all of this massive amount of processing, I could imagine there are so many use cases that, to Sam&#39;s point, are being thought about. So that&#39;s really, really encouraging.</p><p> What [does] the road map here look like? I mean, is this a constant sort of innovation ideation approach going on to say, “What else could we do in these three pillars of personal, safe, and sustainable?” What is the process for coming up with these ideas and picking up the good ones and pursuing them or not?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think that those ideas can either come from the technology side and be really inspired by that, or it could come from the analytics side. And often it&#39;s when the new technology and the really customer-centric needs … where they meet, and also, of course, where we have the agility in the organization to execute on it. That&#39;s really where we have something that&#39;s really fruitful. It&#39;s typically a mix of different sources of this: innovations and new directions, I would say.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And there&#39;s a mechanism to create this interdisciplinary inspiration in the company?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I would say so. I would say that there are both formal mechanisms but also informal mechanisms. [As] a car company, Volvo Cars is not super big. Of course there are also smaller ones, but I think it&#39;s also an advantage that, I mean, pretty much all the different steps, from product strategy, design, the R&amp;D, engineering, and then the later stages …</p><p> The headquarters is in Gothenburg [in Sweden], within walking distance. The US department is literally 50 meters from where I&#39;m sitting right now, while 50 meters in the other direction, there are the crash test facilities and the safety center.</p><p> So, what I want to say with that is that it&#39;s more easy to get connections and to create this kind of — how should I put it? — informal innovation activities.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> This is where relatively smaller size and colocation really, really helps. To have teams that close to each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It&#39;s funny to talk about it being small, because it&#39;s certainly not a small company.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Everything&#39;s relative, I guess. As we&#39;re chatting, I&#39;m thinking about some of the people we&#39;ve talked to before, and one of the recurring themes that people have mentioned is, oh, this idea [of] starting with a business problem: “You don&#39;t have AI and find a place to use it. You start with a business problem and then solve it.” But this is kind of a nice mix on that — that it sounds like there&#39;s a lot that starts with a business problem, but then, interestingly, once these processes are in place, and once these technologies are in place, then there becomes a grassroots innovation to say, “All right; how can we use that?” And that&#39;s an interesting perspective that, I think, hasn&#39;t come through strongly — or maybe I&#39;m forgetting something — but it seems like that hasn&#39;t come through as strongly. This is a nice mix of that, that maybe works in this size organization … this colocated organization.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, and not least in the prototyping and ideation stages. But, then, of course, before it actually goes into the product, it needs to go through a more thorough review and so on.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> There&#39;s been quite a few investments and acquisitions of smaller AI startups and firms by Volvo. Tell us a bit about the overall ecosystem of internal and vendor and partner companies that come together to bring to life some of these AI-enabled ideas that you&#39;re talking about. Is it internal? Is it external? Is it a mix? How do you think about the ecosystem?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I would definitely say that it&#39;s a mix. Some of the things … we need to do it ourselves to get the full understanding or where we really want to be in the forefront, and [in] some other areas, we definitely want to partner with other companies that are strong in those areas. Traditionally speaking, a car is a super complex product. It has hundreds or thousands of different parts that all need to come together. And, of course, it is a space where there is traditionally a lot of suppliers supplying different parts.</p><p> Lately, we are moving more toward bringing software implementation in-house to increase the speed and agility in the development process.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That seems particularly complicated in auto manufacturing because if I think about how cars got started, they were independent systems. There was a braking system, and a power train system, and an air conditioner, and an infotainment system, and all these were separate. And that&#39;s kind of nice because then we have a certain, different standard than we would have for the infotainment system than we would have for the braking system — or at least I hope that there would be. But what you&#39;re pointing out is, each one of these may be using sensors that come from a different area, and how the whole car has become more complicated independently, but it&#39;s also become more complicated cohesively, trying to connect all these parts and have them work together.</p><p> And that seems, on the one hand, an opportunity for artificial intelligence but, at the same time, a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah. It&#39;s 100% true. It&#39;s both a really big opportunity, but that also means that&#39;s really one of the core challenges — I mean, how to build the cohesive understanding of both the inside and the outside of the car.</p><p> We speak about the customer digital twin and vehicle digital twin and so on, and in some sense, those aspects can mean a lot of different things. But, of course, these different systems that you speak about, they are traditionally in different parts of the company, so that also means that there is a lot of cross-functional collaboration that is needed. But we really need to bridge those kind of organizational borders.</p><p> I think that that&#39;s really one of the key points — that is, in order to get successful adoption of the analytics and AI, it really means that different parts of the company need to work together to make it happen. Because otherwise, it will just become a silo. Some people will not really have the benefits of it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You know, it&#39;s very true. It&#39;s a common theme, and in our work at BCG, we have this rule of thumb — the 10:20:70 — where we say 10% is the data and algorithms, and 20% is the technology and the digital platform, but 70% of it is the business integration and implementation and bringing different parts of the organization together. This, perhaps, is nowhere more true than at a car company, where you have, as you said, Sam, seemingly disparate systems that are coming together to create a bigger system, but each one of these units has been perfected individually, and now you want the collective perfection as well.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we talked a lot about Volvo. How did you personally get interested in artificial intelligence, in data, in technology and analytics? What&#39;s your origin story?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> I think I&#39;ve always been interested in computers. My father was really an addict, so I kind of grew up with that.</p><p> I started out as an engineering student [and got a] master&#39;s in computer science. And then I started off as a research engineer in the medical area, at the university hospital in Gothenburg, then found out fairly quickly that in order to really make use of data — conclusions and so on come from data … so I then went into the area of mathematical statistics.</p><p> So I did a Ph.D. in that, then went back to software product development. After some time, I went back to academia for a couple of years, did a postdoc, and then was offered a good opportunity at Volvo Cars. So I&#39;ve essentially been here for seven years now. That&#39;s a bit of my history.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Quite inspiring.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Anders, we also want to ask you a few rapid-fire questions, and the idea is just to answer it as quickly as you can. These are not particularly Volvo questions.</p><p> What have you been proudest of that you&#39;ve done with artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The problem is that most of the things, I can&#39;t speak about.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer too.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You have to wait and see. OK, well, what worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> The worries?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Oh, I think, of course, one is the longer term — the kind of singularity things. But I think a bit closer to now, so to speak, we definitely see that this super-fast progression of large language [models] and what they can do, and also the kind of systems that don&#39;t just take one problem and give one answer but can really produce a series of steps, in sequence. And that is a super-powerful technology, but a super-powerful technology can be used both for good and for bad.</p><p> That&#39;s both something that makes me super excited but also a little bit worried. What will the world look like in 20 years?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Motorcycling, but obviously using technology. But it&#39;s more of a … yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Technology&#39;s involved. Everything&#39;s involved in technology in some way.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, pretty much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were a kid? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Medical doctor.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, that ties with your first career in working in the medical company, then.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Yeah, I think so, but then I found mathematics and those things to be super exciting, so I went into that area.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What do you hope that we can gain from the advent of these technologies?</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> If we say the greatest wish, I think it is that we find a way to use it in a way for our common good. We need to find a way to integrate it into society, and I think that that is really my biggest wish for it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In a relatively short time, we learned so much about various uses of data, AI, and technology, in just what it takes to build a car in new ways, and all the different ways that AI and tech are helping and serving the people who are driving them. It&#39;s been really enlightening, Anders. Thank you for joining.</p><p> <strong>Anders Sjögren:</strong> Thanks for having me.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Shilpa Prasad, entrepreneur in residence at LG Nova.请加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/fueling-interdisciplinary-innovation-with-ai-volvos-anders-sjogren/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>