<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 12 月 5 日，星期二 12:00:26 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title>数字孪生和安全模拟：雪佛龙的 Ellen Nielsen</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulations-for-safety-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulations-for-safety-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Solutions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Energy Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Ellen Nielsen, Chevron’s first chief data officer, sees data as the common thread throughout a career that has spanned systems, digital data, procurement, and supply chain. In her current role, she applies what she’s learned to Chevron’s wide-ranging AI and machine learning initiatives, including the use of robots and computer vision to inspect tanks, digital [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>雪佛龙第一位首席数据官埃伦·尼尔森 (Ellen Nielsen) 将数据视为贯穿系统、数字数据、采购和供应链的整个职业生涯的共同主线。在目前的职位上，她将所学到的知识应用到雪佛龙广泛的人工智能和机器学习计划中，包括使用机器人和计算机视觉来检查储罐，使用数字孪生来模拟操作，以及使用传感器来监控炼油厂的设备。</p><p>在本期《<cite>我、我自己和人工智能</cite>》播客中，艾伦分享了这家石化巨头在机器学习和生成人工智能方面的用例示例，她描述了该公司的公民发展计划，该计划将安全可靠的人工智能和机器学习工具置于整个雪佛龙员工的手中。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E5-Nielsen-Chevron-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="艾伦·尼尔森"></p><h4>艾伦·尼尔森，雪佛龙</h4><p>艾伦·尼尔森 (Ellen Nielsen) 是雪佛龙公司的首席数据官，她专注于创建与价值链思维相结合的以数据为导向的文化。作为多学科领导者，尼尔森在 IT、数字、数据、采购和供应链领域拥有 30 多年的全球高管经验。她曾与石油和天然气、快速消费品、汽车、制造、零售、银行和保险领域的行业领导者合作。</p><p> Nielsen 经常在行业活动中发表演讲，并获得了众多奖项和认可，包括入选<cite>CDO 杂志</cite>2023 年全球数据力量女性名单。她还在 2023 年 DataIQ 100 美国数据领域最具影响力人物排行榜上排名第五。</p><p>她还担任多个董事会成员，包括 PIDX（石油工业数据交换）国际委员会和数据与人工智能女性领袖委员会。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>数字孪生？工程领域的生成式人工智能？在今天的节目中，了解一家石化公司如何系统地提高员工技能，以从生成式人工智能等新技术中受益。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我是来自雪佛龙的艾伦·尼尔森，你们正在听的是<cite>我、我自己和人工智能</cite>。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p>大家好。今天，萨姆和我正在与雪佛龙首席数据官埃伦·尼尔森进行交谈。艾伦，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。欢迎来到节目。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>谢谢你邀请我。我很高兴今天能进行一次非常有趣的谈话。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>让我们开始吧。我想我们的大多数听众——事实上，他们所有人——都听说过雪佛龙，但他们可能不知道人工智能在雪佛龙整个价值链中的流行程度。那么请告诉我们一些关于您的角色以及雪佛龙如何使用人工智能的信息。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>也许是在谈论我的角色……它始于三年前。我是雪佛龙公司的第一位数据官。这并不意味着我们[已经]处理数据很长一段时间了，但是需要更多地关注数据的需求开始出现，因此，我的任务是传播数据——驱动决策，当然，包括一路上的任何类型的数据科学/分析。看到它随着时间的推移而增长是非常非常有趣的。</p><p>我们在很多地方都使用人工智能。我们使用机器人的某些领域——例如今天的储罐检查——你可以想象，如果有人参与，那是非常麻烦的。现在我们用机器人来做这件事。我们基本上将人类带出这些有限的空间，这是计算机视觉的结合——拍摄图像、比较图像——并[做出]预测该坦克和设备的状态。生锈了吗？是否需要维护？我们是否需要以一种非常有预测性的方式来解决这个问题，以便它在未来以更加可靠和安全的方式运行？</p><p>另一个例子是，当我们谈论压缩机或任何类型设备中的传感器时，过去我们当然会安装它们，但这些传感器和数据收集的价格大幅下降，我最近才看到……实际上，它是一个已经创建的公民开发应用程序，因为这些传感器必须安装，安装时基本上是拿一个二维码，一键点击就可以将地理空间位置添加到传感器中，然后您可以在地图上看到您的设施中安装的所有这些传感器，因此您实际上可以看到……正在发生的事情以及该设备是否实际工作以及已在那里盘点哪些传感器。因此，我们在这里结合了计算机视觉、利用公民发展，然后，当然，以机器学习、基于人工智能的方式使用传感器来进行预测及其工作方式。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我知道你们做得很好的一件事就是数字孪生。也许你可以对这个例子发表一些评论。</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen：</strong>数字孪生是我们使用它的众多例子之一。是什么触发[一个]进行数字孪生？一是，你可以想象我们有人在现场，所以我们想让他们的生活更轻松、更安全。这意味着我们收集的有关现场资产以及如何操作它们的数据和信息越多，将有助于实现更安全、更可靠的运营。这是一个触发因素。</p><p>第二个触发因素是，您收集了大量基于物联网、[工业]物联网设备、传感器等的信息，并将这些信息输入到另一个信息池中，您甚至可以在这些资产中做出预测性决策。因此，通过数字孪生，我们基本上希望同时服务于这两点：我们希望变得更安全、可靠，但也希望我们所做的事情更具预测性，从而提高效率并在正确的时间做正确的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您能给我们举一个使用数字孪生的具体例子吗？这对安全有何帮助？这对提高效率有何帮助？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>如果你采用数字孪生，那么你基本上可以“数字孪生”一个设施，一个炼油厂……所以在炼油厂中，你可以想象有很多管道，有很多设备，有压缩机，还有发电机——有些东西非常机械地工作，人们必须维护它们才能生产出产品。</p><p>当你看到从产品进来或材料进来到产品出来的价值链时，这之间的一切都经过这个炼油厂。如果一切都实现了数字孪生，您就可以更好地规划、更好地运营。您知道事情何时发生。您可以更好地预测如何获得更好的输出。这基本上就是我们在我们运营的炼油厂或设施中所做的事情——真正关注信息流和数据驱动的决策。</p><p>我们总是用信息来推动决策，你知道吗？过去，信息更多地存在于经验丰富的人的头脑中，当然，有时会通过设备信息进行增强，但可能更多的是手动收集或将东西放在一起，而通过数字孪生，我们可以信息触手可及，推动这一目标的实现。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个很好的例子。我想长期听众都会知道我和谢尔文都是化学工程师。但你可能不知道——好吧，我不再是一名化学工程师，部分原因是我对模拟化学过程的想法如此着迷。我们发现我们不必构建一个小流程来测试某些东西；只需构建一个小流程即可。我们可以在计算机上构建它并进行测试。你知道，那是很久以前的事了，那时候的工具真的很丑陋。我猜你比这更老练——或者我希望你更老练。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我认为这是一个不断发展的领域，但我对这些机会感到非常兴奋。我可以想象，你知道，当你有催化剂或者你必须测试原材料时，你必须与生产负责人一起计划，你必须停止生产，你必须实时测试它。这带走了产出。</p><p>现在，您可以通过更有效的方式进行模拟，并且规格在您手边，而不再需要进行实际操作。我也在世界上，在我以前的公司里，我们必须一遍又一遍地测试东西，甚至是在实验室里进行物理测试。我认为[那些]时代[大部分]已经结束了。它以更好的方式变得更加模拟。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Ellen，您能给我们另一个例子吗？也许是关于勘探或开采，或者在没有数据和人工智能的情况下过去也非常需要经验、昂贵且危险的事情？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我认为我们还有一个很好的例子，实际上是公司在去年年底发布的。当您想到石油和天然气时，您会想到如何从储层中获取更多资源？您希望以非常高效、负责任的方式充分利用水库。在收集数据方面，你可以想象，如果你没有计算机能力，也没有以数字方式掌握手头的数据，这是相当麻烦的。我无法想象过去人们是如何做到的。他们可能正在打印一些东西并将其放在上面，并根据他们的经验提出假设 - 当然他们获得了很多经验。现在我们通过机器学习和算法来做到这一点。我们了解岩石的成分是怎样的。我们甚至创建了一个“岩石百科全书”来了解不同的岩石条件和成分，以便我们每天在需要时都可以利用这些数据。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，我认为有一个更大的主题，随着这些技术的出现，天空是极限，所以问题是，你还能如何应用它，你还能用它做什么？我认为这让我想到了一个关于使命和目的的问题，因为显然有大量的数据。显然有很多工具。用例是由任务以及我们想要做的一些事情驱动的。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的。实际上，我会将雪佛龙的这一点与我们的战略联系起来。我们安全地实现更高的回报和更低的碳排放。这是我们的指导原则：我们所做的一切当然应该有利于公司的成功、公司的影响，而且还要在低碳环境下进行。我们知道几十年后世界将有所不同。我们关注甲烷，我们关注温室气体排放，我们关注我们的整体碳足迹。所以这是我们一直在解决的问题。数据和人工智能发挥着各自的作用，同时也影响着我们的运营方式和安全运营方式。安全是雪佛龙价值体系的重要组成部分。当你思考未来并思考人工智能、机器人和数字孪生以及所有这些时，我们可以通过技术帮助我们的员工以更好的方式和新的方式更安全、更可靠地完成工作将来。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>对于雪佛龙或一家主要是工程和科学公司的公司来说，我感兴趣的是人工智能被投入生产以增强工人、工程师和科学家正在做出的一些决策和一些见解。但作为一名工程师，作为这些工厂的操作员，我可能不太同意这一点。我不知道这是否引起共鸣：如何让科学家和工程师轻松地使用这些工具？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>嗯嗯。我认为这实际上很有帮助，因为工程师有非常逻辑的思维方式，他们了解科学，而且我们公司有很多科学人员。所以当你谈论数据科学及其背后的东西时，我们有很多人对学习数据科学非常感兴趣，我们也会说我们已经开始提供教育。所以我想，“我从哪里开始？”你从学习开始：“嘿，我不明白这个。”这是典型的工程思维：“我不明白；我不明白”。我想理解它。我正在寻找“它告诉我什么？”它如何影响我的解决方案？”</p><p>我们[拥有]数字奖学金计划已经有一段时间了。事实上，我们和麻省理工学院一起做这件事，我们有一批人在那里工作了一年，而且他们不是来自一个院系；而是来自麻省理工学院。他们真的是从整个公司走出来，在一年内完成设计工程硕士学位，这确实是一件很难做到的事情。但他们回来后了解了新技术，了解了……我们如何以不同的方式使用它。他们是第一个回到正常环境的人，并影响并基本上让其他人利用他们的知识参与进来，并冒险尝试他们以前从未尝试过的不同事物。所以影响文化是一回事。</p><p>第二件事：在数据科学领域，我们开始与莱斯大学合作。我们有一个为期六、七个月的计划，也在整个公司范围内进行，不仅让 IT 人员了解数据科学的含义，而且让他们将其带回到自己的环境中。所以他们并没有完全离开自己的角色。他们在六个月、七个月后离开，然后以尽可能最好的方式回来影响公司：“嘿，什么是可能的？”</p><p>最后一部分可能是最广泛的方法，因为我们称之为<em>公民发展</em>。我们相信，随着人工智能的发展，公司里很多很多人现在都掌握了事情。我们刚刚看到新一代人工智能现在掌握在……每个想要它的人手中。通过这种整体公民发展，我们希望将这项变得更加容易的技术带给许多人，以便他们能够使用它。当然，他们为此需要数据，这就是我们在这些系统中提供数据的原因——以提高自我效率。所以我想说，有一种三管齐下的方法来影响文化、领导力，而且我们在人工智能公民发展方面有非常好的[使用]案例。我们还公开讨论了我们所做的某些用例。我认为这就是文化。进入公司的每条动脉需要一段时间，但我觉得公司现在真的很兴奋沿着这条路走下去。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我喜欢你所说的是，[你]实际上加倍了公司以工程和科学为主的文化，并使之成为科学、工程和人工智能之间的跨学科合作，而不是任何其他公司这些相互替换。这是一个<em>and</em> ，而不是一个<em>or</em> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>有没有一个具体的例子，有人参加了这些为期七个月的项目或数字学者项目，并带回了一些改变、产生了影响的东西？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的，当然。所以我们有很多，因为我认为我们已经进入这个领域两三年了，当然，他们把它带回来并解决了几个问题。有时我们甚至在实习时也会遇到这种情况；两三周后，他们认识到他们可以解决他们正在思考的规划问题……而且它相当复杂，但有了新的观点、数据和人工智能，结果确实令人惊叹。</p><p>实际上，我们有人也影响了我们领域的规划——领域开发——并创建了一个低代码环境，这确实打破了我们的工作方式，并真正改变了我们的工作方式。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>在提高公司生产力、效率、确保安全、确保以各种不同形式造福于人类、社区、环境和物种方面，挑战是什么？有什么难的？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我想说肯定有一些具有挑战性的部分。这是一项早期技术，尤其是新一代人工智能。事情进展得非常快。所以，具有挑战性的是，无论你今天做什么，三个月后可能会有所不同。具有挑战性的部分是，您不能以过去的方式工作。也许你必须更快地转向。这并不是说你要构建一个解决方案。我想一家公司告诉我他们构建了一个解决方案，六个月后，如果他们现在再次构建它，他们会采取完全不同的方式。所以当你——我称之为可能把鸡蛋放在篮子里时，你必须注意。您必须考虑哪种用例的正确时机并弄清楚这一点，因为您不想在技术仍处于这种发展阶段时将自己锁定。这是我们所关注的。</p><p>第二件事是，在安全性或以正确方式处理数据方面，并非所有问题都在生成人工智能中得到解决。那只是……技术还没有准备好。目前还没有解决方案。你可以构建一种沙箱或某种围栏环境，但你必须自己围栏。我认为超大规模企业，比如微软等，我认为他们也在努力在正常环境中调整这些用例，在那里你可以有一个授权流程，在那里你有多余的流程，你如何管理和以正确的方式进行管理。所以我想说，这仍然是缺失的。</p><p>我非常希望这能很快关闭，但今天，你必须采用不同的技术。如果它是一个矢量数据库——我们将在这里谈论一点技术语言——它还没有准备好在非常广泛的范围内非常安全地使用。你必须想象，如果你有一家公司，就可以共享哪些信息、不应该共享哪些信息等等方面都有权利。我们认为这是一个挑战。</p><p>我想提到的第三个挑战是政策制定者，你知道。因此，我们通过负责任的人工智能密切关注这一点。我们是 Responsible AI Institute 的成员，并且非常仔细地关注那里发生的事情。什么样的政策即将出台？我们如何负责任地将其纳入我们的运营、人工智能模型的产品化中？当然，这就是进化。它不是你可以购买和运行的东西。是的，我们将看到公司如何填补这些空白。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Ellen，您能否评论一下生成式人工智能，以及它是否以及如何被使用或计划使用？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的，绝对是。我们已经关注生成式人工智能两年左右了，也许更长一点。我们对事态的发展并不完全感到惊讶。也许你可以说，“好吧，ChatGTP 什么时候来？”这可能让每个人都感到惊讶——它来得如此之快。但我们正在关注这一点，并且已经在一种创新的沙箱环境中做了一些用例，看看会发生什么。当它问世时，我们说：“好吧，这是新技术。我们想了解它。我们将它交到人们手中并使用它，然后了解遥测‘我们用它做什么，它如何产生共鸣？’”</p><p>在五月/六月，我们决定组建一个更专注的团队来开展这些活动，现在我们有数百个用例正在酝酿中，我们会筛选出最突出的用例并进行处理。但在技术方面，我想说，我们确实非常了解正在发生的事情，并且有非常聪明的人在研究它。</p><p>我可以告诉你我自己的用例。我用它来写下来。您可以与您的主管或您的团队讨论是否撰写绩效协议。您检查必须做的演示文稿或文档，以真正优化写作。我知道我的团队正在使用它，因为我们正在思考产品开发、产品管理和产品组合管理。所以在过去，他们需要更长的时间来写下他们的想法，我和我的一位团队成员交谈，她说：“你知道，在过去，我可能花了一两周的时间。现在我只需要一个小时就能完成这件事。”因此，在该领域使用 ChatGTP 可以提高效率。</p><p>当我们查看其他示例时，您可以想象我们拥有知识数据库。我们拥有系统工程方面的知识以及公司内部广泛提供的其他信息。在过去，如果您想知道这个生成器是如何工作的，您基本上必须输入搜索条件，然后最终找到文档，并且必须阅读该文档。或者这个文件还不够；你需要另一份文件。好的，你找到第二个文档，然后你基本上完成你的答案，然后你返回[并]基本上执行它。</p><p>我们创建了一个聊天系统，您可以[更轻松地]与此类信息进行协作并更快地解决问题。所以这可能是两个——也许还有一个是关于日常事务的，还有一个可能与我们在系统方法中的工作方式有关。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果我结合您的一些想法，我会发现一些困难。早些时候，您谈到了公民开发人员以及将大量这些工具交到人们手中的想法。后来，您谈到了安全和策略问题，这些问题还不是基础设施的一部分。从历史上看，安全总是遵循功能。我们首先关心功能，然后关心安全性。因此，我们面临着公民开发者工具的广泛扩散和基础设施护栏或政策的薄弱，以及对无法快速跟进的担忧。这些似乎可能会撞在一起并造成很大的紧张。你如何导航？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的，我想说也许我们必须谈谈一般的人工智能，然后是生成式人工智能。因此，当我谈论政策制定者时，这更多的是生成式人工智能的观点。</p><p>当你考虑公民发展时，我们有模型或算法。我们已经证明了[他们]；我们已经保护了[他们]。他们遵循了审查流程。我们从负责任的人工智能方面对它们进行了检查。因此，任何想要使用它的公民开发人员都可以使用它们。所以它们是安全的，而且它们实际上在我们安全的环境中。所以您已经可以从那里开始并确保安全。但是，新一代人工智能的新技术，以及这些大型语言模型和大型语言模型学习背后的数据，可能还没有准备好纳入公民发展的角度。因此，为了清楚地说明这一点，当我谈论公民发展时，一切——安全的东西、那里的遥测、那里的空间——我们都确保我们在做正确的事情。这可供公司中的每个人使用。</p><p>其他可能还不安全的东西，我们不会将其放入系统中。我们正在等待。因此，我们不能在我们的公民发展计划中只承担没有保障的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>是的，这在公民数据传输和数据科学家无法构建的想法之间带来了很好的区别。 ......有一个持续的策划过程。听起来您在管理过程中非常积极地决定向公民开发人员提供哪些工具以及您仍在调查和保护哪些工具。这就说得通了。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的，就是这样；确切地。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>雪佛龙显然是一家全球性的大型石化公司。每个人都知道。而你是首席数据官。你是怎么到达那里的？请告诉我们一些您的历史。你是如何担任这个角色的？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>是的，我很高兴担任这个角色。这是一个我一直充满热情的超级令人兴奋的领域。当你关注我职业生涯的开始时，我来自德国。我获得了系统工程学位，然后涉足数字数据领域——后来又涉足采购和供应链。我认为贯穿我整个职业生涯的大红线是数据部分，但当然是以不同的方式。所以可以说，当我涉足供应链时，你要从第三方收购的公司那里处理很多钱。你是如何组织的？关于如何做到这一点，有大量的数据、思考和战略思考。我想说我是一个学习者。我是一个谦虚的学习者。我喜欢拥抱新事物和非常多样化的观点，以实现公司的最佳发展，也许我进入这个职位只是巧合，因为当我五年前加入雪佛龙时，我开始从事采购领域，因为我有一个采购部门我称之为数据数字腿。</p><p>我们立即处理数据，因为数据不足以推动这些决策，也许前两年证明我在“这是可能的”方面是正确的。我也坚信数据和人工智能将无处不在。因此，这是一个令人兴奋的空间，值得进入、学习并了解接下来会发生什么。</p><p>所以我很高兴能在那里。事实上，一位前高管说，当我对他说——不是在雪佛龙——“我对职业生涯中拥有的所有机会感到非常幸运”时，他说，“艾伦，你并不幸运。”于是他寄给我一本书；你基本上会调整你的道路，所以你对事情持开放态度，即使你认为它不在你的直接轨迹上，但它确实提高了你的技能以及你如何连接点。我喜欢把这些点串联起来，这就是我喜欢这个角色的原因。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个很棒的故事。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>好的，这是我们提出的一系列快速问题。请告诉我们您想到的第一件事。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>这也许是一个快速约会的问题。好的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您认为目前人工智能最大的机会是什么？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>医疗保健。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>取代人类。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您想要的第一个职业是什么？你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我不想坐在办公桌前。我失败了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>人工智能在我们的日常生活中得到了广泛的应用。什么时候人工智能太多了？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我想说，如果人工智能引导我走向错误的方向，并以不基于真实事实的方式影响我，那么人工智能就太过分了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我的车里已经有太多的人工智能，因为我无法打开车库，因为它可以识别我在哪里以及必须打开哪个东西，如果它不起作用，我就无法进入。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我喜欢这个。我们这里有一个非常智能的家，配有各种语音识别电子设备、车库门开启器、洒水器、启动器等等。但是，我想说，这有助于提高效率，如果网络出现故障，现在真的很难，你知道吗？</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。最后一个问题：你希望人工智能现在能做但它不能做的一件事是什么？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>嗯；治愈癌症。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>非常好。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>似乎每周都会有一个头条新闻说这种新的人工智能将解决癌症，然后你回头看，这些似乎都没有成功。我并不是说我们应该停止尝试，但这始终是一个例子，而且似乎永远不会到达那里。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>但这也是一个随机过程，对吧？我的意思是，如果你有足够的尝试，对吗？由于人工智能和我们的实验能力，我们肯定会尝试更多的事情。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>我的回答可能略有不同吗？所以我认为另一件事是人工智能可能无法做到的事情，这将是伟大的，它确实可以帮助我们解决气候转型，解决我们在这个星球上面临的气候问题。我认为它在这里和那里都有帮助，但如果它能提供更多帮助那就太棒了。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>但与此同时，我认为我们不能放弃，只是希望机器能够解决我们造成的问题。我认为这需要我们双方共同努力。没关系;这是希望的一部分。</p><p>人工智能有什么让您感到兴奋的吗？您现在最兴奋的下一件事情是什么？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>嗯，好问题。我认为我们想要改善我们的生活，而且我认为我现在居住的地方，我们非常荣幸。我们在很多方面已经存在人工智能过剩，你知道吗？我们刚刚谈到了这一点——在我们的智能家居和汽车等领域——但这并不适用于世界上的每个人。如果这些进步和好处能够[更广泛地]获得，那就太好了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，你没有问我，Sam，但我完全同意。我的意思是，我认为当你考虑教育及其对贫困社区和国家的影响时，他们不再需要建立学校。你可以做很多事情，帮助很多人学习、发展和培养通常依赖于基础设施、人员和教师等的技能。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你可能会认为我会受到威胁，但我一点也没有。我的意思是，我认为这是我们最大的机会。我们有这么多人……我的意思是，我们无法让他们全部通过教育计划，而且我们的教育计划并不是特别优化或快速。如果我们能够解决这个问题并从我们的大脑中获得更好的资源，那么这将是一个巨大的胜利。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森：</strong>嘿，山姆，我可以问你一个问题吗？我知道我现在扭转了这个局面，但如果你认为知识的保质期正在缩短，对吧，最近有一些关于它的文章，也许你今天学到的东西可能值得四五年，然后就有点过时了。那么您认为这将如何在教育系统中发展？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这很大，因为我考虑了这一点。我的意思是，我教机器学习和AI课，我敏锐地意识到，除非他们在学期毕业，否是短暂的。我们已经看到了这一发展的速度。我认为这促使我们退后一步并更高。如果我们进入教学工具，教授如何单击“文件”，如何单击“新”，如何单击“打开”，如何单击“保存”，那是非常低级别的技能。当我们考虑我们应该教什么样的东西时，我的意思是，我的大学是一所文科大学，我认为这很重要，因为如果我们考虑在文科世界中教授技术技能，我认为这很重要。我们拥有21世纪最性感的工作是数据科学。 [关于]下一个，[[]对我来说尚不清楚数据科学涉及。并不是说数据科学并不重要。它正迅速被商品化。</p><p>因此，我们拥有诸如哲学之类的东西，这些东西变得越来越重要，道德规范，随着数据科学的成本下降，这些事情变得越来越重要。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>语言学。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>语言学，是的。就这样吧。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>大语言模型，正确。精彩的。艾伦，非常感谢。这是如此有见地，我们感谢您的时间。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>是的，谢谢。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>感谢您的调整。在我们的下一集中，我和Shervin与[MARS]毅力机器人操作的首席工程师和NASA喷气推进实验室的副经理Vandi Verma一起冒险使用AI。请加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德（Allison Ryder）：</strong>感谢您听<cite>我，我自己和AI的话</cite>。我们相信，像您一样，关于AI实施的对话不会开始并停止此播客。这就是为什么我们专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个专门为LinkedIn创建组的原因。它称为领导者的AI，如果您加入我们，您可以与表演创作者和主持人聊天，提出自己的问题，分享您的见解，并从<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和BCG获得有关AI实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">MITSMR.com/aiforleleders</a>访问它。我们将在展示笔记中放置该链接，我们希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulation-for-safety-chevrons-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为您的员工打造更好的盟友</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ayse Karaevli and Serden Özcan. <p>Ayse Karaevli 是 WHU-Otto Beisheim 管理学院企业管理和变革系主任，Serden Özcan 是创新和企业转型系主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors used ESG data from Refinitiv to analyze workforce controversies in Germany’s top 50 companies that were significant enough to gain media attention over the past 10 years. They calculated an average score for each company, taking workforce size into account, and identified the companies in the top and bottom [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Karaevli-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼尔·韦伯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者使用 Refinitiv 的 ESG 数据分析了德国 50 强公司中的劳动力争议，这些争议在过去 10 年中足以引起媒体关注。</li><li>他们考虑到劳动力规模，计算了每家公司的平均分，并确定了最高和最低四分位的公司，表明与劳动力相关的争议的最高和最低水平。</li><li>为了深入了解排名靠前和垫底的公司的决策和治理流程以及这些流程的结果，他们对外部董事、现任和前任高管以及员工代表进行了深入的半结构化访谈。</li></ul></aside><p>在经济不确定性、供应链重组和新一波自动化浪潮的背景下，曾经大量招聘的企业现在面临大幅裁员。许多公司正在取消由疫情引发的灵活工作安排。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>与此同时，员工越来越希望看到自己的价值观和优先事项体现在公司的运营方式中。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>自疫情爆发以来，许多人正在重新划定工作与个人生活之间的界限，以保护自己的福祉。</p><p>这些趋势加剧了美国工人和企业领导人之间的紧张关系，导致信任逐渐削弱，关系日益紧张。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>我们可以直接从劳动力争议的兴起中看到这一点，例如罢工和其他有关工资、工作条件、多样性、平等机会、健康和安全的争议；以及间接地通过员工脱离。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p></p><p>除了造成代价高昂的运营中断和降低工作质量之外，劳工争议和离职还给企业吸引和留住人才带来了重大挑战。此外，此类争议阻碍了公司应对网络安全、数字化和可持续发展等业务挑战的能力，这些挑战需要员工保持警惕并与员工合作。</p><p>我们对德国 50 强上市公司的分析表明，尽管长期以来一直有让员工参与公司董事会的传统，但管理层管理劳动力纠纷和促进员工敬业度的能力却各不相同。我们发现董事会的结构和组成与其有效性关系不大；相反，对于减少冲突最重要的是最高管理层和董事会领导人在多大程度上积极让员工参与关键战略决策。 （参见“研究”。）我们采访了经历过较少劳动力争议的公司的主要利益相关者。通过与一系列行业的董事会董事、首席执行官、首席财务官和员工代表的对话，我们确定了领导者用来包容员工的三种策略：确定共同目标和利益，促进包容性决策流程，并赋予员工战略责任。</p><p>这些战略促进最高管理层领导者、外部董事和员工在关键问题上的积极合作，同时促进三个群体之间的信任。 （参见“避免劳动力争议的三种策略。”） </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>避免劳动力争议的三项策略</h4><p class="caption">当公司关注员工和领导者的共同利益，让员工参与决策，并赋予员工与高级管理人员一起制定业务战略的责任时，他们可以提高参与度并减少劳动力争议。 </p><p style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MAG_Karaevli_Figure-1.png" width="80%" alt="避免劳动力争议的三项策略"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>采用这些战略的领导者可以更有效地解决广泛的战略问题，包括商业模式转型、重组、并购、撤资、分拆、技术采用、环境可持续性和社会问题。同时，为解决问题奠定坚实的基础，可以为员工加入管理层创造价值奠定基础。</p><p>任何地区的公司都可以利用这些好处，即使它们缺乏让员工参与决策的正式结构（例如董事会代表）。虽然研究重点是在董事会中拥有员工代表的公司，但在文章末尾，我们将解释没有这种结构的公司如何将这些策略纳入其现有的决策流程。</p><h3> 1. 确定共同目标和利益</h3><p>企业领导者常常忽视这样一个事实，即员工对公司的长期成功至关重要——毕竟，他们的生计以及未来的安全往往都依赖于公司。但我们样本中劳动力争议最少的公司认识到并利用了员工利益与组织利益之间的内在联系。这些公司的领导者努力确定共同目标，并专注于如何以解决管理层和员工担忧的方式实现这些目标。他们没有将潜在冲突视为两个对立双方之间的谈判，而是将此类情况视为需要解决的共同问题。在此过程中，他们形成了寻找解决方案的共同主人翁意识和责任感。</p><p>而且，这些公司偏离了让人力资源主管主要负责与员工沟通的传统做法。在我们研究的公司中，首席执行官和首席财务官直接与员工董事会代表接触，解释可能有争议的决策背后的理由，然后再将这些决策提交给全体董事会。阿迪达斯前首席执行官、美国和欧洲多家公司董事会董事赫伯特·海纳表示，首席执行官公开透明的沟通可以为员工提供更广泛的决策背景，并帮助他们与公司目标保持一致。</p><p>风力涡轮机制造商 Nordex 董事会主席、半导体制造商英飞凌科技公司前首席执行官沃尔夫冈·齐巴特 (Wolfgang Ziebart) 建议强调，如果董事会成员、最高管理层领导人和员工代表只关注自己集团的权利和议程，可能会产生后果。 “从长远来看，每个人都会遭受损失，”他观察到。</p><p>工业工程和钢铁制造集团蒂森克虏伯的重组工作说明了缺乏连贯的沟通策略时所产生的影响。 2019年，为了应对蒂森克虏伯竞争行业的全球变化，首席执行官玛蒂娜·梅尔茨制定了一项雄心勃勃的计划，其中包括出售电梯制造、船舶系统和钢铁三大核心业务。经过充分讨论，董事会和员工代表同意了该方案。</p><p>蒂森克虏伯在2020年以204亿美元剥离了电梯业务。随后出售钢铁部门的努力失败了。尽管管理层在两年多的时间里为钢铁和船舶部门探索了一系列选择，包括出售、政府股权合作和首次公开募股（IPO），但他们从未向董事会提出具体计划。</p><p>这种模糊性阻碍了员工代表评估和解决员工的担忧，他们的挫败感引起了董事会的共鸣。在 2023 年 3 月发给蒂森克虏伯 10 万名员工的备忘录中，员工代表批评管理层缺乏远见且浪费时间。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>一周后，默茨辞职。四个月后，首席财务官宣布合同到期打算离职。</p><p>蒂森克虏伯的员工并没有抵制重组。相反，他们希望看到公司成功适应行业变化。他们支持最初的计划，尽管数万名工人将受到影响——仅钢铁部门就有 26,000 名工人受到影响。他们并没有撤回对这一目标的支持。管理层未能与员工沟通和参与，引发了争议。</p><p>相比之下，当金融服务提供商安联改变其核心业务模式时，公司领导者确保员工理解并被改变​​背后的原因及其时机所说服。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>该组织各个级别的领导者都参与了沟通工作，包括业务转型和战略劳动力规划的全球负责人、安联集团在 30 个国家的公司的首席执行官以及这些公司内运营实体的领导者。他们解释了这种转变对员工意味着什么，包括在新的业务模式下当前和未来的角色会是什么样子。他们还提供了变革过程的时间表，以及具体的里程碑以及如何评估它们。</p><p></p><p>这种方法使公司领导者获得了安联董事会员工代表的重要支持，这对于成功推出重新配置的组织、产品和服务至关重要。</p><p>当公司与员工沟通并让他们参与有关敏感问题的决策时，即使一项举措没有成功，他们也会赢得他们的信任。欧洲最大的工业制造公司西门子的长期员工董事哈拉尔德·科恩 (Harald Kern) 讲述了西门子移动与飞机制造商庞巴迪之间的拟议合并。西门子的员工代表发现，快速理解管理层的意图并预测对公司及其员工的影响具有挑战性。为了帮助他们了解合并决策背后的动机，管理层利用行业分析师的见解补充了公司信息。</p><p>最终，外部因素阻碍了合并。但科恩表示，管理层对公开对话和共享资源的承诺巩固了员工对西门子领导层的信任。</p><p></p><h3> 2. 促进包容性决策过程</h3><p>企业领导者通常优先考虑结果而不是实现结果的方式。然而，我们发现，在决策时采取刻意措施将员工纳入其中的公司，所遇到的劳动力争议较少。</p><p> 2020年，西门子剥离了能源业务，该部门拥有近10万名员工，占公司销售额的40%。在关于董事会决定的初步讨论中，员工代表提出了在这种不确定情况下常见的担忧，例如潜在的工作不安全感和员工角色的变化。管理层不仅回应了这些担忧，还分享了有关能源部门面临的战略和财务挑战的信息。随着员工获得更深入的了解，他们开始将分拆视为最可行的解决方案，并且流程后期阶段发生冲突的可能性显着减少。西门子能源公司工会主席罗伯特·肯斯博克表示，“虽然存在风险，但增长机会胜过风险。” <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p>通过从一开始就让员工参与，西门子管理层不仅获得了他们的支持，而且随着计划的展开，对业务运营有了更深入的了解。员工们提出了提高效率并将节省的成本重新分配给员工培训的建议。</p><p>此外，他们建议并倡导将一家专门建造石油和燃气轮机的工厂转变为一个创新中心，专注于为使用可再生能源的工厂开发发电和输电技术。首次公开募股后，该工厂推出了开创性的创新技术，为西门子能源公司赢得了全国赞誉，并使该公司成为可再生能源行业的领导者。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p></p><p>在我们研究的这个案例和其他案例中，董事会的行为（从主席开始）既为员工的参与奠定了基调，也决定了员工的参与方式。一位具有重组经验的受访者表示，当董事会主席积极邀请员工批评管理计划、保持开放的心态并寻求了解他们的观点时，员工就更有可能接受、理解并有效应对重组过程中的挑战。多个行业的公司。另一位曾在多个德国董事会任职、曾任高盛国际非执行董事的受访者强调，这种做法应该得到所有股东代表的认可，而不仅仅是董事会主席。</p><p>此外，我们的采访表明，劳动力争议最少的公司的董事会主席会采取措施，确保所有员工感到舒适和受到尊重，并确保他们的贡献得到平等重视。我们的受访者指出了员工代表在董事会中占有一席之地的公司的一些有效做法，包括以下内容：</p><ul><li>按字母顺序排列董事的座位，以防止轻易识别他们各自作为股东或员工代表的角色。</li><li>或者，定期轮换席位，以便在每次董事会会议上，员工代表坐在不同的股东董事旁边。</li><li>指导新员工代表，让他们感到舒适并学习如何在董事会审议过程中保持高效。</li><li>指定股东董事作为导师，指导员工董事会技能的发展。</li></ul><p>董事会主席可能会更进一步，要求每位股东董事每三到六个月与两名员工代表共进午餐或晚餐，从而为董事会外的非正式讨论创造机会。我们采访的一位董事会主席举办节日晚宴等社交活动，以营造更具包容性的氛围。我们的采访表明，这些做法提高了董事会成员之间的社会凝聚力，否则他们自然不会花时间相互了解。</p><p>空客公司非执行董事 Stephan Gemkow 表示，当董事会承诺让员工参与关键决策时，整个决策过程就会变得更加协作。主席不是围绕由股东成员或管理层的优先事项驱动的严格议程来构建董事会活动，而是成为鼓励公开讨论、邀请不同观点并营造所有成员积极贡献的环境的促进者。 Gemkow 表示，这种方法对于发现复杂战略问题的创新解决方案是必要的，例如如何解决重组期间的裁员问题。</p><h3> 3.赋予员工战略责任</h3><p>我们的研究表明，劳动力争议较少的公司通过在正式委员会和非正式渠道赋予员工代表战略性角色和责任，努力缩小员工、领导层和股东代表之间的权力差距。</p><p>董事会委员会是行动的所在地。成员对其领域内的问题进行严格的研究和分析，与组织中的关键人物会面，并为全体董事会提出行动建议。他们有权制定董事会议程并影响其决策。</p><p>在德国公司治理框架下，董事会在任命员工代表进入委员会时拥有很大的自主权。我们发现，在董事会委员会任职的员工代表比例与公司面临的劳动力争议数量之间存在直接关系。</p><p>在过去五年没有发生过劳动力争议的公司中，董事会委员会中平均有 70% 的员工代表。相比之下，在这段时间内面临五次或更多争议的公司，董事会委员会中的员工代表平均只有 38%。此外，当除了主要关注员工或非战略事务的委员会之外，将员工代表分配到财务或技术等战略董事会委员会时，公司遇到的劳动力争议也会大大减少。</p><p>在我们的分析中得分最高且劳动力争议最少的公司包括物流提供商 DHL、电信运营商德国电信和软件制造商 SAP。在这三家公司中，绝大多数员工代表都在董事会委员会中任职：DHL 为 80%，SAP 为 89%，德国电信为 100%。除了专注的审计和人事委员会之外，他们还是财务和投资、技术和创新、战略和可持续发展等战略委员会的成员。</p><p>相比之下，大众汽车和汉莎航空是我们研究期间劳动力争议最多的公司之一。在大众汽车，只有一半的员工代表在董事会委员会任职，而在汉莎航空，这一比例为 40%。此外，在每家公司，员工代表主要在审计等战略性较低的委员会中任职。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p>当员工代表在数量更多、范围更广的委员会中任职时，他们会对公司的整体战略和财务要求有更深入的了解。他们不仅可以有效影响决策，还可以承担更大的执行决策的责任。</p><p>这种安排通过提高透明度和客观性来促进健康的制衡。他们还确保股东董事在考虑管理层决策时从员工那里获得有关管理层决策潜在长期影响的第一手信息。具体来说，员工代表可以提醒外部董事注意供应链中断、生产效率低下、投资积压和员工流动趋势等重大风险。</p><p>我们采访的员工和股东代表表示，当员工被赋予战略责任时，还可以帮助公司实现长期目标，例如将可持续发展融入公司系统和流程，以及保持领导层继任决策的连续性。</p><p>例如，在拜耳，员工和股东代表在监督关键绩效指标和高管薪酬（包括首席执行官）的委员会中拥有平等的代表权。员工代表影响了激励措施的纳入，以鼓励高层管理人员追求可持续发展目标。 2021年，委员会建议首席执行官20%的薪酬基于与环境、社会和治理（ESG）因素相关的六个目标的进展情况，包括为可持续农业以及全球妇女的健康和福祉提供支持，通过减排或抵消举措应对气候变化。</p><p>西门子董事会走得更远。它促进员工代表与正在考虑担任高管职位的最高管理层以下两级的经理之间的会议。这种做法使员工代表能够评估潜在未来领导者的能力和概况，评估他们与公司价值观的一致性，并为未来与他们的合作奠定基础。重要的是，这一举措向员工传达了一个强烈的信息：他们是塑造公司未来领导力的重要合作伙伴。</p><h3>让员工参与的多种方式</h3><p>公司有多种途径将员工纳入战略决策，即使他们没有正式的结构，例如董事会中的员工代表。下面，我们建议一些执行这三种策略的替代方法。</p><p><strong>委员会和工作组。</strong>包括员工和管理层在内的委员会或工作组对于实施我们的前两项战略至关重要——确定共同目标和利益以及促进包容性决策流程。当公司有一个明确的项目或问题需要解决时，例如决定一个业务部门的命运，这些小组使员工能够直接向公司领导传达他们的担忧和建议。此外，首席执行官和首席财务官还有机会阐明关键决策背后的战略和财务逻辑。</p><p>委员会应包括负责制定和实施正在讨论的计划的高级管理人员以及代表最有可能受到影响的单位的员工。员工应由同事选出，以确保他们反映与领导者决策结果密切相关的人员的观点。</p><p>理想情况下，领导者从一开始就让员工参与其中。通过这种方式，他们向整个组织展示了委员会的价值及其对包容性决策的承诺。这将表明员工正在参与游戏。</p><p><strong>与董事会成员的互动。</strong>可以邀请员工参加董事会会议或务虚会，以促进更具包容性的决策流程。这样做可以让外部董事了解他们可能无法从公司领导那里获得的观点和信息。</p><p>例如，在定期董事会会议上，关键员工可以分享他们的同事在合并后遇到的运营和文化整合问题。在特别的董事会会议或务虚会上，整个组织的员工可以分享他们对更广泛主题的见解和专业知识。例如，如果董事会开会探讨自动化机会，员工可以权衡拟议举措的实用性和适用性，并为受影响的角色推荐解决方案。</p><p><strong>员工咨询小组。</strong>员工咨询小组提供了一种赋予员工战略责任的方法。与委员会和工作组不同，顾问小组旨在长期运作。他们通常关注广泛的组织问题，包括员工对公司及其工作的感受。由于这些团体在帮助其组织应对员工的价值观、担忧和愿望方面发挥着作用，因此他们可以负责针对持续存在的问题和公司的未来方向开发和推荐解决方案。</p><p>例如，由 IT、营销和运营员工组成的数字化转型咨询小组可以持续评估人工智能等新兴技术的影响，监督数字化举措的实施，并就数字化战略提供建议，从而确保组织保持灵活性和竞争力。</p><p>同样，由来自业务领域的擅长环境合规和可持续发展实践的员工组成的咨询小组可以指导组织在这些领域的方法和举措，以确保符合 ESG 标准。</p><p>当董事会认真对待员工咨询小组的建议并将其纳入决策时，员工就会获得更大的权力，他们的观点也会融入公司的长期目标中。</p><p></p><p></p><p>我们对德国领先公司的分析表明，当董事会和公司领导者对员工对战略决策的意见持开放态度并愿意赋予他们有影响力的作用时，会带来好处。他们不仅可以更有效地解决劳动力和劳工问题，还可以通过挖掘员工对企业长期成功的兴趣，获得使他们更具弹性的见解。</p><p>员工参与委员会、工作组和员工咨询委员会以及与董事会成员的接触可以帮助公司在董事或公司领导者与其员工之间建立更牢固的关系，同时从员工为公司决策和治理带来的见解中获益。</p><p>采用这些做法的组织可以在最高层培养协作、公平和包容的决策。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>大语言模型的工作局限性</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikhail Burtsev, Martin Reeves, and Adam Job. <p>Mikhail Burtsev 博士是伦敦数学科学研究所的 Landau AI 研究员、人工智能研究所前科学主任，在 AI 领域发表了 100 多篇论文。 Martin Reeves 是 BCG Henderson Institute 的主席，专注于商业战略。 Adam Job 博士是 BCG 亨德森研究所战略实验室主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com Large language models (LLMs) seem set to transform businesses. Their ability to generate detailed, creative responses to queries in plain language and code has sparked a wave of excitement that led ChatGPT to reach 100 million users faster than any other technology after it first launched. Subsequently, investors poured over $40 billion into [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Burtsev-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>大型语言模型（LLM）似乎将改变企业。他们能够用简单的语言和代码对查询生成详细的、创造性的响应，这引发了一股兴奋浪潮，使得 ChatGPT 在首次推出后以比任何其他技术更快的速度覆盖 1 亿用户。随后，投资者在 2023 年上半年<a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/venture-capital-funding-plunges-globally-first-half-despite-ai-frenzy-2023-07-06/">向人工智能初创公司投入了超过 400 亿美元</a>——占全球风险投资总额的 20% 以上——从种子期初创公司到科技巨头，公司都在开发该技术的新应用。</p><p>但是，虽然法学硕士非常强大，但它们生成类人文本的能力可能会导致我们错误地认为它们具有其他人类能力，从而导致技术的误用。通过更深入地了解法学硕士的工作方式及其基本局限性，管理人员可以就如何在其组织中使用法学硕士做出更明智的决策，通过互补技术和人类治理的结合来解决其缺点。</p><p></p><h3> LLM 的机制</h3><p>LLM 本质上是一种机器学习模型，旨在预测单词序列中的下一个元素。早些时候，更基本的语言模型按顺序运行，根据训练数据中单词的概率分布来预测序列中的下一个单词。 （想象一下您的智能手机键盘会建议短信中的下一个单词。）但是，这些模型缺乏考虑单词出现的更大上下文及其多重含义和关联的能力。</p><p>最新的神经网络架构——变压器——的出现标志着现代法学硕士的重大演变。 Transformer 允许神经网络同时处理大量文本，以便在单词与其出现的上下文之间建立更牢固的关系。在越来越多的文本上训练这些变压器已经带来了复杂性的飞跃，使法学硕士能够对提示产生类似人类的反应。</p><p> LLM 的这种能力取决于几个关键因素，包括模型的大小（由可训练权重的数量（称为<em>参数 ）</em>表示）、训练数据的质量和数量（由<em>标记</em>的数量定义，指的是单词或子词单元） ），以及模型可以接受作为提示的最大输入大小（称为其<em>上下文窗口大小</em>）。模型中的每个参数都封装了从训练数据推断出的关系的一些信息，因此参数数量较多的模型往往知识更丰富、更细致。 （例如，OpenAI 的 GPT-3 拥有 1750 亿个参数。）训练数据量也会显着影响模型的泛化能力，更大的数据集可以提供更多样化的语义关系和事实表示。 （GPT-3 接受了大约 5000 亿个令牌的训练。）模型可以接受的提示的大小也会影响其准确性。 （GPT-3 的上下文窗口包含 2,000 个标记。）上下文越详细，模型的预测就越准确。</p><p>为了响应提示，法学硕士利用其训练建立的关系来逐个标记地生成文本的延续。每个步骤都需要根据提供的上下文预测下一个标记的概率，并且算法根据这些概率选择标记。此选择的随机程度由模型的<em>温度</em>设置调节。较高的温度会产生更多“创造性”或不太可能的选择，而较低的温度会产生更可预测的反应。为了提高法学硕士对特定提示的反应的准确性，并限制其产生不适当、不相关或有毒反应的能力，可以通过<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/09/25/technology/chatgpt-rlhf-human-tutors.html">人类反馈强化学习或 RLHF 等</a>技术对预训练模型进行微调，该技术已被用于微调- 调整 ChatGPT 等模型。</p><h3>法学硕士的四个重要限制</h3><p>基于对法学硕士如何工作的理解，我们可以检查当我们将人类直觉应用于看似人类的输出时，它们可能产生的错误印象。</p><h4> 1. 推理的局限性</h4><p><strong>提示：</strong><em>根据2007年卷心菜种植者联盟的报告，收集的卷心菜中80%是重的（超过0.5公斤），10%的卷心菜是绿色的，60%是红色的，50%是大的（直径超过0.5公斤）。 10 厘米）。以下哪项陈述一定是错误的？</em></p><ol><li><em>所有的红甘蓝都不大。</em></li><li> <em>30%的红甘蓝很大。</em></li><li><em>没有既绿又大的卷心菜。</em></li><li><em>一半的卷心菜很小。</em></li></ol><p> <strong>LLM 回复：</strong><em>错误的说法是 4。一半的卷心菜很小。</em></p><p>正确的答案是陈述 1 是错误的——至少有些红甘蓝一定很大。</p><p>与他们可能给人的印象相反，法学硕士并不是为了复杂的推理而建立的。例如，研究发现 OpenAI 最先进的法学硕士 GPT-4 只能在 2.4% 的情况下正确<a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-just-few-months-chatgpt-232905189.html">验证数字为素数</a>，在视觉模式预测方面也存在类似的弱点。其他研究表明，<a href="https://owainevans.github.io/reversal_curse.pdf">法学硕士</a>无法理解训练数据集中单词之间的关系：例如，GPT-4 可以正确回答“谁是汤姆·克鲁斯的母亲？”这个问题。 （玛丽·李·菲佛）但无法推断出“谁是玛丽·李·菲佛的儿子？”的答案。 ——模型正确回答前一类问题的正确率是 79%，而后者的正确率是 33%。</p><p>从本质上讲，法学硕士只学习<em>口头模拟</em>基本逻辑规则，但不具备将它们链接在一起以产生和验证复杂结论的技能。此外，法学硕士在多步骤逻辑推理中很容易出现错误累积，因为该模型的基本概率性质意味着每个步骤都有非零的错误机会。最后，法学硕士无法总能勾勒出得出结论的“思路链”，这使得人们很难确定错误是否发生或发生在何处。</p><p></p><p>最近由波士顿咨询集团 750 多名顾问进行的一项实地实验强调了这一限制对现实生活的影响。在尝试解决简单业务问题时使用GPT-4的参与者比无法访问LLM的对照组更频繁地获得答案23％ - 因为<a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2023/how-people-create-and-destroy-value-with-gen-ai">GPT-4不仅经常错误地答案</a>，而且提供了这样一个有说服力的答案用户以面值接受的解决方案的理由。</p><p></p><h4> 2.知识或专业知识的局限性</h4><p>我们要求LLM在同行评审的学术期刊上为我们提供有关核融合的可行性，纸质标题，出版年以及主要作者名称的五篇论文。 LLM返回了五个结果，其中有两篇是新闻文章，而不是同行评审的论文，另一篇是不存在的论文。</p><p> LLM的知识取决于其培训数据。如果数据缺乏特定的领域知识，没有特定概念的实例不足或不采取最新情况，那么LLM可能会响应提示而浮出水面。同样，LLM可能会重现培训数据中存在的错误。最后，这些模型可以通过“幻觉”陈述中不在培训数据中创建错误。负责ChatGpt的研究人员为各种癌症病例生成治疗计划，发现<a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/chatgpt-generates-error-filled-cancer-treatment-plans-study-2023-8">LLMS的回答中有三分之一包含不正确的信息</a>- 通常与正确的适应症混合在一起，并以一种使外行者难以确定什么方式表达是准确的。在另一个备受瞩目的例子中，两名律师及其公司在提交了Chatgpt在法院申请中产生的<a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jun/23/two-us-lawyers-fined-submitting-fake-court-citations-chatgpt">假引用</a>后被罚款：LLM幻觉了六个法律案件，包括司法意见和行情。</p><p>最后，知识的局限性也可能导致缺乏一致性，而LLM在矛盾的举止上对不同时间点的同一提示做出了响应。例如，爱荷华州的教育工作者使用Chatgpt来确定<a href="https://www.popsci.com/technology/iowa-chatgpt-book-ban/">学校图书馆的书籍适当性</a>，以遵守一项新的州法律。他们为LLM提供了所有图书馆书籍的列表，并要求它指出包含违反法律的内容的内容，从而导致图书馆删除了19个标题。但是，当记者后来询问Chatgpt时，这表明其中只有4个包含与法律不一致的内容。</p><h4> 3.理解的局限</h4><p><strong>提示：</strong><em>蓝色盒子里有一个苹果。蓝色盒子里还有一个红色盒子。红色盒子上有一个盖子。我该如何获得苹果？</em></p><p> <strong>LLM响应：</strong><em>要从盒子中检索Apple，您可以按照以下步骤操作：</em></p><ol><li><em>打开红色盒子的盖子：由于红色盒子在蓝色盒子内部并且上面有一个盖子，因此您需要先打开红色盒子的盖子。</em></li><li><em>从蓝色框中卸下红色盒子：一旦打开红色盒子的盖子，您就可以从蓝色框中取出整个红色盒子。</em></li><li><em>打开红色框：从蓝色框中删除红色框后，您可以打开红色框以访问其内容。</em></li><li><em>取回苹果：最后，您可以在红色盒子内伸出来，然后取出苹果。</em></li></ol><p> Chatgpt未能理解Apple不在红色框中。</p><p> LLM可能无法“理解”它的提示。缺乏足够的背景，它可能会使它动摇，并且其输出可能会变得脱节或不连贯。<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.02312">研究人员分析了Chatgpt对在线软件工程论坛堆栈溢出的500多个人类提取的问题的回答</a>。他们发现，该模型的响应中有52％是不准确的，其中一半以上是由于Chatgpt而导致的一半错误不了解问题的概念或细节，或者关注问题的错误部分。这意味着，当用户缺乏足够的问题来提供良好提示时，LLM甚至可能不会有所帮助。</p><h4> 4.计划和执行的局限性</h4><p>LLM可以为请求的任务输出明确的分步指南，从而给人以一种模型可以计划实用解决方案的印象。但是，鉴于LLMS的推理能力有限和对任务的有限理解，建议的行动可能是不切实际的或天真的。例如，当被要求制定<a href="https://fortune.com/recommends/mortgages/i-used-chatgpt-as-my-financial-planner/">为房屋所有权节省的</a>计划时，Chatgpt提供了一些扎实的财务建议，但没有考虑到收入或利率转移的潜在变化。此外，它不考虑人类的谬误：既不质疑目标的现实主义，也不质疑用户的信念，而是要意识到他们的确切支出习惯。</p><p>对于企业，所有这些限制都会破坏可靠性；不能确定LLM提供的信息是完整的，相关的，可行的或真实的。鉴于这些限制，LLM当然不能指望做出关键决定或自动执行计划。但是，委派平凡的任务似乎仍然很吸引人 - 例如，涉及与现有IT服务的程序交互的人，例如Web浏览和刮擦，或社交媒体监视和消息传递。的确，Auto-GPT是由GPT-4提供支持的开源应用程序，该应用程序将LLM输出融合在一起以自主执行用户设定的目标 - 使爱好者能够创建许多令人印象深刻的自动化示范，包括 <a href="https://lifehacker.com/you-can-try-auto-gpt-the-next-generation-of-chatgpt-r-1850343691">对产品进行研究</a>，编码网页编码网页或应用程序，甚至<a href="https://dataconomy.com/2023/04/19/best-autogpt-examples-use-cases/">订购披萨</a>。但是，AI研究员吉姆·范（Jim Fan）建议，工作演示<a href="https://twitter.com/DrJimFan/status/1647616587199815684?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1647616587199815684%7Ctwgr%5E53a5539ffd940932a855d641438099af4aa992a5%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechcrunch.com%2F2023%2F04%2F22%2Fwhat-is-auto-gpt-and-why-does-it-matter%2F">“大量挑选了樱桃”</a> - 对自主代理的研究表明，在现实的环境中，它们的<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.13854.pdf">成功率仅约为10％</a> 。</p><h3>克服限制</h3><p>与其仅仅将LLMS的应用程序限制为不适用其限制或错误并不关键的常规案例（例如为进一步考虑生成新产品创意），还应考虑其所有实施情况，考虑到局限人类的监督和其他技术。</p><p>将人类保持在循环中至关重要，因为企业将LLM集成到其运营中。这应该包括验证AI生成的输出，以增强技术对技术的信心。它也可以扩展到让专家将业务问题转化为AI的提示，并通过适当地量身定制上下文和细微差别来确保模型提供的信息足够。</p><p>除了考虑如何制定人类和人工智能的最佳系统外，企业还应探索可以解决LLM局限性的补充技术。在这个快速发展的空间中，正在不断进行新的创新，这有望增强技术的能力，因此不断更新您的理解也是至关重要的。</p><p>例如，为了增强<em>推理</em>能力，研究人员正在<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.07697.pdf">通过推理引擎探索扩大LLM</a> ，这些引擎将特定于领域的信息编码为代表专业概念与事实之间关系的<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.01157.pdf">知识图</a>。研究人员还正在培训专业模型，以评估提示和LLM输出中的前提之间的逻辑连贯性。为了增强<em>知识</em>和<em>专业知识</em>，正在对特定领域的数据库进行培训，例如<a href="https://www.wired.com/story/chatgpt-can-help-doctors-and-hurt-patients/">Google和DeepMind的Med-Palm模型</a>，该模型已显示出在美国医疗许可考试上的表现明显超过了通用的LLM。通过<a href="https://github.com/opendilab/awesome-RLHF">从人类专家收集的反馈意见，</a>可以通过加强学习来提高LLM的可靠性。 LLM还可以通过编程来提出澄清后续问题，然后再提供答案，从而提高他们对用户初始提示的理解。</p><p></p><p></p><p> LLMS近乎全世界适用性的承诺意味着，企业对探索这项强大的新技术感到兴奋。但是，这些模型的产生类似人类文本输出的不可思议的能力很容易使我们归因于它们所没有的功能。对他们的局限性的正确理解应指导其实施的方式和背景。</p><p>企业在涉及逻辑推理，事实很重要，可复制性或赌注很高的领域应特别警惕。在这些情况下，公司需要使用互补技术来探索，以解决LLM的局限性（例如知识图，推理引擎和专业领域模型），并确保有适当的人类投入和监督。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitation-of-large-lange-models/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>引领透明爆炸时代</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-the--age-og-of-exploding-transparency/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-the-the--age-of-exploding-transparency/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Melissa Swift. <p>Melissa Swift（ <a href="https://twitter.com/meswift">@meswift</a> ）领导Capgemini Invent的北美劳动力和组织实践。她<cite>现在是这里工作的作者：像人类一样思考并建立一个强大的工作场所</cite>（Wiley，2023年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Frank is having a terrible morning. The seasoned CIO wakes up groggy to a flurry of texts from his team, who found out about the CEO’s retirement from LinkedIn because the internal announcement got stuck in everyone’s spam filters. As Frank huffs and puffs around the park during his [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Swift-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>弗兰克度过了一个糟糕的早晨。</p><p>经验丰富的CIO醒来时，他的团队一连串的文字醒来，他们发现了首席执行官从LinkedIn退休，因为内部公告陷入了每个人的垃圾邮件过滤器中。弗兰克·霍夫斯（Frank Huffs）和公园（Frank Huffs）在公园里跑来跑去时，他的老板通过电话向他询问全新的仪表板上一些令人不安的数字。到达办公室已经感到困扰的办公室时，他在键盘上吐了冰咖啡，当电子邮件提醒他该组织中的另一位领导者大量记录了她在“ <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/quittok?lang=en">quittok</a> ”上的离开 - 已经获得了半百万的观看次数。</p><p>他在早上的大部分时间里都从一组软件工程师那里进行了问题，他们发现与目前的薪水相似的角色类似于在工作现场上市的角色，而他的营销领导团队来回探讨了新仪表板上的数字是否或旧电子表格正确。就在午餐前，他的女儿给他发短信：“爸爸。你最近看过你的玻璃门吗？”她用诸如“我无法确定管理层是愚蠢，罪犯或只是犯罪愚蠢的评论”之类的评论屏幕截图了他的公司的糟糕评级。”</p><p></p><p>到他踩踏公司自助餐厅时，弗兰克已经有一个星期的痛苦。而且只是中午。</p><p>欢迎来到一个超透明世界中的领导力。弗兰克是虚构的，但他的挑战是真实的。 HoaryCliché是真实的：今天的信息以光速流动……它的移动太快了，许多领导人都无法抓住它。无论是社交媒体渠道使公司肮脏的洗衣店公开（甚至显示“干净的内衣”信息 - 不是丑闻，但并非打算广泛看到），还是内部技术系统将一系列脱皮数据扔到未经准备的人的屏幕上，以解释它自工作世界黎明以来，技术正在有意义地侵蚀了信息优势的信息。</p><h3>再见饮水机的抱怨；你好退出托克</h3><p>知识就是力量——今天，似乎每个人都拥有知识。</p><p>不幸的是，在微观和宏观尺度上<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/">，有关工资，裁员或多样性（裁员或多样性）以及业务绩效指标等劳动力问题</a>的信息有更多的信息，这意味着普通的工人受到了更糟糕或至少不舒服的袭击。对于领导者和员工来说，这会引发艰难的对话，从而产生有意义的压力源：我一遍又一遍地从客户那里听到，即使是经验最丰富的领导者也常常难以参与这些具有挑战性的对话，导致双方在离开时更加不安。当他们开始的时候。</p><p>如今，领导者的行动立即以书面形式和大规模的内部和外部平台进行讨论。仅内部消息传递应用程序即可拥有<em>每秒</em>发送的300,000条消息，每天有1.45亿人登录Microsoft团队，进行类似的讨论。每月<a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">有1500</a>万人使用公司反馈平台Glassdoor，而LinkedIn上有7.74亿人来谈论工作。截至2022年4月，人们对#quittok主题标签标记的社交媒体<a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">内容</a>被认为是令人震惊的4100万次<a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">。3</a>对战略领导决策的反应被限制在一些水冷却器的日子里，已经消失了。</p><p></p><p>那么，在一个可以感觉到每个人都知道一切并一直在谈论的世界中，领导者如何保持理智和有效？组织可以做些什么来确保适当的信号在噪音的刺耳上弹出，并且噪音不会从自上而下挑战他们所使用的每个人的福祉？</p><p></p><h3>领导者的四项实用策略</h3><p>以下是在超透明世界中实现理智和清晰的四种途径。</p><p> <strong>1.通过拨打正确的组织诚实来减轻领导者的负担。</strong>陷入困难的对话似乎不可能 - 但是，一个客户最近对我照亮了一个简单的策略：“当我们更诚实时，我们的领导者更容易。这样，他们只是不必进行那么多艰难的对话。”这个声明有这样的真相。如果人们无论如何都会看到特定情况的现实，那么从跳跃中沟通这一现实意味着在面对团队时，各个领导者不必争先恐后地和背部。</p><p>现在，这是否需要将每种情况的每个细节传达给每个受众？绝对不。这意味着将每个沟通的框架从“我们希望人们相信的是什么？”中改变框架？要“在这种情况下，人们需要做出明智的决定的基本事实和背景是什么？”这改变了信息级联的性质。</p><p>在旧模型中，领导者将配备一组静态的消息，该组织认为该消息将不受干扰地传播到团队的手中，并毫无疑问地（或至少有礼貌）采取行动。在新模型中，该组织更加专注于为一系列新兴事实建立背景 - 隐含的理解是，具有挑战性甚至矛盾的信息可能会通过未被禁止。该目标从强加一组想法转变为创建讨论，该讨论即使存在分歧或信息正在发展，也可以最大程度地减少人际摩擦并最大化生产行动。</p><p> <strong>2.基于“一个世界”基础进行交流 - 结束内部/外部区别。</strong>人们经常说，我们生活在环境崩溃的世界中，在这些世界中，信息通过看似截然不同的沟通圈立即传播，而这些沟通圈本来会脱节或至少在过去的时间段。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>领导者曾经有奢侈的内部交流，然后将信息在周到的进步中选择外部数字。今天，一旦发生了什么事情，他们就可以合理地假设它将在各种各样的受众中在内部和外部闻名。为了解决这一现实，许多组织已合并了内部和外部通信功能，或者迄今迄今派往外部集中的通信部门，以确保与内部利益相关者的消息传递一致。以统一的方式塑造通信不仅会在泄漏的世界中创造稳定的消息传递，而且通常提高了内部通信工作的标准 - 因为内部消息的压力与向外界发布的声明相同的严格测试。</p><p>即使组织没有相应地重组其通信功能，各个领导者也可以努力确保他们的消息传递在内部和外部受众中保持一致。尽管有价值的练习，但这可能是一个微妙的平衡行为：领导者面临模仿社交媒体帖子的语言，同时又抚养他们的同事和主管，以确保发布足够的信息以满足奇怪的内部利益相关者的需求。</p><p> <strong>3.“回到未来”学习基本沟通技巧——但要增加 21 世纪的情商。</strong>尽管超透明的世界是一系列快速发展的技术的产物，但在这种情况下，最终的超级领导力显然是低技术含量的：能够说或写出简单、清晰的句子。就像钟声在拥挤的城镇广场上划破喧嚣一样，具有出色基本沟通技巧的领导者更擅长在喧嚣中让别人听到自己的声音。在刺激快速而疯狂地传递（例如通过社交媒体或内部聊天渠道）并且信息可能从某种程度上到完全不准确的情况下，尤其需要简洁的口头交流。我们需要有能力喊“别动！”让每个人都停下来思考。</p><p></p><p>历来被允许支支吾吾或大言不惭的领导者会发现自己很快就会被当代沟通流的冲击力所淹没——无论这些流是否真实或对业务进展是否有帮助。所有的话，事实和逻辑本身是不够的。一句伟大的句子一如既往（经典写作指南<cite>《风格的要素》</cite>在 100 多年后仍然保持良好状态），但科学已经教会了我们很多关于人们如何吸收信息的知识。例如，触发情感反应的信息更有可能在社交媒体上重新发布，从而使其常常更快，更广泛地散发。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5名</a>被教导要冷静和无情地交流的领导人可能会发现他们的信息不会像同龄人更情绪化的陈述那样快。</p><p>在一个超透明世界中，我们甚至可能想研究神经科学的发现，即警告我们，将理性和情感思维分开是一种错误的二分法，因此，我们应该停止尝试制作完全无情感的领导力信息。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> <strong>4.建立您的判断力肌肉和您的团队。</strong>让我们考虑到世界和工作场所的透明本质只会从现在开始增加。在这样的环境中，您有能力快速，明智地决定如何处理一条信息（您的判断）成为生存和成功的关键工具。领导者将自己想自觉地从事这项技能，但是鉴于他们不能一直在一组倍增的对话中进行，因此他们还希望他们的团队能够更好地判断。我几年前与我合作的一家银行开始为前线工人提供与历史上为高级管理人员保留的一些相同的领导力发展机会，这是基于这样的理由，即有了更多的信息，这些工人将做出同样的类型曾经做过许多步骤的呼叫。</p><p>即使您不在周围时，也能够信任您的团队做正确的事情，即使面对奇怪而矛盾的信息，也有巨大的价值。在这方面，练习场景规划是一个有用的工具，即使对于那些可能没有天生强烈的判断力来到桌子的团队成员也是如此。对于团队来说，练习评估信息的真实性以做出更好的决定也可能会有所帮助。在一个生成AI的世界中，这是一项关键技能。</p><p></p><p></p><p>当领导者手头有一些实用的策略时，在超透明世界中领导不必感觉像通过一条矛盾，不完整且经常充满情感的信息通过小行星驾驶摇摇欲坠的航天器。我们有时可能会有弗兰克早晨的版本，但是我们也可以有弗兰克的下午 - 在那里他清理日历，开始专注于与合适的人在他的公司及其他地区进行正确的讨论。</p><p>六个月后，有人在社交媒体频道上发布了有关弗兰克公司的信息：“管理并不完美，但他们试图说实话，我完全感谢。他们真的在努力做正确的事情，您每天都可以看到它。”</p><p>弗兰克喜欢并分享信息。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-the--age-og-of-exploding-transparency/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为未来的工作构建神经多样性人才管道</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodoverity-talent-pipeline-pipeline-futor-the-future-fork/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodoverity-talent-pipeline-pipeline-future-the-future-fork/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maureen Dunne. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/maureen-n-dunne-ph-d-a2609a45/details/experience/">莫琳·邓恩（Maureen Dunne）</a>博士是全球认可的神经多样性专家，也是伊利诺伊州社区学院受托人协会的前主席，这是美国第三大社区学院财团。她是即将<cite>出版的《神经多样性边缘：拥抱自闭症，ADHD，阅读障碍和其他神经系统差异的基本指南》的</cite>作者（Wiley，2024）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Neurodiversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition & Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images During recent economic policy updates, Jerome Powell, chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve, announced that the American labor market is suffering from a structural labor shortage. Its origins are varied — demographic variables such as an aging population and early retirements, the tragic loss or persistent absence of many [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Dunne-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>在最近的经济政策更新中，美国美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）宣布，美国劳动力市场正处于<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/01/11/briefing/labor-shortage.html">结构性劳动力短缺</a>状态。它的起源是多种多样的 - 人口变量，例如人口老龄化和提前退休，由于19009年大流行而导致的许多工人的悲惨损失或持续的缺席以及移民的历史下降等等，但现在数量太大了忽略。去年年底，每个可用的工人大约有两个职位空缺，将劳动差距扩大到约1000万工人。政治经济学家<a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2022/09/20/american-post-pandemic-labor-shortage-explained/">尼古拉斯·埃伯斯塔特（Nicholas Eberstadt）以这种方式对其进行了核心</a>：“是的，美国有一个抑郁级的工作问题。”</p><p>同时， <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/20/-neurodivergent-workers-help-companies-meet-the-demand-for-talent.html">目前估计有30％至40％的神经变性成年人失业</a>。受过大学教育的自闭症患者的失业率可能<a href="https://www.benefitnews.com/news/how-to-create-equitable-workplace-experiences-for-autistic-talent">高达85％</a> 。今天，美国估计有5000万人， <a href="https://dceg.cancer.gov/about/diversity-inclusion/inclusivity-minute/2022/neurodiversity">全球人口的15％至20％</a>属于今天的神经脱落伞。</p><p></p><p>神经多样性范式倡导一种基于优势的理解方法，包括和评估具有认知类型的神经差异的个体，例如自闭症，注意力缺陷/多动障碍，阅读障碍，衰弱障碍，副局局，亲切性和失调症。太多的神经差异人正在裂缝中掉下来。这种失败不仅是道德问题。在高等教育，我们的工作场所和我们的社区中，成功和真实的神经多样性途径的匮乏具有切实的影响，并阻碍了各地组织的成功。由于如此多的工作空缺以及许多可能未实现的候选人，这些失衡的理论双赢解决方案肯定值得探索。</p><h3>认知多样性和明天的工作场所</h3><p>利用神经厌恶的人的潜力可以帮助雇主建立更具未来的劳动力。创造力，横向（或非线性）思维，解决问题的逆向工程，复杂的视觉空间技能，系统思维，直观的见解，超焦点和多感官模式识别 - 神经差异候选者可能会变得越来越重要的不同领域 - 所有这些都变得越来越重要，因为它们都变得越来越重要人工智能将自己嵌入我们的日常生活中。</p><p>神经化的领导人已经在包括军队在内的每个行业都占据了顶级职位，尽管许多人不愿透露其地位。有足够的证据表明，在有效且合适的工作环境中，这些相同的人可以在一系列职位上表现出色，甚至比其神经型同龄人更好。根据摩根大通（JPMorgan Chase）的自闭症工作计划负责人詹姆斯·马奥尼（James Mahoney）的说法，一项内部研究发现，自闭症员工（正确入职） <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/viewpoint-how-to-become-a-champion-for-employees-with-autism.aspx">的生产率比在同一职位上雇用的神经型同伴高出140％</a> 。</p><p></p><p>没有两个神经化的人是一样的，鉴于不同的人表现出自己的独特优势和挑战，重视各种思想的丰富性和多样性很重要。也就是说，越来越多的证据表明，不同的不同神经型和罕见的技能之间存在相关性，例如增强的创新能力或创新的意识。众多研究的结果表明，神经认知与增强的创造力和创新思维呈正相关，并且自闭症患者比一般人群更容易出现认知偏见，而<a href="https://psyche.co/ideas/autistic-people-challenge-preconceived-ideas-about-rationality">在做出理性决策方面更加一致</a>。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这些独特的观点和技能本质上对雇主在个人层面上有价值，同时提供了额外的群体级别价值作为对集体思维的关键对冲。</p><p></p><h3>社区大学人才管道</h3><p>很大一部分神经异常的人开始了在社区大学的高等教育之旅；一项2015年的一项研究发现，在自闭症上学的人中，有多达80％的人参加了一所社区大学。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>将神经差异带入商业经济的努力应开始或至少与这些机构合作，并可能是改变神经多样性友好的就业机会途径的游戏规则改变者。</p><p>鉴于美国最高法院最近对<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/">大学录取决定的多样性</a>裁决所定的基调，这可能是尤其如此的，该裁决剥夺了精英大学生机构的多样性。致力于这样一种观念的公司，各种多样性都是无价的资产，可能需要更具创造性地思考可以找到多样性的地方。</p><p>然后，负担依靠社区大学的学生扩大机会途径。在担任伊利诺伊州社区学院受托人协会主席期间，我们希望激励社区学院，地方和地区经济发展组织和雇主之间的合作。全州工作委员会的第一个未来，旨在促进与雇主的直接行业合作伙伴关系，以为学生，社区和企业创造新的机会途径，并促进有关新兴行业和职业的对话。</p><h3>与行业建造桥梁</h3><p>英镑，社区大学系统是我们生产合格候选人的最有效方法，以满足教育系统最终用户的需求：公司经济。但是，只有在从一开始就培养和维持的神经多样性友好的机会途径，雇主才能利用该人才池的全部深度和广度。</p><p>社区大学已经充当满足当地雇主需求的强大合作伙伴。如果他们提供诸如心理健康支持，专业辅导，时间管理工具，执行功能指导以及同伴导航员等环绕式支持，神经厌恶的学生将更有可能在学位完成和随后的工作中浏览学位的道路。</p><p>学徒制，付费实习和与社区雇主的工作障碍机会在弥合赚取技能和成功就业之间的差距中起着关键作用。许多社区学院提供了“赚钱和学习”模式的学徒制，例如杜佩奇学院的项目雇用学徒计划，雇主在这里支付学生的学费，以帮助他们在开发新技能的同时学习新技能工作经验在相关角色中工作。</p><p></p><p>鉴于神经化的人在该领域工作，网络安全为此类计划的目标行业提供了一个很好的例子。根据美国劳工统计局的，信息安全分析师职位预计将从<a href="https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/information-security-analysts.htm">2022年到2030年增长32％</a> 。全国各地的社区学院，包括芝加哥城市学院和拿骚社区学院，提供了更多负担得起的网络安全证书计划，该计划将候选人定位在当地需求的职业道路上。基于能力的教育，例如刘易斯和克拉克社区学院的焊接技术计划，代表了一个同样有吸引力的框架，可以为有不同需求的学习者提供灵活的选择，通过技能掌握铺平了赚取的学分的途径。</p><p>神经多样性运动提高了人们对神经异常求职者的才能的认识，并在上学教育和工业之间发展了更强大的协作计划。例如，彭博社报道说，美国情报服务已开始寻找<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-18/people-on-the-autism-spectrum-may-be-ideal-for-some-ai-work#xj4y7vzkg">神经化社区</a>，以增强他们的机器学习和网络安全实践。目睹<a href="https://businesschief.com/human-capital/top-7-companies-hiring-and-nurturing-neurodiverse-talent">EY，JPMORGAN，MICROSOFT</a>和其他备受瞩目的公司之后，完全不同行业的公司遵循诉讼，利用了优先考虑多样性的优势。</p><p>这些努力提供了路线图。行业合作伙伴，经济发展协会和社区大学之间的合作，这些社区学院利用神经多样性友好的环绕式支持计划，学徒制，付费实习和造成工作范围的计划代表了劳动力市场生态系统中的一项新功能。通过依靠这一趋势，我们有机会培养了一条准备工作的神经化的人才管道，能够对合格候选人的外观挑战过时的，无效的假设。</p><h3>在办公的地方</h3><p>为了真正利用神经化的人才库，工作安置协调员和雇主必须实施正确的流程。在雇主方面，人力资源部门应审查招聘和招聘实践，并强调包容性。他们还应努力进一步将同事和管理层的入职策略制度化，以促进对如何支持神经运动团队的更深入的了解。</p><p>从实际层面上讲，这可能需要在入职期间为神经差异人员提供指导 - 提供明确的成功指标，避免歧义，并允许普遍访问噪声遇到的耳机以及其他适应性的工具和实践。此外，在熟悉的环境中，一些神经差异的人的生产力要高得多，因此证明对混合或远程工作场所协议的开放性可能表明对他们的需求更加接受态度。</p><p></p><p>但是，当组织文化未能接受心理安全，信任，反欺凌政策和明确的沟通标准时，这些步骤几乎没有影响。换句话说，无论您有多少阳光和水，花园都不会在有毒的土壤中生长。赌注很高，对于愿意接受真实的神经多样性包容和归属感的前瞻性组织而言，收益可能是巨大的。但是，化妆品的努力不会产生任何影响。</p><p>通过打击刻板印象；允许灵活的结果驱动的工作安排；并促进热情的组织文化，在人们不需要掩盖其认知差异的情况下，我们可以开始集体利用神经多样性劳动力的全部潜力。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodrovesity-talent-pipeline-pipeline-futor-the-future-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>数据科学中连接器角色的兴起</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas C. Redman and Thomas H. Davenport . <p>Thomas C. Redman 是 Data Quality Solutions 总裁，也是<a href="https://www.koganpage.com/hr-learning-development/people-and-data-9781398610828"><em>《People and Data: Uniteding to Transform Your Organization》</em></a> （Kogan Page，2023 年）一书的作者。 Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) 是巴布森学院信息技术与管理学校长杰出教授、牛津大学赛德商学院客座教授以及麻省理工学院数字经济项目研究员。他是<a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047241/working-with-ai/"><em>《Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration》</em></a> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Science]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images For all of the current focus on using data, analytics, and AI to improve organizational decisions and operations, too many data science projects fail. Even for those that succeed, progress is often slow and expensive. Why? Organizational gaps between teams are wreaking havoc with the ability to develop, apply, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Redman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>尽管当前所有重点都集中在使用数据、分析和人工智能来改进组织决策和运营，但仍有太多数据科学项目失败了。即使对于那些成功的人来说，进展也往往是缓慢且昂贵的。为什么？团队之间的组织差距正在严重影响开发、应用和扩展数据科学项目的能力。需要一种新型角色来弥合这些差距。</p><p>我们不要忽视数据科学的许多方面，这些方面可能会让公司陷入困境——从定义正确的业务问题到开发解决方案，然后提供适当的支持。然而，我们与同事罗杰·霍尔 (Roger Hoerl) 和迭戈·库宁 (Diego Kuonen) 合作进行的部分研究对这种情况的诊断表明，许多公司更多地是在解决组织问题，而非解决方案。</p><p></p><p>我们已经确定了造成这种情况的三个根本原因。首先，数据科学已被<a href="https://hbr.org/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone">“固定”到组织结构图上</a>。这在一代人之前可能是可以接受的，当时数据科学只用于解决相对较少的问题，但现在需要建立它，因为数据科学对每个团队都很重要。</p><p>其次，数据科学旨在改善日常运营和决策，这意味着颠覆。但大多数直线经理都力求控制力、可预测性，并且不出现意外。鉴于破坏和控制是截然相反的，生产线管理和数据科学之间存在着比正常情况更大的紧张关系。</p><p>第三，许多公司似乎期望数据科学家能够完成这一切：神奇地了解业务及其所有细微差别，处理数据质量问题，并说服顽固的经理和员工改变他们长期以来所珍视的流程。许多数据科学家更喜欢简单地创建更好的算法，这意味着其他任务常常受到冷遇。</p><p>这些问题无法最小化——它们是深刻的、结构性的，而且往往是政治性的，很可能需要额外的管理策略。在这里，我们将解决组织问题的一个关键方面，即阻碍数据科学模型开发和部署的各个部门之间的差距。</p><h3>使用连接器缩小差距</h3><p>缩小组织差距的明显方法是用人员来填补这些差距。我们通常将担任这些角色的人称为<em>“连接者”</em> 。一段时间以来，公司指派具有系统分析师、业务分析师、覆盖官员和系统工程师等职称的人员来缩小业务和技术部门之间的差距。他们还试图弥合数据科学项目中出现的差距，标记负责这样做的人，数据牧马人，数据工程师，紫色人员和翻译人员。</p><p>尽管许多这样的努力有助于将数据科学项目移动，但通常感觉像是一款精心制作的whack-a摩尔游戏：封闭一个差距，另一个差距弹出。另外，仅这些努力并不能解决一些相关的问题：</p><ul><li>线经理和数据科学家通常不了解彼此。这使得双方特别困难就可以解决问题，并使数据科学家在所需数据中获得和理解细微差别。</li><li>实施模型需要在业务中进行广泛的更改：重新设计的流程，培训模型的工作原理，并为运行它们而努力。</li><li>双方可能看不到IT基础设施决策，例如与技术债务有关的决策。</li></ul><p>由于这些原因，我们建议公司以这三个步骤以更纪律的方式处理该问题。</p><p> <strong>1.定义数据科学项目流程并确定相关人员。</strong>尽管细节可能会有所不同，但该过程应始于构建问题并了解业务上下文，并以监视/更新生产中的新模型结束。关键工作：确定数据科学团队以外的人必须参与每个步骤。</p><p>例如，在解决问题并选择一个项目时，公司希望参与高级领导者和中层管理人员，他们的团队将受到影响。当是时候获取和准备数据时，了解数据细微差别的商业领域专家以及准备数据的IT专业人员应该在房间里。开发模型时，应咨询外部软件提供商。当需要将模型插入流程，业务和流程分析师，受影响流程的经理，培训师和变革专业人员的经理时，都应参与其中。最后，随着组织将模型部署到IT基础架构中，然后监视并更新它时，IT专业人员，构建数据管道以及供应链经理应做出贡献。</p><p> <strong>2.评估连接器可以提供帮助的地方。</strong>本质上，此步骤旨在阐明差距。问：“所有参与的人是否完全联系在一起 - 也就是说，他们了解自己的角色，并且是否有足够的沟通以使工作以相当有效的方式完成？”</p><p>我们发现，答案通常是“否”。确实，我们发现连接器通常以以下方式至关重要：</p><ul><li>通过数据科学解决了要解决的问题：例如，高管可能已经听到了围绕AI的炒作，但对它可以帮助解决的问题或整个组织中的技术潜力缺乏足够深的了解。</li><li>在商业和技术人员之间翻译 - 一个古老的差距尚未封闭。</li><li>处理数据质量问题。</li><li>交流团队中的需求，进度和问题 - 换句话说，将数据科学项目的许多部分绑在一起，并成为不同团队之间的连接器。</li><li>当没有其他人看到大局时，跟踪进步朝着部署和组织变革的整体目标。</li></ul><p> <strong>3.阐明连接器的特定角色并将其放置在适当的位置。</strong>对于单个项目，此步骤通常很简单。我们建议公司还考虑在整个数据科学计划与其他业务之间具有连接器。线经理之间存在 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/to-succeed-with-data-science-first-build-the-bridge/">自然的紧张关系</a>，他们努力地在日常工作中建立控制的量度，而数据科学专业人士则旨在破坏事情。</p><p></p><p>不受组织的检查，这种张力使数据科学团队在公司内建立自己非常困难。计划级别的连接器旨在缓解这种紧张关系：它们帮助高级企业领导者了解数据科学的潜力和挑战，帮助数据科学领导者了解业务面临的最高问题，并建立与企业保持一致的数据科学项目的组合需要。</p><p></p><h3>公司现在正在尝试哪些公司</h3><p>鉴于建立组织成功的组织能力是如此重要，我们很高兴看到公司通过各种连接器角色进行实验和享受成功。例如，地区银行和许多其他组织利用端到端观点的数据产品经理。根据最近<a href="https://aws.amazon.com/data/cdo-report/">对首席数据官的调查</a>，现在有40％的组织采用数据产品管理方法。</p><p>科威特的海湾银行已经建立了一个数据大使网络，以领导部门级别的质量和数据科学项目。瑞士联邦统计办公室采用“数据科学桥”来协调其许多统计功能。克罗格（Kroger）的数据科学子公司84.51º拥有一组它所谓的解决方案设计顾问 - 具有业务背景的人在数据科学家和业务利益相关者之间进行调解。 （84.51º是指子公司辛辛那提办公室的纵向位置，就像经度地图的早期供应商一样，该公司对复杂的数据问题有意义。）克罗格（Kroger数据科学项目从启动到持续的管理层，并使所有各方告知。许多其他组织还采用了此类连接器角色和工具。</p><p>让我们更详细地研究地区银行和瑞士联邦统计办公室的工作。</p><h4>地区银行的数据产品合作伙伴</h4><p>地区银行首席数据和分析官Manav Misra观察到，许多数据科学项目没有成功实施，因此他建立了<em>数据产品</em>的概念以及<em>数据产品合作伙伴</em>的新连接器角色来管理它们。</p><p> Misra将数据产品定义为企业遇到的问题的端到端软件解决方案。他说：“数据产品利用数据和高级分析来提供该解决方案。”数据产品合作伙伴是数据产品经理和与企业合作伙伴一起运作，他们随着时间的推移将产品实现并管理它们。</p><p>每个数据产品合作伙伴都被分配给银行的特定业务或支持部门，并参加与业务合作伙伴的员工会议，以便更好地了解其优先事项。大多数合作伙伴来自银行的业务方面，尽管有些也有分析背景。</p><p>数据产品合作伙伴的工作包括了解业务部门和最终用户的需求，并使用最低可行的产品开始开发周期。在该过程的早期阶段，数据产品合作伙伴是双向翻译人员，将分析和AI的机会与业务需求联系起来。在后期阶段，他们负责评估如何采用和使用完整的解决方案，监视用户界面的工作状况，跟踪有多少人使用它，并确保产品提供或超过该产品中承诺的价值原始业务案例。</p><h4>瑞士的数据科学桥</h4><p>瑞士的联邦统计办公室认识到，如果要满足瑞士政府不断增长的需求，就需要改善其核心数据科学流程，因此它创建了一个数据科学能力中心，这是一种卓越中心。为了确保能力中心与瑞士政府的其他地区完全连接，领导人配备了“数据科学桥”，这是一组专门负责<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-data-science-management-process/">管理六个高级流程的</a>连接器：</p><ul><li>驾驶协作。</li><li>发展人力资本。</li><li>确保数据质量。</li><li>管理项目组合。</li><li>确保积极的业务影响。</li><li>确保以人为本和值得信赖的数据科学应用。</li></ul><p>这座桥正在支付真正的股息。它促进了客户群中的实践社区，帮助人们成为数据工具和报告的更有效的用户，并鼓励他们根据通用语言和理解来交换他们在数据科学和AI方面的经验。在上面列出的六个过程中，该桥正在减少混乱。</p><p>此外，“最重要的决定是在桥上做出的，”库宁指出，他是瑞士数据科学政府的顾问。 （Kuonen还是Statoo Consulting的负责人，Statoo Consulting是一家位于瑞士的咨询公司，也是日内瓦大学经济与管理学院数据科学教授。）Kuonen认为，随着其成熟的成熟，该桥梁将带来更多的价值。</p><h3>连接器管理挑战：五个要问的问题</h3><p>尽管连接器显然具有优势，但管理它们仍带来了一些棘手的问题。在某些方面，连接器在组织图中的“空白空间”中运行，管理层总是很艰难。例如，公司在试图使公司各个数据元素的定义保持一致时，管理数据管理员的运气并没有太多运气。</p><p>公司在定义连接器角色时应该考虑以下问题。答案会因组织情况而有所不同，但是某些模式开始出现。</p><p></p><p> <strong>1.连接器在组织上应该在哪里？</strong>最常见的是，连接器位于主要数据和分析官或数据科学组织下，但有时会在业务组中找到。如果该公司在矩阵管理中成功担任其他角色，则连接器可以向这两个领域报告。</p><p> <strong>2.公司应该如何吸引，评估和保留连接器？</strong>正如数据专家<a href="https://tdan.com/how-to-find-the-right-tweener-for-your-organization/31029">特蕾莎·库什纳（Theresa Kushner）指出的</a>那样，鉴于连接器的角色需要了解业务和数据以及相当大的软技能，因此连接器角色具有挑战性。现在，商学院有数百个分析和数据科学学位课程，这是招募连接器的好地方。组建一个连接团队的组织通常会要求业务领导者评估候选人的此类角色；例如，宝洁（Procter＆Gamble）要求领导者确定每个候选人帮助实现的“突破业务结果”。保留很大程度上取决于为这些员工提供可行的职业道路。</p><p> <strong>3.什么是连接器职业道路？</strong>经验丰富的技术人员很可能认识到需要连接器的需求，但担心如果扮演这样的角色，他们将失去技术优势。经验丰富的商人可能不想在其业务部门或职能中脱离当前的职业道路。在短期内，公司应在数据科学组织中建立越来越多的责任感的角色，例如高级和富有补偿的数据产品经理。我们认为，从长远来看，许多组织都希望每个高级高管都在其背景下具有数据科学经验。</p><p> <strong>4.是否需要多种连接器？</strong>由于某些连接的级别非常高，而其他连接则集中在详细的技术级别上，因此合乎逻辑的答案是“是”。但是，一家公司可能无法负担为一个项目雇用多个项目，因此一些公司也要求数据产品经理也发挥低级连接器的作用。其他组织要求连接器一次在两个或多个项目中扮演角色。</p><p> <strong>5.连接器的职责到底是什么？</strong>由于连接器可能具有一个项目的最佳整体视图，因此通常会向他们收取端到头的管理（就像数据产品经理的角色一样）。如果连接器经历了，并且他们理解并重视数据科学项目的技术角色，这是合适的。如果他们不这样做，则应该更限制其连接器责任，例如不涉及项目成功端到端责任的翻译角色。</p><p>随着时间的推移，您的组织将出现这些问题的更详细的答案。</p><p></p><p>在我们与已成功使用连接角色的公司的合作中，有关的软件供应商和数据科学领导者告诉我们，随着连接器的增殖，数据科学项目的部署百分比已经增加。我们认为，这是一系列重要且持续的角色，几乎每个大型公司都需要进一步的制度化。否则，数据科学可能会成为一门令人沮丧的科学，其部署百分比较低，而改善业务绩效的记录很差。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>问三阴：我怎样才能说服自己我属于领导者？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-in-readhips//<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-i-belong-in-leadhips/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang是首席执行官教练，并领导杜克大学的Fuqua/Coach K领导力与道德中心（Cole）。需要建议吗？将<a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">电子邮件发送给Sanyin</a> 。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managerial Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Pinnolis/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images I have just moved up to an executive job, and while I know I’m ready, I don’t feel very confident in front of my team. I was the first in my family to go to college and still carry the feeling of having to prove I belong, even though [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AskSanyin_Col05_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Pinnolis/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question">我刚刚从事高管工作，虽然我知道我已经准备好了，但在团队面前我并不有信心。我是我家庭中第一个上大学的人，仍然有证明自己属于的感觉，即使我在这家公司的成就方面有记录。我该如何打击冒名顶替综合症并感觉像个领导者？</p><p>不要因为体验冒名顶替综合症而殴打自己。在扮演更高级角色时，一些自我怀疑是正常的。当您与团队成员建立新的关系时，您可以将其转变为有力的东西，而不是试图放逐它。</p><p>冒名顶替综合症被视为对我们的能力的关注，但是我认为这是由于我们是否觉得自己属于特定的空间引起了人们的关注。关于被看到，包括和接受的不安全感是您团队中其他人有时可能会感到的关系。</p><p></p><p>冒名顶替综合症的最佳解毒剂之一，尤其是对于处于领导地位的人来说，是建立一种归属感和社区感。通过建立联系并促进他人的包容性，我们还可以为自己创造更大的归属感和信心。经理可以使用三种实践来增加包容性并激发团队成员之间的信心。</p><p><strong>承认贡献。</strong>人们在会议上大声疾呼可能需要勇气。但是，当我们无法充分认识说话者或不给予信誉的情况下采用他们的想法时，他们可能会让会议感到闻所未闻或没有欣赏。养成当下承认人们的习惯：“这是一个新的想法 - 谢谢”或“以汤姆的想法为基础……”。经理可以并且必须营造一种氛围，在这里团队成员感到欢迎他们的贡献。</p><p><strong>进行良好的介绍。</strong>通过向人们介绍其优势，专业知识和历史的评论来建立一种归属感。良好的介绍可以帮助他人了解人的角色及其带来的价值，但他们也增强了该人的自我意识，并确认了他们对职责的所有权。作为领导者，以这种方式将团队成员介绍给公司以外的人可能特别有意义。它显示了对他们的尊重，并确认它们很重要。</p><p></p><p><strong>强调超级大国。</strong>我相信每个人都有一个无与伦比的固有礼物 - 他们的超级大国 - 当您在实践中看到一个人的超级大国，这一点很重要。这些能力通常是看不见的，未发现或最小化的。直到有敏锐的领导者或同事指出他们之前，我们许多人都不认识他们。帮助员工看到他们的礼物可以使内心的声音保持安静，告诉他们他们不属于他们。</p><p>经历冒名顶替综合症的领导者通常是那些从较少特权的背景中扮演角色，遵循非传统道路或来自代表性不足的人群群体的领导者。这些经历可以建立我们对自己脆弱性的认识，并了解我们能够独自控制的局限性，即谦卑。为团队成员增添真正的同情心，并猜测什么：您拥有那种在这些挑战时期最有效的领导者的特征。您的团队将为您的领导而拥抱。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-i-belong-in-leadhips/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>多元化推动</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Paola Cecchi-Dimeglio. <p>Paola Cecchi-Dimeglio（ <a href="https://twitter.com/hlspaola">@HLSPAOLA</a> ）是妇女和少数民族律师的执行领导力研究计划主席，也是哈佛法学院法律职业中心的高级研究员。她是<cite>多样性红利的作者：对您的公司消除偏见，吸引多样化的人才，更好地管理每个人并赚更多的钱的小小变化的变革力量</cite>（麻省理工学院出版社，2023年），从中得出了这种适应性。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Roy Scott/Ikon Images Despite their commitments to diversifying their workforces, many companies continue to struggle with attracting, hiring, and retaining employees from underrepresented groups. Achieving workplace diversity is not easy, but leaders can target, address, and nudge specific data points and thoughtfully incentivize behaviors that support it. These interventions are often small, easy to implement, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Cecchi-Dimeglio_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">罗伊·斯科特（Roy Scott）/伊肯（Ikon）图像</p></figcaption></figure><p>尽管他们致力于多元化劳动力，但许多公司仍在努力吸引，招聘和保留人数不足的群体的员工。</p><p>实现工作场所多元化并不容易，但领导者可以瞄准、解决和推动特定的数据点，并深思熟虑地激励支持它的行为。这些干预措施通常很小，易于实施且价格便宜，但是当它们应用于吸引人，招聘，人员的入职以及员工路径周期中的选择，过程和组织杠杆时，它们可以帮助使工作场所变得更加多样化。和包容。</p><p></p><h3>推销吸引多样性的人才</h3><p>一个电子商务巨头的转换率（CRS）在购物者的某些细分市场中，包括有色人种和中等收入LGBTQIA+人的目标。同时，该公司的主要竞争对手成功地雇用了更多的女性，黑人和拉丁人，太平洋岛民和LGBTQIA+在营销，行为分析和其他角色的人，他们的不同观点正在转化为更高的CRS。</p><p>该公司发起了一项重要的运动，以吸引多样化的人才。它聘请了一家搜索公司，该公司投掷了全国网，并运行了印刷和数字广告，该广告强调了公司对多样性和包容性的承诺。然后，领导人坐下来等待那些不同的候选人出现。在广告闪电战之后的三个半星期内，在线作业发布的景色达到了顶峰，但在第七周就坦率地挂着。不到11％的现场访问者申请了职位。只有三名申请人接受了采访；两个收到的报价，其中一个被拒绝。换句话说，如果您以令人印象深刻的资源和巨大的费用来构建它，那么它们仍然可能不会来。</p><p>正如这家公司发现的那样，仅仅吸引您吸引的潜在候选人的关注是不够的。将适当的人才转换为申请人和候选人需要额外的外展和培养。来自代表性不足的人口统计的人（包括有色人种，被识别为LGBTQIA+的人以及残疾人）通常与竞争性雇主的联系更少，并且知道可以帮助他们在申请过程中导航的人更少。想要提高多样性的组织可以通过使用淡淡的人才（在人才获取过程中提出的语言和内容修改）来吸引更多代表性群体的候选人，这有助于产生多样化的候选人池，在整个过程中维持池，鼓励顶级候选人。接受工作机会，并帮助他们继续上车。</p><p></p><p>午睡可以帮助建立信任并尽早减少信息不对称。在此类干预措施中，一家公司在其领导层中展示了女性和代表性不足的人的数量，以及其多样性和包容性目标和时间表，以及在线职位发布旁边。屏幕右下角的视频中有首席执行官谈到了他对包容和多样性的承诺。这项干预措施增加了妇女和代表性不足的群体的百分比，这些群体在短期内申请了22％，长期申请了18％。来自不同社会经济背景的候选人总体上升了17％。而且，重要的是，从申请工作到接受职位的转换率上升了8个百分点。</p><p>提高对潜在雇主的熟悉程度的轻推可以在整个过程中帮助维持申请人池。例如，即使求职者不认识公司的某人，促进连接也可以使公司更具吸引力。一项在线实验在提交申请和公司听到之前，将1,276名申请人随机分配给了四个条件之一：</p><ul><li>申请人有机会在申请正在进行时向公司雇用的妇女提出问题。</li><li>申请人有机会在申请正在进行时向公司雇用的男性提出问题。</li><li>申请人有机会问一个由一名男性雇员和一名女雇员组成的小组的问题。</li><li>申请人没有机会问任何员工的问题。</li></ul><p>当妇女可以提出有关该公司雇用的妇女的问题时，这些候选人在面试中的表现要比其他任何条件下的情况要好。他们所评估的访调员评分增长了34％。这些相同的候选人也对申请过程和公司的形象更加满意。那些未收到工作机会的人更有可能在接下来的24个月内重新申请。</p><p>同样，在一家科技公司的在线实验中，我在提交申请后和在收到公司听到之前，将1,478名申请人随机分配给了几个条件之一。一些申请人被分配为求职者作为伙伴，如果他们被选为面试，他们可以与他们一起练习所需的任务；有些不是。在分配伙伴的那些申请人中，有些女人与女人配对，有些女人与男人配对，有些男人与男人配对。</p><p>申请后与伙伴合作的求职者经历了40％的面试选择率；在代表性不足的群体和初级职位中，影响尤其值得注意。与男子配对的女性获得的采访得分比其他情况高9％。参加伙伴系统的候选人对这一过程更加满意，即使他们没有被选中接受面试或接受采访但没有提供职位。女性的满意度增加为28％，男性的满意度增加了29％。</p><p>在该行业中拥有朋友或熟人可以减少在传统上排除他们的领域寻求就业的人们感到的恐惧。这些候选人正在寻找信息：“这是什么样的？我应该穿什么？我应该如何准备？我应该说些什么？如果什么 …？”知道消除了许多恐惧，潜在的雇主可以通过识别这种情况并干预以重新设计动态来填补这一信息差距。平衡交流与候选人寻求的信息，可以修补鸿沟和促使信任。潜在雇主提供的信息使候选人可以决定公司是否合适，是否可以看到自己在那里工作，以及组织是否会被组织所接受。</p><p>例如，考虑运输和物流行业，这是男性以压倒性的。缩小如此广泛的性别差距需要创造力。一家试图雇用更多妇女的公司拍摄了该公司雇用的每个妇女的照片。然后，它通过将妇女的图片放置在空白空间附近，以图形方式说明了性别差距，该空间代表了缩小性别平等差距所需的其他女性。该组织想雇用足够的妇女来填补空白空间的日期还包括在插图中。</p><p>该公司不仅在其网站上显示了图像和文本，而且还与所有相关搜索和招聘公司进行了交谈，并发起了一项旨在吸引妇女申请的大型运动。在六个月的时间里，这项努力使女性申请人增加了30％，其中包括来自代表性不足的群体的女性。</p><p>工作应用程序的设计也会影响申请候选人的数量。在以前的实验和干预措施中，诸如请求与性别和种族有关的信息之类的小事已经很重要，但是这些请求的放置可以排斥或吸引候选人。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>一项涉及320名申请人的公司研究试图确定在申请开始时，最后而不是根本不是在申请开始时收集性别信息的影响。在最终要求性别认同的地方，与其他两个条件相比，女性完成了7％的申请。</p><p></p><h3>招募多样化人才的推销</h3><p>从简历中删除人口统计指标可以允许对候选人进行公正的评估。在一家全球公司，申请人被指示进入在线门户网站，这使每个人的外观，感觉和格式都相同。所有审稿人都看到了同样的事情，所有种族和性别的指标都被删除了。剥离的数据包括名称，隶属关系，与宗教或文化团体相关的志愿活动，爱好，语言技能或与特殊倡导或社区组织的联系。</p><p>删除此类数据减少了偏见的可能性，并使工作经历成为招聘团队的主要重点。还要求候选人描述他们的工作场所结果和贡献。这种中性格式集中于评估过程，并在18个月内增加了欧洲和美国的代表性不足群体的池。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>在与科技公司的咨询参与期间，我们使用AI语音更改来掩盖性别。候选人使用了​​一种名为Gap Jumper的工具来解决基于技能的挑战，而无需透露其性别，以及语音调制设备以匿名化性别，种族或种族背景。妇女的工作机会增加了几乎16％，而代表性不足的种族群体成员为18％。</p><p>在设计了公平且中立的过程之后，仍然有必要做出招聘决定。练习招聘艺术时，有用的策略是从“我们应该包括谁？”中改变问题。要“我们应该排除谁？”在这种情况下，决策者并没有为应选择谁的标准而苦苦挣扎，而是确定应排除谁应该被排除在外，并且能够确定一个较小的候选人中的较小群体。尽管这种方法在寻求更具包容性的背景下似乎是违反直觉的，但它迫使决策者将重点放在核心资格上，并排除不符合他们的候选人。</p><h3>推销多样化的人才</h3><p>在一家在纽约市地区拥有多个办事处的全球金融服务公司，几个合作伙伴正在庆祝雇用八名新员工。该小组的性别，种族和年龄多样，千禧一代，Xers将军和婴儿潮一代的混合。</p><p>千禧一代似乎毫无疑问地找到自己的立足点，Xers对组织很熟悉，并且有许多同事已经成为他们网络的一部分。但是，入职过程并不欢迎和吸收卡尔顿，卡尔顿是一个在50多岁时被执行级别雇用的黑人，就像其他七个人一样。尽管卡尔顿（Carlton）具有令人印象深刻的才华和熟练性，但卡尔顿（Carlton）却减少了获取信息的访问，并影响了他的几个分配项目。在不到18个月的时间里，他在他的第一次表演审查后不久，他离开了公司参加竞争对手。他的离职可测量损害了公司。 In the short term, the cost of replacing him would range between $1.5 million and $1.75 million. In the long term, his assessment of the company as a place of employment would negatively resonate throughout his network.</p><p> The data has found a link between individuals leaving an organization after 12 to 24 months and their onboarding experience — a correlation that stands out more than any other factor in the life of the employee at the company. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> In short, get onboarding right or pay the price.</p><p> An effective onboarding process ensures that new hires are brought fully and inclusively into the organization. Small modifications enable new hires to better navigate this process and access the information and services that can help them integrate comfortably and become productive.</p><p> Like new immigrants, new employees seek information about the norms, policies, politics, and behaviors that will help them function successfully in the new setting. New hires require clarity regarding roles and expectations. They want background information about the company. They want to know how to thrive, what it takes to excel and get promoted, and what it takes to master their jobs. They also want to know what constitutes a high standard and where they should aim.</p><p> One large professional services firm nudged its onboarding process by sending a series of short videos featuring the CEO, some board members, and some members of the executive team to candidates as soon as they received job offers. These three-minute videos were aligned with company strategy and were sent each day for 15 days. They were paired with messaging about the company&#39;s commitment to diversity, what it felt like to be part of the company, what to expect if you were to make a mistake as part of a team, and how people were expected to handle such an occurrence. The videos also discussed what it meant to have equal opportunities to succeed.</p><p> In another variation, the new hires were assigned to a work project for a large client right away. The data showed that the 15 videos plus the assignment to a large project upfront resulted in improved performance among women and individuals from underrepresented groups because the interventions increased job clarity. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> In the banking industry, an effective onboarding nudge featured stakeholder meetings at two weeks, three months, six months, nine months, and 12 months. In the meetings, the hires heard from people who had been at the organization for at least five years, who discussed problems the new employees had encountered during onboarding, how they had overcome those challenges, and their perceptions of the company as they moved through the 12-month process.</p><p> A variation of that approach used intervals of six months, 12 months, 18 months, and 24 months, during which stakeholder meetings took place every six weeks. The result was a higher retention rate for women and underrepresented groups 48 months after hiring.</p><p> One of the important elements of onboarding is the opportunity to create and structure one&#39;s network. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> The network brings with it access to information and opportunities for mentorship. It sets a social-emotional tone and influences how at ease a new hire will feel in the job.</p><p> One intervention at a financial institution hinged on sharing with new hires a list of 10 people that they were encouraged but not required to contact within 12 months. Each list included a mix of employees, some of whom were at the executive level. Some of the newcomers received an explanation of why they should reach out to the people on their lists, while others did not. And some participants in the experiment received email reminders to contact the people on the list at three months, six months, and nine months.</p><p></p><p> Individuals were selected for inclusion on a given new hire&#39;s list based on information that had been captured during the recruitment process. If an employee had expressed interest in a particular business unit, the list included a partner from that area. The list might also include leaders or HR contacts from cities or regions where the new hire&#39;s close family members lived. If the employee needed to relocate to take care of a parent or other family member, that essential information had already been provided.</p><p> Individuals from underrepresented groups who received a contact list, an explanation of why they should make contact, and email reminders performed better in their jobs. There was an acceleration in their network spread, which was measured along their lifetime at the company. Even 72 months later, people who had received all three elements of the intervention were still expanding their network faster than those who had not received all three elements of the intervention. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> A large company with many offices discovered that the onboarding process at its smaller workplaces seemed more effective. People felt more integrated, and their networks were established faster than in the large offices. In contrast, at the larger sites, new lateral hires were not mixing across generations and were not building their networks.</p><p> In response, the company applied a nudge that involved the cafeteria. Employees were assigned plate colors based on the number of years they had been at the company. New people were assigned a blue plate, employees who were six months into a role got a yellow plate, and other employees had green plates. Once a week, when people dined together, people with the same color plates could not sit together. Color mixing created interaction among employees who would otherwise be invisible to one another.</p><p> The strategy made onboarding easy because people were creating new networks. The intervention led to a 34% shift in the degree of directness characterizing an individual&#39;s connections within the network. It also produced an 18% increase in “betweenness centrality,” a metric quantifying an individual&#39;s role in passing information within the network.</p><p></p><p> Throughout my research, consulting, writing, and experimentation, 10 points along the career trajectory stand out as places where specific kinds of nudges and interventions can support the goal of building and sustaining a diverse workforce. In addition to attracting, recruiting, and onboarding candidates, diversity nudges can be applied to skill-building, avoiding office drudgery, flexibility and well-being, pay equality, origination and credit, feedback and promotion, and networking and sponsorship.</p><p> To benefit an organization and become part of a company&#39;s strategic advantage, women, people of color, and individuals from other underrepresented groups must be intentionally welcomed, integrated fully into the organization, and sustained. This process should be data-driven, harnessing the potential of big data and AI to achieve sustainable inclusion. They must be purposely supplied with the same or equalizing information, connections, skills, projects, and support that are provided to others within the organization. Inequalities must be recognized, and intervening actions must be devised to nudge these conditions in a manner that creates equality and inclusivity. The companies that win at diversity are the ones that design processes that are advantageous to and level the playing field for everyone.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/diversity-nudges/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>具有 Gen AI 的微型实用程序：Shopify 的 Miqdad Jaffer</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Experimentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[High-Tech Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Online Retail]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Miqdad Jaffer brings a background in engineering to his role as director of product for digital marketplace platform Shopify. Users might recognize the commerce platform as one that enables a fast and secure online checkout experience. On the merchant side, Shopify enables business owners to set up e-commerce sites where they can list and sell [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Miqdad Jaffer 拥有工程学背景，担任数字市场平台 Shopify 的产品总监。用户可能会认为该商务平台能够提供快速、安全的在线结账体验。 On the merchant side, Shopify enables business owners to set up e-commerce sites where they can list and sell their products.</p><p> Using generative AI, the platform also now offers merchants the ability to complete administrative tasks much more quickly, including writing product descriptions and customizing their sites. As Miqdad explains on this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, a key to enhancing Shopify&#39;s offerings with generative AI technology is ensuring that users always remain in control. He shares Shopify&#39;s approach to doing this while incorporating cutting-edge tools to help entrepreneurs start, operate, and grow their businesses more efficiently. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E4-Jaffer-Shopify-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Miqdad Jaffer"></p><h4> Miqdad Jaffer, Shopify</h4><p> Miqdad Jaffer is the director of product for Shopify, where he is responsible for the oversight and development of the company&#39;s AI-powered offerings. He joined the company in 2018 and has overseen the launch of Shopify Magic, its suite of AI-powered tools, and Shop.AI, an AI-powered shopping assistant. Before joining Shopify, Jaffer was the director of product management for the mobile consumer marketplace app Flipp. He has more than 15 years of product development and oversight experience.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How can generative AI tools help grow businesses while keeping users in control? Find out on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I&#39;m Miqdad Jaffer from Shopify, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Hi, everyone. Today Shervin and I are pleased to be joined by Miqdad Jaffer, director of product at Shopify. Miqdad, thanks for taking the time to talk with us.让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Thanks for having me. I&#39;m happy to be here and excited to talk a little bit about AI.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Great. We all use Shopify, but we may not know it. Can you give us a brief overview of Shopify and tell us what a director of product actually does?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Sure. So Shopify is a platform for entrepreneurs to be able to set up their storefronts online. You may have seen Shopify whenever you&#39;re going to purchase an item from a retailer. You may have gone to the checkout and seen that purple Shop Pay button, and for many of us, that&#39;s probably where you&#39;ve been exposed to Shopify. It&#39;s a way for an entrepreneur to be able to set up their storefront on the internet and for … you as a buyer to be able to transact in the fastest, simplest way possible to be able to make sure that the item arrives at your door.</p><p> In other cases, you may have seen Shopify on a platform like Shop.ai, where you might have searched for a specific event that you&#39;re putting together, a specific product that you&#39;re looking for, and tried to filter it all down across the many merchants on Shopify.</p><p> A merchant would go into Shopify and log in. There is a product section on the left, as an example. They would go into the product section, they would click “Add a new product,” and then within “Add a new product,” there is space for a title, description, and some other fields.</p><p> In terms of my role, my responsibilities are, how do we think about AI and how can it fit into that realm of entrepreneurship, and what can we do to accelerate our merchants&#39; success and progress as they build up their storefronts, sell their products, and grow as entrepreneurs?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So how does that involve artificial intelligence? I hear a lot of “e-commerce,” I hear a lot of “connecting,” but how does that involve artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah, it&#39;s a great question. I think that when people are looking to start as an entrepreneur, there&#39;s a lot to it, so there are considerations of “What&#39;s the right product?合适的价格是多少？ What&#39;s the right placement? What&#39;s the right promotion? How do I set up everything with my storefront? How do I maintain what &#39;good&#39; looks like as I grow and as I advance?” What we&#39;ve seen is that AI is an opportunity to make entrepreneurship accessible for everyone.</p><p> With every business unit, we wanted to utilize AI to create more efficiency, from managing administrative tasks to supporting business operations. Administrative tasks can be as simple as creating a new product description [or] figuring out what the right subject line for an email could be. And then, the business operation side of it could be just about everything from understanding the business, figuring out the analytics of it, what questions should I ask, what&#39;s the strategy that I should employ? And we view AI as a powerful assistant that can weave itself in and out of that process.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What you&#39;re saying is, Shopify is letting the entrepreneurs focus on the actual product and their brand and all of that kind of stuff but then have Shopify be a platform for how they take that to market, how they want their brand to appear, and a lot of the back-end operations. Obviously, AI could be quite prevalent across all of those. Was AI embedded from day one as it launched?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> We&#39;ve had AI in its most traditional sense embedded since early days. We did things along the lines of fraud detection, where a transaction comes in — and it&#39;s not as easy to tell whether this is fraudulent or nonfraudulent. We&#39;ve done basic classification models to be able to determine whether something <em>is</em> fraudulent and then provide a score back to the merchant in a reasonable fashion. That&#39;s been in there from the start.</p><p> Then generative AI comes along, and there are opportunities to be able to do a lot more, and what we&#39;ve seen is, we&#39;ve created a suite of products called Shopify Magic. And the idea behind this was, how do we embed this directly into the workflows that our merchants are having to go through, and how do we make that easier to start, run, and grow your business?</p><p> We did things like Autowrite, where we can create a description for a product, create a blog, create a new page, help with the subject line of an email, create the body of an email, and look at ways, on the customer service side, to be able to provide responses for a merchant as they interact with their customer. So those are some of the early stages, but we&#39;re trying to accelerate it even more these days.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> A lot of companies are thinking about generative AI, and it seems like you&#39;ve been <em>doing</em> it for quite some time. Can you comment a bit on when you started thinking about it, prepping for it, and, I would assume, to some extent, redirecting or upscaling or reskilling some of your technical folks to be able to actually take these things to market.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I&#39;ll give you a little bit of the genesis of how we kind of started with the first thing and accelerated it even more. We have some general themes that come up every year in terms of things that we should be looking at, and one of the ones that&#39;s usually pretty prevalent on there is [that] staying on the cutting edge of technology is critical. What we want to do is try to bring as much of the latest technology into the hands of our merchants so they have every advantage possible.</p><p> And we&#39;ve always tried to do things with AI, and one of the more recent ones, even before generative AI, was product classification — so the idea of being able to determine the category of a product using its text as well as its image to be able to figure out where this belongs. It helps in channels. It helps you basically market to a wider audience and get a reasonable taxonomy set.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Mm-hmm.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> When ChatGPT came out, the question was, what can we do with this technology to put it in front of merchants? And this was one where we wanted to lean in for a couple reasons. One, it&#39;s important to get this in the hands of merchants as fast as possible, staying with the cutting edge of the technology side. And the other part of it was, we actually saw that there was utility for the first time, and that utility was important to get out there and to see whether our merchants would use it and what we could learn from it.</p><p> So we started with a simple path of “What&#39;s the thing that merchants are struggling with?” And we saw them struggling with product descriptions daily. There&#39;s billions of them across Shopify, and we saw that as a wide space to work in, and we had all of the conditions around what would make a good product description. And then we felt “OK, let&#39;s get this in and see how people use it and see whether this is something that&#39;s palatable.”</p><p> So we quickly spun up a team, and we relied upon a couple different principles. Shopify generally builds off of a set of principles and allows the team to go fast. Some of the principles we worked off of were, this has to be easy, this has to be integrated into their workflow, and the merchant needs to be able to have final say as to what goes out there to represent their business.</p><p> It&#39;s a simple start. We said, “OK, let&#39;s figure out what the rules of a good product description are.应该多长？ What&#39;s the tone it should be used in? What are the types of words that will be used, and what makes it really good?” We did the basic thing of prompting against that and then said, “OK, what additional context should the merchant provide, and what should we look for to be able to help them?”</p><p> And so we said, “OK, well, they can probably list out a couple keywords about their product, and that fits into the realm of knowledge <em>they</em> know about, and the rest of it should be us. Like, this should be as simple as like pressing a button. It should feel like magic.” So apropos to that, we named it Shopify Magic, and we wanted to stick with that. All a merchant has to do is they enter a couple keywords, they pick a tone of voice, and they press “Generate.”就是这样。 That was the first version. We tried to ship that real quick and see what would happen, and the feedback we got was, “This is amazing. Can you do this everywhere?”</p><p> So it&#39;s like, “OK, so there&#39;s, there&#39;s some positivity here. So, what can we do next?” And so we added a “special instructions” field, and initially in our trials, we were doing things like “Add a quote from a famous celebrity that would relate to my product,” just as, like, a meme for how to try it 。 And then we saw merchants using it in different ways.</p><p> We saw them using it for language, and this was an interesting one. We introduced the ability to support eight languages, and we saw people writing translations with it, and that was expected, but it was interesting to see. And I think one of the most interesting ones we saw was, there were merchants that didn&#39;t speak English and wanted to sell to an English audience and saw product descriptions as a way to bridge that gap — unexpected, but at the same time, it&#39;s one of those things where you put the product in the hands of the user and then the user decides what they&#39;re going to use it for. And it was remarkable to see that we opened up entrepreneurship for even a small window more of people than were there previously.</p><p> And that&#39;s what kind of got the ball rolling on the AI efforts. After that, it was every team wanted a piece, every team wanted to do something, and we accelerated it in every way we could. We&#39;ve tried to systematize things from a UX [user experience] perspective; whenever a merchant sees something, they know that this is what that&#39;s going to do. And we&#39;ve also tried to look into building Sidekick, which is a first-of-its-kind AI-enabled assistant, purpose-built for commerce. And so that&#39;s kind of been the journey that we&#39;ve gone into. We have dedicated teams that are working on specific features, and then we have the entire company that is looking at opportunities of where AI can accelerate commerce.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So when Shervin and I first heard about what you were doing, I think what kind of got us excited was how pervasive this is. The effect of something like Shopify integrating artificial intelligence into its tool is huge. And I think we were talking earlier, you had talked about introducing this product in February [2023]. This is very early on in the generative [AI] days.</p><p> A lot of people are investigating generative, but this was an exciting story where you&#39;re using these tools in production very quickly. I&#39;m sure that was a little bit painful — maybe you could speak a little bit about any of the pain or difficulty you had; maybe other people have learned from that, but also at how pervasive it is. Both of those are interesting ways that people can learn from what you&#39;ve done.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. Early days came with the challenges, but I think that that&#39;s kind of the fun of it. It was interesting because this was the latest technology. There was so much utility to it, and we just wanted to get that in the hands of our users. Along the way we had to figure out things like, how do you do evaluation? What is this prompting stuff? How do you systematize this and make this make sense? What&#39;s all this RAG stuff about — RAG being <em>retrieval augmented generation</em> ? How do I bring more data into this context of a prompt, and how do I make this make sense?</p><p> And the crazy part was, every week, a months&#39; or a years&#39; worth of other technology time passes, and all of a sudden there&#39;s a new thing to try and a new thing to explore, and we didn&#39;t want to miss that ， 任何一个。 Every time something new came out, we tried, we explored. And I think that the culture at Shopify is one of exploration and one of crafters and builders. And what we tried to do is put this in the hands of people that could build, and to try things. And we also did things internally to encourage the use of AI, and we built our own kind of internal ChatGPT instance equivalent. We have it for our internal wikis for search and discovery. And what we&#39;ve tried to do is just make this into the fabric of the company.这是正常的。 It&#39;s expected. And then, all of the risks and challenges that come with it — hallucinatory included — are things that people are familiar with. And once we got them familiar with it, then we figured out ways to work around it and to embrace it in some cases, too.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I think that&#39;s a very important point you&#39;re making because as I reflect back on my own experience and BCG&#39;s experience in this field, we&#39;re working with many companies, and many of them have the same mindset and ambition as you&#39;ve described and are putting solutions in production and are embracing it. And then there are some that are, I would say, quite reserved about this. And some of that is based on, I would say, some unfounded fears.</p><p> I mean, the reality is this is new technology and it comes with a lot of risk, and maybe a little bit more risk than traditional AI because of how pervasive it can become. But I think the mentality of waiting for all of the risks to be figured out by other people then puts you at somewhat of a huge disadvantage, because the only way, as you describe — I mean, I love how you said it — the only way to actually get ahead of these things is to start experimenting with it and getting comfortable with it.</p><p> I&#39;m sure at the board level there were some risks and some concerns. Maybe just comment on what many people thought back then versus what the reality was and put it in perspective for some of our listeners so that they understand that these risks can be mitigated versus you just stay away forever.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. One of the first things I&#39;ll say is that I want to describe who an entrepreneur is, to even put this into context. Every entrepreneur I have ever come across has the highest risk tolerance of anyone I&#39;ve ever met. They are willing to drop everything in their life to start a business, and sometimes they don&#39;t know anything except that they want to start a business. And these people are inherently risk tolerant, so our user group is very different than others. And obviously, you&#39;re going to get a spectrum of tolerances across that user base, but by nature, this is a group that is willing to dive in, take risks, and try things. And then one of the things that we observed was that they were already using it. So we already had merchants that were using ChatGPT or whatever was out there, to be able to prompt it, figure out alternatives, and use it directly into their software.</p><p> We did a brief round of research where we asked a number of merchants: Is this something that you know about?你用得怎么样？ What are you doing with it? And many of them were like, “Yeah. Well, I mean, I just ask it everything, and so I&#39;m just getting to figure it out.” And we already saw that happening. So for us it was, “All right. Well, we already have this risk-tolerant merchant base, and the biggest concerns that we have are typically on two vectors.”</p><p> Vector one is a fear of losing control. So asking questions along the lines of “What&#39;s it going to say? What do I do if it hallucinates? Is this going to be right for me? Is it going to speak to my buyer?” So all of those initial questions and that fear of losing control was easily mitigated. So we said, “OK. Well, here&#39;s a quick fear. How do we mitigate this fear?” And we mitigate a fear of losing control by putting the control back in the hands of the user.</p><p> So the carte blanche principle was “The AI will never write without user intervention,” and so the merchant will always be able to see what the message is that&#39;s going to go out there. So all of the hallucination risk, all of the “What&#39;s it going to do?” risk is gone because now it puts control right back in the hands of the user.</p><p> The second risk is around whether it&#39;s factually accurate or not, and that&#39;s typically one that a lot of people come across. The way that we&#39;ve tried to manage that is, the person that knows the most is the person selling the product. The thing that they know the most about is their product, and that&#39;s what they&#39;re trying to talk about, and they&#39;re trying to talk about <em>their</em> brand. And so that one didn&#39;t feel as risky for us either because it was going to be up to the merchant to decide how they were going to be represented in a factual way.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You talk about this in such a matter-of-fact way, but when you think about the actual key word here, it&#39;s the <em>user</em> , which is actually, when you think about it, Sam, a lot of our work around human and AI versus just human alone or AI alone. Thanks for talking about that. That&#39;s very key.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One of the things I really like, too, is you keep using the word <em>utility</em> . A lot of the examples that Shervin and I talk about, we&#39;ll ask people for an example, and they&#39;ll bring out some AI-heavy application that they&#39;ve implemented that crosses lots of parts of their organization and it&#39;s a big deal, and those are great. But the utility you&#39;re talking about seems like micro utility. And so, what I mean by that is that, as you mentioned, people may have already been going out to some large language model and generating some text and then pasting it into Shopify.</p><p> Your incremental utility here was saving them some back and forth between those two tools, but also then incrementally making it work better within your tools and within your context. And I think that&#39;s exciting, when you think about how all those tiny pieces multiply by the billions. And that&#39;s a different story than what Shervin and I see sometimes, which is, “We have a big system which has a big utility, and there may be not so many users of it.”</p><p> I want to come back to something that you mentioned earlier — and maybe I just picked up on your tone of it — but you were talking about fraud detection and these somewhat traditional uses of artificial intelligence. That feels like an oxymoron now, but you said, “Oh, yeah. We&#39;re using it for fraud. We&#39;re using it for back-end business optimization and these sorts of things.耶耶耶。 We do all that stuff, but here&#39;s the really cool stuff.” It seems really exciting that you&#39;re able to stay forward.下一步是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> It&#39;s a great question. I think the hope for us is that we want AI to lower the barrier of entry for entrepreneurship, period. And I think the idea for us is, let&#39;s look at everything that&#39;s on the space. So we did something relatively recently about image generation. And we saw this as “OK, well, we can lean in here, too. There&#39;s different modes of operating that we can play with.” So we release the Hugging Face pipeline, and the idea behind this was “Let&#39;s put this out into the market, let&#39;s see how people are going to use it, and let&#39;s do it in a way that&#39;s going to be innocuous.”</p><p> The idea behind it is you upload a product image, and then you pick what background needs to be switched out. And some of this, there&#39;s some fun stuff behind the scenes of uplift, upscaling the image, figuring out the right mask for it, making sure that the reflections and shadows are going to be good, and then generating all sorts of backgrounds that make sense in the vein of commerce. And what we see from this is the ability to explore in a different way. What we&#39;ve tried to do with AI, and to your point about the risk tolerance of our user base, it&#39;s not meant to be something that is just disruptive to their existing workflows. Many of them — especially established ones — have existing workflows where they do everything in their specific way, and that&#39;s what works for them.</p><p> All we&#39;re doing is, for anyone that needs that extra push or needs that extra piece, there&#39;s a button to click, a way to invoke this, and it is their choice to make on that. And, Shervin, I like some of the stuff that you were talking about in terms of putting the user in place, and our adage has always been that this is meant to be something that augments and isn&#39;t a replacement. So this is always going to be something that helps a user be the best version of themselves.</p><p> And with image generation, we see the opportunity for them to holistically change their storefront if they want to. If they have a Thanksgiving sale coming up and they want to be able to change all the backgrounds to be fall themed, it&#39;s a quick, easy move for them to do. Their product stays at the forefront, their branding stays at the forefront, but they can merchandise just for the specific event — if it&#39;s Thanksgiving, if it&#39;s Christmas, if it&#39;s New Year&#39;s, whatever it might be. Something that would require additional photo shoots might be a lot easier to achieve now than [it was] previously.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Exactly. Let&#39;s just remember how complex and unnecessarily process-oriented something like this would have been, you know, a few years back, where you have just agreeing on the background and the photoshoot and the look and feel and impact on brand and all of that, and now you&#39;re putting it all in the hands of the merchant.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> For us, it was really important that many people across Shopify were using this, asking the right questions, pushing the boundaries, and understanding some of the nomenclature around it. When I say “hallucination,” I can almost guarantee that 99% of Shopify knows what that means and how that happens and [how] that works. And that makes the conversation much different every time you go toward product development, because it&#39;s not bringing it up and relitigating it every single time. It&#39;s people trying a solution around the normal problems that come up with this technology.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> If I squint, I kind of see something developing over this market of artificial intelligence. You alluded to it with the ease of transfer learning. You&#39;re able to take these existing models and augment them slightly, and I see that as an improvement over the past decade from “Oh, yeah.当然。 You can download these tools and build them yourselves” to “Hey, no, you can take what we&#39;ve done and what we&#39;ve trained our GPUs and burned up our GPUs on and incrementally burn up a little GPU on your own but then move forward.” I think that&#39;s a dynamic that&#39;s happening in this market here.</p><p> But let me go darker here and talk about another dynamic. Is there, let&#39;s say, a race toward mediocrity? And I think that&#39;s a little charged way of saying it, but if all of your users in Shopify are using the same tools to generate the same sort of product descriptions, isn&#39;t that going to lead to a sort of vanilla feeling of all product descriptions? How do we push back and get beyond that? It&#39;s great that we get everybody to mediocre well; how do we get people distinctive? Where do we build off of that? How do we make that beyond mediocre?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Yeah. The problem you&#39;re talking about is a local maxima, effectively, right? So everyone moves toward this standard, simplistic, homogeneous, boring thing. And what we&#39;ve looked at is that all of the tools that we provide will get you started. The idea is not to be “This is the finish line.” The finish line is the merchant. The finish line is their product. The finish line is their brand and being able to represent accordingly. For many cases, this is about getting you something, which is better than nothing, and getting you started and thinking.</p><p> We had one merchant that really described it well for me. He wanted to set up an outlet store for some of the overstock inventory that they had, and they had 3,000 SKUs that they wanted to put together — 3,000 different products that they wanted to put on this initial outlet store. And what he said to me was, “Typically, what I would have done is I would have hired a team, we would have taken three months to get this thing spun up, and we would have tried to put it together.” And he said, “I spent the weekend by myself, and I just used your generation feature. It got me started. I made a couple changes. And in three days, I had an outlet store stood up and ready to go for all my products. And I made the changes necessary. I don&#39;t like the style that you had, so I gave it some specific instructions, and it got to what I wanted.”</p><p> And I think the idea is flexibility within the framework. So provide a framework, let them get started, but give them all the flexibility in the world to do what is appropriate for their business and for them to be able to differentiate to their audience. And I think the key is, every audience is different, and nobody understands that better than the merchant themselves. The idea is capability and augmentation, not replacement. And you&#39;re right; there could be a point of local maxima for people. But we want to leave every escape hatch possible so that they can get out of that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing I want to stick back to, and you&#39;d alluded to it, was the deterministic versus stochastic nature of this. That seems really difficult to work with [from] a production standpoint — that you&#39;re using tools that have stochastic outputs, but you&#39;d like to have a “defined, tested, refined” process. And those two things seem antithetical to me in many ways.你怎么处理那件事呢？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Part of it is, there needs to be a risk tolerance built in. So there needs to be almost an expectation that the system will fail and that the user needs to have a way to be able to work through that failure. So product description is a great one. We actually see that it takes multiple generations before the user is happy with what they have in front of them. So with that in mind, you have to allow for that second, third, fourth, fifth generation to take place with no effort whatsoever.</p><p> And so that&#39;s an error case that we know is going to happen, so we plan for it. So there&#39;s this “Regenerate” button right there; it presents multiple options. In other cases, we will try to present as many options as we possibly can to make it easier. So subject lines: You get three options to choose from.你可以改变它。做任何你想做的事。 Then, the other part of this is that we understand that technology is going to change, and the way that people use it is going to change, and their expertise level is going to change.</p><p> So there are people that are going to try and break the system, and there are people that are going to try and work around the system. It&#39;s important that we plan for that scenario, too. So every risk and every failure case has to be considered upfront. And then you almost do it in a fun way, and the one that is typical is prompt hacking, where people are trying to figure out what the prompt was that was used for this. In most of those cases, you do the best you can, but you expect that the prompt will get out there. So you write the prompt in a way that, when it gets out there, it&#39;s like, “Hey, you found me.那太棒了！ You want to apply for a job or something?” There are lots of different ways to like think about this.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Your human in the loop solves a lot of this too.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Correct.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Your whole design philosophy, it really addresses, I think, a lot of the backstops, a lot of the stochastic nature too. Can you give us a bit of your background? How did you get to your role?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I started out as an engineer. I think since I was, like, 12 years old I was programming and trying to figure out how to make the computer do what I wanted it to do. And I took an initial role as an engineer and was introduced to product management in what was then meter data management. So it was like big data for utilities had just come out. I got to work in that space, and then I moved into document classification, then ad tech, and then retail data platform management.</p><p> I&#39;ve always been adjacent to data, and at Shopify, my journey had been [to] build our infrastructure and data platforms, work on our machine learning platforms, and figure out what needs to be built there. And I always had one toe in the machine learning/AI pool at all times. Then I had teams that were focused on the analytics side of it and what merchants were going to experience and how they were going to understand their business. And the mandate was always like “How do I optimize my business with data?” And we looked at opportunities with ML, we looked at opportunities with AI. And then, when generative AI came out, it was just the next step along the way.</p><p> So it&#39;s by luck, by accident, by design — who knows? But I&#39;ve always been in data for the last 15, 20 years, and this was the next step.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK. Time for five questions. Miqdad, do you know what that is?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I do not.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I mean, I know what five questions are, but …</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Good! So we&#39;re going to ask you five questions rapid-fire style. Just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Sure.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What do you see as the biggest opportunity for AI right now?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I think the biggest opportunity is solving cold start for many people. What I mean when I say “cold start” is looking at a blank screen and not knowing what to do, whether it&#39;s how to navigate a system, write a thing, or whatever it might be — just that unknown moment. I think that&#39;s where AI steps in and does the biggest [benefit].</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I love that. What is the biggest misconception about AI?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> That it will take over. I think that there&#39;s a long way to go. It&#39;s an augmentation, not a replacement, and I think it&#39;s the same as when Photoshop came out. Designers got much better and much more creative, and I think this will raise the bar for everyone in terms of what they can do.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Is there such a thing as too much AI? When is there too much?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I think it&#39;s too much when the user is out of the loop. I think the user needs to have a stronghold in how they use AI and how they interact with it. I think this is not about replacing, and I think this is a matter of augmenting and helping the user be better.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What was the first career you wanted?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I wanted to be a doctor, but I faint at the sight of blood, so that didn&#39;t work out so well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What is the one thing you wish AI could do that it cannot do right now?</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> I wish we could incorporate all of the modes of a user wanting to interact, whether it be a combination of voice, facial expressions — just to be able to get that semantic meaning behind the scenes that words can&#39;t do by themselves 。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Wonderful.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We really appreciate the idea that what you&#39;re doing is using generative AI right now, just barely after it got started. I think a lot of people are wringing their hands and wondering how to use these technologies, and what you&#39;ve shown is a great example of how people can get real utility from this tool right now. Thanks for taking the time to join us today.</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer:</strong> Thank you so much for having me, both.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Sam and I speak with Ellen Nielsen, chief data officer at Chevron.请加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>使用开源进行更安全的生成人工智能实验</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aron Culotta and Nicholas Mattei. <p>Aron Culotta is an associate professor of computer science and director of the Center for Community-Engaged Artificial Intelligence at Tulane University. Nicholas Mattei is an assistant professor of computer science at Tulane University.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Security]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Open Source]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Integrating artificial intelligence into the daily workflow of employees across organizations, from upper management to front-line workers, holds the promise of increasing productivity in tasks such as writing memos, developing software, and creating marketing campaigns. However, companies are rightly worried about the risks of sharing data with third-party AI services, as in [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Culotta-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Integrating artificial intelligence into the daily workflow of employees across organizations, from upper management to front-line workers, holds the promise of increasing productivity in tasks such as writing memos, developing software, and creating marketing campaigns. However, companies are rightly worried about the risks of sharing data with third-party AI services, as in the well-publicized case of a Samsung employee exposing proprietary company information by uploading it to ChatGPT.</p><p> These concerns echo those heard in the early days of cloud computing, when users were worried about the security and ownership of data sent to remote servers. Managers now confidently use mature cloud computing services that comply with a litany of regulatory and business requirements regarding the security, privacy, and ownership of their data. AI services, particularly generative AI, are much less mature in this regard — partly because it is still early days, but also because these systems have a nearly inexhaustible appetite for training data.</p><p></p><p> Large language models (LLMs) like OpenAI&#39;s ChatGPT have been trained on an enormous corpus of written content accessed via the internet, without regard for the ownership of that data. The company now faces a lawsuit from a group of bestselling authors, including George RR Martin, for having used their copyrighted works without permission, enabling the LLM to generate copycats. Proactively seeking to protect their data, traditional media outlets have engaged in licensing discussions with AI developers; negotiations between OpenAI and <cite>The New York Times</cite> , however, broke down over the summer.</p><p> Of more immediate concern to companies experimenting with generative AI, however, is how to safely explore new use cases for LLMs that draw on internal data, given that anything uploaded to commercial LLM services could be captured as training data. How can managers better protect their own proprietary data assets and also improve data stewardship in their corporate AI development practice in order to earn and maintain customer trust?</p><h3> The Open-Source Solution</h3><p> An obvious solution to issues of data ownership is to build one&#39;s own generative AI solutions locally rather than shipping data to a third party. But how can this be practical, given that Microsoft spent hundreds of millions of dollars building the hardware infrastructure alone for OpenAI to train ChatGPT, to say nothing of the actual development costs? Surely, we can&#39;t all afford to build these foundational models from scratch.</p><p> Safer experimentation with generative AI is becoming increasingly possible thanks to a burgeoning open-source AI movement that recalls the excitement around Linux in the 1990s. Back then, the development of a free operating system whose source code could be read and edited by anyone birthed an international community of developers who built upon one another&#39;s work to develop a mature suite of software tools that run much of the internet today.</p><p></p><p> Such a <a href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2023-01-30-ai-linux">“Linux moment” for AI</a> has now arrived. Open-source models such as <a href="https://bigscience.huggingface.co/blog/bloom">Bloom</a> , <a href="https://lmsys.org/blog/2023-03-30-vicuna/">Vicuna</a> , and Stable Diffusion, among many others, provide foundational models that can be fine-tuned to specific tasks. Research into highly optimized training routines (such as <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2106.09685">LoRA</a> and <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2106.10199.pdf">BitFit</a> ) has found that they can be fine-tuned using commodity hardware, leading to a burgeoning <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3545111">ecosystem of models</a> approaching the performance of ChatGPT (though many <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.15717.pdf">technical challenges</a> remain). A leaked memo in which a Google researcher laments “we have no moat” reveals that some see this explosion of open-source innovation as threatening the tech giants&#39; control of LLMs. Still, capitalizing on the rapid developments of these emerging open-source tools safely and responsibly will require new investments in people and processes.</p><p></p><h3> Managing the Risks of Open-Source AI</h3><p> While locally controlled AI solutions keep proprietary data in hand, managers must still take a number of actions to ensure their safe, effective, and responsible use.</p><p> <strong>Navigate model and data licenses.</strong> The term <em>open source</em> is, in many cases, misleading. While some models allow commercial uses, others are restricted to academic or nonprofit use. Sometimes the source code is released with the model; other times, only one or the other is released. Recently created types of licenses restrict specific use cases deemed to be harmful or irresponsible. For example, Bloom and Stable Diffusion are released under <a href="https://www.licenses.ai/">Responsible AI Licenses</a> , which might legally prevent their use in certain criminal justice and health applications. One must also consider the types of data the model was trained on. While including copyrighted material in data sets for training AI models might be considered fair use in some scenarios in the US, case law is far from settled. Having a thorough accounting of the data fed into each model will help organizations better navigate these issues. Emerging efforts like the Data Nutrition Project are adding more structure and reporting requirements to data sets to help users better understand their contents and risks.</p><p> <strong>Prevent data leakage.</strong> Even without submitting data to third-party AI services, organizations risk leaking their own data through open-ended user interfaces such as chatbots. An emerging use case allows LLMs to serve as a conversational interface to a database, which can be a powerful way to let customers quickly find answers to common questions that are customized to their own data. However, preventing the LLM from revealing private information about other customers, or proprietary data of the company, can be challenging. Research by Pew shows that these conversational agents are a <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/science/2023/02/22/60-of-americans-would-be-uncomfortable-with-provider-relying-on-ai-in-their-own-health-care/">concern for many users</a> , especially around sensitive topics like health care. Safeguarding data is made even more difficult by <em>prompt injection attacks</em> , in which malicious users attempt to trick the agent into revealing information it was explicitly instructed not to reveal. In an adversarial setting, the same aspect of AI systems that allows them to be creative and flexible also becomes a security threat.</p><p> <strong>Adapt to changing data.</strong> Another complication with hosting on-premise models is ensuring that they are using the latest data. While the initial release of ChatGPT (GPT-3) famously could not answer questions about events past 2021, more recent models can combine current data with models pretrained on historical data. Firms must balance updating the system with new information while also maintaining stability and consistency in user experience.</p><p> <strong>Mitigate systemic biases.</strong> AI systems can easily perpetuate and amplify social and economic inequalities encoded in the training data. It is well known that LLMs are prone to stereotyping based on gender, race, and ethnicity — such as assuming that nurses are female and doctors are male. While there has been considerable research into how to reduce such behavior, in the end this problem will not be solved by solely technological solutions. Organizations should continuously audit AI systems, measuring their performance and results to ensure that different subpopulations are being treated equitably.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Build trust with customers.</strong> Companies should anticipate heightened sensitivities over how personal data is used and be transparent with customers about any intentions to use their data for AI training — and, ideally, allow individuals to opt in. This is particularly important when it comes to data that is perceived as being extremely personal, such as audio, video, and health data. Simply updating the terms of service and sending out notifications about the change, as some companies have done, can leave customers feeling exploited and broadly damage trust. For example, after Zoom&#39;s recent move to claim such rights to using customer data made news, blowback from users and privacy advocates compelled the videoconferencing provider to not only walk back the changes but declare in its terms of service that it would never use such data to train AI models.</p><h3> Responsible Data Use in the AI Era</h3><p> If open-source AI models continue to be adopted across industries, it will not just be Big Tech facing concerns over data ownership. Every company that wants to deploy these models for tasks as wide-ranging as internal help tools and public-facing chatbots will have to confront issues related to how data is collected and used by AI systems.</p><p></p><p> While there are <a href="https://mozilla.ai/">startups</a> , <a href="https://data.humdata.org/dataset/2048a947-5714-4220-905b-e662cbcd14c8/resource/60050608-0095-4c11-86cd-0a1fc5c29fd9/download/ocha-data-responsibility-guidelines_2021.pdf ">governmental working groups</a> , and <a href="https://responsibledata.io/">academic communities</a> all working on these topics, best practices and recommended policies are still emerging. Stanford Law School&#39;s <a href="https://law.stanford.edu/2023/03/09/a-data-stewardship-framework-for-generative-ai/">AI Data Stewardship Framework</a> specifically addresses generative AI techniques. The Association for Computing Machinery, the world&#39;s largest computing professional organization, has also recently released a set of guidelines around the <a href="https://www.acm.org/binaries/content/assets/public-policy/ustpc-approved-generative-ai-principles">design and deployment of generative AI</a> systems, including LLMs. Those resources cover some of the issues discussed here, including limits on deployment, data and output ownership, and personal data control. We recommend that organizations of all sizes looking to capitalize on open-source AI keep a close eye on relevant guidelines and frameworks for the responsible and ethical collection and use of data for training models. They can be helpful for thinking through the potential technical and social risks of any potential project, and for developing rigorous auditing and monitoring processes to ensure safe and effective deployment.</p><p> At Tulane, we have recently established the <a href="https://tulanecs.github.io/tuceai/">Center for Community-Engaged Artificial Intelligence</a> to investigate such issues. Through a cross-disciplinary team of technologists, social scientists, and civil rights activists, we are working with nonprofits and community groups in New Orleans to understand how AI affects their work. We are brainstorming new ways of building AI systems that cede control over the data and technology behind AI to the people most affected by it. Our work is part of growing efforts around participatory or human-centered AI and data, which recognize that all stakeholders need to be included in the value created by these systems. As corporations move deeper into AI development, adhering to similar values might help them be better stewards of the data that they collect and use.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何明智地利用人才市场</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Williamson and Donncha Carroll. <p>Jeff Williamson is a leader in human resources at Booz Allen. Before joining the company in 2019, he was chief HR officer and executive vice president of the US Postal Service. Donncha Carroll is a partner at Lotis Blue Consulting and the firm&#39;s data science leader. He has nearly 30 years of consulting experience.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Networks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Many leaders can now make a strong case for establishing an internal talent marketplace, but getting one off the ground remains difficult. At Booz Allen, we experienced that truth during the first year after launching our pilot project. Here, we’ll examine some of the challenges we faced, how we overcame them, and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> Many leaders can now make a strong case for establishing an internal talent marketplace, but getting one off the ground remains difficult.在博思艾伦，我们在启动试点项目后的第一年就经历了这一事实。 Here, we&#39;ll examine some of the challenges we faced, how we overcame them, and what we learned about change management and talent marketplaces.</p><p> Having a talent marketplace represented an important change for Booz Allen. For years, we&#39;d been deploying professional staff members through informal, internal networks that operated based on who you knew and who you trusted. But this path limited our flexibility to make use of available resources and match the right talent to the right work. More importantly, it limited our people&#39;s control over their own career paths, and that hurt engagement and retention.</p><p></p><p> To test a better approach, Booz Allen launched a talent marketplace pilot project in partnership with Lotis Blue Consulting in January 2022. With the pilot, we sought to address talent management challenges that constrained growth and hurt our ability to deliver a compelling value proposition to employees — namely, issues in hiring, deployment, talent development, technology and its adoption, and culture change. We wanted to solve these problems systematically and holistically rather than introduce point solutions, which often fail to compound value.</p><p> But the level of cultural transformation required to activate and operate a talent marketplace is significant. It takes a sustained effort to work through several human behavioral- and perception-driven issues — and overcoming these issues is key to success.</p><h3> The Road to a Talent Marketplace</h3><p> Booz Allen wanted to end its reliance on traditional hiring networks centered around clients or teams. These highly localized networks made it tough to find resources in other parts of the organization that would meet enterprise, regional, or local needs. In contrast, the marketplace established a centralized approach to assess demand and source talent enterprisewide (via external hiring, internal deployment, or upskilling) and created the capability to deploy people across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> The marketplace pilot focused on skills rather than networks. This gave employees new visibility to open opportunities across the enterprise and managers new insights into talent who could do the work. This high-resolution view on job and development opportunities vastly expanded the scope of what people could explore, improving employee engagement and delivering higher levels of individual and business performance. The pilot doubled the internal fill rate on open positions for the pilot population and garnered positive employee feedback on transparency and ease of pursuing new opportunities. Additionally, this skills-based approach gave underrepresented candidates more opportunities in technical domains with public sector clients.</p><p> In the early months of the pilot, we needed to overcome a few important challenges to build interest and excitement. Most importantly, we needed to seed the marketplace with a sufficient number of high-quality opportunities and available talent to engage both employees and managers. In so doing, we learned several important lessons — especially around change management.</p><h4> Lesson 1: Bring on the gamification.</h4><p> As our clients&#39; environments and needs are changing, the nature of our work is evolving, and we are seeing a rapid shift in in-demand skill sets. Our technical talent&#39;s ability to deliver against a client&#39;s mission depends on how quickly they can learn and adapt.</p><p> To address this, Jim Hemgen, Booz Allen&#39;s strategic talent development leader, and his learning and development (L&amp;D) team designed and launched a badging program alongside the marketplace pilot. The program aimed to develop strategic enterprise capabilities by illuminating different career pathways and the skills required to access different opportunities. To qualify for a badge, an employee needed to both earn the credential and have a manager validate that they had applied the skill on the job. This gamified learning and offered recognition and rewards to employees who invested in their own development.</p><p> The L&amp;D team engaged a large segment of the company&#39;s technical workforce in building strategic capabilities through a combination of internal badging and external certifications. In the past year, employees have earned more than 4,000 badges or certifications that are critical to the future of the business.</p><p></p><h4> Lesson 2: Data goals must be relevant to individual career goals.</h4><p> We encountered several technical challenges associated with the pilot, including data structure (establishing the right job architecture), data quality (ensuring that skills data was complete, for example), and algorithm design (how best to perform the recommendation process for talent and open positions).</p><p> To get the complete skills data, we needed wide adoption. In reality, adoption closely correlated with the value that users expected to extract from the platform. We had a slow start as employees and managers explored the functionality and benefits.</p><p> That changed once John Grumbine, the marketplace operations leader, helped launch the Career Hub, an internal web app, in January 2023. The app served as a one-stop shop for employees to find jobs, training and development, mentors, and communities in the talent marketplace based on their skills and preferences. Employees now had a vested interest in keeping their skills and preferences up to date because that information drove recommendations for the opportunities, training, and the mentors they could access; further, it drove how they might be discovered or identified by project managers seeking to fill roles.</p><p> Launching the Career Hub app led to a substantial increase in talent marketplace adoption. As of September 2023, more than 50% of Booz Allen employees had onboarded into the Career Hub and were accessing job, learning, and mentoring opportunities.</p><h4> Lesson 3: Even change management needs to change.</h4><p> In the realm of cultural transformation, we quickly experienced four key challenges after launching the pilot. (See “Four Culture Challenges to Conquer.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Culture Challenges to Conquer</h4><p class="caption"> You&#39;re likely to encounter these issues as you lead through the culture change related to a talent marketplace:</p><table id="Chart#" class="no-mobile"><thead><tr><th>挑战</th><th>Business Implications</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>Managers want to keep their best resources or are concerned about becoming a net exporter of talent in an open market.</strong><p></td><td><p> Instead of leaving the team, high-performing talent leaves the organization.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Employees are reluctant to seek out reassignment openly for fear that they will appear disloyal to their current supervisors.</strong><p></td><td><p> Engagement and performance of captured staff declines over time.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Project managers are reluctant to accept resources they don&#39;t know personally and to trust recommendations from managers outside of their personal network.</strong></p></td><td><p> Assembling the right team for each project is much more challenging. The hiring process takes longer and is more susceptible to hiring manager bias.</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Hiring managers are rejecting less-than-perfect applicants who often require only a small investment to close skill gaps.</strong></p></td><td><p> Staff members become less engaged, and performance degrades on work misaligned with their personal interests. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson_Talent_Essay_Table.png" alt="Four Culture Challenges to Conquer" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> Those challenges were causing a lot of problems. In response, our team prioritized several important actions to drive the culture change we needed:</p><ul><li> Build, refine, and map out skills-based talent profiles to provide greater clarity on the work people can do or have done.</li><li> Focus (initially) on high-volume in-demand job profiles to create enough liquidity in the system that participants have the opportunity to move.</li><li> Form a small, agile, and action-oriented operations team to collaborate with subject matter experts (for example, from business leadership and talent acquisition) as different challenges arise.</li><li> Provide human-centric support in the form of marketplace navigators — people specifically tasked with helping all participants (employees and managers) follow marketplace rules and guidelines and get the most value from the platform.</li></ul><p> All of these steps can be built into a launch plan for a talent marketplace.</p><h4> Lesson 4: Momentum, motivation, and measurement matter a great deal.</h4><p> At a high level, it&#39;s important to launch several services of an integrated talent management system simultaneously in order to exceed expectations and build adoption momentum.</p><p> To effect behavioral change, leaders must deeply understand what motivates different people, as well as how the changes they&#39;re making will address people&#39;s needs. The pilot provided valuable feedback on marketplace utility, helped prioritize enhancements, and established the level of change management required to support evolving and scaling the design.</p><p></p><p> Monitoring and measuring marketplace performance helped our team try new things, fail fast, and continually enhance the marketplace&#39;s value to participants. More specifically, our metrics included the number of opportunities posted, trends within those opportunities, the level and breadth of employee interest by type of posting, the percentage of aging opportunities (those that went unfilled for a long time), and the percentage of positions填充。 This data helped us evaluate the health and strength of the platform and gave us insight into how system adjustments were influencing performance.</p><h3> Commit to Continuous Improvement</h3><p></p><p> Through the talent marketplace and our other talent system investments, we are delivering a better employee value proposition. Our employee retention improved more than 4% after the pilot. However, this journey never ends. Continuous investment in evolving talent, as well as the solution, is essential to success for the business.</p><p> Addressing obstacles that come up along the way is part of the journey and ultimately leads to a better design and better results. A talent marketplace offers important benefits in today&#39;s evolving labor market: By prioritizing employee mobility and development, companies can better adapt to the changing skill requirements and realize higher levels of innovation, collaboration, and flexibility within their workforces.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>