<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 27 日星期四 12:20:57 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>消除职业障碍以获得更公平的结果</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian 是劳动力科学研究所的联合创始人和共同领导者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts. That was the message from [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/W23-QA03_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>即使是专门致力于推进多样性、公平性和包容性 (DEI) 的组织，也难以以可持续的方式提高代表性。女性和有色人种继续面临晋升更高职位的障碍，并且往往无法像白人男性同行那样取得成功。</p><p>这是劳动力科学研究所联合创始人兼共同领导人 Haig R. Nalbantian 在 2023 年 5 月举办的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间传达的信息。Nalbantian 帮助组织应用基于证据的实证方法来加强其 DEI 工作和保留策略，并断言“在人力资源领域大量使用分析来为工作和劳动力管理提供信息”是未来工作的重要组成部分。</p><p></p><p>虽然天赋和干劲对于塑造职业生涯很重要，但情境因素会深刻影响员工在工作中的表现。其中包括员工获得“加速器”角色，例如面向客户的工作；员工如何适应灵活的工作安排，例如兼职状态；以及员工的汇报关系，例如他们是否向上级或高绩效主管汇报。纳尔班蒂安指出，这些易于识别的情况（他称之为<em>“解释差异”</em> ）很普遍。</p><p></p><p>许多组织在选择晋升人员方面也普遍存在巨大且<em>无法解释的差异</em>。纳尔班蒂安表示，在他自己和其他人的研究中，在所有条件相同的情况下，精英大雇主的经理“实际上更有可能对女性给予高度评价”，“但在大多数公司中，她们不太可能”得到晋升。”</p><p>他表示，公司必须解决已解释的差异并探索无法解释的差异。</p><p>纳尔班蒂安无法回答活动期间与会者提出的所有问题，因此他在下面回答了其中一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>您的研究在分析中是否涉及交叉性？您谈到了女性和有色人种，但是有色人种女性和其他具有多重交叉少数群体身份的人呢？</h6><p>在我的研究中涉及的许多客户案例中，我们确实直接检查了交叉性。我们在美国较大的组织中已经做了很多这样的事情，这些组织拥有足够的这些人口群体的人口用于建模目的。</p><p>客户组织特别感兴趣的领域之一是报告关系的交叉性。也就是说，主管的具体人口统计数据是否会影响员工是否得到晋升、获得高评价或获得更高的加薪？例如，白人男性主管对待黑人女性报告的态度是否比白人男性或白人女性报告更差？白人女性主管是否会帮助她们的女性报告的前景，无论肤色如何？</p><p>我可以说，这些结果几乎没有什么规律性——当然远远少于我在绩效评级、角色、主管绩效和水平以及灵活工作方面报告的结果。</p><p></p><h6>这项研究是否将社会经济地位映射为交叉影响？</h6><p>不幸的是，我们关于社会经济因素的数据要有限得多，部分原因是我们的大多数客户将这些研究重点放在他们的受薪人群上，而忽略了他们的小时工。这让我感到担忧，因为它揭示了一种低估一线工人的倾向。我试图提醒组织，一线人员发生的事情可能会对业务成果产生重大影响。我在客户作业中看到并记录了这一点。尽管如此，组织的趋势仍然是优先考虑受薪员工——专业人士、经理和高管。</p><h6>您提到，比同龄人年轻是成功的一个有利因素。您能否详细说明一下您的研究发现的有关年龄不平等的情况？</h6><p>在我们对客户组织的分析结果中，年龄的负面影响几乎是普遍存在的。一个简单的事实是，一旦员工超过了其群体的中位年龄，所有事情都会变得消极：他们升职的可能性较小，获得高绩效评级的可能性较小，而且他们的薪资增长会趋于平稳或拒绝。</p><p>积极的一面是，老员工的流动率较低，而且通常要少得多。事实上，可能正是因为年长的员工倾向于留下来，雇主才觉得有必要像对待年轻员工那样对他们进行晋升、支付工资或认可。后者有更多的外部机会，因此可能需要不断地吸引他们。</p><p></p><p>这些关于老年工人的负面信号可能非常具有误导性。我们经常发现，年长员工较多的群体实际上比年轻员工较多的群体表现更好。与团体或组织层面相比，个人层面的发现存在不一致。</p><p>这表明，老年工人的生产力并不体现在他们自己对个人绩效的衡量上，而是体现在与他们一起工作的人的绩效上。我们称之为<em>溢出效应</em>。因此，举例来说，如果年长的员工不太可能跳槽，他们可以促使年轻的同事效仿，从而为他们的工作团队带来更多的稳定性并提高他们的工作效率。有关老年工人生产力的更多证据，请参阅我最近与 Richard A. Guzzo 和 Nicholas L. Anderson 进行的研究，我们在文章“<a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">年龄、经验和业务绩效：工作单位的元分析”</a>中讨论了该研究<a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">水平效应</a>”，发表在<cite>《工作、老龄化和退休》</cite>杂志上。</p><h6>组织如何确保将年龄多样性和包容性纳入其公平和多元化计划？</h6><p>同样，企业领导人普遍认为年长员工的生产力较低。由于它们的成本往往更高，因此它们更多地被视为负债而不是资产，尽管有大量证据表明事实并非如此。出于某种我难以解释的原因，打击年龄歧视在 DEI 议程上并不重要，尤其是与解决性别和种族不平等问题相比。我责怪 DEI 社区在这方面没有更加积极主动。</p><p>劳动力老龄化几乎在所有地方都是一个不争的事实。如果组织不能有效应对这一长期趋势的影响并确保有效管理年长员工，则可能会面临组织绩效下降的风险。实际上，他们可能会将毫无根据的刻板印象变成自我实现的结果。</p><p></p><p>我总是敦促我的客户进行严格的诊断工作，以评估他们自己员工队伍的现实，以确定溢出效应是否确实在他们的组织中发挥作用，并做出相应的反应。通过这个过程，他们中的许多人会发现他们拥有需要保护的资产，而不是需要丢弃的负债。</p><h6>是否对公司业绩或股价与调查显示的情况之间的相关性进行了分析？</h6><p>我进行了客户研究，其中我们将劳动力特征和管理实践与各种业务成果联系起来，包括盈利能力、财务和运营生产力、收入增长和客户保留率等。我们的结果好坏参半。在某些方面，我们发现工作组或单位组成的更大多样性可以提高业务绩效；在其他方面，我们没有发现任何影响或统计结果可以忽略不计。对这些研究结果最有力的回顾和综合是对上述年龄和任期影响的荟萃分析。该研究并未关注种族和性别的影响。</p><h6>组织可以采取哪些具体步骤来对抗这些偏见？</h6><p></p><p>我在<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite> 2023 年夏季刊上发表的文章“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/">开启职业公平的快车道</a>”直接回答了这个问题。我将解释组织如何使用此类建模的结果来帮助消除或减少人口统计数据对员工在工作中取得成功的影响。现实情况是，情境因素常常极大地影响员工取得成功的能力，而女性和有色人种则处于不利地位。</p><p>认识到自己没有让这些人才取得成功的雇主可以采用一种我称之为<em>主动职业管理的</em>方法来改变这一现实。这可能包括让更多的女性和有色人种担任监督或其他加速角色、改变报告关系、消除灵活工作的负面影响等。我在文章中分享了一个案例研究来说明这种方法的实际应用。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>消费者是否将您的企业视为正义的力量？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cynthia E. Clark. <p>辛西娅·E·克拉克 (Cynthia E. Clark) 博士是本特利大学管理学教授。她还是<cite>《商业与社会：道德、法律和数字环境》</cite> （Sage Publications，2020 年）一书的合著者，也是<cite>《Giving Voice to Values in the Boardroom》</cite> （Routledge，2021 年）一书的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[The public’s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s efforts to impose fines on businesses for greenwashing, point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald’s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Clark-Eco-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>公众对环境问题日益关注，加上美国联邦贸易委员会<a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/04/13/ftc-is-expected-crack-down-greenwashing/">对洗绿企业处以罚款</a>，都表明企业从事破坏环境的行为可能产生潜在后果。汉堡王、肯德基和麦当劳等公司最近都成为政府和投资者减少塑料垃圾压力的目标。去年， <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/blog/2022/04/55-million-total-ftc-settlements-kohls-and-walmart-challenge-bamboo-and-eco-claims-shed-light">Kohl&#39;s 和沃尔玛</a>分别达成了 250 万美元和 300 万美元的和解协议，因为他们错误地声称数十种人造丝纺织品实际上是由环保竹子制成的。</p><p>当如此大的、知名的公司发布虚假声明或未能采取行动时，就会导致错失机会、业绩与预期差距不断扩大，并最终损害消费者的声誉。那么，当涉及到我们环境的未来时，是什么让企业成为正义的力量呢？为了找到答案，本特利大学和盖洛普最近对 5,757 名美国人进行了一项调查，以评估他们对商业的看法及其对社会和环境产生积极影响的潜力。 <a href="https://www.bentley.edu/news-Announcing-the-Bentley-Gallup-Force-for-Good-survey-results">“Force for Good”调查的结果</a>突显了企业（无论大小）未能满足人们期望的领域，以及它们如何可以做得更好。</p><p></p><p>我们的研究清楚地表明了公众对科尔、麦当劳或沃尔玛等大公司的期望。略多的受访者 (53%) 表示，企业总体上对环境产生了负面影响。近三分之二 (65%) 的人表示他们对<em>大型</em>企业有这种感觉，而 16% 的人表示<em>小型</em>企业对地球/环境有负面影响。我们研究中的年轻受访者对企业总体抱有更高的期望，在 18 至 29 岁的受访者中，高达 81% 的受访者表示大型企业对地球产生负面影响，而 70 岁或以上的受访者中这一比例为 54%。</p><p>深入研究数据，我们发现超过十分之九的受访者将企业可以采取行动的四个社会和环境问题评为极其或有些重要：实行可持续制造（92%）；促进增加接受教育和培训的机会（92%）；向当地社区投入时间和金钱（92%）；并以对环境可持续的方式运营（91%）。只有三分之一的受访者表示，企业目前在这些领域中的任何一个领域都做得非常出色或良好，大约四分之一（26%）的人表示，企业在以环境可持续的方式运营方面做得非常出色或良好。</p><h3> T 恤实验</h3><p>关于可持续发展的一种观点是，企业应该为了更大的利益而履行环境责任——“行善以行善”的观点。另一种方法侧重于“做好事而做好事”的重要性，以便企业和社会都能从领导者的行动中受益。但这些方法是否处于紧张状态？需要吗？</p><p> “Force for Good”调查的一部分——我们称之为 T 恤实验——旨在更好地了解人们如何看待这种紧张局势。在几乎所有商品的价格都在上涨的情况下，我们询问受访者是否愿意根据不同公司的特点额外支付一件 T 恤费用。 63% 的受访者表示，如果生产 T 恤的公司因对环境产生积极影响而闻名，他们愿意额外支付 82% 的费用。对于 18 至 29 岁的受访者和女性来说，这一数字甚至更高：年轻人最有可能表示愿意支付更多费用（约十分之八），而女性中则有近十分之七。 （参见“T 恤实验的结果”。）这两个消费群体都是许多公司的关键市场。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> T 恤实验的结果</h4><p class="caption">根据年龄和性别，受访者在不同程度上表示他们愿意根据企业的可持续发展实践为同一产品支付更多费用。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig1-1.png" alt="T 恤实验的结果" /><br /></article></aside></div><p>当人们被问到愿意花多少钱购买这件 T 恤时，没有提供任何其他信息，回答的中位数是 10 美元。对于个人收入在 24,000 美元到 179,000 美元之间的人来说也是如此。换句话说，个人收入对他们赋予产品的价值几乎没有影响。</p><p></p><p>然后，受访者被问到，如果该公司因以下各项而闻名：对环境有积极影响、对当地社区产生积极影响、善待员工以及为慈善事业做出贡献，他们愿意多付多少钱。在这四个属性中，已知对环境有积极影响的公司的溢价最高，中位数为 7 美元。</p><p>我们的数据表明，美国人实际上愿意奖励做好事的公司。一家以积极的环保表现而闻名的公司可以对其产品收取更高的价格——这证明“做好事才能做好”是有效的。</p><p></p><h3>错误的二分法？</h3><p>大多数受访者认为良好的环境绩效和良好的财务绩效之间没有权衡。换句话说，他们相信两者可以同时发生，尽管商界领袖认为可持续实践会损害财务业绩。大约十分之七的受访者 (69%) 表示，优先考虑对社会产生积极影响的企业与竞争对手一样盈利 (47%) 或更高 (22%)。那些自称在拥有、领导或管理企业方面拥有专业知识的人，与那些没有这些专业知识的人相比，更有可能表示，优先考虑产生积极影响的企业至少与竞争对手一样有利可图。</p><p>不同政党的成员对于可持续发展的重要性存在显着的意见分歧。例如，84% 的民主党人表示，企业以环境可持续的方式运营极其重要，而共和党人的这一比例为 31%，独立人士的比例为 59%。然而，绝大多数共和党人 (80%) 表示可持续性至少在<em>某种程度上很</em>重要。这些观点可能会影响公司的许多行为，例如选择红色州与蓝色州的广告内容和支出金额以及产品的设计。</p><p></p><p>同样，我们发现不同种族身份之间存在显着差异。 70% 的黑人受访者、82% 的亚裔受访者、65% 的西班牙裔受访者和 59% 的白人受访者表示，他们认为企业以环境可持续的方式运营极其重要。当被问及对关注环境等长期利益与利润等短期利益有何看法时，77% 的亚洲受访者表示他们可能支持这种关注，而总体受访者的这一比例为 56%。黑人和西班牙裔受访者的这一数字都徘徊在 60% 左右。</p><p>即使我们以稍微不同的方式提出问题，受访者也不认为这是一种权衡，而是更多地认为是“两者兼而有之”的情况。例如，当被问及满足投资者的财务目标时，79% 的人表示他们认为这有些重要或极其重要。百分之八十八的受访者还表示，让世界变得更美好在某种程度上或极其重要。</p><h3>您的公司如何成为一股正义的力量？</h3><p>对广泛而多样的美国人的看法进行深入研究的结果表明，公司可以采取或计划采取一些行动。</p><p><strong>注意您在当地的足迹。</strong>小公司被认为在大多数与利益相关者相关的活动中表现更好。受访者认为小型企业对人们的生活产生积极影响的可能性是大型企业的两倍（分别为 82% 和 41%）。此外，受访者更有可能认为大型企业（38%）对美国人的整体生活产生负面影响，而对小型企业（4%）也持相同看法。这些数据，结合下图中不同年龄和性别的积极社区影响结果（参见“可持续发展对消费者来说很重要——但企业是否正在实践它？”），表明公司——尤其是大公司——应该改善与他们周围的社区。</p><p></p><p><strong>认识到年轻的美国人期望更多。</strong>千禧一代（1981 年至 1996 年出生）和 Z 世代（1997 年至 2012 年出生）比年长受访者对企业在社会和环境责任方面的期望更高。在我们的 T 恤实验中，82% 18 至 29 岁的受访者愿意花更多钱购买一家因对当地社区产生积极影响而闻名的公司生产的 T 恤。同样，年轻受访者 (73%) 比任何其他年龄组都更认同企业减少碳足迹和/或排放的努力很重要。公司需要对其客户和未来的员工负责其环境管理工作。</p><p><strong>注意绩效与期望的差距。</strong>环境利益相关者和监管机构正在关注公司负责任的环境管理的期望与其实际行为之间的任何差异，即绩效与期望差距。绝大多数受访者 (89%) 表示企业拥有“很大”或“一定”的能力对人们的生活产生积极影响，但只有 57% 的人表示企业在这方面非常有效或有些有效。在环境方面，调查结果显示，多个环境目标的“重要性”和“绩效”之间的绩效预期差距至少为 30 个百分点。在减少企业碳足迹、参与可持续制造以及让世界变得更美好等问题上，我们发现存在相当大的差距：在这三点上，52%至57%的受访者表示企业这样做极其重要，但只有 24% 到 28% 的人认为自己很优秀或擅长。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>可持续发展对消费者来说很重要——但企业是否在践行可持续发展？</h4><p class="caption">受访者对可持续发展实践重要性的看法与他们对企业实际实践的看法之间存在相当大的差距。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig2.png" alt="可持续发展对消费者来说很重要——但企业是否在践行可持续发展？" /><br /></article></aside></div><p>虽然拥有专门的可持续发展领导者、高级管理层的支持以及对员工和高管的教育是必要的，但在解决不断扩大的绩效与期望差距时保持警惕也很重要。在日益挑剔的商业环境中，领导者必须更加关注人们对公司所做事情的看法与他们实际所做的事情的比较。</p><p></p><p><strong>设定可持续发展目标。</strong>仔细考虑如何衡量你正在做的事情。这是获得高级管理层支持后合乎逻辑的下一步，它可以帮助您的公司确定已取得的进展以及存在的弱点或盲点。事实上，监管机构已提议要求公司披露如何制定气候相关目标并衡量实现这些目标的进展情况。考虑签署广泛认可和接受的目标，例如联合国全球契约 (UNGC) 的<a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">可持续发展目标</a>，这可以帮助您的公司逐步公开承诺实施行动计划。 UNGC 还要求每年发布进展报告，以帮助防止“漂绿”行为。</p><p></p><p>随着人们对环境可持续性的日益关注，了解不同利益相关者如何看待您的言论和行动至关重要。通过识别和理解当前的看法及其影响，正如本特利-盖洛普研究所做的那样，公司可以修改其环境承诺和流程，以确保他们努力成为一股向善的力量，这将使公司、其利益相关者和利益相关者受益。 ，最重要的是环境。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>主流的神话</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus Collins. <p>马库斯·柯林斯 (Marcus Collins) 是密歇根大学罗斯商学院的临床营销学教授，也是纽约维登肯尼迪公司的前战略主管。他是<cite>《为了文化：我们购买什么、做什么、以及我们想成为谁背后的力量》一书</cite>的作者（PublicAffairs，2023 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com For years, McDonald’s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension. The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Collins_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">贝内代托·克里斯托法尼/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>多年来，麦当劳似乎体现了美国饮食中的一切错误。该品牌已成为食品选择的象征，导致肥胖和高血压的发病率不断上升。</p><p>该公司花了十多年的时间，试图通过向美国消费者传达有关其更新菜单的信息来对抗美国消费者的这种看法，该菜单提供了更符合当代饮食趋势的更健康的替代品，但没有成功。麦当劳的销售额逐年下降，其品牌认知度持续下降。</p><p></p><p>最后，该公司决定继续进攻。麦当劳没有与反对派的仇恨作斗争，也没有试图赢得中间派的支持，而是决定把重点放在它的粉丝身上——那些自认为是麦当劳爱好者的人，尽管该品牌受到了尖酸刻薄的批评。该公司的策略包括推出“Famous Orders”活动，庆祝超级明星粉丝（如嘻哈大亨特拉维斯·斯科特和韩国流行巨星 BTS）最喜欢的菜单项目；打造针对成人的开心乐园餐；并推广粉丝自己的菜单技巧。此举充分利用了这些麦当劳爱好者对麦当劳的喜爱，不仅激活了他们的集体消费，还激励他们代表品牌传播信息。这一战略的结果是，从 2018 年到 2021 年，麦当劳的全球收入增长了 10.4%，并且休眠顾客又回来了：例如，前来购买 Travis Scott 餐食的顾客中有超过四分之一没有光顾过麦当劳。连锁一年多了。似乎一夜之间，麦当劳从一个警示故事变成了品牌营销的宠儿和广告效果的案例研究。</p><p></p><p>这里发生了什么？传统智慧告诉我们，在一个意见日益两极分化的世界里，我们最好的选择是安抚中间派，哪怕只是因为那是市场的大多数。对于许多公司来说，这似乎也是一个安全的选择，因为中间立场不太可能疏远潜在客户。但麦当劳向我们展示了当你放弃这种传统方法时会发生什么。它没有试图与大众市场对话，而是选择了站在一边。它选择拥抱爱，对抗恨，并放弃了吸引庞大但冷漠的中间市场的想法。通过这样做，麦当劳的营销活动激活了大批粉丝，他们不仅消费，还赢得了其他人的支持。麦当劳的认识对当代营销人员来说是一个重要的教训：如果你想让人们移动，你必须选择一方。认为打到中间就可以获胜的想法是一个误导性的神话。</p><p></p><h3>选择一方</h3><p>营销的核心功能是影响人们采取期望的行为。也就是说，我们去市场是为了让人们行动起来——购买、投票、回收、订阅、下载、观看、传播福音、戴口罩——并推动一系列其他理想的行为结果将有利于我们的组织或利益。什么对人影响最大？好吧，根据我们对人类行为的了解，我们最受其他人的影响——不是广告，不是价值主张，而是其他人。更具体地说，<em>我们</em>最受员工的影响：那些遵守文化上既定惯例和期望的人，这些惯例和期望决定了像我们这样的人可以接受的行为。这些人通常拥有相似的世界观，因此坚持共同的生​​活方式，努力促进他们之间的社会团结——他们的亚文化。他们以亚文化的方式消费，以亚文化的方式投票，以亚文化的方式行事，因为这就是对他们这样的人的期望。</p><p>如果这些人因为像他们这样的人（他们的文化）有共同的惯例和期望而反对你，那么让他们代表你采取行动的可能性就会很小。这就是为什么右翼共和党人不会费心试图说服左倾民主党人。相反，共和党人向他们的基础群体说话——他们对世界有着相似的看法，表达了与品牌相似的文化特征，并且更倾向于与品牌步调一致，作为社会团结的行为。他们认同该群体的成员并遵循其行为规范。</p><p>另一方面，那些处于人口中间的人则本质上冷漠且厌恶风险。尽管他们可能有意见，但他们在任一方向上都缺乏坚定的信念，因此不太可能采取行动。在政治上，他们不参加初选或候选人竞选活动；相反，他们袖手旁观，等待事情如何发展。他们在品牌方面的行为是相同的。</p><p>中间并不急于采用新产品。他们不是第一个对营销传播做出回应的人，也不太可能参与支持者和反对者之间的辩论。他们通过先退后一步并观察其他人的反应，来降低自己与普遍接受的观点不一致的风险。</p><p>转移注意力的是，我们将这种冷漠视为说服他们站在一边或另一边的机会。但事实是，他们通常不会被任何营销传播说服。相反，他们也会从其他人那里得到暗示——有时是那些支持你的人，有时是那些反对你的人。</p><p></p><p>考虑到这一点，很明显，在两极分化的情况下，当我们激活集体意愿时，营销人员让人们行动起来的机会要大得多，而不是试图说服批评者，甚至说服冷漠的人。然而，从历史上看，营销人员将精力集中在中间部分，因为它代表了最大的市场机会。然而，当我们选择针对最有可能采取行动的人时，我们成功影响行为的机会就会增加。当我们有效地做到这一点时，我们就会催化传播效应，导致产品、行为或想法在整个人群中级联传播，这要归功于社会传染的过程——由于直接或间接的影响、行为、认知和欲望的传播。 “像我们这样的人”的同伴影响。</p><h3>传播的力量</h3><p>传播的理念要求营销人员放弃针对中产阶级（大多数人口居住的地方）的传统方法。如上所述，除了有效性值得怀疑之外，达到中间水平还需要昂贵的媒体支出（想想黄金时段的电视和超级碗广告），并将营销信息置于一个嘈杂且充满竞争信息的舞台上。营销人员很少关注边缘人群，传统观点告诉我们，这个人群太小、太小众。但现在主流的一切都曾经是从边缘开始的：它始于亚文化，然后传播成为流行文化。</p><p>例如，如果你 20 年前喜欢漫画书，你会被认为是书呆子。然而如今，全球许多收视率最高的电影，例如漫威的<cite>《复仇者联盟</cite>》系列，都源自漫画。二十年前，如果你沉迷于电子游戏，你会被视为一个不成熟的成年人。如今，游戏不仅被认为很酷，而且还是一个价值数十亿美元的产业。事实上，现在的正常现象曾经是边缘现象。由于社会传染，一个社区的文化特征从边缘传播到中间——从亚文化传播到流行文化。它是从外到内发生的，而不是从内到外发生的。</p><p></p><p>与传统的营销传播不同，通过这种传播实现的影响力和随后的采用并不依赖于人们听到来自公司或品牌的信息。 （这有帮助，但不是必需的。）相反，人们从他们信任的人（像他们一样的人）那里听到它，这增加了他们被收养的可能性。正如网络科学家尼古拉斯·克里斯塔基斯（Nicholas Christakis）和詹姆斯·福勒（James Fowler）所说，“当一小群人开始一致行动——表现出相似的明显症状时——流行病就会通过情绪传染沿着社交网络关系传播，而大群体的情绪就会迅速同步。”这就是当你激活集体意愿时所催化的网络效应。不要关注中间的人：关注那些以你的方式看待世界的人。选择一方，他们就会说服旁观者、被动者、冷漠者。</p><p></p><p> Although broadcast messaging might get our attention, it&#39;s the influence of people like us, people with whom we identify, that changes our outlook and, subsequently, our behaviors. This provides a new perspective, and corresponding strategies, for marketers who aim to communicate with consumers in a culture where ideological binaries seem to divide the market. Like McDonald&#39;s did, marketers benefit from choosing a side that is most likely to move and then activating its members so that they might convert people on the brand&#39;s behalf. Status quo practices position the middle as a safe bet. However, the dynamics of cultural diffusion subvert these long-standing best practices for connecting with consumers and influencing behavioral adoption, and demand that today&#39;s practitioners develop new strategies and accompanying tactics.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sustainability Progress Is Stalled at Most Companies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[CB Bhattacharya and Rob Jekielek. <p>CB Bhattacharya is director of the Center for Sustainable Business and the HJ Zoffer Chair in Sustainability and Ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business at the University of Pittsburgh. Rob Jekielek is managing director of The Harris Poll.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Sustainability & Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability-Driven Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else’s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual.1 On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bhattacharya-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else&#39;s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming their business models to be more sustainable have embedded sustainability into their corporate DNA. This means that they have endowed their employees with a sense of sustainable ownership, spurring them to engage in more sustainability-supporting behaviors. When every employee integrates environmental and social concerns into every business decision, sustainability progress is accelerated — an aspirational goal for all companies.</p><p> To shed light on the state of play in embedding sustainability and identify key bottlenecks, the Center for Sustainable Business at the University of Pittsburgh collaborated with The Harris Poll to conduct a survey of US employees. We wanted to find out whether their employers were taking measures that our earlier research had identified as important to prompting employees to conduct business through a sustainability lens. Our survey drew responses from 1,056 employees, representative of the US employee base. We defined sustainability for the respondents as “integrating environmental and societal concerns into business decisions and actions.”</p><p></p><p> We asked respondents to rate their level of agreement with a series of 19 statements about the status quo, such as “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance,” on a 4-point Likert scale (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”). We also presented respondents with a series of 12 issues that could pose challenges to sustainability progress, such as “Sustainability is not built into our business strategy,” and asked them to rate the extent to which that is an actual challenge at their company (from “major challenge” to “not at all a challenge”).</p><p> Roughly one-third of the respondents asserted that their employers have made significant strides in their sustainability journeys. Although that number might sound low given the enormity of the task facing us, the good news is that there is momentum, which we can help accelerate by pointing out the roadblocks as perceived by employees. Below, we provide six key recommendations that emerged from our data for managers seeking to embed sustainability in the organizational culture and business models.</p><p> <strong>Establish a purpose based on values.</strong> Purpose is a business&#39;s raison d&#39;être — the answer to the all-important question, “Why do we do what we do?” Paul Polman, former CEO of Unilever and a leader in the corporate sustainability movement, has said, “Sustainability is totally driven by purpose.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Organizations that are successful at embedding sustainability articulate the societal benefit they aim to deliver to their stakeholders, and this overarching purpose guides everything the organization does.</p><p> In our study, 36% of the respondents strongly agreed with the statement “My company wants to make a difference in people&#39;s lives, not just make profits,” while 33% strongly agreed with “My company has a higher purpose beyond profit maximization.” If purpose is the starting point for sustainability, we aren&#39;t doing very well; it is apparent that the profit-maximization narrative is alive and well. Consistently, 43% of employees cited short-term focus, a lack of investor interest, and, importantly, “Our leaders don&#39;t believe in sustainability,” as challenges. Unless CEOs and top management teams realize that profit is the <em>consequence</em> of value creation for all stakeholders and not the starting point for strategy development and execution, progress will be stifled. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p></p><p> <strong>Bake sustainability into corporate strategy.</strong> Academic researchers and others have noted that efforts to make meaningful progress toward sustainability must be driven by corporate strategy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Doing so increases the likelihood that, over time, “doing the green thing” will be seen as a normal part of employees&#39; jobs, and more and more decisions will be made through the lens of sustainability. With only 29% of respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance” and 27% with “Sustainability is core to how my company executes our business strategy,” it appears that we have a long way to go. Consistent with the status quo, 43% agreed that their company&#39;s failure to build sustainability into its business strategy represents a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Train employees, and incentivize actions that advance sustainability.</strong> Companies that are successful in engaging their workforce have invested in training that gives employees guidance on how to improve sustainability. With only 30% of employees surveyed strongly agreeing with the statement “I understand how I can improve my company&#39;s sustainability performance through my role,” there seems to be a dearth of role-specific knowledge at the individual employee level. Lack of training was cited as a major/moderate challenge by 44%, while a similar number (45%) indicated that they don&#39;t know what actions to take to improve sustainability performance. Companies need to invest more in training and sustainability knowledge creation so that employees know <em>what</em> they can do in their roles and <em>how</em> to do what needs to be done.</p><p> Managers must also do more to provide employees with incentives to advance the sustainability agenda: Forty-nine percent of those surveyed found the lack of such incentives to be a major or moderate hurdle to improving sustainability performance. Leaders should also consider whether the management culture encourages engagement and intrinsic motivation by giving employees the autonomy to solve sustainability challenges, which often require creative thinking. However, when we asked survey respondents to rate their level of agreement with the statements “My company allows me to make a lot of sustainability-related decisions on my own” and “My company gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out sustainability initiatives,” we found that, at most, 29% of respondents strongly agreed.</p><p> <strong>Create a sustainability culture in your organization.</strong> Managers can keep sustainability salient in the organizational culture by communicating progress, celebrating milestones, recognizing achievements, and collaborating on solutions both internally and with industry partners. Our research has identified the lack of a sustainability culture as one of the biggest impediments to progress, with 48% of respondents indicating that that is a major or moderate impediment at their organization. Communicating sustainability progress to employees is a key component of a sustainability culture, because it keeps issues top of mind. Celebrating successes will pique employee interest and legitimize the importance of sustainability to the organization — but only 31% of respondents strongly agreed that their company celebrates sustainability successes.</p><p></p><p> Collaborating with traditional competitors — which is increasingly necessary to address those complex “ <a href="https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/tragedy-of-the-commons-impact-on-sustainability-issues">tragedy of the commons</a> ” problems — signals to employees that the company is serious about transformational change and reinforces the culture to employees. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> With only 25% of survey respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company collaborates with other organizations to address complex sustainability issues,” it is evident that much work is required to open corporate leaders&#39; eyes to the potential of progress via collaboration.</p><p> <strong>Conduct business through a sustainability lens.</strong> Imagine the progress we would make if every employee in every company — from the mailroom to the boardroom — integrated environmental and social issues into every business decision they made. This, in our view, is conducting business through the lens of sustainability — an aspirational but necessary goal to reach if we are to surmount our existential crises. As previous research has shown, employees taking individual ownership of sustainability is a key driver for engaging in sustainability behaviors. In our survey, 28% of respondents strongly agreed with the statement “Employees at my company take ownership of improving sustainability performance,” while 45% identified a belief among employees that “sustainability is someone else&#39;s responsibility” as a challenge. This lack of personal ownership of sustainability performance is reflected in our survey results: Only 27% of respondents strongly agreed that they “invested ideas and creativity” to help their company be more sustainable, and just 24% strongly agreed that every business decision they make is viewed through the lens of sustainability.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Bridge the last mile.</strong> We noted a significant difference between how corporate and front-line employees responded to our questions. Compared with front-line nonmanagers working in roles such as customer support, managers working in corporate roles were, on average, about 15% more likely to see sustainability as embedded.</p><p> To ensure that their commitment to sustainability is real and provides tangible benefits to their organizations, leaders must address this last-mile gap between corporate and front-line employees. Broadly communicated messaging about the corporate purpose and environmental, social, and governance targets might not suffice in this instance; there is a real need to drive sustainability through practical initiatives and actions that can be integrated into daily tasks and routines that employees perform across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> Interestingly, perceiving sustainability as more embedded in the organization also opens employees&#39; eyes to the roadblocks and challenges that impede progress. Our data shows that employees who are more engaged and perceive sustainability to be more embedded also perceive more roadblocks, on average, than those who are less engaged.</p><p> The implication here is that as companies bridge the last-mile gap in embedding sustainability, they should be prepared to field more questions and listen to more opinions as employee engagement on the issue increases. Companies should use one-on-one coaching, action playbooks, and tailored communication to make sustainability everyone&#39;s job. Companies need to be prepared to invest more resources into embedding sustainability — and get the entire organization to conduct business through the sustainability lens.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Robots Can Enhance Performance Management for Humans</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Hong and Lynn Wu. <p>Bryan Hong is associate professor of entrepreneurship and management at the Bloch School of Management at the University of Missouri-Kansas City. Lynn Wu is associate professor of operations, information, and decisions at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Efficiency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to invest in robotics for their business. Our research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Wu-Robots-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/advanced%20electronics/our%20insights/growth%20dynamics%20in%20industrial%20robotics/industrial-robotics-insights-into-the-sectors-future-growth-dynamics.ashx">invest in robotics</a> for their business. Our research has found an equally and perhaps more important transformation taking place: The adoption of robots is improving companies&#39; ability to recognize and reward good employee performance.</p><p> Within every organization, leaders face a fundamental question: How do we get the best from our people? One of the most common methods is offering monetary rewards — usually, periodic bonuses — that are linked to performance. This practice is grounded in the idea that better performance should be more highly rewarded. But that approach is rarely simple to implement in practice because it requires that performance be measured well enough to be evaluated effectively. This is challenging to accomplish for most roles and even more so for individual employees. Because so much work is done in teams and managers can&#39;t monitor the specific activity of each employee or accurately measure individual performance, many organizations choose to pay bonuses based on team or company performance rather than on individual performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p></p><h3> Measuring Human Performance When Colleagues Are Robots</h3><p> What does all this have to do with robots? In our research, we have found that companies that adopt robots improve their ability to measure human performance. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> To illustrate, let&#39;s say you&#39;re working in a team of two. Your manager can see and evaluate your combined productivity as a team but not what each of you is doing individually at all times. In theory, both of you are supposed to be contributing equally; in practice, you&#39;re doing far more of the work, which isn&#39;t visible to your busy manager.</p><p> Then, let&#39;s say your teammate is replaced with a robot. As a machine, the robot is much more precise and consistent in doing its work tasks and might even provide data about its performance while operating. Because it&#39;s so consistent and transparent, any disruptions or spikes in productivity can much more clearly be identified as coming from either the robot or from you. If there are others in your organization who work with the same type of robot in a similar way, then it&#39;s much easier to see how their individual productivity varies from yours.</p><p> In other words, because robots are, by their very nature, much more consistent and transparent than humans, human activity becomes easier to observe if robots join the team. The more robots there are relative to humans, the easier it is to distinguish and measure individual human performance.</p><p></p><p> In one real-world example, a repair facility at a major US-based electronics company experienced a dramatic improvement in its ability to observe employee productivity after robots were implemented to assist workers in the repair process. Because robots, unlike humans, do not get physically tired while performing repetitive tasks, they were able to perform more consistently. This reduced variance in the production process and allowed managers to more clearly observe individual employee behaviors. Many employees followed a regular pattern of being more productive in the morning than in the afternoon, with substantial variance in their afternoon productivity. As a result, many workers ended up with more repairs to finish later in the day as they rushed to meet their daily quotas. This “cramming” of work was especially problematic because it typically resulted in more errors due to the workers having rushed.</p><p> Integrating robots into the repair process eased the tracking of individual employee productivity in two ways. First, robots made different types of errors than humans. The robots&#39; errors were consistent, which made human errors easier to distinguish. Second, the robots themselves provided precise data about their own performance, which made it easier to isolate performance outcomes, both positive and negative, caused by human behavior. This data generation capability allowed managers to better monitor productivity overall and to more easily detect weaknesses in the production process. Managers at the repair facility, for example, hadn&#39;t been aware of the extent of the afternoon cramming behavior until robots were incorporated into the production process. Once the problem was clearly identified, they were able to reorganize the work process to reduce errors; overall error rates at the facility have since improved.</p><p></p><p> These types of improvements in performance measurement can have especially dramatic effects on productivity in combination with performance-based incentives. If it&#39;s easier to observe and measure the performance of individual employees within organizations, good performers — who may have received little reward or recognition because of measurement challenges — become easier to identify and reward, and leaders really can do better in getting the best from their teams. And this is exactly what we find in our research: Companies that adopt robots are also more likely to adopt bonus incentives tied directly to individual performance as opposed to team or organizational performance. With better measurement comes increased rewards for an organization&#39;s good performers, and a more productive workplace. Using robots is fairer for the people who work at an organization.</p><p></p><p> Robots are changing the nature of work. Beyond eliminating some jobs and creating new ones, robots are also changing organizations&#39; ability to get the best from their people, as well as the way we experience work itself. Robots offer an exciting opportunity for businesses to redesign the roles and responsibilities of the humans that work with them, giving those companies a competitive edge over rivals not because of superior technology but because of better processes. The robot revolution isn&#39;t going to eliminate the need for humans. Rather, it&#39;s bringing both new challenges and opportunities for identifying, rewarding, and managing human talent.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Detecting the Good and the Bad With AI: Airbnb&#39;s Naba Banerjee</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operational Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Predictive Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Psychological Safety]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Naba Banerjee’s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Naba Banerjee&#39;s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to let curiosity be her guide as she applies her previous data science experience to the travel industry.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Naba joins hosts Shervin Khodabandeh and Sam Ransbotham to talk about how she and her team use AI and machine learning to increase the safety of the guests and hosts who use Airbnb&#39;s platform. She also discusses collaboration between humans and machines and the importance of recognizing that neither is an infallible decision maker. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-S7-E1-Banerjee-Airbnb-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Naba Banerjee"></p><h4> Naba Banerjee, Airbnb</h4><p> Naba Banerjee is the director of trust product and operations at Airbnb, overseeing the company&#39;s efforts to combat fraud, build trust between hosts and guests, and stop bad actors from using the platform. Her most recent work includes the development of Airbnb&#39;s reservation screening technology, which helps to identify users making potentially high-risk reservations and prevent them from taking advantage of the platform.</p><p> Banerjee has over two decades of experience building products that deliver innovative, customer-centric solutions. She joined Airbnb after spending 13 years at Walmart.com, where she played an instrumental role in the evolution of product management, including shipping packages to customers more quickly and building mobile apps to enable customers to check out faster.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-banerjee"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Machine learning can detect fraudulent activity, but it may also miss good behavior. Find out how one platform company manages these risks and trade-offs on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m Naba Banerjee from Airbnb, and you are listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Today, Shervin and I are speaking with Naba Banerjee, director of trust product and operations at Airbnb. Naba, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you; a pleasure to be here.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think most people know Airbnb, but maybe tell us a brief overview of the company and what you do.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Airbnb stands for a place which fosters connection and belonging. Millions and millions of hosts open up their homes to complete strangers, and you and I and our families get to travel to an exotic destination, and instead of staying at a hotel, you actually get to truly immerse yourself in the local culture. And at times, if you&#39;re really lucky, you get to stay at the house of a host and actually experience hosting as it&#39;s meant to be, thereby creating and fostering connection and belonging.</p><p> And in this world that is increasingly becoming insular and connection is becoming a rare thing, I am so glad to be part of a company that is trying to create more connection. And what my team does, the trust and safety team at Airbnb, is along the entire customer journey, right from the time that you create an account on Airbnb throughout the journey. At times, it is possible that something could go wrong: A fake account could get created, or your account could get taken over. The listing you&#39;re trying to stay at could be a fake listing; the reviews you&#39;re looking at may not be exactly genuine. But our job is to make sure that you can focus on your magical stay, the host can focus on being the perfect host, and we try to anticipate some of these risks, and we minimize the risk of those kinds of issues from happening. And using technology and data to enable that magical user journey is what my team does.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think we all hear headlines where something goes wrong. How much goes wrong in the course of the gazillions of transactions that you do?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. In 2021, we had around 70 million trips that happened on Airbnb, and less than 0.1% of those trips resulted in a host or a guest reporting potentially an issue that happened in that stay. And when our team went in and investigated and actually looked at where the real harm happened or somebody had to be removed from the platform, that number is even smaller.</p><p> I know that even one bad incident is probably too bad and should not be happening, but in the bigger scale of things, what you come back to realize is the majority of people are actually good. Ninety-nine point nine percent of people are meaning to just go about their daily business, enjoy a great stay, or be a great host. But sometimes, [on] that very rare occasion when that bad thing happens, we want to make sure that we reduce the risk of that.</p><p> If you really look at where a person is causing harm to another person, those incidents are like a fraction of a fraction of a fraction. But when we talk about safety, we&#39;re looking at [things like] a carbon monoxide gas leak. It could be slip and fall; it could be property damage, where glass broke and you probably had a stain on your carpet. We are also looking at those kinds of issues.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I&#39;m hearing from what you&#39;re saying is, your role is, No. 1, a good role. You&#39;re the protector of the good and the “warder-offer” of evil, right?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I love that. You should be part of our branding team.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s a good thing, right? It&#39;s a very purposeful role. And the second part of it is, you&#39;re talking about microscopically small incidents.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, needles in a haystack.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Right? And those are fun problems. Tell us more about under the hood — what happens?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I would say it&#39;s three parts. One is, we start with the “why,” which is — you framed it really well — that we are the protector of the good and trying to ward off the bad. We can never say that we stop everything bad. Like, to Sam&#39;s point, you cannot do that. But how are we learning and getting better? And that&#39;s where AI and ML [machine learning] comes in, where [we ask], “How can we use [the] power of data and technology to learn and get better?” And every year, the risks don&#39;t stay the same; the data keeps growing.</p><p> And then the second thing is, “How do we use technology responsibly?” Which is, you could go too blunt and try to block as much as possible to specifically look at fraud and safety incidents and keep them down, but then, if the data that you are using to make these decisions has bias in it, is potentially creating unfairness, then you could close off your doors to a lot of good people who genuinely are just trying to have a good stay. So [it&#39;s about] using technology responsibly. … It is having self-governing mechanisms, which is, we have our privacy team, our data privacy team, our infosec team, our anti-discrimination teams, which are … almost like mirrors to the trust team. [There are also] other teams in Airbnb, where every time we are really laser-focused on this particular fraud vector, this bot detection, this account-takeover detection or party detection, they are constantly making sure that are we using the data in a safe way and a transparent way, giving users control and then not introducing bias.</p><p> And then, lastly, having ways for us to give people a path back, which is, we are going to — based on the data available to us, and the technology available to us, and the maturity of that technology — make our best possible decision. But if we get it wrong, can we create transparency and a process for users to appeal and get back on the platform when we do block them or remove them so that, again, we can learn and get better? So that, at the highest level, is how my team is working under the hood.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And what are some of the use cases?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> One of the use cases that we have talked about quite a bit is, you know … I&#39;ll take you on a little story, which is, when I joined the trust team in 2020, the world had just shut down; the pandemic was raging. And very similar to how the world was waiting for a vaccine, while waiting for a vaccine, we went into lockdown mode.</p><p> That was a blunt instrument … to prevent people from exposing themselves to situations which would make them unsafe. Similarly, Airbnb became an unfortunate product-market fit for unauthorized house parties. When the hotels and bars shut down, unfortunately that less than 1% or 0.1% of users who were looking for places where they could throw these parties, they started renting out Airbnbs. And as a result, we realized that it was causing a lot of pain to our communities of hosts and guests who use this platform, which was based on a foundation of trust. So initially, we had to use some very blunt instruments.</p><p> We first instituted our global party ban, saying that Airbnb does not allow for any kind of party whatsoever. Second, we started looking at some patterns and found that someone under 25 booking an entire home for just one night or two nights less than 50 or so miles away from their home — those seem to be all signals that lead to parties. When parties happen, we usually find … that account was created yesterday. Then we implemented a blunt rule called “under 25,” and we put that in place. Now, we had to be careful, because those rules don&#39;t exactly work globally. But that worked in North America, and we saw right away that there was a reduction in the number of unauthorized parties.</p><p> But over time, just as it happens with rules, we saw that people started to game those rules. They would get an older friend to book the reservation for them. And instead of one night, they would book it for three nights, and so on and so forth. [And] the impact on good users was so high that we said, “We kind of need to move to machine learning. We need to get smarter.” And so we did our first pilot in Australia, where we segmented the place and looked at the place that had this new party model that we&#39;d built versus the other. Do we see a reduction? And again, this is like looking for a needle in the haystack, but we still saw 35% fewer parties in the area that had the party model versus not. And when we started experimenting in North America, we did see that it was as effective as the heuristic, with lesser impact to good users.</p><p> And that kind of gave us the confidence to keep moving forward, because not doing anything was not an option. We had to do something and had to be smart about it. That was one of the use cases where we could go out and talk about it — not claiming that we are stopping all parties, but at least Airbnb is taking a strong stance about it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> One common thread that I&#39;m hearing in how you&#39;re describing the problem and the solution is a need for constant adaptability and ongoing learning, and using the right instrument for the right job. At times it&#39;s a rule, then maybe its unsupervised learning, then there&#39;s a human intervention. It does sound quite multidisciplinary, including the part where the rules change, or the fraudster&#39;s mode of operation changes, and you also have the issue of “Is it too blunt? Does it limit some unintended but good or benign behaviors?” How does the human and machine collaboration or interaction work in these situations?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You summarized it really well, Shervin, which is, it&#39;s not a one-and-done thing. You build it, and then you have to constantly learn and optimize from even the kind of decisions you are making, as well as how the world around you is evolving. And that is an area [that] humans are really good at, which is, you do have to have the discipline of training your models with the latest data, with the right data, making trade-off decisions on what is the optimal threshold at which you are going to say, “OK, this is risky, and we are ready to use that risk.”</p><p> At Airbnb, we have been constantly on this journey of how to leverage humans in the loop. I have a trust operations team in addition to the product and planning teams. This operations team constitutes full-time employees as well as agents globally. And whenever we build a new model, in the beginning we often have the model make a risk threshold-based decision: “This is the top 1%. This is the next tranche. This is the next tranche.” And at times, we will route that to human beings to then create labels on top of that to say, “I agree with the model&#39;s decision,” or, “I don&#39;t agree with the model&#39;s decision,” which then serves as training data back to the model.</p><p> And then, when we have more confidence in the decision-making capability of the model, we would go toward auto-decisioning. This party model, to your point, right now it&#39;s completely auto-decisioned. But what ends up happening is, when we get an appeal back from a user saying, “I was incorrectly blocked,” that then serves as data that&#39;s coming by the customer telling us. And then an agent looks at that appeal and says, “Actually yes, this decision was incorrect.” And if the agent made a correct decision, that customer appealed correctly, and no incident happened, we know that that was a false positive.</p><p> But let&#39;s say the agent approved, and then that customer went on to throw a party; that was a false negative. We are learning from that continuously, but we do it iteratively. First, we try to have the model direct to a human. And again, there is no guarantee that the human is better at decision-making than the model, but we constantly measure the performance. Then we go toward higher-order decisioning [with less] human decisioning. And sometimes we will also have … let&#39;s say the party model makes decisions. People go about their merry way, have the reservation. Sometimes after the reservation has been booked, we will also still have humans look at the top 1% risky reservations to try and correct anything that they can.</p><p> So it is either trying to balance that out as to, when are humans the right people to make the decision? When should the machine make the decision? It&#39;s been a not-easy, nonlinear journey that we have been on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned at first you&#39;re maybe reviewing more cases and then learning from those cases. But at the same time, you have people … these 70 million transactions are happening constantly. And, for example, when you gave the illustration of the hotel … shutdown at the beginning of the pandemic, that&#39;s a time where it&#39;s happening to individual hosts and customers. How do you balance that trade-off of needing to get something in place quickly [while] at the same time needing to go through a process?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That probably is the hardest thing, and the hardest thing in my entire career I would say that I have dealt with. Before this, I was managing all of product for Samsclub.com, which is part of Walmart, and I thought my job was hard then. And while we were serving customers, helping them check out, it still felt like we were on a growth path, and we could choose how fast we grew or how slowly we grew. And I always had teams that were looking at people who were trying to check out [but] couldn&#39;t and serving them while we were building longer-term architecture, but people&#39;s lives were not at stake; [it was] people&#39;s money — fraudsters using stolen credit cards and swindling the company of millions of dollars.</p><p> There is a team at Airbnb that is trying to protect the good and ward off the bad. What we do is that you have to get really good at prioritization, which is also very hard to do in the world of trust and safety.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And in many ways, I mean, the choices are what, Sam, you said in the beginning: These kinds of economies are not risk-free. They cannot be risk-free. And the good collectively outweighs the evil, so then it becomes all about prioritization. But I have to say, we&#39;ve talked to many people in analogous roles that you have, in other organizations — you mentioned Sam&#39;s Club, others — where they&#39;re using technology, digital AI/ML to drive a variety of use cases. I think yours stands out in the sense that it is a continuous balancing act, and the stakes are high. And then you have this sort of thread of purpose and the humility of saying, “Well, we believe that we&#39;ll make mistakes, and the system cannot be mistake-free.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But over time, things are getting better. Which brings me to my next question: How do you measure this, your effectiveness? Is it in terms of number of incidents, and some severity and frequency of bad things happening?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m glad you asked this question, because I was naturally going to go toward this, which is, at the highest level, the metrics that we measure ourselves on are number of fraud incidents per million trips, number of safety incidents per million trips, as well as good user impact. That&#39;s the balancing metric to see “How many good listings did we block? How many good hosts and good guests did we prevent from moving forward to truly understand our false positives and false negatives?” But at the end of the day, it&#39;s good trips that we are looking at across the board.</p><p> We are also looking at dollars in terms of fraud loss that is potentially happening. We are looking at customer support tickets that are coming in, user NPS [Net Promoter Scores] resulting from anyone who encounters a friction that is thrown by our teams. So at a basic level, we are looking at these metrics. But one of the challenges that, for the first time, again, in my career I&#39;ve run into — not so much in the fraud world, where we can A/B test — we are constantly iterating our models.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You are probably also, when you do that, preventing quite benign behaviors and intentions as well. But as you said, there is a point where the human judgment needs to trump and say that this is something where even the risk to one person might be too high. And yes, I mean, we always talk about exploration and exploitation when it comes to machine learning, and sort of ongoing feedback loops, but there&#39;s a cost to learning, always, right? But when I send you a marketing message you may not like, the cost of learning is very minimal, so I will send you many of them, and I&#39;ll do all kinds of A/B/X testing. But when I do that kind of A/B testing to groups or populations where the stakes are higher, then you might as well make that human judgment call of not doing it and relying on retrospective data.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I think you elucidated that point quite well for us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And one question that we ask ourselves is, what makes a human being trust another human being? What makes a human being trust Airbnb? And we are realizing that we can [train] all kinds of models in the background, and you wouldn&#39;t even know whether you were in the risk threshold 1% or 2%, or marked as a good user.</p><p> But there is also a dialogue that needs to happen between Airbnb and you as a guest or you as a host, or between the host and the guest, that truly instills trust. Like when we ask someone, “Would you be comfortable sending your 17-year-old girl to a stranger&#39;s house in Greece, when she wants to backpack before joining college?” You can probably tell this is a personal experience. I have a 17-year-old who&#39;s about to go to college. And I realized that the first thought is, “No — not happening,” and I run trust and safety at Airbnb. But then when I think, “Well, if I could talk to the host; if she&#39;s going to stay with someone else in a house; if that person is a mom like me …”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And we as Airbnb could say, “We are running all these models in the background; don&#39;t worry, your daughter is safe” — I don&#39;t think that&#39;s going to fly. I think as a parent, you will want to have the information you need to see, even though your judgment may not be better than the machine&#39;s. So we are also working on, what is it that we need to say, that we need to do? And sometimes when we say things like, “Airbnb is not going to allow one-night stays that are booked at the last minute within the same neighborhood,” I think it makes a lot of parents feel better too, that OK, at least this option is gone. They will probably figure something else out. And that message cannot be convoluted. That message has to be simple. That message has to be clearly understood. And in addition to asking people what not to do, we also need to encourage people on what good behaviors they should do, like, talk to the host, talk to the guest, ask questions.</p><p> We have launched a program for solo female travelers because we were starting to see a slightly higher rate of maybe personal safety incidents in private rooms with solo female travelers. We started encouraging [women to] find out, is there going to be a lock in your room? Is that lock going to be working? Will you have access to the bathroom just by yourself? Which spaces are shared? Which are not? So this was not a model that was stopping anything. This was simply an educational module that we had published in multiple languages, which was really helpful for our solo travelers. Part of my team&#39;s work is not just to build invisible defenses but also to create trust and the perception of trust upfront through education and messaging.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. I have to say, you mentioned you&#39;re a mother of five. And I have to say, I think you stand on very solid ground when it comes to telling your kids what they can and cannot do, because you have so much data and so much experience, versus me when I say something and they&#39;re like, “Well, how would you know?” And you could say, “Well, trust me; I do 70 million transactions a year, and I know what&#39;s going on.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And growing.是的。 I&#39;m happy to talk to your kids, by the way. Anytime.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes, that would be great. I&#39;ll take you up on that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing about your measurements that I thought was interesting, maybe come back a little bit to that. You mentioned some positive metrics, too. So I think it&#39;s a little tempting, and I think even in this conversation we&#39;ve done that, is we titrate toward the negative. And that&#39;s the news problem in general — is that bad news sells papers. Well, I think in the course of this conversation, we&#39;ve shifted toward that. But some of the metrics you mentioned I thought had a more positive ring to them, didn&#39;t they?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And this was an epiphany that we have been having over the past few years, because any kind of machine learning model typically does well when there is a lot of data to learn from. And with these kinds of cases, where out of 70 million-plus trips, when 0.1% of those result in even a report, and a fraction of a fraction of those results in an actual incident where someone gets removed, there is very little to learn from, and as a result, these models take time to mature. Of course, with technology evolving, that is going to get better, but we realized that we have a lot more data about good user behavior.</p><p> We have a lot more users who are actually coming in, booking their stay months in advance; they are probably checking in on time, leaving the property even better than they found it, communicating with the host and the guests, leaving honest reviews. So if we can actually flip the switch, and while we need to continue to look for the anomalies and the trends and the bad actors, if we can get really good at learning what good behavior looks like while making sure that we are also measuring for potential bias or discrimination and privacy compliance in how we collect and use this data, then that can be really powerful in informing when something does look risky. For example, if an account typically is accessed from the US, [and] suddenly we see that that IP is now accessing from the Philippines, and it feels like “Oh, this is an account takeover.” But if this is a good user who has typically been traveling around the world quite a bit, maybe this is not an account takeover, and there is history there from the good user behavior for us to be smarter about “What does normal look like and what does an anomaly look like?” Not broadly, but very specifically, based on the user segment.</p><p> So this is not new stuff, but I think we sometimes tend to obsess about just really learning what bad behavior looks like and getting good at detecting that, as opposed to complementing what an anomaly looks like [compared] to what normal behavior looks like.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. And you have such a wealth of insights and information in a field that is really an evolving field. I mean, it&#39;s not like a typical collaborative filtering situation where “users like you also bought this.” I mean, so much more goes on in terms of matching. This must be a very interesting and worthwhile problem to get your arms around.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And it requires us to get out of our trust and safety silo and work really closely with our search, relevance, and personalization teams because our job — unlike my job when I used to work in e-commerce — is not just to do the collaborative filtering and say, “People like you bought this, so you should buy this,” or, “You traveled to Paris, so maybe next you want to go to Rome.”</p><p> It&#39;s about … you&#39;re traveling with the family this time. You have little kids; you probably want day care, and we know that this host offers day care, and this location might be great for you. Or with the same customer maybe traveling alone, maybe we need to offer up different recommendations. And having these trust and safety signals embedded into our search-relevance algorithms can get really powerful in matching the right person with the right listing.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Naba, you didn&#39;t start at Airbnb. Tell us a bit about how you got there. You referenced Walmart and some background there, but how did you end up in your current role?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I was the first female engineer in my family. My father took a chance on me and said, “You&#39;re curious. You&#39;re a forever learner. Do you want to do engineering?” And I had no idea what engineering was at that time, but I signed up anyway and went on to become the first female engineer in my family.</p><p> I worked with Tata Consultancy Services, then went on to join Cognizant, came through Cognizant to the US, and worked for some time at AAA. I would just keep going to different projects and different jobs that would help me learn something completely new.</p><p> Walmart happened around 2006. I was asked to work on supply chain at Walmart, which is probably, if you want to learn supply chain at a company, that&#39;s the company to go to. And while I was doing supply chain, every year I kept getting bigger and bigger responsibilities and projects until I found myself, from Walmart, leading almost all of the supply chain teams to going to Sam&#39;s Club, which is a part of Walmart — leading all of product and front end and cart and checkout and marketing and pricing, which I had never done before. But it gave me a chance to get a well-rounded experience learning how the back end of a large retailer works, as well as [how] front-end customer experience works.</p><p> And right after Sam&#39;s Club, I was asked to lead search. Right around that time, I was starting to get really interested in a world that runs on machine learning and AI, and search was a great landing ground for me. I did a course from MIT, interestingly, to learn about the application of AI and ML, and that gave me the courage to take on the search job.</p><p> And from there, Airbnb happened, after 13 years, almost, at Walmart. I was so curious about the travel industry and this marketplace that was so different from anything I had done in Walmart. So the theme here is that I have always gravitated toward something that helps me leverage the skills that I have but then use my curiosity and learning to do something completely new and build myself up as I go along. That&#39;s kind of my background.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Naba, we have a section now where we ask you a series of rapid-fire questions, and just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind. What is your proudest AI/ML moment?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You&#39;re asking me to choose between my different teams, which is career-limiting for me. But I will say that the work that we did on party detection and party risk reduction was groundbreaking, and there&#39;s no one else in the industry who did it the way we did, so that is [a] really proud [moment for me]. But I am proud of all my teams, just for the record.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer. What worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> What worries me is how powerful it is. We had a chance to get to see [OpenAI CEO] Sam Altman up close and in person as he came to Airbnb. And just how fast this technology is improving and how much capability it has … I worry about it falling into the wrong hands. I worry that while my team has this technology, the fraudsters have this technology too, and so I worry about, if today we are worried about fake IDs and fake spam messages being sent to our hosts and guests, how much more advanced this technology is going to get and how much more difficult it is going to get for us to detect the good from the bad. And I think it&#39;ll be AI to the rescue as well in detecting fake AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Your favorite activity that involves no technology?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Painting with watercolors. I love painting nature. And so paper, watercolors, and just peace and tranquility, no technology, is my favorite thing to do. And of course hugging my kids and spending time with them just listening to their day, trying to make them not be on their cellphones while they talk to me. Those two.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I wanted to be a teacher. I come from a family of teachers, and I feel so much joy when I&#39;m seeing someone&#39;s eyes light up with the gift of knowledge. I am a forever learner. Every job that I take has been completely different from my previous job; it&#39;s because I love to learn. And so, yeah, that&#39;s what I wanted to be.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And you probably do a fair amount of teaching in your current role anyway.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I do a lot of mentoring.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;ve taught us quite a lot.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, thank you. I do do a lot of mentoring, because I feel like if someone else can see me do what I do, that will make them feel that they can do it too. So if I can just do that, that&#39;s my life&#39;s mission accomplished.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> My greatest wish for the world, actually, is to not be so afraid; to give it a chance. Because I think sometimes our fear of the bad holds us from embracing the good. There is so much wasted effort that goes into activities that should be automated through AI — so many patients who are not getting treatment; so many companies that probably need help and need so much funding to stand up basic things that can be done by AI; so many countries, probably, who are underdeveloped [but could] get so much advantage. I know that when it falls into the wrong hands, it can be used for bad, but the world has more good people than bad people, and I believe in the power of us using AI for good — using our collective goodness.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think everyone will probably resonate with your idea that the world is better than it is bad. We do tend to hear most of the negative stories, but it&#39;s refreshing to hear how, one, how much attention you&#39;re paying to try and to prevent those, but also to hear something about the good stories too that your platform enables. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. We&#39;ve enjoyed it.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, Sam. Thank you, Shervin. My pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, we&#39;re joined by Zan Gilani, principal product Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Case Against Restricting Stock Buybacks</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Guest, S.P. Kothari, and Parth Venkat. <p>Nicholas Guest is an assistant professor of accounting at the Johnson Graduate School of Management at Cornell University. SP Kothari is the Gordon Y. Billard Professor of Accounting and Finance at MIT&#39;s Sloan School of Management, where he was previously deputy dean. Parth Venkat is an assistant professor of finance at the Culverhouse College of Business at the University of Alabama.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com Are stock buybacks as bad as they’re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Kothari-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Are stock buybacks as bad as they&#39;re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 budget). In addition, senior Democrats have shown interest in barring executives from selling shares for three years after a repurchase, the federal government has suggested that companies that give up buybacks will receive preferential treatment, and the Securities and Exchange Commission has proposed a significant increase in the extent and frequency of repurchase reporting.</p><p> The debate on the economic consequences of stock buybacks has so far tended to focus on small samples or cherry-picked examples. Given that thousands of companies repurchase their shares each year, and aggregate repurchases have exceeded $500 billion annually for the past five years, we decided that a large-sample study of repurchasing behavior was warranted. Our study, published in the journal <cite>Financial Management</cite> , outlines the benefits of the practice, as stated by its proponents, and provides evidence that casts doubt on the alleged costs cited by its critics.</p><p></p><p> Critics of buybacks typically make three arguments against the practice. First, they claim that share repurchases enable companies to manipulate the market either by increasing the demand for — and therefore the price of — shares or by tricking naive investors by inflating earnings per share (EPS). Second, they allege that share repurchases enable insiders to benefit through compensation contracts or the sale of shares at inflated prices. And lastly, critics charge that share repurchases crowd out investment and thus sacrifice innovation and long-term economic growth.</p><p> Meanwhile, those who support or engage in stock buybacks offer several justifications for the practice. First, payouts to shareholders align manager and shareholder incentives by reducing the potential misuse of free cash flow. Second, using repurchases instead of or in addition to dividends gives corporations flexibility in the amount of cash returned to shareholders, the ability to award repurchased shares to employees as equity compensation, a modest tax advantage to shareholders (less pronounced since the 2003 dividend tax cut), and the ability to signal the company&#39;s good prospects to the market. Finally, share repurchases represent well-disclosed and regulated arm&#39;s length transactions at current market prices between willing participants.</p><p> Given the drive to regulate share repurchases, we would expect evidence of their drawbacks to be observable in public data. To test this, we documented trends in repurchases and compared trading volume, share price performance, CEO pay, and corporate financial activities (evidenced by investment and profitability) of companies that do and do not repurchase shares. We segmented the businesses that repurchased shares in two ways: (1) small positive versus large positive repurchase amounts (defined as below versus above median values), and (2) frequent versus infrequent repurchasers (defined as companies that repurchase in one or two quarters as opposed to three or four quarters of the year).</p><p> Our large-sample evidence on thousands of US exchange-listed companies over the past three decades shows that repurchases in the US are a mainstream corporate financial activity that returns several hundred billion dollars of capital to shareholders annually. At an aggregate level, we found that this activity neither creates nor destroys much wealth (that is, it does not produce significant changes in share price). In addition, while repurchases are associated with higher past profitability, they are not associated with excessive CEO pay or underinvestment.</p><p> Trends in aggregate repurchasing activity over time indicate that while repurchases have quickly grown in value, much of the growth can be attributed to inflation and increases in market capitalization. In addition, repurchases are now similar in size to dividends and have not grown faster than dividends for quite some time. However, unlike dividends, repurchases drop precipitously (and temporarily) in times of corporate stress, indicating that they do in fact provide companies with the aforementioned benefit of payout flexibility.</p><p></p><h3> A Closer Look at the Data</h3><p> Through our analysis, we were able to systematically address each of the stated criticisms of stock buybacks.</p><p> First, do companies use share repurchases to manipulate the market by creating excess demand to drive up stock prices? If they do, companies that repurchase shares should have higher trading volumes than those that do not. But average trading volumes have largely remained quite similar for all listed companies, regardless of whether or how often they repurchase shares. In fact, in recent years, the trading volumes for companies that do not repurchase shares have greatly exceeded those of repurchasing companies, suggesting that any excess volume arising from repurchases is dwarfed by other forces.</p><p> If naive investors are tricked into buying shares of companies that engage in repurchasing behavior because of the resulting EPS inflation, we should observe short-term price bumps followed by poor long-term performance. However, regardless of whether or how intensely and frequently companies repurchased shares, we found no evidence that companies significantly outperformed in the quarters with repurchases. While we did find some marginal evidence that companies that intensely repurchase do outperform slightly in the quarter after repurchases, we found no evidence of future reversals in the short or long terms. This pattern of outperformance is more consistent with companies using repurchases to signal undervaluation — a benefit to investors — rather than to manipulate the market.</p><p></p><p> The second critique is that repurchases allow insiders to unfairly profit. If share repurchases as rent-seeking behavior by insiders were a common, systematic abuse, CEOs whose companies buy back shares would receive abnormally high pay, including salary, bonuses, and the value of equity awards. Using a model-generated measure of excess pay that has been vetted in earlier academic literature, we estimate that CEOs of companies that make large positive repurchases earn only $51,000 more than CEOs of companies that do not repurchase shares — a statistically and economically insignificant amount of excess pay. The difference is even smaller — $4,000 — when we compare CEOs of companies that repurchase frequently with those that do not repurchase. These differences are economically tiny in relation to the average CEO&#39;s pay of several million dollars. Surprisingly, CEOs of companies that repurchase infrequently or repurchase small positive amounts earn the least excess pay, less than even the CEOs of non-repurchasing companies. None of this evidence suggests that companies use repurchases to boost CEO pay.</p><p> The third and final critique is that repurchases reduce companies&#39; ability to take advantage of investment opportunities, thereby sacrificing innovation and economic growth. We found that companies that do not repurchase shares invest more but are significantly less profitable than those that do repurchase shares. The companies that repurchase frequently and in large amounts are highly profitable and have steadily made investments in the past, and they continue to make large investments and, at the same time, return capital to shareholders. This suggests that profitable companies repurchase shares while maintaining a steady level of investment, whereas less profitable or loss-making companies do not (or maybe cannot) repurchase shares but are more investment-intensive in the hope of becoming profitable. While there might be isolated examples of poorly governed companies that choose to avoid profitable investments and instead return capital to willing shareholders, it is hard to see how directives encouraging or incentivizing such poorly run companies to retain cash would lead them to make good investments.</p><p> Potential stakeholders who may be affected by repurchase regulations include managers, other employees, shareholders, governments, and society at large. If a company is profitable, a CEO can pay excess cash out to shareholders in the form of buybacks or dividends, keep the money on their balance sheets, or invest in new projects. A small tax on share repurchases may not change corporate behavior significantly and might raise a small amount of revenue for the government. But if the tax rate grows high enough, companies will choose to not buy back shares and instead pay out exclusively via dividends or retain cash. In that case, the government raises no revenue but implements a de facto ban on share repurchases.</p><h3> How a Buyback Ban Could Backfire</h3><p> If a company were to switch to only paying out dividends, shareholders would lose the ability to choose whether to receive a cash payout and could face negative tax ramifications, given that dividends are taxed as income while capital gains are often taxed at a lower rate, and only when gains are realized. In addition, the company would lose important flexibility in difficult times, because cutting dividends is punished more by the market than cutting repurchases.</p><p></p><p> However, the move to restrict stock buybacks seems intended not to motivate companies to shift to paying back shareholders through dividends but to invest more in the business. There is evidence that retained cash is correlated with CEOs making value-destroying decisions, such as pursuing empire-building mergers, accruing personal expenses, or funding pet projects. It seems implausible that restrictions on share repurchases would induce CEOs of poorly governed companies to invest in value-enhancing projects that they otherwise would not have been funding.</p><p></p><p> From an employee standpoint, there is some evidence that labor unions are able to negotiate more successfully if their employers have excess cash, but there is plenty of evidence that constraints on a company&#39;s flexibility to raise and distribute capital is bad for employees, especially during downturns. Empire-building mergers can also be bad for employees, given that M&amp;As often result in the employees of the acquisition target being laid off and employees of the acquiring company being misallocated. In addition, some repurchased shares are reissued to employees, making any actions that are bad for shareholders also bad for stockholding employees.</p><p> Overall, our results show an absence of correlation between share repurchases and price manipulation, return reversals, excess CEO compensation, and underinvestment, which makes it highly implausible that economically significant causal effects of share repurchases still underlie the data. Corporations lose flexibility if they have to rely only on dividends, and evidence shows that poorly governed CEOs who retain cash often spend it on value-destroying mergers, expenses, or pet projects. It is implausible that policies designed to reduce repurchases will also reduce alleged but unobserved malpractices without imposing costs on US public companies and other stakeholders.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Are You Ready for the Next Supply Disruption?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:46:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Johnny Rungtusanatham, David A. Johnston, and Elizabeth Heichler . <p>M. Johnny Rungtusanatham is a professor of operations management and information systems and the Canada Research Chair in Supply Chain Management (Tier 1) at the Schulich School of Business at York University. David A. Johnston is a professor of operations management and information systems and the research chair and director of the George Weston Ltd. Centre for Sustainable Supply Chains at the Schulich School of Business. Elizabeth Heichler is editorial director, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Capabilities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &#8220;Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Nov. 7, 2022. Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &#8220;black swan&#8221; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently. M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption</a> ,&quot; <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , Nov. 7, 2022.</p></aside><p> Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &quot;black swan&quot; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently.</p><p> M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have researched the triggers and performance consequences of supply disruption. Their ADDAPT framework can help leaders better manage disruptions and maintain product flow.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why traditional risk management may not be adequate to prepare for the next catastrophic supply disruption.</li><li> Why you need to develop six capabilities — anticipate, detect, diagnose, activate, protect, and track — to prepare for and manage for supply disruptions.</li><li> What changes you need to make to your business strategy, practices, processes, and systems to improve supply chain resilience.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Flexible and Effective: Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workplace</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Elliott. <p>Brian Elliott is the executive leader and a cofounder of Future Forum, a research-driven consortium that helps senior executives around the globe reimagine how people, processes, and tools come together to make work better through data and dialogue. Future Forum was formed through a partnership between Slack, BCG, Management Leadership for Tomorrow, and MillerKnoll. He&#39;s coauthor of <cite>How the Future Works: Leading Flexible Teams to Do the Best Work of Their Lives</cite> (Wiley, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Many leaders don’t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it’s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA02_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Many leaders don&#39;t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it&#39;s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be managed differently.</p><p> That was the message of Future Forum&#39;s Brian Elliott, who presented on a panel with N. Sharon Hill of the George Washington University School of Business and Julie Dervin of Atlassian during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023.</p><p> Elliott said that 93% of the 10,243 knowledge workers his company polled said they want flexibility in when they work. Those who were given some choice, he said, had <a href="https://futureforum.com/research/future-forum-pulse-winter-2022-2023-snapshot/">productivity scores 39% higher</a> than those who were not. Those with some flexibility about <em>where</em> they work also scored higher (8%).</p><p></p><p></p><p> Finding an equilibrium between employees&#39; desire for flexibility and an organization&#39;s strategic goals requires a reexamination of the kinds of work that need to be done in person. It also may require different work configurations for different groups within the same organization, and it certainly requires different ways of benchmarking the work employees accomplish.</p><p> Attendees had more questions for the presenters than there was time for, and Elliott agreed to answer some after the event. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> How do you measure productivity? Most workers say they are more productive working from home and on their own schedule, but are they really?</h6><p> Here&#39;s a heretical take: We need to stop trying to measure productivity in knowledge work and focus all that time and energy on measuring outcomes.</p><p> Productivity metrics take outputs (emails sent, cases closed) and divide them by inputs (hours active), and the better ones adjust for quality (cases reopened). That can work, somewhat, for rote, routine tasks, which are what get automated over time. But also, those metrics can be gamed, and people will game them — up to and including buying <a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07VHBQQVG">mouse jigglers</a> . As Dominic Price of Atlassian has <a href="https://www.atlassian.com/blog/productivity/the-problem-with-productivity-metrics">written</a> , “Productivity has always been a good way to measure the impact of machines and capital. It&#39;s just never been a good way to measure the impact of <em>humans</em> .”</p><p> At Future Forum, we&#39;ve ventured into this; we compared populations with and without flexibility to see that those with location flexibility report higher productivity scores, and those with schedule flexibility have an even bigger advantage. There are also academic studies by Stanford&#39;s <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">Nick Bloom</a> , HBS&#39;s <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">Raj Choudhury</a> , and others that show the same thing.</p><p> But it&#39;s an odd question in that we didn&#39;t ask it when people were in the office. We simply assumed that because people were present, they were doing something productive. We all know that&#39;s not accurate.</p><p> Instead, let&#39;s skip the whole mess and take the time to get clear on our organization&#39;s objectives and key results (OKRs), and do it in a way that those can cascade down by business unit and function, and to the team level. From the team level, much can be taken to the individual level to find the individual&#39;s impact both in terms of what they did and how they were as a teammate.</p><p> Assessing people on the impact they have on a team&#39;s goals is harder but will take us a lot further than installing more productivity metrics that measure their inputs and outputs.</p><h6> Random collisions seem to be key in driving innovation. How do you promote serendipity in terms of making connections across teams?</h6><p> Connections are an essential part of employee engagement and retention, but the connection to innovation is at best spurious. <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=991">Study</a> after <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4093796">study</a> has shown that what really enables innovation is psychological safety.</p><p> In research we conducted in 2021, Future Forum found that location (whether fully onsite, hybrid, or fully remote) had little to no correlation to team innovation. Instead, what <em>did</em> matter were factors like whether people felt they could ask questions and whether teams were willing to take risks — that is, whether they felt psychological safety.</p><p> Building connections is important, but we should do it intentionally in organizations instead of relying on random chance. Here are three ways you can do this:</p><p> <strong>1. Intentional cross-team connections.</strong> Programs like open brown-bag lunches where a rotating cast of internal experts present or host an “ask me anything session,” bringing leaders from other functions into your quarterly planning cycles, and creating public channels in Slack or Teams for sharing insights based on topics (like AI) can go a long way.</p><p> <strong>2. Leverage tools to build connections.</strong> Products like Donut, an app for Slack or Teams that pairs up individuals across teams programmatically, help ensure that everyone gets connected, not just those who work on the same floor or in the same building.</p><p> <strong>3. Help new employees build a network.</strong> One of the big challenges of the past few years is that too many companies hired people without rethinking how they build connections and get to understand the culture. One of my favorite tips comes from Genpact in Europe, where new employees are given six people to meet outside their team, either in person or at a virtual coffee, and each of those is supposed to provide two to three more contacts.</p><p> Investing in new tools and processes can also be a big boost. Think about processes like <a href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/12/using-brainwriting-for-rapid-idea-generation/">brainwriting</a> before a brainstorming session: Allowing people the heads-down space to think about some research results or a problem, write out their thoughts ahead of time, and then share with the group at the same time brings out more new ideas. It also lowers the odds of groupthink.</p><p></p><h6> How can you communicate an expectation that people should come into the office one or two days a week in a way that is inspiring and inclusive, and not forceful and dictatory?</h6><p> The last two years are littered with companies that declared that three days a week in person is the answer and saw 1.5 days a week as an average. This hides the fact that there&#39;s typically a more junior group of employees coming in two or three days a week, while more senior employees are coming in less often.</p><p> Repeating the policy doesn&#39;t work, and threatening to fire people who don&#39;t come in more often is unrealistic and breeds resentment. Leadership knows that it&#39;s some of the more experienced, critical talent that&#39;s coming in less often. The junior staff knows this too.</p><p> Instead, what we&#39;ve seen work is focusing on helping teams figure out their own rhythms through team-level agreements. The needs of a sales team and an engineering team, for instance, are different. The sales team might end up mandating two days a week that are default days in the office, and stacking those days with specific activities that are more “heads-up” than heads-down, such as training sessions, mentoring hours, and one-on-ones. The engineering team, on the other hand, might end up with one week of the month in person for planning, lunches together, and demo days.</p><p> Encouraging senior staff to come in at least one day a week for mentoring sessions, to be available for training, and for coffee with junior staff goes a lot further than simply telling them to show up.</p><p> The other critical element is that coming to the office can&#39;t be consistently worse than working at home. People don&#39;t want free lunch all the time, they want a place for team meetings, the ability to find a quiet spot for customer calls, and Wi-Fi that works. For a large number of companies, that requires redesigning the workspace.</p><h6> What should managers do to avoid having flexible work perpetuate or even exaggerate existing biases in the workplace? Being “out of sight, out of mind” is a real concern.</h6><p> Proximity bias and the chances of presenteeism leading to better opportunities as well as rewards is a real risk. We need to create a level playing field, and that starts with training managers and leaders to assess team and individual performance on the outcomes they generate, not the inputs (hours in the office, speed of response, being always-on). Leaders and their people partners need to look not only at the promotion and rewards cycle but also at their talent development pipeline and who&#39;s getting the new, shiny projects.</p><p> Working with the Slack executive team, we set a rule that all of the senior executives&#39; regular reviews — such as the CMO&#39;s weekly review of new project proposals — be done entirely virtually. That helped not only the usual challenges of people not hearing those at the other end of the room but also the pressure to be “in the room where it happens” for those meetings, which more junior staff might attend only once or twice a year.</p><h6> Many companies and industries outside of tech have a split between knowledge workers and those who need to be present in person to do their job (such as retail and manufacturing). How would you recommend positioning flexibility so as not to create an unfair dual standard?</h6><p> The differences between desk (office) workers and deskless (or front-line) workers extend far beyond the ability to work remotely: They include pay, benefits, facilities, training, and more.</p><p> The talent shortage in deskless workers is a massive challenge for many companies. But I don&#39;t think the answer is to force desk workers back into offices full-time. That doesn&#39;t really solve any issues for deskless workers.</p><p> The answer here is investing in the specific needs of deskless workers. According to <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2022/why-deskless-workers-are-leaving-and-how-to-win-them-back">research by Boston Consulting Group</a> , schedule flexibility and choice are top factors in talent retention. Leaders are investing in programs like the ability to swap shifts and having multiple types of schedules for call center workers. Neiman Marcus Group reduced turnover by 20% by offering sales associates flexibility in choice of stores and departments, as well as hours.</p><h6> I&#39;m at a startup. In a budding company, management focuses a lot on work culture as they grow. How does a startup, or any enterprise for that matter, build culture while allowing a remote or hybrid model?</h6><p> I&#39;m a strong believer that culture is built regardless of where you are located, the slogans on the wall, or the quality of the happy hours. Culture gets built based on the everyday experiences your employees have and the decisions you make: what you prioritize as a company, how you treat your customers and employees, what projects you resource, and whom you reward.</p><p></p><p> That said, there are a set of practices that I&#39;ve seen used that really help build a solid foundation. Here are three of them:</p><p></p><p> First, digital-first doesn&#39;t mean “never in person.” Getting people together, even if widely distributed, is an important part of building culture. For teams, I&#39;d recommend — at least quarterly — a few days focused primarily on team building, socialization, and connection. As a startup grows, this often goes from everyone quarterly to teams quarterly and everyone once a year.</p><p> Second, get clarity on how you work together, and share more about yourself. Your <a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/06/23/team-level-agreements/">team-level agreement</a> shouldn&#39;t just focus on how often people are together, it should also get into how you communicate, how you make decisions, and more. Sharing tools like <a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/07/15/personal-user-manual/">personal user manuals</a> can also go a long way toward establishing a culture of trust.</p><p> And third, create transparency at work. One of the key factors that drive culture is leadership communication, and as a company scales, it&#39;s important to remain transparent while putting in place guardrails. What topics matter to your company and mission most? How do we interact with one another? Scaling internal communications from CEO “ask me anything” sessions to public forums for knowledge sharing takes time and effort; <a href="https://slack.com/blog/transformation/a-modern-leaders-guide-to-organizational-transparency">guidelines from others</a> can help.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Support Your Team When Uncertainty Is High</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Liz Fosslien. <p>Liz Fosslien ( <a href="https://twitter.com/fosslien">@fosslien</a> ) is an expert on emotions at work and the coauthor and illustrator of <cite>The Wall Street Journal</cite> bestseller <cite>No Hard Feelings: The Secret Power of Embracing Emotion at Work</cite> (Portfolio, 2019) and <cite>Big Feelings: How to Be Okay When Things Are Not Okay</cite> (Portfolio, 2022). She is also on the leadership team of Atlassian&#39;s Team Anywhere and previously served as the head of content and communications at Humu.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[“My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don’t really know what’s going to happen in six months either. What can I do?” If you’ve found [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fosslien-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> “My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don&#39;t really know what&#39;s going to happen in six months either.我能做些什么？”</p><p> If you&#39;ve found yourself in a similar situation recently, you&#39;re not alone. Almost every people leader I&#39;ve met with over the past year has asked me some version of this question. And in a recent study, 89% of HR leaders shared that their teams have voiced concerns about <a href="https://www.humu.com/blog/the-toll-of-workplace-anxiety-and-what-to-do-about-it">job security, leadership changes, or reorgs</a> .</p><p> When uncertainty is high, managers should aim to make work a place of stability rather than another source of stress. “The most effective managers clearly communicate that they care about the people on their team,” explained Molly Sands, head of practices for Atlassian&#39;s Team Anywhere. “Research shows that what managers of top-performing teams consistently do differently is to make their reports <a href="https://assets-global.website-files.com/601872ae12d42e2264ff9ac4/62d6d89b1037a1bb82393638_Infographic _ Actions that drive great management.pdf">feel valued and comfortable</a> .”</p><p></p><p> How can you offer assurance when a lot of big decisions — and broader economic conditions — are outside of your control? It may seem almost impossible, but it&#39;s not. Here are seven ways managers can support their teams during turbulent times without making promises they can&#39;t keep.</p><p> <strong>Help each employee work toward their dream job.</strong> You can&#39;t always guarantee someone a promotion (or, unfortunately, even job stability), but you can commit to giving your employees the kinds of valuable learning opportunities that will help them no matter what comes next.</p><p> To surface the experiences or projects your team members would be excited to take on, ask them to show you a job posting for a role they&#39;d be thrilled to have in three to five years. Walk through the listed responsibilities together, and pinpoint any for which they think they lack the skills or compelling experience. Then commit to helping them grow in these areas by offering them relevant tasks or projects.</p><p> It can also be useful to make career chats a habit. Every six weeks, schedule 30 minutes with each of your reports to ask questions like these:</p><ul><li> What kinds of projects or tasks do you enjoy most?</li><li> What parts of your current responsibilities do you find energizing?</li><li> Do you feel like you&#39;re learning and growing in your role?</li><li> Are there skills you&#39;re looking to grow in the future?</li></ul><p> Make it a point to create or offer them relevant opportunities based on these conversations.</p><p> <strong>Cocreate a medium-term mission with your team.</strong> When faced with uncertainty or frequently shifting priorities, we often feel stuck or like we have little to show for all the effort we&#39;re putting in. This sense of helplessness can lead to apathy and disengagement. In fact, research my team at Humu conducted in February on the impact of continued uncertainty showed that roughly 40% of <a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/web-assets-humu/eBooks/FY24 Q1 eBook - Uncertainty/eBook_Uncertainty_01.pdf">employees felt less ambitious</a> than they did a year earlier.</p><p> To reenergize your team members, bring them together to define and work toward a shared three-month goal. Looking three months out can create a longer-term sense of stability for your people, but it&#39;s a short enough time period that, even if things shift around you, you likely won&#39;t have to change your mission. For example, a marketing team might aim to increase website traffic by 25% over the next quarter, or run experiments on how to more quickly share information and make decisions. As Jamie Woolf and Heidi Rosenfelder, founders of Creativity Partners, advise, “To better enlist your team in the cocreation of the future, try asking questions like &#39;What new sources of profit can replace dwindling ones?&#39; or &#39;What can we do to break down silos within our team?&#39;”</p><p></p><p> <strong>Help your team achieve wins within two weeks.</strong> Quickly boost your team members&#39; sense of progress by focusing them on what they <em>can</em> control and giving each of them a specific task they can cross off within a week or two. Start by dividing your medium-term mission or longer-term goals into mini-milestones, and track and celebrate each one as it&#39;s achieved.</p><p> Sarah, an engineering manager, recently split an ambitious product launch into a series of specific features and updates and then assigned her reports individual tasks from the list. She also set up a 15-minute team check-in at the end of each week to celebrate what they had achieved and track the group&#39;s collective progress toward their shared goal.</p><p> <strong>Create clarity when you can.</strong> Thoughtful explanations in tough situations are critical to earning trust and reducing anxiety. The next time you have an update to share, prepare to walk through the story of how the decision was made, and think through any concerns or questions that might come up. Plan how you&#39;ll address each one. If you&#39;re unsure of what to say, ask other leaders or HR for recommendations. When you do share the decision with your team members, encourage them to ask clarifying questions.</p><p> It&#39;s also important for managers to speak to their own emotions — while avoiding emotionally processing news in front of their team. “You should say, &#39;I am disappointed about the results this quarter,&#39; but not, &#39;I am so disappointed by the results. I am so terrified we are all going to lose our jobs. I don&#39;t know what to do,&#39;” Sands suggested. “Transparency doesn&#39;t mean you have to share everything you feel or are concerned about.”</p><p></p><p> You can also run a clarity audit by talking with your team about a recent decision that affected them (such as a new product road map or a change in the expense policy). In your next series of one-on-one meetings, ask the following questions:</p><ul><li> How and when did you learn about this decision?</li><li> Is anything unclear?</li><li> What can I do differently the next time I&#39;m communicating a change with the team?</li></ul><p> These conversations can help you identify how to improve transparency — and make it clear to employees that you&#39;re doing your best to keep them up to date.</p><p> <strong>Provide context when you can&#39;t create clarity.</strong> Managers tend to stay quiet until they can share a concrete decision. But a lack of communication is still a form of communication — and it usually breeds mistrust and gossip.</p><p></p><p> To avoid misunderstandings, explain why you can&#39;t offer more details, and aim to provide a timeline for when you expect to have more information. For example, you might say something along the lines of “I haven&#39;t heard back on what changes will be made to the sales pitch. I&#39;m hoping to have more to share with you in a week or so, but I wanted to be as transparent as possible with where we are right now.”</p><p> <strong>Encourage your team to benefit from benefits.</strong> Studies show that up to 80% of employees are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbeshumanresourcescouncil/2019/07/02/only-half-of-employees-understand-their-benefits-heres-what-hr-leaders-can-do-about-it/?sh=a4a1a578133c">confused about the benefits</a> their company provides. When budgets shrink, it can be an uphill battle to design and fund new ways to support your team. You might be surprised at how much you can boost morale simply by making employees aware of what already exists. For example, though my former employer offered women returning from maternity leave the option to work part time for their first month back, many expectant mothers were unaware of this policy. After Sands, then a product leader at Humu, flagged this option on a companywide Slack channel, several women (including me) took advantage of it and expressed gratitude for the policy.</p><p> Review your company handbook, or schedule a quick meeting with HR for a refresher. In an upcoming team meeting, give a brief overview of your organization&#39;s benefits, and encourage your team members to take full advantage of them. You might want to specifically highlight mental health benefits, vacation policies, or flexible work options. Start by saying something like “I know it&#39;s been a stressful time and uncertainty is high, so I want to highlight a few programs and benefits our company offers that might help you feel better.”</p><p> <strong>Help your team say no.</strong> Preserve your team&#39;s mental health by stepping in to protect their time. Set clear and reasonable expectations, and back your reports when they turn down nonurgent requests.</p><p></p><p> You can also look for ways to get more visibility into everything they&#39;re being asked to do — and aim to set up friendly barriers. For example, when I learned that my team was being overwhelmed with requests from sales, I created a short form and advised my reports to direct all of the requesters to complete it in order to start the process. This served three functions: (1) It allowed me to better understand what my team was being pulled into, (2) I could help my reports prioritize or say no as necessary, and (3) it reduced the number of requests, because few people actually filled out the form.</p><p></p><p> Uncertainty breeds anxiety, and although managers can&#39;t snap their fingers and magically make everything fall perfectly into place, they can take steps to help their teams feel more empowered, supported, and able to succeed. Offering team members personally meaningful growth opportunities and helping them achieve quick wins can restore their sense of control and motivation. Creating transparency around changes and updates — or explaining why a decision has not yet been announced — can restore employee trust. And helping people invest in their well-being and set healthy boundaries can make it easier for them to weather workplace storms.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Improve Key Performance Indicators With AI</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Schrage, David Kiron, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>Michael Schrage</strong> is a research fellow with the MIT Sloan School of Management&#39;s Initiative on the Digital Economy. His research, writing, and advisory work focuses on the behavioral economics of digital media, models, and metrics as strategic resources for managing innovation opportunity and risk.</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>David Kiron</strong> is the editorial director, research, of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and program lead for its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">Big Ideas research initiatives</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at Boston Consulting Group and the global director of the BCG Henderson Institute, where his research focuses on the impact of technologies on business and society. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong> is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG&#39;s AI business in North America. He is a leader in BCG X and has over 20 years of experience driving business impact from AI and digital. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong> is a partner and associate director at BCG who focuses on applying AI and machine learning to business problems in commercial functions, including optimizing pricing, promotions, sales, and marketing. He can be reached at <a href="mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a> .</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics and Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Prediction Tools]]></category><category><![CDATA[Smart Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In the spring of 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_1290x860-scaled.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> About the Research</h4><p> This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group. In the spring of 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also interviewed 17 executives leading AI initiatives in a broad range of companies and industries, including financial services, media and entertainment, retail, travel and transportation, and life sciences.</p><p> Our research examines how managers and leaders use AI to enhance strategic measurement to advance strategic outcomes. It explores how organizations have adapted — and even generated new — KPIs with AI to define and deliver measurably better performance.</p></aside><p> Improving key performance indicators is a clear mandate for most organizations. According to our seventh annual <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">global executive AI survey</a> , 7 out of 10 respondents agree that enhancing KPIs — not just improving performance — is critical to their business success. As one executive notes, “We need to evolve our KPIs all the time so we don&#39;t run our business on legacy metrics.”</p><p> A growing number of companies now use AI — in a variety of ways — to accelerate that evolution. “I&#39;m very excited about what machine learning can do in terms of having our senior leaders move away from metrics that look backward to metrics that can look forward,” says Avinash Kaushik, chief strategy officer at digital marketing agency Croud and a former senior director of global strategic analytics at Google.</p><p></p><p> Early on at Lyft, engineers designed an algorithm to maximize revenue by matching driver supply and customer demand. “It looked at all the possible combinations of riders and drivers and picked the combination that — based on the ride being requested, where the driver was located, all of the system dynamics — would maximize revenue,” says Elizabeth Stone, former vice president of science at Lyft. Then, as data scientists began testing other objectives, something interesting emerged. One AI solution discovered that optimizing conversion rates — how often a user ordered a ride after opening the app — would, in turn, deliver more ride requests in the future. More ride requests ultimately mean more revenue. As a result of using AI, Lyft transformed its revenue KPI from one focused on ride and driver combinations to one that also focuses on optimizing conversion rates. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> At Tokopedia (part of GoTo Group), one of Indonesia&#39;s largest marketplaces, AI sifts through petabytes of data to detect signals that are correlated with credibility and reliability. These are key considerations, given that 86.5% of its 14 million merchants — selling 1.8 billion products — are new entrepreneurs. Having more-credible merchants makes the marketplace more appealing, effective, and efficient. “They might have good products to sell, but they don&#39;t know how to manage their stock,” says Herman Widjaja, Tokopedia&#39;s CTO. “With AI, we connect our customers to the right product that is served <em>by the right merchants</em> that they want.” The company synthesized millions of possible signals into a scoring system that represents a new KPI around merchant quality.</p><p> While most respondents understand the need for enhanced KPIs, a clear majority currently rely on inadequate tools and technologies to manage their metrics. Even as machine learning algorithms and generative AI transform enterprise capabilities, human judgment remains the overwhelmingly dominant approach to KPI enhancement. Two-thirds of survey respondents affirm that managers make judgment calls when adjusting their organization&#39;s KPIs. While common, this approach often fails to yield the desired results: Barely a third of survey respondents relying only on human judgment see their KPIs improve.</p><p></p><p> In contrast, companies that use AI to inform their KPIs are far more likely to see improved metrics. Ninety percent of respondents who use AI to create new KPIs say they see their KPIs improve. These AI-informed KPIs offer business benefits and demonstrate new capabilities: They often lead to more efficiency and greater financial benefit and are more detailed, time sensitive, and aligned with organizational objectives. (See “Creating New KPIs With AI.”) We observe a growing awareness among executives that KPIs need to become smarter and more predictive. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Creating New KPIs With AI</h4><p class="caption"> Of the 34% of organizations surveyed that use AI to create new KPIs, 90% see improvements. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig1-final.png" alt="Creating New KPIs With AI" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> All of the leaders we interviewed for our research voiced similar rationales for enhancing KPIs. As legacy metrics become static and outdated, their value as tools for defining and achieving organizational goals diminish. In fact, they become measurably less useful. Both individually and collectively, KPIs need to be updated and enhanced to ensure that they advance desired organizational outcomes. Improving performance without enhancing KPIs creates competitive risk. Companies that focus on — or align around — suboptimal measures are at a competitive disadvantage. Focusing on performance without a commensurate focus on its measure creates an inherent imbalance that can sabotage a company&#39;s efforts to compete effectively.</p><p> Based on our research — which includes results from a global survey of more than 3,000 managers and qualitative analysis of more than a dozen executive interviews — we have identified three ways to enhance strategic metrics with AI:</p><ul><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">I</strong> mprove existing KPIs.</li><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">C</strong> reate new KPIs.</li><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">E</strong> stablish new relationships among KPIs.</li></ul><p> This article explains how this Improve-Create-Establish, or ICE, framework can help leaders and managers repurpose KPIs to make their people, processes, and technologies more effective. Our research shows that AI-enhanced KPIs are associated with strategically valuable business benefits, including increased efficiency, better alignment, and greater financial benefit. Integrating AI into the strategic measurement process has enormous implications for the future of capital allocation, customer engagement, employee experience, EBITDA, and every other executive metric. (See “Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations that create new KPIs using AI are more likely to see stronger alignment, increased collaboration, more accurate forecasts, and more efficiency than organizations that do not create new KPIs using AI. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:25%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:15%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:60%;"></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 5x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Incentive structure is in line with objectives:</strong> 5.13 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (6% → 29%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 4x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Increased collaboration between employees:</strong> 3.97 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (11% → 44%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>More effective at predicting future performance:</strong> 3.37 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (13% → 45%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Greater financial benefit:</strong> 3.27 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (11% → 34%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 2x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"> <strong>Greater efficiency:</strong> 2.31 times more than at organizations that do not use AI to create new KPIs (24% → 56%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig2-fallback.png" alt="Benefits From AI-Adjusted KPIs" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> We offer several practical steps on how to use AI to enhance their KPIs.</p><p></p><h3> Improve Existing KPIs With AI</h3><p> Companies that initially use AI to boost performance numbers tend to find that the technology creates opportunities to revisit and review key performance parameters.</p><h4> The Substitution Effect at Wayfair</h4><p> Wayfair&#39;s AI approach makes that case. While losing a sale may appear to be a straightforward measure, the online furniture retailer used AI to reexamine the fundamentals behind its lost-sales KPI. As CTO Fiona Tan recalls, “We used to think that if you lost the sale on a particular product, like a sofa, it was a loss to the company. But we started looking at the data and realized that 50% to 60% of the time, when we lose a sale it is because the customer bought something else in the same product category.”</p><p> This AI-enabled analysis allowed Wayfair to experiment with substitute offers based on customer concerns such as price points, shipment times, and other factors. Demand for these substitute products provided a new lens on what had been previously measured and interpreted as lost sales. Recognizing this “substitution effect” led Wayfair to adjust pricing across its entire sofa domain, revamp product configurations in its fulfillment centers, and reprioritize legacy KPIs.</p><p></p><p> At one level, Wayfair used AI to transform its legacy lost-sales KPI into a more valuable metric that differentiated truly lost sales from actual sales. But at another level, the AI behind this upgraded KPI also enabled more sweeping changes. Tan&#39;s team used the substitution effect to develop a “profit-awareness framework,” which changed the way the company interacted with customers. Wayfair&#39;s furniture recommendations began to factor in delivery times and shipment costs, as well as product incidents and product profitability, when making next-best offers. Explicitly measuring and incorporating the substitution effect reframed lost sales as sales opportunities and led to pricing shifts. This reframing consequently aligned product placement decisions with the needs and capacities of distribution centers and warehouses, which improved both employee and customer experiences.</p><p> Companies across the industry landscape are finding ways to use AI to improve existing KPIs. Some use AI to deepen their understanding of factors that drive KPI outcomes, whereas others use AI to identify and prioritize which KPIs deliver the most value to the organization. While our survey results suggest that most companies will satisfice around improving KPIs (that is, rely on human judgment), we also see companies recognizing that AI makes possible altogether new KPIs that can achieve, and drive, next-level performance.</p><h3> Create New KPIs</h3><p> In addition to improving existing performance metrics, AI offers the potential for managers to algorithmically discover and generate entirely new KPIs. While our survey shows that only 16% of respondents&#39; organizations use AI to generate new KPIs, 90% agree that their use of AI has measurably improved their KPIs.</p><p> For example, hunting for indicators that can help physicians preempt sudden cardiac death, which afflicts 300,000 people in the US every year, is an ongoing effort for physicians and researchers. These types of deaths come out of nowhere; doctors can&#39;t predict them, since patients don&#39;t present as high risk. It&#39;s an especially frustrating condition because there is a known effective treatment — installing a cardiac defibrillator — if doctors can identify at-risk patients in time. One of the researchers in this hunt, Ziad Obermeyer, a physician and professor at the University of California, Berkeley, is working with Region Halland Health System in Sweden whose electronic health record data can be linked to a variety of government data. He and his collaborators trained an algorithm to predict sudden cardiac death in the year after an electrocardiogram (ECG) is performed, using death certificates, and a variety of other data points taken from government records and electronic health records.</p><p> “The algorithm became quite good at predicting who&#39;s going to succumb to sudden cardiac death in the year after an ECG is taken. Every time someone gets an ECG, it generates a risk score that measures the probability the individual will die from sudden cardiac arrest,” says Obermeyer. That ECG score can also function just like a key performance indicator: With the score in hand, a doctor might observe how it changes if the patient is prescribed a medication such as a beta blocker or an ACE inhibitor. While the research is at a very early stage, it might one day empower doctors and patients to work together to reduce the risk of sudden cardiac death — and identify new interventions that might decrease the risk. “Having the ability to turn these very complicated biological signals into indicators is very powerful,” Obermeyer says, “and I think that&#39;s going to be something that we&#39;ll see a lot more of, not just for sudden cardiac death but for diabetic complications and all sorts of other preventable, high-stakes conditions.”</p><p> Obermeyer&#39;s use of AI to create a new KPI for sudden cardiac death promises to improve patient outcomes, reduce costs, and enhance physicians&#39; sense of their own efficacy. Developing and discerning new key performance indicators with AI is an emergent phenomenon across the business landscape and among large companies we interviewed, such as DBS Bank, General Electric, General Motors, Sanofi, Schneider Electric, and Walmart. These companies are using AI to identify indicators of future performance at earlier and earlier stages of corporate activity. This capability facilitates better situational awareness and a more effective response to changing market conditions, among other benefits.</p><h3> Establish New Relationships Among KPIs</h3><p> No KPI is an island. Many executives we spoke with emphasized that better managing their business requires that they bring local KPIs together into a more integrated set of metrics. Executives across industries explicitly remarked on the inherent organizational and computational tensions between maximizing local KPIs and optimizing higher-level, more macro KPIs. As KPI features and parameters evolve, the importance of anticipating, modeling, and coordinating multiple KPI interactions with AI becomes more critical.</p><h4> DBS Bank Integrates Its KPIs With AI</h4><p> Singapore-based DBS Bank once relied on independent KPIs for each function touching different points along a customer journey. That is, for a given product, marketing would, for instance, have its own customer engagement metrics, product would have its own attrition metrics, finance would have its own revenue metrics, etc. Over the past three years, however, the multinational banking and financial services company has replaced that vertical model with a horizontal one. DBS created a value map that ties the use cases together into a single customer journey with outcomes in four categories: customer experience, employee experience, profitability, and risk. “We call it &#39;managing through journeys,&#39;” says Sameer Gupta, DBS&#39;s chief analytics officer. “Each customer journey would have multiple drivers, and each driver would in turn have multiple metrics to measure. You can imagine how quickly these scale, and it would be humanly impossible to optimize such a large number of drivers and metrics. AI is a force multiplier that gives us the ability to analyze large numbers of drivers and metrics and also identify those that need to be acted on now.”</p><p> In the new model, the outcome data is visible to cross-functional squads, whose members all have a stake in optimizing results in all four categories. “Everyone is looking at the same data, and everyone is accountable for the same outcome,” Gupta notes. The squads use experimentation, data analytics, customer immersion, and AI to continually review the factors driving different outcomes. In addition, they retain a sharp focus on choosing the correct metrics.</p><p> Establishing these interrelationships among their KPIs has been, in Gupta&#39;s words, “a fundamental shift.” He anticipates that AI will have an increasingly prominent role as the organization continues to coordinate its metrics in a drive toward continuous improvement. “We are starting to unpack to ask, &#39;Do we currently make that decision through data and AI enablement? Is there an opportunity to make it through data and AI enablement? If there is, how can we do it?&#39;” Gupta says. Discerning new relationships among KPIs with AI and other analytical techniques can yield new business opportunities, new insights, and a valuable set of data around which to manage organizational behaviors.</p><h3> Leadership Takeaways</h3><p> The future of strategic measurement belongs to smarter KPIs. Our research suggests, however, that few legacy organizations are strategically using AI to improve their KPIs. This makes both AI and KPIs undervalued assets. Leadership needs to invest accordingly. Using AI to improve KPIs, create new KPIs, and establish new relationships among KPIs creates an opportunity to capture measurably greater value. The ICE framework invites executive and boardroom discussions that should lead to management investment in improving strategic measurement.</p><p> Our research also emphasizes the need for leaders to align not only on which KPIs to pursue but, even more fundamentally, on the purpose of those KPIs. Will KPIs be primarily retrospective, or will they predictively lean into the future?</p><p> If the latter, organizations need road maps for improving existing KPIs; a commitment to exploration and experimentation around creating new KPIs; and a recognition that relationships among KPIs may matter as much as, if not more than, the individual KPIs themselves. Intelligent KPIs should not be primarily managed as independent performance silos; rather, their interdependencies and interrelationships must be understood and addressed. As our examples have shown, these shifts represent operational, organizational, and cultural challenges to leadership.</p><p> As has been the case with almost every successful AI initiative, KPIs, like the algorithms that comprise them, must be transparent and explainable. KPIs — organizationally, culturally, and operationally — cannot be seen as black boxes. They should be designed and deployed to be trusted. This cultural component should not be minimized or taken for granted. Otherwise, people at all levels of the organization will seek to game the metrics that guide them, ensuring organizational misalignment.</p><p></p><p> Underlying this new emphasis on AI and KPIs, and on strategic measurement more broadly, is an acknowledgment that quality KPIs depend on quality data. KPIs trained or supervised on biased, incomplete, and flawed data sets are likely to be biased, incomplete, and flawed. Data quality matters more wherever KPIs matter more. We see organizations committed to AI-driven KPIs becoming even more committed to cultivating data as an asset. They see investments in data reflected in KPI improvements.</p><p> Finally, as AI-influenced KPIs become more influential in the enterprise, their own performance will require new levels of monitoring and oversight. Leadership will need to be able to evaluate how well their KPIs are doing, individually and collectively. Are they the right KPIs for sustainable success? Are they appropriately anticipating the future? Are they making the right decisions — and helping humans make the right decisions — for achieving desired and desirable outcomes? Simply put, KPIs will require their own KPIs to help answer those important questions.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>