<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 11 月 21 日星期二 12:00:41 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title>具有 Gen AI 的微型实用程序：Shopify 的 Miqdad Jaffer</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Experimentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[High-Tech Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Online Retail]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Miqdad Jaffer brings a background in engineering to his role as director of product for digital marketplace platform Shopify. Users might recognize the commerce platform as one that enables a fast and secure online checkout experience. On the merchant side, Shopify enables business owners to set up e-commerce sites where they can list and sell [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Miqdad Jaffer 拥有工程学背景，担任数字市场平台 Shopify 的产品总监。用户可能会认为该商务平台能够提供快速、安全的在线结账体验。在商家方面，Shopify 使企业主能够建立电子商务网站，在那里他们可以列出和销售他们的产品。</p><p>利用生成式人工智能，该平台现在还使商家能够更快地完成管理任务，包括编写产品描述和定制网站。正如 Miqdad 在<cite>Me、Myself 和 A​​I</cite>播客的这一集中所解释的那样，利用生成式 AI 技术增强 Shopify 产品的关键是确保用户始终保持控制。他分享了 Shopify 的做法，同时结合尖端工具来帮助企业家更有效地启动、运营和发展业务。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E4-Jaffer-Shopify-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="米克达德·贾弗"></p><h4> Miqdad Jaffer，Shopify</h4><p> Miqdad Jaffer 是 Shopify 的产品总监，负责公司人工智能产品的监督和开发。他于 2018 年加入公司，负责推出人工智能驱动的工具套件 Shopify Magic 和人工智能购物助手 Shop.AI。在加入 Shopify 之前，Jaffer 是移动消费市场应用 Flipp 的产品管理总监。他拥有超过 15 年的产品开发和监督经验。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>生成式人工智能工具如何帮助业务发展，同时让用户保持控制？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我是 Shopify 的 Miqdad Jaffer，您正在听的是<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>大家好。今天，Shervin 和我很高兴邀请 Shopify 产品总监 Miqdad Jaffer 加入我们的行列。 Miqdad，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>谢谢你邀请我。我很高兴来到这里，并很高兴能谈论一下人工智能。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>太好了。我们都在使用 Shopify，但我们可能不知道。您能给我们简单介绍一下 Shopify 并告诉我们产品总监的实际职责吗？</p><p><strong>米格达德·贾弗：</strong>当然。因此，Shopify 是一个让企业家能够在线开设店面的平台。每当您要从零售商处购买商品时，您可能都会看到过 Shopify。您可能在结账时看到了紫色的 Shop Pay 按钮，对于我们中的许多人来说，这可能就是您接触 Shopify 的地方。对于企业家来说，这是一种在互联网上建立店面的方式，而对于...作为买家的您来说，能够以最快、最简单的方式进行交易，以确保物品到达您家门口。</p><p>在其他情况下，您可能在 Shop.ai 等平台上看到过 Shopify，您可能在其中搜索了您正在组织的特定活动、您正在寻找的特定产品，并尝试将其全部过滤掉Shopify 上的众多商家。</p><p>商家可以进入 Shopify 并登录。例如，左侧有一个产品部分。他们将进入产品部分，单击“添加新产品”，然后在“添加新产品”中，有一个用于标题、描述和其他一些字段的空间。</p><p>就我的角色而言，我的职责是，我们如何看待人工智能以及它如何融入创业领域，以及我们可以做些什么来加速我们的商家在建立店面、销售产品时的成功和进步，并成长为企业家？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>那么这如何涉及人工智能呢？我听到很多“电子商务”，我听到很多“连接”，但这如何涉及人工智能？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>是的，这是一个很好的问题。我认为，当人们想要开始创业时，需要考虑很多因素，因此会考虑“什么是合适的产品？合适的价格是多少？什么是正确的放置位置？什么是正确的促销？如何设置我的店面的所有内容？随着我的成长和进步，我如何保持‘良好’的样子？”我们看到的是，人工智能是一个让每个人都能创业的机会。</p><p>对于每个业务部门，我们都希望利用人工智能来提高效率，从管理管理任务到支持业务运营。管理任务可以像创建新产品描述一样简单，[或]确定电子邮件的正确主题行是什么。然后，业务运营方面几乎可以是一切，从了解业务、弄清楚业务分析、我应该问什么问题、我应该采用什么策略？我们将人工智能视为一个强大的助手，可以将自己融入到这个过程中。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>你的意思是，Shopify 让企业家专注于实际产品和他们的品牌以及所有类似的东西，然后让 Shopify 成为他们如何将产品推向市场、如何想要他们的品牌的平台就出现了，还有很多后端操作。显然，人工智能在所有这些方面都可能相当普遍。人工智能从推出的第一天起就嵌入了吗？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我们从早期就已经嵌入了最传统意义上的人工智能。我们按照欺诈检测的思路进行操作，即交易发生的地方，但要判断这是欺诈性的还是非欺诈性的并不那么容易。我们已经完成了基本的分类模型，以便能够确定某些东西是否<em>具有</em>欺诈性，然后以合理的方式向商家提供分数。那从一开始就在那里。</p><p>然后生成式人工智能出现了，我们有机会做更多的事情，我们已经看到，我们创建了一套名为 Shopify Magic 的产品。这背后的想法是，我们如何将其直接嵌入到我们的商家必须经历的工作流程中，以及我们如何使您的业务更容易启动、运营和发展？</p><p>我们做了像自动写入这样的事情，我们可以在其中为产品创建描述，创建博客，创建新页面，帮助处理电子邮件的主题行，创建电子邮件正文，并在客户服务上寻找方法一方面，能够在商家与客户互动时为商家提供响应。这些只是一些早期阶段，但这些天我们正在努力加快速度。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>很多公司都在考虑生成式人工智能，而且你们似乎已经这样<em>做了</em>很长一段时间了。您能否评论一下您何时开始考虑它，为它做准备，并且我认为在某种程度上，重新调整或升级或重新培训您的一些技术人员，以便能够真正将这些东西推向市场。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我将向您介绍一下我们如何从第一件事开始并进一步加速它的起源。我们每年都会出现一些我们应该关注的一般主题，其中通常非常流行的主题之一是保持技术前沿至关重要。我们想要做的就是尝试将尽可能多的最新技术带到我们的商家手中，以便他们拥有一切可能的优势。</p><p>我们一直尝试用人工智能做事，最近的一项，甚至在生成人工智能之前，就是产品分类——因此能够使用文本和图像来确定产品类别的想法能够弄清楚它属于哪里。它有助于渠道。它基本上可以帮助您向更广泛的受众进行营销并获得合理的分类集。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>当 ChatGPT 出现时，问题是，我们可以用这项技术做什么来将其呈现在商家面前？出于几个原因，这是我们想要依靠的地方。第一，重要的是要尽快将其交到商家手中，并保持技术方面的最前沿。另一方面，我们实际上第一次看到了实用性，这种实用性对于走出去并看看我们的商人是否会使用它以及我们可以从中学到什么很重要。</p><p>因此，我们从一条简单的路径开始：“商家遇到的困难是什么？”我们看到他们每天都在为产品描述而苦苦挣扎。 Shopify 中有数十亿个这样的产品，我们认为这是一个广阔的工作空间，并且我们拥有构成良好产品描述的所有条件。然后我们觉得“好吧，让我们把这个放进去，看看人们如何使用它，看看这是否是可口的东西。”</p><p>因此，我们很快组建了一个团队，并遵循几个不同的原则。 Shopify 通常建立在一系列原则的基础上，并允许团队快速前进。我们遵循的一些原则是，这必须很容易，必须集成到他们的工作流程中，并且商家需要能够对代表他们业务的内容拥有最终决定权。</p><p>这是一个简单的开始。我们说：“好吧，让我们弄清楚一个好的产品描述的规则是什么。应该多长？应该用什么语气？将使用哪些类型的词语，以及什么让它真正变得好？”我们做了基本的提示反对这一点的事情，然后说，“好吧，商家应该提供什么额外的背景信息，我们应该寻找什么来帮助他们？”</p><p>所以我们说，“好吧，好吧，他们可能会列出一些关于他们产品的关键词，这些关键词符合<em>他们</em>所知道的知识领域，其余的应该由我们来完成。就像，这应该像按下按钮一样简单。这应该感觉就像魔法一样。”因此，我们将其命名为 Shopify Magic，并且我们希望坚持这一点。商家所要做的就是输入几个关键字，选择语气，然后按“生成”。就是这样。那是第一个版本。我们试图快速发货，看看会发生什么，我们得到的反馈是，“这太棒了。到处都可以这样做吗？”</p><p>所以这就像是，“好吧，所以这里有一些积极的一面。那么，接下来我们可以做什么呢？”因此，我们添加了一个“特殊说明”字段，最初在我们的试验中，我们正在做类似“添加与我的产品相关的著名名人的引言”之类的事情，就像一个关于如何尝试它的模因。然后我们看到商家以不同的方式使用它。</p><p>我们看到他们用它来表达语言，这很有趣。我们引入了支持八种语言的功能，我们看到人们用它编写翻译，这是预料之中的，但看到它很有趣。我认为我们看到的最有趣的事情之一是，有些商人不会说英语，想要向英国受众销售产品，并将产品描述视为弥合这一差距的一种方式——出乎意料，但同时，这是你将产品交到用户手中，然后用户决定他们将使用它的用途之一。值得注意的是，我们为比以前更多的人打开了创业之窗，哪怕只是一小部分。</p><p>这就是人工智能工作取得进展的原因。在那之后，每个团队都想要一块，每个团队都想做一些事情，我们尽一切努力加速它。我们尝试从 UX [用户体验] 角度将事物系统化；每当商人看到某件事时，他们就知道这就是要做的事情。我们还尝试构建 Sidekick，这是一款首创的人工智能助手，专为商业而设计。这就是我们所经历的旅程。我们有专门的团队致力于特定功能，然后我们整个公司都在寻找人工智能加速商业发展的机会。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以，当 Shervin 和我第一次听说你在做什么时，我认为让我们兴奋的是这种做法的普遍性。像 Shopify 这样的工具将人工智能集成到其工具中的效果是巨大的。我想我们之前讨论过，您曾讨论过在 2023 年 2 月推出该产品。这是生成式 [AI] 时代的早期阶段。</p><p>很多人正在研究生成式，但这是一个令人兴奋的故事，您可以非常快速地在生产中使用这些工具。我确信那有点痛苦——也许你可以谈谈你所经历的任何痛苦或困难；也许其他人已经从中吸取了教训，但也了解了它的普遍性。这两种方式都很有趣，人们可以从你所做的事情中学习。</p><p><strong>米克达德·贾弗：</strong>是的。早期充满了挑战，但我认为这就是其中的乐趣。这很有趣，因为这是最新的技术。它有很多实用性，我们只是想将其交到用户手中。一路上我们必须弄清楚诸如如何进行评估之类的问题？这是什么提示性的东西？您如何将其系统化并使其有意义？ RAG 到底是怎么回事——RAG 是<em>检索增强生成</em>？如何将更多数据带入提示上下文中，以及如何使其有意义？</p><p>最疯狂的是，每周，一个月或一年的其他技术时间都过去了，突然之间就有一个新的事物需要尝试，一个新的事物需要探索，我们不想错过它， 任何一个。每当有新事物出现时，我们都会尝试、探索。我认为 Shopify 的文化是一种探索文化，也是一种工匠和建设者文化。我们试图做的就是将其交给可以构建并尝试的人手中。我们还在内部做了一些事情来鼓励使用人工智能，并且我们构建了自己的内部 ChatGPT 实例等效项。我们将其用于内部 wiki 的搜索和发现。我们试图做的就是将其融入公司的结构中。这是正常的。这是预期的。然后，随之而来的所有风险和挑战——包括幻觉——都是人们所熟悉的。一旦我们让他们熟悉了它，我们就会找到解决它的方法，并在某些情况下也接受它。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我认为您提出的这一点非常重要，因为当我回顾自己的经历以及 BCG 在这一领域的经验时，我们正在与许多公司合作，其中许多公司与您有着相同的心态和雄心已经描述了解决方案并将其投入生产并正在接受它。我想说，有些人对此持保留态度。我想说，其中一些是基于一些毫无根据的恐惧。</p><p>我的意思是，现实情况是，这是一项新技术，它伴随着很大的风险，而且可能比传统人工智能的风险更大一点，因为它的普及程度很高。但我认为，等待其他人解决所有风险的心态会让你处于某种巨大的劣势，因为正如你所描述的，唯一的方法——我的意思是，我喜欢你所说的——唯一的方法真正领先于这些事情的方法是开始尝试并适应它。</p><p>我确信在董事会层面存在一些风险和一些担忧。也许只是评论许多人当时的想法与现实是什么，并为我们的一些听众提供正确的视角，以便他们明白这些风险可以减轻，而不是永远远离。</p><p><strong>米克达德·贾弗：</strong>是的。我首先要说的一件事是，我想描述谁是企业家，甚至将其置于上下文中。我遇到的每一位企业家都具有我见过的最高的风险承受能力。他们愿意放下生活中的一切去创业，有时他们除了想创业之外什么都不知道。而且这些人本质上具有风险承受能力，所以我们的用户群与其他人有很大不同。显然，你会在整个用户群中获得一系列的容忍度，但本质上，这是一个愿意投入、承担风险和尝试的群体。然后我们观察到的一件事是他们已经在使用它了。因此，我们已经有商家使用 ChatGPT 或其他任何工具，能够提示它，找出替代方案，并将其直接使用到他们的软件中。</p><p>我们做了一轮简短的研究，询问了一些商家：您知道吗？你是怎么用的？你用它做什么？他们中的许多人都说：“是的。嗯，我的意思是，我只是问它一切，所以我只是想弄清楚。”我们已经看到了这种情况的发生。所以对我们来说，“好吧。好吧，我们已经拥有了这个能够承受风险的商业基础，而我们最大的担忧通常集中在两个方面。”</p><p>第一个向量是害怕失去控制。因此，可以提出这样的问题：“它会说什么？如果出现幻觉怎么办？这适合我吗？它会和我的买家说话吗？”因此，所有这些最初的问题以及对失去控制的恐惧都很容易得到缓解。所以我们说：“好吧。好吧，这是一个快速的恐惧。我们如何减轻这种恐惧？”我们通过将控制权重新交到用户手中来减轻失去控制的恐惧。</p><p>因此，全权委托原则是“如果没有用户干预，人工智能永远不会书写”，因此商家始终能够看到将要发出的消息是什么。所以所有的幻觉风险，所有的“它会做什么？”风险消失了，因为现在它将控制权重新交到了用户手中。</p><p>第二个风险是它是否真实准确，这通常是很多人遇到的问题。我们试图管理的方式是，最了解的人是销售产品的人。他们最了解的是他们的产品，这就是他们想要谈论的东西，他们想要谈论<em>他们的</em>品牌。因此，我们也不觉得有什么风险，因为将由商家决定如何以事实的方式代表他们。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您以一种就事论事的方式谈论这个问题，但是当您考虑这里的实际关键字时，它是<em>用户</em>，实际上，当您考虑时，Sam，我们的很多工作都围绕着它人类和人工智能与仅人类或仅人工智能的比较。谢谢你谈论这个。这是非常关键的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我真正喜欢的一件事是你一直使用<em>“实用程序”</em>这个词。 Shervin 和我谈论的很多例子，我们都会要求人们提供一个例子，他们会提出一些他们已经实现的人工智能应用程序，这些应用程序跨越了他们组织的许多部分，这是一件大事，这些都很棒。但你所说的实用程序似乎是微型实用程序。因此，我的意思是，正如您所提到的，人们可能已经使用了一些大型语言模型并生成一些文本，然后将其粘贴到 Shopify 中。</p><p>您的增量实用程序在这里节省了他们在这两个工具之间来回的时间，而且还逐步使其在您的工具和您的上下文中更好地工作。当你想到所有这些微小的碎片如何乘以数十亿时，我认为这是令人兴奋的。这与舍文和我有时看到的情况不同，即“我们有一个具有很大实用性的大型系统，但它的用户可能没有那么多。”</p><p>我想回到你之前提到的一些事情——也许我只是听懂了你的语气——但你谈论的是欺诈检测和人工智能的这些传统用途。现在感觉这有点矛盾，但你说，“哦，是的。我们用它来进行欺诈。我们将它用于后端业务优化等。耶耶耶。我们做了所有这些事情，但这是非常酷的事情。”您能够继续前进似乎真的很令人兴奋。下一步是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>这是一个很好的问题。我认为我们的希望是希望人工智能能够降低创业的准入门槛。我认为我们的想法是，让我们看看这个空间中的一切。所以我们最近做了一些关于图像生成的事情。我们认为这是“好吧，好吧，我们也可以靠在这里。我们可以采用不同的操作模式。”因此，我们发布了 Hugging Face 管道，其背后的想法是“让我们将其投入市场，看看人们将如何使用它，并以一种无害的方式进行。”</p><p>其背后的想法是上传产品图片，然后选择需要切换的背景。其中一些，在提升图像的幕后有一些有趣的东西，放大图像，找出合适的遮罩，确保反射和阴影良好，然后生成各种有意义的背景在商业的脉络中。我们从中看到的是以不同方式探索的能力。我们尝试用人工智能做的事情，以及您关于我们用户群的风险承受能力的观点，这并不意味着只是破坏他们现有的工作流程。他们中的许多人（尤其是成熟的公司）都有现有的工作流程，他们以自己特定的方式做所有事情，这对他们来说是有效的。</p><p>我们所做的就是，对于任何需要额外推动或需要额外部分的人来说，有一个可以点击的按钮，一种调用它的方法，这是他们的选择。而且，Shervin，我喜欢你所谈论的一些关于让用户就位的内容，我们的格言一直是，这意味着增强而不是替代。因此，这始终会帮助用户成为最好的自己。</p><p>通过图像生成，我们看到了他们如果愿意的话可以全面改变店面的机会。如果他们即将举办感恩节促销活动，并且希望能够将所有背景更改为秋季主题，那么这对他们来说是一个快速、轻松的举措。他们的产品始终处于领先地位，他们的品牌始终处于领先地位，但他们可以针对特定活动进行商品销售 - 如果是感恩节，如果是圣诞节，如果是新年，无论是什么。需要额外拍摄照片的事情现在可能比以前更容易实现。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>确实如此。让我们记住，几年前，这样的事情是多么复杂和不必要的流程导向，你们刚刚就背景、照片拍摄、外观、感觉以及对品牌的影响等等达成一致，现在你把一切都交给了商人。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>对我们来说，Shopify 中的许多人都在使用它、提出正确的问题、突破界限并理解一些相关术语，这非常重要。当我说“幻觉”时，我几乎可以保证 99% 的 Shopify 都知道这意味着什么、它是如何发生的以及[如何]发挥作用。这使得每次进行产品开发时的对话都大不相同，因为它并不是每次都提出并重新争论它。人们尝试用这项技术解决常见问题。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果我仔细观察，我会看到人工智能市场正在发展。您提到了迁移学习的简易性。你可以采用这些现有的模型并稍微增强它们，我认为这是过去十年从“哦，是的。当然。你可以下载这些工具并自己构建它们”到“嘿，不，你可以采用我们所做的以及我们训练 GPU 的内容，并自行消耗掉我们的 GPU，然后自己逐步消耗一点 GPU，然后继续前进。”我认为这就是这个市场正在发生的动态。</p><p>但让我在这里谈谈另一个动态。比方说，是否存在一场走向平庸的竞赛？我认为这种说法有点过分，但如果 Shopify 中的所有用户都使用相同的工具来生成相同类型的产品描述，这是否会导致所有产品都产生一种普通的感觉描述？我们如何反击并超越这一点？我们让每个人都表现平平，这真是太好了；我们如何让人们与众不同？我们在哪里以此为基础？我们怎样才能超越平庸呢？</p><p><strong>米克达德·贾弗：</strong>是的。您所说的问题实际上是局部最大值，对吧？所以每个人都朝着这个标准、简单化、同质化、无聊的方向发展。我们所关注的是，我们提供的所有工具都可以帮助您入门。这个想法并不是“这就是终点线”。终点线是商人。终点线是他们的产品。终点线是他们的品牌并能够相应地代表。在很多情况下，这是为了给你一些东西，这比什么都没有好，并让你开始思考。</p><p>我们有一位商人向我描述了这一点。他想为他们的一些积压库存建立一家直销店，他们有 3,000 个 SKU，他们想将 3,000 种不同的产品放在一起，放在这家最初的直销店里。他对我说的是，“通常情况下，我会雇佣一个团队，我们会花三个月的时间来完成这件事，然后我们会尝试将其组合在一起。”他说：“我一个人度过了周末，我刚刚使用了你们的生成功能。这让我开始了。我做了一些改变。三天之内，我就开设了一家专卖店，准备出售我的所有产品。我做了必要的改变。我不喜欢你的风格，所以我给了它一些具体的说明，它达到了我想要的效果。”</p><p>我认为这个想法是框架内的灵活性。因此，提供一个框架，让他们开始，但要给他们所有的灵活性，让他们做适合他们业务的事情，并让他们能够在受众中脱颖而出。我认为关键是，每个受众都是不同的，没有人比商家自己更了解这一点。这个想法是能力和增强，而不是替代。你是对的；人们可能存在一个局部最大值点。但我们希望留下所有可能的逃生口，以便他们能够逃脱。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我想强调的一件事，你也提到过，是它的确定性与随机性。从生产的角度来看，这似乎确实很难——您使用的工具具有随机输出，但您希望有一个“定义、测试、完善”的流程。在我看来，这两件事在很多方面都是对立的。你怎么处理那件事呢？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>部分原因是，需要内置风险承受能力。因此，几乎需要预期系统会发生故障，并且用户需要有一种方法能够解决该故障。所以产品描述是一个很好的描述。我们实际上看到，用户需要经过几代人的时间才能对他们面前的内容感到满意。因此，考虑到这一点，你必须毫不费力地允许第二代、第三代、第四代、第五代的发生。</p><p>因此，我们知道这种错误情况将会发生，因此我们会为此做好计划。所以那里有一个“重新生成”按钮；它提供了多种选择。在其他情况下，我们将尝试提供尽可能多的选项以使其更容易。所以主题行：您有三个选项可供选择。你可以改变它。做任何你想做的事。然后，另一部分是我们知道技术将会改变，人们使用技术的方式将会改变，他们的专业水平将会改变。</p><p>所以有人会尝试打破这个系统，也有人会尝试绕过这个系统。我们也为这种情况做好计划很重要。因此，必须预先考虑每一个风险和每一个失败案例。然后你几乎以一种有趣的方式做到这一点，典型的就是提示黑客，人们试图找出用于此目的的提示是什么。在大多数情况下，您会尽力而为，但您希望提示会出现。因此，您以这样的方式编写提示，当提示出现时，就像是：“嘿，你找到了我。那太棒了！你想申请工作还是什么？”有很多不同的方式可以思考这个问题。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您的循环人也解决了很多问题。</p><p><strong>米克达德·贾弗：</strong>正确。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为，您的整个设计理念确实解决了很多背景，也是许多随机性质。你能给我们一点背景吗？您是如何扮演自己的角色的？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我最初是一名工程师。我认为，由于我已经12岁，所以我正在编程，并试图弄清楚如何使计算机做我想做的事情。我担任工程师的最初角色，并在当时的仪表数据管理中被介绍给产品管理。因此，就像公用事业刚刚出现的大数据一样。我必须在那个领域工作，然后进入文档分类，然后进行广告技术，然后进行零售数据平台管理。</p><p>我一直与数据相邻，在Shopify，我的旅程一直在建立我们的基础架构和数据平台，在我们的机器学习平台上工作，并找出需要在那里建造的东西。而且我总是在机器学习/AI池中有一个脚趾。然后，我有专注于分析方面的团队，以及商人将经历的内容以及他们将如何了解他们的业务。任务始终像“如何通过数据优化我的业务？”我们研究了ML的机会，我们研究了AI的机会。然后，当生成AI出来时，这只是沿途的下一步。</p><p>因此，是出于运气，偶然的设计 - 谁知道？但是我一直在过去的15，20年中一直在数据中，这是下一步。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>好的。是时候提出五个问题了。 miqdad，你知道那是什么吗？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我没有。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>好的。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我的意思是，我知道五个问题是什么，但是…</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>很好！因此，我们将问您五个问题快速风格的问题。只需告诉我们您想到的第一件事即可。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>当然。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您现在认为AI最大的机会是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我认为最大的机会是解决许多人的冷门。当我说“冷启动”时，我的意思是看着空白屏幕，不知道该怎么做，是如何导航系统，写东西还是其他可能的事情 - 只是那个未知的时刻。我认为这是AI介入并获得最大的[好处]的地方。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我喜欢那个。关于AI的最大误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>它将接管。我认为还有很长的路要走。这是一种增强，不是替代品，我认为它与Photoshop出来时相同。设计师变得更好，更具创造力，我认为这将在每个人的能力方面为每个人提高标准。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是否有太多的AI？什么时候有太多？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我认为当用户不在循环中时，这太多了。我认为用户需要在使用AI以及如何与之互动方面具有据点。我认为这不是要替换，我认为这是增强和帮助用户更好的问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>我想成为一名医生，但我在鲜血时昏昏欲睡，所以效果很好。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您希望AI可以做什么，现在无法做什么？</p><p> <strong>MIQDAD JAFFER：</strong>我希望我们可以结合想要交互的用户的所有模式，无论是语音的组合，面部表情的组合 - 只是能够在幕后获得语义含义，而在幕后含义单词无法自行做到。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>很棒。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们非常感谢您正在做的是现在使用Generative AI，只是在启动后才使用。我认为很多人都在扭动自己的手，想知道如何使用这些技术，而您所展示的是一个很好的例子，说明人们现在如何从该工具中获取真正的实用程序。感谢您抽出宝贵的时间加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Miqdad Jaffer：</strong>非常感谢您拥有我。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您的收听。在下一集中，我和山姆与雪佛龙首席数据官艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）交谈。请加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德（Allison Ryder）：</strong>感谢您听<cite>我，我自己和AI的话</cite>。我们相信，像您一样，关于AI实施的对话不会开始并停止此播客。这就是为什么我们专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个专门为LinkedIn创建组的原因。它称为领导者的AI，如果您加入我们，您可以与表演创作者和主持人聊天，提出自己的问题，分享您的见解，并从<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和BCG获得有关AI实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">MITSMR.com/aiforleleders</a>访问它。我们将在展示笔记中放置该链接，我们希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/micro-utility-with-gen-ai-shopifys-miqdad-jaffer/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>使用开源进行更安全的生成人工智能实验</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-use-open-source-for-safer-generative-ai-experiments/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-use-open-source-for-safer-generative-afer-generative-ai-experiments/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aron Culotta and Nicholas Mattei. <p>Aron Culotta是计算机科学的副教授，也是杜兰大学社区参与人工智能中心主任。尼古拉斯·马蒂（Nicholas Mattei）是杜兰大学计算机科学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Security]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Open Source]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Integrating artificial intelligence into the daily workflow of employees across organizations, from upper management to front-line workers, holds the promise of increasing productivity in tasks such as writing memos, developing software, and creating marketing campaigns. However, companies are rightly worried about the risks of sharing data with third-party AI services, as in [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Culotta-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">帕特里克·乔治/伊肯图像</p></figcaption></figure><p>将人工智能整合到整个组织的员工的日常工作流程中，从高层管理人员到一线工人，都有希望提高诸如编写备忘录，开发软件和创建营销活动等任务的生产力。但是，公司正确地担心与第三方AI服务共享数据的风险，就像三星雇员通过将其上传到chatgpt的备受关注的情况一样。</p><p>这些涉及的问题与云计算初期听到的那些人相呼应，当用户担心发送给远程服务器的数据的安全性和所有权。管理人员现在自信地使用成熟的云计算服务，符合有关其数据的安全性，隐私和所有权的一系列监管和业务要求。 AI服务，尤其是生成性AI，在这方面的成熟程度要少得多，部分原因是它仍然是早期的，但这也是因为这些系统几乎无法取之不尽的培训数据。</p><p></p><p>像OpenAI的Chatgpt这样的大型语言模型（LLM）已经接受了通过Internet访问的大量书面内容的培训，而无需考虑该数据的所有权。该公司现在面临着包括乔治·RR Martin在内的畅销书作家的诉讼，因为他在未经许可的情况下使用了受版权保护的作品，使LLM能够生成模仿者。传统媒体主动寻求保护其数据，与AI开发人员进行了许可讨论；然而，在夏季，Openai与<cite>《纽约时报》</cite>之间的谈判破裂了。</p><p>然而，试验生成AI的公司更加直接关注的是，如何安全地探索利用内部数据的LLM的新用例，鉴于可以将任何上传到商业LLM服务上传的东西都可以作为培训数据捕获。管理人员如何更好地保护自己的专有数据资产，并在其公司AI开发实践中改善数据管理，以赢得和维护客户信任？</p><h3>开源解决方案</h3><p>对于数据所有权问题的一个明显解决方案是在本地构建自己的生成AI解决方案，而不是将数据运送到第三方。但是，鉴于微软花费了数亿美元建立硬件基础设施来培训Chatgpt，这对实际开发费用一无所知？当然，我们都不能负担得起从头开始构建这些基础模型。</p><p>由于新兴的开源AI运动使人联想起1990年代Linux的兴奋，因此对生成AI进行更安全的实验变得越来越可能。当时，开发了一个免费操作系统的开发，其源代码可以由任何人孕育了一个国际开发人员社区的人来读取和编辑，这些开发人员建立了彼此的工作，以开发成熟的软件工具，这些软件工具今天运行了许多互联网。</p><p></p><p> <a href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2023-01-30-ai-linux">AI的这样的“ Linux时刻”</a>现已到来。开源模型，例如<a href="https://bigscience.huggingface.co/blog/bloom">Bloom</a> ， <a href="https://lmsys.org/blog/2023-03-30-vicuna/">Vicuna</a>和稳定的扩散等等，提供了可以对特定任务进行微调的基础模型。对高度优化的培训程序（例如<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2106.09685">Lora</a>和<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2106.10199.pdf">BitFit</a> ）的研究发现，它们可以使用商品硬件进行微调，从而导致<a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3545111">模型的新兴生态系统</a>接近Chatgpt的性能（尽管仍然存在许多<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.15717.pdf">技术挑战</a>）。泄漏的备忘录在其中，Google研究人员对“我们没有护城河”的哀叹表明，有些人认为开源创新的爆炸式爆炸威胁着技术巨头对LLM的控制。尽管如此，安全，负责任地利用这些新兴的开源工具的快速发展将需要对人和流程的新投资。</p><p></p><h3>管理开源AI的风险</h3><p>尽管本地控制的AI解决方案掌握了专有数据，但管理人员仍必须采取许多措施，以确保其安全，有效和负责任的使用。</p><p><strong>导航模型和数据许可。</strong>在许多情况下，<em>开源</em>一词是误导性的。尽管某些模型允许商业用途，但其他模型仅限于学术或非营利性使用。有时，源代码与模型一起释放；其他时候，只有一个或另一个被释放。最近创建的许可类型限制了被认为是有害或不负责任的特定用例。例如，在<a href="https://www.licenses.ai/">负责的AI许可</a>下发布了Bloom和稳定的扩散，这可能在法律上阻止其在某些刑事司法和健康申请中的使用。还必须考虑对模型进行培训的数据类型。在培训AI模型的数据集中，将受版权保护的材料包括在美国的某些情况下可能被认为是公平使用的，但判例法远未解决。对馈入每个模型的数据进行彻底的核算将有助于组织更好地解决这些问题。诸如数据营养项目之类的新兴工作正在为数据集增加了更多的结构和报告要求，以帮助用户更好地了解其内容和风险。</p><p><strong>防止数据泄漏。</strong>即使没有将数据提交给第三方AI服务，组织也有可能通过聊天机器人等开放式用户界面泄露自己的数据。新兴的用例允许LLMs充当数据库的对话界面，这可以使客户快速找到对自己数据自定义的常见问题的答案。但是，防止LLM揭示有关其他客户或公司专有数据的私人信息可能具有挑战性。皮尤（Pew）的研究表明，这些对话剂<a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/science/2023/02/22/60-of-americans-would-be-uncomfortable-with-provider-relying-on-ai-in-their-own-health-care/">对许多用户来说是一个关注</a>，尤其是围绕诸如卫生保健等敏感主题。通过<em>及时注射攻击</em>，使数据更加困难，在这种攻击中，恶意用户试图欺骗代理商明确指示不透露的信息。在对抗性环境中，AI系统的相同方面使它们具有创造力和灵活性也成为安全威胁。</p><p><strong>适应不断变化的数据。</strong>托管本地模型的另一个并发症是确保它们正在使用最新数据。虽然Chatgpt（GPT-3）的初步发布无法回答有关2021年过去事件的问题，但最新的模型可以将当前数据与在历史数据预处理的模型相结合。公司必须平衡更新系统与新信息的平衡，同时还保持用户体验的稳定性和一致性。</p><p><strong>减轻系统性偏见。</strong> AI系统可以轻松地永久化和扩大培训数据中编码的社会和经济不平等。众所周知，LLMS很容易根据性别，种族和种族刻板印象，例如假设护士是女性而医生是男性。尽管对如何减少这种行为进行了大量研究，但最终，仅通过技术解决方案将无法解决这个问题。组织应不断审核AI系统，衡量其性能和结果，以确保对不同的亚群进行公平处理。</p><p></p><p><strong>与客户建立信任。</strong>公司应预期对个人数据的使用方式提高敏感性，并与客户对使用其数据进行AI培训的任何意图透明 - 理想情况下，允许个人选择。这在被认为是被认为是的数据时尤其重要非常个人化，例如音频，视频和健康数据。像某些公司所做的那样，简单地更新服务条款并发出有关更改的通知，就会使客户感到被剥削并损害信任。例如，在Zoom最近提出此类权利来使用客户数据的权利之后训练AI模型。</p><h3> AI时代的负责数据使用</h3><p>如果开源AI模型在整个行业之间继续采用，那么对数据所有权的担忧不仅仅是大型技术。每个想要将这些模型部署到像内部帮助工具和面向公共聊天机器人一样广泛的任务的公司都必须面对与AI系统收集和使用数据相关的问题。</p><p></p><p>尽管有<a href="https://mozilla.ai/">初创企业</a>， <a href="https://data.humdata.org/dataset/2048a947-5714-4220-905b-e662cbcd14c8/resource/60050608-0095-4c11-86cd-0a1fc5c29fd9/download/ocha-data-responsibility-guidelines_2021.pdf ">政府工作组</a>和<a href="https://responsibledata.io/">学术社区</a>都在研究这些主题，但最佳实践和推荐政策仍在出现。斯坦福法学院的<a href="https://law.stanford.edu/2023/03/09/a-data-stewardship-framework-for-generative-ai/">AI数据管理框架</a>专门解决了生成的AI技术。全球最大的计算专业组织的计算机协会最近还发布了一系列有关<a href="https://www.acm.org/binaries/content/assets/public-policy/ustpc-approved-generative-ai-principles">生成AI系统（包括LLMS）的设计和部署</a>的准则。这些资源涵盖了此处讨论的一些问题，包括有关部署，数据和输出所有权以及个人数据控制的限制。我们建议，各种规模的组织都希望利用开源AI，密切关注相关的指南和框架，以负责培训模型的负责任和道德收集和使用数据。他们可以通过任何潜在项目的潜在技术和社会风险思考，以及开发严格的审计和监视过程以确保安全有效的部署。</p><p>在杜兰（Tulane），我们最近建立了<a href="https://tulanecs.github.io/tuceai/">社区参与中心的人工智能中心</a>，以调查此类问题。通过技术人员，社会科学家和民权活动家组成的跨学科团队，我们正在与新奥尔良的非营利组织和社区团体合作，了解AI如何影响他们的工作。我们正在集思广益地建立AI系统的新方法，以将AI背后的数据和技术控制给受其影响最大的人们。我们的工作是围绕参与性或以人为本的AI和数据努力的一部分，这些AI和数据认识到所有利益相关者都需要将所有利益相关者都包括在这些系统创造的价值中。随着公司更深入地进入AI开发，遵守类似的价值可能会帮助他们成为他们收集和使用的数据的更好的管理者。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/use-use-open-source-for-safer-generative-afer-generative-ai-experiments/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何明智地利用人才市场</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-to-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-to-start-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Williamson and Donncha Carroll. <p>杰夫·威廉姆森（Jeff Williamson）是布兹·艾伦（Booz Allen）的人力资源领导者。在2019年加入公司之前，他曾担任美国邮政局首席人力资源官兼执行副总裁。 Donncha Carroll是Lotis Blue Consulting和该公司数据科学领导者的合伙人。他拥有将近30年的咨询经验。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Networks]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Many leaders can now make a strong case for establishing an internal talent marketplace, but getting one off the ground remains difficult. At Booz Allen, we experienced that truth during the first year after launching our pilot project. Here, we’ll examine some of the challenges we faced, how we overcame them, and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p>现在，许多领导人可以为建立内部人才市场做出有力的理由，但要脱离地面仍然很困难。在Booz Allen，我们在启动试点项目后的第一年经历了这一真相。在这里，我们将研究我们面临的一些挑战，如何克服它们以及我们对变更管理和人才市场的了解的知识。</p><p>拥有人才市场代表了Booz Allen的重要变化。多年来，我们一直通过基于您认识的人和信任的人进行操作的非正式内部网络部署专业工作人员。但是，这条道路限制了我们利用可用资源的灵活性，并将正确的人才与正确的工作相匹配。更重要的是，它限制了我们人民对自己职业道路的控制，这损害了参与和保留。</p><p></p><p>为了测试更好的方法，Booz Allen于2022年1月与Lotis Blue Consulting合作启动了人才市场飞行员项目 - 即，招聘，部署，人才发展，技术及其采用和文化变化方面的问题。我们希望从系统和整体上解决这些问题，而不是引入点解决方案，而点解决方案通常无法复杂化值。</p><p>但是，激活和运营人才市场所需的文化转型水平是显着的。要努力解决以人类行为和感知为导向的问题，克服这些问题是成功的关键。</p><h3>通往人才市场的道路</h3><p>Booz Allen希望结束对以客户或团队为中心的传统招聘网络的依赖。这些高度局部的网络使得在组织的其他部分可以满足企业，区域或当地需求的方式很难找到资源。相比之下，市场建立了一种集中的方法来评估需求和资源人才企业范围（通过外部招聘，内部部署或高技能），并创建了整个组织部署人员的能力。</p><p></p><p>市场飞行员专注于技能而不是网络。这为员工提供了新的知名度，可以在整个企业中开放机会，经理对可以完成这项工作的人才进行新的见解。这种关于工作和发展机会的高分辨率观点极大地扩大了人们可以探索的范围，改善员工的敬业度并提供更高水平的个人和业务绩效。飞行员在开放式职位上为飞行员人口增加了一倍，并获得了积极的员工反馈透明度和易于寻求新机会的反馈。此外，这种基于技能的方法为代表性不足的候选人与公共部门客户提供了更多的技术领域机会。</p><p>在飞行员的早期，我们需要克服一些重要的挑战，以建立兴趣和兴奋。最重要的是，我们需要为市场种植足够数量的高质量机会和可用人才，以吸引员工和经理。这样一来，我们学到了几个重要的课程，尤其是在变更管理方面。</p><h4>第1课：进行游戏化。</h4><p>随着客户的环境和需求正在发生变化，我们工作的本质正在发展，我们看到了需求的技能迅速转移。我们的技术人才能够反对客户使命的能力取决于他们能够学习和适应的速度。</p><p>为了解决这个问题，布兹·艾伦（Booz Allen）的战略人才发展领导者吉姆·亨根（Jim Hemgen）以及他的学习与发展（L＆D）团队设计并与市场飞行员一起启动了徽章计划。该计划旨在通过阐明不同的职业道路和获得不同机会所需的技能来发展战略企业能力。为了获得徽章的资格，员工既需要获得证书，又要让经理验证他们已将技能应用于工作。这种游戏化学习，并向投资于自己发展的员工提供认可和奖励。</p><p> L＆D团队通过内部徽章和外部认证的结合，参与了公司技术劳动力的大部分技术劳动力。在过去的一年中，员工获得了4,000多个对业务未来至关重要的徽章或认证。</p><p></p><h4>第2课：数据目标必须与个人职业目标有关。</h4><p>我们遇到了与飞行员相关的几个技术挑战，包括数据结构（建立正确的工作架构），数据质量（例如，确保技能数据完成）和算法设计（如何最好地执行人才的推荐过程和开放的建议。位置）。</p><p>为了获取完整的技能数据，我们需要广泛采用。实际上，采用与用户期望从平台中提取的价值密切相关。当员工和经理探索功能和收益时，我们的起点很慢。</p><p>一旦市场运营负责人约翰·格鲁宾（John Grumbine）于2023年1月帮助启动了内部网络应用程序的职业枢纽。人才市场基于他们的技能和偏好。现在，员工对保持自己的技能和偏好为最新有既得利益，因为这些信息为机会，培训以及他们可以访问的导师提供了建议；此外，它推动了如何被寻求扮演角色的项目经理发现或确定的。</p><p>启动职业枢纽应用程序导致人才市场采用大幅增加。截至2023年9月，超过50％的Booz Allen员工已经进入了职业枢纽，并正在获得工作，学习和指导机会。</p><h4>第3课：甚至更改管理都需要改变。</h4><p>在文化转型领域，我们在发射飞行员后很快遇到了四个主要挑战。 （请参阅“征服四个文化挑战”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>征服四个文化挑战</h4><p class="caption">当您通过与人才市场相关的文化变化领导时，您可能会遇到这些问题：</p><table id="Chart#" class="no-mobile"><thead><tr><th>挑战</th><th>商业影响</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p><strong>经理希望保持最佳资源，或者担心成为公开市场中人才的净出口国。</strong><p></td><td><p>高表现的人才没有离开团队，而是离开了组织。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>员工不愿意公开寻求重新分配，因为担心他们对当前的主管似乎不忠。</strong><p></td><td><p>随着时间的流逝，被捕员工的参与和表现会下降。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>项目经理不愿接受他们不认识的资源，并信任其个人网络以外的经理的建议。</strong></p></td><td><p>为每个项目组装合适的团队更具挑战性。招聘过程需要更长的时间，并且更容易招聘经理偏见。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>招聘经理正在拒绝比完美的申请人不那么完美的申请人，这些申请人通常只需要一笔少量的投资来弥合技能差距。</strong></p></td><td><p>工作人员的参与度降低了，表现因其个人利益而错过的工作降低。 </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Williamson_Talent_Essay_Table.png" alt="征服四个文化挑战" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p>这些挑战引起了很多问题。作为回应，我们的团队优先考虑一些重要的行动来推动我们需要的文化变革：</p><ul><li>构建，完善和绘制基于技能的人才资料，以更明确人们可以做或完成的工作。</li><li> （最初）将重点放在大量的需求工作概况上，以在系统中创造足够的流动性，以使参与者有机会搬家。</li><li>在出现不同的挑战时，组成一个小型，敏捷和以行动为导向的运营团队，与主题专家（例如，来自商业领导力和人才获取）合作。</li><li>以市场导航员的形式提供以人为中心的支持 - 专门为帮助所有参与者（员工和经理）遵循市场规则和准则的人，并从平台中获得最大的价值。</li></ul><p>所有这些步骤都可以纳入人才市场的启动计划中。</p><h4>第4课：动力，动力和测量很重要。</h4><p>在很高的水平上，同时启动综合人才管理系统的多个服务非常重要，以超越期望并建立采用势头。</p><p>为了实现行为改变，领导者必须深入了解什么激励了不同的人，以及他们所做的变化将如何满足人们的需求。该飞行员在市场公用事业公司提供了宝贵的反馈，帮助优先考虑增强功能，并确定了支持不断发展和扩展设计所需的变更管理水平。</p><p></p><p>监视和衡量市场绩效帮助我们的团队尝试新事物，快速失败，并不断提高市场对参与者的价值。更具体地说，我们的指标包括发布的机会数量，这些机会内的趋势，员工兴趣的水平和广度，按张贴类型，衰老机会的百分比（那些很长一段时间没有填写的机会）以及职位的百分比填充。这些数据帮助我们评估了平台的健康和力量，并使我们深入了解系统调整如何影响性能。</p><h3>致力于持续改进</h3><p></p><p>通过人才市场和我们的其他人才系统投资，我们正在提供更好的员工价值主张。飞行员后，我们的员工保留率提高了4％以上。但是，这一旅程永无止境。对发展人才以及解决方案的持续投资对于企业成功至关重要。</p><p>解决途中出现的障碍是旅程的一部分，最终导致了更好的设计和更好的结果。人才市场在当今不断发展的劳动力市场中提供了重要的好处：通过优先考虑员工流动性和发展，公司可以更好地适应不断变化的技能要求，并实现更高水平的创新，协作和劳动力中的灵活性。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-to-toart-smart-with-a-talent-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>在转型过程中平衡变化和连续性</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/ballancing-change-ange-ange-continuity-during-a-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/ballancing-change-ange-ange-during-during-a-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Carsten Lund Pedersen and Laurianne McLaughlin. <p>Carsten Lund Pedersen是丹麦哥本哈根IT大学的副教授。 Laurianne McLaughlin是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>的数字高级编辑。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading C.L. Pedersen, &#8220;Cracking the Culture Code for Successful Digital Transformation,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, April 6, 2022. As digital transformation work unfolds, many companies find cultural barriers insurmountable. Why? Because leaders often fail to strike the right balance between continuity and change, creating cultural chaos that stalls progress. Carsten Lund Pedersen, associate professor [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>CL Pedersen，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cracking-the-culture-code-for-successful-digital-transformation/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">破解成功的数字化转型文化法规”</a> ， <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> ，2022年4月6日。</p></aside><p>随着数字化转型工作的展开，许多公司发现文化障碍无法克服。为什么？因为领导者常常无法在连续性和变化之间取得适当的平衡，从而造成了陷入前进的文化混乱。</p><p> Carsten Lund Pedersen是丹麦IT哥本哈根数字化转型副教授，可帮助组织找到这种平衡。</p><p>在本网络研讨会中，您将学习：</p><ul><li>为什么许多组织在数字化转型期间遭受身份危机的苦难。</li><li>为什么领导者需要表现<em>出</em>改变和尊重现有文化的开放性。</li><li>如何使用矩阵工具以及支持真正转型的文化转变的公司的示例来平衡变化和连续性。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/ballancing-change-ange-ange-ange-during-during-a-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>营销预算平均值的终结</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nader Tavassoli and Christine Moorman. <p>纳德·塔瓦索利（Nader Tavassoli）是伦敦商学院的市场营销教授和领导学院共同学院主任。他还是CMO调查的英国总监。克里斯汀·摩尔曼（Christine Moorman）是杜克大学富夸（Fuqua）商学院的T. Austin Finch高级工商管理教授。她是CMO调查的创始人兼总监，也是<cite>《市场营销杂志》</cite>首席编辑。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Resource Allocation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR In his 2015 book The End of Average, Todd Rose warns against “averagarians” designing systems based on the mean or judging success in terms of the deviation from the mean. He highlights Gilbert Daniels, an anti-averager hero, whose research in the 1950s led the U.S. Air Force to design planes with personalized [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Moorman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p>托德·罗斯（Todd Rose）在他的2015年著作<cite>《平均终结》（The Plases of Plaasis）</cite>中，警告“阿维拉加尔人”（Averagarians）根据均值偏离平均值的平均值或判断成功设计系统。他凸显了反verager的英雄吉尔伯特·丹尼尔斯（Gilbert Daniels），他在1950年代的研究带领美国空军设计了具有个性化驾驶舱功能的飞机，以适合各种形状和大小的飞行员，而不仅仅是普通的男性飞行员，这是一种急剧提高安全性的创新记录。</p><p>营销策略还取决于差异的原则。思考细分：营销人员倾向于不为普通消费者设计产品或服务。的确，像红牛之类的品牌以两极分化为基础，因为许多人都讨厌自己的产品，因为他们喜欢它。</p><p>然而，在营销预算方面，一种常见但有缺陷的做法是使用善意的研究人员吹捧的平均数字。检查营销预算的两项最具成熟的CMO调查是CMO调查，该调查由杜克大学（Duke University）进行双人（并自2008年以来本文的第二作者经营）和Gartner的年度CMO支出和战略调查。 CMO调查发现，2023年的营销预算平均占美国收入的11％，而Gartner发现，2023年的预算占北美和欧洲部分公司总收入的9.1％。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>我们从经验中知道，这些平均值通常是以表面上的为价值。当预算低于平均水平时，CMO不可避免地会获得更多的支出能力。当它们高于平均水平时，首席财务官可以找到收紧金融拇指螺旋体的理由。</p><p>但是，我们认为，出于计划目的，平均营销预算可能会引起高度误导。 CMOS应该照顾<cite>Brian的Monty Python电影生活</cite>- “你们都是个人。 …你们都必须自己解决！” - 选择适当的同行基准。为了帮助领导者这样做，我们通过新的镜头分析了营销预算数据。</p><p></p><h3>关键区别：CMO的控制领域</h3><p>因此，如果平均营销预算不正确，哪个尺寸合适？这得看情况。首先，全身部门差异的平均光泽。如CMO调查所示，例如，平均收入的13.9％，B2C营销预算往往高于B2B预算，平均9.3％。从不同的角度来看，产品品牌的营销预算往往比服务品牌占收入的11.4％，占10.3％。 Companies with $10 million or less in sales have the largest budgets (16.8% of revenues), but this number drops to 9.5% for companies with $10 billion or more in sales. Similarly, budgets exceed 17% at companies with 50 or fewer employees, but they drop to 9.8% for companies with 10,000 or more.</p><p> But why does company size matter, and why are B2C and product brand budgets higher than B2B and service brand budgets? To examine this question, The CMO Survey asked 314 marketing leaders about the breadth of their strategic responsibilities. We found that a significant factor affecting marketing budgets is the realm of control CMOs have at different types of companies. The results highlight significant deviations in marketing budgets based on these responsibilities and entirely account for variations based on company size. In fact, the marketing responsibilities we refer to below account for over 71% of the differences between sectors. In other words, although a peer-benchmark budgeting approach might be appealing, it is also misleading.</p><p></p><p> Our research showed that in 28% of companies surveyed, marketers&#39; job descriptions did not extend beyond communications to operational responsibilities such as sales or e-commerce. And for those “comms-only” companies, marketing budgets were roughly half of the average, at 5.6%. (Almost universally, communication activities included positioning, brand advertising, digital brand promotion, PR, social media, and/or lead generation.) In B2B comms-only companies, marketing budgets stood at 5.9%, or less than two-thirds of the sector average, and in B2C companies, they stood at a meager 4% — less than one-third of the sector average. Comparisons for service (6.1%) and product brands (5.1%) tell a similar story. Surprisingly, for these comms-only brands, budgets are actually larger for B2B and service companies than for B2C and product brands — the opposite of what we see in the average analysis.</p><h3> Strategic Marketers Have the Biggest Budgets</h3><p> In companies where marketing is responsible not only for communications but also for at least one key <em>operational</em> activity — such as sales, distribution, customer service and experience, e-commerce, or customer relationship management — the average budget is higher, at about 7.6% of revenues.</p><p> As in the comms-only organizations, B2B budgets (8.1%) are higher than B2C budgets (5.7%). However, among these marketing-plus-operations companies, budgets are back to being higher for product brands (8.6%) than for service brands (6.8%), which makes sense given the potentially higher channel costs for the former. Having said that, even for this broader realm of control, budgets are still lower than the average, even at the sector level.</p><p> The real difference maker is the addition of at least one <em>strategic</em> activity, such as new products and innovation, market selection and entry, pricing, or growth, to a company&#39;s marketing responsibilities. Among them are areas that business schools have traditionally taught as marketing functions but are not under the auspices of marketing in many companies. The average budget for marketing functions responsible for communications, operations, and strategy stands at 13.4% across companies. Among these, it is now higher for B2C brands (15%) than B2B brands (11.8%) because B2C marketers tend to have a broader realm of control than B2B marketers do. Interestingly, budgets for these companies are also higher for service (14.5%) than for product brands (12.8%), perhaps due to customer experience expenditures.</p><p> Many more areas of control could be considered. When marketing is responsible for privacy in addition to the more traditional marketing functions above, overall budgets leap to 17.7% of revenues. And when managing talent is added to the mix, marketing budgets account for a whopping 23% of revenues. However, comparisons here become unreliable, especially at the sector level, because there are relatively few companies at which marketing is responsible for areas such as talent (11.5%) or privacy (9%).</p><p></p><p></p><p>这个故事的寓意是什么？ If your budget-setting process relies on averages as a benchmark or the wisdom of crowds, make sure you&#39;re using the right crowd as a peer comparison. This requires identifying a benchmark that matches the responsibility profile for your company. Our CMO Survey analysis now provides a way to do so. While the above numbers don&#39;t provide a personalized benchmark, they are far more meaningful than the broad averages typically kicked around in research reports and the popular press.</p><p> A final thought for CMOs is that it&#39;s not all about the money. Above-average budgets come with above-average responsibilities. And that is a topic for organizational design: selecting a distribution of responsibilities that fits the company&#39;s strategy and marketing capabilities.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-end-of-averages-for-marketing-budgets/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> AI Ethics at Unilever: From Policy to Process</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) is the President&#39;s Distinguished Professor of Information Technology and Management at Babson College, a visiting professor at Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School, and a fellow of the MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy. He is coauthor of <cite>Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration</cite> (MIT Press, 2022). Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) is an industry thought leader, author, founder, and CEO and currently serves as innovation fellow, data strategy, for global consultancy Wavestone. He is the author of <cite>Fail Fast, Learn Faster: Lessons in Data-Driven Leadership in an Age of Disruption, Big Data, and AI</cite> (Wiley, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Many large companies today — most surveys suggest over 70% globally — have determined that artificial intelligence is important to their future and are building AI applications in various parts of their businesses. Most also realize that AI has an ethical dimension and that they need to ensure that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Davenport-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Many large companies today — most surveys suggest over 70% globally — have determined that artificial intelligence is important to their future and are building AI applications in various parts of their businesses. Most also realize that AI has an ethical dimension and that they need to ensure that the AI systems they build or implement are transparent, unbiased, and fair.</p><p> Thus far, many companies pursuing ethical AI are still in the early stages of addressing it. They might have exhorted their employees to take an ethical approach to AI development and use or drafted a preliminary set of AI governance policies. Most have not done even that; in <a href="https://www.conversica.com/conversation-automation-resources/report/ai-ethics-survey/">one recent survey</a> , 73% of US senior leaders said they believe that ethical AI guidelines are important, yet only 6% had developed them.</p><p></p><p> We see five stages in the AI ethics process: <em>evangelism</em> , when representatives of the company speak about the importance of AI ethics; <em>development of policies</em> , where the company deliberates on and then approves corporate policies around ethical approaches to AI; <em>recording</em> , where the company collects data on each AI use case or application (using approaches such as <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2021/05/27/the-future-of-work-now-ethical-ai-at-salesforce/?sh=312432713eb6">model cards</a> ); <em>review</em> , where the company performs a systematic analysis of each use case (or outsources it to a partner company) to determine whether the case meets the company&#39;s criteria for AI ethics; and <em>action</em> , where the company either accepts the use case as it is, sends it back to the proposing owner for revision, or rejects it.</p><p> It is only in the higher-level stages — review and action — that a company can actually determine whether its AI applications meet the transparency, bias, and fairness standards that it has established. For it to put those stages in place, it has to have a substantial number of AI projects, processes, and systems for gathering information, along with governance structures for making decisions about specific applications. Many companies do not yet have those preconditions in place, but they will be necessary as companies exhibit greater AI maturity and emphasis.</p><h3> Early Policies at Unilever</h3><p> Unilever, the British consumer packaged goods company whose brands include Dove, Seventh Generation, and Ben &amp; Jerry&#39;s, has long had a focus on corporate social responsibility and environmental sustainability. More recently, the company has embraced AI as a means of dramatically improving operations and decision-making across its global footprint. Unilever&#39;s Enterprise Data Executive, a governance committee, recognized that the company could build on its robust privacy, security, and governance controls by embedding the responsible and ethical use of AI into the company&#39;s data strategies. The goal was to take advantage of AI-driven digital innovation to both maximize the company&#39;s capabilities and promote a fairer and more equitable society. A multifunctional team was created and tasked with exploring what this meant in practice and building an action program to operationalize the objective.</p><p> Unilever has now implemented all of the five stages described above, but, looking back, its first step was to create a set of policies. One policy, for example, specified that any decision that would have a significant life impact on an individual should not be fully automated and should instead ultimately be made by a human. Other AI-specific principles that were adopted include the edicts “We will never blame the system; there must be a Unilever owner accountable” and “We will use our best efforts to systematically monitor models and the performance of our AI to ensure that it maintains its efficacy.”</p><p> Committee members realized quickly that creating broad policies alone would not be sufficient to ensure the responsible development of AI. To build confidence in the adoption of AI and truly unlock its full potential, they needed to develop a strong ecosystem of tools, services, and people resources to ensure that AI systems would work as they were supposed to.</p><p></p><p> Committee members also knew that many of the AI and analytics systems at Unilever were being developed in collaboration with outside software and services vendors. The company&#39;s advertising agencies, for example, often employed programmatic buying software that used AI to decide what digital ads to place on web and mobile sites. The team concluded that its approach to AI ethics needed to include attention to externally sourced capabilities.</p><p></p><h3> Developing a Robust AI Assurance Process</h3><p> Early on in Unilever&#39;s use of AI, the company&#39;s data and AI leaders noticed that some of the issues with the technology didn&#39;t involve ethics at all — they involved systems that were ineffective at the tasks they were intended to accomplish. Giles Pavey, Unilever&#39;s global director of data science, who had primary responsibility for AI ethics, knew that this was an important component of an AI use case. “A system for forecasting cash flow, for example, might involve no fairness or bias risk but may have some risk of not being effective,” he said. “We decided that efficacy risk should be included along with the ethical risks we evaluate.” The company began to use the term <em>AI assurance</em> to broadly encompass its overview of a tool&#39;s effectiveness and ethics.</p><p> The basic idea behind the Unilever AI assurance compliance process is to examine each new AI application to determine how intrinsically risky it is, both in terms of effectiveness and ethics. The company already had a well-defined approach to information security and data privacy, and the goal was to employ a similar approach that would ensure that no AI application was put into production without first being reviewed and approved. Integrating the compliance process into the compliance areas that Unilever already had in place, such as privacy risk assessment, information security, and procurement policies, would be the ultimate sign of success.</p><p> Debbie Cartledge, who took on the role of data and AI ethics strategy lead for the company, explained the process the team adopted:</p><blockquote><p> When a new AI solution is being planned, the Unilever employee or supplier proposes the outlined use case and method before developing it. This is reviewed internally, with more complex cases being manually assessed by external experts. The proposer is then informed of potential ethical and efficacy risks and mitigations to be considered. After the AI application has been developed, Unilever, or the external party, runs statistical tests to ascertain whether there is a bias or fairness issue and could examine the system for efficacy in achieving its objectives. Over time, we expect that a majority of cases can be fully assessed automatically based on information about the project supplied by the project proposer.</p></blockquote><p> Depending on where within the company the system will be employed, there also might be local regulations for the system to comply with. All resume checking, for example, is now done by human reviewers. If resume checking were fully automated, the review might conclude that the system needs a human in the loop to make final decisions about whether to move a candidate to interview. If there are serious risks that can&#39;t be mitigated, the AI assurance process will reject the application on the grounds that Unilever&#39;s values prohibit it. Final decisions on AI use cases are made by a senior executive board, including representatives from the legal, HR, and data and technology departments.</p><p> Here&#39;s an example: The company has areas in department stores where it sells its cosmetics brands. A project was developed to use computer vision AI to automatically register sales agents&#39; attendance through daily selfies, with a stretch objective to look at the appropriateness of agents&#39; appearance. Because of the AI assurance process, the project team broadened their thinking beyond regulations, legality, and efficacy to also consider the potential implications of a fully automated system. They identified the need for human oversight in checking photos flagged as noncompliant and taking responsibility for any consequent actions.</p><h3> Working With an Outside Partner, Holistic AI</h3><p> Unilever&#39;s external partner in the AI assurance process is Holistic AI, a London-based company. Founders Emre Kazim and Adriano Koshiyama have both worked with Unilever AI teams since 2020, and Holistic AI became a formal partner for AI risk assessment in 2021.</p><p> Holistic AI has created a platform to manage the process of reviewing AI assurance. In this context, “AI” is a broad category that encompasses any type of prediction or automation; even an Excel spreadsheet used to score HR candidates would be included in the process. Unilever&#39;s data ethics team uses the platform to review the status of AI projects and can see which new use cases have been submitted; whether the information is complete; and what risk-level assessment they have received, coded red, yellow (termed “amber” in the UK), or green.</p><p> The traffic-light status is assessed at three points: at triage, after further analysis, and after final mitigation and assurance. At this final point, the ratings have the following interpretations: A red rating means the AI system does not comply with Unilever standards and should not be deployed; yellow means the AI system has some acceptable risks and the business owner is responsible for being aware of and taking ownership of it; and green means the AI system adds no risks to the process. Only a handful of the several hundred Unilever use cases have received red ratings thus far, including the cosmetics one described above. All of the submitters were able to resolve the issues with their use cases and move them up to a yellow rating.</p><p> For leaders of AI projects, the platform is the place to start the review process. They submit a proposed use case with details, including its purpose, the business case, the project&#39;s ownership within Unilever, team composition, the data used, the type of AI technology employed, whether it is being developed internally or by an external vendor, the degree of autonomy, and so forth. The platform uses the information to score the application in terms of its potential risk. The risk domains include explainability, robustness, efficacy, bias, and privacy. Machine learning algorithms are automatically analyzed to determine whether they are biased against any particular group.</p><p></p><p> An increasing percentage of the evaluations in the Holistic AI platform are based on the European Union&#39;s proposed AI Act, which also ranks AI use cases into three categories of risk (unacceptable, high, and not high enough to be regulated). The act is being negotiated among EU countries with hopes for an agreement by the end of 2023. Kazim and Koshiyama said that even though the act will apply only to European businesses, Unilever and other companies are likely to adopt it globally, as they have with the EU&#39;s General Data Protection Regulation.</p><p></p><p> Kazim and Koshiyama expect Holistic AI to be able to aggregate data across companies and benchmark across them in the future. The software could assess benefits versus costs, the efficacy of different external providers of the same use case, and the most effective approaches to AI procurement. Kazim and Koshiyama have also considered making risk ratings public in some cases and partnering with an insurance company to insure AI use cases against certain types of risks.</p><p> We&#39;re still in the early stages of <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">ensuring that companies take ethical approaches to AI</a> , but that doesn&#39;t mean that it&#39;s enough to issue pronouncements and policies with no teeth. Whether AI is ethical or not will be determined use case by use case. Unilever&#39;s AI assurance process, and its partnership with Holistic AI to evaluate each use case about its ethical risk level, is the only current way to ensure that AI systems are aligned with human interests and well-being.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Rise of Exit Bans and Hostage-Taking in China</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-taking-in-china/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-taking-in-china/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack Wroldsen and Chris Carr. <p>Jack Wroldsen is an assistant professor of business law and public policy in the Orfalea College of Business at Cal Poly, San Luis Obispo, California. He was an NSEP scholar to Chile and also studied and worked in Argentina and Mexico. Chris Carr is a professor of business law and public policy in the Orfalea College of Business at Cal Poly, San Luis Obispo. He is also a four-time Fulbright award recipient (Italy, Tunisia, Pakistan, and Mongolia).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[China]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Austin/theispot.com Foreign entities doing business in China are facing increasingly grave risks. On top of the high-level geopolitical and economic risks to consider, the growing incidence of exit bans, which prevent foreign executives from leaving China if their company becomes involved in a dispute, imposes a very individual human risk. While there has been [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Carr_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Michael Austin/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Foreign entities doing business in China are facing increasingly grave risks. On top of the high-level geopolitical and economic risks to consider, the growing incidence of exit bans, which prevent foreign executives from leaving China if their company becomes involved in a dispute, imposes a very individual human risk. While there has been widespread media coverage of a few cases — the exit ban placed on a Singaporean executive from US investigations company Mintz Group and the <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-65061116">detention of five of its Chinese employees</a> ; the tit-for-tat <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/huawei-s-meng-wanzhou-2-michaels-what-next-china-u-n1280229">detention of two Canadian businessmen</a> in retaliation for US fraud charges brought against a Huawei executive arrested in Canada — many companies operating internationally confront the reality of exit bans and commercial hostage-taking in relative obscurity.</p><p> This risk is increasing and unlikely to abate soon. Little in the ordinary course of business is more disruptive or volatile than the detention of company executives or employees abroad. Companies operating in China should prepare for these potential scenarios in advance.</p><p></p><p> Exit bans can arise from civil business disputes as well as more serious legal entanglements. <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-chinese-law-raises-risks-for-american-firms-in-china-u-s-officials-say-cf62c1a0">Recent amendments to China&#39;s counterespionage law</a> , including vague, open-ended prohibitions on possessing “documents, data, materials, or items related to national security,” could easily encompass everyday business activities in any industry, exposing foreign executives to greater risk of arrest. The <a href="https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/traveladvisories/traveladvisories/china-travel-advisory.html">US Department of State recently warned</a> that the Chinese government “arbitrarily enforces local laws, including issuing exit bans on US citizens and citizens of other countries, without fair and transparent process under the law.”</p><p> Someone subject to an exit ban for business reasons often receives no advance notice before being prevented from boarding an international flight at the airport. The person is typically interrogated but not given information about the reason for the exit ban or how to contest it.</p><p> Exit bans in cases of business disputes are typically lifted only after the foreigner accedes to the demands of their Chinese counterparty — which gains enormous leverage in the dispute by limiting the individual&#39;s personal freedom. Even if the foreigner is willing to spend the necessary time and money to pursue the case in court while remaining trapped in China, a Chinese court is unlikely to rule in favor of the foreign party.</p><p></p><p> Consider Henry Cai, a native of China who moved to California with his wife in the 1980s and became a US citizen. In 2012, Cai invested in a Chinese technology startup for an 8% stake and served as a director of the company. A few years later, when the startup faced cash-flow problems and defaulted on a loan, Cai traveled to China multiple times to deal with the situation. Then, in 2017, Cai was stopped at the airport and denied exit from China, at which time he realized that he had been implicated in a lawsuit filed against the company by its creditors. Six years later, he remains <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-us-exit-ban-diplomacy-11668357015">stuck in China</a> , unable to pay the millions of dollars demanded to lift the exit ban. The human, emotional, and financial toll is high, for him in China and for his wife and their two children in California.</p><p></p><p> Another example is Brian Horowitz, a California businessman who purchased gas-powered blenders from a Chinese manufacturer. After a contract dispute arose because the blenders failed to meet California air-quality standards, Horowitz traveled to China to meet with the supplier. When he attempted to return home, he was <a href="https://www.latimes.com/archives/la-xpm-2011-jan-28-la-fi-china-horowitz-20110128-story.html">detained at the Shanghai airport</a> ; the supplier had filed a contract claim against his company, and the court had imposed an exit ban without Horowitz&#39;s knowledge. After two weeks, his wife wired $250,000 to the Chinese supplier to allow her husband to return home.</p><p> While exit bans in the case of business disputes are legal in China, foreign executives are also at risk of falling victim to illegal commercial hostage situations. In such cases, they might be confined in a hotel room or a company facility such as an office or factory. Holding commercial hostages is punishable by up to three years&#39; imprisonment. In practice, however, Chinese <a href="https://foreignpolicy.com/2017/08/08/chinas-police-think-hostages-arent-their-problem/">law enforcement often refuses to</a> intervene in these situations unless violence occurs.</p><p> In one case, a senior executive of a US jewelry company traveled to China to discuss a dispute with a manufacturer over a product order and a <a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3692138">$650,000 payment</a> . After the executive entered the manufacturer&#39;s facility, her purse and passport were confiscated. She was then taken back to her hotel and guarded by employees of the manufacturer for five days. She escaped with the help of a US lawyer fluent in Chinese who traveled to China, helped her evade the guards, and brought her to the embassy.</p><p> Another case occurred when a US company sent two midlevel executives to visit a Chinese factory that produced goods for it. The US company had already paid the manufacturer for the goods, but its executives learned that the factory workers were refusing to release the products because their wages had not been paid for months. The workers locked the executives inside the factory and demanded payment for their release. To free the hostages and obtain the goods, the US company had to pay both the manufacturing company and the workers.</p><p> Commercial hostage-taking situations are usually resolved within days or weeks, whereas exit bans might not be lifted for months or years. Neither situation is officially tracked, and businesspeople often keep their predicaments confidential. Nonetheless, based on data from the governments of six countries (the United States, Canada, the United Kingdom, Germany, the Netherlands, and Australia) and media reports, we documented more than <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/tie.22261">100 business exit bans and commercial hostage situations</a> in roughly the past十年。 This is likely a significant undercount, given that government documentation on this phenomenon is not comprehensive, and not every case would have received media attention.</p><h3> Take a Multifaceted Approach to Prepare for the Worst</h3><p> The acutely personal nature and the geopolitical dynamics of these situations make them particularly challenging to plan for and to resolve. How much should you pay to free your colleague (or yourself) from being held hostage? How do you talk to your employee&#39;s spouse about the reasons for their partner&#39;s detention and your plan to negotiate for their return? Is it part of your job to engage with the media to bring about political pressure to free an employee?</p><p> To prepare for such a scenario, it&#39;s critical that business leaders acknowledge the risk of this happening to their employees who travel to China, in addition to becoming more informed about it — such as by establishing a dialogue with others who have experienced it. They should also develop and maintain trusting relationships with US consular officials abroad, Chinese officials and police chiefs in the cities where the company operates, federal and state government leaders in the US, members of local and national media, and applicable industry groups, such as the US-China Business Council.</p><p> Companies should preassemble a crisis team and develop an action plan that assigns specific responsibilities to key employees and advisers in both China and their home country. This plan should include external communications, such as using social media to draw attention to the plight of trapped employees. And a company should consult with its business insurer to find out whether any relevant coverage is available to mitigate the financial impact of an exit ban or commercial hostage situation.</p><p> Executives with business interests in China should also pay close attention to accounts payable, contractual obligations, and the tone of business relationships to identify potential sources of conflict or disagreement. They should try to anticipate problems before they arise and should be especially vigilant about any outstanding debts or situations where a product has been delivered but, for any reason whatsoever, has not yet been completely paid for.</p><p></p><p> If a lawsuit has been or is suspected to have been initiated, or any debts are owed to a Chinese entity, companies should avoid having employees travel to China. If such travel is unavoidable, employees should remain in frequent communication so that others know their whereabouts and schedules, and they should avoid traveling alone. If a dispute has arisen but not yet materialized into a lawsuit, and employees must travel to China, consider suing preemptively in the US, assuming that a US court has jurisdiction over the Chinese business. For example, if the US company alleges a contract breach in a US court, then the employee should carry documentation of the US lawsuit, translated into Chinese, while abroad.</p><p></p><p> Leaders must also be prepared to support and help employees and their families. A crisis team set up in advance should have a plan for communicating honestly and sensitively with employees trapped abroad and with their families, as well as with employees throughout the company.表现出你的关心。 Be transparent and truthful. These situations are emotionally draining, disorienting, and frightening; they are also opportunities to build trust, solidarity, and a culture of care. It is more about people than money.</p><p> Of course, it&#39;s important to remain committed to helping affected employees and their families in tangible ways. Arrange for the delivery of personalized care packages to affected families; visit their homes, and meet face-to-face with them. Where possible, also send care packages to employees trapped abroad and facilitate calls with family members.</p><p> Scenarios like exit bans and commercial hostage situations are human rights and geopolitical issues that are also intensely personal business challenges. Business leaders are wise to prepare for such challenges by developing a comprehensive strategic approach.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-taking-in-china/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Are RAI Programs Prepared for Third-Party and Generative AI?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Infographic]]></category><category><![CDATA[Policy Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[In 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review and BCG completed their second year of researching responsible AI (RAI). In addition to producing a series of articles that draw on insights from an expert panel and a survey-based research report, the team has highlighted its key findings in this infographic. Although many organizations are prioritizing RAI and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> In 2023, <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and BCG completed their second year of <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">researching responsible AI</a> (RAI). In addition to producing a series of articles that draw on insights from an expert panel and a survey-based research report, the team has highlighted its key findings in this infographic.</p><p> Although many organizations are prioritizing RAI and developing programs to manage artificial intelligence tools responsibly, a majority of companies rely on third-party AI tools (tools they buy, access, or license, including generative AI tools such as ChatGPT and Bard) — which come with significant risks. It is clear that most organizations are not prepared to address these new risks, but our research has enabled us to develop a set of recommendations to help them get RAI right.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何在棘手的话题上有效地表达不同意见</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenji Yoshino and David Glasgow. <p>Kenji Yoshino ( <a href="https://twitter.com/kenji_yoshino">@kenji_yoshino</a> ) is the Chief Justice Earl Warren Professor of Constitutional Law at the New York University School of Law and the faculty director of the Meltzer Center for Diversity, Inclusion, and Belonging. David Glasgow ( <a href="https://twitter.com/dvglasgow">@dvglasgow</a> ) is the executive director of the Meltzer Center for Diversity, Inclusion, and Belonging and an adjunct professor at the NYU School of Law. They are the coauthors of <cite>Say the Right Thing: How to Talk About Identity, Diversity, and Justice</cite> (Atria Books, 2023), on which this article is based.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cultural Differences]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com &#160; Conversations about identity, diversity, and justice are some of the thorniest human interactions of our time. Consider Uber’s head of diversity, who hosted a workplace event titled “Don’t Call Me Karen” to highlight the “spectrum of the American White woman’s experience” and foster an “open and honest conversation about race.” Following backlash [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Yoshino_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Neil Webb/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p></p><p> Conversations about identity, diversity, and justice are some of the thorniest human interactions of our time. Consider Uber&#39;s head of diversity, who hosted a workplace event titled “Don&#39;t Call Me Karen” to highlight the “spectrum of the American White woman&#39;s experience” and foster an “open and honest conversation about race.” Following backlash from employees of color, she was placed on a leave of absence. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p> Or consider Stanford Law School&#39;s associate dean for diversity, who tried to “de-escalate” student protests during a speech by conservative judge Kyle Duncan. The dean tried to placate the students, who were angered by the judge&#39;s anti-LGBTQ+ views, while giving the judge the space to finish his talk. But her intervention led to a public furor due to a perception that she had prioritized students&#39; feelings over the judge&#39;s right to free speech. She, too, was placed on leave. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p> If these conversations stymie senior diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) professionals, what hope do ordinary leaders have?比你想象的还要多。</p><p> We lead a research center at the New York University School of Law dedicated to issues of diversity, inclusion, and belonging. Together and separately, we&#39;ve taught tens of thousands of individuals from all walks of life to have more meaningful and effective conversations across their differences. We focus our efforts on coaching people in positions of power because they have the greatest opportunity to transform the dynamics of these interactions — to foster empathy instead of provoking fear and division.</p><p> While the people we coach struggle with many types of identity conversations, disagreements are often the most agonizing. It&#39;s relatively easy to participate in identity conversations when you and the other person are aligned. When you disagree, you&#39;re likely to be flooded with angst and self-doubt. You might wonder: <em>Am I as enlightened as I thought I was? Will people feel hurt or betrayed by me?</em></p><p> You might be tempted to respond to such angst by capitulating to whatever your conversation partner says. Yet that approach is often not desirable, because it compromises your dignity and authenticity. We believe it&#39;s still possible to disagree on identity issues, even in today&#39;s polarized and overheated political climate. The key is to do it respectfully.就是这样。</p><h3> Locate the Conversation on the Controversy Scale</h3><p> We&#39;re both in same-sex relationships — Kenji married his husband in 2009, and David married his in 2014 — and we&#39;ve participated in debates over same-sex marriage in many forums. We have never enjoyed these discussions, but we&#39;ve found one feature of them uniquely awful: Our opponents have rarely acknowledged what the debate means to us or to other LGBTQ+ people.</p><p> In a prominent work opposing marriage equality, the authors insisted that people can reject same-sex marriage “without denigrating same-sex-attracted people, or ignoring their needs.” <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> They&#39;ve taken the same position in live conversations. In a televised debate about same-sex marriage, the moderator asked one of the authors, Ryan Anderson, to explain to financial adviser Suze Orman, a lesbian, “what&#39;s wrong with her.” “I don&#39;t think there&#39;s anything wrong with you,” Anderson told Orman. “The question is, what is marriage? I think that marriage is intrinsically … a union of a man and a woman.” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Although it sounded diplomatic, this response didn&#39;t recognize that from many gay people&#39;s perspectives, Anderson&#39;s opposition to same-sex marriage logically meant he thought Orman was a second-class citizen. Yet in our myriad conversations on this topic, we can count on one hand the number of times the opposing side recognized that we might experience their view as a strike at our basic humanity. That approach didn&#39;t require them to change their opinion. It just required them to acknowledge how that opinion might land on the other side.</p><p> In part due to that frustration, we developed a controversy scale that plots the subjects of disagreement along a straight line. On the left are the safest subjects, where disagreement is expected or even celebrated. On the right are the most controversial subjects, where the conversation is most likely to turn ugly.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>如何表达不同意见</h4><p class="caption">Locating the topic of a conversation on this controversy scale can help you frame a difficult topic at a level where respectful discussion is more likely. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Yoshino_Essay_Winter_2024_Figure-1.png" alt="如何表达不同意见" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Disagreements over personal tastes are usually warm and good-natured. When friends mock us for our love of trashy TV shows, those disagreements can strengthen rather than weaken the relationship. Disagreeing over facts is also relatively comfortable, provided it really is a debate about facts (such as who, what, when, where, or how) rather than a thinly veiled debate over values (framed as “alternative facts” or “fake news” ）。 The real danger comes when the topic drifts further to the right on the controversy scale. The most intense conversations are those in which one or both sides feel that their equal humanity has been put into question.</p><p> Imagine you&#39;re a Latine proponent of a workplace diversity and inclusion initiative, and you&#39;re debating a non-Latine colleague who opposes the program. We think you&#39;ll find it uncomfortable but manageable to discuss whether the initiative has succeeded in advancing Latine representation in the workplace (facts). You&#39;ll find it harder to debate whether diversity considerations should be factored into promotion decisions (policies). And you&#39;ll find it excruciating to debate psychologist Richard Herrnstein and political scientist Charles Murray&#39;s infamous hypothesis that IQs differ among racial and ethnic groups (equal humanity). <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> The trouble with identity disagreements is that more privileged conversation partners almost always locate the issue at different positions on the controversy scale than less privileged ones do. If you think your company focuses too much on anti-racism, you might see the dispute as a policy debate over how the organization should prioritize different aspects of its mission. Your conversation partner, an Asian American colleague, might think you&#39;re trivializing her sense of belonging at the company. She&#39;s the one, after all, who has to contend with anti-Asian bias in the workplace. You locate the issue in the middle of the controversy scale at “policies.” She locates it at the rightward extreme of “equal humanity.”</p><p></p><p> You might find that after you recognize where the other person is on the controversy scale, you&#39;ll reassess the nature of the disagreement, moving the issue closer to where they&#39;ve positioned it. But you might not, and we&#39;re not pushing you to do so. All we ask is that you explicitly acknowledge your counterpart&#39;s position. At the outset of the conversation, you might say something like, “To me this is a policy debate, but I see how it could be deeply personal for you, and I&#39;ll do my best to respect that reality when sharing my views. ” There might also be times during or after a conversation where you realize you treated the topic as a purely intellectual exercise and need to recognize the impact the discussion might have had on the other person: “I&#39;ve been bringing policy arguments to the table, but can I ask how you&#39;ve been experiencing this discussion as someone whose life might be more directly affected by this issue?”</p><p> We think you&#39;ll be shocked at how much acknowledging your relative subject positions can take the hurt or heat out of a disagreement. This holds true even if those positions seem obvious to both parties. Often, what&#39;s needed is not more knowledge but more acknowledgment of shared knowledge.</p><p></p><h3> Find Uncommon Commonalities</h3><p> In the 1987 movie <cite>Predator</cite> , the character of Dutch (played by Arnold Schwarzenegger) and the character of Dillon (Carl Weathers) greet each other with what&#39;s come to be known as an epic handshake. “Dillon, you son of a bitch,” Dutch says as they walk up to each other and clasp their hands together with their hulking arms in a V-shape like they&#39;re about to arm-wrestle. They refuse to let go of each other&#39;s hand. Then the handshake turns into an actual arm-wrestling match. It&#39;s an almost parodic display of over-the-top masculinity.</p><p> The scene might have been forgotten but for a viral meme. When social media users want to show two seemingly unrelated people, groups, or concepts that share a surprising commonality, they post a picture of Dutch and Dillon shaking hands. They put one label over Dutch&#39;s arm, another over Dillon&#39;s arm, and the commonality in the middle. In one instance, revenge and ice cream shake hands over the phrase “best served cold.” The epic handshake has also spawned other attempts at highlighting unpredictable overlaps using Venn diagrams. We learn that bank robbers, DJs, and preachers share “put your hands up.” These images help us see the handshake hidden in each arm-wrestling match.</p><p> This capability is critical, and cultivating it is harder than it looks. It&#39;s conventional wisdom that offering points of agreement is an effective strategy when disagreeing with someone. But as philosopher Daniel Dennett has noted, it&#39;s particularly helpful to find points that “are not matters of general or widespread agreement.” <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> The idea is to find uncommon commonalities that surprise you out of your defaults. Too often, people settle for the bland ones that feel like empty gestures. It&#39;s like posting the bank robbers, DJs, and preachers meme and making the commonality “occupations.”</p><p> Instead, try to find uncommon commonalities that can liberate you as well as your conversation partner and help make even the most inflammatory of subjects easier to discuss. In recent years, hordes of concerned parents have streamed into usually sleepy town hall meetings to express outrage over the conversations about race being held in their children&#39;s classrooms. One such parent is Bart Glasgow (no relation to David), a conservative evangelical Christian White man from Canton, Georgia, who spoke up at a school board meeting to oppose the hiring of a DEI administrator in his local district.</p><p></p><p> Bart and his wife, Coley, decided to speak with four experts on the subject of race. One was Carol Anderson, a professor and chair of African American studies at Emory University and author of several books, including <cite>White Rage</cite> . On the surface, Anderson and the Glasgows have little in common. Yet in their hour-long conversation, both sides made considerable effort to find points of connection. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Bart Glasgow noted that he wrote his senior college thesis on the topic of civil disobedience, examining figures like Henry David Thoreau, Mahatma Gandhi, and Martin Luther King Jr. “I think what Dr. King did was amazing,” he said. “To take that biblical principle of turning the other cheek and to show love when hate&#39;s being shown to you.” Anderson noted that her father was “career military” and described being raised in the church and in a “God-fearing” community. They all bonded over their experience of growing up with the <cite>World Book Encyclopedia</cite> in their homes and with parents who would take them “to the woodshed.” They continued by sharing experiences of being in the minority in an educational setting. Anderson, who is Black, talked about being bussed to a majority-White high school. Coley Glasgow, who is White, shared that she completed her higher education at two historically Black colleges.</p><p> This exploration of common ground paid dividends. As the conversation continued, they aired disagreements. Bart Glasgow argued against an emphasis on systemic racism; Anderson disagreed. Later, Bart advocated for school vouchers that would allow parents to move their children out of underperforming local schools, and again Anderson disagreed. Yet these disagreements were remarkably civil. When the conversation concluded, Bart said to Anderson, “I could talk to you for hours. I really could.” Anderson replied, “Thank you so much for being here and asking these wonderful questions and engaging in this great conversation.谢谢。我喜欢它。”</p><p> The next time you are confronted with a disagreement, try asking yourself what you have in common with your conversation partner that might surprise them. If you&#39;re debating same-sex marriage, you might point out that many people — straight and gay — think marriage is an antiquated institution. So, despite your differences, you both believe in the importance of marriage as an institution. Finding those uncommon commonalities requires a bit of ingenuity, and it might feel taxing at times. But the payoff is big: Finding them can jolt both of you out of the reflexive and unconscious sense that you are adversaries in the conversation.</p><h3>展示你的作品</h3><p>Shortly after we launched the Meltzer Center for Diversity, Inclusion, and Belonging, we received an unnerving email from a respected colleague. She asked us to use our platform as diversity and inclusion scholars to advocate for people who don&#39;t fully vaccinate themselves or their children. In her view, excluding people from schools and workplaces for defying vaccine mandates had “troubling” implications for the values of diversity, inclusion, and belonging. She invited us to discuss the issue with her so it could be addressed university-wide.</p><p> We received this request before the COVID-19 pandemic turned vaccines into a white-hot issue. Even so, we knew this conversation might be difficult. We passionately disagreed with her perspective, but we feared that neither acknowledging her position on the controversy scale nor offering an epic handshake would suffice.</p><p> So we shared our reasoning in depth. We stated politely but firmly that we didn&#39;t believe opposition to vaccines fit within the scope of our center&#39;s work. We explained that the center&#39;s primary function was to address bias against marginalized social groups, like people of color or women. We acknowledged that some groups, like religious minorities, were mistreated because of their beliefs rather than because of their physical characteristics. But particularly as a newly launched center, we weren&#39;t eager to stretch the definition of a marginalized group to people defined by their views on a single issue. We also noted that the topic of vaccine hesitancy raised complicated medical, ethical, and public health questions outside our expertise.</p><p> We had no illusions that this approach would change our colleague&#39;s mind. But it showed we&#39;d given her viewpoint real consideration, and it also offered her an opportunity to point out where we might be wrong. She thanked us for the thoughtfulness of our response, noted that she completely understood our position, and invited us to participate in an event on a separate topic.</p><p> Our approach to our colleague&#39;s inquiry was an example of showing your work — that is, explaining a disagreement in as much detail as possible to demonstrate to the other person that you&#39;ve thought carefully about the subject. The advice to highlight points of disagreement might seem out of step with our previous emphasis on finding common ground. But you can and should do both — look for points of agreement and share points of disagreement in detail. Paint a complete picture of the facts and values on which you&#39;re basing your disagreement, any research and conversations that have informed your current thinking, and any remaining doubts or uncertainties you hold. Over your conversation partner&#39;s lifetime, they&#39;ve probably encountered many people who have reflexively opposed their views based on shoddy or incomplete work. Showing the effort you&#39;ve made will distinguish you from those opponents. It will help them respond to you rather than to all those voices from their past.</p><p> A word of caution: When showing your work, don&#39;t offer a slapdash summary of the opposing argument before immediately dismissing it. Writer Moira Weigel has likened this mistake to “the first sentence of the last paragraph” of a high school essay: “I have thought of the other side already. Do not accuse me of not having thought of the other side!” <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Rather than taking that cursory approach, take the time to research and understand the opposing view, and then share that understanding generously before you explain why you continue to see the issue differently. Show your work to show your respect.</p><h3> Manage Expectations</h3><p> Many people have a low tolerance for disagreement in general. If a contentious identity issue comes up at a conference room table, they immediately change the subject. If they have an argument with someone, they replay the conversation in their mind for weeks. David, unfortunately, is one such person. He&#39;ll run away from voicing a disagreement to avoid conflict, then stew alone in frustration that the other person doesn&#39;t agree with him. For whatever reason, he seems to have an unrealistic expectation that identity conversations should always end in a group hug.</p><p> People sometimes ask us anguished questions along these lines: “I&#39;m an atheist and staunch liberal, but a colleague on my team at work is a conservative evangelical Christian. How can we work together despite our disagreements?” Our answer: Lower your expectations. We admit this advice probably won&#39;t make its way onto a motivational poster. But we think it&#39;s completely appropriate to scale the intensity of the passion you bring into the disagreement to the intensity of the relationship.</p><p></p><p> A cartoon by Randall Munroe shows a stick figure furiously tapping away at a computer keyboard while a voice from the other room calls out, “Are you coming to bed?” The stick figure responds, “I can&#39;t.这个很重要。 Someone is <em>wrong</em> on the internet.” <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Most people have enough perspective not to care fiercely about disagreements with random internet trolls. But it&#39;s worth cultivating that healthy instinct in other situations, too. Each of us would struggle if we had a major disagreement with our spouse about issues of identity. Nevertheless, we&#39;ve both supervised and advanced the careers of students who disagree with us, because the teacher-student relationship is less intense than the marital one. The same goes for colleagues, neighbors, and acquaintances. When the relationship isn&#39;t as close, the need for agreement should be lower.</p><p> You can also manage your expectations of what can be achieved in a single conversation. As with any dispute over a heavy subject, identity conflicts often aren&#39;t neatly resolved in one encounter. The first conversation might go poorly, but the second might go better and the third better still. You might need to take multiple off-ramps and on-ramps to and from a conversation before you make progress.</p><p></p><p> When people engage in conversations about identity, diversity, and justice with someone who has opposing views, we encourage them to practice the four strategies we&#39;ve described:</p><ul><li> Locate the conversation on the controversy scale. To you, the conversation might be a factual or policy debate, but to the other person, it might be a debate over their equal humanity.</li><li> Find uncommon commonalities — points of agreement that are not matters of widespread agreement.</li><li> Show your work on the remaining disagreements to demonstrate that you&#39;ve thought carefully about the subject.</li><li> Manage your expectations. Scale the intensity with which you care about the disagreement to the intensity of the relationship.</li></ul><p> Despite the examples we&#39;ve shared, you might think we&#39;re being unrealistic about your ability to disagree agreeably on matters of identity by practicing these strategies. It&#39;s true that they can&#39;t ensure positive outcomes in all conversations. But we&#39;re confident that you&#39;ll see an immediate improvement in the quality of your conversations if you follow these guidelines.</p><p></p><p> Sometimes, of course, the rift between you and the other person will be too wide. Sometimes an attempt at conversation will end without a resolution. Sometimes the relationship itself will end. As awful as that outcome can feel, it&#39;s sometimes a necessary one. We&#39;re not here to guarantee that every disagreement will end happily. Rather, we want to help you ensure that a divide is truly unbridgeable before you walk away from it.</p><p> Other times, of course, you might be surprised in a positive way. Few, if any, meaningful relationships are devoid of conflict. When handled well, moments of tension can deepen a bond. Rather than nodding along insincerely or offering fake opinions, sharing a thoughtful difference of opinion can show the other person that you value them enough to be honest with them. Moreover, by modeling how to productively disagree, you can set the tone for how others throughout your organization can navigate today&#39;s thorniest conversations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Real Measure of Presentation Success</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a> is the CEO of <a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a> , a communication company in the Silicon Valley. She&#39;s the author of six books, including <cite>DataStory: Explain Data and Inspire Action Through Story</cite> (Ideapress Publishing, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Historically, it’s been tough to quantify the success of events, presentations, and speeches. We’ve long known that the spoken word is a powerful tool for influence and action, but how do you measure that power? When many organizations flipped from in-person to virtual and hybrid meetings and events, presentation [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Duarte-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Historically, it&#39;s been tough to quantify the success of events, presentations, and speeches. We&#39;ve long known that the spoken word is a powerful tool for influence and action, but how do you measure that power?</p><p> When many organizations flipped from in-person to virtual and hybrid meetings and events, presentation analytics became a whole new ballgame. Speakers used to measure impact largely by surveying people and reading the literal room. While those forms of feedback still provide useful information about whether and how a message is landing, presenters now have many other metrics they can use.</p><p></p><p> Here&#39;s a quick example: For decades, my firm built all the decks for a large company&#39;s annual software developer conference. When the conference went remote because of COVID-19, we reworked all the content — each of the breakout sessions, as well as the keynotes — for a virtual audience. After that conference, the organizers stack-ranked the most popular sessions and realized they&#39;d put the same amount of energy into creating a session that garnered 40 views as they&#39;d put into creating sessions that earned hundreds of thousands of views. The organizers also got data on the percentages of participants actively engaging with the sessions, along with related numbers on downloads and shares. Combined with the substance of attendee comments, these insights told the conference folks which topics were resonating both broadly and deeply, helped them manage their time investments, and shaped their choice to keep the conference mostly virtual.</p><p> That&#39;s just one of many ways you can slice, dice, and analyze. But to gauge a presentation&#39;s success, what should you measure <em>for</em> ? In the example above, a key organizational goal was for developers to learn and build new software features into products, so the conference folks were looking specifically at how long each attendee stayed in the critical sessions, how active they were in the learning sessions, which tools they downloaded, and, after the event, how many applications the developers rolled out. Once the event team knew which sessions had turned out to be the most useful, they could create better-targeted content for the next conference.</p><p> All of these yardsticks measured some form of action. And really, that&#39;s what all presenters should be looking for: evidence that they&#39;ve moved people to <em>do</em> something, whether it&#39;s learning a new skill, adopting a new approach to organizational culture, changing a deeply ingrained process or behavior, or treating customers differently 。</p><p> To measure a presentation&#39;s success, you need to assess your audience members&#39; feelings and actions before you speak, while you speak, and after you&#39;re done.</p><p></p><h3> Before Your Talk</h3><p> To define what baseline result you&#39;re after — that is, what action you want people to take after they walk away from your talk — it helps to know your audience. In studying hundreds of powerful speeches (and even checking out business speeches from the Stanford University library all the way back to the 1950s), I found that most of their <a href="https://www.duarte.com/how-to-write-a-call-to-action-in-a-persuasive-speech/#:~:text=Who's%20in%20Your%20Audience%2C%20and,they%20bring%20to%20the%20table.">calls to action</a> targeted one of four audience types: <em>doers</em> , who could instigate activity and get things moving in the organization; <em>suppliers</em> , who could provide resources and other types of support needed to achieve a desired goal; <em>influencers</em> , who could mobilize others to adopt a new idea or approach; or <em>innovators</em> , who could generate new ideas and apply their smarts to solve a problem or seize an opportunity.</p><p> Which type of audience will you address in your talk? Once you&#39;ve sorted out that critical “who,” you can analyze the “what” and the “how” of getting people to adopt and implement your idea. Specifically, you can take one of the following approaches.</p><p> <strong>Delve into your audience&#39;s thoughts and feelings.</strong> Ask yourself about the people you want to reach: <em>What</em> do they think about your idea now? If it&#39;s not on their radar yet, <em>how</em> will they feel about it when they hear what you have to say? And how do you want their thoughts and feelings to <em>change</em> as a result of your talk?</p><p></p><p> This isn&#39;t just a hypothetical stepping-into-their-shoes exercise. Gathering that information in advance — and articulating the points of view you want to move people <em>from</em> and <em>to</em> — will determine the way you frame an issue and possible responses to it. That could mean doing some research or surveying the audience to assess what people currently know about your topic and how they feel about it. For example, you might interview the people closest to your customers or culture. Are they excited about your idea, or skeptical of it? What questions do they have about it? Not only will you figure out what baseline you&#39;re starting from — you&#39;re also likely to gain insights about your audience that will help you <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-storytelling-techniques-to-bring-your-data-to-life/">craft your message</a> . You can also identify a benchmark to measure against later on, after your presentation — say, one of your organization&#39;s KPIs or an important talent-recruitment metric.</p><p> <strong>Anticipate emotional sticking points.</strong> The bigger the transformation you&#39;re trying to trigger in your audience, the more difficult it can be to quantify, especially if it&#39;s an emotional shift. As you research what&#39;s currently going on in your audience members&#39; heads, consider their hearts as well. What&#39;s going to be the hardest part of your message for people to accept or process, no matter how logical the argument or solid the evidence? What sources of potential resistance can you identify? If you do win over people&#39;s heads, how will you know when you&#39;ve won over their hearts, too?</p><p> Emotional change often won&#39;t show up on a dashboard. Even technologies that allow organizations to <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/employee-emotions-arent-noise-theyre-data/">track customer or employee sentiment</a> won&#39;t collect data on everything you need to know. Sometimes you&#39;ll know you&#39;ve overcome emotional resistance only when you see it later in new behaviors — when employees stop pushing back on important initiatives, for example, or when customers change their minds and buy the new release of your product.</p><h3> During Your Talk</h3><p> You can gauge your talk&#39;s likelihood of success as it&#39;s happening. To do this, you&#39;ll measure audience reactions in a few ways.</p><p> <strong>Observe audience behavior in the room or online.</strong> The most immediate form of measurement is to watch how people respond to a presentation in real time. When everyone takes out their phones to snap pictures of slides, you know something&#39;s grabbing their attention. Notice, too, when people laugh, gasp, or applaud — these basic behavioral cues signal <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-data-insights-visually-consumable/">which moments in your talk are resonating</a> . Tech comes in really handy here. If your talk (whether delivered in person or remotely) is recorded, you can easily go back and look for places where the audience visibly or audibly responded.</p><p> <strong>Look at the number of attendees.</strong> If you&#39;re addressing a crowd at a big event such as an industry gathering, another useful metric is the number of people who showed up to hear you speak when they could have attended other sessions instead. If you&#39;ve packed a physical or virtual room, that means you&#39;ve teed up your talk effectively before even opening your mouth. When I spoke this year at Dreamforce, a Salesforce conference, most of my audience members skewed young and weren&#39;t familiar with my work, but the talk was still oversubscribed, with overflow attendees clustered in the doorway. My name wasn&#39;t the draw — rather, it&#39;s the way I&#39;d titled and framed the message that hit a nerve. When attendees rated the talk, the data showed that it had lived up to the promise in the title and program description.</p><p> <strong>Spark and track social engagement.</strong> If your talk is getting everyone buzzing, especially at a large event, they might share quotes or images from your presentation in real time on social channels. Be sure to add your social handles and event-specific hashtags to your slides so it&#39;s easier for your audience to tag you and for you to track the ideas they&#39;re engaging with most. (Those posts, comments, likes, reshares, and other in-the-moment social reactions can later be captured in a post-event report.) You can also accelerate and measure the spread of ideas by providing repackaged presentation content in easily shared formats like infographics or <a href="https://www.duarte.com/resources/books/slidedocs/">Slidedocs</a> (slides that have more text because they are meant to be read by the audience rather than simply presented by the speaker). One of our tech customers has us build their keynote speeches into skimmable e-books with the script and slide visuals as well as trackable links to additional material.</p><h3> After Your Talk</h3><p> Your post-talk metrics can track both satisfaction with the presentation and some of the steps audience members have taken to implement the ideas.</p><p> <strong>Use surveys to assess audience satisfaction.</strong> Many speakers use surveys to measure audience sentiment after a presentation. If you surveyed people before you spoke as well, you&#39;ll be able to see whether your talk has moved the doers, suppliers, influencers, or innovators in the audience any closer to your point of view. One Fortune 100 tech company we work with also uses audience ratings as a management tool to motivate speakers to perform well. Everyone wants to get the highest possible score, and those who don&#39;t score well are likely to work hard to raise their score the next time they speak — or not be invited back.</p><p> <strong>Examine the speaker&#39;s own satisfaction.</strong> In companies without a strong measurement culture, sometimes one of the most telling signs of success is how the speakers themselves think their presentations went. That might seem like navel-gazing, but it&#39;s a bigger deal than most people assume. If a leader who consistently works on their skills and performance as a communicator and is sensitive to cues from the audience feels that they&#39;ve delivered an effective presentation, chances are actually pretty good that they have. And, hey, when your CEO wants to feel like a rock star, and they walk off the stage feeling like one, I call that a win.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Quantify actions taken.</strong> This is where you come back to that baseline result you&#39;ve defined — the audience behavior you wanted to elicit or change when you developed your presentation. While reactions like satisfaction and buy-in matter, actions matter more. The whole point of giving a presentation is to persuade people to adopt and implement your ideas. So look at the traction that your initiative gained as a result of your talk. Did your employees complete the enrollment forms your HR team mentioned in the benefits presentation? Did your sales team download the new corporate overview deck you launched at kickoff? How many deals closed as a result? I embed QR codes in my slide decks — most people know how to use them — and share my slides. This allows attendees to do a deeper “double-click” on a concept. My marketing team can track all that activity for post-talk analysis.</p><p></p><p> If you&#39;re trying to prevent certain actions, it&#39;s important to measure those, too. One year, a company hired my team to help them deliver news of a planned reorganization, one of the most difficult presentations to deliver. Executives worried about two kinds of fallout in particular: highly valued employees leaving their jobs in frustration, and a decline in productivity. So they decided to track two data points after the announcement: the number of resignations over the next several months, and any productivity dip as reflected in customer relationship management data over the next several weeks. With those reports in, they were relieved to see that both numbers were much better than company leaders had anticipated. In this situation, measuring success meant tracking a <em>lack</em> of (that is, negative) action after delivering a sensitively crafted message.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Looming Challenge of Chemical Disclosures</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lori Bestervelt, Colleen McLoughlin, and Jillian Stacy. <p>Lori Bestervelt, Ph.D., is the former global operations lead, and Colleen McLoughlin, Ph.D., DABT, ERT, is the director of toxicology at Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry. Jillian Stacy is the business manager of Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Life Cycle]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Practices]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Sam Falconer/theispot.com New and emerging rules in the U.S. and Europe that make companies responsible for the environmental impacts of products through their entire life cycles are forcing brands to confront a striking knowledge gap: their often inadequate understanding of the chemicals found in their supply chains. The European Green Deal’s Circular Economy Action Plan, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bestervelt_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Sam Falconer/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> New and emerging rules in the US and Europe that make companies responsible for the environmental impacts of products through their entire life cycles are forcing brands to confront a striking knowledge gap: their often inadequate understanding of the chemicals found in their supply chains.</p><p> The <a href="https://environment.ec.europa.eu/strategy/circular-economy-action-plan_en">European Green Deal&#39;s Circular Economy Action Plan</a> , which was adopted in March 2020; newly proposed <a href="https://wwd.com/sustainability/business/legislation-moves-in-the-eu-new-laws-in-france-germany-and-the-netherlands-1235458823/">eco-design rules</a> affecting fashion and textiles; and the proposed <a href="https://commission.europa.eu/business-economy-euro/doing-business-eu/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence_en">Corporate Sustainability Due Diligence Directive</a> will require companies to disclose any risks to human rights and the environment. They apply throughout the product life cycle, from the formulation of ingredients and materials to product manufacturing, packaging and distribution, and recycling and disposal. In the US, four states — California, Colorado, Maine, and Oregon — have adopted <a href="https://www.packworld.com/news/sustainability/article/22419036/four-states-enact-packaging-epr-laws">extended producer responsibility laws aimed at packaging materials</a> , and the issue will be a focal point of the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#39;s eventual <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-46">Scope 3 supply chain requirements</a> . On top of such legislation, a host of new regulatory actions focused on <a href="https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billTextClient.xhtml?bill_id=202120220SB54">materials sourcing and disposal</a> , <a href="https://www.nysenate.gov/legislation/bills/2021/S8922">safety in global supply chains</a> , and the protection of employee safety and human rights are rolling out in jurisdictions around the world.</p><p></p><p> These rules pose a challenge for many of the brands that manufacture, market, and sell the clothes we wear, the cosmetics we apply, and the toys our kids play with, because their companies have very little visibility into the detailed chemical composition of their products 。</p><p> In the face of regulatory developments, fashion brands have had to reconsider their use of materials, dyes, and a host of chemicals that have been linked to deforestation and pollution. They also need to be able to trace these compounds through every link in the supply chain.</p><p> Tracing the chemical composition of a piece of clothing is no easy task, given that the many dozens of substances and materials that go into a single garment are sourced from various suppliers and are incorporated into the product at different stages. A basic clothing item like a pair of jeans will be made up of fabric combinations, dyes, softeners, fading enzymes, biocides, and preservatives from dozens of different suppliers in different formulations that need to be applied using different techniques. All of these elements can create environmental hazards at various points in the supply chain and the full product life cycle.</p><p></p><h3> Beyond Safety Data Sheets</h3><p> Marquee brands that sell consumer products face the greatest pressure from regulators to clean up their supply chains. While many have made <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/companies-rush-to-trace-sprawling-supply-chains-as-sustainability-rules-loom-11674512050">public commitments</a> to improve their sustainability, gaining needed cooperation from suppliers and partners has been a challenge. Most brands have relied on safety data sheets (SDSs) provided by their suppliers for information on product chemical composition. However, these documents are designed primarily to disclose information on chemicals and chemical compounds that could harm workers or others in the supply chain. They don&#39;t provide detailed information on the chemical composition of every material used in a product or offer any meaningful insight into its impact on recycling and disposal.</p><p> In our work conducting chemical hazard assessments and product toxicology analyses for some of the world&#39;s largest brands, approximately one-third of the SDSs we reviewed contained incomplete or inaccurate information on the chemical makeup of the products and materials they covered. Whether that is a result of suppliers intentionally omitting information or a reflection of the limitations of the SDS as a disclosure tool, the end result is that the brands responsible for these products are often in the dark about what&#39;s inside them.</p><p> Filling in the gap between the basic information provided in SDSs and the detailed disclosures that will soon be required by global authorities has become a source of conflict and confusion for many brands. Some suppliers are reluctant to share detailed chemical formulations to protect trade secrets, and many brands have been unwilling (or unable) to invest in costly chemistry assessments.</p><p></p><p> We expect that this problem will be addressed in two ways. First, the market will likely shift to suppliers that can attest to the safety of their products and processes. We&#39;ve already begun to see this in the fashion industry: Brands like Gucci, H&amp;M, Stella McCartney, and Zara recently committed to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fashion-giants-vow-to-buy-more-recycled-fibers-in-boost-to-sustainable-textile-mills-11668451031">buying more recycled materials</a> from sustainable textile mills. Second, companies will have to invest in detailed chemical screening to provide more comprehensive hazard assessments and full formulation disclosures. This approach has also been gaining in popularity as brands seek certainty and an objective means of evaluating their suppliers.</p><p> In both cases, the key objective for the big brands at the center of this shift to sustainability will be transparency. Brands need to start having candid conversations with suppliers about what exactly is in their products and what&#39;s expected in terms of regular reporting and disclosures. They might need to staff up in order to have sufficient resources to engage with suppliers, especially in seeking to extend working relationships beyond the first tier. Brands might also have to coordinate requests for information across multiple parts of the organization to get buy-in. Engaging the full supply chain can be tedious and hard work.</p><p></p><p> And these are not always easy conversations. The most common communication roadblocks we see here are confidentiality concerns, suppliers saying they are just too busy to deal with a litany of chemical composition questions from customers, and misunderstandings over what&#39;s being asked and why. Brands don&#39;t necessarily know what to ask for from their suppliers. They also don&#39;t know how to assess the impact of chemicals when they do get the information. Brands might also have to manage multiple internal chemical inventory systems and harmonize data from suppliers across different platforms.</p><p> To get to a place where all parties are on the same page, brands need to standardize a process for determining what questions to ask, whom to ask, and how to manage the information gathered. Brands also need to explain to suppliers why this information is important to the business and how they will use it, to allay privacy concerns.</p><h3> Evaluating Chemical Risk by the Numbers</h3><p> As we&#39;ve noted, we expect more brands to produce their own hard evidence of the chemical composition of their products when they are unable to get reliable information from their supply chain partners.</p><p> The only way to deliver objective certainty on the chemical risk of products is by performing chemical hazard assessments, which identify the specific chemical components used in the production of a product and screen them against comprehensive lists of known toxins to provide a hazard score. They are not cheap, though. Companies can expect to spend anywhere from $3,000 to $10,000 per substance for each assessment; the cost is at the higher end of that range for substances on which there is a great deal of scientific literature that must be carefully reviewed. Because even the most basic apparel, cosmetics, toys, and consumer products contain dozens of individual chemicals, the costs can mount quickly.</p><p> Add to those costs the challenges of retooling and replacing toxic substances in the production process once they&#39;re found, and it starts to become clear how looming deadlines like the European Green Deal&#39;s Net Zero by 2050 target are much closer than they appear.</p><p></p><p> The critical first step in the process of removing toxic substances from a supply chain is systematically identifying them. For example, we recently worked on a project with a global footwear brand that had a companywide mission to make its rubber supply chain more environmentally sustainable. It began by building a comprehensive database of its current chemical inventory and checking all entries against a list of known toxins and regulated chemicals in each jurisdiction in which it operates. Only then could it start the process of transitioning to safer chemicals.</p><p> As they make progress, brands need to build this institutional knowledge into their sourcing and product development processes to mitigate or eliminate the harmful chemical impacts of future products throughout their life cycles.</p><p> In the long run, these initiatives will result in safer, more sustainable consumer products. In the near term, however, expect to see a great deal of disruption and reshuffling of supply chains as more brands start to recognize that the tried-and-true methods of manufacturing and distribution are no longer sufficient in today&#39;s sustainability-oriented economy.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>