<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 24 日星期二 18:11:08 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>企业中的创业型人工智能：LG Nova 的 Shilpa Prasad</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[A former startup employee herself, Shilpa Prasad knows the level of commitment and effort required to begin a new venture. That’s what led her to join LG Nova, electronics manufacturer LG’s innovation incubator, as an entrepreneur in residence. In her role, Shilpa identifies promising startups — particularly those working with AI — and coaches and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>希尔帕·普拉萨德 (Shilpa Prasad) 本人曾是一家初创公司的员工，她知道创办一家新企业所需的承诺和努力程度。这促使她作为入驻企业家加入电子产品制造商 LG 的创新孵化器 LG Nova。 Shilpa 在她的角色中发现了有前途的初创公司——尤其是那些与人工智能相关的初创公司——并指导和培养企业家，同时密切关注有一天可能会进入 LG 生态系统的产品。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客中，Shilpa 解释了如何把握初创企业的脉搏帮助 LG 电子对创新和新商机保持开放态度。她还讨论了为什么人工智能是她与初创公司合作的最前沿，以及她认为使用增强现实和人工智能技术来改变技能培训提供方式的光明前景。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MMAI-S8-E2-Shilpa-Prasad-LG-Nova-headshot-3000-1x-scaled.jpg" alt="希尔帕·普拉萨德"></p><h4>希尔帕·普拉萨德，LG Nova</h4><p> Shilpa Prasad 是创业生态系统中经验丰富的领导者，对创业和企业创业参与/创新充满热情。她将超过 15 年的企业创业战略和风险投资全球经验带入 LG Nova 担任常驻企业家，帮助公司识别市场趋势并建立合作伙伴关系。</p><p>普拉萨德在推动企业、政府和加速器之间的各种开放式创新项目的创新以及在全球创业生态系统中建立新的合作伙伴关系方面发挥了重要作用。作为一位经验丰富的创始人，她还投入时间为初创企业提供指导和建议。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>常驻企业家如何在大型现有组织中启动基于人工智能的新业务？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我是 LG Nova 的 Shilpa Prasad，你们正在听<cite>我、我自己和 AI 的</cite>声音。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p>大家好。今天，Sam 和我很高兴能与 LG Nova 驻场企业家 Shilpa Prasad 一起加入。嗨，希尔帕。欢迎来到节目。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>谢谢你，谢尔文。很高兴来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>请介绍一下 LG Nova 以及您在那里的角色。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我经常被问到这个问题。 LG Nova 是 LG 电子的创新中心，总部位于硅谷。我们的任务非常简单：我们的任务是为 LG 电子寻找新的商机，而这些商机并非其主要业务的核心。 LG电子是一家传统的消费电子制造商，希望进军解决方案驱动的业务。因此，[它]不断地识别他们可能感兴趣的新技术和领域，并希望以此为基础开展价值数十亿美元的业务。</p><p> LG Nova 就是这样。我在 LG Nova 的角色是常驻企业家，这意味着我身兼数职，其中之一是公司的普通顾问。我所说的顾问并不是传统的咨询，而是更多的背景，比如需要关注哪些趋势、哪些新技术领域可能会很有趣、[以及]我们如何能够结合多种技术，也许，为了一个商业机会？这是其中的一部分。</p><p>它的第二部分非常关注由外而内的创新。我们的根基是这样一个事实：我们不想做别人已经做过的事情，而初创公司就是他们创新速度的一个很好的例子。我们希望将这种创新带入我们所在的企业，并利用其中的一些能力来共同规划一条道路。</p><p>因此，与初创公司的合作是关键，这就是我作为企业家的一面发挥作用的地方——你必须能够理解企业家的心态、他们运作的速度、他们的动力、是什么让他们做事他们所做的事情——并以有效的方式将其传达给公司。当然，还有相反的角色，企业家在公司之外不一定了解大公司的运作方式，我认为如何弥合这一差距对于这个角色非常关键。这听起来很简单，但从这个意义上讲，有很多问题悬而未决，您必须能够同时兼顾所有这些问题，同时密切关注建立新业务的目标。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您谈论的是一家大型、全球性、价值数十亿美元的公司，该公司以给定的速度运营，并且您还希望该集团以更快的速度（我认为是创业速度）运营。所以我可以想象为什么它要玩很多球。</p><p>我想问你，是对这些技术或创新机会/颠覆者的识别，还是对这些技术或创新机会/颠覆者的补充——孵化和建设？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。因此，既有构思部分，也有风险建设部分，而风险建设的一部分就是孵化。因此，您可能有六个月的时间来识别机会，朝着某些目标迈进，然后在必要时向高级利益相关者和投资者展示产品方面和业务方面的能力，然后将其推动到新业务。所以这绝对是我在那里所做的一个重要部分。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>也许这就是 Shervin 和我经常听到的说法，但是初创公司中有很多人工智能，而你还没有提到人工智能。那么人工智能如何与你的角色交叉呢？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>人工智能并不交叉。这是我正在做的事情的最前沿。如果你还记得一年半前，萨姆，关于虚拟宇宙的大肆宣传，技术来来去去。我的重点是确定可以使用其中一些技术来解决的现实世界问题。所以AI绝对是走在最前沿的。企业内部有很多与人工智能相关的工作，重点是为现有业务部门提供服务，但这不是我要做的事情。我的职责是将人工智能视为一种技术，并确定在这个巨大的世界中可能有兴趣解决的问题，并围绕它建立业务。</p><p>我无法详细说明我正在构建的内容，但我可以谈论这样一个事实：我个人在内部绘制了增强现实和人工智能的交叉点，这可能会改变技能培训的方式转移、技能提升、再技能以及围绕这些的内容将会发挥作用。</p><p>我相信你已经知道这一点——现在有了人工智能的混合，很多事情都可以变得如此直观，可以为受训者和审阅者生成一个反馈循环，并且基本上允许劳动力发展或技能培训特别是要以更快的速度前进。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>看来人工智能将更多地成为其中的关键成分，而不仅仅是添加剂，因此让人类参与其中将更加关键。我听到你所谈论的主题集中于此。请告诉我们一些有关正在发生的人工智能的信息。你说你不能说太多，但我还是想从你嘴里套出一些信息。因此，谈谈这个创新中心内发生的人工智能，或者将其与企业中发生的人工智能进行对比。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我相信你们俩都非常熟悉一家大型企业以及将任何产品推向市场所必须通过的渠道。我所说的“将任何东西推向市场”的意思也是指发布对企业内部影响更大的东西，对吧？因此，当你观察企业内部围绕人工智能进行的传统研究时，尤其是 LG 电子，到目前为止，我的理解是，冒险的兴趣是有限的，因为它扰乱了他们现有的许多工作，[而] 我正在规划的类似的东西是利用现有的一些技术，当我们向市场推出类似的东西时，现有的部分都不会受到影响 - 事实上，它们会受益。</p><p>以 LG 为例，全球有 85,000 多名工人在工厂环境中工作。今天每个人都明白，从一线工人的角度来看，工厂中的劳动力存在缺口。企业内部不断提出与生产力相关的要求，以确保满足整个……产能。这些都是企业内部人工智能研究尚未解决的现实问题。</p><p>您询问了上市时间。我的任务是在六个月内确定一家企业是否可以上市。我认为在企业方面，即使不是更长，也需要几年，对吧？两到五年之间的任何时间。</p><p>这一直是人们谈论的话题：“企业发展缓慢；启动速度很快。”所以我本质上是在公司内部建立一家初创公司。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以，我所听到的是，摆脱了许多传统规模的束缚——随之而来的是惯性——并且像新企业一样，速度要快得多。当然，其中一些创新可以帮助一些现有的企业人工智能，对吧？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。绝对地。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>太棒了。您谈到了技能提升、再培训，以及可能重新想象人类在与人工智能的整个组合中的角色——在您谈到的组合中。请告诉我们有关生成式人工智能的信息以及您认为它在其中发挥的作用。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为可能性是巨大的，就像人工智能领域的任何其他机会一样。例如，增强现实技术与人工智能交叉的一个方面意味着我们不仅关注人工智能方面的语音和文本，而且还关注正在捕获和处理的计算机视觉相关数据流，以便进行技能转移尽可能有效地发生。</p><p>因此，考虑一下护士培训环境。我们不是在真正的病人身上练习，而是在假人身上练习。如果您必须教见习护士如何将患者放在床上以执行特定的程序，那么从首席培训护士那里捕获数据流以了解如何做到这一点具有很大的价值，并且，当你真正练习的时候，得到实时反馈，对吧？</p><p>所以我们在这里研究多个数据流。因此，不仅仅是 NLP [自然语言处理]，我们还会研究基于计算机视觉的技术，并引入人工智能来几乎增强该过程以及双方的受训者和培训经验，对吗？这就是我们如何以不同方式做事的一个例子。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通常情况下，我对我们谈论的人工智能的应用感到非常兴奋，但我在这里受到了一点威胁。我的意思是我是这里的一名教育家，我听到你谈论各种不同的重新技能和再培训方式。我要去哪？您之前提到过护士的一个模型，经验丰富的护士会教经验不足的护士。也许其中很多都被替换了。在这种新模式中，经验丰富的护士现在扮演什么角色？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。好吧，实际上，山姆，我认为你的恐惧可能在这里是错误的，让我解释一下。我们并不是想更换教练。我们正在做的实际上是让培训师有更多机会去做他们应该做的事情。因此，在护士培训的例子中，护士长必须实际上站在实习护士旁边，可能在一天中多次，并教他们如何完成特定的任务。现在想象一个场景，在首席培训师真正参与进来并了解发生了什么之前，我们已经消除了至少两个级别的反馈、审查和评估。</p><p>所以我认为认证还是非常非常重要的，对吧？无论是制造业，还是医疗保健——我们正在谈论的两个例子——认证仍然很重要，而该认证来自培训师，他是专家。所以我们不会删除专家。它实际上使专家能够有效地进行培训，而不必监视正在工作的实习护士的 100 个屏幕。所以你希望看到差异。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。萨姆是一位终身教授，所以我认为他不会去任何地方。但是，山姆，这有点像正教授，即你自己，不会陷入研究生可以处理的事情中，而你只做困难的事情和那些真正考验你大脑的事情。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这对我来说听起来很光荣。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为这是一名助理，对吗？你会有一个人工智能助手，它实际上可以完成很多繁重的工作，否则你必须坐下来做。所以我认为它是有价值的。至少我们看到了我们能够在早期的对话中产生的一些有价值的推论。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>太棒了。 Shilpa，请告诉我们一些您的背景，以及您如何最终担任这个角色。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我的职业生涯是一条曲折线，Shervin；这与我今天所做的事情并不是一条直线。多年来，我认为从头开始创造一些东西总是能找到很多价值和乐趣。从无到有、创造出新东西所需的能量、动力和严谨性一直是我所做的一切的核心。</p><p>因此，在我职业生涯的早期，我有机会与某人合作创办一家平面设计工作室。在那里，我了解了实际创建企业所需的机制。它教会了我很多其中的内容。</p><p>从那时起，我一直让自己担任实际上具有创业性质或为创业生态系统服务的角色。我想提一下我第一次来硅谷时曾在这里工作过的一家名为 YouNoodle Inc. 的公司。在那里，我了解到选择合适的初创公司或创新公司进行合作以推动创新向前发展的力量，无论是在企业、政府、大学甚至大型加速器项目的背景下。</p><p>这让我在新冠疫情期间再次踏上自己的创业之旅。真的很难。我创办了一家名为 LongPlay 的初创公司，并组建了一个大约 10 人的团队。它的重点是改变企业创新的方式。我认为有一件事是，当你在公司之外时，你根本没有办法理解正在发生的所有不同的活动部分。因此，我们无法证明产品与市场的契合度，而这正是 Nova 发挥作用的地方。我再次有机会尝试在一个与我习惯的有点不同的行业和环境中进行产品市场适应，但我认为具体细节是相同的。这只是我的简单背景介绍。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这非常令人兴奋——非常跨学科。这让我想到了下一个问题：人工智能没有一刀切，当然它是一个由工程师、软件工程师、提示工程师、人工智能工程师和数据科学家等组成的完整生态系统。但是我注意到过去的技能逐渐演变，我想说，10年、12年、15年左右，从仅限于核心技术到更加多学科，并且“多学科”可以是多种形式的区域。它可以是社会科学，也可以是人机交互，也可以是哲学或其他领域。但您是否也有同样的看法？您对人工智能领域未来人才有何看法？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>这是一个有趣的问题。我不得不说我没有看到同样的事情。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>好的。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我看到的不是宽度，而是深度。我认为，在跨学科能力方面，劳动力仍然存在巨大差距。就您而言，有很多深入的技术工作正在发生，特别是围绕人工智能。</p><p>我认为，在接下来的几年里，许多像我这样负责这项技术如何发展的人将不得不随身携带。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这也涉及到测量。我的意思是——谢尔文，我知道这<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">对你来说是一个热门话题</a>——但是当你谈论影响力时，你必须弄清楚如何衡量它。必须采取某种措施来衡量“这有效吗？这不行吗？”这些看起来像是一些难题，特别是考虑到技术的新颖性和你所谈论的时间表的新鲜度。似乎很难弄清楚这对你的角色是否有效。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。我的意思是，我可以给出一点个人看法。我的构建项目风格总是提到尽可能多地与有问题的客户一起进行测试。</p><p>这就是产品焦点对我来说非常重要和中心的地方，这就是为什么风险投资令人兴奋。当我们谈论衡量时，肯定有不同的方法可以衡量我们正在创造的东西或我们试图创造的东西的影响。这里有一个市场验证方面，对吗？肯定有一个投资者验证方面，这意味着我们的投资者......这不仅仅是关于我的项目，对吧？这不仅仅是关于我正在创建或构建的项目。实际上更多的是钱的去向。当然，其中有一点是炒作，但也有一点是抓住了下一件可能改变人工智能在日常环境或环境中使用方式的机会。 。</p><p>我认为这里的第三部分也是关于最终为用户提供我们正在创建的任何解决方案和我们正在构建的任何解决方案的授权，以便获得商业机会......最终[它]必须为人类增加价值 - 也就是说，你和我，实际上将使用这项技术来改善我们的生活。今天，我们正在以与我们被教导的或我们习惯的或我们已经学会的方式完全相同的方式做工作，我们将不得不改变它或适应它并转向一种新的方式做事。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>人工智能是否能让您获得更好的数据和信息？人工智能是否能让你了解 20 年前可能需要更长时间才能了解的事情？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>当然，但我认为“人工智能能够帮助我吗？我认为，只有<em>它</em>才能做到这一点，这可能对人工智能有很大的影响，而与过去 10、15 年在特定行业所做的事情不太相关。我认为人工智能也有它的另一面，那就是，有时它把太多的东西摆在你面前，然后你必须真正浏览顶层才能真正弄清楚这些数据可以在哪里使用以及如何使用这些数据被应用。所以人工智能也有优点和缺点。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你提到了缺点。您从与您合作的这些初创公司中看到了哪些缺点？这里的人们在挣扎什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为尤其是初创公司仍在寻找可以应用他们所开发的内容的方法。人工智能的有效应用方式仍有待确定。因此，初创公司正在创建所有这些与项目相关的 LLM（大型语言模型），但他们不知道它将<em>如何</em>实际翻译。</p><p>所以我想说，初创公司要想理解它，还有一段路要走。例如，就我今天所担任的角色而言，我还使初创公司能够了解他们如何使用他们创建的技术并将其转化为有意义的问题，但是……这就是为什么我说之前咨询。它还为初创公司提供咨询：为他们提供一些真实的场景，您可以应用我们共同构建的东西，然后看看它如何转化为价值。所以我认为初创公司肯定仍在学习，萨姆。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以这些事情实际上可能与谢尔文关于知识广度和多学科的评论有关，因为你没有具体提到他们正在与技术作斗争。我在那里听到了很多并不是特别以技术为导向的事情。</p><p>让我们在这里过渡一下。我们在本集结束时做的一件事是问您五个问题。我们要尽快询问他们。我们只想了解您对他们的第一反应。您认为目前人工智能最大的机会是什么？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>医疗保健。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>好的。人们对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>它将取代它们。它将取代我们作为人类。我想这不会发生。我们离这个还有很长的路要走。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>很远。好的。你想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>成为一名企业家。我认为它一直存在于我的 DNA 中。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>很好。你小时候有过柠檬水摊吗？</p><p>什么时候人工智能太多了？我们要在哪里将方钉插入圆孔？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong> Sam，我想我没有给你一个具体的答案。所以，如果你要换一个问题……</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这样问：会不会太多？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你能在产品中投入太多人工智能吗？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的，绝对如此。我认为我想到的一个领域是协作机器人——协作机器人。它可能有效，也可能无效，而且它很大程度上是由人工智能驱动的。因此，自动化是关键，但我认为其中有多少相关性对我个人来说是值得怀疑的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果你在幻想的话，你希望人工智能现在能做但目前还不能做的一件事是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>让我听起来尽可能好。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Shilpa，非常感谢你。这很有启发性，也很精彩。感谢您参加节目。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>谢谢。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您今天的收听。在我们的下一集中，我们将听到哈佛商学院教授 Ayelet Israel 如何建议通过生成人工智能来增强企业市场研究。请加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>摩擦可以改善客户体验吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli. <p>Marco Bertini 是巴塞罗那 Esade 和 Ramon Llull 大学的营销学教授，也是 Globalpraxis 的高级顾问。迭戈·阿帕里西奥 (Diego Aparicio) 是巴塞罗那 IESE 商学院营销学助理教授。艾林·艾丁利 (Aylin Aydinli) 是阿姆斯特丹自由大学市场营销学副教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Journey]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bertini_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">奥托·德特默/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>公司的使命是设计尽可能没有挫折和不便的购买旅程。 “摩擦会破坏客户体验！”已成为常识。人们认为，在为在线购物者提供服务时尤其如此，众所周知，在线购物者缺乏耐心且注意力集中时间较短。毕竟，只需点击几下鼠标即可到达竞争对手的网站。</p><p>我们认识的大多数企业领导者在显示价格和收款时都会优先考虑消除“关键时刻”的摩擦，因为除了想让热切的客户生活更轻松之外，他们还担心让客户有理由停下来重新考虑他们的决定。但正如我们将要证明的那样，正是在资金紧张的情况下，让客户有时间考虑他们的购买决定，才能为公司带来长期利益和成本节约。</p><p></p><h3>摩擦与善变的在线购物者</h3><p>很容易理解为什么让购物尽可能无缝对电子商务公司来说如此紧迫，因为过去 12 个月的全球平均购物车放弃率总体高达 71.7%（使用台式机或笔记本电脑的人为 60.7%）。使用平板电脑的比例为 65.1%，使用手机的比例为 77.4%。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>最后一个数字可能是最令人不安的，因为美国的移动购物在三年内增长了 2,000 亿美元以上，到 2022 年将达到 4,310 亿美元。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>根据 Baymard Institute 的数据，大型电子商务网站平均可以提高转化率通过简化结账流程，成本降低了 35%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>毫不奇怪，亚马逊和阿里巴巴等电子商务巨头正在大力投资，通过使价格和支付几乎不可见来快速引导消费者度过关键时刻。亚马逊早在 1999 年就率先推出了一键式购物。如今，人们的注意力集中在其 Just Walk Out 技术上，该技术融合了计算机视觉、重量传感器和深度学习，为实体店带来了在线购物的一些便利：顾客可以利用信用进入零售店时使用卡打开虚拟购物车，从货架上选择商品，然后离开，无需在收银台停留。在阿里巴巴，数字支付和自助结账台已成为其 300 家盒马超市的常态。人们甚至可以利用其支付宝子公司的面部识别技术来“刷脸支付”。</p><p>资源较少的公司正在对其采购流程进行改变，这些改变更加渐进但同样重要。例如，考虑一下最近流行的“立即购买，稍后付款”分期付款融资或基于订阅的服务的自动续订条款，这些条款允许公司避免客户重新考虑是否仍然需要该服务的年度清算。在线企业已经抓住了这些和其他机会，通过让客户不去思考花钱的问题，从而减轻花钱的痛苦。</p><p>然而，将摩擦视为具有严格的负面影响（例如惹恼客户或抑制销售）的想法过于简单化。诚然，购买过程中阻力太大很容易抑制购买欲望，但阻力太小会降低决策效率，导致错失与客户更好联系的机会。那么，我们建议企业领导者问问自己，他们是否真的希望客户自动购买。</p><p>在本文中，我们解释了购买过程中的一些摩擦如何帮助公司吸引客户，并就如何利用这些影响建立更牢固的客户关系提供指导。</p><h3>一分耕耘一分收获</h3><p>购买过程中的一些摩擦可以保护消费者免受欺诈、隐私侵犯或他们自己的意外行为。例如，要求两步验证和要求客户确认他们想要完成购买是两个常识性的不便，但最终确保客户免受威胁和错误。</p><p>但围绕购买决策的摩擦过多或过少都会产生负面影响。购买过程中的步骤过多可能会分散购物者的注意力，使他们没有足够的认知能力来仔细考虑自己的决定。这会提高购物车放弃率，并消除客户通过评论、推荐、推荐或其他互动与公司互动的机会。摩擦太少，人们就不会充分考虑自己的决定，从而屈服于人类节省脑力劳动的倾向。这种没有摩擦的情况令人麻木，购物者与购买的联系越少，他们就会变得越矛盾。从长远来看，缺乏承诺反过来会导致产品退货、削弱品牌并降低满意度。</p><p>然而，具有足够挑战性的购买过程却很有吸引力。由于交易既不紧张也不简单，因此人们有动力在这项任务上投入脑力。换句话说，适量的摩擦可以促使客户完善和巩固他们的偏好，并可以为公司带来三个好处。</p><p></p><p> <strong>1.摩擦力帮助卖家选择合适的客户。</strong> Companies that prioritize the long-term profitability of their customer bases over the immediate gain from making a sale must take a holistic and equally long-term perspective on developing relationships with their target audiences. This involves investing in acquisition, retention, and growth. With that idea in mind, the question is whether hurdles that increase the psychological pain of considering an expense will disproportionately deter would-be customers who are more costly to acquire, less likely to purchase again on future occasions, or less likely to increase their spending on the brand over time or recommend the brand. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Friction to weed out the wrong customers or select the right ones is a familiar technique in luxury goods markets and in any context where a company wants prospective customers to demonstrate commitment. Ferrari, for example, is known for making it difficult to buy special-edition cars. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Similarly, luxury fashion brands don&#39;t mind fostering queues, whether virtual or real, or complicating the purchase process by temporarily withholding prices, lengthening the checkout process, or using other approaches. The simple logic behind these tactics is that only the customers who are most interested in the company&#39;s products or most invested in the brand will find working through these inconveniences and complications acceptable in the shopping journey.</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. When friction enables better decisions, customer satisfaction improves.</strong> Using friction to give consumers a moment to pause and consider the implications of their purchases can forestall buyer&#39;s remorse and encourage shoppers to choose the most appropriate option among the available alternatives.</p><p> Making the trade-off between what the potential buyer will pay and what they will receive sufficiently obvious can help prevent mindless purchasing decisions made in the heat of the moment. For example, social media may pitch “buy now, pay later” financing as a savvy way to buy on a budget, but the ease and convenience of such services, now available in many e-commerce sites&#39; checkout processes, can encourage households to overspend, leading to financial strain and debt accumulation. One survey found that 42% of Americans who took out such a loan made at least one late payment on it. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In addition, research shows that payments made either long before or long after the natural moment of consumption can reduce people&#39;s attention to cost. Proponents of buy now, pay later assert that this “separates the fun experience of buying from the tedious process of paying,” when in fact such “transaction decoupling” has been shown to reduce the likelihood that the consumer will use the item purchased. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> The advantage of avoiding bad decisions is relatively clear from a public policy perspective: Most people would agree that overspending and chronic underutilization of purchased goods are not desirable qualities in a society. But encouraging more thoughtful engagement by customers via friction in the purchase process can pay off for businesses, too.</p><p> One immediate benefit is a drop in return rates. In many sectors, online returns are a considerable drag on financial performance — adding up to as much as 15 to 30 cents per dollar of the price of returned merchandise. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> According to a study by Appriss Retail and the National Retail Federation, close to $220 billion worth of merchandise was returned to US digital retailers in 2021, or approximately 21% of total online sales. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> And this drag, of course, is not just financial — it&#39;s also environmental. Returned products might not be resalable due to wear and tear or other issues and thus end up being sent to landfills or destroyed. According to one report, online returns in the US alone create 5 billion pounds of landfill waste and 15 million tons of carbon emissions annually. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Adding friction also provides customers with time to consider the purchase and become more invested in it. Brands such as Chanel, Louis Vuitton, and Balenciaga delay the communication of prices in a variety of ways — for example, by introducing personalized experiences with salespeople — not only to select better customers, as discussed above, but to put the product center stage and help customers internalize its quality and meaning. Research at the intersection of marketing and neuroscience reports that revealing prices after product information focuses evaluations on attractiveness and desirability (people ask themselves, “Do I like this?”), while doing the opposite focuses evaluations on monetary worth (people ask themselves, “Is it worth it?”). <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> In a Gartner study, B2B and B2C customers agreed that if they “realized something new about their needs or their own goals,” they were 1.73 times more likely to buy more. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p> Using friction to stimulate thinking that results in a decision to purchase can foster a sense of ownership of the product. This can trigger a stronger bond between company and customers and increase customers&#39; willingness to invest additional resources in the relationship. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> As customers put more thought into the purchase decision, they tend to feel more emotionally attached to the product they ultimately choose. And there&#39;s evidence that connecting with customers at the emotional level is a valid route to maximizing customer value. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Finally, research also shows that people tend to value products more when they are obtained through effort — the aptly named “Ikea effect,” in reference to the retailer&#39;s policy of outsourcing the assembly of its furniture to customers. <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> The experience of effort can influence how people perceive the value and quality of a product or service, and adding effort to the online purchase process can trigger this effect.</p><p></p><p> Overall, we see that friction is successful at triggering engagement, and we know that engaged customers are generally more satisfied with their interactions and experiences with brands and retailers. Engaged customers become advocates, increasing visibility and credibility for companies. They are likely to engage in positive word of mouth, which can lead to new-customer acquisition and elevated brand reputation. They are also likely to have better customer service experiences, feel valued by the company, and provide meaningful feedback and suggestions. Such feedback is valuable for understanding evolving customer needs and making the right improvements to products or services over time.</p><p> <strong>3. Friction creates space for companies to communicate with customers.</strong> Retaining some friction exactly when people face prices and payment, especially when this friction is unexpected, gains attention. This is an opportunity for companies to advertise what they stand for and the merits of their offerings.</p><p> There are several ways to use friction for promotion. First, companies can involve customers in the payment process to evoke positive emotions. For example, one common practice is to give customers the option to round up the transaction amount to the next highest dollar, with the difference being donated to charity. Another possibility is to introduce pay-what-you-want campaigns, where customers choose the price they will pay for the product. While these initiatives do not expedite payment (it is surprisingly effortful to consider how much one wants to pay for something), they can lead to greater emotional connections.</p><p> Companies can also express prices in ways that are intentionally unconventional to force customers to think harder about the underlying message. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> For instance, an advertisement from Ikea uses cans of soda to playfully quantify the prices of its products. Of course, the retailer won&#39;t accept soda as payment for furniture. And although it takes a moment of cognitive effort to understand the “exchange rate,” the message that the furniture is as affordable as a number of small-ticket purchases, such as soda, is conveyed to customers.</p><p> Another example is Stella Artois&#39;s award-winning “reassuringly expensive” campaign. The brand attempted to signal the high quality of its beer by introducing the dependency between price and quality into its price communication. Stella upended consumer expectations by playfully offering a coupon that increased the price of the product (“Bring this coupon and pay an extra $1.25 on your next Stella Artois”). By presenting a seemingly confusing and illogical “deal,” it nudged customers to conclude that the product is far superior to that of its competitors (and worth the cost).</p><p> Friction in the payment process can also be used to communicate the brand&#39;s values. For example, in 2014, the relief organization Misereor increased donation rates by deploying interactive screens in locations such as airports that asked passersby to donate 2 euros by swiping their credit cards over the screen. The swipe activated an engaging interactive sequence, such as depicting the credit card slicing a piece of bread to feed the hungry or freeing an imprisoned child.</p><p> Finally, in a bold example of extreme friction, outdoor retailer REI closed its physical stores and stopped processing online payments on Black Friday, the biggest shopping day of the year in the US Its goal was to take a stand against consumerism and encourage would-be shoppers to spend time outdoors instead — a message that underscores the company&#39;s dedication to accessible exploration. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a></p><h3> The Friction Sweet Spot</h3><p> Better customer selection, consumer decisions, and promotion are three good reasons to abandon the simplistic goal of zero friction. Given the drawbacks of encouraging customers to purchase on autopilot, business leaders should seek to determine the right degree of friction for their companies&#39; purchase processes. In our experience, there are at least five factors to consider. We&#39;ll review them and introduce a scorecard that brings them together and helps to guide decision-making. (See “What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> What&#39;s the Right Amount of Friction for Your Online Customer Experience?</h4><p class="caption"> Use this scorecard to help you determine the optimal amount of friction to help you<br /> cultivate enduring customer relationships.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> The first step for every company is to adopt a more accurate definition of what friction is. At the moment, all friction is viewed negatively, which reduces organizations&#39; sense of needing to specify what it actually is. By most accounts, friction is operationalized in terms of time saved. But not all time is created equal. In fact, companies should view negative friction as anything that blocks or distracts customers from the purchase decision, and positive friction as anything that optimizes deliberation.</p><p> The second step is to understand what contexts benefit from positive friction — because this need is not universal. What&#39;s at stake in a particular purchase decision, and does it typically require high or low customer involvement? The two often go together, such that high-stakes decisions also require high involvement, but this is not necessarily the case. For instance, a consumer who is financially secure might not engage more with a purchase decision simply because the item is expensive. And it is exactly when this relation breaks down that you want to step in to proactively manage friction. High-stakes decisions might be such because of the significance of the product or service in question, the scale of the financial outlay, or the personal or social consequences of the purchase. In this spirit, using a technology like Amazon&#39;s Just Walk Out in stadiums might not be good for people who are no longer dissuaded from buying unhealthy snacks by excessively long lines at the concession stand.</p><p> Third, think about your commercial objective. If you care about highlighting cost savings relative to competitors&#39; prices, then, yes — reducing friction by posting your almost-too-good-to-be-true price upfront is worthwhile. However, if you compete on the basis of innovation, quality, or customer service, then perhaps retaining a little friction by delaying when the price is presented is best, because this gets customers to think about and crystallize their preferences. Some friction allows businesses to shift the conversation from “Is it worth it?” to “Do I like it?” And if the goal is to strengthen one&#39;s brand, then adding friction is the right way to go.</p><p> Fourth, consider the makeup of your customer base and the relative closeness of customer relationships. Different customer demographics might require more or less friction, depending on expectations around their understanding of a product or service or their ability to pay. Likewise, relationship stage is important. You might want to include more friction in transactions with new customers versus returning customers, in particular those who might be less familiar with your products or product category. You might want to make it harder for a prospective customer to make a purchase, add a bit of friction for a returning customer, and present a frictionless experience to a loyal customer who fully understands the product or service. A company should maximize enduring relationships with clients — because that is the only path to increase customer value.</p><p> Fifth, think about your choice of route to market. All retail environments could potentially benefit from some friction, but their application will be different. In a brick-and-mortar store, adding pain points that incentivize interaction between a salesperson and the customer might be the right type of friction. In an online store, however, adding steps to foster deliberation can reduce returns and increase subsequent satisfaction with the company. On social media, a company could look to balance content that engages customer interaction and not just click-through rates, thereby helping to dissuade users from mindlessly or impulsively shopping.</p><p></p><p> In fact, for a business selling the same product in brick-and-mortar stores and online, more (positive) friction might be needed in the online or mobile channel, given that product returns tend to be greatest in those channels. One interesting technique that some fashion brands have recently introduced is imposing a fee for online returns. Companies like Anthropologie, H&amp;M, and Zara are charging for returning items online (but not for making in-store returns). <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a> Yes, charging for returns can antagonize some customers. But, again, this point can be key to retaining the most relevant customers and strengthening relationships with those who persist and make a purchase.</p><p></p><p> “How can we make our prices a little less conspicuous and easier to pay?” is among the most common questions asked of user experience teams and experts. But business leaders should embrace the customer moment of truth rather than work to eliminate it. They should not buy into the popular idea that friction is the ultimate conversion killer.</p><p> Without a doubt, when used poorly, friction can derail the customer experience. But a frictionless world is just as dangerous. This is a lesson most of us learned years ago from our high school physics teacher: Too much friction prevents progress toward a goal, but too little friction can throw everything into chaos.</p><p> Indeed, many business leaders are already telling us that they want customers to spend more productive time on their purchase decisions. This sounds like the perfect job for friction. If thinking leads shoppers to make safer, better choices, and in turn these choices impact companies through lower product returns, more sustainable consumer behavior, higher customer satisfaction, and higher loyalty, then let&#39;s all accept and embrace some hassles and hurdles as yet another — albeit surprising — tool at the disposal of customer centricity.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Is Your Organization Investing Enough in Responsible AI? &#39;Probably Not,&#39; Says Our Data</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Priorities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year’s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> For the second year in a row, <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year&#39;s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to respond to this provocation: <em>As the business community becomes more aware of AI&#39;s risks, companies are making adequate investments in RAI.</em></p><p> While their reasons vary, most panelists recognize that RAI investments are falling short of what&#39;s needed: Eleven out of 13 were reluctant to agree that organizations&#39; investments in responsible AI are “adequate.” The panelists largely affirmed findings from our <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/building-robust-rai-programs-as-third-party-ai-tools-proliferate/">2023 RAI global survey</a> , in which less than half of respondents said they believe their company is prepared to make adequate investments in RAI. This is a pressing leadership challenge for companies that are prioritizing AI and must manage AI-related risks.</p><p> The need to expand investments in RAI marks a significant shift now that “AI-related risks are impossible to ignore,” observes Linda Leopold, head of responsible AI and data at H&amp;M Group. While making adequate investments in RAI used to be an important but not particularly urgent issue, Leopold suggests that recent advances in generative AI and the proliferation of third-party tools have made the urgency of such investments clear.</p><p> Making adequate investments in RAI is complicated by measurement challenges. There are no industry standards that offer guidance, so how do you know when or if your investments are sufficient? What&#39;s more, rational executives can have different opinions about what constitutes an adequate investment. What&#39;s clear is that epistemic questions should not be a barrier to action, especially when AI risks pose real business threats.</p><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3> The Panelists Respond</p></h3><h2> It is unclear if organizations are making appropriate investments in RAI.</p></h2><p> Most panelists are reluctant to agree that organizations are making “adequate” investments in RAI.</p><p> <a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">Jump to panelists&#39; detailed responses below.</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-Chart.jpg" alt="Chart: 0 strongly agree; 15% agree, 46% neither agree nor disagree; 39% disagree; 0% strongly disagree"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source"> Source: Responsible AI panel of 13 experts in artificial intelligence strategy. </p></p></div><p><path id="Path" d="M0,0,14.067,15.065,28.941,0" transform="translate(1.096 1.054)" fill="none" stroke="#fff" stroke-miterlimit="10" stroke-width="3" /> <a href="" class="callout-chart-add__button"><span class="callout-chart-add__button-text"><strong>Show</strong> Global Survey Results</span></a> </p><div class="callout-chart-add"><div class="callout-chart-add__container"><div class="callout-chart-add__info"><h4></h4><h3> Responses from the 2023 Global Executive Survey<br /></h3><p> “To what extent do you believe that your organization is prepared to invest (reduce revenue, increase costs) to comply with responsible AI initiatives?” </p></p></div><div class="callout-chart-add__chart"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-survey.jpg" alt="Bar chart: To a moderate or great extent: 48%; To some extent: 29%; To a minor extent: 8%; Not at all: 3%; Don't know: 12%" class="mt0"></p><p class="callout-chart-add__source"> Source: Survey data of 1,240 respondents representing organizations reporting at least $100 million in annual revenues. These respondents represented companies in 59 industries and 87 countries. The survey fielded in China was localized.</p></p></div></p></div></p></div></div><h3> Companies Are Investing in RAI, but Not Enough</h3><p> Panelists offered several reasons why companies aren&#39;t making adequate investments in responsible AI. Several panelists suggested that profit motives are a factor. Tshilidzi Marwala, rector of the United Nations University and UN undersecretary general, contends that only “20% of the companies aware of AI risks are investing in RAI programs. The rest are more concerned about how they can use AI to maximize their profits.” Simon Chesterman, the David Marshall Professor and vice provost at the National University of Singapore, adds, “The gold rush around generative AI has led to a downsizing of safety and security teams in tech companies, and a shortened path to market for new products. … Fear of missing out is triumphing — in many organizations, if not all — over risk management.”</p><p> Another reason behind underinvestment is that greater use of AI throughout an enterprise expands the scope of RAI and increases required investments. As Philip Dawson, head of AI policy at Armilla AI, observes, “Investment in AI capabilities continues to vastly outstrip investment in AI safety and tools to operationalize AI risk management. Enterprises are playing catch-up in an uphill battle that is only getting steeper.” Leopold adds that generative AI and an increasing number of possible applications “significantly increases the size of the audience that responsible AI programs have to reach.”</p><p></p><p> A third reason is that growing awareness of AI risks does not always translate into accurate assessments of those risks. Oarabile Mudongo, a policy specialist at the African Observatory on Responsible AI, suggests that some companies might not be investing enough in their RAI programs because they “underestimate the extent of AI risks.”</p><h3> How Do You Know Whether You&#39;re Investing Enough?</h3><p> Other panelists pointed out that although making adequate investments in RAI is important, it&#39;s hard to gauge whether the investment is large enough or effective. How should companies calculate a return on RAI investments? What counts as an “adequate” return? What even counts as an investment? David R. Hardoon, CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation and chief data and AI officer of Union Bank of the Philippines, asks, “How can the investments in RAI be broadly, and generally, considered adequate if (1) all companies are not subjected to the same levels of standards, (2) we have yet to agree on what is &#39;sufficient&#39; or &#39;acceptable,&#39; or (3) we don&#39;t have a mechanism to verify third parties?”</p><p> Triveni Gandhi, responsible AI lead at Dataiku, agrees: “Among those companies that have taken the time to invest in RAI programs, there is wide variation in how these programs are actually designed and implemented. The lack of cohesive or clear expectations on how to implement or operationalize RAI values makes it difficult for organizations to start investing efficiently.”</p><p> “It is difficult to determine the extent to which companies are making adequate investments in responsible AI programs, as there is a large spectrum of awareness and relevance,” asserts Giuseppe Manai, cofounder, chief operating officer, and chief scientist at Stemly. Aisha Naseer, director of research at Huawei Technologies (UK), adds, “It is not evident whether these investments are adequate or enough, as these range from trivial to huge funds being allocated for the control of AI and associated risk mitigation.”</p><p></p><h3> Recommendations</h3><p> For organizations seeking to adequately invest in RAI, we recommend the following:</p><p> <strong>1. Build leadership awareness of AI risks.</strong> Leaders need to be aware that using AI is a double-edged sword that introduces risks as well as benefits. Focusing on investments that increase the benefits of AI without a commensurate focus on managing its risks undermines value creation in two ways. One is that without appropriate guardrails, the benefits from AI might be underwhelming: Our research has found that innovation with AI increases when RAI practices are in place. Second, risks from AI are proliferating as quickly as the tools they are embedded in. A robust awareness of AI&#39;s risks and benefits supports leadership efforts to manage risks and grow the company. Building management awareness can take many forms, including executive education, discussion forums, and RAI programs that have a variety of stakeholders with different types of exposure to (and experience with) AI risks.</p><p> <strong>2. Accept that investing in RAI will be an ongoing process.</strong> As AI development and use increase — with no foreseeable end — RAI practices and implementations need to adapt as well. That requires ongoing RAI investment to continually evolve an RAI program. With the regulatory landscape poised for change in the European Union, the US, and Asia, leaders will face growing pressure to evolve their AI-focused risk management systems. Waiting to invest (or halting investment) in these systems — technologically, culturally, and financially — can undermine business growth. When new regulations and industry standards take effect, rapidly overhauling processes to meet compliance requirements can interfere with AI-related innovation. It&#39;s better to co-evolve RAI programs with AI development so they complement each other rather than create this unnecessary interference. As companies scale their AI investments, so, too, will their RAI investments need to grow. But those companies that are already behind will need to move quickly and invest aggressively in RAI to avoid always lagging behind.</p><p> <strong>3. Develop RAI investment metrics.</strong> Investing in RAI is complex — and what does a return on such an investment even look like? Much like with cybersecurity investments, the best RAI returns might be the sound of silence when AI-related issues are discovered before they create damage to brand reputation, regulatory issues, and increased costs. That said, silence should not be mistaken for adequate investment. As our survey results show, companies making minimal investment might not find issues simply because they aren&#39;t looking for them. Leaders should align on what constitutes an RAI investment, the appropriate metrics to evaluate these investments, and who will decide on investment levels. Metrics that gauge RAI program success are necessary to support RAI programs over time, but they can be a lagging indicator. Metrics should also evaluate forward-looking dimensions such as leadership commitment, program adoption, training and workforce needs, and culture change. Leaders must also determine how RAI funding is related to funding for AI projects. Should every large AI project have a budget set aside for RAI? Or should RAI funding be independent of specific projects or some combination of project-based (decentralized) and institutional (centralized) investments?</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probably-not-says-our-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Real Issues Driving the Nursing Crisis</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Jack Daly</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4> The Research</h4><p> We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research on various elements of employees&#39; experiences, including culture, compensation and benefits, work schedules, and perceived organizational support. We clustered related topics together into two dozen broader themes.</p><p> We used the topics as features in an XGBoost model that predicted each nurse&#39;s overall rating of their current or former employer on a 5-point scale. We then calculated SHAP values (which assign an importance value to each feature in a model) to directly compare the relative importance of different topics in predicting job satisfaction (measured by the overall rating each nurse gave their employer). We also used textual analysis to compare how favorably travel nurses spoke about topics compared with nurses on staff at health care systems.</p><p> Using the topics nurses mentioned and their sentiment toward each topic as predictors, our models explain between 29% and 39% of the variance in ratings across nurses — nearly an order of magnitude more than we could account for using ownership, organizational type, and location as predictors. <a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">i</a></p></aside><p> Health care leaders face a daunting set of challenges — rising costs, the transition to digital health, and shifting payment models, to name just a few. But according to a recent survey from the American College of Healthcare Executives, the No. 1 problem hospital CEOs face is staff shortages and burnout. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Ninety percent of the CEOs surveyed cited nursing shortages as a particularly acute pain point.</p><p> In 2021, the total number of registered nurses working in the US dropped by the largest amount in 40 years, with younger nurses leading the exodus. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> By 2025, the US health care system could suffer a shortfall of up to 450,000 nurses, or 20% fewer than the nursing workforce required for patient care. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p> High levels of job dissatisfaction and burnout are driving nurses from the profession. The COVID-19 pandemic placed tremendous pressure on all health care workers, but dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses have not improved since the pandemic ended. And by some measures, it might be getting worse: In 2021, nearly two-thirds of registered nurses would have encouraged others to become a nurse, but only half said they would recommend nursing as a profession two years later. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> One of the richest sources of insight on dissatisfaction among nurses is how they describe their job, in their own words, on employment sites like Indeed and Glassdoor. This information is voluminous but difficult to synthesize because most of it takes the form of unstructured free text. To understand the challenges nurses face, we analyzed how 150,000 of them had described their employers in Glassdoor reviews since the beginning of the pandemic. (See “The Research.”) In this article, we share key insights from that analysis and offer advice to health care leaders about how they can address nurses&#39; most pressing issues.</p><h3> Health Care Leaders Are Out of Touch</h3><p> Nurses view their managers as out of touch with the daily realities of patient care. We categorized their comments about managers into nearly 50 leadership traits. The second most frequently cited trait described managers as being unaware of the challenges that nurses struggle with in the workplace. When nurses discussed how managers understood life at the bedside, their comments were negative 9 times out of 10.</p><p></p><p> Nurses are particularly critical of members of the senior executive team for their disconnectedness. The top team was 10 times more likely than front-line supervisors and middle managers to be criticized for being out of touch. Our results reinforce a separate survey in which nearly half of hospital nurses said they believe management does not listen to their concerns. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> To address dissatisfaction and burnout, health care leaders must first understand what&#39;s happening at the bedside. This can be challenging, particularly in large health care systems with thousands of nurses working across multiple sites and specialties.</p><p> Historically, leaders have struggled to systematically analyze the gold mine of insights into nurses&#39; frustrations that can be gleaned from their comments in employee surveys or external reviews. Reading, understanding, and analyzing huge volumes of unstructured textual data has simply not been practical. However, recent advances in artificial intelligence make it possible to identify deep patterns in large bodies of text and understand feedback at scale. Leaders can now mine free text to gain a nuanced understanding of the issues driving dissatisfaction and burnout among nurses and use that insight to improve life at work for their nursing staffs. (See “Getting Started With Text Analytics.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Getting Started With Text Analytics</h4><p> Our research analyzes data from hundreds of organizations and hundreds of thousands of nurses, but you can delve more deeply into your own employees&#39; feedback as well. Regardless of whether you develop AI text analytics capabilities internally, through a workforce analytics function, or with an external partner, you should keep these principles in mind to maximize the effectiveness of the cultural measurement.</p><p> <strong>Precision matters, but so does recall.</strong> Precision — the percentage of text instances that are correctly classified as discussing a topic — is a critical element of free text analysis. So is recall — the percentage of total mentions of the topic in a body of text that are captured by your text analytics platform. If you gauge success solely through precision, you will end up with an analytical platform that is highly accurate but misses most of what employees actually say. A sophisticated AI tool will pick up on slang, idioms, acronyms, cultural references, and organization-specific language to capture the long tail of seldom-mentioned but information-rich terms.</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p> <strong>Keep subject matter experts in the loop.</strong> The heart of text analytics is classifying natural language into meaningful topics. Ideally, the people measuring culture will engage subject matter experts when developing topics for analysis. Subject matter experts can ensure that the cultural and workplace topics selected are clearly defined, linked to existing research, and properly measured.</p><p> <strong>Likert questions have severe drawbacks but, used in moderation, can be very helpful.</strong> Too many Likert-scale questions can lead survey takers to shift into autopilot mode. But Likert questions should not be thrown out altogether. Effective cultural measurement combines Likert-scale outcomes on broad topics (such as engagement, attrition intent, and other important measures) with free-text data to identify which, out of hundreds of free-text topics, have the most powerful impact on outcomes.</p><p> <strong>Transparency matters and will probably matter more going forward.</strong> While it remains to be seen how AI will be regulated, it is likely that legislators or courts will not look kindly on important decisions being made by black-box models with no explanation of how the models are reaching their conclusions. Leaders often rely on culture measurement to make important decisions such as compensation policies, personnel changes, and how to prioritize resources. They should be wary of relying exclusively on models that make decisions that humans cannot understand.</p><p> <strong>Employees hate it when you spy on them — and you won&#39;t learn much about culture.</strong> Leaders should resist the temptation to expand their text analytics efforts to the content of emails, Slack channels, phone messages, and other forms of communication that were not designed to provide employee feedback. Many employees consider listening to their work conversations eavesdropping or worse. Moreover, work emails and Slack messages tend to contain far less cultural information than question prompts that explicitly invite employees to discuss what is working and not working in their organization. Keep employee listening consensual, and keep Big Brother out of the workplace.</p></div></article></aside></div><h3> Identify Relative Strengths and Opportunities Through Benchmarking</h3><p> Nursing satisfaction varies widely across employers. We identified 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies. For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic through June 2023. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> Among large employers, nurses&#39; Glassdoor ratings ran the gamut from poor (2.6) to nearly perfect (4.9) on a 5-point scale. Nurses&#39; assessments of how well senior leadership has performed during and after the pandemic were even more varied, ranging from 2.1 to 4.9 on the same 5-point scale. The wide variance in Glassdoor ratings is consistent with a separate survey in which the percentage of dissatisfied nurses ranged from 2% to 48% across 60 US hospitals. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Employees of the 200 large health care organizations can use our <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">interactive tool</a> to see how their organization ranks against others. The index is sortable by nurses&#39; overall ratings, their assessments of the top leadership, and the four most powerful predictors of nurses&#39; satisfaction: compensation, workload, organizational support, and toxic culture. </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4> How Do Nurses Rate Their Employers?</h4><p class="caption"> Use the Nursing Satisfaction Index to compare how nurses evaluated the employee experience at 200 large health care organizations.</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p> Nurses who work for staffing agencies (who are sometimes referred to as travel nurses) are, on average, much more satisfied than other nurses. The five highest-ranked employers in our sample (and six of the top 10) are staffing agencies.</p><p> Higher compensation, of course, accounts for part of this difference, but not all of it. We compared how positively nurses working with staffing agencies spoke about 200 topics compared with their counterparts employed by hospitals and health care systems. (See “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors.”) While compensation was viewed more favorably by agency nurses, issues around solving nurses&#39; problems and open, honest communication had a larger sentiment gap between the two groups. By focusing on nurses as clients, staffing agencies excel at practices that improve satisfaction beyond simply paying higher wages. Other health care leaders can learn from their example, and we&#39;ll make some concrete recommendations below.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors</h4><p class="caption"> We analyzed the free text of US Glassdoor reviews by nurses from the start of the pandemic to June 2023 to see how positively they spoke about a variety of topics. We then compared the positive sentiments of nurses working with staffing agencies to those of nurses working in hospitals and health care systems. While staffing agencies rate higher on many key topics — including honest communication, resolving issues efficiently, and building trust — hospitals and health care systems are stronger when it comes to learning and development, benefits, colleagues, and opportunities for promotion. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3> Prioritize Drivers of Job Satisfaction</h3><p> To understand the drivers of job satisfaction among nurses, we analyzed the free text of all reviews that had been written by the nurses in our sample since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into nearly 200 topics. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> We then clustered topics into two dozen broader themes and used those themes to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers. We then compared each theme&#39;s relative importance in predicting ratings. (See “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction.”)</p><p></p><p> Compensation was the top predictor of satisfaction among nurses reviewing their current employer, which is not surprising, given that inflation eroded the purchasing power of take-home pay during the period we analyzed. The importance of workload, the second-most-important driver, jibes with findings from a separate large-scale survey that found insufficient staffing was the strongest predictor of nurses&#39; job dissatisfaction, burnout, and intent to quit. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Workload and compensation are root causes of the nursing crisis that must be addressed, but they are not the only factors influencing nurses&#39; job satisfaction. Our analysis surfaced other aspects of the work environment, including toxic culture, organizational support, work schedules, communication, and learning and development opportunities, that leaders can focus on to improve nurses&#39; work lives.</p><p> This analysis also highlights areas that are unlikely to move the needle in improving the workplace experience for nurses. Perks are nice, but they will not compensate for a punishing workload or wages that fail to keep pace with inflation. Highlighting the corporate mission to promote patient health won&#39;t help much either. Nurses already know that their job serves a higher purpose; that&#39;s why most of them became nurses in the first place.</p><h3> Mine Free Text for Actionable Insights</h3><p> Many health care organizations rely on annual employee surveys, with dozens of items rated on a 5-point scale and a few open-ended questions tacked on as an afterthought. Faced with a long list of multiple-choice questions, employees are prone to switching to autopilot and assigning similar scores to very different items. The choice of questions constrains what employees can discuss, and there is seldom room to expand on why they chose a particular numeric response.</p><p> Open-ended, free-text feedback provides a rich source of nuanced and actionable insights. When nurses can decide which topics to write about, they use their freedom to discuss what matters most to them. Open-ended questions provide nurses with the space to expand on their concerns in their own words, offer crucial context, and propose concrete and actionable fixes to the problems they face. Individual free-text responses can be aggregated into broader themes to prioritize where leaders could focus their attention and limited resources to achieve the largest improvements in nurses&#39; satisfaction.</p><p> While organizational averages are useful, it is important to remember that distinctive subcultures can coexist within the same organization. This is particularly true among large health care systems that have grown through mergers and acquisitions. One national hospital chain, for example, has ratings that range from 1.9 to 3.9 across nearly 50 sites. Rather than relying on organizational averages alone, health care leaders must measure and analyze differences across locations, departments, functions, teams, and individual leaders.</p><p> Women, underrepresented minorities, and older employees can also experience organizational culture very differently from other employees. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> It&#39;s crucial to understand the drivers of job satisfaction and burnout across diverse employee populations.</p><p></p><p> Leaders can mine the free text for detailed insights about the most critical pain points for specific groups and tailor their interventions accordingly. Schedules, for example, have a significant impact on nurses&#39; job satisfaction, but which aspects of scheduling matter most will depend on the specific position. Flexibility in scheduling shifts and the ability to take uninterrupted work breaks is very important for nurses in hospitals and primary care practices, while home health care nurses place a premium on predictable schedules. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Nurses&#39; comments provide a treasure trove of practical suggestions to improve the workplace and patient care. The Glassdoor reviews we studied, for example, include dozens of actionable suggestions for how employers can improve scheduling. Some are easy-to-implement actions, such as using an app to make it easier to pick up or swap shifts, or paying a $20 to $50 bonus to nurses who pick up shifts at the last minute. Others are more systemic changes, like including nurses on a committee established to set schedules or ensuring that employees who receive tuition assistance are able to schedule work around their classes.</p><h3> Listen to Nurses Who Leave Your Organization</h3><p> Most organizations limit their surveys to current employees. Exit interviews are administered haphazardly, if at all, and the feedback from former employees is too often dismissed as the rantings of malcontents. But ignoring feedback from former employees is a big mistake. </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> Interviewing or surveying former employees can surface the reasons for their departure and pinpoint the most effective actions to retain talent. Free of the threat of retaliation, nurses who are leaving (or have left) an organization are more likely to provide candid feedback, even about taboo issues that current employees are reluctant to discuss. By collecting feedback from those who have left, organizations can uncover potential blind spots.</p><p> More than one-third of the Glassdoor reviews in our sample were written by former employees and provide insights on what mattered most to nurses who voted with their feet. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> The bars on the left side of the figure “Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction” rank the factors that predict how nurses who quit rank their former employers, and it sheds light on a critical reason nurses might head for the exits.</p><p> In an <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">earlier article</a> , we argued that five behavioral attributes — disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive — mark an organizational culture as toxic. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> Among nurses who quit, toxic culture is more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction than compensation or workload. The importance of toxic workplaces among nurses who quit is consistent with earlier research that found toxicity to be the strongest predictor of industry-adjusted attrition during the first six months of the Great Resignation. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> Toxic culture has become more important for nurses in the post-pandemic era. When we compared which factors best predict how nurses rated their employer before and after the pandemic, toxic culture experienced the largest gain in relative importance post-COVID-19 (followed by workload, well-being, and compensation). If your organization suffers from cultural toxicity, another article of ours, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">How to Fix a Toxic Culture</a> ,” presents several evidence-based interventions health care leaders can use to detox their own organization.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses&#39; Job Satisfaction</h4><p class="caption"> We classified the text of over 150,000 nurses&#39; Glassdoor reviews into two dozen themes that affect the employee experience, and we then analyzed which themes best predict how nurses rate their employer. The chart ranks the importance of each theme in predicting these ratings by showing how much each theme contributes to the overall prediction. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="Top and Bottom Predictors of Nurses’ Job Satisfaction" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3> Learn From Staffing Agency Practices</h3><p> As the figure “Staffing Agencies Rate Better on Many Key Factors” shows, nurses are very positive about the processes staffing agencies have in place to resolve problems quickly and efficiently. Of nurses who mentioned the efficiency of staffing agencies&#39; processes, 75% were positive, compared with 23% expressing positive sentiment for health care systems. For travel nurses, common process issues include onboarding, obtaining required credentials and licenses, contract negotiation, and reimbursement. The best staffing agencies listen to feedback, develop a deep understanding of the typical problems travel nurses face, and optimize their work processes to address these issues.</p><p> Many of the pain points encountered by staff nurses will differ from those of agency nurses. Health care systems, home health agencies, and long-term care providers could, however, adopt a similar approach to capture and analyze nurses&#39; feedback, prioritize the most common and frustrating challenges they face, and work with staff members to address these issues.</p><p> Consistently listening to and acting on feedback can also build trust with the nursing staff. Staffing agency nurses are more positive about having the psychological safety to speak up about difficult issues and be heard than are nurses working in hospitals and health care systems.</p><p> The benefits of psychological safety are blunted, however, if management is slow to respond to issues that nurses raise. Nurses speak highly of how quickly staffing agencies respond to their questions and concerns. In contrast, nurses frequently complain that other types of employers are slow to respond to emails raising issues, if they get a reply at all. Nurses also place a high value on having multiple channels of communication with their supervisors, including text, email, Facebook, Jabber, and a 24/7 hotline.</p><p> Another insight from our research is that nurses value honesty and transparency. They understand the challenges health care faces as well as anyone, and they expect honest communication about what is happening in the organization, how it affects them, and why decisions were made. Triage, a staffing agency and the fourth most highly rated large employer we studied, places honest communication at the center of its value proposition: “We tell it like it is so you won&#39;t be surprised by how it goes.” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p> Health care systems can learn from staffing agencies, but they can also leverage their own distinctive advantages to attract and retain nurses. Nurses in full-time staff positions rate hospitals and health care systems higher than staffing agencies on three important aspects of organizational life: learning and development (including promotion opportunities and reimbursement for training), benefits, and colleagues. Those three factors are among the top 10 predictors of how nurses rate their employers. Health care systems should invest in their comparative advantages and emphasize them when communicating their value proposition to potential and current employees.</p><p></p><h3> Translate Feedback Into Action to Build Trust</h3><p> It&#39;s one thing to collect employee feedback, but it&#39;s another to consistently act on those insights. Employees are less likely to surface issues or propose potential solutions if they believe that managers will not act. <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Worse yet, employees are more likely to quit if they believe that management lacks the power, resources, or interest to make changes based on their suggestions. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Nearly half of nurses believe that management will not fix problems that clinical staff members bring to their attention. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p> Organizations need to put in place structures to consistently act on employee feedback. One well-known example is Kaiser Permanente&#39;s unit-based teams (UBTs), which consist of clinical staff members and managers who regularly work together in a specific unit or department. <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a> The teams, which meet at least once per month, are responsible for their unit&#39;s performance and are co-led by a manager, a labor representative, and, typically, a clinical staff member.</p><p> The UBTs identify opportunities to improve along four dimensions: quality (including patient outcomes), patient service, affordability, and employee experience. The teams use employee feedback to identify and prioritize improvement opportunities. Next, the teams develop and test solutions using best practices and evidence-based methods. Once a solution has been deemed effective, it is implemented across the unit, department, or, in some cases, the entire organization. The UBTs then monitor the impact of these changes in terms of patient outcomes, employee satisfaction, and cost reduction.</p><p></p><p> Our study of 150,000 reviews written by US nurses since the onset of COVID-19 reveals wide variation in how nurses rate their employers as a whole, and specifically in terms of compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support — the four factors that most shape nurses&#39; job satisfaction. In our view, this variation offers a message of hope. Despite the structural challenges that all health care organizations face, it <em>is</em> possible to provide an environment where nurses look forward to going to work every day.</p><p> Many organizations, including some of the largest employers of nurses, have significant room for improvement. These rankings are not designed to “name and shame” but rather to make health care leaders aware of the magnitude of the gap between their organization&#39;s performance and what is possible when it comes to providing a healthy workplace for nurses. We also hope that the objective data on how health care organizations rank on factors that matter most to nurses can provide their leaders with the impetus to make improvements and the evidence to convince all stakeholders of the urgent need for change.</p><p></p><p> What leaders should not do is ask nurses to work harder and endure more frustration and stress while failing to understand and address the organizational factors that make life miserable for many of them. Leaders who continue business as usual should not be surprised when staff members quit, workers unionize, and state and federal legislators dictate regulations to protect the interests of nurses.</p><p> To improve the work lives of nurses, and indeed all health care workers, leaders must collect and act on their feedback, recognizing that different parts of the organization and different populations will face distinctive challenges and issues. Listening to nurses demonstrates that there are meaningful steps health care leaders can take to fix the nursing crisis. The single most important step is to listen to them in the first place.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Explore How Nurses Rate Their Employers</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) is a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management and a cofounder of CultureX. Charles Sull is a cofounder of CultureX.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses&#39; own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by US nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers.</p><p> We calculated the relative importance of each theme in predicting nurses&#39; overall satisfaction. Four factors — toxic culture, organizational support, compensation, and workload — emerged as the strongest predictors of how satisfied nurses were with their employer.</p><p></p><p> One significant finding for health care leaders: Among nurses who had quit, toxic culture was more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction compared with compensation or workload.</p><p> Nurses&#39; job satisfaction varies widely among employers. Our interactive Nursing Satisfaction Index shows how nurses evaluate the employee experience at 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies.</p><p> For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. We also report on how positively or negatively nurses spoke about compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support. Each employer&#39;s score on all dimensions is expressed as standard deviations above/(below) the average for all 200 employers.</p><p> <a href="#interactive-launcher">Explore the index above</a> .</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Health Care Leaders Need to Know to Fight the Nursing Shortage: Nurses Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read is multimedia editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What&#39;s driving that burnout? What&#39;s most important to a nurse&#39;s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this video, we talk to five current and former nurses to learn about the reality of working in health care, including the toxic cultures and stressors they&#39;ve experienced, and get advice from them and health care experts on what needs to change.</p><p> Article author and researcher Donald Sull also discusses the truths about job satisfaction revealed by the analysis of 150,000 employer reviews by nurses on job site Glassdoor, and what health care leaders can learn from them.</p><p></p><p> “The key, actionable finding from our research is, nurses are telling you what&#39;s not working for them, often in very granular detail, and they&#39;re offering concrete recommendations to address these issues. They want to help. They want their voices heard, and they want to make a positive impact,” Sull says.</p><p> “One of the most difficult or frustrating things about being a nurse is really not having enough time to spend with the patient,” says Jennie Evans, who served as a pediatric oncology and ICU RN for 18 years. “Those moments where you can sit, talk with the patient, hold their hand, talk with the family, and really get to know them and understand not just the disease but other underlying anxieties or fears that the patient might have.”</p><p> Watch the video to hear more from nurses on what they want health care leaders to know about toxic cultures, mental health, growth opportunities, and other issues that are critical to caregivers.</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Upgrading Culture for Growth and Transformation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander is a strategic adviser and professor of practice at Hult International Business School. His work on decision-making, problem-solving, and culture has been published in <em>Harvard Business Review</em> , <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , and <em>Knowledge at Wharton</em> . Per shares his thoughts and ideas on his blog <a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">leadershipbackbone.com</a> . Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> P. Hugander, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , May 22, 2023.</p></aside><p> Many leaders know that their organization&#39;s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don&#39;t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and growth. But despite ambitious efforts to infuse such skills into their culture, many organizations fail. The secret to success: Shorten the time to reward when people experience the new skills helping teams beat longtime challenges.</p><p> Per Hugander has helped leaders at organizations including Swedish financial services group SEB make progress on complex strategic challenges. His practical approach helps people to link psychological safety to tangible business results.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why many organizations fail at culture change: Just testing the waters can be dangerous.</li><li> How to go deep — not wide — on culture change and win over skeptics.</li><li> How to put the new skills to use quickly on the organization&#39;s toughest problems and create lasting culture benefits.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Steps to Build and Sustain Diversity in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> , Ed.D., is a managing partner and the US practice leader of CEO and Board Services at Boyden, a global executive search firm. He built his career as a turnaround (glass cliff) specialist in corporate America and writes on issues related to diversity, governance, and strategic growth for private and public corporations and boards.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; however, less attention is paid to what happens after the hire. Only when we effectively create a more equitable landscape and support women and people of color in navigating it can we benefit from the full engagement and contributions of all of our people and avoid losing them to turnover or disengagement.</p><p> Occupational minorities — those individuals who are <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">relative rarities</a> in their profession due to their gender or sexual identity, ethnicity, age, or other factors — have accomplished what countless more have only dreamed of: They have broken through the glass ceiling, navigated the often inhospitable <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">corporate jungle</a> , and often successfully negotiated the <a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">glass cliff</a> . Although the executives who represent diverse populations in your organization have successfully overcome these challenges, an important task remains: building a path for others to follow. This is hard, painstaking work that requires many different tools and competencies, yet it is necessary if others are to safely navigate the landscape.</p><p></p><h3> Steps to Sustaining Diversity</h3><p> Although various resources offer suggestions for how professionals from underrepresented populations can navigate and overcome organizational challenges, it is equally essential that organizations identify where <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">persistent systemic bias and racism</a> lurk and take concrete action to address them. Organizations can take the following five steps to begin the process of creating more inclusive environments where all employees have equal opportunities to thrive and advance in their careers.</p><h4> Step 1: Establish leadership commitment to diversity with sponsorship.</h4><p> Leadership throughout the organization must demonstrate a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion. When leaders model these behaviors, employees throughout the organization naturally follow their example. However, this commitment cannot be limited to one-off efforts or statements on corporate values.</p><p> Leaders must consciously exhibit their commitment to hiring people from underrepresented populations by helping to develop and equip these candidates for advancement. Specifically, every leader, regardless of organizational level, should identify at least one such candidate to intentionally sponsor. After getting to know the candidate&#39;s background, career goals, and support needs, the leader should (1) counsel them in navigating the organization, (2) support them in developing the competencies needed to advance in their career, and, critically, (3) help them secure progressive leadership positions.</p><p></p><p> Although formal mentoring, sponsorship, and buddy programs can be helpful in this effort, relationships that develop informally often are equally, if not more, rewarding and beneficial and tend to continue long after one or both individuals have advanced in or moved out of the organization.</p><h4> Step 2: Remove glass ceilings by addressing systemic factors.</h4><p> The metaphor of the glass ceiling depicts the systems of discrimination that prevent certain groups of people (typically women and people of color) from accessing high-level opportunities for career growth and advancement. Clues that glass ceilings exist within your organization include a lack of diversity within the upper-management and executive ranks compared with your overall workforce; pay disparities between individuals with similar roles and qualifications; limited mentorship, sponsorship, development, or advancement for certain groups of people; explicit or implicit biases regarding which groups are a better fit for leadership roles than others; and attrition levels within underrepresented groups that exceed those of other groups.</p><p> To identify and eradicate glass ceilings in your organization, closely scrutinize every aspect of the employee experience. For example, address biased hiring and promotion practices using blind recruitment techniques; review salary ranges and promotion criteria to ensure that equal pay is awarded for equal work; and make clear career paths and development opportunities available to all employees. Diversity goals, inclusion initiatives, and employee education on recognizing and avoiding unconscious biases also can support a diversity-conducive climate. Supporting flexible work arrangements and work-life balance can encourage the full participation of employees who might otherwise be overlooked due to their needs to balance personal and professional responsibilities.</p><p></p><h4> Step 3: Reduce glass cliffs through due diligence.</h4><p> The term <em>glass cliff</em> describes a phenomenon in which women and other minorities are preferentially selected for leadership positions in times of crisis, placing them at increased risk for failure. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This phenomenon occurs across industries and geographies, and for women and ethnic minorities alike. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The problem with giving people from underrepresented populations leadership opportunities only in times of crisis is that those who lead during turbulent times tend to be seen as part of the problem, which perpetuates stereotypes and reduces future opportunities for such candidates. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> To avoid this outcome, care must be taken to recognize and fully examine the situation before assigning a leader to address it. While the temptation to dive in and do something to “stop the bleeding” is overwhelming, taking the appropriate time to first fully understand the problem is a small price to pay for a much-improved chance of success. The diagnosis process should include identifying project parameters (such as performance targets, deadlines, and budget), project stakeholders, past actions taken, the current situation, and desired outcomes — from the perspectives of all stakeholders. My article on the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">glass cliff phenomenon</a> provides more details on the process of due diligence and the questions that can be used to diagnose these situations. Only after diagnosing the problem will it be possible to select the most appropriate candidate to lead the effort.</p><h4> Step 4: Broaden the pathway by changing the conversation.</h4><p> Corporate environments can be fraught with challenges for women and people of color. Many challenges are systemic, such as organizational cultures that <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">disadvantage certain groups</a> versus others, or workloads and behavioral expectations that require long hours in the office and around-the-clock responsiveness. These systemic challenges can make the corporate landscape seem foreign and antagonistic. In turn, occupational minorities might compensate by nursing cognitive biases that result in too much or too little confidence; limiting their social networks to similar peers rather than nurturing<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">vital connections</a> to sponsors, mentors, and career guides; and failing to strike an appropriate work-life balance.</p><p> Although leaders must deliberately sponsor occupational minorities (Step 1), mentors, sponsors, and allies throughout the organization also play important roles in guiding candidates toward success because they, too, have already successfully navigated the organization. Supporting emerging leaders means changing the typical mentoring conversation. Typical conversations involve identifying a mentee&#39;s short- and long-term goals and seeking the mentor&#39;s situational advice, guidance on skill development, and feedback on performance. Mentoring that supports diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging should be adapted to include a clear framework for professional development, an explanation of how various opportunities and positions contribute to the candidate&#39;s career goals, and a discussion of how to navigate the organizational culture — all in light of the glass ceilings, glass cliffs, and systemic challenges they face as occupational minorities.</p><p> Cognitive biases also should be part of the conversation so that candidates can avoid the traps of both being overconfident and overcompensating for perceived shortcomings. Evaluation and adjustment of cognitive biases might be best accomplished by gathering 360-degree feedback regarding the mentee&#39;s performance on key tasks and engaging the mentee to describe their feelings, thoughts, and general experiences related to performing those tasks. Overconfidence might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is at or below average while their own experience of that task reflects strong enthusiasm, satisfaction, and a sense of achievement. In contrast, overcompensation might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is evaluated as or above average yet their described experiences suggest that they are spending too much time on tasks or that they harbor concerns about their performance.</p><h4> Step 5: Measure and track progress.</h4><p> A popular business adage is that we must inspect what we expect. This truism applies equally to any diversity effort. The process begins with defining what success looks like according to key diversity metrics such as hiring, retention, and advancement for various employee populations. It might be tempting to stop there; however, defining the goal is only the beginning. Additionally, it is necessary to measure the organization&#39;s current performance on these KPIs and then examine why that is the current state. Understanding the organization&#39;s current performance requires the following assessments:</p><p> <strong>1. Gauge buy-in.</strong> To what extent do organizational leaders and members understand and agree that the KPIs defined are the right indicators and performance targets?</p><p> <strong>2. Gauge feasibility.</strong> What organizational structures, processes, and other features facilitate the achievement of the KPI? What features threaten or obstruct achievement?</p><p> <strong>3. Gauge support needs.</strong> Leaders are taught to adapt to the needs of individual subordinates based on each person&#39;s skill level. In the same way, leaders throughout the organization need to adjust the amount of oversight, encouragement, and direction they provide as departments and employees across skill levels work to achieve diversity goals. For example, a recruiting department that is relatively inexperienced at hiring professionals from underrepresented groups will need strong, step-by-step guidance and frequent feedback until their competency grows, while a manager who is highly skilled at developing and including such professionals generally should be allowed the autonomy to exercise their talents to their fullest.</p><p></p><p> As initiatives are implemented, continue to regularly assess these metrics to gauge your progress and fine-tune your efforts. As the saying goes, “What gets measured gets done.” Achievement of your diversity goals will happen only if they are deliberately defined and regularly assessed.</p><p></p><p></p><p> I often have been one of few Black leaders in the organizations where I&#39;ve worked. At one point in my career, I was a town hall presenter at two meetings separated by level — one attended by rank-and-file employees, and the other attended by management. Although the Black customer service representatives were pleasantly surprised to see someone who looked like them in an executive role, I was shocked and dismayed to realize that nearly our entire customer service representative force was Black while all of our supervisors and managers were White. This was puzzling because the leadership team seemed to care about diversity from a recruiting standpoint, but it was glaringly obvious that systemic barriers were obstructing the retention and advancement of professionals from underrepresented groups.</p><p> Often, it is only when executives, board members, or the HR team notices a lack of diversity in their organization&#39;s upper levels that problems in the talent management system are noticed — but typically poorly understood and only rarely solved. Such disparities in advancement might be at least partially explained by inhospitable organizational settings and the need to broaden the pathway for these professionals from underrepresented populations to succeed.</p><p> Organizational leaders, coaches, mentors, sponsors, and other potential career enablers all have a part to play in eliminating sources of inequity and equipping occupational minorities to survive and thrive in corporate environments. As more and more diverse groups of professionals travel the pathway to career success, the pathway will become smoother and broader, resulting in an ongoing and cumulative organizational transformation.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why Pay Transparency Regulations Are a Strategic Management Opportunity</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>Tamara Montag-Smit is an assistant professor of management at the University of Massachusetts (UMass) Lowell. Karoline Evans is an associate professor of management at UMass Lowell. Brandon Smit is an assistant professor of management at Bentley University. Cassondra Batz-Barbarich is an assistant professor of business at Lake Forest College.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Annalisa Grassano</p></figcaption></figure><p> Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, <a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">pay transparency laws</a> are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women&#39;s Law Center reports that altogether, more than one-quarter of US employees live in a location where <a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">pay information is regulated</a> .</p><p> By and large, pay transparency regulations have emphasized disclosing a salary range for advertised positions and internal opportunities for advancement. These laws are designed to ensure equal pay for equal work and effectively close the gender wage gap. The logic is simple: If underpaid employees, including women and minorities, aren&#39;t aware of what their coworkers are paid, they are at a significant disadvantage in leveling the playing field through litigation and negotiation. How can inequities be addressed when they remain in the dark? Without pay transparency, enforcement of existing laws, such as the <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">Equal Pay Act of 1963</a> , becomes difficult. Based on <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">recent cases</a> and notable discrepancies that have been exposed (some spanning years of underpayment), it seems that greater transparency has an important role to play.</p><p></p><h3> Organizational Responses to the Changing Regulatory Landscape</h3><p> Despite the increasingly widespread adoption of pay transparency regulations, many organizations have responded with pushback, resistance, and minimal compliance. After Colorado became the first state to require organizations to disclose pay ranges in advertised positions in 2021, organizations soliciting applicants from across the country began <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">explicitly excluding Colorado residents</a> from consideration to skirt the new laws, prompting the state&#39;s department of labor to issue <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">warnings and fines</a> . Another organizational tactic is to comply with pay information requirements with pay ranges that are so wide that applicants cannot meaningfully predict what salary they might be offered. In one notable example, Netflix posted a job with a salary range that <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">spanned $90,000 to $900,000</a> .</p><p> While approaches to compliance with transparency laws at the organizational level have taken many forms, leaders have expressed several common concerns regarding the potential negative consequences of pay transparency to their business operations and culture:</p><ul><li> <strong>Will everyone just ask for more money?</strong> More pay information might prompt more conversations about pay (and why someone is receiving what they are). Managers worry that they&#39;ll be caught in the middle trying to juggle competing goals around budgeting and employee satisfaction.</li><li> <strong>What happens if some employees find out that they&#39;re paid less than others?</strong> Explaining to long-standing employees why they are paid the same as a new hire is likely to be uncomfortable and prompt substantial criticism of the employer.</li><li> <strong>Will pay transparency affect our ability to work together?</strong> Pay transparency can elicit jealousy and counterproductive competition when individuals perceive themselves as inequitably rewarded. Managers worry that employees might fight and undermine one another when discrepancies are exposed.</li></ul><p></p><h3> New Insights Into Managing Pay Transparency</h3><p> Our work provides new insights into addressing some of the main questions organizations have about transparency. Most new laws focus exclusively on creating pay transparency by requiring organizations to disclose pay ranges for open positions. In academic research, this form of transparency is referred to as <em>distributive transparency</em> , because it reveals information only regarding the <em>amount</em> of money employees are paid.</p><p> In our research, however, we have delineated several ways in which pay information can be transparent. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> With <em>procedural transparency</em> , the emphasis is on sharing information about how pay <em>decisions</em> are made; at the most transparent level, this would include a formula for calculating compensation (such as base pay or a merit-based raise).</p><p> Distinguishing between distributive versus procedural transparency is crucial because, as our research shows, procedural transparency can mitigate many of the risks and drawbacks associated with distributive transparency.</p><p> Implicit in pay transparency regulations is the idea that underpaid employees will take it upon themselves to <a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">negotiate for a fairer wage</a> . In fact, a large-scale study of over 100,000 academics over the past two decades found that changes in pay transparency were related to significantly more wage parity between men and women. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> However, the research also showed that transparency doesn&#39;t equate to <em>everyone</em> asking for more.</p><p> To explore this further, we conducted a series of four experiments to better understand <em>how</em> and <em>when</em> pay transparency can encourage employees (especially women) to more effectively negotiate for fair wages. In our first study, lab participants were paid for their performance after four rounds of a popular word search game and were given the opportunity to negotiate for better compensation. In studies 2, 3, and 4, online participants prepared themselves to go into a performance review, armed with varying degrees of information regarding performance and pay, to possibly negotiate for a better annual raise. They were told that they were slated for a 3% raise but that raises could range from 3% to 10%. Across these studies, we varied the amount of information participants could access regarding both the amount other people were paid and participants&#39; performance relative to their peers&#39;.</p><p> These studies yielded four important findings regarding distributive and procedural pay transparency:</p><p> <strong>1. People made clearer comparisons.</strong> We found that the best predictor of whether someone tried to negotiate for higher pay was their performance relative to that of peers. Compared with average performers, high performers were approximately 50% more likely to request higher pay when they knew their ranking relative to others. It&#39;s important to note that in our study, participants saw the previous year&#39;s performance and pay data for their team members, and it was clear that increased performance was directly related to increased pay. Although not an explicit formula indicating performance-based pay, this information provided a clear signal to participants that pay raises were largely determined by performance.</p><p> <strong>2. People negotiated fairly.</strong> Average performers were more likely to accept the minimum raise offered to them, often citing the raise as fair based on their performance. As one person stated, “Considering I only met expectations throughout the year rather than exceeded them, asking for a higher raise seems fruitless and unearned.” Generally, average performers rarely asked for the maximum raise, in part because they considered the fact that they were performing at a lower level than some peers. This was true, though, only when they had all of the information. When they were told nothing about their performance, 85% of people requested the maximum pay amount. Lacking performance information, average performers asked for the highest raises available within the pay range.</p><p> <strong>3. Women <em>do</em> ask for higher pay.</strong> Counter to a pervasive assumption, women didn&#39;t seem to need much encouragement to negotiate. In fact, when the percentage of participants who negotiated is considered, women were often more likely than men to negotiate (though this was not a statistically significant difference). These findings cast some doubt on the idea that one reason for the gender wage gap is that women negotiate less often than their male counterparts. Recent research combining information from dozens of negotiation studies has come to the same conclusion: Many of the negotiation gaps between men and women have largely disappeared in recent years. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Although this is good news, it does little to close the gender pay gap as it currently stands.</p><p> <strong>4. People were motivated to perform better.</strong> Average performers expressed motivation to work harder and perform better to earn a higher raise during the next review cycle. When asked why they did not negotiate for more money, one participant stated, “My numbers did not show that I deserved a higher raise. With better numbers the following year, a case would be made for a higher raise.” Another stated, “I knew I&#39;d done an average job, so I hope to do better in the future and hope to get a better raise next year.”</p><p> Our findings replicate and extend an old but powerful notion in management research: the <em>fair process effect</em> . <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Employees will accept unfavorable outcomes if they believe those outcomes were produced by a fair system. Put differently, if people know <em>why</em> they are being paid less (in other words, there is procedural transparency), they will not respond negatively and might even work harder.</p><h3> Make Pay Transparency a Win-Win for Your Organization</h3><p> Pay transparency can be a win-win opportunity rather than a compliance hurdle. But simply listing pay data in job postings without any context in response to regulations might be a big mistake. These practices not only disregard the spirit of the laws but also come at a heavy price and forfeit significant opportunities. Leaders should think beyond compliance and consider ways to strategically leverage pay transparency for their organization to improve applicant attraction and employee retention. Our research offers some insights into how this can be done.</p><p> <strong>Make pay only <em>part</em> of the transparency equation.</strong> Counter to some pervasive fears that transparency will increase labor costs, cause jealousy, and create conflict, the reality is that secrecy around pay creates problems of its own. As researchers at Payscale found, most employees are <a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">unsure whether they are paid fairly</a> , with many believing they are underpaid when they are not, which leads to greater turnover and dissatisfaction. Our research suggests that without a reference point for performance, employees have little to no basis for judging what compensation would be fair and are therefore more likely to make unreasonable requests. Transparency in both performance <em>and</em> pay can enable employees to better assess the fairness of their pay and make more reasonable requests.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on the pay decision-making process.</strong> Procedural transparency helps managers more clearly communicate with employees about pay because salaries/bonuses are based on performance rather than on seemingly intangible or, worse yet, bias-laden factors. Providing information on how pay is determined helps incumbent employees understand why their pay is higher or lower than their peers&#39; and, more importantly, how to move up. Managers can&#39;t be accused of favoritism and bias when pay is directly determined by performance, which puts them in a collaborative role during pay conversations. With a focus on performance, these conversations can focus on development and examine how employees can perform better and earn higher raises.</p><p> <strong>Recognize that (distributive) pay transparency will not fix inequity on its own.</strong> There&#39;s an assumption that distributive pay transparency will close pay gaps; however, evidence suggests that this alone is not enough to create an equitable workplace. Research has shown that women and men are <em>asking</em> for salary increases in <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">relatively equal proportions</a> , but women are still less successful at getting what they ask for. Distributive pay transparency can help reduce some ambiguity, but both performance and pay transparency (procedural transparency) together equip employees with the tools they need to ask for what they deserve. When people know what to expect from negotiations (that is, what the bargaining zone is and what&#39;s reasonable to ask for), gender differences are minimized. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> For example, <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">women of color</a> don&#39;t often take advantage of opportunities to negotiate roles, responsibilities, or flexible work arrangements, creating long-term inequities that explain pay gaps beyond starting salary. Broader transparency helps reduce the ambiguity that often leaves women and members of other minority populations hesitant to negotiate, even when they know they could.</p><p> <strong>Consider the benefits for current employees <em>and</em> applicants.</strong> Simply posting pay ranges is only one piece of the puzzle. Applicants have negative reactions to excessively wide pay ranges because they don&#39;t offer useful information. In this case, pay is still essentially secret. As we found in our study, without meaningful information, individuals are inclined to ask for the maximum amount to see what is possible. This creates yet another headache for hiring managers. A better approach would be to leverage procedural transparency to clearly outline the factors used when determining a salary offer, and perhaps even how heavily those factors are weighted. For example, Buffer, a marketing company, has done a great job of creating a <a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">pay system</a> that balances simplicity (for better understanding) and complexity (for capturing nuance) by using a standard formula for making pay decisions: salary = job type x seniority x experience + location + $10,000 or equity.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Despite organizational concerns and hesitancy to implement government regulations around pay transparency, such policies continue to gain traction and are just one force behind growing expectations around salary disclosures. In a 2022 report from HR technology firm Visier, 79% of surveyed employees said they want <a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">pay transparency</a> ; Gen Z employees were the strongest proponents of it.</p><p> Our research highlights the potential for procedural transparency to strategically mitigate the perceived organizational risks while also meeting legal requirements and social expectations. While changes are clearly happening, we hope business leaders think more deeply and creatively about <em>how</em> to make pay transparent in ways that both support organizational goals and meet employee needs.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Delicate Dynamics of Challenging a Superior</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>Benjamin Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one&#39;s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person and the situation.</p><p> For those keen on maintaining professional decorum and growing in their roles, this guide can help ensure that your challenging conversations are both constructive and respectful.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Choose your battles wisely.</strong> Workplaces are vibrant ecosystems of opinions, processes, and methodologies. It can be enticing to address every single discrepancy or divergence in opinion that one encounters, but wisdom lies in discerning which battles are worth fighting. Every time a potential disagreement arises, consider: Is this issue so significant that it warrants a confrontation? Minor differences in opinion might be addressed more effectively through passive channels or should even be overlooked. But larger concerns, especially those affecting team dynamics, company culture, or broader business objectives, require a more direct approach.</p><p> <strong>Understand the importance of timing.</strong> In the world of professional communication, timing can be everything. Choosing the right moment can make the difference between a concern being genuinely considered or hastily dismissed. Before even considering challenging a superior, it&#39;s crucial to pause and assess the situation from a holistic viewpoint. Is your concern so immediate that it demands to be addressed immediately? Alternatively, would it be better to earmark it for a detailed, private discussion later? It&#39;s wise to avoid confronting superiors during high-pressure situations or public forums because it can be misconstrued as an attempt at disruption or showmanship. By choosing the optimal time, you create a smoother path for constructive dialogue.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prioritize private discussions.</strong> The environment in which you choose to voice your concerns plays a pivotal role in how those concerns are received. Engaging in public disagreements or conflicts can lead to multiple unforeseen complications, including being perceived as aggressive or confrontational. By choosing a private setting for these discussions, you provide both yourself and your superior with an atmosphere conducive to open and genuine dialogue. This approach not only minimizes distractions and potential biases but also reinforces the idea that the intent is constructive feedback, not public criticism.</p><p> <strong>Master the art of “I” statements.</strong> Effective communication is as much about content as it is about delivery. The words we choose and the manner in which we frame our concerns can significantly influence the reception of our message. Instead of adopting a potentially confrontational tone, use “I” statements to express observations, feelings, and suggestions. For instance, instead of bluntly stating, “You&#39;ve overlooked this crucial aspect,” a more collaborative approach would be, “I feel that this particular aspect could benefit from further attention.” This approach ensures that the focus remains on the issue at hand and not on personal biases or confrontations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Embrace the feedback process.</strong> The journey of challenging a superior or expressing concerns is inherently bilateral. It&#39;s not just an avenue for you to voice your thoughts but also an opportunity to understand the other person&#39;s perspective. Demonstrating a genuine openness to feedback, even if it&#39;s contradictory to your viewpoint, is vital. This approach not only paves the way for mutual respect but also fosters a culture of continuous learning and collaboration within the organization.</p><p> <strong>Align with like-minded peers, but tactfully.</strong> While individual concerns have their merit, there&#39;s undeniable strength in numbers. Finding allies or colleagues who share your perspective can provide additional weight to your concerns. However, it&#39;s imperative that this alignment is not perceived as cliquey or divisive. The primary focus should always remain on the collective benefit of the organization rather than on forming factions within the team.</p><p> <strong>Keep the organization&#39;s goals at the forefront.</strong> Any concerns or challenges you raise should inherently resonate with the broader objectives and goals of the organization. By consistently aligning your feedback and suggestions with the company&#39;s mission and values, you reassure your superiors of your commitment to the collective success of the organization over your individual aspirations.</p><p> <strong>Brace for a spectrum of outcomes.</strong> While we all hope for positive and constructive outcomes from our disagreements, it&#39;s essential to be prepared for a variety of reactions. Your superior might be receptive, indifferent, or even defensive. By anticipating these potential responses and planning your strategies accordingly, you ensure that you remain balanced, constructive, and professional, irrespective of the immediate feedback.</p><h3> The Aftermath: Reflect, Adapt, and Evolve</h3><p></p><p> Every professional interaction, especially those involving challenges or confrontations, provides a rich opportunity for personal and professional growth. After the discussion, take the time to evaluate the effectiveness of the conversation, the strategies employed, and the outcomes achieved. These reflections will bring invaluable lessons to light and help you to continuously refine and enhance your communication skills for future challenges.</p><p> Ultimately, while the task of challenging a superior might seem steeped in potential pitfalls, with the right strategies and a focus on mutual growth and respect, it can be navigated with tact and professionalism. Encouraging open dialogue and a culture of feedback is the bedrock of innovative and forward-thinking organizations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Ghost Scenarios Haunt Strategy Execution</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trudi Lang and Rafael Ramírez. <p>Trudi Lang is a senior fellow in management practice at the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Collaborative Strategy Lab. Rafael Ramírez is professor of practice at Saïd Business School and director of the Oxford Scenarios Programme.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Scenario Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George/Ikon Images Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2024WINTER-Lang_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Patrick George/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Executives engaged in strategic planning typically have a blind spot. They focus almost exclusively on possible courses of action and pay little attention to the future socioeconomic and environmental context in which those actions will play out. During our combined 70 years of research, practice, and teaching, we, as well as others, have observed that business leaders are inclined, and their organizations configured, to work with only a single implicit view of the future. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That view is typically deeply embedded within their strategies as a set of unquestioned assumptions about the future context. We call these sets of unexamined assumptions <em>ghost scenarios</em> because they are invisible — and because they may come back to haunt executives and companies in unanticipated and unwelcome ways.</p><p></p><p> Underpinning every ghost scenario is a small set of implicit trends that leaders project into the future without questioning whether they might change. Consider the ways in which dramatic changes in climate have come to haunt rail services in Britain. In July 2022, temperatures above 40 degrees Celsius (104 degrees Fahrenheit) were recorded in the country for the first time. These high temperatures heated the rails to slightly over 62 C (143 F), causing them to bend. As a result, many train trips were canceled and service on other routes slowed to 60 mph. The rail tracks had been engineered for a future in which the air temperature did not exceed 27 C (80 F). In short, the British rail network was designed and built to work not in the scenario in which it found itself in 2022 but in a scenario that made the implicit assumption that historical climate trends would continue unchanged.</p><h3> Assumptions Hide in Plain Sight</h3><p> Research on human perception has demonstrated that people differentiate the object of their visual focus from its background by bringing that object to the forefront of their attention while everything else recedes. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Humans can focus on either the figure or the background but never both at the same time.</p><p> The <a href="https://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Rubin_vase">Rubin vase illusion</a> is a well-known example of this figure-ground (or background) perception challenge. Depending on how you look at the picture, you will see either a vase or two faces in profile. Importantly, however, you cannot see both at the same time: One or the other perceptually recedes to become the background of the figure you see. To see both figures, you must alternate between them.</p><p> It&#39;s important that executives are able to recognize how people&#39;s ability to focus can also blind them to important contextual information, since leaders often fail to see the background upon which their strategies will play out — and on which their strategies depend. They may consider hard infrastructure — such as rail tracks — to be a relatively static background issue and focus their attention on trends that seem more salient to business planning, such as changes in customer preferences and habits. But that can lead executives to implement a strategy that may be unexpectedly disrupted by the unexamined assumptions about its context that are woven through its background issues.</p><p></p><p> Particularly today, given the fast pace of change, soaring uncertainty, and high levels of turbulence, failing to surface the assumptions built into strategic planning is risky, as is a failure to consider multiple possible alternative futures through <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-scenario-planning-to-reshape-strategy/">scenario planning</a> . <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Scenario planning exercises can help executives explore how their strategies might play out in different business contexts and conditions, with an eye toward honing those strategies to be more effective.</p><p> To understand how scenario planning can keep executives from being haunted by a ghost scenario, let&#39;s look at two global organizations we recently worked with in the Oxford Scenarios Programme. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><h3> AXA Examines Its ESG Assumptions</h3><p> Insurance company <a href="https://www.axa.com/en">AXA</a> serves 95 million clients in over 50 countries with products and services in the areas of property-casualty insurance, life insurance and savings, and asset management. One of the company&#39;s key strategic goals is to sustain its climate leadership position. Wisely, executives from AXA decided to make the future context of that goal the focus of their attention for a limited period of time so that they could explore how it might change and how they might need to adapt if it did.</p><p> The company was particularly interested in understanding how future environmental, social, and governance (ESG) trends might affect its stated goal. For example, what might be the impact of some US states&#39; proposed legislation that would penalize financial institutions pursuing ESG investment strategies? Or, how might the public react if companies are seen as greenwashing or misrepresenting their ESG credentials? Thus, instead of letting ESG requirements, as currently understood, be the ghost scenario, the company asked questions about the future of ESG and, more broadly, about the emerging sustainability context for corporations.</p><p> Participants and facilitators in the scenario-planning exercise worked in teams to look at the future environment. One scenario imagined that stand-alone insurance companies had been swallowed up by dominant tech platforms whose own ESG priorities superseded those of the insurers. In another scenario, governments set stringent regulations regarding ESG issues, with compliance implications for companies&#39; strategic choices. In yet another imagined future, climate change accelerated more than expected, causing businesses to shift their priorities to urgently address climate-related crises — or to focus exclusively on reducing CO2 emissions, abandoning social and governance agendas.</p><p> By explicitly engaging with the ghost scenario and its equally plausible alternatives, AXA came to understand that continuing to strive to deliver superior ESG performance as it is currently understood might not be the only future it should be preparing for. Within AXA, these insights have been used to inform a conversation about future ESG challenges and their implications for possible announcements and commitments to be made, including when and with whom. They&#39;ve prompted AXA to start preparing alternative strategies in the event that delivering great performance against current ESG expectations becomes irrelevant.</p><p></p><h3> Swift Anticipates Digital Currencies</h3><p> Swift (the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication) is a member-owned cooperative that enables financial messaging and related services for cross-border payments around the world. It currently delivers over 30 million messages a day for more than 11,000 institutions in over 200 countries and territories. It was created in the early 1970s by 239 banks in 15 countries to solve the growing problem of clunky, slow, and costly cross-border payments communications via a new technology platform. With disruption as part of its origin story, Swift is proactive about potential changes in its context.</p><p> In 2021, Swift executives were interested in understanding how digital currencies, including those issued by central banks, might evolve in the years ahead. The category more than doubled in 2021, to more than 9,000 cryptocurrencies.</p><p> Rather than assuming this unfolding and rapid growth in digital currencies to be the only possible scenario, executives at Swift paused to better understand what other developments might occur, how they might shape the future digital currency ecosystem, and how Swift might be affected. For example, economists and other experts have pointed to the lack of intrinsic value of many digital currencies, as well as concerns about <a href="https://concerned.tech/">the security and reliability of their underlying technologies</a> .</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Where the Ghosts Hide in Common Strategic Planning Processes</h4><p> <strong>In a SWOT analysis,</strong> leaders consider their organization&#39;s strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats in relation to only the current scenario and to known competitors, suppliers, customers, regulatory rules, and the like. When identifying and analyzing risks, executives implicitly assume that there is only one scenario. However, in another context (a different scenario), risks might evaporate and new opportunities might arise.</p><p> <strong>In stakeholder mapping,</strong> leaders make an assessment about the attention and power of stakeholders now and in one expected future. An implicit scenario is the background to this assessment. But the importance of stakeholders could change significantly if the context unexpectedly changes.</p><p> <strong>In game theory and war-gaming,</strong> competitors&#39; moves are considered within the context of a ghost scenario, and war games are typically conducted with no consideration of a different future other than the one that is underway. However, changing scenarios could require new tactics and surface unforeseen future combatants.<br /></article></aside></div><p> Swift&#39;s own stance on digital currencies was open and neutral. It would potentially support them if they were properly regulated and added value to the economies, businesses, and communities it served.</p><p> The scenarios developed for Swift&#39;s executives explored different ways in which trust in the technology might evolve. In some of them, trust associated with digital currencies would disappear as the opaque technology and algorithms upon which they are based became suspect. In other scenarios, digital currencies could be manipulated, and thus the authenticity of what was being exchanged could no longer be guaranteed. And in another scenario, a more generalized lack of trust in for-profit financial institutions would spread to providers of digital currencies, leading some segments of society to hesitate to engage with either, with related consequences.</p><p> For the Oxford participants envisioning these scenarios, it was not clear that the values held by those promoting the technology, or the values that the technology supposedly enabled, would be accepted by governmental regulators or by those in society at large in all imaginable future contexts. Swift&#39;s executives have since explored those sets of scenarios, which provided rich and divergent insights about the ways digital currencies might pan out. Those insights have helped them avoid relying on overly simplistic views of the future — and being swayed by hype.</p><h3> How to See a Ghost Before It Haunts You</h3><p> Based on our experience leading scenario planning exercises for AXA, Swift, and many other organizations, we have developed the following suggestions for executives who want to bring their ghost scenarios into view and make the figure-ground reversal a key part of their strategy practice.</p><p> <strong>Use scenario planning to acknowledge implicit assumptions.</strong> Recognize that every organization&#39;s strategy presumes a future scenario that often remains unquestioned. That is, every executive engages in a form of implicit scenario planning, whether they are conscious of it or not. Making scenario planning a regular part of the strategy-making process achieves two important goals: It alerts leaders to how turbulent conditions could change the context within which they work and compete, and it acknowledges the reality that current conditions themselves present a hypothetical future scenario, not a fixed reality.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize the figure-ground dilemma.</strong> Acknowledge that the figure that is attended to (most often, the organization&#39;s strategy) and the background that is so often ignored (the unexamined ghost scenario) cannot successfully be the focus of attention at the same time. Instead, executives need to flexibly and sequentially shift between the two to investigate each fully and avoid the trap of making implicit assumptions about the other. AXA took the time to deliberately explore the future of ESG rather than assuming there would be no changes to how it is currently used and understood. Swift purposefully focused on understanding the potential future contexts of digital currencies rather than just implicitly assuming subsequent options from the existing trends.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Dedicate executive time and resources to the problem.</strong> Organizations must intentionally create a time and space for leaders to explore how relevant economic, political, technological, social, and environmental factors might be changing. Contrast a small set of future scenarios with the ghost scenario to pinpoint where current strategy might need to be adapted to be well positioned for the range of ways the context might develop. Some organizations even have dedicated units, such as the <a href="https://www.shell.com/energy-and-innovation/the-energy-future/scenarios/what-are-scenarios/meet-the-shell-scenarios-team.html#vanity-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2hlbGwuY29tL2VuZXJneS1hbmQtaW5ub3ZhdGlvbi90aGUtZW5lcmd5LWZ1dHVyZS9zY2VuYXJpb3MvbWVldC10aGUtc2hlbGwtc2NlbmFyaW9zLXRlYW0uaHRtbA">Global Business Environment scenarios team</a> at Shell International. <a href="https://horizons.gc.ca/en/home/">Policy Horizons Canada</a> plays this role for the Canadian government.</p><p></p><p> For all of these efforts to be truly useful, scenario planning outputs must be fed back into strategic decision-making rather than written up in a report and placed on a shelf. They should also be disseminated more widely in an organization so that people at all levels and functions can consider possible implications from their own perspective — implications that might not occur to leadership. For a strategy to be successful when the context changes, executives need to have a balanced approach — recognizing both figure and ground as important areas for discernment. That is, they must recognize the importance of the background or ground upon which their actions will play out, even as they plan their next move. Savvy executives know that they must both envision and embrace change. The trick is learning to adeptly shift one&#39;s attention between the figure and the ground to see how the context might unfold, so it doesn&#39;t leave your strategy ungrounded.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>