<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 9 日星期一 14:35:04 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>领导者将阻力转化为进步的五种方法</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phillip G. Clampitt and Bob DeKoch. <p>菲利普·G·克兰皮特 (Phillip G. Clampitt) 是威斯康星大学绿湾分校布莱尔传播学教授。 Bob DeKoch 是领导力咨询公司 Limitless 的创始人，也是 Boldt Co 的前总裁。他们是<cite>《Leading with Care in a Tough World</cite> 》（罗丹图书，2022 年）的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Effectively responding to pushback may well rank as one of the most important competencies that leaders can possess, and it’s especially critical during times of transition, like returning to the office post-pandemic. Such resistance to an organizational policy, directive, or decision can take many forms, ranging from voicing concerns [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Clampitt-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>有效应对阻力很可能是领导者可以拥有的最重要的能力之一，在过渡时期尤其重要，比如在大流行后重返办公室。这种对组织政策、指令或决定的抵制可以采取多种形式，从表达担忧和提出问题到积极反对和破坏。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>高效的领导者将阻力视为促进团队学习、同时推动组织向前发展的机会。目标应该是通过调和倡导热情和逆向悲观情绪来增加人们的理解和支持。这种更深层次的理解虽然不一定能让所有人满意，但会营造一种坦诚、谦逊、适应和信任的氛围，从而巧妙地引导人们远离潜在的破坏性倾向。</p><p></p><p>根据数十年的研究、高管观察和访谈，我们确定了领导者在遇到阻力时所犯的主要错误，并提供了五项指导方针来帮助他们更好地应对。</p><h3>什么不起作用</h3><p>领导者在面对矛盾、分歧或阻力时会犯三个主要错误：</p><p><strong>抑制不确定性。</strong>当提出的问题可能无法立即得到答案或引入最近可能出现或被搁置或忽视的观点时，阻力会增加不确定性。一些领导人通过边缘化担忧、提供安抚保证或援引独裁声音来应对不确定性引发的阻力。这种做法提供了虚假的确定性，从长远来看会损害信任。</p><p>根据我们的研究，即使是那些在工作生活中寻求更多确定性的员工也希望他们的组织能够拥抱不确定性。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>高效的领导者会避免掩盖不确定性，即使他们面临着根本不存在的确定性要求。即使他们现在不知道答案，他们也可以通过讨论如何找到这些答案来提供操作层面的确定性。</p><p><strong>忽略权力动态。</strong>拥有职位或后天地位的领导者会直接或微妙地影响阻力的性质。高度专制的权力结构往往会将阻力推向地下。同样，更微妙的权力信号可能会压制对合理关切的公开讨论。领导人可能会错误地将沉默等同于同意。有些人会假装接受，而另一些人会在“一次又一次的会议”中散播异议，从而暴露并往往放大人们的恐惧。</p><p></p><p>当一个经验丰富的高管团队的首席执行官提出一项新举措时，我们有机会观察他们的反应——包括不温不火和象征性的反馈。首席执行官意识到缺乏坦诚，因此寻求更多意见。一位沮丧的高管最终脱口而出：“我们不会在这个问题上分享我们的想法，因为无论我们说什么，你都会做你要做的事。”这一极其坦诚的评论提出了一个更深层次的挑战：对特定问题持有强烈观点的有权势的人如何鼓励坦诚？有效的领导者会采取积极措施来减少破坏性对话（如下所述），因为他们认识到固有的权力动态极大地影响任何讨论的质量。</p><p><strong>假设声音最大代表共识。</strong>抵制有多种形式：其中一些是显而易见的，例如投诉或员工请愿，而另一些则更为微妙，例如会议中的询问或缺乏参与。领导者常常倾向于更多地关注最敢于发声的员工，认为拥有最大扩音器的人代表了大多数人的意见。他们可能会也可能不会。</p><p>当最响亮或最具政治影响力的声音主导讨论时，这种动态往往会造成对支持或分歧程度的不准确印象。有效的领导者认识到两种极端的危险：狂热者掩盖相关问题，或者逆向者破坏潜在的支持。</p><p></p><h3>参与抵制的建议</h3><p>有效的领导者不仅避免压制不确定性，忽视权力动态，并假设最直言不讳的人代表共识，他们还采取反映以下指导方针的积极对策。</p><p> <strong>1. 设定对话的基本规则。</strong>以下基本规则可以提高期望，缓和不尊重的宣传，并增加每个人抵制机会的价值：</p><ul><li><strong>寻求理解您不同意的观点。</strong>在讨论有争议的问题时，许多人的第一本能是立即反驳或反驳。通过表现出接受不同观点的意愿来抵制这种诱惑。提出问题或重新表述别人的论点（尤其是那些你不同意的论点）等简单的策略可以缓和反驳，并且几乎神奇地增强对话语气。同样，诸如“告诉我我的想法可能是错误的”或“我可能错过了一些东西；我可能错过了一些东西”之类的陈述。请说更多”表明对新想法持开放态度。</li><li><strong>尊重地不同意别人的观点。</strong>用诸如“让我提供另一个观点”之类的语言尊重地表达分歧，可以设定正确的讨论基调，同时也鼓励那些比较犹豫的人大声说出来。不愿分享不同观点通常表明存在潜在的信任缺陷。有时，尽管房间里存在固有的权力差异，领导者仍需要鼓励其他人分享他们的担忧。</li><li><strong>避免两极分化、扎根的断言。</strong>过于确定地倡导很可能会引发权力动态问题。表明概率水平，例如“我对这个事实有 95% 的把握”，通常会引发更激烈的争论。</li><li><strong>消除阻力的个性化。</strong>如果一项决定被贴上“首席执行官计划”的标签，许多人会进行自我审查，并因为害怕冒犯当权者而避免提出担忧。通过在白板上记录问题而不进行归因来消除个性化的阻力，可以减轻这种权力动态，同时缓和强烈的情绪。</li><li><strong>随着讨论的进展改变你的观点和反应。</strong>经常需要提醒员工，在考虑新证据或获得新观点后改变观点并不是软弱的表现。没有人应该担心因为改变观点而丢脸。事实上，有效的领导者会在他们的观点发生转变时通过发表诸如“我看到一个不在我的雷达屏幕上的问题”之类的声明来强调。随着对话的出现，重新构建关键问题以强调新的观点。</li></ul><p> <strong>2. 引导团队了解阻力机会。</strong>许多会议或倡议的推出都以问答期结束，而没有首先向与会者提供有关阻力的期望的方向。由于缺乏清晰度，人们常常会做出各种未经检验和未言明的假设，这些假设可能并不准确。</p><p>一些员工因抵制机会而被剥夺了权利，因为他们认为自己的所有想法都应该被完全接受。他们不期望发生合理的辩论或对<em>他们的</em>抵制进行反击。这就是为什么明智的领导者会仔细地引导员工了解可能的结果，而不是接受/拒绝极端的情况。他们提出了其他替代方案，例如调整计划、引入测试期、推迟实施、修改决定或重新考虑提案。</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. 选择正确的论坛和设置。</strong>有些场合，比如市政厅聚会或在线论坛，往往会鼓励更情绪化的观点表达、姿态和发泄。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>这种情况可能会阻碍那些不太愿意进行情绪化争论的人进行有用的询问和提问。合适的场所和论坛可以最大限度地增加富有洞察力的提问、深思熟虑的讨论和相互尊重的辩论的机会。通常，配备适当讨论参数的小团体效果最好。同样，对较小群体的在线论坛进行适当监控可以鼓励更好的抵制动力。</p><p>领导者还需要注意，有些人不愿意在别人面前分享担忧，因为他们担心被视为团队合作能力差，或者他们对如何表达担忧或捍卫自己的观点缺乏信心。为了鼓励那些不太愿意发言的人，提前向他们提供会议的讨论要点并鼓励他们写下他们的担忧和疑问通常会有所帮助。</p><p> <strong>4.先教育后倡导。</strong>熟练的教育工作者很快就会放弃这样的想法：一个好的解释就足以建立理解。通常，他们会讨论得出结论的方法，包括相反的观点和现有的问题。这种方法将不确定性融入结论，为进一步讨论和相反观点腾出空间。</p><p>相比之下，倡导者很少讨论可能与他们坚定的观点相矛盾的证据或方法。当他们确实接受相反的观点时，他们常常会轻视或嘲笑这些观点。支持者可能会回避任何批评，淡化不确定性，并认为简短的解释会启发其他人。即使是聪明的高管也常常陷入这个陷阱，高估了他们教育工作的程度和深度。</p><p>在教育之后的某个时候，倡导可能会发挥作用，但最终，有效的领导者认为允许人们表达担忧会带来好处。短期来看，阻力可能会导致调整，从而提高长期接受度和顺利实施。</p><p> <strong>5.路标拐点。</strong>随着决策、举措和政策的发展，领导者对阻力的确定性和开放程度也会发生变化。在领导层对这些拐点缺乏明确说明的情况下，员工会采用有关抵制的潜规则，例如以下内容：</p><ul><li>规则A：如果领导还没有做出最终决定，那么我可以大声说出我的观点。</li><li>规则B：如果领导者有很强的立场或者已经做出了最终决定，那么我支持它或者闭嘴。</li><li>规则 C：如果我在一个问题上争论足够长的时间，领导者就会屈服。</li></ul><p>如果潜规则 A 和 B 强化了阻力动态，那么领导者可能会高估某项举措或决策的支持程度。为什么？因为按照规则 B 运作的员工认为反馈请求是为了剧院或旨在制造支持；他们进行自我审查或仅提出象征性的反对。结果，不同意见和潜在有价值的声音都消失了。</p><p></p><p>规则 C 恰恰相反，引发了无穷无尽的争论。这会在决策被调整、修改或最终确定后滋生抱怨文化。高效的领导者知道，开放并不意味着可以进行无休止的讨论。毕竟，反推反推可以永远持续下去。</p><p>阻止这些无声规则扎根的最佳方法是在抵制期间明确指出拐点。以开放之名掩饰自己情绪的领导人破坏了整个对话的坦诚。相反，有效的领导者会分享他们对调整拟议计划的开放程度，宣布他们的情绪何时发生变化，并明确表明抵制的时间何时结束。</p><h3>一个成功的反击故事</h3><p>Capital Credit Union 首席执行官劳里·布茨 (Laurie Butz) 经常使用这些指导方针来进行抵制，以充分了解员工认为随着新举措的推出，他们正在失去什么。例如，随着 COVID-19 威胁的消退，她试图重新启动面对面的全体员工会议，以增强包容性，并就悬而未决的举措进行更强有力、深思熟虑的讨论。她认为教育过程是双向的，这需要更多的面对面论坛，鼓励遵守比屏幕发泄更富有成效的讨论基本规则。</p><p>然而，这一消息遭到了员工的强烈抵制，因为他们需要长途跋涉才能参加一年两次的聚会。一些人通过在线调查表达了对费用和时间的担忧，而另一些人则直接向直接主管表达了不满，认为“Zoom 会议在新冠疫情期间效果很好”。</p><p>巴茨承认了这些担忧，同时恭敬地为现场聚会辩护，因为毕竟，“你可以举办一场 Zoom 婚礼，但会缺少一些重要的东西。”类似的信息在她的“大使”（意见领袖）的更个人渠道中得到了回应。</p><p></p><p>随着时间的推移，面对面的会议 (1) 提高了员工参与度，(2) 重新激发了员工参与流程的兴趣，(3) 引发了对关键问题更深入的讨论。定量证据支持了这些观察结果。例如，在恢复面对面会议后，全员调查的参与率从 60% 增加到 91%，83% 的调查受访者表示他们“高度投入工作”。轶事证据也出现了：员工在离开现场会议时经常询问，“我们什么时候还有机会像这样见面？”</p><p></p><p>通过抑制不确定性、引发权力动态以及过多关注最敢于表达的员工来抑制阻力，很可能会导致短期的顺从和服从，但代价是<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/decision-downloading/">破坏长期信任</a>。巧妙而尊重地管理阻力需要预先投入时间，让员工参与进来，同时提供前进的动力。好处是：领导者学会更巧妙地影响员工如何解释趋势、事件和决策，并对新出现的问题有更深入的洞察。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ Five-ways-leaders-can-turn-pushback-into-progress/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> ChatGPT 如何帮助经理设计更好的工作角色？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Fangfang Zhang and Sharon K. Parker. <p>张芳芳博士是科廷大学变革性工作设计中心的研究员。她还是 CEPAR（人口老龄化研究卓越中心）研究员。她的研究兴趣包括工作设计、工作重塑、工作未来、资历过高和老龄化。莎伦·K·帕克 (Sharon K. Parker) 是科廷大学约翰·科廷杰出教授、澳大利亚研究委员会获奖者、变革性工作设计中心主任。她是澳大利亚社会科学院和工业与组织心理学会的院士。她是 SMART 模型的创建者和 Thrive at Work 计划的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Today’s leaders are pushing to increase employee engagement and decrease turnover but face a harsh reality: widespread employee burnout. To fight it, managers need to offer employees more healthy and meaningful work. In surveys conducted in the United States by Gallup in 2022, 40% of employees reported that their [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Parker-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>当今的领导者正在努力提高员工敬业度并减少人员流动，但面临着严峻的现实：员工普遍倦怠。为了应对这一问题，管理者需要为员工提供更健康、更有意义的工作。盖洛普 2022 年在美国进行的调查显示，40% 的员工表示，他们的工作对他们的心理健康产生了负面影响，约 30% 的员工表示，他们经常感到倦怠。此外，到 2022 年，美国员工敬业度创下七年来的最低点，盖洛普调查显示，只有 32% 的员工表示自己敬业度很高，17% 的员工表示自己在 2022 年积极脱离敬业度<a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">。1</a>在全球范围内，员工缺乏敬业度估计会给雇主带来损失7.8 万亿美元——相当于全球国内生产总值的 11%。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>脱离和工作压力的根本原因往往在于组织如何设计人们的工作。数十年的广泛研究一致认为，糟糕的工作设计与员工的负面结果有关，包括精神紧张、高流动率、工作不满、生产力下降和学习障碍。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>现在许多公司都在努力做得更好。</p><p></p><p>不幸的是，我们的研究表明，许多管理者缺乏设计高质量工作的必要理解。这就是 ChatGPT 等人工智能技术可以发挥关键作用的地方，它可以弥合管理者的知识差距并帮助设计对员工和组织都有利的高质量工作。然而，对于管理者来说，首先了解使用 ChatGPT 进行工作设计的利弊非常重要。让我们来探讨一下我们的研究为管理者带来的一些启示。</p><h3>管理挑战：平凡且没有成就感的工作</h3><p>哪些因素决定了一份工作是否高质量？ <a href="https://www.futureofworkinstitute.com.au/smart-workdesign">SMART 工作设计模型</a>是 Sharon K. Parker 创建的一个框架，它将高质量工作定义为具有<em>刺激性的</em>工作（具有任务多样性和发展新技能的机会的工作），并融合了<em>掌握</em>（例如角色清晰度和工作反馈） ，是<em>代理性的</em>（例如工作自主性和变革参与），是<em>关系性的</em>（可以获得社会支持和积极的团队合作），并且是<em>可容忍的</em>（具有可管理的工作时间和合理的时间压力水平）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>尽管设计良好的工作有很多好处，但设计​​不当的工作仍然普遍存在。根据盖洛普 2019 年优秀就业调查，只有 40% 的美国人从事具有 SMART 特征的工作。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>另一方面，16% 的人发现自己的工作缺乏基本的 SMART 特征，44% 的人的工作只具备一些令人满意的 SMART 特征。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>当今的管理者缺乏对工作设计的了解可能可以解释这一发现。我们最近进行的一项研究探讨了人们如何为他人设计工作。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>在线模拟（模拟 1）的参与者被要求设计一个行政工作角色。半职工作全部由四项复印和归档任务组成。参与者被要求从 11 项任务列表中选择 4 项额外任务来全职完成这项工作，其中包括 5 项重复性复印和归档任务以及 6 项更有意义和有趣的任务，例如问候访客或帮助同事安排会议。</p><p></p><p>参与者的评分范围为 0 到 4，分数越高表明创造了更具刺激性的工作设计。近一半（45%）的大学管理专业学生和从事公共服务行业的专业人士/经理倾向于从事重复性和单调的工作，这表明在高质量工作设计方面存在知识差距。</p><p>在第二次模拟（模拟 2）中，参与者被要求扮演经理的角色并解决四种场景中的劳动力问题。在每种情况下，工作角色设计显然都很糟糕。为了解决这些问题，参与者评估了他们采取策略的可能性，其中包括“修复工人”方法（将问题归咎于员工）和“修复糟糕的工作设计”方法（承认质量差）。工作设计。</p><p>例如，在一种情况下，一名仓库工作人员尽管经常跑去取货，但在收集产品并将其运送到调度方面始终未能满足 50% 的规定期限。虽然大多数参与者关注的是改进工作设计的选择（例如，“让员工及其同事参与审查，以确定可以更好地组织他们的工作的方式”或“重新组织工作，以便任务不需要”），令人惊讶的是，数量惊人的参与者（40％）仍然选择了旨在固定工人的策略（例如“谨慎观察该人的行为，看看他们移动的速度有多快”）。这些发现证实了我们的发现，即管理者和员工缺乏工作设计知识。</p><h3>生成式人工智能可以提出强有力的工作设计</h3><p>在研究的下一阶段，我们研究了 ChatGPT 等人工智能驱动的工具是否可以帮助管理者做得更好。简短的回答是：ChatGPT 有潜力增强工作设计中的决策。然而，对于管理者来说，了解 ChatGPT 能做什么、不能做什么很重要。</p><p>我们使用 ChatGPT 为行政工作设计模拟（模拟 1）做出假设的工作设计决策。我们运行模拟任务 20 次，每次都在 ChatGPT 中使用新的独立聊天会话并提供相同的提示。生成式人工智能模型始终从提供的列表中选择丰富任务，在创造有趣且有意义的工作方面优于学生和专业人士/经理。 ChatGPT 的表现与工作设计专家的表现相似。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>不同组的工作设计决策得分</h4><p class="caption">当模拟 1 的参与者被要求设计行政工作角色时，45% 的参与者大多选择为工人分配重复且单调的任务（评分从 0 到 4 表示参与者选择的丰富任务的数量）。当模拟 2 的参与者被要求解决四个设计不良的工作角色中的问题时，40% 的人选择了旨在修复工人而不是不良设计的策略（得分从 1 到 5 表示参与者将采用这些策略的程度，1=极不可能，5=极有可能）。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023_1005_Parker_Fig1-1.png" alt="不同组的工作设计决策得分"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>然后，我们要求 ChatGPT 处理模拟 2，解决四种管理人员场景（包括上面提到的理论仓库工人），从列表中选择策略。在每种情况下，ChatGPT 始终选择旨在修复工作设计的策略（有利于员工福祉、积极性和绩效的良好策略），而不是专注于修复员工的策略。与模拟 1 一样，ChatGPT 在专注于解决劳动力问题的工作设计方面优于学生、经理和专业人士。</p><p>然而，ChatGPT 在模拟 2 中的得分不如工作设计专家，这表明需要谨慎对待。例如，在一次针对错过最后期限的仓库工人的会议中，ChatGPT 总体得分为 4，但选择了“当员工和她的同事按时完成任务时，我会给他们奖金”的策略，这忽略了该角色的不合理时间分配。</p><p></p><h3>一大教训：具体提示是关键</h3><p>为了进一步评估 ChatGPT 独立生成建议的能力，我们运行了模拟 2 工作设计任务，但没有提供多项选择解决方案列表。我们在关闭聊天记录功能的新帐户和独立的新聊天中运行每个测试，以便 ChatGPT 的输出不会受到之前输入的影响。</p><p>首先，结果令人担忧。当我们简单地指示人工智能模型在错过最后期限的情况下“提供有效的策略来解决问题”时，ChatGPT 倾向于通过尝试修复工人并创建老式的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-progressive-roots-of-management-science/">泰勒主义工作系统方法来</a>解决问题，例如进行计时和运动研究。例如，ChatGPT 提出了时间管理技能和额外培训等解决方案，以帮助我们命名为 Karen 的仓库员工提高绩效（例如，“重点提高 Karen 在仓库中查找和收集物品的速度和准确性”） 。它还建议提供绩效反馈和激励措施，以激励凯伦更快地行动（例如，“通过将绩效与奖励联系起来，将鼓励凯伦专注于提高速度和效率”）。这些解决方案中的每一个都隐含地假设问题是工人的动机或能力而不是工作设计。</p><p>在得知这种开放式方法并非最佳选择后，我们接下来指示 ChatGPT 使用特定提示来解决相同的场景：“考虑为 Karen 设计一份高质量的工作”； “考虑凯伦的健康、幸福、动力、满意度和工作意义”；和“考虑凯伦的工作设计。”然后，AI 模型提供了与改进 Karen 的工作设计相关的解决方案，包括以下内容：</p><ul><li>审查时间分配和工作量以设定切合实际的时间目标。</li><li>让凯伦参与决策过程，并寻求她对改善工作的意见。</li><li>提供支持性反馈和认可，以提高员工满意度和积极性。</li><li>提供充足的培训和技能发展机会，以增强信心和参与度。</li></ul><p>这些策略将提升凯伦的 SMART 工作设计特征，提高需求的容忍度，增强能动性，提高掌握程度，并使工作更具刺激性。</p><p> ChatGPT 还提出了一些解决方案，例如营造支持性的工作环境、鼓励团队支持和协作、提供职业发展机会以及促进工作与生活的平衡。这些解决方案都与工作设计和幸福感的广泛研究相吻合，将使工作变得“更智能”，从而培养出更健康、更有生产力的员工。</p><p>我们从 ChatGPT 的这个特殊实验中了解到，生成式人工智能可以做出有价值的工作设计决策，但管理者需要提供明确的指示，优先考虑员工的结果。例如，要求ChatGPT“设计高质量的工作”而不是简单地要求“良好的工作设计”可以产生更相关和有效的策略。因此，为了提高ChatGPT生成的策略建议的质量，管理者需要在问题提示中提及具体的、理想的目标，例如高质量的工作；员工的健康、福祉和积极性；和工作的意义。</p><p></p><p>好消息是：不经常使用 ChatGPT 的经理可以学习如何通过 ChatGPT 工具本身编写有效的提示。例如，当被问及“如何制作结构良好且清晰的提示来有效应对工作设计挑战时？” ChatGPT 提供了有关如何编写有效提示的分步指南。 ChatGPT 建议我们确定核心问题并具体化——可以通过使用提示将建议应用于工作设计，例如“设计高质量的工作，增强销售团队的积极团队互动和协作”或“设计有意义的工作”促进员工接受工作中的技术变革。”</p><p>实验还表明，有效的提示需要进行审查和测试。难以编写有效的 ChatGPT 提示的经理可以通过使用诸如“以下提示旨在从工作设计专家的角度向 ChatGPT 寻求建议的提示”来提高自己的技能。请分析并提出改进建议，以便从 ChatGPT 获得可行且实用的建议。”在这种情况下，ChatGPT 将提供更具体的建议，以推动更高质量的输出。</p><h3>给管理者的五个教训</h3><p>为了解决工作角色设计不佳及其有害影响这一普遍问题，采用创新解决方案至关重要。根据我们的研究，ChatGPT 已成为一种很有前途的人工智能工具，可以帮助管理者设计更健康、更高效的工作。但它不是万能药，需要明智地使用。我们对管理者的建议：</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 无法替代培训。</strong>管理者需要<em>意识到</em>，糟糕的工作设计可能会产生员工问题，而工作设计反过来又会影响员工的福祉、积极性和工作意义。这意味着，在使用ChatGPT设计更好的工作之前，管理者仍然需要进行工作设计理念的基础培训。要开始了解此主题，请参阅相关文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-well-designed-work-makes-us-smarter/">精心设计的工作如何让我们变得更聪明</a>”和<a href="https://www.smartworkdesign.com.au/">SMART 工作设计网站</a>。</p><p><strong>管理者需要获得支持，以实现创建精心设计的工作的目标。</strong>管理者需要有<em>动力</em>为员工创造更好的就业机会。这意味着管理者本身需要将创建健康的员工工作角色视为合法且重要的责任，而不是只关注底线。例如，如果管理者纯粹根据生产力成就获得晋升，他们就没有太多动力为团队设计 SMART 工作。</p><p><strong>管理者本身也需要健康的工作。</strong>管理者需要足够的时间来关注员工的工作设计得如何。这意味着管理者自己的工作必须是<em>可以忍受的</em>，并且没有过多的时间压力。</p><p></p><p><strong>管理者需要学习ChatGPT提示技巧。</strong>应鼓励管理者使用生成式人工智能来帮助应对工作设计挑战，但他们需要关于如何有效使用它的清晰而全面的指导。例如，管理者在向 ChatGPT 寻求工作设计建议时需要具体并提及员工福祉和动机等目标。</p><p> <strong>ChatGPT 将增强而不是取代人们设计更好的工作。</strong>与模拟不同，现实生活中的工作设计情况通常具有模糊性和复杂性，并且存在许多可能影响结果的变量。真实情况需要对背景、人类情感、社会动态以及政治和道德考虑因素有深入的了解，所有这些对于像 ChatGPT 这样的人工智能工具来说要完全掌握都是具有挑战性的。我们建议使用 ChatGPT 作为人类管理者的<em>补充</em>，而不是<em>替代</em>它们。</p><p>通过将 ChatGPT 的建议与人类专业知识相结合，组织可以提高员工敬业度、工作满意度和整体绩效。在管理者和人工智能之间实现这种协同作用可以为工作设计和员工体验的更美好未来铺平道路。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-chatgpt-can-and-cant-help-managers-design-better-job-roles/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>文化在推动变革中的作用</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jonathan Knowles, B. Tom Hunsaker, and Melanie Hughes. <p>乔纳森·诺尔斯 (Jonathan Knowles) 是咨询公司 Type 2 Consulting 的创始人。 B. Tom Hunsaker 是亚利桑那州立大学雷鸟全球管理学院战略与领导力临床教授。梅兰妮·休斯 (Melanie Hughes) 是穆迪、American Eagle 和 Tribune Media 的前首席人力资源官。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Culture is often described as “how we do things around here” — a passive reflection of legacy norms and behaviors. It’s more helpful to think of culture as the nervous system of an organization. In biology, the central nervous system is the pathway by which thoughts in our brains are translated into actions by our [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Knowles-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p>文化通常被描述为“我们在这里做事的方式”——传统规范和行为的被动反映。将文化视为组织的神经系统更有帮助。 In biology, the central nervous system is the pathway by which thoughts in our brains are translated into actions by our muscles, and how our experience of acting in the world updates our brain&#39;s understanding of the world. In organizations, this means thinking of culture as the transmission mechanism by which a company both communicates its intended strategy to the front lines and receives feedback and intelligence from the field about whether the strategy is achieving the intended outcomes in the market.</p><p> This nervous system metaphor illuminates the factors behind two of the most common reasons given for business failure: “We had a great strategy but failed to execute it” (a failure in the communication from the center to the field) or “Our leaders surrounded themselves with people who were afraid to tell them how the business was really performing” (a failure to relay important feedback and intelligence from the field). Both are examples of the failure to create an effective transmission mechanism from thought to action and back again.</p><p></p><p> A strategic approach to culture involves an active effort to create the environment and infrastructure to promote the necessary information flow between strategy and execution — treating them as complementary components of purposeful doing. These tools can include town halls, customer site visits, postmortems on lost bids, employee engagement surveys and any number of other mechanisms that facilitate the exchange of valuable information about what is (or is not) working. These tools nurture a culture of contextual awareness and adaptability that enables the business to perform better in its current environment and to prepare for future success.</p><p></p><p> There are certain aspects of culture that are universally desirable and others whose value is more context-dependent. When Donald Sull and Charles Sull analyzed 1.4 million employee reviews on Glassdoor, they <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/10-things-your-corporate-culture-needs-to-get-right/">identified four key factors</a> that contribute to a positive corporate culture (respect, leadership, compensation/benefits, and job security). But when organizational change is the imperative, this requires deliberately adding context-dependent factors to the culture.</p><p> The importance of adaptation has been the defining theme of our earlier articles about <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">strategy</a> ,<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/effective-innovation-begins-with-strategic-direction/">innovation</a> , and <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-change-means-changing-how-you-lead/">leadership</a> . To illustrate how different change objectives require different choices about culture, we&#39;ll draw on the corporate human resources leadership experiences of one of the authors (Melanie Hughes) across her career. At three different companies, she used three different strategies first to determine the change need and then to identify the characteristics of an effective culture to operationalize this change priority.</p><h3> Identify the Organization&#39;s Change Priority</h3><p> One of the most important — but often overlooked — responsibilities of HR is to analyze what aspects of the corporate culture are enabling the company to perform well in its current environment and what aspects are inhibiting its ability to act in the way and/or with the speed that the context requires.</p><p> The first step in this process is investigating the type of change that the business, unit, or team should be trying to achieve. As we described in “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-essence-of-strategy-is-now-how-to-change/">The Essence of Strategy Is Now How to Change</a> ,” there are three approaches to making such changes:</p><ul><li> Reinforce magnitude: Refine and deepen the actions that are contributing to high levels of relevance for key stakeholders and distinctiveness from competition.</li><li> Reimagine activity: Refresh the approaches, channels, and tools being used to pursue the current strategy.</li><li> Rethink direction: Reinvent the business model to deliver the levels of relevance and distinctiveness necessary for an economically viable business.</li></ul><p> Based on its understanding of the desired form of change, HR can identify the mechanisms to achieve the desired results, which staff members are best placed to play the role of change agent (those tasked with infusing new elements into the culture), and who can play the role of culture carrier (demonstrating how these new elements can be integrated with the legacy elements of the culture that are being maintained).</p><p> We review each of the change types and what kinds of tools and actions can best enable each one, drawing from <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/melaniehughes/details/experience/">Hughes&#39;s experiences</a> as the chief administrative officer at Gilt Groupe and the chief human resources officer (CHRO) at Moody&#39;s and Tribune Media.</p><p></p><h4> Change Type 1: Reinforce Magnitude</h4><p> Launched in 2007, New York-based Gilt Groupe was a pioneer of the luxury goods flash sale. The company was in hypergrowth mode from 2009 to 2012, when Hughes was the chief administrative officer: expanding from women&#39;s clothing to offering menswear and travel as well, launching operations in Japan, raising capital at a valuation of more than $1 billion in 2011, and actively planning for an initial public offering. With Gilt Groupe as a recognized market leader in the fashion space and a preferred partner of luxury goods manufacturers, the change priority was to reinforce magnitude — that is, expand the actions that were making the company relevant and distinctive — by replicating the successful core business model in new categories.</p><p> The central challenge was determining how to combine the entrepreneurial, growth-focused orientation of the existing culture with the knowledge sharing and repeatable processes necessary to support expansion into multiple new categories and manage their different stages of development. Two of the key enablers of this change were revised messaging by the CEO in the company&#39;s all-hands meetings and adjustments to the incentive schemes for executives and managers.</p><p> In both cases, the prior focus on growth alone was replaced by an emphasis on manageable growth, efficiency, and profitability. The CEO assumed the role of principal change agent, focusing on stories that celebrated costs avoided and efficiencies achieved, not just revenues won. The incentive programs were adjusted, with the focus on the performance of the individual businesses shifting instead to a balance of contributions to “Gilt corporate” and individual business performance. Specific individuals were identified as culture carriers because they had already demonstrated the behaviors of knowledge sharing, mentorship, and effective delegation — three key aspects of the new culture. These individuals were given increased responsibilities and promotions as visible signs of recognition (in addition to nonpublic compensation increases) to underscore the behaviors that the company now valued.</p><p> These actions paved the way for organizational changes that the previous culture would have resisted as bureaucratization infringing on the autonomy of the individual businesses. Instead, the centralization of certain services and infrastructure (such as marketing, development, finance, and recruiting) was accepted as the means to enable the businesses to scale faster.</p><h4> Change Type 2: Reimagine Activity</h4><p> The context of Hughes&#39;s most recent role, as CHRO at Moody&#39;s (2017 to 2021), was, in contrast, one in which reimagining activity was the appropriate stance, given the objective of innovating the approaches and tools being used to pursue the existing strategy. Moody&#39;s comprised a highly successful but mature ratings business and a fast-growing analytics business. There was rising cultural tension as each organization championed the merits of its approach to risk, innovation, customers, and staffing. Recognizing the incompatibility of these modes of operating, the CEO and president of each business worked with HR leadership on a program designed to evolve the corporate culture while also establishing an operating infrastructure and a performance management system specifically designed to support the needs of Moody&#39;s Analytics.</p><p> Several organizational initiatives were developed to support the change. Among them were expanding the corporate values to include elements such as speed and innovation (primarily associated with the analytics business) and to celebrate examples of those values in communications to employees and on investor calls. Leadership development programs were established to cross-train managers on the critical skills for each line of business and identify change agents who could cross-seed desired behaviors into each business. A new talent-planning process called Talent to Value identified the roles with the greatest strategic impact on each business and the skills required to perform those roles. This enabled leaders to understand which internal candidates were truly qualified for roles and where they needed to look for external talent to fill critical roles and support the new culture.</p><p> The CEO explicitly articulated a change from the previous “promote from within” culture, emphasizing the benefits of a broader and more diverse employee base to the performance of both businesses. These communications included LinkedIn posts from the CEO, signaling both internally and externally what was required to progress in the modern Moody&#39;s. This messaging was reinforced by the publicity given to new hires and internal promotions, emphasizing how these employees embodied the desired skills and traits described in the Talent to Value effort.</p><p> Reimagining these activities supported the transition of Moody&#39;s to a multibusiness firm with cultures, structures, and skills sets appropriate for each entity. The stock grew 60% in two years, reflecting a strong profit performance of the legacy Moody&#39;s ratings business combined with a higher multiple attributed to the growth potential of the analytics business.</p><h4> Change Type 3: Rethink Direction</h4><p> Hughes&#39;s time as CHRO at Tribune Media (2013 to 2016) represented an entirely different challenge. Tribune Media had gone through the largest media industry bankruptcy in US history in 2008, and as it emerged from four years of bankruptcy proceedings in 2012, the priority was to rethink its direction by establishing a business based on viable economics. A creative and action-oriented CEO was recruited for this purpose. The company adopted a strategy to spin off the legacy print journalism assets into a separate company (Tribune Publishing), invest heavily to grow the digital media and content-creation capabilities of Tribune Media, and make selective acquisitions in the broadcast business to build the necessary economies of scale.</p><p> For a business that had been beaten down by years in the bankruptcy courts and a relentless focus on cost cutting, the new strategy necessitated a complete cultural reboot. Certain behavioral norms — aversion to risk, a focus on the short term, reluctance to take on additional responsibility — had become ingrained during the bankruptcy years and needed to be reset. The CEO and Hughes recruited a new executive team ready to establish the type of culture required to support the new strategy. They, in turn, brought in new leaders and employees to start to transform their teams. The leadership team worked together to identify “Trib traits” — the set of values and competencies that would encourage new behaviors, which included “curious and courageous,” “competing with passion,” and “exemplifying leadership.”</p><p></p><p> The Trib traits became the blueprint for recruiting new employees and for a new performance evaluation and rewards system. The latter now tied fully 50% of managerial bonuses to the demonstration of competencies, to emphasize that how things got done was as important as the outcome. (Historically, bonuses had been entirely based on financial results.) This shift was reinforced in newly established televised town halls, where the CEO spoke about doing the <em>right</em> thing rather than doing the <em>thing</em> right to give employees the license to venture away from the safe path and experiment with new ways of operating — as was appropriate for a business emerging from bankruptcy and competing in the dynamic environment of digital media and entertainment.</p><p> As the above cases illustrate, the enablers of cultural change vary according to the type of change that an organization is trying to achieve. The table below summarizes how the type of change needed informs a consistent set of culture actions to be taken. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive </h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Culture Impact Area</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reinforce Magnitude</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Reimagine Activity</th><th style="width:25%;line-height:1.5;"> Rethink Direction</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>Definition of strategic goal</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine and double down on sources of existing advantage</p></td><td><p> Adapt approach to deliver greater value</p></td><td><p> Identify a new basis for a viable business model</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of communication</strong></p></td><td><p> Reaffirm existing beliefs; encourage consistency</p></td><td><p> Evolve core beliefs; encourage experimentation</p></td><td><p> Revisit core beliefs; encourage new ways of thinking</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Performance and risk metrics</strong></p></td><td><p> Reinforce current market position; minimize risk</p></td><td><p> Experiment around the core; be selective in terms of risk tolerance</p></td><td><p> Reinvent; iterate rapidly; have a high risk tolerance</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Changes to organizational structure</strong></p></td><td><p> Refine to optimize efficiency and minimize disturbance</p></td><td><p> Realign to support new products and customer priorities</p></td><td><p> Restructure to focus on areas where a sustainable advantage can be achieved</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Priority for talent acquisition</strong></p></td><td><p> Deepen expertise</p></td><td><p> Expand expertise</p></td><td><p> Redefine expertise</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Focus of learning and development</strong></p></td><td><p> Emphasize skills for leading and delivering operational excellence</p></td><td><p> Make focused investments in leadership and high-demand technical skills</p></td><td><p> Make an enterprisewide investment in culture change</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong>Basis for rewards and recognition</strong></p></td><td><p> Incentivize growth and efficiency initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize redesign initiatives/outcomes</p></td><td><p> Incentivize novel and disruptive initiatives/outcomes </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Knowles_Culture_Essay_Table_mobile-fallback-1.png" alt="Effective Cultures Are Context-Adaptive" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p></p><p></p><p> Culture is the enabler of business strategy. It either facilitates or inhibits the speed and reliability with which information flows within an organization, determining how well the company understands and responds to its environment.</p><p> Businesses are collaborative human endeavors that require the harnessing of the skills and shared beliefs of the individuals within them. Culture is the nervous system that promotes cohesion and integrates strategy and execution into purposeful doing. While certain aspects of a healthy culture might be universal (respect for individuals, ethical leadership, fair rewards for work performed), the effective management of culture is also contextual — involving the deliberate introduction of elements that enable the business to evolve to reflect the need for reinforcing magnitude, reimagining activity, or rethinking direction.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-role-of-culture-in-enabling-change/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Burden of Proof for Corporate Sustainability Is Too High</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) is a globally recognized expert on how to build resilient, profitable companies that help people and planet thrive. He is coauthor of <cite>Net Positive: How Courageous Companies Thrive by Giving More Than They Take</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people, respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of Fortune magazine asserted that companies were “swapping exuberance for efficiency” and pointed out that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Winston-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Tang Yau Hoong/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Throughout 2023, tech companies have continually laid off workers. The year started with Amazon and Salesforce<a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3685936/tech-layoffs-in-2023-a-timeline.html?page=2">cutting 18,000 and 8,000 people</a> , respectively, and sector momentum grew into the spring. An article in the April/May 2023 issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> magazine asserted that companies were “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-finance-crypto-making-seismic-110000390.html">swapping exuberance for efficiency</a> ” and pointed out that they had collectively laid off more than 150,000 people since January. (By August, that number was up to <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/09/07/tech-industry-layoffs-2023/">nearly 225,000</a> .)</p><p> An article in that same issue of <cite>Fortune</cite> focused on Salesforce, asking whether there was a conflict between the company&#39;s layoffs and CEO Marc Benioff&#39;s commitment to empathetic leadership and sustainability. That&#39;s a fair question, but the article went further, declaring that Benioff&#39;s dilemma could “serve as a referendum on the whole <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/m-willing-bullets-marc-benioff-153000800.html">model of stakeholder capitalism</a> .” If that&#39;s true, then why aren&#39;t the collective woes across the tech industry, which another article declared “ <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-150-000-people-let-153000599.html">a confession of bad management</a> ,” a referendum on <em>shareholder</em> capitalism?</p><p></p><p> There&#39;s a serious inconsistency in how the business world sees sustainability. Whenever a company that prioritizes sustainability gets in trouble, people say the leaders took their eye off the ball. But when companies stumble while pursuing the “normal” strategy of maximizing profits above all — which is, by the way, wrongly implied to be the opposite of sustainability — their troubles are rarely blamed on that single-minded focus.</p><p></p><h3> Sustainability as Scapegoat</h3><p> The burden of proof on sustainability became crystal clear when, in 2021, activist investors and the board ousted the CEO of Danone, the French multinational food company, in a dramatic move that made headlines across the world. CEO Emmanuel Faber had faced harsh criticism for the company&#39;s financial performance versus that of its competitors, but here&#39;s how some of the press approached it at the time: The <cite>Financial Times</cite> editorial board&#39;s take: “ <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/668d9544-28db-4ad7-9870-1f6671623ac5">Danone: A Case Study in the Pitfalls of Purpose</a> .” <cite>Forbes</cite> : “ <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/frankvangansbeke/2021/03/20/sustainability-and-the-downfall-of-danone-ceo-faber-12/?sh=7dc8835b16de">Sustainability and the Downfall of Danone CEO Faber</a> .” <cite>Time</cite> : “ <a href="https://time.com/6121684/emmanuel-faber-danone-interview/">A Top CEO Was Ousted After Making His Company More Environmentally Conscious. Now He&#39;s Speaking Out</a> .”</p><p> Unfortunately, this two-year-old story has legs. I was recently speaking to leaders of a big consumer packaged goods company, and one of the execs expressed skepticism about sustainability, pointing to what had happened at Danone (and at Unilever, which has also <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-under-pressure-show-sustainability-focus-is-good-business-2022-02-09/">taken heat about its sustainability focus</a> ).</p><p> The finger-pointing at sustainability is, if anything, accelerating in some circles; to use modern parlance, it just triggers some people. Without diving into the morass of the anti-ESG movement, I think it&#39;s clear that some prominent voices will blame sustainability for <em>any</em> corporate trouble. When Silicon Valley Bank went under, for example, some pundits and politicians hit the airwaves to claim, ludicrously, that it was because the company had <a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/columnist/2023/03/15/silicon-valley-bank-failure-republicans-blame-diversity-woke/11472710002/">mentioned its diversity and inclusion efforts</a> in its proxy statement.</p><p> Blaming sustainability for financial woes just rings true for most execs. But <em>why</em> ?</p><p> I believe it&#39;s about a deeply flawed base assumption: Sustainability, even as companies embrace it like never before, is still generally assumed to be a drag on earnings and to <em>always</em> add to costs. But that&#39;s never been remotely true.</p><p> The idea that sustainability is a trade-off or is incompatible with financial responsibility is false. Some of the companies most famously focused on sustainability, such as Walmart and Ikea, are relentless cost cutters and have fit their environmental and social efforts into that strategy. These companies know that sustainability not only can cut expenses but also slashes risk, drives innovation and revenues, and builds intangible or brand value. It&#39;s not true that running a business in a sustainable fashion always costs more, although new ways of operating don&#39;t always pay off quickly. And, to be fair, the sustainability community — and that includes me — has sometimes implied as much.</p><p></p><p> But let&#39;s go back to the burden on sustainability and try a quick mental exercise. If a focus on sustainability causes failures, then are the companies that focus only on shareholder profits always successful?当然不是。 The failure rate for companies is high: Roughly 50% of <a href="https://www.chamberofcommerce.org/small-business-statistics/">small businesses close</a> within about five years. Even among the Fortune 500 giants, failure is the norm. Of the original list in 1955, <a href="https://www.aei.org/carpe-diem/fortune-500-firms-1955-v-2017-only-12-remain-thanks-to-the-creative-destruction-that-fuels-economic-prosperity/">only 60</a> of them survived until the late 2010s. Obsessing over shareholder value didn&#39;t save 88% of the biggest companies.</p><p> All companies, at some point, emphasize a strategic focus. Consider a sample list of core strategies — some fads, some lasting additions to the management arsenal — that companies have embraced across a century: mass production, specialization, product differentiation, quality, safety, customer satisfaction, employee happiness, cost cutting, reengineering, agile and lean development, data-driven decision-making. Companies that embraced these things often outcompeted others, but none of those core strategies was ever the <em>only</em> factor in their success.</p><p> Companies rise and fall for diverse reasons. The most celebrated success stories, like those profiled in the influential book <cite><a href="https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/bhag.html">Built to Last</a></cite> , can also face scrutiny over time. Decline occurs when companies fail to adapt to sectoral transformations (Blockbuster), neglect technological shifts (Kodak), or lose brand relevance when they fail to attract younger consumers as their core audience ages (a fate shared by numerous apparel and consumer packaged goods brands).</p><p> So, in that context, what really happened with Danone? Is it possible that sustainability was the problem?当然。 But perhaps it was something more nuanced. In his book <cite><a href="https://www.harpercollinsleadership.com/books/purpose-profit/ ">Purpose &amp; Profit</a></cite> , Harvard professor George Serafeim analyzed how Danone was doing at the time of the CEO&#39;s ouster and found that the company was underperforming peers not just on financial outcomes but also on <em>sustainability</em> outcomes: The intentions and plans were solid, but the results lagged. Serafeim concluded, “Maybe Danone is underperforming not in spite of its focus on impact but because it&#39;s failing to generate enough impact.” Whether this conclusion is correct is the right debate to be having rather than simply chalking up the company&#39;s problems to sustainability.</p><h3> Stop the Blame Game</h3><p> The good news is that sustainability must now be mainstream or attention-seekers wouldn&#39;t find it worth attacking. It&#39;s becoming core to how business is done, with evidence everywhere — signs like increased regulation and transparency demands from stakeholders, sustainability reports issued by nearly every large company, and countless courses added to business school curricula globally.</p><p></p><p> Given how widespread sustainability efforts are now, perhaps it&#39;s time to do something paradoxical. Could we make sustainability in business more important by lowering the intensity of focus? This does not mean going light on the issues sustainability is grounded in — like climate change and inequality, which are, quite literally, deadly serious — but instead just turning down the heat. Can we normalize sustainability and stop blaming it for anything that goes wrong at companies with a purpose and vision? And can we stop crediting it for being the only factor that drives some companies&#39; success? I&#39;m willing to stipulate, for example, that sustainability darling Patagonia also succeeds because it has <a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/travel-backpacks/patagonia-black-hole-mini-mlc-travel-backpack-review-a1476285024/">kick-ass products</a> that last a long time and a culture that <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Overview/Working-at-Patagonia-EI_IE5474.11,20.htm">attracts employees</a> and customers.</p><p> It&#39;s time to truly embed sustainability into business and treat it like any other unquestioned part of operations (think HR, R&amp;D, and safety). Sustainability need not be the scapegoat or the hero. It can just be a powerful way to do business and stay relevant in a fast-changing world … and help society and the planet thrive.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-burden-of-proof-for-corporate-sustainability-is-too-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Want More Clarity on Generative AI? Experiment Widely</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) is a professor of management practice at London Business School and founder of HSM Advisory. Her most recent book is <cite>Redesigning Work: How to Transform Your Organization and Make Hybrid Work for Everyone</cite> (MIT Press, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT’s release in November 2022, more than 1 million people (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Gratton-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Thomas Kuhlenbeck / Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> The launch of generative AI represents an era-defining moment. Never before have so many people become so excited by a technology program. Within five days of ChatGPT&#39;s release in November 2022, <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/12/05/technology/chatgpt-ai-twitter.html">more than 1 million people</a> (including me) had logged on to try it out. If financial investments are a predictor of growth, then the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.de/~/media/mckinsey/locations/europe%20and%20middle%20east/deutschland/news/presse/2023/2023-06-14%20mgi%20genai%20report%2023/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier-vf.pdf">$12 billion invested in generative AI</a> in the first five months of 2023 shows the depth of commitment.</p><p> To get a sense of current momentum and direction, I ran a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=74OaRCKn92k">research webinar last month on the impact of generative AI</a> on the workplace. Some 260 executives from organizations in Australia, Europe, Japan, and the United States joined me to describe their current use of generative AI in human capital domains. What I heard is that generative AI is a top priority for many CEOs, experiments abound alongside ambiguity, and organizations are already beginning to use artificial intelligence to augment their human capital strategies. I&#39;ll share more details about those findings in a moment.</p><p></p><p> I wanted to hear directly from practitioners because it seems to me that, as with the previous era-defining event — the COVID-19 pandemic — and its <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/making-sense-of-the-future/">impact on the workplace</a> , imagining what is ahead with this new technology is a tough call. As with the emergence of hybrid work and work-from-home initiatives in response to the pandemic, figuring out the right approaches to generative AI is a process replete with ambiguity, experiments, and changes of mind. In other words, it is a learning process driven both by the initiative of individuals and the strategies of organizations.</p><p> Like the response to the pandemic, debate and action around gen AI are moving fast.</p><p></p><p> Two facts are emerging. First, this is a rapidly developing technology. The size of investment gives a sense of this. So, too, does the volume of experimentation: One executive told me, “We have created a head of generative AI with a role simply to moderate and make sense of the hundreds of experiments we have running on any day.” Second, unlike previous workplace technologies, generative AI is not being positioned as a substitute for routine tasks — either analytical tasks, like keeping records or providing repetitive customer-oriented services, or manual tasks, like picking and sorting products or performing routine assembly. Instead, it&#39;s a technology with the potential to hit at the heart of nonroutine analytical work. This is knowledge work, such as forming a hypothesis, creating content, recommending medical diagnostics, or making a sales pitch. The source of this impact is generative AI&#39;s growing capacity to understand natural language. Around 25% of the total work time of knowledge workers is spent on the kinds of creative tasks that generative AI is beginning to get good at.</p><p> Yet, like during the early days of the pandemic and hybrid work, much is currently conjecture. There will certainly be pushback, changes of direction, and believers and resisters, just as there has been throughout the ongoing debate about hybrid work. There will be many experiments before leaders begin to develop their own narratives about how best to support their workers in these complex and ambiguous times.</p><p></p><h3> Experiments, Projections, and the Great Ambiguity</h3><p> The potential for generative AI to very quickly have a real impact in the workplace is fueling the attention it&#39;s getting. Consider the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier#key-insights">McKinsey report on generative AI</a> published in June 2023. McKinsey asked a group of technology experts at what point they believed generative AI would substitute for a number of human tasks. It then compared those estimates with pre-gen AI projections made in 2017 about when human performance might be achievable by technology. What is striking is the extent to which their estimated timelines have contracted. For one work task, for example — “coordination with multiple agents” — the experts in 2017 estimated a timeline of substitution that ranged from 2035 to 2058. Today, they estimate that happening from 2023 to 2035. That feels very soon. As important, in 2017, the estimate for when we&#39;d see technology achieve human-level performance for the task of “creativity” was 2030 to 2045; today, the projection is from 2025 to 2030. These dates are for tasks where technology performance is expected to match median human performance. For top-quartile human performance, the timelines are pushed out somewhat.</p><p> How do we make sense of this? What I learned from observing the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-increase-collaborative-productivity-in-a-pandemic/">impact of the pandemic on work</a> is that watching closely and asking questions of people in the field about their current lived reality is a useful practice. So my Sept. 19 webinar was essentially a listening process. Many executives came from human capital functions, so their interest was primarily in the people side of their business.</p><p> I began by asking where generative AI currently sits on the leadership agenda. Over half of attendees (52%) agreed with the statement “It is a CEO priority where leadership teams are discussing impact.” Only 13% said “It is not yet on the agenda in any meaningful way.” This is a topic that is definitely consuming bandwidth at the top levels of organizations across the world.</p><p></p><p> Generative AI is at the top of leaders&#39; agendas — but what about the scope of debate? What issues are coming forward as people talk through its consequences? For the webinar, I focused on a central aspect of this question: machines and creativity. The technologists in the McKinsey panel estimated that human creativity will be achieved by generative AI within the time span of 2025 to 2030, but what did this group of leaders believe? This, for me, is an important question because the McKinsey panelists are technology experts. I have a hunch that people like them will overestimate technological progress, whereas people like me (psychologists) will overestimate human progress.</p><p> What is fascinating is the lack of agreement among webinar attendees about whether they think human creativity at the top quartile will be achieved by gen AI from 2023 to 2030: Just 10% strongly agreed, while 34% agreed, 22% neither agreed or disagreed, 30% disagreed, and 4% strongly disagreed. I ran a Menti (a quick survey at the website Mentimeter) to collect participants&#39; real-time thoughts and asked why they had come to their conclusions. Within seconds, more than 80 comments had emerged: Those who agreed pointed out that creativity can be broken down into logical steps; that creativity sits on a lot of data; that prompts will be more important than AI; and that use cases, such as songs, already demonstrate creativity. Those who disagreed described how generative AI would augment, not substitute for, creative people and asserted that creativity was about empathy and vulnerability, that humans can generate new ideas, while AI pulls from the past, and that governments will provide regulation. Those who did not know said there are simply too many unknown unknowns.</p><p> For me, the takeaway here is the sheer richness of conversation and variance in opinions about generative AI. These are debates we need to be open about and continue to have.</p><p> I wondered, of course, how generative AI is currently being experimented with and used. My interest is in the human capital agenda and how generative AI will impact the everyday experiences of workers. One of the “promises” of AI, according to the McKinsey report, is a productivity boost from the automation of a wide variety of activities. For knowledge workers, this will come by technology either substituting for or augmenting tasks such as creating connections, retrieving stored data, personalizing content, automating activities, increasing the speed of response, and collaborating.</p><p> I asked about the current velocity of the use of generative AI in three human capital domains: talent development (like recruitment, induction, and career management), productivity (like skills training and managing collaboration), and change management (like internal knowledge management). I was interested in the current use of generative AI in each domain and the use cases. Of course, the data set of attendees comprised self-selected people who had an interest in generative AI, but still, what is clear is that there are many, many experiments currently underway.</p><p></p><p> The human capital domain with the greatest reported use of generative AI right now is “internal knowledge management.” Forty-six percent of attendees said they are experimenting in this sphere, with use cases such as creating communications, conducting market research analysis, finding resources and competencies, and engaging in employee listening. Almost as many attendees (44%) reported using gen AI for recruitment, with use cases such as creating job advertisements, developing simple approval flows, and onboarding new hires. About a third of attendees (34%) said they&#39;re using gen AI for skills training, with use cases that include self-directed learning, the creation of learning content, and virtual reality-based training. And 23% said they&#39;re using the technology for assessment and feedback, with use cases such as developing bespoke assessments, improving performance feedback, designing career paths, and creating chatbots for employees.</p><p> I feel that what I captured in this research webinar is a sense of the sheer depth of conversation and experimentation taking place right now across the world. How to think about and use generative AI is being debated in the C-suite as use cases are being created and tough questions (like the relationship between machines and creativity) are being debated. For organizations to be aligned with this emerging narrative, it is imperative that they experiment freely and observe closely.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/want-more-clarity-on-generative-ai-experiment-widely/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sound Business: The Promise of Audio Machine Learning Technologies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mark Purdy. <p>Mark Purdy ( <a href="https://twitter.com/mjpurdyecon">@mjpurdyecon</a> ) is managing director of Purdy &amp; Associates, an independent economics and technology research company.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Purdy-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Sounds are everywhere — the chatter and babble of humans and animals, the whirring and thrumming of machines, the background hum of the natural environment, and the murmur of bees on a summer day. These sounds provide crucial input to our decision-making, whether as pedestrians crossing the road or as engineers testing the safety of a vehicle or machine.</p><p> But until recently, the systematic analysis of sounds in dynamic situations — a busy train station, a shopping mall, or an urban park, for example — has been difficult due to the sheer number of complex acoustic signals interacting at once. But this is now changing, thanks to major advances in sensor technology and deep learning algorithms that can harvest enormous quantities of acoustic input and rapidly extract key information.</p><p></p><p> Two branches of sound-related machine learning are emerging: one focused on the detection and analysis of sounds and the other on the AI-powered creation of sounds. Both have significant potential for business and societal value creation. In fact, according to one estimate, the <a href="https://www.astuteanalytica.com/industry-report/audio-ai-recognition-market">global market for AI audio-recognition technologies</a> is set to more than triple, from $4.1 billion in 2021 to $14.1 billion by 2030.</p><p> Deep learning algorithms are now being used to pioneer innovations across a diverse range of industries and sectors, such as these applications of sound detection and analysis:</p><p> <strong>Commercial and household security.</strong> Every year, US businesses and consumers spend billions of dollars protecting buildings and other physical assets. Smart home devices, such as Amazon&#39;s Echo, already use AI-driven voice recognition technology to authenticate different users and provide personalized entertainment and shopping experiences. But now AI systems&#39; sensors and deep learning algorithms can analyze nonvoice ambient sounds from every part of an office, a factory, or a military facility, distinguishing between innocuous sounds and those that may indicate an emerging threat, such as breaking glass.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Health care.</strong> AI sound technologies could transform many areas of health care, particularly by enabling low-cost, rapid diagnoses of diseases in their early stages. In health care, they could be used to provide real-time measurements for an array of biometric data, such as heart rate, blood pressure, respiration rate, and stress level. Deep learning has been used to extract and classify the <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34433880/">“crackles” and “wheezes”</a> of different lung diseases. <a href="https://www.cochl.ai/">Cochl</a> , a South Korean startup, is pioneering AI applications to rapidly identify health problems based on the coughs and sneezes of patients. Such early-warning systems could prove to be pivotal in the fight against COVID-19 and future virus outbreaks.</p><p> <strong>Hearables.</strong> Acoustic deep learning technologies are being pioneered in the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/03/2681513/0/en/Exploring-the-Global-Hearable-Market-Size-Is-Estimated-to-Exceed-96-53-Billion-by-2030-At-an-Exponential-Growth-Rate-of-16-74-Revenue-and-Market-Share-Projections-from-2022-to-2030.html">“hearables” market</a> — which includes headphones, earphones, and other listening devices — to improve people&#39;s listening experience. Such technologies can <a href="https://edtechmagazine.com/higher/article/2022/01/hearables-combine-machine-learning-and-microchips-smart-listening">screen out unwanted noise</a> or alert users to potential dangers, such as when someone is wearing earphones while jogging near traffic. Machine learning algorithms can be used to curate listening content to different contexts, such as by playing more relaxing or softer sounds when breathing signals indicate signs of stress, or more stirring content when the user is exercising.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Retail and leisure industries.</strong> Machine learning technologies can now recognize individuals through the sounds of their <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1809.08783.pdf">footsteps</a> by isolating these distinctive footfall echoes from background noises and the sounds of other pedestrians. Sound-based gait-recognition technologies offer significant advantages over other surveillance systems, given that they work even in poor lighting conditions and are less intrusive than facial recognition, computer vision, or biometric identification systems.</p><p> One of the biggest potential applications of this technology is in footfall-intensive industries such as retail. Sound-based footfall recognition can be used to recognize returning customers and help identify linger points on the shopper&#39;s journey — places where they pause to compare different products or respond to particular discounts or promotions — or pinpoint the time sensitivity of customers at different times of the day or week, based on the rapidity of footsteps.</p><p> <strong>Predictive maintenance and early-warning systems.</strong> Deep learning algorithms can analyze acoustic signals such as noise pressure and reverberations from machines and engine parts to assess wear and tear and predict when a particular part is likely to need replacing. NASA has used sound-sensing algorithms to monitor the functioning of equipment aboard the <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/research/experiments/explorer/Investigation.html?#id=7860">International Space Station</a> . Deep learning algorithms are being used to classify underwater acoustic signals to potentially develop an early-warning system for <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-021-02483-w">deep-sea earthquakes and tsunamis</a> .</p><p> <strong>Marketing and media content production.</strong> Speech-to-text technologies have been around for some time, but the reverse is now happening with the growth of AI-powered text-to-speech or <a href="https://www.cs.unc.edu/~yipin/pub/cvpr2018.pdf">video-to-sound technologies</a> . <a href="https://audiostack.ai/">AudioStack</a> , a UK-based startup, provides AI-enabled audio creation, drawing on a database of more than 600 voices in more than 60 languages. Use cases include generating audio ads with different regional nuances, music, or voice tones, or generating synthetic or cloned voices for podcasts or narrated news flashes based on textual content. The algorithm that <a href="https://deepzen.io/">DeepZen</a> uses for artificial voice creation from text is able to infer different emotional tones from the content, such as excitement, enthusiasm, or comfort. <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2002.10981.pdf?utm_source=thenewstack&utm_medium=website&utm_campaign=platform">AutoFoley</a> was developed to replicate the role of Foley artists, who add audio effects — such as the gallop of a horse or footsteps on a staircase — to movies. Applications like these have huge potential in industries such as gaming, marketing, and publishing, where <a href="https://speechify.com/blog/what-is-the-voice-over-actor-market-size">global demand for voiceovers</a> is forecast to grow by 9% per year to reach $2.3 billion by 2026.</p><h3> Recommendations for Business Leaders</h3><p> The rise of AI-based sound detection and creation will raise several challenges for businesses, especially in the intellectual property arena. To capitalize on the opportunities and mitigate the risks, business leaders should consider these recommendations:</p><p> <strong>Understand and protect your sonic assets.</strong> Most large companies will trademark or register a well-known jingle or catchphrase associated with their products or services, but in a world of AI-based sonification, businesses will also need to carefully assess the sonic print of their entire product portfolios — the distinctive whir of a washing machine or vacuum cleaner, the signature ignition of a sports car, the pop of a soda can opening. Counterfeiting of sounds will become a growing problem that businesses will need to prepare for.</p><p></p><p> <strong>“Sonify” the product experience.</strong> Businesses will pay increasing attention to the sonic signatures of their products, either to diminish cacophonous elements (such as a noisy clothes dryer) or to enhance aesthetically pleasing sounds (such as the tick-tock of a <a href="https://www.soundoflife.com/blogs/design/product-sonification-elevating-the-consumer-s-experience-via-the-beauty-of-sound-engineering">car&#39;s turn indicator</a> ). In the future, manufacturers could incorporate sonic signatures that track the product life cycle — for example, by varying a sound profile from a consumer durable as its components start to wear out. Businesses of all types will need to make sonic signatures a core part of user interface design, by identifying both the right functional and informational sounds for different uses and contexts, and by combining these with visual and other sensory elements.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prompt for sound.</strong> Generative AI systems — large language models capable of creating and synthesizing text, sounds, speech, images, and code — are increasingly enabling businesses to create completely new sounds and sonic combinations, or to combine audio with video, text or images to create new product campaigns. With a single prompt, marketers will be able to create an advertising tune for a new brand of ice cream, turn a wordy blog or product description into a music video, or alter a product jingle to make it more appealing to younger or older consumers or potential customers in a new market overseas. With “prompt engineering” now becoming a major discipline in the AI and automation fields, businesses will need to train designers, marketers, and product developers to write efficient prompts for sound-based use cases, taking into account factors such as brand values, product tone of voice, intellectual property rules, and ethics.</p><p> As the saying goes, “Wisdom is the reward for a lifetime of listening.” Today, AI-powered acoustic technologies are opening up a world of sounds previously inaccessible to us. They&#39;re providing new insights and opportunities for businesses and policy makers in areas as diverse as consumer behavior, health care, urban planning, commercial security, and infrastructure management. Businesses that choose to listen to this new world, and act upon the insights, will be well positioned for future success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/listen-up-machine-learning-holds-great-promise-for-audio-applications/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thorny Talent and AI Challenges Now: 5 Experts Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you’ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with MIT Sloan Management Review authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston. This distinguished group of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6uXF_DY4e0k?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p> If you ask leaders about their toughest leadership challenges right now, you&#39;ll hear wide-ranging concerns about both talent management and artificial intelligence. Seeking fresh insights and advice for leaders on both topics, we spoke with <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> authors at the most recent Academy of Management (AOM) event in Boston.</p><p> This distinguished group of management and leadership experts from the MIT Sloan School of Management and other institutions weighed in on two questions:</p><ul><li> What are the top talent management issues for 2024?</li><li> What is a manager&#39;s role in advocating for workers in the age of AI?</li></ul><p> “AI really changes how we work; it changes how we relate to each other and how we can talk to each other,” said Christine Moser, associate professor of organization theory at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, who spoke with <cite>MIT SMR</cite> at the event.</p><p></p><p> How should forward-looking leaders adjust to those new realities? Watch the video, recorded at AOM Boston, to learn what these experts have to say about AI checks and balances, how to motivate workers, and what happens when black-box AI models meet your organizational processes.</p><p> Want to learn more about leading people in the age of AI? Read our related article, “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-humans-lose-when-we-let-ai-decide/">What Humans Lose When We Let AI Decide</a> .”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thorny-talent-and-ai-challenges-now-5-experts-speak/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 27 Sep 2023 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, and Leslie Owens. <p>Barbara H. Wixom is principal research scientist at the MIT Center for Information Systems Research (CISR). Cynthia M. Beath is professor emerita at the University of Texas and a research collaborator at MIT CISR. Leslie Owens is an industry research fellow at MIT CISR. They are the authors of <cite><a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262048217/data-is-everybodys-business/">Data Is Everybody&#39;s Business</a></cite> (MIT Press, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business Opportunities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Competitive Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Decision-Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Value Creation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Companies can’t manage what they don’t measure. They also can’t manage what they can’t discuss. Take the term data monetization: Definitions range from the narrowly focused “selling data sets” to the overly broad “creating benefits from data.” Too little consistency among curricula in academia and too much siloed business [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Wixom-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Companies can&#39;t manage what they don&#39;t measure. They also can&#39;t manage what they can&#39;t discuss. Take the term <em>data monetization</em> : Definitions range from the narrowly focused “selling data sets” to the overly broad “creating benefits from data.” Too little consistency among curricula in academia and too much siloed business thought leadership only add to the proliferation of data babel. When leaders try to have productive conversations about a data monetization strategy within a complex business environment, they often reach an impasse. They need a simple, common language to break through.</p><p> Try using this definition: Data monetization is the conversion of data into financial returns. In the new book <cite><a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262048217/data-is-everybodys-business/">Data Is Everybody&#39;s Business</a></cite> , we offer two simple data frameworks that — when combined — represent an easy yet comprehensive set of data products. The first framework offers three different approaches to converting data into money: <em>Improve</em> , <em>wrap</em> , or <em>sell</em> . The second framework reflects three points along the data value creation process: People or systems need to use <em>data</em> to develop <em>insight</em> that informs <em>action</em> . Combine the two frameworks, and you have a matrix that offers nine distinct product choices, each with its own set of commitments and outcomes.</p><p></p><p> Leaders can use the data monetization matrix to explore current activities, future opportunities, and the interrelatedness of work. The simplicity of the matrix can help leaders be more transparent and open to breakthrough ideas. The objectivity of the matrix removes the heat from discussions and encourages conversations about <em>how</em> to monetize data instead of whether to monetize data.</p><h3> Explaining the Monetization Approaches: Improve, Wrap, and Sell</h3><p> If you sat down and began to list possible ways to create value from your company&#39;s data assets, you likely could come up with hundreds of ideas. Fundamentally, however, you can organize your ideas into three buckets. Does the idea make a work task or process better, cheaper, or faster? If so, you&#39;re looking at the improving approach. Does the idea make a product more valuable to customers? That&#39;s wrapping. Does the idea identify information that a customer would pay for? You&#39;re proposing selling. Improving, wrapping, and selling are very different in terms of risk, ownership, and requirements. When you know whether you are improving, wrapping, or selling, you can have smart conversations about data investments, capabilities, and returns.</p><p> Let&#39;s break down each of the three approaches in plain terms, with examples and questions to ask yourself about each approach.</p><p> <strong>Improve.</strong> Most companies find it easy to identify ways to use data to do things better, more cheaply, or faster. Consider Femsa, a multinational beverage and retail company that operates 21,000 Oxxo convenience stores in Latin America. The Oxxo subsidiary&#39;s senior management invested in creating a method of calculating SKU-level revenues and costs to arrive at a true measure of profit. In this way, they generated a data asset out of a host of revenue and cost data. With this new data asset, the organization could help its people understand the profitability of their decisions, leading to more profitable choices. Oxxo didn&#39;t just develop a data asset. The company soon used it for myriad improvements in store management, merchandising, product assortment, and operations.</p><p> Companies often fail to establish the kind of internal accountability that Oxxo achieved and then miss out on having efficiencies materialize as financial returns. Conversations about improving with data need to explore who in the company can drive workplace change and how to support them. Ask these questions: Who has the experience to make an improvement viable, appealing, and scalable? Who else or what else is needed to reduce or redeploy slack resources to activities that hit the bottom line? Does the company have the willingness and ability to measure and track the financial impact of improvements?</p><p> <strong>Wrap.</strong> Almost any product can be wrapped. A tractor can be wrapped with a digital display that shows operational performance; a bank account can be wrapped with a chart that categorizes the account owner&#39;s spending; and freight delivery can be wrapped with notifications of expected delivery times. Consider wrapping initiatives when products are being commoditized (a threat) or when products can be enhanced using new kinds of data via sensors, mobile apps, or surveillance feeds (an opportunity).</p><p> Wrapping conversations are customer-centric: How can the company use data to help customers better acquire, use, or retire its product? How can it use data to help its customers make money, save money, or better reach their goals? Such conversations need to include the owner of the product that is being enhanced because they are the person ultimately in charge of monetizing a wrap. How will wrapping be evaluated, monitored, and managed as a part of the company&#39;s product management and development processes? How does the company ensure that wrapping delights rather than disappoints customers?</p><p> <strong>Sell.</strong> An organization might be attracted by the higher margins that selling information seems to promise, but it&#39;s important to understand that this approach also comes with the greatest risks. Companies like Healthcare IQ, LexisNexis, and Verisk have learned how to solve specialized problems using their data assets after decades of investing in technology platforms, building algorithms, deepening subject matter expertise, cocreating with customers, and learning how to price solutions.</p><p> The crux of any selling conversation is whether it is worthwhile to invest in a new business model. Who in the company has the skills and experience to lead an information business? How can the selling initiative be established, protected, and nurtured while it gains traction? How can the company identify markets that want solutions based on its data? How can the company learn how much to charge them and how to sustain profitability in the face of competition?</p><p></p><h3> Explaining the Value-Creation Journey Points: Data, Insight, and Action</h3><p> To truly create value from data, organizations need a person or system to take an action that would not have happened otherwise. There are three ways in which a company can help make this happen. First, it can give data to someone (or to a system) who uses it to derive insight and take action that generates benefits. Better yet, a company can give an insight directly to the consumer, who then needs to choose the appropriate action. Or, taking an even more active approach, a company can trigger or prompt action, and the consumer sees results without having to do much.</p><p> Leaders need to understand where and how the company should participate in the data value-creation process and consider the related trade-offs.</p><p> <strong>Data.</strong> Offering data involves putting new or better data into the hands of someone executing part of a process (for example, machine speed data, for an equipment maintenance supervisor), someone using an existing product (for example, medical history data, for a health care patient), or an entirely new customer (for instance, someone buying a list of registered voters). When offering data, consider if the recipient will know from the data alone what action to take in order to generate value. Will someone take the time to turn that value into money?</p><p> <strong>Insight.</strong> Offering insight, as a rule, involves analyzed or contextualized data. Using the same examples as above, insight might include machine speed compared against standards, the likelihood of a patient having certain medical conditions, or a comparison of voting behavior across ZIP codes. Insight conversations debate consumer behaviors and require exceptional subject-matter expertise. Your team will want to be well-versed in what common questions consumers ask of the data and how they ask them. Your company will also need a strong sense of the competitive marketplace and the latest analytical platforms. What exactly do consumers need to know and for what reason, and what inefficiencies can be removed from their analyses?</p><p> <strong>Action.</strong> Offering action prompts specific behaviors or automates tasks. Examples include automating the scheduling of machine service to prevent equipment downtime, providing a set of tailored dietary recommendations along with a food log to help a patient manage their health, or automating delivery of voter registration forms to selected recipients. Take caution here: Action always appears to be an ideal place to participate in data monetization because it positions the company closest to value creation, with a high likelihood of influencing it. However, leaders need to thoughtfully explore whether they have the capabilities, the rights, and the trust to offer action. Does the consumer want the company to trigger an action on their behalf, and would that be legal? Is the company confident that its data and insights are good enough to inform the correct action?</p><p> As you can see from these examples, leaders can deliver data, insight, or action using any of the three data monetization approaches (improve, wrap, sell).</p><h3> The Data Monetization Matrix: Examples in Action</h3><p> To help a team evaluate potential options, use the data monetization matrix to frame the discussion. Explore these real-world examples that a company might tackle and how the matrix helps explain the options. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Using the Data Monetization Matrix: 3 Scenarios</h4><p class="caption"> The matrix helps frame discussions of how to monetize data. Start by considering whether your organization wants to use data for improving, wrapping, or selling (as shown on the horizontal axis). Then discuss where in the value creation process you will participate: by offering data, insight, or action (as shown on the vertical axis). The first example shows an improving/data decision, the second a wrapping/insight choice, and the third a selling/action approach. Note that your company could pursue one type of product, three in a row — or even products for every single matrix square. The key is for your team to understand the implications of each choice. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/2023_0927_Wixom_Fig-1.png" alt=""></p><p class="attribution"> Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, and Leslie Owens, <cite class="normal">Data Is Everybody&#39;s Business</cite> (MIT Press, 2023).</p></article></aside></div><p> Let&#39;s start with an improving example. Consider an organization that has an employee performance data asset that includes employee evaluations, skill profiles, and recognition histories. Leaders believe that talent development could be improved by using this data to help supervisors identify, develop, and reward good performance more cheaply, easily, and quickly.</p><ul><li> A <em>data</em> product based on employee performance data might give supervisors direct access to this data, along with some features that allow them to sort and select from it.</li><li> An <em>insight</em> product might provide supervisors analyzed and contextualized performance information — say, a dashboard identifying which employees performed above or below standard expectations. Supervisors might use this information to give feedback and monitor progress.</li><li> An <em>action</em> product might automatically send a bonus and a recognition certificate to employees who consistently performed above expectations.</li></ul><p> Now consider wrapping opportunities at an organization that has a device that collects historical blood sugar readings for patients and their doctors. The product owner believes that if patients received more benefits from the device, its price could be raised.</p><ul><li> A <em>data</em> product would add a display of the historical daily blood sugar level readings for the patient. Hopefully, the patient would see patterns and get insights about how to better control their blood sugar.</li><li> An <em>insight</em> product would display the patient&#39;s recent blood sugar levels relative to established standards for their age/gender cohort. Patients would need to learn how to use this insight to behave differently.</li><li> An <em>action</em> product would send the patient an alert to have their midmorning apple snack within the next 15 minutes.</li></ul><p> Finally, let&#39;s review opportunities that a grocery store chain might investigate in the sell column. This company has a sales data asset consisting of purchase data and other customer-specific information for shoppers who have joined its loyalty program.</p><ul><li> The chain can develop a <em>data</em> product that provides data on items scanned at checkout that the company can sell to product manufacturers.</li><li> That data, coupled with an analysis of customer purchase history (using loyalty card data and shopping cart items), can be the basis of an <em>insight</em> product that the company can sell to organizations that want information about trends in dietary habits.</li><li> In the <em>action</em> box, the team could create a cross-selling algorithm that automatically suggests additional purchases to consumers — and charges the manufacturers who participate in the program.</li></ul><p> Take note: Data monetization opportunities don&#39;t need to flow in a straight line across the matrix. Your conversations might need to flip around. For example, leaders at the grocery store chain might decide that it&#39;s not appealing to monetize by selling at all. Instead, they might want to engage in conversations about how to use the company&#39;s sales data asset to improve store operations and make them better, cheaper, or faster. Or commoditization pressures might lead them to explore how to wrap existing grocery goods and services with the sales data asset to distinguish their services from those of other grocers.</p><h3> 4 Ways to Improve Your Strategy</h3><p> As these examples show, you can use the 3x3 matrix to have more effective conversations about data monetization strategy. To continuously improve, consider using the matrix in these four ways.</p><p> <strong>1. Conduct a rough inventory of your crucial data-heavy initiatives and slot them into the matrix.</strong> Key questions: Have you tried improving, wrapping, and selling? Or just improving? Have you delivered data, insight, and action products? Or mostly just data products? You might find that your activities are weighted toward improving with data (pumping clean data from one system to another, for example, or revealing more data to a partner). If so, start conversations around how to evolve into wrapping or selling, or into insight and action.</p><p> <strong>2. Use the matrix as a benchmark.</strong> From time to time, ask whether you are expanding your repertoire of data monetization approaches. Key questions: Is data monetization activity spreading from pockets of the organization to broader parts of the enterprise? Is data monetization keeping pace with digital transformation goals and accomplishments? Do data monetization efforts have the right accountability, funding, and support?</p><p></p><p> <strong>3. Look for opportunities to reuse and recombine data assets.</strong> Key questions: Are the same data assets being used across the matrix or in just one cell, row, or column? Does each data monetization opportunity require new data preparation, permissions, and provisioning? If so, consider how data can be converted into liquid data assets that can be reused broadly in many data monetization efforts.</p><p> <strong>4. Identify open spots on the matrix.</strong> Key questions: Do empty cells represent hidden opportunities? Or are the open spots unachievable for some reason, like missing enterprise capabilities, skills, or customer connections?</p><p> All companies need a data monetization strategy, but creating, sharing, and executing the strategy can be fraught with misunderstanding and resistance. The solution is not more data or more AI but, rather, better communication. If leaders can get their teams up to speed on the matrix, they&#39;ll encourage people to engage in productive conversations and get on track to manage the right data monetization strategy in the right way.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Halt Impostor Syndrome Before It Happens</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/halt-impostor-syndrome-before-it-happens/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/halt-impostor-syndrome-before-it-happens/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Angélica S. Gutiérrez. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/angelicagutierrez/">Angélica S. Gutiérrez</a> is an associate professor of management at the College of Business Administration at Loyola Marymount University in Los Angeles.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Isabela is an associate at a global management consulting firm, where she started working shortly after earning an MBA from a top business school. Her strong analytical and quantitative skills, coupled with her interpersonal and communication skills, have garnered Isabela high performance ratings. But despite a stellar performance record [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Gutierrez-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>Isabela is an associate at a global management consulting firm, where she started working shortly after earning an MBA from a top business school. Her strong analytical and quantitative skills, coupled with her interpersonal and communication skills, have garnered Isabela high performance ratings. But despite a stellar performance record and clients&#39; and senior managers&#39; characterization of her as “at manager level,” Isabela did not apply for the manager position that recently became available.</p><p> Senior partners at the firm might be quick to conclude that Isabela didn&#39;t apply because she has impostor syndrome — which refers to feelings of inadequacy that individuals experience, and a fear that others will discover that they do not belong in the positions that they occupy. They have likely read articles and attended professional development seminars that discussed employees&#39; susceptibility to experiencing impostor syndrome. Psychologists Pauline Clance and Susan Imes coined the term <em>impostor syndrome</em> to describe high-achieving women who feel incompetent and fear that others will eventually discover that they are a fraud and unfit for their position — a characterization that seems to fit Isabela.</p><p></p><p> But Isabela neither felt inadequate nor questioned her ability to manage — at least not initially. Rather, she decided not to apply because she had been denied a promotion the previous year. Her colleague Greg, who has not been with the company for as long and is less qualified, was promoted instead. Isabela concluded that perhaps she was not as intelligent, competent, and fit for the position as she believed.</p><h3> The Real Problem: &#39;Impostorization&#39;</h3><p> Isabela&#39;s experience underscores the danger in assuming that such behaviors, including the decision not to apply for leadership positions, stem from self-perceived deficiencies. For Isabela and other employees, impostor syndrome is the presumed issue, but <em>impostorization</em> is the real problem.</p><p> <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0749597822000930">Impostorization</a> refers to the policies, practices, and seemingly innocuous interactions in the workplace that make (or intend to make) individuals question their intelligence, competence, and sense of belonging. The strategies that are often recommended to help individuals counter impostor syndrome — such as standing in power poses, reciting positive affirmations, and taking an inventory of past successes — have limited value in countering impostorization.</p><p></p><p> This is not to say that employees such as Isabela do not experience impostor syndrome and that managers need not focus on providing the support that employees need to counter its effects. A <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-high-achievers-overcome-imposter-syndrome/">recent <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> article</a> provides valuable insights on how managers can identify impostor syndrome in employees and support them. But before managers assume that the issue is impostor syndrome, it is critical that they examine how the workplace might be inadvertently engaging in impostorization and triggering the feelings that they seek to address.</p><p> Certain policies, practices, and seemingly harmless interactions might unintentionally lead employees to question their intelligence, competence, and sense of belonging. The following are a few examples.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Biased promotion decisions.</strong> Employees like Isabela might have a high degree of self-esteem and self-efficacy — uncharacteristic of people with impostor syndrome — yet employer promotion decisions might trigger feelings of inadequacy. The company&#39;s decision to promote a male employee over Isabela is consistent with the findings of a recent study by MIT Sloan School of Management professor Danielle Li and colleagues that found that male employees tend to receive <a href="https://danielle-li.github.io/assets/docs/PotentialAndTheGenderPromotionGap.pdf">higher ratings than female employees</a> on questions related to “potential,” such as, “If given the opportunity, would this person make a good manager?” These ratings, which are intended to predict an individual&#39;s performance, are often influenced by gender biases and assumptions about leaders, which often favor men. The study found that differences in ratings of people&#39;s potential account for about 50% of the gender promotion gap. Promotion decisions based on factors unrelated to performance can trigger impostor syndrome among employees not selected. Left without feedback to the contrary, employees might attribute these decisions to their own perceived failings, such as a lack of qualifications or poor fit.</p><p> <strong>Glass cliff appointments.</strong> Ironically, women and people of color tend to be promoted at lower rates relative to their White male counterparts, yet the former are promoted more often to lead poorly performing organizations. Studies of promotion and the tenure of Fortune 500 CEOs found that minorities are more likely than White men to be appointed CEO of weak-performing companies, a <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">phenomenon referred to as the glass cliff</a> . As the entities continue to struggle, minority leaders are blamed. Glass cliff appointments might trigger impostor feelings among minorities — despite their prior records of success — by leading them to question their competence and to interpret organizational failings as a reflection of their own deficiencies rather than circumstances that are objectively challenging or a lack of support.</p><p> <strong>Interruptions and idea-stealing.</strong> Isabela arrived at her employer with confidence and a determination to excel. She often made recommendations and shared insights during meetings, but she observed a pattern: She would either get cut off when speaking, or her ideas would go unnoticed only to be presented minutes later by a colleague who was then praised for the novelty of the idea. While it is common for individuals to interrupt others, studies find that men <a href="https://hbr.org/2017/04/female-supreme-court-justices-are-interrupted-more-by-male-justices-and-advocates">interrupt women more often than they interrupt other men</a> during meetings, and they get credit for <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/featured%20insights/diversity%20and%20inclusion/women%20in%20the%20workplace%202022/women-in-the-workplace-2022.pdf">regurgitating the ideas presented by women</a> . Given the frequency of interruption in meetings, such behaviors might appear innocuous; their cumulative effect, however, could be impostorizing. The individuals who are interrupted and whose ideas go unnoticed might begin to question the value of their contributions. They might wonder whether they failed to articulate their ideas well enough and experience self-doubt, which in turn can decrease their participation and contributions.</p><h3> Avoiding Impostorization</h3><p> Avoiding triggering impostor syndrome is just as important as supporting employees who might be experiencing it. Managers can take the following steps to avoid it and, in the process, increase employees&#39; job satisfaction, organizational citizenship behaviors, motivation to lead, and retention.</p><p> <strong>Use objective criteria in promotion decisions.</strong> Unconscious biases can influence decisions based on subjective assessments. Ensure that opportunities for promotion are communicated to eligible employees, and use clear and explicit criteria when evaluating candidates. Consider providing specific feedback to employees who are denied promotions. Humans have an innate need to make sense of outcomes, and a promotion denial might be impostorizing when employees interpret the decision as a reflection of their inadequacy. Take the time to provide feedback not only on areas that the employee could work on to strengthen their competitiveness for the next promotion but also on what they are doing well. Balanced feedback can help avoid triggering impostor syndrome among employees by drawing attention to their strengths.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Provide employees with sufficient resources.</strong> As the saying goes, “By failing to prepare, you are preparing to fail.” Whether stepping into the C-suite or an entry-level position, employees are more likely to thrive when they have organizational support. Similarly, failing to equip employees with the resources they need, including effective onboarding and mentoring, can set them up to fail. Failure can be an impostorizing experience by leading otherwise intelligent and competent employees to believe that they are inadequate rather than lacking organizational support.</p><p> <strong>Implement meeting norms that promote listening and idea-crediting.</strong> IDEO, a global design and innovation company, promotes creativity by encouraging employees to avoid criticizing others&#39; ideas; when they do so, a bell is rung. Establishing meeting norms — whether ringing a bell or instituting a “no interruptions” rule — might lead employees to actively listen, avoid cutting off colleagues who are speaking, and give credit where credit is due. Such norms could also help avoid impostorization by conveying to employees that they are heard, their contributions are recognized, and that they are integral members of the organization — in other words, that they are not impostors.</p><p></p><p></p><p> While much of the literature and discussions on impostor syndrome have focused on the individual, and strategies to counter its effects have taken a fix-the-individual approach, it is in fact organizations — through policies, practices, and seemingly innocuous interactions — that might be inadvertently triggering the problem. Managers must consider that the feelings and behaviors of employees might not be symptoms of impostor syndrome, but rather the consequences of impostorization.</p><p> Examine how the organizational culture — through bias, microaggressions, sexism, or racism, for example — might be impostorizing employees. If an employee with a promising performance record decides not to apply for a leadership position, is it because they believe they aren&#39;t capable of leading — or because there is no evidence to suggest that the organization supports structural diversity? If an employee initially contributes to discussions and then begins to stay silent, is it because they are no longer confident — or because their ideas have been repeatedly ignored or credited to someone else? Is the problem really impostor syndrome, or impostorization? Create a culture of psychological safety and pose these questions to those who are most qualified to answer: your employees.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/halt-impostor-syndrome-before-it-happens/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Reconnecting When Network Ties Go Dormant</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reconnecting-when-network-ties-go-dormant/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reconnecting-when-network-ties-go-dormant/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:00:58 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Emanuela Rondi, Daniel Z. Levin, and Alfredo De Massis. <p>Emanuela Rondi is an associate professor of management at Università degli Studi di Bergamo in Italy. Daniel Z. Levin is a professor of management and global business at Rutgers Business School — Newark and New Brunswick, at Rutgers University in New Jersey. Alfredo De Massis is a professor of entrepreneurship and family business at the Free University of Bozen-Bolzano in Italy, the Wild Group Chair in Family Business at the International Institute for Management Development (IMD) in Switzerland, and a professor at Lancaster University Management School in the United Kingdom.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business Relationships]]></category><category><![CDATA[Networks and Networking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Partnerships]]></category><category><![CDATA[Relationship Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR We’ve known for a while that relationships that have fallen into a state of inactivity — or become dormant ties — can be resurrected. As people venture back into professional social settings after having experienced pandemic-induced disconnection, they are particularly keen to revive these inactive ties. Such connections have the potential to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Rondi-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> We&#39;ve known for a while that relationships that have fallen into a state of inactivity — or become <em>dormant ties</em> — <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/20868904">can be resurrected</a> . As people venture back into professional social settings after having experienced pandemic-induced disconnection, they are particularly keen to revive these inactive ties. Such connections have the potential to be incredibly valuable: During the period of dormancy, former contacts have been learning new things and developing new networks that could yield advice, referrals, emotional support, and even tangible resources.</p><p> We used to assume that <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-power-of-reconnection-how-dormant-ties-can-surprise-you/">reawakening a dormant tie</a> was a simple process — just, you know, reach out and start talking to people. This view presumes that people can simply reengage as if no time has elapsed.</p><p></p><p> However, new research shows that the process of reviving a dormant tie is more complex than that. Simple mistakes can derail the reconnection process, sometimes so dramatically as to cause a relationship to end. For instance, one of us was with an innovation manager at a convention immediately after a former colleague had made a poorly executed attempt at reconnection. “Unbelievable. Did you hear what he asked me?” this manager said. “I will never talk to that guy again!” Less dramatically, dormant contacts will sometimes seem friendly when responding to an overture (“Well, it was great to see you”) but later admit that they were holding back and felt reluctant to fully engage, collaborate with, or share what they know with the other person.</p><p> Why are some reconnection attempts so suboptimal or even downright harmful? And what makes some reconnections more successful than others? We investigated these questions by observing and interviewing managers to understand how to refresh a level of trust in ways that benefit both parties.</p><h3> The Three Key Elements of Reconnection</h3><p> Over the course of several years, our research has included observing dozens of real-time reconnections at industry conventions and conducting 71 interviews with executives across the textile industry in Northern Italy. We identified three elements consistently associated with successful reconnections: how well both parties remember each other, how they go about catching up, and whether they perceive the relationship similarly. We developed a model of reconnections that result in activity where one or both parties obtain resources through the tie, such as a productive collaboration or useful advice.</p><p> We then tested this model in an experiment with 331 US workers to assess the impact of each of the three elements on another person&#39;s willingness to help. We provided a vignette describing a reconnection attempt by a former coworker and asked, “How willing would you be to help this person?” We measured whether people&#39;s willingness changed based on whether a reconnection element was present or absent. We found that with none of the elements present, people&#39;s willingness was neutral at best — 3.86 on a scale from 1 (unwilling) to 7 (willing). When all three elements were present, it went from neutral to, essentially, “Yes, I&#39;d agree to help” (5.72). This validated our findings. We also confirmed that the three reconnection elements are useful specifically because they increase people&#39;s trust that the other person cares about and will look out for them. Our research was <a href="https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2023.1685?journalCode=orsc">published earlier this year</a> in <cite>Organization Science.</cite></p><p> Here&#39;s how to work with each of the three key elements that enhance the success of a dormant-tie reconnection.</p><p></p><p> <strong>1. Remembering.</strong> Recognizing each other is critical, and a failure to do so can feel embarrassing and even insulting. Trying to reconnect with someone who does not recognize you is painful and might even make you seem less trustworthy. This often ends the relationship permanently.</p><p> Overtures that give the other person time to look you up on social media such as LinkedIn can provide a way for the person being approached to see your face, read your bio, and be reminded of how they know you. Cold-calling can be risky: An R&amp;D manager told us about calling a CEO and having to explain multiple times who he was and how and where they had met. Eventually, the CEO did remember him as “the young guy with very big hope.” The R&amp;D manager felt humiliated and decided not to ask for the advice he was looking for and never called the CEO again.</p><p> Approaching someone in person at a professional event can also be tricky. Keep in mind, for instance, that everyone&#39;s appearance changes over time, including yours, so providing clues such as a prominent name tag can help.</p><p> After recognizing each other, reminiscing over shared experiences helps to reestablish the relationship by reminding each other of what was happening when the tie was active. You want to talk about times spent together, and even shared hardships. For example, we observed a successful reconnection where one participant said, “Do you remember our director? He was such a jerk.” The other recalled that person the same way: “Ha ha, how could I forget? The most unapproachable guy — super moody.” As memories came flooding back, the former colleagues created a bridge between past and present.</p><p> <strong>2. Catching up.</strong> Updating the other person on professional and even personal matters since you last saw each other brings the relationship into the present and allows you to fill in the picture of what has happened while the relationship was dormant. This is more than just small talk; it lets people see what you&#39;re all about now. One executive said that hearing about the other person&#39;s career path “not only helps but is probably also critical to understanding who you are dealing with.” Note that catching up does not mean providing a detailed chronological account of everything that has happened since you last were in touch. Focusing on just the relevant highlights can help to strategically orient the conversation.</p><p> Including details on personal matters can make the reconnection less transactional. “If you season it all with some mention of your personal life, it can help bring the talk back to a little bit more human level,” said one executive. “If you go straight to the point, people might feel you want to exploit them.” It&#39;s important not to get too personal, though. One manager, in describing catching up with a dormant contact after eight years, explained, “I didn&#39;t want to cross the line and be too intrusive, so I tried to limit this to pleasantries, showing that I care without being indiscreet.” Unfortunately, not everyone follows this advice. Indeed, we witnessed several reconnection disasters brought on by insensitive questions, both in the professional realm (“Did they at least pay you well when you were let go as CEO?”) and in the personal realm, with an inquiry into how a person was coping with the death of a spouse. Both reconnection attempts were cut short by the other person.</p><p></p><p> Reacquainting yourselves also helps both sides assess whether they like and trust each other. It may initially seem like a gratuitous ritual, but it allows people to check whether their mental image of you, including your trustworthiness, is still accurate. How you present yourself — your views, your recent experiences — will affect not just how the other person sees you but the relationship itself. You will likewise have the same opportunity to reassess your old contact. This stage is when both parties evaluate, often subconsciously, whether the other person represents a viable tie for the future.</p><p> <strong>3. Perceiving the tie similarly.</strong> Both sides need to be on the same page about the relationship, such as how close you two feel, whether your roles or companies are in competition, and whether you are of similar or different status. For example, it is fine to reconnect with people you used to know either really well or barely at all, as long as you treat the other person accordingly. Treating someone as a close confidant when you had a distant relationship with them (or vice versa) undermines the reconnection.</p><p> Dormant contacts who are now competitors can still reconnect successfully and sometimes even work together — such as on efforts to promote the industry — but both people need to be in sync about the nature of the relationship. As one executive put it, “If I think that asking that person something would cause them a conflict of interest, I do not ask.”</p><p> One R&amp;D manager told us of a reconnection he tried to make that went poorly, with a former employee who had since become CEO of a small but fast-growing company. The CEO “kept the conversation very brief before hanging up.” Afterward, the R&amp;D manager told us sheepishly that he might have been too bossy, coming off as if his former colleague owed him something. “Maybe he felt like I was treating him as my employee instead of the CEO of an important company,” he said. The two were not seeing the tie similarly, and the reconnection attempt failed.</p><p> Being on the same page sets the boundaries for what is or is not appropriate when making requests in the reconnection process. The other person needs to trust that you will not pressure them into sharing resources they are not comfortable sharing given the type of relationship you have.</p><p></p><p></p><p> These latest findings are on <em>how</em> to reconnect your dormant ties. Don&#39;t forget, though, that it also matters <em>who</em> the other person is. Past research has found that <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-reconnect-for-maximum-impact/">the most useful reconnections</a> are to dormant contacts who are likely to provide novelty — such as higher-status contacts and people you never spent a lot of time with in the past — and who are also likely to be fully engaged, such as people you expect will care about you and be willing to help.</p><p> Refreshing dormant ties can be as important to enhancing your network as adding new people or strengthening existing ties. Savvy executives reconnect, but they do it thoughtfully. The payoff is that requests to collaborate or seek advice will be greeted less warily, with a willingness by the other person to go above and beyond in helping without feeling like they&#39;re being taken advantage of. Those who take the time to pay attention to these three steps are better able to restore past relationships to their full potential — refreshed, trusted, and ready to help.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reconnecting-when-network-ties-go-dormant/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Managing RAI Requires a Central Team</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-rai-requires-a-central-team/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-rai-requires-a-central-team/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Management Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts that includes academics and practitioners to help us gain insights into how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented in organizations worldwide. As companies increase their use of internally developed and third-party AI tools, including large language models, responsibly [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts that includes academics and practitioners to help us gain insights into how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented in organizations worldwide.</p><p> As companies increase their use of internally developed and third-party AI tools, including large language models, responsibly managing AI will become a more complicated, broader, and higher-stakes set of activities. Who, then, should manage RAI efforts? Should RAI management be centralized on a single team or be decentralized, with accountability distributed across the enterprise? We wanted to understand how our expert panelists would address these questions, so we asked them to react to the following provocation: <em>The management of RAI should be centralized in a specific function (versus decentralized across multiple functions and business units).</em></p><p> While half of the panelists agreed or strongly agreed that RAI management should be centralized, the vast majority of panelists — 11 out of 12 — indicated in their responses that managing RAI should be centralized <em>and</em> decentralized. Proponents of this hybrid view shared these common perspectives:</p><ol><li> A centralized, cross-functional team is necessary to set RAI standards and practices and to have accountability for RAI efforts across the enterprise. A centralized team is needed to govern RAI practices.</li><li> Management of RAI should also happen at the project level and across functions. It is the responsibility of everyone involved with AI implementations to embed, and abide by, RAI standards and practices. A decentralized approach is necessary to ensure that the organization, broadly, is responsible for RAI. </li></ol><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3> The Panelists Respond</p></h3><h2> Managing RAI should be centralized <em>and</em> decentralized.</p></h2><p> While 50% of our panelists explicitly agree or strongly agree that RAI management should be centralized, 92% mentioned centralized management in their open-text response to this prompt.</p><p> <a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">Jump to panelists&#39; detailed responses below.</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/RAI2023_Article3-Chart-1.jpg" alt="Chart: 8% strongly disagree, 8% disagree, 33% neither agree nor disagree, 33% agree, 17% strongly agree"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source"> Source: Responsible AI panel of 12 experts in artificial intelligence strategy. Percentages may not total 100% due to rounding.</p></p></div></div><h3> The Case for Centralizing Management of RAI</h3><p> A primary function of RAI efforts is to govern the use of AI across the enterprise. As a governance mechanism, RAI helps establish and communicate standards, ensures that standards are followed, cultivates a culture that embraces the responsible use of AI, and provides expertise to support AI product teams.</p><p></p><p> To deliver on these objectives, panelists encourage the creation of cross-functional or centralized teams. Linda Leopold, head of responsible AI at H&amp;M Group, asserts that “someone needs to be in charge of the RAI strategy and vision — providing topic expertise, leadership, and coordination. This should preferably be handled by a specific, centralized team.” According to Riyanka Roy Choudhury, a CodeX fellow at Stanford Law School, “Leadership should assess, analyze, and create an integrated organizational structure to manage RAI across multiple functions and business units.”</p><p> Panelists were consistent in describing the purpose of a centralized team. Triveni Gandhi, responsible AI lead at Dataiku, says its function is to provide guidance and “clear accountability structures.” Giuseppe Manai, cofounder and chief operating officer of Stemly, adds, “A designated [RAI] unit sets ethical guidelines and standards for AI implementations across the organization. This unit acts as a focal point for RAI initiatives, equipped with specialized expertise in AI ethics and compliance. Their main task is to develop ethical frameworks that all other units and business functions must adhere to when implementing AI solutions.”</p><p> Intel has a cross-functional RAI council that conducts a rigorous review throughout the life cycle of an AI project, assessing and mitigating ethical risks. Elizabeth Anne Watkins, a research scientist at Intel Labs, notes that the council&#39;s members “provide training, feedback, and support to the development teams and business units to ensure consistency and compliance with our principles across Intel.”</p><p> Cultivating an RAI culture often means cultivating RAI ambassadors, advocates, and influencers from across the enterprise. “To foster durable RAI cultures,” Watkins says, “it&#39;s also helpful to complement this central team with a strong network of champions who can advocate for RAI principles within teams and business units.” Leopold concurs: “By having RAI champions or similar across functions or business units, the message … is that it is <em>everyone’s</em> responsibility to be responsible.” And, as Choudhury and UNICEF digital policy specialist Steven Vosloo observe, a centralized RAI function minimizes coordination costs between AI implementations and function-level RAI initiatives.</p><p></p><h3> The Case for Hybrid Management: Centralized Accountability, Distributed Responsibility</h3><p> Even those panelists who responded in the negative shared views that were consistent with having a central team that has ultimate accountability for RAI. Vosloo&#39;s response reflects the view of several panelists: “While there should be a dedicated function that is ultimately accountable for responsible AI, the practice of RAI is a whole-of-organization undertaking. A hybrid approach is thus ideal: a central function, made up of a diverse range of stakeholders in the organization, that relies on responsible practices across multiple functions and business units.”</p><p> Business unit and functional leaders who manage AI implementations are de facto managers of RAI implementations. As professor Simon Chesterman of the National University of Singapore says, “Strategic direction and leadership [for RAI] may reside in the C-suite, but operationalizing RAI will depend on those deploying AI solutions to ensure appropriate levels of human control and transparency so that true responsibility is even possible.” David R. Hardoon, CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation and chief data and AI officer of Union Bank of the Philippines, contends that “the implementation-operationalization of governance needs to be decentralized and the responsibility of each specific function.”</p><p></p><p> As with any governance mechanism, exerting too much control can have a chilling or disruptive effect on efforts to innovate with or implement AI. Belona Sonna, manager of ethics and gender issues for AfroLeadership, observes that a central governance mechanism needs to accommodate project complexity or else it will run afoul of broader goals.</p><p></p><h3> Recommendations</h3><p> For organizations seeking to establish an effective RAI management structure, we recommend the following:</p><ol><li> <strong>Establish a central, cross-functional team that has accountability for RAI efforts across the organization.</strong> It is important, however, to define what constitutes accountability for this team: What are the roles and responsibilities of this group? What does successful accountability look like? What measures and metrics can be used to evaluate success? Clearly establishing the role and decision rights of the central team is critical; otherwise, it will have the responsibility but none of the authority needed to be successful. One caution: Defining the central team&#39;s accountability broadly or narrowly invites trade-offs. Defining RAI broadly — say, if it covers any use of AI anywhere in the enterprise — will introduce scalability challenges for the central team, creating additional organizational bottlenecks and risks. Defining accountability narrowly — say, only for recognized AI projects — can reduce the organization&#39;s ability to identify and mitigate risks from other uses of AI.</li><li> <strong>Ensure that centralized teams have a mix of strategic leaders and technical experts from across domains (such as AI development, risk, legal, and infosec).</strong> Their combined expertise, networks, and influence will strengthen efforts to establish and communicate standards, cultivate RAI champions, and support a broader culture of responsible AI development and use. Furthermore, a team that includes a mix of leaders and experts can better address the inherent nature of AI implementations, which embody both organizational and technical risks.</li><li> <strong>Create feedback loops so that RAI governance is not a top-down process.</strong> Front-line managers can be a critical source of information about what is and is not working with RAI-related activities. No RAI program can be static. Constant iteration and improvement is needed to ensure a program&#39;s ongoing effectiveness in light of organizational change, technology development, and shared lessons across the broader RAI community.</li></ol><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-rai-requires-a-central-team/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>