<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 6 月 13 日，星期二 14:20:08 +0000</lastbuilddate><language>英文</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1个</sy:updatefrequency><generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>什么，我担心？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Elizabeth Heichler ( <a href="https://twitter.com/eheichler">@eheichler</a> ) 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>杂志的执行编辑。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades Call me shortsighted, but I am not losing sleep over the prospect of a supercharged AI gaining consciousness and waging war on humans. What does keep me up at night is that humans are already wielding the power of artificial intelligence to control, exploit, discriminate against, misinform, and manipulate other humans. Tools that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-Edit-Letter-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><p>说我目光短浅，但我并没有因为超级人工智能获得意识并对人类发动战争的前景而失眠。</p><p>让我夜不能寐的是，人类已经在运用人工智能的力量来控制、利用、歧视、误导和操纵其他人。可以帮助我们解决复杂和棘手问题的工具也可以被网络犯罪分子使用，或者赋予专制政府前所未有的权力来监视和指导其公民的生活。我们可以建立模型来开发新的、更可持续的材料或重要的新药——我们可以建立模型，将有偏见的决策嵌入到系统和流程中，然后让个人陷入困境。</p><p></p><p>换句话说，AI 已经让我们担心了很多。我们不应该被反乌托邦的狂热梦想分散注意力，这些梦想会误导我们对当今风险的注意力。</p><p>最近出现的 ChatGPT 和类似的大型语言模型引起了更广泛的公众意识，这提高了人们对 AI 的潜在好处和危险的普遍兴趣。在我写这篇文章的前几天，人工智能领域的巨人 Geoffrey Hinton 辞去了他在谷歌的职位，他告诉<cite>纽约时报</cite>，他想自由地谈论生成人工智能的风险. “很难看出你如何才能阻止坏人利用它来做坏事，”他告诉该报。</p><p>那里确实是我们应该关注的地方。纵观人类历史，新技术已被用于推动文明进步，但它们也被不良行为者武器化。这次的不同之处在于，不仅这项技术极其复杂，而且大多数人都难以理解——潜在的结果也是如此。</p><p>如果我们希望 AI 利大于弊，那么我们所有人都必须准备好攀登一条陡峭的学习曲线。对这些工具的可能用途的兴奋必须通过关于如何做出自动化决策、如何训练人工智能系统以及因此产生了哪些假设和偏见的好问题来缓和。企业领导者尤其需要意识到声誉和物质风险和价值破坏的可能性，因为它们是利用人工智能的机会。</p><p></p><p>虽然人工智能的发展可能会继续以任何公开信都无法阻止的惊人速度进行，但我们其他人应该谨慎行事。在“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dont-get-distracted-by-the-hype-around-generative-ai/">不要被围绕生成式 AI 的炒作分散注意力</a>”中，Lee Vinsel 提醒我们，技术泡沫伴随着大量噪音。我们需要放下对错失恐惧症 (FOMO) 的恐惧，采取审慎、理性的方法来评估新兴技术。</p><p>在<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite> ，我们将继续为商业领袖提供头脑清醒的决策制定和明智的实验所需的研究和情报。我们持续<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">关注负责任的 AI 实践</a>，由圣母大学的客座编辑 Elizabeth Renieris 领导，这是该承诺的关键部分。</p><p>我们都是人工智能革命的利益相关者。让我们承担起这一责任，并努力确保好人多于坏人。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>我们的 2023 年夏季刊指南</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Algorithms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here’s How to Keep Them on Track. Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi Key Insight: When algorithms aren’t updated to account for changes in the environment, they deliver poor-quality predictions. Top Takeaways: AI models designed to dynamically account for new circumstances don’t always do so effectively. This [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-EXECSUM-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="no-underline">预测模型可能会失去情节。以下是如何让他们走上正轨。</a></h4><h6> Vern L. Glaser、Omid Omidvar 和 Mehdi Safavi</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>当算法未更新以应对环境变化时，它们会提供低质量的预测。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>旨在动态解释新情况的 AI 模型并不总是有效。这种情况称为<em>算法惯性</em>，可能会导致指导不力和决策错误。作者通过调查信用评级机构穆迪及其在 2008 年金融危机前几年使用算法模型对抵押贷款支持证券进行评级的情况，探讨了算法惯性的原因和后果。他们发现，算法惯性最重要的影响因素是隐藏的假设、表面的重塑、对未知未来的模拟和专门的划分。公开数据和假设，以及定期重新设计算法例程，是消除这种惰性的两个关键做法。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="no-underline">风险情报和有弹性的公司</a></h4><h6>Ananya Sheth 和 Joseph V. Sinfield</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>采取更合乎逻辑的风险管理方法可以帮助领导者在混乱和不确定的情况下维持价值创造。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>在当今相互关联的世界中，构建大型复杂企业的弹性至关重要。风险情报——严格解释风险及其对公司造成的后果或机会的磨练能力——通过帮助领导者识别和管理随着时间的推移和不断变化的业务对公司价值交换系统的广泛潜在威胁，支持组织的弹性上下文。为加强组织的风险情报，领导者应系统地对风险事件进行分类和解释，区分不确定性并减少其影响，并构建企业风险网络并将其置于情境中。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="no-underline">专业服务公司如何避免颠覆</a></h4><h6>朱利安·伯金肖和大卫·兰斯菲尔德</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>长寿的专业服务公司为其他试图在动荡的市场中生存下来的企业提供了经验教训。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>十年前，大型专业服务公司似乎处于以技术为动力的新竞争对手的十字准线，但许多公司保持甚至巩固了自己的地位。这些咨询巨头、顶级律师事务所和其他机构在诊断潜在中断的不同原因并做出相应响应的能力中发现了弹性。他们在解决客户最具挑战性的问题以及在高影响、大规模、高风险情况下提供建议和合规性方面加倍发挥传统优势——并为此收取额外费用。他们学会了务实地承认自己的基本面是健全的，同时对新兴技术和竞争对手抱有一丝偏执的怀疑。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="no-underline">未能扩大规模背后缺失的纪律</a></h4><h6>安迪·宾斯和克里斯汀·格里芬</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>为新企业开发扩展路径既是一门艺术，也是一门科学，但领导者可以利用它来学习和迭代。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>公司在开发新业务计划方面进行了大量投资，但很少有人遵循严格的途径来广泛实施这些计划。虽然 80% 的公司声称构思和孵化新企业，但只有 16% 的公司成功地扩大了规模。扩展路径需要明确的雄心壮志等于机会的规模；一套合理的战略选择，用于确定实现这一目标所需的资产；就如何获得这些资产进行聪明的头脑风暴；以开放的态度引入新的领导者以支持不断扩大的活动范围；为不可避免的高风险时刻做好准备，此时决策需要做出即使并非不可能也难以逆转的承诺。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="no-underline">帮助神经分歧的员工取得成功</a></h4><h6>Emily R. Russo、Dana L. Ott 和 Miriam Moeller</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>公司可以通过制定具有神经包容性的招聘策略和工作环境来扩大人才库。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>在工作场所的招聘、管理和保留方面，有神经系统差异的人，尤其是自闭症谱系的人，经常被雇主低估，这对每个人都不利。将神经多样性纳入有关工作场所多样性、公平性和包容性的更广泛对话很重要，不仅因为这是公平的事情，而且因为神经分歧的个人可以做出有价值的贡献。创建一个神经包容性组织需要有利于神经分歧员工和更广泛员工队伍的特定培训和发展工作。管理人员是这些项目取得成功的关键，需要接受有关如何支持神经分歧员工的培训。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="no-underline">您的财务办公室的数字化成熟度如何？</a></h4><h6>克里斯托夫·斯托海森</h6><p><strong>重要见解：</strong>许多财务办公室都停留在传统的运营角色中，无法从高级分析中受益。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>各行各业的财务领导者都在尝试整合数据和分析以改善运营，但并非所有 CFO 都破解了密码。特别是，许多人没有利用新机器学习应用程序的前景。能够挑战通常保守、谨慎的文化并设法成功部署高级分析的首席财务官可以提供更多实时见解，减少人为错误和偏见，并加快流程和决策制定。更重要的是，虽然更多的传统财务领导者通常会保护他们拥有的数据，但那些采用高级分析的人（作者称之为<em>数字财务领导者</em>）成为了跨公司孤岛实现数据民主化的强烈倡导者。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="no-underline">兑现卓越</a></h4><h6>罗伯特·D·奥斯汀、罗伯特·H·海耶斯和理查德·L·诺兰</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>太多的领导者从事<em>绩效黑客活动</em>——提供特定指标以提供有效领导的表象，但没有产生真正的绩效。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>最近的破坏性事件，如欧洲的流行病和战争，暴露了因短视的领导决策而削弱的企业。对西南航空公司、波音和通用电气的分析着眼于为什么成功的公司会牺牲他们多年来建立的卓越业务——包括作为其基础的价值观和关系——以换取短期的财务收益，例如成本削减和股价上涨最终损害利益相关者。作者分享了表明领导者正在参与实践的典型警告标志。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="no-underline">打开职业公平的快速通道</a></h4><h6>黑格·R·纳尔班提安</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>了解推动员工晋升的因素可以帮助管理者更公平地定位女性和有色人种以获得晋升。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>新研究表明，与员工的知识、能力或行为无关的因素对职业发展有巨大影响。向高绩效人员报告、担任主管等职业加速器角色以及不利用灵活的工作选择等情况都对晋升和加薪起到了主导作用。绩效评级的差异也会产生连锁效应，对有色人种产生不利影响：在作者的研究中，大多数公司的有色人种获得高绩效评级的可能性降低了 50%。由于评级往往会持续存在，一年的高评级预示着下一年的高评级的可能性，从一开始就被拒之门外会严重阻碍职业发展。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="no-underline">工作中同伴支持的不平等回报</a></h4><h6>南希·贝姆和康斯坦斯·努南·哈德利</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>工作满意度部分来自人们对他们的组织认可和重视他们为同事提供的社会支持的感觉。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>员工之间的支持行为可以提高敬业度和生产力，但研究表明，男性从这种努力中获得的收益比女性多。社会支持包括情感帮助、增强自尊、社会陪伴、信息或建议以及工具性帮助。在作者的研究中，与男性相比，更多的女性将精力集中在倾听、表现出个人兴趣和赞美同事上，而男性则报告说更频繁地提供职业建议。尽管男性表示他们提供的社会支持总体上比女性少，但他们获得了更高水平的组织鼓励、奖励和工作满意度。管理者可以通过让看不见的东西变得可见和有价值来鼓励更公平的同行文化——明确哪些行为很重要，同时修改绩效管理系统。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="no-underline">超越实验孤岛，走向人工智能无处不在</a></h4><h6>Amit Joshi、Ivy Buche 和 Miguel Paredes Sadler</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>从孤立的实验开始人工智能工作可能是有意义的，但需要新的、全公司范围的结构来扩展它们并获得更广泛的利益。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>人工智能通常在组织内的孤立实验中扎根，许多公司因为难以超越这些试点而在 AI 之旅中停滞不前。扩展技术需要不同类型的正式结构：作者发现，人工智能项目通常以实验孤岛开始，然后围绕企业<em>卓越中心</em>聚集在一起。然后，一小部分人转向建立在知识、系统、流程和工具的集中基础以及分散的嵌入式功能之上的复杂的<em>专业知识联合</em>模型。有 AI 雄心的企业如果打算发挥该技术的潜力，就需要准备好在启动阶段进行两次结构性飞跃。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="no-underline">管理您的劳动力生态系统，而不仅仅是您的员工</a></h4><h6>伊丽莎白·J·奥特曼、大卫·基隆、杰夫·施瓦茨和罗宾·琼斯</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>需要新的组织结构来协调包括大量外部员工和合作伙伴在内的劳动力生态系统。</p><p><strong>要点：</strong>大多数高管同意“劳动力”的概念正在重新定义。他们说它比组织的全职员工更广泛，而是包括承包商、临时工、服务提供商甚至技术的生态系统。这些网络需要创新的管理实践，因为分层的、命令和控制的领导不适合跨越内部和外部边界的劳动力。在开发新实践时，领导者必须解决三类问题：结构设计（与劳动分工、目标和激励有关）、政治（与资源、权力和地位有关）和文化（影响个人对身份的寻求）和意义）。有意识地协调一个考虑所有参与者的视角，可以更细致地了解组织及其合作伙伴如何合作以实现其战略目标。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><p></p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>专业服务公司如何避免颠覆</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:23:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Julian Birkinshaw and David Lancefield. <p>朱利安·伯金肖 (Julian Birkinshaw) 是伦敦商学院战略学教授，兼任副院长。大卫·兰斯菲尔德 (David Lancefield) 是 CEO 催化剂、战略家和教练，曾任普华永道高级合伙人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors conducted in-depth interviews with more than 25 senior professionals in consultancies and law firms. They also reviewed case studies of a dozen would-be disrupters and carried out an extensive review of the literature. Professional services firms have been threatened with disruption for a long time. In 2015, Richard and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Birkinshaw_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">西蒙·普拉德斯</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者对超过 25 位咨询公司和律师事务所的高级专业人士进行了深入访谈。</li><li>他们还回顾了十几个潜在颠覆者的案例研究，并对文献进行了广泛的回顾。</li></ul></aside><p>专业服务公司长期以来一直面临中断的威胁。 2015 年，Richard 和 Daniel Susskind 预见到技术将导致“对传统有血有肉的专业人士的需求稳步下降”，而最近，CB Insights 表示“结构性破坏正在冲击管理咨询”。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>更早之前，克莱顿·克里斯滕森 (Clayton Christensen) 及其同事警告说：“虽然我们无法预测咨询行业颠覆的确切进展，但我们可以非常有信心地说，无论其速度如何，一些现任者都会措手不及。” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2个</a></p><p>但事情并没有像预期的那样发展。在咨询和法律领域，成熟的公司一如既往地具有影响力和盈利能力。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>许多潜在的破坏者已经出现。有些失败了，有些获得了强大的利基地位，但没有人挑战——更不用说推翻——现有秩序了。大多数老牌领导者都使用了广泛的战略和策略来快速适应威胁。</p><p></p><p>与许多成熟行业的情况一样，专业服务市场由一小部分可清楚识别的顶端群体和大量在其影子下运营的低端公司主导。咨询的巨头包括麦肯锡、波士顿咨询集团和贝恩；科技公司 Accenture 和 Capgemini；以及四大会计师事务所安永、德勤、毕马威和普华永道。在法律领域，顶级律师事务所包括五家总部位于伦敦的律师事务所，非正式地称为“魔圈”——年利达律师事务所、高伟绅律师事务所、富而德律师事务所、安理国际律师事务所和斯劳特梅律师事务所——以及凯易律师事务所、瑞生律师事务所和欧华律师事务所。</p><p>这些公司为何如此有弹性？我们的研究包括对 25 位高管的访谈以及对十几个潜在颠覆者的案例研究的回顾，揭示了许多因素在起作用。最有效的公司的区别在于它们有能力诊断潜在的破坏原因并做出相应的反应。</p><p>我们将<em>行业颠覆</em>定义为对既定秩序的颠覆，现有企业输给新的竞争对手。正如 Joshua Gans 所说，当现有公司对客户的需求存在盲点（需求方效应），或者当新技术使现有公司的现有能力过时（供应方效应）时，就会发生颠覆——或者是以下因素的组合他们俩。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> （参见“咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁</h4><p class="caption">专业服务公司在需求和供应方面都面临着威胁。</p><p class="caption">随着在职者交付的能力对客户的价值下降，供应方中断会增加。需求方中断随着客户行为变化的增加而增加。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Birkinshaw-Figure.png" alt="咨询和法律领域的四种潜在威胁" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>由于每种情况都需要自己的应对措施，因此了解供需双方影响的动态可以使任何部门的高管更容易识别潜在的破坏者并将其拒之门外。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5个</a></p><h3>需求方和供应方的威胁</h3><p>根据我们的研究，我们将人工智能技术确定为最大的供应方风险，威胁要接管专业人士传统上视为自己的工作。在需求方面，威胁来自客户寻求更好地控制他们购买和使用专业服务的方式。还有其他潜在的颠覆者同时从供需双方挑战现有企业。与此同时，新的精品和专业公司已经出现，以满足利润丰厚的业务领域的特定客户需求，尽管它们很少真正具有颠覆性。下面，我们将详细介绍每个潜在威胁。</p><p><strong>人工智能破坏了商业模式。</strong> 2022 年 11 月推出的生成式 AI 加速了专业服务工作许多方面的持续转型，从而提高了准确性并显着节省了成本。</p><p>在律师事务所，人工智能工具扫描法律文件并审查合同。基于人工智能的服务公司，如 Kira Systems、Clio、Reveal-Brainspace、iManage 和汤森路透，在发现、尽职调查以及合同管理和审查方面提供帮助。 97% 的大型律师事务所使用汤森路透的服务。</p><p>这些公司并不将自己定位为律师事务所的竞争对手，但随着它们规模的扩大和技术能力的增强，它们可能会开始破坏这些公司的商业模式。例如，Clio 的法律软件可以对索赔进行电子发现，甚至可以通过扫描先例案例进行诉讼分析，从而有可能减少公司可以向客户收取的计费小时数。</p><p>在咨询中，人工智能可以帮助专业服务公司发现新的关系、识别客户行为模式并突出节省成本的机会，从而提供额外的价值。 “与一个比其他任何人都更了解这个行业的团队一起出现已经不够好了，”一位四大咨询合伙人说。 “你还需要一个数据集或算法来提供额外的价值来源。”</p><p>但人工智能也可以成为强大的破坏者。 Palantir Technologies 开始使用 AI 来检测欺诈，后来扩展到应用最先进的机器学习来解决各种政府和私人客户的问题。它支持政府监督的工作引起了争议，但其预测分析帮助一家大型汽车供应商在其工程和制造职能方面取得了巨大的效率提升。这样的结果代表了咨询公司可以提供的洞察力的严谨性和质量的重大进步。</p><p>老牌公司已经通过收购和内部开发建立自己的人工智能能力来应对威胁。自 2013 年以来，麦肯锡收购了 12 家主要是小型人工智能公司，其中包括总部位于英国的 QuantumBlack，该公司使用先进的数据分析来提高组织绩效。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>在法律方面，总部位于旧金山的 DLA Piper 开发了 Aiscension，这是一种监控合规风险的人工智能产品。保险律师事务所 Kennedys 创建了 Kennedys IQ 衍生产品，它使用人工智能来评估医学证据并建议赔偿金额。</p><p>这些收购和合作伙伴关系提供的不仅仅是新功能；他们可以扩大他们的公司可以为客户处理的问题的范围。</p><p>现任者也在加强他们作为高接触可信顾问的作用，这是人工智能无法复制的。几家大型咨询公司通过投资体验中心扩大了他们的产品范围——客户和顾问在物理和虚拟环境中使用设计思维和其他创造性技术来设想可能的未来。在过去五年中，IBM、德勤、埃森哲和其他公司收购了 200 多家创意机构来帮助开发这些中心。</p><p><strong>客户控制：拆分服务。</strong>最深远的需求方威胁是分拆，因为越来越精明的客户正在寻找降低成本的方法，并对他们与服务公司的关系施加更大的影响。这可能意味着回收以前由外部公司处理的活动或求助于专家而不是大型专业公司的广泛服务。这两种选择都可以帮助客户建立内部能力，并对业务成果承担更大的责任。但分拆威胁到现有公司的杠杆模式，因为它剥夺了通常分配给许多初级和低薪通才的工作。</p><p>在法律上，替代法律服务提供商 (ALSP) 的出现证明了这种需求方威胁。 ALSP 本身并不是律师事务所，但它们以较低的成本提供广泛的法律服务，例如文件审查或合同管理。 2017 年，位于弗吉尼亚州的 IT 服务公司 DXC Technology 将其几乎全部法律职能外包给了位于堪萨斯州欧弗兰帕克的 ALSP UnitedLex。 DXC 将 150 名内部律师转移到 UnitedLex，只保留了少数高级专业人员。虽然外包内部法律部门并不少见，但律师事务所认为这是一个巨大的威胁，因为这是当时同类交易中最大的交易，而且它涉及 ALSP，可以提供更低的成本结构。</p><p>咨询网络的兴起（例如总部位于伦敦的 Eden McCallum）和在线平台（例如总部位于纽约的 Gerson Lehrman Group）也面临着类似的挑战。这些公司在逐个项目的基础上为客户匹配顾问，绕过大公司。总部位于伦敦的 Kubrick Group 与公司签订合同，提供数据科学家和技术专家团队，客户稍后可以聘用他们。</p><p>这种安排让客户有责任定义其问题并整合工作团队——传统上由大型咨询公司处理的事情。但是除了最大和最复杂的项目外，它们消除了雇用大公司的需要。如果没有现任者更高的管理费用，费用就会低得多。</p><p>客户也在改变商业安排，越来越多地要求基于结果的交易，要求顾问证明他们对预期结果直接负责，例如成本降低 5%。因为对于涉及顾问影响之外的因素（例如收入增长）的项目，这可能更难做到，所以大多数公司只有在他们有信心为预期结果做出贡献时才会同意基于结果的交易。</p><p>现有公司正在以多种方式应对这些需求方的挑战。律师事务所已经成立了自己的 ALSP；总部位于伦敦的 Allen &amp; Overy 于 2013 年创建了 Peerpoint，这是一个独立的业务，拥有 350 名主要是自由职业的律师和 5300 万英镑（6400 万美元）的收入。在咨询方面，德勤创建了一个名为 Pixel 的部门，将客户问题分解成各个组成部分，然后使用众包平台寻找合适的专家来处理每个部分。</p><p>大公司也在加倍发挥其传统优势：解决客户最大和最具挑战性的问题。他们的价值来自他们在高影响、大规模、高风险情况下提供建议和合规的能力，并且他们可以为服务收取额外费用。 “我们做的是心脏直视手术，而不是提供 [全科医生] 服务，”一位资深律师说。</p><p><strong>精品店和专家在市场关注中找到优势。</strong>随着前顶级合作伙伴建立自己的精品店或风险投资公司支持新的创业公司，专业服务领域不断出现新的竞争对手。成功的公司在特定的利基市场占据了市场份额，但很少引起顶级公司的关注。它们对需求或供应方造成的干扰有限，它们只是反映了市场的异质性和复杂性。</p><p>在咨询方面，总部位于伦敦的 Baringa 通过专注于能源行业、确定可再生能源等热门话题并聘请使用情景建模来预测未来能源价格的专家，实现了快速发展。总部位于纽约的 AlixPartners 专注于扭亏为盈、诉讼支持和转型。两家公司都有 1,000 多名员工。法律行业见证了专家的快速成长，例如美国的 Caldwell Intellectual Property Law 和英国和新加坡的争议专家 Mishcon de Reya。这些公司的成功表明，深厚的专业知识可以如何创造一个可以抵御基础广泛的竞争对手的可防御的利基市场。</p><p>大公司并不将这些小企业视为直接威胁，而且常常完全忽视它们。 “他们不在我们与 C-suite 的工作中，”伦敦一家大型律师事务所的合伙人说。尽管如此，它们仍可以帮助现任者保持警惕。</p><p>其一，它们为不断变化的市场提供了一个窗口，通常会促使老牌公司进入它们原本可能被忽视的业务领域。例如，德勤针对专业精品公司的出现推出了数字业务。贝恩创建并剥离了 The Bridgespan Group，以专注于非营利组织。</p><p>专业公司还可以暴露顶级公司工作方式中需要注意的弱点。例如，专注于电信、媒体和技术领域的全球最大战略咨询公司 Altman Solon 吸引了最高管理层的关注，这在很大程度上是因为整个公司由在这些领域具有深厚专业知识的专家组成，这与许多填补初级职位的大公司不同有很多聪明的多面手。因此，它已经跟上了其运营所在行业的步伐，因此能够更好地快速制定客户特定的战略。</p><p><strong>潜在的破坏者会带来供需双方的风险。</strong>现任者的噩梦场景是同时影响供需双方的中断。这最终就是杀死柯达和宝丽来的原因：数字技术改变了图像的创建方式和消费方式，让现任者没有任何价值可以依靠。摄影行业的幸存者，如富士和佳能，是通过进入邻近市场而不是留下来战斗来做到这一点的。</p><p>这些挑战者已经出现在专业服务领域，但到目前为止，他们还没有成为颠覆者。例如，成立于 2013 年的 HourlyNerd 雄心勃勃，希望成为连接技术客户与自由顾问的市场，以比典型采购流程更快的速度为客户提供更广泛的顾问选择。 “我们喜欢将自己视为可能聘请咨询公司的替代者，”其中一位联合创始人说。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Axiom Law 成立于 2000 年，致力于通过员工和合作伙伴网络提供随需应变的法律人才，从而更有效地提供法律服务。 “Axiom 有机会颠覆一个世纪以来未发生实质性变化的行业，”一位投资者表示。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8个</a></p><p>两家公司都做得不错。 HourlyNerd 于 2016 年更名为 Catalant，转向软件即服务模式，如今拥有数百名员工。 Axiom 是一家中型律师事务所，拥有约 1,600 名员工，年收入为 8.425 亿美元，其商业模式比大多数竞争对手都更加灵活。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>但两者都没有达到它所期望的破坏性效果。</p><p></p><h3>地平线上的破坏性威胁</h3><p>那么，是什么迫在眉睫的干扰让管理咨询和律师事务所的高管们夜不能寐？</p><p>我们采访的高级专业人士指出的一个因素是人工智能和分析能力的显着加速。在法律中，编纂——捕捉经验丰富的合作伙伴的法律推理并将其转化为可以应用于未来案件的算法的过程——可能会消除专业人士现在所做的大部分认知工作。 “那将是破坏性的，”伦敦一家大型公司的合伙人说。</p><p>其他一些人表示，近期最大的威胁很可能来自科技巨头：尤其是谷歌、亚马逊、微软和 Salesforce。 Each has built client-facing capabilities, some from the large consulting firms, to enhance their strength in selling solutions to clients&#39; technology challenges.</p><p> With their AI capabilities and global reach, they could affect both the supply and demand sides of professional firms&#39; businesses. For example, using the vast amount of data at its disposal, Amazon Web Services could exploit its unique insights into customer behavior to provide retail clients with forecasts of online shopping trends.</p><p> “The greatest impact of Amazon Web Services won&#39;t lie in its position as a supplier of cloud services, but in the extraordinary scale and depth of its information on consumer buying behavior, which no conventional consulting firm could begin to compete with,” said a partner in a large consulting firm.</p><p> Others downplayed the threat. “The likes of Google are not actually that good at client service,” one interviewee said. While it is possible that a tech company could buy a large consulting firm, that would represent a significant strategic pivot from the typical approach of developing partnerships with consulting firms and would reduce the number of firms it could partner with in the future.</p><h3> Staying Nimble</h3><p> The big professional services firms haven&#39;t avoided disruption simply because of the actions they&#39;ve taken. More important is their vigilance and responsiveness to changes in their business environment. While consulting and law firm executives often disparage their seemingly old-fashioned ways of working, their professional partnership models have proved to be remarkably resilient.</p><p> From our interviews, we identified three elements of success that are worth highlighting as potentially applicable to other sectors as well.</p><p> <strong>Innovation efforts are devoted to solving client problems.</strong> This contrasts with many other businesses, where innovation activities are pursued separately from the customer-facing parts of the organization. The best professional services firms pursue product and service innovations based on common limitations, frictions, and opportunities they&#39;ve identified in their clients&#39; businesses. They then develop, test, and refine those innovations with selected clients and partner organizations — such as technology providers — before launching them across their client portfolios.</p><p> <strong>Partners and their juniors work closely together with clients.</strong> The firms&#39; apprenticeship model means that the sense-response gap — the difference between sensing client needs and then taking appropriate action to address them — is narrower than in firms where the leaders are a long way removed from those doing the work.</p><p> <strong>Firms take a cautious approach to investing in new activities.</strong> While this might seem to be a weakness in a fast-changing world, the truth is that most emerging technologies take a long time to realize their potential, and plenty of firms have failed by moving too quickly. Because of the project-based nature of their work, professional firms are able to test new technologies, see what works, and then move forward based on project success and client demand.</p><h3> Staying Ahead of Disruption</h3><p> The experience of professional services firms in holding off potential disruption suggests four actions that firms in other sectors can take to prepare for and respond to change.</p><p> <strong>Diagnose the threat.</strong> While every new competitor or technology can be seen as a potential threat, it&#39;s necessary to assess the magnitude of the risk and the part of the business that it might affect. The consulting and law firms we studied were mostly very thoughtful about separating out the demand- and supply-side effects. (See “Diagnosing the Nature of the Disruptive Threat” for how to apply this logic.)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Diagnosing the Nature of the Disruptive Threat</h4><p class="caption"> Consider an emerging technology or new competitor in your industry and answer the following questions to determine the nature of the disruptive threat.</p><p class="print no-mobile no-desktop caption"> Take the assessment at https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/</p><p> <a id="interactive-modal" href="#modal-container" class="is-button aqua no-print" style="max-width:275px">Take the assessment now</a> </p><p class="caption"><svg height="20.25" viewBox="0 0 18.183 20.25" width="18.183" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><clipPath id="a"><path d="m0 0h18.183v20.25h-18.183z"></path></clipPath><g clip-path="url(#a)"><path d="m17.081 12.4a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v5.648a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1 1.1h-15.981a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1-1.1v-5.648a1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1-1.1 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v4.546h13.642v-4.546a1.324 1.324 0 0 1 1.24-1.1m-11.71-4.135 2.618 2.617v-9.642a1.214 1.214 0 0 1 1.102-1.24 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v9.643l2.617-2.48a1.012 1.012 0 0 1 .827-.276 1.958 1.958 0 0 1 .827.276 1.254 1.254 0 0 1 0 1.653l-4.545 4.548c-.138.138-.276.138-.413.276a.878.878 0 0 1 -.827 0c-.138 0-.276-.138-.413-.276l-4.546-4.684a1.081 1.081 0 0 1 0-1.515 1.257 1.257 0 0 1 1.653 0" fill="#000000"></path></g></svg> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a3e29f5546.pdf" target="_blank" class="marketing_click" id="Download_Assessment[Birkinshaw_article]" rel="noopener">Download the scorecard (PDF)</a></p><div id="modal-container"><div  id="btn-close-modal" class="close-modal-container"> ← RETURN TO ARTICLE </div><div class="modal-content"><iframe src="https://survey.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_eWAtUnHf3GCdswu" width="100%" frameborder="0"></iframe></div></p></div><p><script>$("#interactive-modal").animatedModal({modalTarget:'modal-container',animatedIn:'fadeInRightBig',animatedOut:'fadeOutRightBig',animationDuration:'.6s',color:'#292929',overflow:'hidden'});</script></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Match the response to the challenge.</strong> Once the supply and demand effects have been mapped, it&#39;s possible to target the appropriate response. Demand-side challenges require experimentation in how clients&#39; needs can be anticipated, understood, met, and adjusted to. Professional services firms are inherently good at this. Project teams are empowered to come up with creative solutions and to experiment with alternative models for forming partnerships and delivering services. This should serve as a cautionary note to firms that have become too “corporate,” with decisions flowing from the top down to partners and teams.</p><p> Supply-side changes, in contrast, require investment in new capabilities and an openness to restructuring and even outsourcing internal activities. This often requires a higher level of centralization, frequently with a dedicated team that hires from the outside or makes small acquisitions. The challenge is to integrate them with client project teams so they are deployed in the market.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Stay focused on the organization&#39;s true mission.</strong> While there are plenty of genuine threats out there, there&#39;s also a lot of noise. Paying too much attention to all of the changes swirling around can cause leaders to lose sight of the bigger picture. For professional services firms, the client relationship transcends all else, and the appropriate response to both demand- and supply-driven threats is to double down on that relationship. “We want to retain the overall relationship, focusing on the areas of premium work,” the partner in a large London law firm said. “The debate is how much we leave ... to other law firms and how much we retain and do via third parties or alternative delivery models.”</p><p> <strong>Balance pragmatism with a healthy paranoia.</strong> The law and consulting partners we spoke with in our interviews were genuinely torn. On the one hand, they saw little or no evidence that their strong positions were under threat, and they agreed that the dire predictions of disruption from a decade ago had been unfounded. On the other hand, they did not want to appear complacent, and they certainly didn&#39;t want to send a message to their junior colleagues that there were no future risks of disruption. Executives must learn to live with a dual mindset: a pragmatic acknowledgment that the fundamentals are sound, coupled with a paranoid suspicion of emerging technologies or new competitors. After all, it was those incumbents that might be caught by surprise that Christensen and his colleagues considered most at risk of disruption.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Risk Intelligence and the Resilient Company</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:05:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ananya Sheth and Joseph V. Sinfield. <p>Ananya Sheth ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ananyasheth">@ananyasheth</a> ) is a postdoctoral research fellow at the School of Business, Stevens Institute of Technology. Joseph V. Sinfield is a professor of civil engineering and the director of the Institute for Innovation Science at Purdue University.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Business Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors undertook a holistic study of enterprise resilience that began with the extraction of corporate risk factors from two decades of 10-Ks filed by S&#038;P 500 companies, investment analyst reports, and academic databases. They organized the risks into a value-centric framework composed of eight functions and 99 major risk categories; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Sheth_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Simon Prades</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors undertook a holistic study of enterprise resilience that began with the extraction of corporate risk factors from two decades of 10-Ks filed by S&amp;P 500 companies, investment analyst reports, and academic databases.</li><li> They organized the risks into a value-centric framework composed of eight functions and 99 major risk categories; they then cross-linked the categories and functions with input from risk experts and leaders in 10 economic sectors and 26 industries to create a quantitative risk network.</li><li> They also analyzed cybersecurity risk acknowledgment in S&amp;P 500 10-Ks for five sectors.</li><li> This material is based upon work supported by the National Science Foundation under grant no. 2049782.</li></ul></aside><p> Building the resilience of large, complex enterprises is critical in today&#39;s uncertain and interconnected world. At a time when a container ship grounded in the Suez Canal can bottle up 12% of the world&#39;s trade, or a virus can disrupt the global flow of commodities, components, and talent, a corporation&#39;s ability to quickly adapt in the face of unfolding events is essential to its survival and prosperity.</p><p> Business resilience is a dynamic property that is retrospectively measured by the stability and longevity of corporate value across changing contexts. In real time, it manifests in an enterprise&#39;s timely adaptation to both immediate and gradual changes in the business environment.</p><p> Our work, which employs a complex adaptive systems view of businesses, shows that resilience derives from three fundamental adaptive capacities: sensing and monitoring, to recognize emerging changes in the business environment; business model portfolio development, to build and test capabilities across operating contexts; and fundamental capability development, to drive growth with longevity and avoid corporate stall. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Moreover, each of these capacities hinges on the development of a capability for <em>risk intelligence</em> .</p><p></p><p> We define risk intelligence as the honed ability to rigorously interpret risks and the consequences or opportunities they pose for a company. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> It allows leaders to see through environmental complexity and systematically identify, categorize, and interpret risks. This enables them to look beyond known risk factors and intentionally explore yet-to-be-known risks, thereby embracing rather than avoiding uncertainty. Importantly, risk intelligence brings recognition that individual risks or the forms in which they manifest matter far less than the often-shared consequences they have on a company&#39;s value exchange system — that is, the manner in which it manages, identifies, creates, conveys, delivers, captures, protects, and sustains value. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> And finally, it provides leaders with a network view of risks that enables more effective allocation of risk mitigation resources by illuminating not just the direct consequences of risks but the manner in which they could cascade across the company&#39;s value exchange system. In this article, we break down risk intelligence into actionable elements that leaders can pursue to help toughen their organizations for the long term.</p><h3> Identify, Categorize, and Interpret Risk Events</h3><p> Leaders cannot accurately predict specific risk events, nor can they prepare their companies for all risks. They can, however, identify, categorize, and interpret risk events in a systematic manner that reveals how seemingly different events could have similar consequences.</p><p> The first step is to work through each business value function and identify plausible risk events that may have implications for its effectiveness. To aid in this process, we constructed an industry-agnostic inventory organizing three tiers of 99 major risk categories identified in our study in relation to individual value exchange system components. (See “A Value Function Risk Inventory.”) While inevitably not exhaustive, this resource serves as a robust starting point to identify potential risks faced by any enterprise. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig1"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> A Value Function Risk Inventory</h4><p class="caption"> This risk inventory derived from 20 years of S&amp;P 500 data shows how the functions of a company&#39;s value exchange system (green nodes) link to business functions and their respective risk categories. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig1.png" alt="A Value Function Risk Inventory"/></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Next, leaders should characterize and group risk events by their <em>scope</em> of impact, the <em>permanence</em> of the changes they induce, and the <em>frequency</em> of event occurrence. (See “Characterizing Risks.”) Leaders can then interpret the linkages between each group of risk events and the components of the company&#39;s value exchange system.</p><div class="callout-highlight" id="fig2"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Characterizing Risks</h4><p class="caption"> Every risk can be characterized according to how widely its impact may be felt, how long the changes it causes may last, and how often it occurs. For example, a major snow event has intra-industry scope, induces temporary changes, and occurs infrequently. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig2.png" alt="Characterizing Risks" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Risk categorization begins with understanding a risk event&#39;s scope, which conveys a sense of how widely a risk&#39;s effects will be felt across the range of affected stakeholders. The wide scope of the COVID-19 pandemic created supply- and demand-side effects across entire value networks, whereas narrow-scope events, such as a labor strike at an individual manufacturing facility, tend to have more bounded effects. When multiple stakeholders experience simultaneous or sequential disruptions, the increased complexity of the impact prevents the system from self-organizing to normalcy. Such circumstances also may invite interventions from sovereign states or international organizations, which can aid recovery or act as new disruptive forces.</p><p> To fully categorize risk events, leaders must also consider the permanence of their consequences. Both the pandemic and the 2021 Suez Canal blockage caused supply-side disruptions, but the permanence of the changes each event induced varied significantly. While supply chain shocks such as the canal blockage often follow a self-organizing correction mechanism in which price increases lower demand and normalize the lagging supply, the same formula cannot be applied to counter a protracted situation like the pandemic. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> It is important to understand permanence before planning and implementing a response strategy. For example, the business interruption created by the pandemic had a scope that was broader and consequences that were of greater permanence, affecting a significantly larger set of value system functions in comparison to the more limited impact of the canal blockage.</p><p></p><p> How often a risk event occurs is important too, because the enterprise mechanisms needed to handle frequent events can be different from those employed for singular events. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Although companies learn from all events, their responses to those that occur repeatedly are typically converted into standard operating procedures. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> For example, the adoption of barcodes and scanners to track and manage inventory in real time has largely eliminated stock-keeping record errors and delays resulting from mismatching data.</p><p> Our scope, permanence, and frequency (SPF) framework provides a structured view that shows how a risk event itself is less important than its consequences. The framework is especially useful when multiple risk events occur at the same time, because it gives managers a common, logical approach for considering them and quickly gaining information and understanding. By then connecting those events to the company&#39;s value exchange system, managers can more easily see when diverse risks are nonetheless leading to similar consequences for its value functions. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Consider a manufacturer dealing with both an overseas supplier whose products are suddenly subject to much higher tariffs due to a trade war, and the bankruptcy of a value chain partner. These risk events share SPF characteristics (the scope of both is interfirm, their permanence is reversible, and their frequency is low), and, as important, both events also affect the same value functions. The bankruptcy and the trade war are both likely to slow inputs and raise costs on the supply side and make it more difficult to meet customer demand. Both also would require the manufacturer to secure new supply sources and stabilize operational cash flow. By characterizing these potential risk events according to the SPF framework and linking them to value functions, managers can then view them more simply as groups of risks that have shared consequences for a company&#39;s specific value functions and deserve similar preparedness and response.</p><h3> Compartmentalize and Reduce Uncertainty</h3><p> Uncertainty about the consequences of a risk event is unavoidable, but it can be managed based on where the level of uncertainty falls on a spectrum between complete knowledge and complete ignorance (both of which are extreme and unlikely). <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Leaders should then seek to convert risks with higher levels of impact uncertainty to lower levels. (See “Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column" id="fig3"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty</h4><p class="caption"> Once managers have mapped risks to the appropriate level, they should take the critical action recommended to convert higher-order risks to lower-order risks. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig3.png" alt="Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p> Risk events causing level 1 uncertainty usually entail a very limited number of future scenarios with clear intrafirm effects, where causal linkages between risk events and the enterprise&#39;s value exchange system can be accurately known. Examples of such events include routine variation in production, expected sales losses, and human errors in performing manual tasks. When specific types of level 1 events occur frequently, they are indicative of errors in process or oversight that can be rectified permanently if diagnosed correctly. For instance, cargo thefts — a recurrent problem at logjammed transport hubs — can be prevented using optical character recognition scanners that track container freight and maintain real-time records. Importantly, at level 1, the overall uncertainty of the impact on firm value is within an expected, acceptable range.</p><p> Risk events causing level 2 uncertainty involve a larger number of alternate future scenarios and have interfirm consequences; however, even though they are more challenging, the probability that they will occur and their effects can be estimated. Businesses&#39; formal scenario planning exercises often involve level 2 events in which previously acquired knowledge regarding the impact of risk factors leads to improved accuracy and an effective exercise overall. The six-day Suez Canal blockage was predictable because a multiship pileup had closed the canal for two days in 2018. As a result, the Pentagon had already worked a longer blockage into its normal operational preparedness. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Risk events causing level 3 uncertainty involve a bounded set of scenarios where certain known risk events may affect the company in unknown ways. There is limited knowledge about how a chain reaction of consequences from a risk event might manifest at this level. Typically, these risks include less frequently occurring events with intra-industry scope and multistakeholder implications, which should be considered worst-case scenarios.</p><p> <a href="https://www.portrevel.com/">Port Revel</a> , a training facility situated on a lake in the French Alps, reduces level 3 uncertainty by helping ocean shipping companies simulate worst cases and identify the previously unknown consequences of operating increasingly large container ships through shipping infrastructure largely designed for smaller vessels. It closely replicates conditions at the trickiest spots in maritime transport, allowing trainee pilots to navigate scaled giant container ships through strong gusts of wind across a mini-Suez, steer and dock cruise ships in a crowded mini-San Francisco Bay, and maneuver oil tankers through an imitation Port Arthur. These exercises draw out unanticipated ship performance and pilot behaviors, helping to identify and address previously unknown event consequences.</p><p> Level 4 uncertainty encompasses events with unknown risk factors that could have a variety of negative consequences, the repercussions of which can&#39;t be estimated. These unknown unknowns are usually expressed in 10-Ks through statements such as “Other unknown risks may impact our business operations and projected performance.” It is challenging to develop scenario models in the presence of unknown unknowns. The models are incomplete representations of the world that could entail risks unimagined while developing them.</p><p> Once leaders order the uncertainty of impact into levels, they can focus on converting higher-level impact uncertainty into lower levels by discovering unknowns through data, simulation modeling, and logical analyses. For instance, the three-year gap between the UK&#39;s Brexit referendum in 2016 and its departure from the European Union in 2019 offered leaders an opportunity to convert the imagined event into likely scenarios and capture its vast trade implications. By focusing on the most vulnerable aspects of their value chains, such as those with the highest number of cross-border transactions, leaders could have recognized the imminent redistribution of goods passing through congested ports and modeled rerouting scenarios. For example, Felixstowe was known to be handling 48% of the UK&#39;s container trade, which could have been sent instead to multiple smaller and less busy ports. Evidence of impending port congestion also could have implied the high likelihood of delays and the need to hold more inventory in the UK to guarantee on-time deliveries.</p><p> Systemwide changes that are likely to have permanent effects are typically caused by noticeable megatrends, such as technological breakthroughs, changes in consumer demand patterns, global events, or regulatory body interventions. Once these trends are on a company&#39;s radar, they can be tracked and rapidly interpreted (if the necessary observation and modeling capabilities are in place). For instance, the European Union&#39;s carbon border tax, which was enacted in December 2022 after years of debate, won&#39;t be fully implemented until 2026, offering companies several years to reduce the uncertainty arising from it.</p><p></p><p> Further, for potential events that may be infrequent yet high impact, businesses can examine other industries where the consequences of similar events might be better recognized; then they can interpret the implications for their own value exchange system. For example, Brexit strategists could have studied cross-border trade between the US and Canada and the US and Mexico in the automobile and white goods sectors to help them navigate looming free-trade agreements and border regulations.</p><p> The active identification of plausible risk events and their potential consequences are the kinds of actions that contribute to building true risk intelligence. However, our research indicates that companies place little emphasis on discovering unknown and plausible risk events and their outcomes and instead focus attention on managing known risks. We also find that companies do not have a similarly complete knowledge of risks, even when those risks are publicly disclosed by direct competitors. Our study of 10-Ks revealed significant variation in the acknowledgment of risk factors, even among companies in the same industry. For instance, there was a lag of as much as eight years in acknowledging cyber risks after the first public data breach within a group of 18 comparable companies in the financial sector. This pattern was consistent in four additional sectors — including retail, telecom, technology, and health care.</p><p> Moreover, our analyses revealed only marginal levels of acknowledgment of causal relationships between risk factors, which are how risks impact companies in the real world. It is only logical that a known or unknown risk factor, when manifested, would likely influence other linked known and unknown risk factors, thereby creating a cascade of consequences. This ultimately would affect a company in potentially known but unexpected (or, worse, misunderstood) ways.</p><p></p><p> While most companies think they are preparing for risk events, they tend to focus only on level 1 and 2 uncertainty and therefore develop highly specific but narrow mitigation plans. Take Maersk, for example, which in 2017 fell victim to a ransomware cyberattack that brought down its entire network for days and halted its operations at 76 port terminals globally at a cost of roughly $300 million. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Yet the shipping company did not publicly acknowledge the risk of a cyberattack until its 2013 annual report, despite the risk of hacking and other cyberthreats having been well known since the late 1990s (although perhaps not seriously regarded as a primary risk for shippers). Thus, few risks are entirely unknown, and industry-specific unknowns may not be unknowns in other sectors.</p><h3> Construct and Contextualize an Enterprise Risk Network</h3><p> To gain clearer insight into level 3 and 4 uncertainty, it is important to understand the linkages among enterprise risks. Developing quantified risk networks (QRNs) can help. A QRN is a weighted map that links all identified potential risks to a company&#39;s value exchange system functions and helps decision makers interpret related impacts. Moreover, QRNs can reveal counterintuitive insights, such as a function&#39;s indirect exposure to risks typically associated with a different but connected function. For example, the risk of inaccurately forecasting shipping demand in a freight company directly affects its operating expense management function and indirectly affects facility capacity, operational capability, and customer concessions, as well as the company&#39;s reputation.</p><p> Companies should build their own risk networks for three reasons. First, each company has its own unique value exchange system that is best understood by its leaders. Second, resilient companies need to build in redundancies, which is challenging to do in resource-constrained environments. Custom QRNs highlight the most connected — and most vulnerable — value functions, creating an order of priority for allocating resources to bolster the enterprise. Third, custom QRNs provide a shared picture of risk for company leaders, who may or may not agree on critical vulnerabilities. The QRN-building activity focuses managerial attention on the often disregarded but potentially crucial functions and related risk categories to ultimately help leaders anticipate and prepare for the future.</p><p> To begin constructing your company&#39;s risk network, identify the risk events that are particularly relevant to your business by working from critical value functions upon which it relies and from the risk categories captured in the inventory. Identify plausible risk events in each category from data sources such as company memos, public risk disclosures, investment analyst reports, and historical knowledge. For example, leaders managing the operations function can use inventory risk categories, such as facilities and process management, sourcing, and distribution, to build a list of plausible risk factors or events (such as an unexpected storm, an equipment malfunction, input shortages, drained emergency supplies, worker health emergencies, communications interruptions, or labor strikes) that could affect business continuity. Note that these lists will likely contain several risk factors under each risk category.</p><p> Next, characterize relevant risks using the SPF framework, identify plausible scenarios related to the company&#39;s value functions, and identify potential responses. This exercise gives managers the opportunity to pay extra attention to less appreciated risks and helps them reduce the overall level of uncertainty of the impact of risks on the company&#39;s value exchange system.</p><p> Since the archetypal company is organized by function, the consequences of potential risks on individual functions (such as a labor strike&#39;s effect on sourcing) and the interconnectivity between different value functions themselves should be estimated for each functional node in the QRN. For instance, once managers define the level of interconnectivity between the sourcing and operations functions in their company, they can deduce the direct consequences of a labor strike for sourcing and its indirect consequences for operations. Weighting impacts, even using relative terms such as high, medium, and low, provides a common language for managers to discuss significant risks and plausible scenarios and can help resolve debate on what is likely or what is important. Functions identified as particularly important or vulnerable should be analyzed by experts to develop a deeper understanding of the risks affecting them and their interconnectivity.</p><p> We created a generalized QRN, beginning by asking leaders with sector and functional expertise to indicate interconnectivity between their function and other business functions on a 10-point scale. (See “A Quantitative Risk Network.”) Then we asked the leaders to indicate the potential impact of specific risks to their functional area arising from these connections. For example, a sales and marketing expert who indicated significant interconnectivity with the business strategy function was asked whether sales forecasting risks, sales execution risks, and reputation risks would have a high, medium, or low impact on business strategy. Companies can follow this process to build a codified understanding by leveraging their internal leaders as well as external experts. Once coded, the data forms the basis for a network representation of risks and a company-specific QRN. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig4"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> A Quantitative Risk Network</h4><p class="caption"> This visual representation of a generalized QRN reveals the linkages between risk categories and enterprise functions. It illustrates how companies can isolate and identify key value functions that link several connected risks and are therefore particularly significant in building enterprise resilience. The more central the function, the larger its font size; the thick links in the QRN imply high-impact relationships between functions and risk categories. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig4.png" alt="A Quantitative Risk Network" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Such a QRN helps leaders better understand a company&#39;s vulnerability to risk events by illuminating those functions that are central to the value exchange system. A risk event affecting a central function would imply a strong cascade of negative effects across the company&#39;s value exchange system. For example, financial capital management connects directly to 15 financial risk categories and indirectly to 30 risk categories from other functions. Any event occurring in any one of the risk categories affecting financial capital management will have implications for all other connected functions; for instance, significant currency exposure will likely affect the company&#39;s sourcing decisions. Thus, protecting the financial capital management function is critical to resilience. In contrast, a negative effect on the marketing and sales function is unlikely to cause a cascading impact in this company. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Expert knowledge, industry insights, experience, and the simulations are all useful in building a network view of enterprise risks. QRNs are baseline resources that help a company isolate and objectively model for worst-case scenarios, estimate cause-effect patterns, and effectively reduce level 3 and 4 uncertainty.</p><p> A company with a well-honed QRN will be able to differentiate between the scope and consequences of a business interruption due to, say, a pandemic and a transport route blockage. It will also be able to pinpoint the parts of the business that will likely experience significant consequences from these events, such as value delivery, value creation, and value protection, and identify the precise business functions that should be guarded for each of these events. In the case of the pandemic, these functions would include financial capital management, market risk assessment, and technology management; for the lower-scope blockage, these would include operations management and operating expense control. Furthermore, the company could use the value function risk inventory and build scenario models for risk events identified within each of these functions.</p><p> Ultimately, pairing the knowledge of plausible risk events and their likely interactions with the company&#39;s value functions enables strategists to develop tailored mitigation plans and response strategies. Leaders who recognize the need to better understand a specific set of scenarios can invest in developing precise models to reduce the uncertainty of their impact on the company.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The value exchange system that drives any large, complex enterprise is continuously challenged as contexts vary in the dynamic business environment. This raises the stakes for anticipating change, exploring new variations of business models, and continuously pursuing the next wave of growth-enabling capabilities. Risk intelligence helps leaders in this work, enabling them to better focus on maintaining continuous value exchange and fostering the adaptability needed to achieve resilience.</p><p> To create and nurture risk intelligence, a company needs a central risk management function that is staffed with broad functional expertise and given the resources required to identify and categorize risks. It needs to embrace a mindset of risk uncertainty versus risk avoidance and reduce the levels of uncertainty. It needs a company-specific quantified risk network that is updated in a dynamic manner. And finally, it needs a culture of risk intelligence in which leaders across the organization share a common framework and language for interpreting risks and guiding resource allocation for risk mitigation efforts. Ultimately, honing a risk intelligence capability represents the key to building a resilient enterprise.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here&#39;s How to Keep Them on Track.</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:57:13 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi. <p>Vern L. Glaser is an associate professor in the Department of Strategy, Entrepreneurship and Management at the University of Alberta&#39;s Alberta School of Business. Omid Omidvar is an associate professor in Organisation and Work at the University of Warwick&#39;s Warwick Business School. Mehdi Safavi is a senior lecturer in strategy and organization in the Strategy Group at Cranfield University&#39;s Cranfield School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Algorithms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Business Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors took a historical case study approach to explore the causes and consequences of algorithmic inertia, centering on the use of algorithms by Moody’s to rate mortgage-backed securities before the 2008 financial crisis. They drew on government reports on official investigations into the financial crisis, which included extensive witness testimony [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM_Glaser_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Simon Prades</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors took a historical case study approach to explore the causes and consequences of algorithmic inertia, centering on the use of algorithms by Moody&#39;s to rate mortgage-backed securities before the 2008 financial crisis.</li><li> They drew on government reports on official investigations into the financial crisis, which included extensive witness testimony that enabled them to effectively reconstruct changes to the Moody&#39;s credit rating routine during the years prior.</li><li> They gained useful information about the Moody&#39;s credit rating routine from an investigation of select credit rating agencies performed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission, as well as from a report by the Securities Industry and Financial Markets Association Credit Rating Agency Task Force.</li><li> They also gathered historical data from Moody&#39;s, such as annual reports and public statements, and reviewed media coverage.</li></ul></aside><p> Organizations are increasingly turning to sophisticated data analytics algorithms to support real-time decision-making in dynamic environments. However, these organizational efforts often fail — sometimes with spectacular consequences.</p><p> In 2018, real estate marketplace Zillow launched Zillow Offers, an “instant buyer” arm of the business. It leveraged a proprietary algorithm called Zestimate, which calculates how much a given residential property can be expected to sell for. Based on these calculations, Zillow Offers planned to purchase, renovate, and resell properties for a profit. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> While it had some success for the first few years, the model failed to adjust to the new dynamics of a more volatile market in 2021. Zillow lost an average of $25,000 on every home it sold in the fourth quarter that year — resulting in a write-down of $881 million. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> This is an example of what we call <em>algorithmic inertia</em> : when organizations use algorithmic models to take environmental changes into account but fail to keep pace with those changes. In this article, we explain algorithmic inertia, identify its sources, and suggest practices organizations can implement to overcome it.</p><p></p><h3> A Credit-Rating Catastrophe</h3><p> To understand the phenomenon of algorithmic inertia, we conducted an in-depth study of another organization that failed to respond to changes in the environment: Moody&#39;s, a financial research firm that provides credit ratings for bonds and complex financial instruments such as residential mortgage-backed securities (RMBSs). These securities aggregated bundles of individual mortgages into distinct tranches with unique characteristics during the period leading up to the global financial crisis of 2008. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Moody&#39;s made a concerted effort to account for environmental changes in its credit ratings by developing a proprietary algorithmic model in 2000 called M3 Prime. The model analyzed data about properties, mortgage holders, and the economy to estimate two parameters central to calculating a credit rating: expected losses for the mortgage pool and the loss coverage protection required for a security to maintain a AAA rating. An analyst would present a recommendation to Moody&#39;s credit rating committee, which assigned a publicly posted rating for the security. Moody&#39;s monitored these ratings and upgraded or downgraded RMBSs as the environment changed. The M3 Prime model achieved early success, so in 2006, Moody&#39;s expanded its scope of algorithmic analysis by introducing a derivative model, M3 Subprime.</p><p> Between 2000 and 2008, Moody&#39;s provided credit ratings for thousands of RMBSs, but it ended up downgrading 83% of AAA-rated mortgage-backed securities valued at billions of dollars by 2008. The US government, along with 21 states and the District of Columbia, held Moody&#39;s responsible for the role that its inflated ratings of those and other products played in precipitating the financial crisis. In 2017, the agency agreed to pay $864 million to settle the allegations. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> This is a particularly illustrative example of algorithmic inertia with devastating societal consequences. Moody&#39;s decisions offer an excellent context for exploring algorithmic inertia because the organization was explicitly responsible for analyzing environmental changes as part of its core service. Moreover, we were able to access detailed information about its algorithmic model from a report produced by the Financial Crisis Inquiry Commission that includes extensive interviews conducted under oath with Moody&#39;s executives who were involved in the business at the time. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> Our analysis enabled us to identify the most significant contributing factors to algorithmic inertia — buried assumptions, superficial remodeling, simulation of the unknown future, and specialized compartmentalization — described below. (See “Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia</h4><p class="caption"> Organizational and process issues can result in algorithms that don&#39;t keep up with environmental changes in the decision domain. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Buried Assumptions</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> The organization uses legacy data inputs for the algorithmic model despite recognizing significant changes in the environment. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;border-bottom-color:black;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Superficial Remodeling</strong></p></td><td  style="background-color:#f0f0f0;;border-bottom-color:black;"><p> The organization makes only minor modifications to the algorithmic model in response to substantive changes in the environment. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Simulation of the Unknown Future</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> The organization overconfidently relies on the algorithmic model to predict the future environment.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Specialized Compartmentalization</strong></p></td><td style="background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Responsibilities for the algorithmic routine are divided between team members in distinct roles based on their specialized expertise. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Glaser_Table_1.png" alt="Four Sources of Algorithmic Inertia" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Buried assumptions.</strong> Failing to revisit fundamental assumptions undergirding inputs of the algorithmic model in light of changes in the environment contributes significantly to algorithmic inertia. For example, loan originators were increasingly underwriting mortgages based on lower credit standards and substantially less documentation than before. So an original assumption undergirding Moody&#39;s M3 Prime model — that the technology that mortgage originators were using to streamline the loan application process was also enabling a more accurate assessment of underlying risks — wasn&#39;t modified to reflect the changing lending environment. The managing director of credit policy at Moody&#39;s told a federal inquiry panel that he sat on a high-level structured credit committee that would have been expected to deal with issues like declining mortgage underwriting standards, but the topic was never raised. “We talked about everything but … the elephant sitting on the table,” he said. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p></p><p> Moody&#39;s model also assumed that consumers&#39; FICO credit scores were the primary predictive factor in loan defaults. But the quality of this data input significantly diminished over time: As the use of these credit scores became increasingly common, individuals found ways to artificially inflate them. As a result, low- and no-documentation mortgages carried latent risk that was not being taken into account in Moody&#39;s algorithmic model. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> <strong>Superficial remodeling.</strong> This phenomenon occurs when organizations make only minor modifications to the algorithmic model in response to substantive changes in the environment. At Moody&#39;s, some major changes to the environment included a growing number of loan originators, increasingly low-quality mortgages, and an unprecedented decline in interest rates.</p><p> Moody&#39;s response to these changes was to seek to capture more business in the rapidly growing market, so it fine-tuned the model to be “more efficient, more profitable, cheaper, and more versatile,” according to its chief credit officer — not to be more accurate. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> When it modified M3 Prime to introduce the M3 Subprime model, it extrapolated loss curves for subprime loans based on premium loans rather than developing fresh loss curves for subprime loans.</p><p> <strong>Simulation of the unknown future.</strong> Relying on an algorithmic model to produce viable scenarios for the future environment can also leave organizations vulnerable to algorithmic inertia. Moody&#39;s constructed a simulation engine featuring 1,250 macroeconomic scenarios that enabled it to estimate possible future losses based on variations in economic markers such as inflation, unemployment, and house prices. However, the simulation engine was limited by its underlying structure and assumptions, so analysts did not consider the changes that were occurring, did not update scenarios, and failed to accurately represent the changing macroeconomic environment. Based on the belief that detailed performance histories could more precisely reveal causal links between economic stresses and loan behavior, Moody&#39;s used estimates based on historical parameters rather than expected pool loss distributions to examine behavior in stress scenarios. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> <strong>Specialized compartmentalization.</strong> This situation arises when experts in different domains are involved in an algorithm&#39;s design and use and there is no overarching single ownership or shared understanding of the model. At Moody&#39;s, responsibilities for the credit rating routine were divided between the domain experts (credit rating committee members) who used the quantitative model and the quantitative analysts who had developed it.</p><p> Because ownership and use of the model were distributed, and Moody&#39;s didn&#39;t strictly define how to use it, credit rating committee members established ad hoc rules to adjust the results of the model when its outputs didn&#39;t conform to what their expert judgment led them to believe it ought to produce. Model outputs weren&#39;t considered final; rather, the models were seen as tools to be used in conjunction with other approaches, and there was much divergence in how different ratings committees made their determinations.</p><p> The models were developed and modified by individuals who were distant from the domains in which they would be applied; disparate groups of domain experts then used the models in inconsistent ways without understanding their underlying logic. The managing director for rating RMBSs described the model as so technically complex that few people understood how it worked. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a></p><p> This issue is at the heart of what makes algorithmic inertia hard to tackle: The models and algorithms are often so complex that domain experts can hardly grasp the details of their functioning, while data scientists are disconnected from how their models are being used in the real world.</p><h3> Develop Practices That Combat Algorithmic Inertia</h3><p> We have described how each of the causes of algorithmic inertia played out in Moody&#39;s use of an algorithmic model to dynamically incorporate changes in the environment into its credit ratings. Despite recognizing flaws in the model and making active attempts to change it, the organization was unable to effectively adapt to the environment, thereby substantially contributing to the 2008 financial crisis.</p><p> To prevent similar degradation of critical algorithms&#39; predictive value, we suggest that organizations implement the four practices described below. (See “Keeping Algorithms Relevant.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Keeping Algorithms Relevant</h4><p class="caption"> Organizations can increase the likelihood that algorithmic tools will effectively adapt to changes in the environment by following four practices. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><th style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th><th style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"></th></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Expose Data and Assumptions</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Articulate and document the data and the fundamental assumptions in the algorithmic model. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;border-bottom-color:black;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Periodically Redesign Algorithmic Routines</strong></p></td><td  style="background-color:#f0f0f0;;border-bottom-color:black;"><p> Periodically redesign — and be willing to overhaul — the algorithmic model and how it fits into broader organizational routines. </p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Assume That the Model Will Break</strong></p></td><td style="border-bottom-color:black;background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Actively consider scenarios outside the scope of algorithmic models by challenging predictive assumptions, assuming that the model will be fundamentally flawed, and envisioning qualitative alternative predictions of the future.</p></td></tr><tr><td style="border-right:hidden;background-color:#f0f0f0;padding-left:0px;"><p> <strong>Build Bridges Between Data Scientists and Domain Experts</strong></p></td><td style="background-color:#f0f0f0;"><p> Ensure that data scientists and domain experts work closely together to design the algorithmic model and the organizational routine in which it is to be embedded. </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Glaser_Table_2.png" alt="Keeping Algorithms Relevant" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p></p><p> <strong>Expose data and assumptions.</strong> Organizations should articulate and document the data used in their algorithmic models, including data sources and fundamental assumptions underlying their data selection decisions, which can have deleterious effects. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> Models often include operationalizations of many concepts, and it is easy for organizations to lose track of these parameters, which can be buried in layers of software code. Parameters representing the environment need to be documented to ensure that they remain visible. Similarly, the fundamental assumptions undergirding the model should be articulated and periodically revisited.</p><p> Moody&#39;s used a data set on premium mortgages to train a model that was intended to be used to rate RMBSs composed of subprime mortgages. Initially, this might have been a reasonable choice due to the availability of data. But when a model&#39;s initial data set isn&#39;t refreshed, algorithmic inertia can result. As the Moody&#39;s case suggests, data is never completely accurate, objective, and flawless. Therefore, making the sources of data and assumptions about those sources transparent to algorithm users, and continually reflecting on the appropriateness of that data, are critical practices for organizations seeking to avoid algorithmic inertia.</p><p> Organizations must keep data sources clearly organized and evaluate them periodically. Different data sources have different qualities and characteristics. Ensuring that these sources are distinguished from one another before they are fed into algorithmic models, processed, and constantly compared against one another enables data scientists to identify and eliminate algorithmic inertia sooner rather than later.</p><p> The assumptions underpinning the use of an algorithm should also be documented and articulated. Any attempt to model the environment involves quantification — transforming aspects of reality into numerical data. Such quantification inevitably involves making assumptions about how the environment works. However, while quantification is necessary for algorithmic models to work, details about how it is performed can get lost in the complex process of designing and using algorithmic models. Therefore, maintaining a living record of such assumptions may prevent the emergence of algorithmic inertia.</p><p> <strong>Periodically redesign algorithmic routines.</strong> Organizations should regularly redesign — and be willing to overhaul — their algorithmic model and reconsider how it fits into broader organizational routines. The initial design of an algorithmic model can take a lot of work, and it is natural for an organization to want to reap the benefits of that work. However, in a dynamic and quickly changing environment, it&#39;s important to be willing not just to make incremental changes to a model but to fundamentally overhaul it if necessary.</p><p> Of course, organizations face a trade-off when it comes to overhauling an algorithmic routine: It can be very expensive to completely re-architect an algorithmic model. However, the consequences of failing to do so can be disastrous.</p><p> For example, when Moody&#39;s had to rate an increasing number of subprime-dominated RMBSs, the organization chose to incrementally modify the M3 Prime model. However, it may have been more effective to specify the distinctions between the prime and the subprime markets and do a deeper overhaul of the original model. In addition to rethinking the algorithmic model itself, an organization can consider how it is deployed in practice: Hypothetically, Moody&#39;s could have applied the M3 Prime model differently to different types of RMBSs — perhaps simply requiring more human intervention for tranches composed of lower-quality loans.</p><p> Redesigning and overhauling an algorithmic model is contingent upon understanding what organizational processes interrelate with the model and analyzing the implications that changes in the environment have for it. If it becomes clear that either the model or the processes that it relies on or feeds into have been rendered obsolete or ineffective, an overhaul should be seriously considered.</p><p> <strong>Assume that the model will break.</strong> It can be dangerous for an organization to think of potential future scenarios only through the prism of what algorithmic models predict: All assumptions embedded in a model limit the potential futures that can be considered. To address algorithmic inertia associated with the simulation of an unknown future, it is important to assume that the model will break. Consider scenarios beyond the scope of the algorithmic model; this requires challenging predictive assumptions as well as presuming that the model is fundamentally flawed.</p><p> An active practice of considering scenarios that are <em>outside</em> the model can help motivate and inspire the prior two practices — exposing data and assumptions and periodically redesigning algorithmic routines — by forcing team members to actively consider the limitations of algorithmic models.</p><p></p><p> One particularly useful approach might be to make use of qualitative predictions of the future instead of quantitative predictions that rely on available data from the past. These forms of scenario planning offer opportunities to consider radically different visions of what the future may hold. This might also entail developing hybrid algorithms that do not precisely rely on past data to predict scenarios but also embed in them qualitative measures and expert rules introduced by domain experts.</p><p> <strong>Build bridges between data scientists and domain experts.</strong> Organizations must create processes for data scientists and domain experts to work closely together to design their algorithmic routines. <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> Practically speaking, data scientists and AI specialists approach problems very differently than domain experts do. Domain experts focus on organizational routines and idiosyncratic situations, whereas data scientists focus on developing generalizable constructs based on mathematical principles. To overcome algorithmic inertia, data scientists and domain experts must work closely together to understand how characteristics of organizational routines and idiosyncratic situations map to the mathematical parameters used in an algorithmic model.</p><p> When the worlds of data scientists and domain experts are completely separate, there is also the danger that data scientists and domain experts will shift responsibility by superficially trusting each other&#39;s work. Such assumptions can actually prevent crucial dialogue between the two worlds. For instance, Moody&#39;s ended up subverting the results of its credit rating model because the credit rating analysts didn&#39;t attempt to understand why the model might be generating results that didn&#39;t fit with their intuitions. Building bridges between data scientists and domain experts enables domain experts to obtain an intuitive grasp of how the algorithmic model works. Such common ground could enable organizations to create and use models that better adapt to changes in the environment.</p><p> One structural bridge-building practice that organizations can use to facilitate communication between data scientists and domain experts is establishing a position such as a product manager. This should be held by one individual with both domain and data science experience who has direct responsibility for overseeing algorithmic routines. For example, some data experts have called for the creation of a new organizational structure that includes an “innovation marshal” role — someone who is respected by both data scientists and field experts. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> Given their knowledge and expertise in both areas, these people can gain the respect of the organization by developing and maintaining “high-bandwidth, bidirectional communication channels” that help ensure that algorithmic routines are able to adapt to environmental changes. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p></p><p> Another bridge-building practice is called <em>model explainability</em> : describing the algorithmic models in a practical and comprehensible manner. For data scientists, such explainability can facilitate access to the expert knowledge needed to counteract the sources of algorithmic inertia; for domain experts, such explainability can help them develop a deep and intuitive understanding of how the model takes environmental changes into account. Model explainability establishes common ground between two groups of professionals who have different types of expertise. Such practices enable organizations to build bridges instead of just talking about them.</p><p></p><p> Organizations seeking to reap the benefits of powerful predictive analytics are increasingly confronting the problem of algorithmic inertia. Despite leveraging dynamic algorithms to adapt to changes in the environment, organizations may find that the results are not keeping pace with new developments. By exposing data and assumptions, periodically redesigning algorithmic routines, assuming that their models will break, and building bridges, organizations can increase the likelihood that their substantial investments in algorithmic solutions will pay off with better decision-making.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>我们应该将摩尔定律引入气候行动</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Winston. <p>Andrew Winston ( <a href="https://twitter.com/andrewwinston">@andrewwinston</a> ) 是全球公认的专家，擅长如何建立有弹性、盈利的公司来帮助人类和地球繁荣发展。他是<cite>Net Positive 的合著者：勇敢的公司如何通过付出超过索取而蓬勃发展</cite>（哈佛商业评论出版社，2021 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business and the Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Gordon Moore, cofounder of Intel and a towering figure of the early semiconductor business, died earlier this year at the age of 94. He leaves behind one of the more successful companies in history and, of course, his famous Moore’s law. He predicted in 1965 that the density of transistors on a microchip would double [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Winston-MooresLaw-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>英特尔联合创始人、早期半导体行业的杰出人物戈登摩尔于今年早些时候去世，享年 94 岁。他留下了历史上最成功的公司之一，当然还有他著名的<a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/news/gordon-moore-obituary.html">摩尔定律</a>。他在 1965 年预测微芯片上的晶体管密度每年都会翻一番，并在 1975 年将他的预测调整为“恰好”每两年翻一番。后一种预测已经成立了将近 50 年。</p><p>人们常说，我们手中的手机比 1969 年的阿波罗登月任务的计算能力更强。的确如此，但这也太轻描淡写了——我们的手机实际上 <a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/moon-mars/a25655/nasa-computer-iphone-comparison/">比当时所有的 NASA 都强大</a>，这一事实证明了指数变化的令人震惊的现实。</p><p></p><p>我们人类倾向于以线性方式思考：如果去年增长了一点，今年就会增长更多一点。我们很难理解半导体发生了什么。 1971 年，每个微处理器大约有 2,400 个晶体管。五十年后，一块芯片拥有 580 亿个晶体管，英特尔计划<a href="https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/opinion/moore-law-now-and-in-the-future.html">到 2030 年达到 1 万亿个</a>。如果每两年翻一番，它大约每十年增长 30 倍，20 年增长 1,000 倍，40 年增长 100 万倍。在 60 年内，您将以 10 亿倍的速度获得某些东西。</p><p>很难夸大这种变化速度对世界造成的影响。有趣的是，我十几岁的男孩们对他们几乎可以立即查询几乎任何事实或流式传输任何视频或歌曲完全不感兴趣。与此同时，错误信息传播得更快。至于人工智能？无论是好的还是坏的，它都会迅速变得更好。 （如果你想害怕，请查找“deepfakes”。）</p><p>摩尔定律还导致了商业史上一些最经典的失败。柯达没有为数码照片做好准备。 Blockbuster 也被打了个措手不及，下载电影在短短几年内就从不可能变成了实时下载。一旦流媒体电影变得微不足道，租用视频的模式就死了。</p><p>在所有这一切中，我看到了两个重要的教训。首先，如果我们能够尽早取得成功，相信还有更多的可能，为此疯狂竞争，并进行<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/">必要的投资，</a>我们就能取得显着进步。这里的核心点是，显而易见，摩尔定律不是定律。几十年来，没有人要求大型芯片公司将晶体管的宽度缩小到纳米级。他们之所以这样做，是因为竞争、为建立芯片市场而进行的大量公共和私人支出，以及理论、制造技术、设备设计和营销方面令人印象深刻的创新水平。 （一旦 iPad<em>可行，我们还需要</em>吗？）根据早期经验和成功，摩尔定律被证明是对一个行业可以实现的目标的有力而大胆的预测。</p><p>其次，我们可以将其与我们时代的关键商业挑战相提并论：如何在管理我们的社会和环境影响（尤其是气候变化）的同时实现繁荣和发展。我们可以拥抱快速变化，以可持续或净积极的方式运营。</p><h3>我们可以再次拥抱指数</h3><p>就像在 1960 年代和 70 年代一样，在外部目标的驱动下，我们再次沿着一条我们不确定如何前进的道路前进——最重要的是，科学告诉我们世界应该以多快的速度去碳化。 “Science-based targets” are a quasi-Moore&#39;s law for fighting climate change.跟上这些雄心勃勃的目标是商业价值的重要创造者，是实现卓越创新和绩效的途径，也是与客户、员工和其他利益相关者保持相关性（而不是被 Blockbuster 化）的核心方式。</p><p></p><p>到目前为止，许多清洁技术领域给半导体世界留下了良好的印象。清洁能源和电池存储的成本即使不是每两年减半，也一直在快速下降。根据国际能源署的数据，2000 年至 2020 年间， <a href="https://www.iea.org/data-and-statistics/charts/evolution-of-solar-pv-module-cost-by-data-source-1970-2020">新太阳能模块的每瓦成本</a>下降了 96%。45 年来，太阳能成本暴跌了 500 倍，大约每五年减半。虽然不是摩尔定律的步伐，但它的速度足以撼动整个行业并创造巨大的新机会。清洁技术转型是我们旅行、建造建筑物、制造事物等方式的数万亿美元的转变。</p><p>与半导体一样，清洁技术领域的这种表现来自于创新、投资、政策支持和大规模制造能力的大规模建设（主要在中国）。但也许在这两种情况下最重要的是，变革的步伐需要意志力和新的思维模式。 10 多年前，当我们这些身处可持续商业世界的人开始推动以科学为基础的目标的想法时，阻力是显而易见的。 “我们怎么可能移动得那么快？”很多人会问。 “考虑到它的成本，我们<em>为什么</em>要移动得那么快？”但是，当您跨越成本和心理临界点时，怀疑会转变为热情。</p><p></p><p>尽管摩尔定律一直在推动社会的深刻技术和社会变革，但它仍然是一个人为的目标。竞争、创新和利润动机驱使公司朝着它迈进。这一次，为了实现气候目标，我们正在使用全球行星阈值来确定我们需要实现多快的目标——不仅是碳，还有水的使用、环境中有毒物质或塑料的数量、人权的普遍性供应链中的滥用行为等等。</p><p>如果我们希望我们的世界繁荣昌盛，那么拥有这些可不是一件好事。我们正在努力应对的可持续性“法则”绝对<em>不是</em>理论上的或发明的——它们基于自然和物理法则。聪明的公司会将这些不容谈判的现实视为他们所拥有的难以置信的机会，并开始行动。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/we-should-bring-moores-law-to-climate-action/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>管理您的劳动力生态系统，而不仅仅是您的员工</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth J. Altman, David Kiron, Jeff Schwartz, and Robin Jones. <p>Elizabeth J. Altman 是马萨诸塞大学洛厄尔分校曼宁商学院的管理学副教授。 David Kiron 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的研究编辑部主任。杰夫·施瓦茨 (Jeff Schwartz) 是 Gloat 负责洞察力和影响力的副总裁，也是哥伦比亚商学院的兼职教授。 Robin Jones 是 Deloitte Consulting LLP 的负责人，并担任劳动力转型实践负责人。他们是<cite><a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047777/workforce-ecosystems/">《劳动力生态系统》</a></cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2023 年 4 月）的作者，本文改编自该书。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jon Krause/theispot.com “How do you define your workforce?” We have posed this question to dozens of executives and in multiple global management surveys. The most common answer is also the most surprising. A confident minority of executives say their workforce is just their employees. But the overwhelming majority, especially leaders on the front lines of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM_Altman_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">乔恩·克劳斯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> “你如何定义你的劳动力？”我们已经向数十名高管和多项全球管理调查提出了这个问题。最常见的答案也是最令人惊讶的。</p><p>少数自信的高管表示，他们的员工就是他们的员工。但绝大多数人，尤其是处于组织转型前线的领导者，所持的观点更广泛，不仅仅是员工。他们越来越多地将劳动力描述为参与实现公司业务目标的所有人员和群体。组织的扩展劳动力对其业务、品牌和价值创造方法变得如此重要，以至于他们需要以不同的方式思考并以不同的方式对待他们的整个员工队伍。</p><p>自从我们几年前开始研究劳动力的未来以来，这代表了管理观点的转变。我们正在看到这种跨行业和各种规模的组织发生的变化——领导者需要重新定义他们的员工队伍由谁组成以及由什么组成，并制定新的管理实践和组织结构，这对领导者提出了挑战。</p><p></p><p>等级制、命令与控制、以内部为中心的管理实践不适合跨越内部和外部组织边界的员工队伍。例如，使用孤立的职能来独立管理员工和外部贡献者充满了挑战：不明确的决策权、治理流程和权力动态甚至会破坏最善意的高管。此外，用于管理员工的技术系统通常与用于访问和跟踪外部贡献者的技术系统不同且相互脱节。缺乏整合会导致效率低下，从而阻碍获得和维持具有战略价值的能力的努力。</p><p>我们将<em>劳动力生态系统</em>定义为一个结构，其中包含组织内外的参与者，他们致力于为组织创造价值。在生态系统中，参与者朝着个人和集体目标努力，参与者之间相互依存和互补。</p><p>劳动力生态系统包括员工以及各种外部贡献者和合作伙伴——长期和短期承包商、临时工、应用程序开发人员、服务提供商和众包参与者。生态系统观点明确认识到，获取和聘用劳动力不再是人力资源职能的唯一权限，而是需要涉及最高管理层、IT、采购、财务、法律和其他领域的领导者的跨职能行动。</p><p>有意识地协调劳动力生态系统需要领导者协调整个组织的活动以及与外部贡献者的活动。为了应对这一挑战，公司需要重新评估人力资源、采购和 IT 等职能之间的协调。还需要决定如何管理与外部贡献者的关系，例如应用程序开发人员和分包商。我们开发了<em>集成架构</em>的概念来定义内部协调以及组织如何与其扩展的员工交互。</p><p></p><p>我们的集成架构模型与大多数劳动力生态系统中管理交互的默认、孤立的方法形成鲜明对比。通常，临时工负责采购。合作伙伴和联盟通常由战略处理，人工智能和自动化是技术组织的一部分（但很少被视为更广泛的劳动力生态系统的一部分）。人力资源部通常监督全职和兼职员工。在这种通用方法中，多个小组独立工作以管理他们有任务的贡献者，但整个组织的努力是不协调的。</p><p>不同部门的经理经常在没有任何集中协调的情况下使用外部和内部员工的组合。这些分散的方法在局部层面可能是有效的，每个业务部门和职能经理都保留最大的控制权，但它们在总体层面上并不是最优的。</p><p>事实上，在协调劳动力生态系统时，权力下放可能会有很大的缺点。分散的努力可能与总体战略重点不一致，并可能破坏企业对新战略方向的追求。缺乏集成可能会限制有关谁（和什么）为组织做出贡献的可用数据。这可能会导致成本效率低下，因为临时工是临时寻找的。这可能意味着内部员工和外部贡献者（现有的和潜在的）都不太了解贡献的机会。虽然权力下放是目前管理员工和扩展劳动力的最常见方法，但它几乎总是不协调的。</p><h3>为什么集中式集成架构具有吸引力</h3><p>鉴于分散架构的缺点，许多协调劳动力生态系统的组织正在创建在其设计中更加集中和跨职能的集成架构。在一些组织中，人力资源部门协调劳动力生态系统管理与采购和 IT 职能；在这些情况下，业务领导者和团队与 HR 和其他人合作，主动管理风险。其他公司正在采用更具跨职能的方法来管理所有类型的个体工人和提供者；在这些情况下，人力资源发挥着关键但不太重要的作用，人才市场在支持跨业务部门和职能的劳动力需求方面发挥着更突出的作用。</p><p>例如，瑞士全球医疗保健公司诺华公司成立了一个跨职能指导委员会来管理其大约 100,000 名内部员工和大约 50,000 名外部员工。诺华正在努力为管理人员提供内部和外部人才来源的可见性，这是​​由来自各种合作伙伴和平台的数据驱动的一项努力。这个过程将由称为劳动力战略家的策展人推动，他们将授予管理人员实时访问员工、承包商和技术团队的权限。</p><p>这场大流行病促使我们研究的另一家全球公司的人力资源部门更多地参与监督更广泛的员工队伍，因为它引发了对临时工和员工的远程和现场工作政策、薪酬连续性、缺勤和病假的担忧。该公司人力资源副总裁报告说，在大流行之前，人力资源部门只密切关注全职员工或兼职员工的情况；通常，对于临时工，“人力资源部门根本不参与，”她说。 At that time, there wasn&#39;t even a shared understanding of who comprises the company&#39;s contingent workforce.大流行病使公司必须更加集中整合和灵活地照顾其临时工的想法变得紧迫。它还强调，公司需要更好地管理更广泛员工的声誉、法律、运营和成本风险，并充分利用全体员工的竞争优势。</p><p>在同一家公司，招聘流程和程序历来因部门而异——而且部门之间往往不相互沟通。人力资源部支持有关雇用长期雇员的决定，而采购则引入临时工。与此同时，人力资源部门不知道的是，管理人员经常将临时工转变为全职员工。一个涉及人力资源、采购和财务的新开发的信息交换平台为公司提供了基于数据的跨职能可见性，以跟踪和批准外部员工。</p><p>根据首席采购官的说法，临时员工的管理一直是公司的一个烫手山芋：“任何处于中心位置的人都将承担所有风险，而没有任何好处。”但他表示，该公司已经转向从战略而非交易的角度考虑与临时工的关系，这涉及跨职能管理临时工。正如人力资源副总裁所解释的那样，“我们的首席财务官、首席法律顾问、首席人力资源官 [chief human resources officer] 和首席运营官都承认他们都参与了这场游戏。”</p><p>人才市场是另一个很好的工具，可以锚定一个集中的、跨职能集成的​​架构。例如，NASA 曾经有六个人才市场平台，分布在多个部门，每个平台都独立地将员工与演出和项目相匹配。现在，航天局使用单一的人才市场——一种协调机制——来协调整个组织对内部人才的访问。将其内部人才市场扩展到外部贡献者是 NASA 的目标。</p><p></p><h3>集成架构挑战</h3><p>虽然集中式和跨职能集成架构使组织能够在其劳动力生态系统中实现更高级别的协调，但这些努力仍处于初期阶段。即使在处于劳动力生态系统转型前沿的公司中，领导者也强调这些努力才刚刚开始获得牵引力。在我们的研究和咨询工作中，我们发现大多数组织仍然采用被动、本地和不协调的方法来招募和留住外部人才和互补贡献者。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1个</a></p><p>领导者意识到，这种分散的努力既没有成本效益，也没有资源效率，并且有可能使内部员工失去积极性。然而，他们努力为劳动力生态系统编排建立一个集中的跨职能集成架构。我们听到了以下担忧：</p><ul><li>您如何确定一组合适的利益相关者来创建用于劳动力生态系统编排的集中集成架构？</li><li>您如何让利益相关者参与本地劳动力生态系统实验，以根据特定情况调整共同目标？</li><li>您如何从本地实验中促进协调学习？</li><li>随着时间的推移，您如何改进您的劳动力生态系统实施流程？</li></ul><p>要打造一个一体化的劳动力生态系统，至少需要解决三类问题：结构设计（涉及分工、目标和激励）、政治（涉及资源、权力和地位）和文化（影响个人对身份和意义的追求）。我们建议对这些问题采取分阶段的方法，这些问题相互交织、重叠并可以相互加强。此过程可能最适合开始采用劳动力生态系统的大型成熟组织，但关键要素应该对中小型企业有所帮助。 （参见“编排集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>协调集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段</h4><p class="caption">下图描述了与协调劳动力生态系统相关的主要挑战以及与解决这些挑战相关的阶段。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Altman_Figure.png" alt="协调集成劳动力生态系统的四个阶段" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>在第一阶段，我们建议创建一个编排团队，与相关的本地和中央利益相关者（内部和外部）协商制定工作计划、目标和指标。该团队应关注组织内部的整合考虑（职能角色和职责）以及与外部参与者的关系。通过与组织内已经聘用外部员工的团队合作，团队可以与在协调部分劳动力生态系统方面经验丰富的经理一起抢先一步。从结构设计的角度来看，他们可以快速开始突出并解决之前发现的技能差距。</p><p>为了解决政治问题，团队可以选择当地德高望重和行动导向的冠军来领导转型。此外，该团队可以包括来自外部贡献者的代表，以将他们的观点带入工作中。团队成员应能够酌情代表职能领域、产品组和业务部门发言；关键是获得所有利益攸关方群体的参与。最后，为了应对文化挑战，至少有一名团队成员应该扮演边界扳手的角色，充当中央团队、地方团队和其他受影响群体之间的中间人。</p><p>第二阶段，我们建议推进地方试点。中央编排团队可以引入试点项目来探索劳动力生态系统关系的潜在配置。这些实验可以解决结构性问题，例如为项目配备内部和外部员工、确定必要的技能、确保能力以及衡量结果的质量。他们可以解决政治挑战，例如内部员工抵制外部员工的贡献，以及当地领导因为失去对团队组成的控制而感到紧张。最后，随着员工适应职责的转变，可能会出现文化问题，特别是如果他们需要承担更多的协调角色，协调来自不同来源的参与者。</p><p>在第三阶段，我们强调协调学习和资源配置，跨越由本地团队确定并由中央团队监督的挑战（和成功）。现有政策和程序（例如知识产权许可模型或培训规则）等结构性障碍可能在传统的员工生命周期模型中为组织提供良好服务，但需要对劳动力生态系统进行修改。资源问题可能会出现，因为当地管理人员雇用了更多的外部工人或更容易与分包商合作，但随后拒绝释放员工接受其他机会。即使最高管理层和较低级别的人接受变革，中层管理人员也可能会抵制，因为他们经常肩负管理这些有时具有高度破坏性的转型的日常挑战的任务。</p><p>在第四个也是最后一个阶段，我们考虑劳动力生态系统的扩展。一旦对初始试点进行了分析并且新实践开始制度化，领导者应该考虑哪些其他新系统、工具、目标、指标和流程已被证明足够成功，可以采用。随着组织不断获得知识和经验，应定期审查这些内容。领导者可能希望扩大中央协调团队，以包括来自其他内部团队的代表。他们可能想考虑将他们的劳动力生态系统与其他人联系起来——例如，与客户组织及其生态系统更紧密地合作。在文化上，领导者可以考虑通过讲故事和其他沟通工具更积极地促进分布式学习和劳动力生态系统活动。他们可能希望强调增长机会，同时也开始解决不可避免地伴随此类转型而来的无数担忧。</p><p>这种四阶段方法提供了一种实用的方法来吸引、连接和激活关键利益相关者。从那里开始，组织可以开始塑造自己的战略和路径，方法是尝试新型集成架构，并在了解不同环境下哪些有效和无效时快速迭代。</p><p>与集成架构定义内部职能和业务部门如何协同工作以协调劳动力生态系统的方式相呼应，领导者需要定义如何管理与外部贡献者的关系。领导者面临着关于哪些集成架构适合外部贡献者的几个决定。</p><p>第三方集成架构的选择可能决定合作伙伴愿意花费资源参与（或贡献）劳动力生态系统的程度。例如，关于如何与开发人员生态系统协调的决策对于有效的劳动力生态系统至关重要。 Google Play 是 Google 的应用程序和内容分发市场。与 Apple 分发应用程序和内容的 Apple App Store 相比，Google 的操作更轻松，要求和合规性测试也不那么严格。众所周知，Apple 的政策要严格得多。与外部开发人员的集成架构可能或多或少有些僵化，也可能或多或少受欢迎。</p><p>与第三方构建集成架构引发了关于谁应该在企业内拥有这些关系的问题。例如，视频游戏机制造商通常允许第三方开发者（补充者）开发可在其系统上运行的游戏；通常，正是对这些第三方游戏的需求推动了特定游戏机的销售。开发者关系应该由业务开发或战略小组（也可能处理战略联盟）负责，还是由专门负责开发者生态系统的单独小组负责？集成架构有助于定义职责并裁定具有竞争利益的内部团队之间的潜在冲突。</p><p></p><p>在您的组织中实施集成架构首先要评估您的劳动力生态系统当前的运作方式。您组织的人力资源职能目前对内部和外部贡献者有多大的可见性和控制力？如果这些贡献者当前以分散的方式进行管理，请评估您的组织是否最适合此架构。</p><p></p><p>如果您认识到更集中集成和协调的劳动力生态系统对您的组织来说是更好的方法，请决定哪些团体和个人应该成为协调团队的一部分。是否应该由某人（或某个团体）集中负责监督整个劳动力生态系统？</p><p>在我们的整个研究过程中，我们听到领导者描述了他们在日益复杂和相互联系的劳动力生态系统中聘请对公司成功至关重要的人才的努力。我们一次又一次地观察到，有意识地协调劳动力生态系统的观点可以帮助领导者对他们自己的组织以及他们实现战略目标所依赖的人员、合作伙伴和技术有更丰富、更细致的看法。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>打开职业公平的快速通道</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian 是 Workforce Sciences Institute 的共同负责人和联合创始人，也是 Mercer 的前高级合伙人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com The Research The author conducted the research underlying this article while coleading Mercer’s Workforce Sciences Institute.i The author analyzed results of his research team&#8217;s statistical analyses of three to five years of employee data for 20 large and midsize, mostly global, employers representing manufacturing and services companies in a range of industries, including [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Nalbantian_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Davide Bonazzi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者在共同领导美世劳动力科学研究所的同时进行了本文的基础研究。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></li><li>作者分析了他的研究团队对 20 家大中型（大部分是全球性）雇主的三到五年员工数据的统计分析结果，这些雇主代表了一系列行业的制造和服务公司，包括消费品和工业产品、制药、技术、金融服务和专业服务。这些公司总共雇用了超过 700,000 名员工。大约 40% 的员工在美国。</li></ul></aside><p>商业领袖倾向于将他们的多元化、公平和包容 (DEI) 工作重点放在解决偏见和歧视上，因为这些做法很普遍，而且歧视是非法的。但在这个过程中，他们忽视了情境因素，这些情境因素在决定女性和有色人种是否获得晋升以及是否属于高薪人群方面起着主导作用——而且更容易解决。</p><p>职业和薪酬公平有着千丝万缕的联系。女性和有色人种在经理和高管中的比例仍然不足，在高级专业人士中也经常如此。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>虽然这些人口群体的薪酬公平正在改善，但许多公司的原始薪酬差距（女性和男性之间以及有色人种和白人员工之间的平均和中位数差异）仍然很高。这些薪酬差距将持续存在，直到女性和有色人种以合理反映其在劳动力中的代表性的比率占据要求最高薪酬的职业级别和角色。</p><p></p><p>不公平不仅伤害个体员工；它还剥夺了企业被忽视的人才。如果领导者了解情境因素如何影响员工的晋升前景，他们就可以应用<em>积极的职业生涯管理 (PCM)</em> ——识别并消除阻碍员工成功的障碍——使他们的工作场所更加公平和高效。</p><p>为了更好地理解这些职业成果差异背后的因素，我检查了 20 家大中型公司多年晋升、​​保留、绩效和薪酬数据的分析结果，这些公司的员工总数超过 700,000。调查结果证实，女性和有色人种在晋升概率方面存在显着的性别和种族差异，这可归因于四个始终对员工成功产生影响的因素：绩效评级、角色分配、报告关系和灵活的工作安排。</p><p>除了绩效评级外，这些因素与员工的情况有关，而不是他们的知识、技能或行为。例如，如果职业发展需要某些角色的经验，但相对于男性，女性在这些角色中的比例不足，最终结果是晋升的女性人数较少。</p><p>当然，偏见和歧视也在起作用：在大多数组织中，我们发现在晋升的可能性方面存在巨大的、无法解释的性别和种族差异，这无法用任何与业务相关的因素来解释。我们发现绩效评估中存在普遍且相当大的种族差异，有色人种，尤其是黑人员工，不太可能获得高评价。这些是企业多元化、公平和包容性努力的合乎逻辑的重点，因为它们是偏见或歧视的证据。</p><p>但由于解释的差异往往对职业发展和薪酬公平影响最大，因此直接解决这些差异很重要。好消息是这些因素通常最容易成功解决。积极的职业生涯管理是一种数据驱动的方法，可提供有效的解决方案。</p><h3>四大因素推动谁在工作中进步</h3><p>让我们更仔细地看看我确定的四个因素，这些因素可以解释谁在工作中获得晋升、高绩效评级和更大的加薪，以及为什么女性和有色人种往往看不到这些好处。</p><p><strong>绩效评级。</strong>由于绩效评级会影响所有其他结果，例如晋升、保留和薪酬，因此该领域的差异会产生级联效应。在 89% 的研究公司中，黑人员工不太可能获得高绩效评级。差异可能相当大，大多数为 25% 或更高。此外，由于绩效评级往往年复一年地持续存在——一年的高评级预示着下一年高评级的可能性——有色人种获得较低评级的趋势实际上成为他们进步的障碍。 Interestingly, women are generally more likely to be highly rated than otherwise comparable men, but that doesn&#39;t translate into a higher probability of promotion for them.</p><p> <strong>Access to accelerator roles.</strong> In every company, certain roles are career accelerators and others are dead ends, regardless of who occupies them. In this study, having a supervisor role at any level almost universally improved the chance that an employee would be promoted and receive high ratings. However, we almost always found that women and people of color were far less likely to be in such roles than men or White employees, respectively.</p><p> The differences are often stark and steep. For example, in a global financial services company we studied, US-based employees who were supervisors were 50% more likely to be promoted and 55% more likely to receive high performance ratings than those who were not supervisors. Outside the US, supervisors were 89% more likely to be promoted and 37% more likely to get high ratings. These effects were even larger for female supervisors than for male supervisors. But across the company, women were half as likely to be supervisors. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> Further, because women are more likely than men to face career disruption during their child-rearing years, they may take on supervisor roles later. In such cases, they don&#39;t experience the same compounding benefit of being in such roles as their male colleagues.</p><p> <strong>Reporting relationships.</strong> Whom one reports to can have a decisive impact on the trajectory of one&#39;s career. We generally found that people who reported to supervisors with high performance ratings were significantly more likely to receive a high rating as well. The probability that they would be promoted also increased.</p><p> We saw similar effects for employees whose managers were higher up in the corporate hierarchy than the norm for someone at their level and thus had more clout. To the extent that women and people of color are less likely to report to high-performing and higher-level supervisors, they are less likely to receive high ratings or promotions themselves.</p><p> They may also be less likely to benefit from these relationships when they do have them. At a global insurance company, those who reported to a top-rated supervisor were about 50% more likely to be promoted and 30% more likely to receive high performance ratings. Those whose supervisors were at a level higher than the norm were 9% more likely to be promoted and 14% more likely to be highly rated. However, having a high-performing or higher-ranked supervisor did not help women and people of color as much as it helped White men.</p><p> <strong>Flexible working.</strong> Increasingly, organizations view flexible work arrangements as essential to attracting and retaining talent, particularly women and younger employees. Since the COVID-19 pandemic, more companies and employees have embraced such arrangements, but historically, they have been career killers. For example, those who work part time or remotely or take family leave are less likely to be promoted, are paid less, and are more likely to leave their companies.</p><p> At a business I&#39;ll refer to as ConsumerCo, opting for flexible work arrangements hurt both women and people of color. The percentage of women working part time was three times that of men; for people of color, it was two times that of White employees. Overall, working part time reduced promotion probability by 50% and the likelihood of receiving a high rating by 70%. It also increased turnover probability by 25% compared with similarly situated full-time workers.</p><p> Likewise, leaves of absence were disproportionately taken by women and people of color. Those on leave were about 50% less likely to be promoted or receive high ratings and much more likely to turn over — at least 150% more likely in the US and at least 80% more likely globally. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Unless companies do something to mitigate the negative consequences of flexible working on employees, the phenomenon of higher levels of flexible work arrangements risks further undermining career progress for women and people of color.</p><h3> The Case for Proactive Career Management</h3><p> With the exception of performance ratings, these drivers of career progress, or lack thereof, are situational. This is telling. It indicates that whether employees advance is not just a reflection of the talents and skills they bring or what they do, but also of how well their employers position them to succeed. All too often, women and people of color simply aren&#39;t positioned to succeed in the same way their White male counterparts are.</p><p> This is not to say that bias and discrimination are not factors, as mentioned above. However, employers can make measurable progress on DEI when they understand the extent of the positioning issues in their workforce and deal with them in a purposeful, systematic way. This is where PCM comes into play.</p><p></p><p> The idea behind proactive career management for DEI is simple: Identify and rank the factors that most influence career success and retention; if and where they skew significantly against certain demographic groups, intervene to eliminate or reduce the disparities. In other words, work to ensure that demographic characteristics bear no relationship to how well or poorly positioned an employee is to stay and succeed at work.</p><p> Every organization has talent flows that shape their workforce. Employers hire, train, and develop employees. And they value employees by giving them promotions, high ratings, raises, and other forms of compensation for the knowledge, capabilities, behavior, and experience they bring, the effort they deliver, and, ultimately, how they perform. Meanwhile, employees&#39; decisions to stay or leave are influenced by whether their careers are progressing.</p><p> These talent flows and rewards define the internal labor market of an organization and produce the supply of people with the attributes needed to meet the demands of the business. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> But as we have seen, different demographic groups within an organization do not have the same opportunities to acquire these attributes or be rewarded for them.</p><p> By not distributing opportunities equitably, companies effectively restrict their talent supplies. Women and people of color become more likely to leave or, if they stay, become less engaged because their careers are stalled. Knowing how the internal labor market functions for different demographic groups within an organization is thus crucial for a company to execute its DEI strategy.</p><p> To implement PCM, organizations should start by creating a success profile that identifies and ranks the factors that drive who advances. From there, they can examine how each factor influences the probability that employees from different demographic groups get promoted and whether the organization is valuing their capabilities and efforts equitably.</p><p></p><p> Small organizations might rely on the four factors described in the previous section. For them, controlled, statistical analyses of their own internal labor market data are likely infeasible. Such organizations might complement the research with qualitative input about the keys to career progress from their leaders and employees who have successfully risen in the ranks there.</p><p> Large employers with complex organizations will be best served by developing an objective success profile based on empirical evidence that identifies and ranks the critical individual and situational factors that drive success in the organization. The natural place to start is with the factors that drive promotions. But organizations might examine other markers of success as well, like pay, ratings, and retention, to see how well the results align with those from the analysis of promotions.</p><p> After creating the profile, the next step is to examine how the profile plays out for different demographic groups. There are two questions to answer.</p><p> First, are the factors that most influence employee success distributed similarly across demographic groups, or do they tend to be concentrated more in some groups than in others? These are <em>quantity effects</em> , and they reflect the relative frequency of the factors across groups. For instance, are women and people of color as likely as men and White employees to have the prized characteristics or to work in circumstances associated with success?</p><p> Second, when people possess the prized characteristics or work in favored circumstances, do they benefit equally from those attributes, or do some demographic groups benefit more? These are <em>price effects</em> . They reflect whether the employer values the attribute, behavior, or situation in question differently for one group than for another.</p><p> Objectively answering these questions is the foundation of PCM, as illustrated in the case of ConsumerCo.</p><p></p><h3> Positioning Employees for Success at ConsumerCo</h3><p> ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders were committed to improving career and pay equity in both their salaried and front-line workforces.</p><p> The company recognized that having a diverse workforce was not a luxury or a concession to social good; it was essential to its success. With an increasingly diverse customer base and growth occurring mostly in markets outside the US and Europe, having a leadership team and a workforce well attuned to the preferences and norms of local cultures was important to achieving growth targets.</p><p> HR and DEI leaders modeled their workforce data to uncover and assess the success profile for their salaried workforce. They identified 12 factors that were most likely to predict whether someone would be promoted. Situational factors dominated this success profile — a finding that stunned company leaders, who viewed the culture as a meritocracy. Of the top 12, only performance ratings and tenure were specific to the talents or accomplishments of an individual employee. The rest were purely circumstantial.</p><p> Being an expat (working outside one&#39;s home country) was the most positively influential factor. Reporting to a supervisor at a higher level than is typical had the least impact among the top 12 factors, but the effect was statistically significant.</p><p> Other factors included three of the four described earlier: having a high performance rating, being in a supervisory role, and reporting to a highly rated supervisor. In addition, working in certain functions or business lines mattered a lot to how one&#39;s career progressed.</p><p> Similar modeling showed that even the probability of receiving a high rating was inordinately influenced by situational factors. This finding suggested that performance ratings were not accurate measures of individuals&#39; contributions.</p><p> When ConsumerCo&#39;s leaders mapped the success profile to women in the company, they found that when women were positioned in situations conducive to their future progress, they usually fared as well as men. But overall, they were less likely to be so positioned. (See “Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile.”) For instance, women who were expats were more likely to be promoted from those roles than otherwise comparable men, but women were less represented among the expat population.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Mapping Women&#39;s Experiences to a Success Profile</h4><p class="caption"> A global consumer products retailer identified the 12 attributes that most strongly influenced whether an employee would be promoted. It found that in most cases, when women possessed any of these attributes, they were as likely to be helped by it as men were. However, women were less likely than men to possess 9 of the 12 attributes. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.) </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:45%;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Traits Favorable to Promotion<br /> <span class="normal">(in order of impact)</span></th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Likelihood That Women Possess Trait Compared With Men</th><th style="width:27.5%;text-align:center;line-height:1.5;text-transform:none;" class="white"> Relative Impact of Trait Compared With Men</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong>1. Being an expat</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>2. In Function M</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>3. In Function C</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>4. In Country A</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>5. In Bonus Plan F</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong style="color:crimson;">降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>6. In Function H</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>7. In Function S</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>8. Receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>9. Supervisor receives high rating</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>10. Being a supervisor</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>11. Longer tenured</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:#43BD29;"><strong>更高</strong></p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>12. Reporting up</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p style="color:crimson;"><strong>降低</strong></p></td><td style="text-align:center;"><p><strong>相似的</strong></p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_Nalbantian_Table_1.png" alt="Mapping Women’s Experiences to a Success Profile" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p> Being a supervisor is also an important stepping stone to success at ConsumerCo, but the company learned that women were less represented in supervisor roles. When they did have those roles, it did not help their careers to the same extent as comparable men, for reasons that were not clear. ConsumerCo leaders could see that female employees faced a double whammy of sorts: Not only were they blocked from this accelerator role, but they also didn&#39;t get the same lift to their promotion prospects as their male colleagues when they did have that role.</p><p> When the company looked at people of color, it found that they tended to be both less well positioned and less valued than White employees. ConsumerCo needed to change its internal labor market dynamics to achieve career and pay equity for women and people of color.</p><h3> A Checklist for Change</h3><p> Focusing on situational factors has a distinct advantage: They&#39;re easier to address than individual characteristics. For instance, although tenure is an important driver of success, it is a fact of people&#39;s employment history, not something that ConsumerCo could change overnight.</p><p> Still, ConsumerCo identified several areas where it could act reasonably quickly, such as changing reporting relationships for women and people of color, finding opportunities for them to gain more supervisory experience earlier in their careers, and addressing the disparities in performance ratings for people of color.</p><p> The company had found that taking a leave of absence thwarted career advancement, especially for women, and so it is also developing new leave and career development policies to address imbalances for that group.</p><p> Here&#39;s where the “proactive” part of PCM comes in.</p><p> The analysis of ConsumerCo&#39;s success profile made it possible to create a simple checklist of green lights (career advancers) and red flags (success blockers) that managers could use to evaluate the positioning of individual employees. By considering whether women and people of color on their teams were experiencing more green lights or red flags, line managers and supervisors could identify who was well positioned to stay and thrive, as well as who might be at risk of stalling in their career or leaving the organization. (See “Green Lights, Red Flags.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Green Lights, Red Flags</h4><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> A global consumer products retailer created a checklist of attributes that help or hurt employees&#39; career progress. Managers use the checklist to identify whether women and people of color on their teams are well positioned to advance or might be at risk of stalling in their careers or leaving the organization. They can then take any steps needed to increase access to success drivers and mitigate unintended consequences. (For reasons of confidentiality, discrete functions are identified only by letter.)</p><h4 style="color:#43BD29;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> GREEN LIGHTS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>FAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceptional” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being more tenured than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Receiving an “Exceeds” rating<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being younger than comparable peers</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p style="margin-bottom:30px;"> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being an expat<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being a supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in function M, C, S, or H<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Being in bonus plan F or L<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a higher-level supervisor<br /> <span style="color:#43BD29;">□</span> Reporting to a top-rated supervisor</p><h4 style="color:crimson;line-height:1.5;font-size:smaller;"> RED FLAGS<br /> <span class="normal" style="font-size:smaller;">(ATTRIBUTES <em>UNFAVORABLE</em> TO SUCCESS)</span></h4><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Individual Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Having a longer time in grade than comparable peers<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being part time<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Recently on leave<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Receiving a “medium” rating</p><h5 style="margin-bottom:0;"> Situational Attributes</h5><p> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working in distribution<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Working on the night shift<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Not in top brands<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Experienced a change in supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a female supervisor<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Being on teams with more older colleagues (reduces promotion likelihood, but increases chances of getting top rating)<br /> <span style="color:crimson;">□</span> Reporting to a supervisor with a larger number of direct reports</p></article></aside></div><p> Meanwhile, HR and DEI leaders used the analysis to evaluate at the aggregate level how employees from different demographic groups were positioned to succeed. For each factor, they could effectively evaluate the situational reality of different groups and tailor their interventions to address the most significant gaps.</p><p> For instance, they found that female, Black, and Hispanic employees were less likely to be reporting to highly rated supervisors, while Asian employees were more likely to have this advantage. And although women were less likely to be reporting to a manager one grade higher than usual, there were no such disparities for people of color. Also, while every non-White racial group was significantly underrepresented in one of the core functions that most contributed to advancement, women were more likely to work in that function than men.</p><p> ConsumerCo is in the early stages of rolling out interventions to address its disparities. But other companies I have worked with have pursued a variety of solutions.</p><p> Closing gaps due to flexible work arrangements often requires changing the culture. In many companies, part-time work is looked upon as evidence of lower commitment, and it can be difficult to shake these perceptions. However, companies can make quick progress on pay if they stop factoring leaves of absence into the statistical models that they use to assess pay equity and adjust wages and salaries to close gaps.</p><p> Situation-based racial disparities in performance ratings have been reduced in some companies through the calibration process used to align ratings by different supervisors. Some have also eliminated forced rankings that provide for a very limited percentage of employees to receive top ratings. These tend to favor people with more tenure, whom supervisors have known longer, and presumably better — and who are more likely to be White.</p><p> Some clients have addressed the importance of supervisor roles by expanding training, both to reinforce the importance of these roles and to help supervisors understand the impact they have on employees&#39; prospects. Leaders can offer training to help women and people of color gain the experience they need to advance — and close the gap between women and men in these positions.</p><h3> Proactive Career Management Has Benefits and Risks</h3><p> Because a success profile is built from an organization&#39;s data, it is more likely to reflect reality than the assumptions that leaders make about how employees succeed. Leaders may be prone to thinking that what got them to the top could get anyone else there as well, and they may oversimplify their own path. Further, people tend to generalize based on their own experiences, even if they don&#39;t represent the organizational norm.</p><p> A good empirical model can counter the tendency of people to engage in wishful thinking or to cling to belief. It can also account for the effects of being in different business lines, functions, geographies, and job families. This is something that&#39;s hard to do based on personal observation and experience alone.</p><p></p><p> Another value of PCM is that it is grounded in what creates value for the business. If, for instance, a role becomes critical to growth, one would expect the employer to accord more value to that role and the employees who successfully deliver value in it. And to the extent that an organization&#39;s DEI strategy helps ensure that high-potential women and people of color are able to access these newly valuable roles and perform them ably, it will serve the greater business need.</p><p> If there is a downside to PCM, it relates to the sharing of sensitive data and intelligence. PCM proceeds from objective modeling of the drivers of success and how they affect different groups. Invariably, the models will surface potentially damaging information about the existence of systemic gender or racial disparities in outcomes and opportunities, which creates legal risk.</p><p> PCM works best when managers understand the realities uncovered by the models and the reasons why specific actions are warranted. Thus, it requires a reasonable level of transparency. Corporate legal departments may, however, object to exposing what they may believe to be strong evidence of bias and inequity.</p><p> There&#39;s a delicate balance to be achieved. Most organizations I work with accomplish it by sharing high-level information with business and line leaders, and sometimes employee groups, about the reasons for particular actions while restricting the more granular data to a smaller group of top executives and HR and DEI leaders. Legal counsel almost always presides over such decisions; however, such advisers have become more understanding of the need for data-driven DEI strategies, appreciating that people can&#39;t solve problems they don&#39;t know about or understand.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The unexplained disparities in career opportunity and advancement at many organizations are important to address because they signal the potential influence of bias and discrimination. But doing so should not override attention to differences that can be explained by legitimate, business-relevant factors. The surest, most sustainable way to create career equity and equitable representation across all levels of an organization is to address the organization&#39;s career development practices (or lack thereof) that systemically impede the progress of women and people of color.</p><p> Of course, the work that employees do, their knowledge and skills, and how hard and effectively they work influence whether they will succeed. But success is also determined by how individuals are positioned to succeed — and organizations can do better at ensuring that all high-potential talent can gain experiences that will set them up for growth.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Empower Your Team, Empower Yourself</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Clayton, Andrew Artis, and Dejun Tony Kong. <p>Russell Clayton is an assistant professor of instruction, teaching MBA courses in the Muma College of Business at the University of South Florida. Andrew Artis is an associate professor teaching sales and strategy courses, also in the Muma College of Business. Dejun Tony Kong is an associate professor of organizational leadership at the University of Colorado Boulder&#39;s Leeds School of Business.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s rapidly evolving work environment, professional development is no longer a nice-to-have perk, it’s an imperative. With budgets tightening and workforce disruptions such as layoffs affecting many sectors, now is not the time for organizations to eliminate employee professional development and training. Likewise, individuals should continue to upskill regardless of whether organizational resources are [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Clayton-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> In today&#39;s rapidly evolving work environment, professional development is no longer a nice-to-have perk, it&#39;s an imperative. With budgets tightening and workforce disruptions such as layoffs affecting many sectors, now is not the time for organizations to eliminate employee professional development and training. Likewise, individuals should continue to upskill regardless of whether organizational resources are plentiful. In this article, we explore ways that executives may approach learning and development (L&amp;D) spending, as well as strategies for employees to secure professional development funding.</p><h3> For Managers: How L&amp;D Can Keep Teams Competitive</h3><p> In this first section, we&#39;ll explore three key strategies for managers to effectively allocate resources for L&amp;D, even during difficult economic times. When they better understand the importance of such programs, leaders can make more informed decisions that benefit the organization in the long term.</p><p></p><h4> 1. Assess the risk of cutting L&amp;D budgets.</h4><p> When budgets are tight, L&amp;D is often among the first programs to suffer cutbacks. This frequently happens because training is perceived as the low-hanging fruit when it comes to justifying budget cuts. However, these types of short-term cost-saving measures may not be a wise strategic move for executives. Having well-trained employees is critical to staying competitive, and we encourage executives to assess the risks their organization will be taking should they decide to eliminate employee training dollars.</p><p> For example, organizations that cut L&amp;D spending may fall behind when the economy recovers compared with those that maintain their investments. As a result, workers could lack the critical skills needed for organizational success. Furthermore, investing in L&amp;D helps companies do more with less. The number of skills needed for a single job has increased 10% annually since 2017, according to <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">research conducted by Gartner</a> . Those organizations that continue to prioritize upskilling will have employees who are up to date on the skills needed to accomplish their work, whereas organizations that significantly cut L&amp;D likely will not.</p><p> <a href="https://www.pwc.com/gx/en/ceo-survey/2020/reports/pwc-23rd-global-ceo-survey.pdf">PwC&#39;s annual CEO survey</a> found that companies with advanced L&amp;D programs in place had higher employee engagement and were better at attracting and retaining top talent. Executives must keep this in mind, even in the face of economic downturns, because slashing L&amp;D budgets can increase the risk of losing talented employees. As Josh Felperin, global sales director of Alps Controls, put it, “Investing in employees&#39; personal and professional development on a consistent basis should be any leadership team&#39;s No. 1 priority, not just financial results.”</p><h4> 2. Shift to framing L&amp;D as an investment.</h4><p> Managers need to consider L&amp;D as an investment rather than a cost. Think about how L&amp;D can generate revenue instead of being just another budget line item. For example, upskilling and promoting from within can save organizations money on recruitment and hiring. According to the Society for Human Resource Management, the average hard cost of recruiting a new employee is $4,700, with total costs — including soft costs such as time — amounting to two to three times the position&#39;s salary. Now imagine what your L&amp;D managers could do with just half of that dollar figure in terms of upskilling a current employee instead of hiring a new candidate. Not only are you saving on recruiting costs — you are also helping your organization close the skills gap that is plaguing many industries.</p><p></p><p> Finally, executives should view their <em>own</em> L&amp;D activities as an investment. In a tight economic environment, it might be tempting to cut both L&amp;D funds and the time dedicated to training. However, research has found a significant relationship between <a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/ijtd.12082">executive L&amp;D activities and organizational performance</a> .</p><h4> 3. Strategically prioritize the skills to be developed.</h4><p> When facing economic headwinds, budget reductions across all departments might be unavoidable, and we&#39;re not arguing that L&amp;D budgets should remain completely untouched. However, we do advocate for allocating funds to strategic training priorities. The reality is that some L&amp;D training may be postponed until the economy flourishes again. It might be necessary to prioritize hard skills, like project management or cybersecurity, over soft skills, like time management, in the short term. While we strongly support <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/answer-sheet/wp/2017/12/20/the-surprising-thing-google-learned-about-its-employees-and-what-it-means-for-todays-students/">soft skills training</a> — they play a key role in every business — we understand that L&amp;D funds may need to be spent on immediate hard-skills training needs in order to keep your organization competitive.</p><p> Match your L&amp;D expenditures to your organization&#39;s KPIs. Amazon is a great example of a company that does this. Despite recent major layoffs, it continues to train employees in key areas through its Upskilling 2025 initiative, including hard skills like cloud computing services and machine learning. Regardless of which skills you value most, the imperative is to be sure you&#39;re providing training opportunities. “Organizations that are not investing in the development of their employees are working against themselves and tripping over their own feet,” Jon Sexton, senior vice president of culture and leadership development at Vibrant Credit Union, asserted.</p><p></p><h3> For Employees: Strategies for Securing Professional Development Opportunities</h3><p> Pursuing professional development opportunities in the workplace can be challenging, particularly when budgets are constrained. Instead of passively waiting for workshop and training opportunities to arise, employees need to be proactive in convincing managers of the mutual benefits of L&amp;D investments.</p><p> That said, asking for money when budgets are tight is never an easy conversation, particularly when L&amp;D is perceived as merely nice to have. We recommend the following approaches to prepare your case, shape a productive conversation, and secure funding for your professional development.</p><h4> 1. Align your goals with your organization&#39;s needs.</h4><p> To increase your chances of obtaining approval for professional development opportunities, frame your request by demonstrating how the training will support your team&#39;s objectives. If you can explain how it will move your team forward, you&#39;re more likely to gain your manager&#39;s support (and funding).</p><p></p><p> Take the case of Nick. His employer already had an in-house training team delivering Continuing Professional Education hours for accountants, so he didn&#39;t think it would sign off on an external CPE course that focused on reviewing skills. To justify the expense and need — given his position as a junior accountant at the time — Nick discussed how the course would benefit the firm <em>first</em> and himself <em>second</em> with the managing partner. Nick emphasized that the course would help the company maintain its commitment to providing accurate, reliable information to clients through specific training on how to avoid making common tax accounting errors. By making the compelling argument that the external training would provide critical skills to help the company achieve its mission, Nick was able to convince his manager that the training would be valuable and received the funding.</p><p> Similarly, when Amanda, an insurance professional, asked her manager to pay for her training to earn her claims adjuster license, she took what she described as a “help me, help my team” approach. Amanda made her pitch for professional development during a time when the team she was on was struggling. While her current job function was <em>not</em> that of a claims adjuster, earning the license allowed her to help her organization in an area that really needed assistance.</p><p> During your pitch, ask your manager how they would like you to share the knowledge gained from training. This might involve a one-on-one follow-up, sharing presentation materials or bullet points summarizing the training, or even hosting a workshop to review the material with your team. By being proactive in sharing what you&#39;ve learned, you further solidify the benefits of professional development for the entire team.</p><h4> 2. Bring your manager on board.</h4><p> As <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/learning-for-a-living/">Gianpiero Petriglieri has noted</a> , many organizations “are not as hospitable to learning as their rhetoric suggests.” While employees may be frustrated by managers who overlook learning or prioritize performance over all else, they can educate managers on the benefits that professional development can bring to the company by taking a tactful approach.</p><p> For example, one vice president at a large industrial services company was reluctant to see training as an investment, fearing that employees might demand a raise or even leave after the training. In truth, this belief is a myth, if not irrational. Employees are a greater flight risk when they do <em>not</em> see internal opportunities and have to look elsewhere for personal growth. After all, employees are humans who have the fundamental need to feel competent, and they appreciate arrangements that are <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.obhdp.2015.08.002">customized to their skills and interests</a> . Employees can share third-party sources that emphasize the importance of targeted training to employee retention and engagement. For example, <a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/236438/millennials-jobs-development-opportunities.aspx">research from Gallup</a> suggests that professional development is a top factor in retaining millennials.</p><p> When discussing the topic with your manager, it&#39;s important to embrace a positive tone and remember that there might be resistance along the way. Shape the conversation in a way that focuses on how professional development increases the retention of valued employees. Be prepared to hear “no,” but probe to find out what might make your manager say “yes.” By understanding their concerns, you&#39;re better equipped to overcome those barriers. Consider asking questions like, “What would help you say yes?” or, “Would you worry about our competitor sending employees to this training?” This encourages your manager to consider the potential upsides of your request.</p><p> Three communication touch points are helpful for closing the circle when it comes to getting your manager invested in L&amp;D as a team resource. First, communicate clearly about the training you&#39;re seeking and gain permission to attend the training. Second, update your manager <em>during</em> the training, expressing your enthusiasm and gratitude. For example, you can send your manager a short status update on how the training is going and initial ideas you have to bring back to the team. Lastly, once the training is complete, acknowledge your manager&#39;s support when sharing your newfound knowledge with the team. By showing your excitement, you can inspire coworkers who also desire professional development.</p><h4> 3. Show your commitment to learning.</h4><p> When pitching your professional development request, consider providing several options, ranging from fully funded by the company to partially funded by you. Demonstrating your commitment to learning new skills, even if it means investing your own money, can make your request more persuasive.</p><p> Divya, for example, found a $2,500 training opportunity to develop the soft skills needed to better serve customers at her government agency job. Knowing that funding was limited, she proposed several options to her manager, including 100%, 50%, and 25% company funding. By having some skin in the game, Divya showed that she was serious about the training. In the end, her request was fully funded by the agency, but she was prepared to accept partial funding and cover the rest herself.</p><p> You can also show your commitment by exploring lower-cost or free opportunities before pursuing other options. An effective way to do this is to detail what you have learned so far through training options at no cost to your employer — and what skills or knowledge gaps still exist. Perhaps you want to earn a certification in data visualization. You can begin by completing online courses for free or at minimal cost, which can provide the foundational knowledge needed in this area and demonstrate your time investment. Then, explain to your manager what you&#39;ve learned and why additional, funded training is necessary to further your goals.</p><p></p><p> This collaborative negotiation process allows you to (1) <a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1571-9979.1999.tb00178.x">adopt an interest-based approach</a> , (2) help your manager <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0065-2601(08)60407-4">overcome psychological barriers</a> , and (3) <a href="https://doi.org/10.5465/amj.2012.0461">build trust</a> and mitigate your manager&#39;s perception of risk.</p><p></p><p> Prioritizing learning and development is essential for both managers and employees to help steer their organizations toward sustainable success and maintain a competitive edge. Even during economic uncertainty, strategic L&amp;D investments can boost employee engagement, close skill gaps, and foster growth. By recognizing the value of professional development and adopting a collaborative approach, leaders and employees alike can create a thriving learning culture that promotes individual and organizational success.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/empower-your-team-empower-yourself/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do You Have a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ane Casajús-Burutaran, Tina C. Ambos, and Gilbert Probst. <p>Ane Casajús-Burutaran is a research assistant and doctoral candidate at the University of Geneva. Tina C. Ambos is a full professor of international management at the University of Geneva. Gilbert Probst is an honorary professor at the University of Geneva and chairman of the Swiss Board Institute.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Reputation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Corporate Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><description><![CDATA[Corporate philanthropy spending reached new heights in 2021, exceeding $21 billion in the U.S. alone and marking a 24% increase over the previous year.1 These contributions, which traditionally focused on supporting galleries, museums, and shiny new buildings, have gained a higher profile in corporate decision-making. While management scholars have long pointed out the importance of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Casajus-Burutaran-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Corporate philanthropy spending reached new heights in 2021, exceeding $21 billion in the US alone and marking a 24% increase over the previous year. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These contributions, which traditionally focused on supporting galleries, museums, and shiny new buildings, have gained a higher profile in corporate decision-making. While management scholars have long pointed out the importance of corporate philanthropy, businesses&#39; approaches to it vary widely, and few have fully integrated it into their corporate strategy. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> This article examines the shifting landscape of corporate giving and the potential implications for businesses and their stakeholders.</p><p> As companies face growing pressures to incorporate purposeful social missions into their core businesses, leaders have gained experience managing initiatives aimed at social impact in addition to profit. While corporate social responsibility (CSR) is part of most companies&#39; business strategies, philanthropy often remains disconnected from core business objectives. This makes it challenging for leaders to discern what types of philanthropic engagement should be prioritized and why.</p><p></p><p> We define <em>strategic corporate philanthropy</em> as voluntary giving that builds on the company&#39;s core competencies to achieve social impact while improving its competitive edge — resulting in a win-win situation. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The scope of corporate philanthropic engagement is vast. (See “Main Types of Corporate Philanthropy Engagement.”) Even though gift matching has led the way for many years in the US, Coca-Cola, Google, and Walt Disney are just a few of the many multinationals that now engage in more than one type of corporate philanthropy. IBM&#39;s Open Source Community Grant program (with annual contributions of $200,000), the Danone Ecosystem (an impact investment fund with over $200 million committed since 2009), and the Ikea Foundation (with unrestricted funding for selected nonprofits working on emergency relief) are examples of the great diversity of corporate philanthropic engagement.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Main Types of Corporate Philanthropy Engagement</h4><p> <strong>Community grants:</strong> The company supports local community efforts or nonprofits with financial or in-kind contributions.</p><p> <strong>Corporate foundations:</strong> The company establishes and funds an independent legal entity to manage its philanthropic projects. These can be directly operated by the foundation or co-led through partnerships or grant giving.</p><p> <strong>Corporate sponsoring:</strong> The company finances the events, projects, or programs of a nonprofit organization.</p><p> <strong>Gift matching:</strong> The company matches the charitable donation of an employee, usually at a 1-1 ratio.</p><p> <strong>Venture philanthropy:</strong> The corporation takes the principles of venture capital financing to select, guide, and support a charitable project. This is often done through a corporate foundation.</p></article></aside></div><p></p><p> Increasingly, companies are establishing corporate foundations, which are legally independent entities that work exclusively on philanthropic activities. This allows them to take a more systematic approach to giving and create a “philanthropic identity.” Examples include the Walmart Foundation (with annual giving of $1.5 billion) and the Chanel Foundation (supporting over 150 charitable organizations since 2011). However, guidance remains limited on what type of philanthropic engagement would best fit a company&#39;s strategy.</p><p> Corporate philanthropy has the potential to create multiple benefits for a business, including enhanced reputation, legitimacy, local integration, network creation, knowledge acquisition, institutional acceptance, and stakeholder trust. But it also bears risks. Thus, companies must think carefully about what, how, and where to engage.</p><p> Our research examines the various strategies companies are testing in the realm of corporate philanthropy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> When building a corporate philanthropy strategy, a business&#39;s most important decisions revolve around three central issues: what topics to engage in, which parts of the company can support these efforts, and how to maximize impact. First, in terms of engagement, companies can either actively engage in the design, implementation, and evaluation of potential projects (operational), or provide the resources for another organization to take the lead (grant giving). This decision should be based on their knowledge and expertise in their respective field. The second decision is whether to house the project in an external entity, like a corporate foundation, or internally under a department like sustainability, HR, public relations, or partnerships. Lastly, the project must be anchored within the community to make a real impact, either through the company&#39;s own networks in the country or through local partners.</p><p></p><p> Our analysis offers a framework to assist managers in their decision-making process, enabling them to ask the right questions to understand the fit of a philanthropic project for their organization. Three dimensions need to be assessed.</p><p> <strong>Cognitive fit:</strong> <em>Does your company have the knowledge and expertise to engage in this social issue?</em> Corporate philanthropy, much like any business activity, demands specialized competencies; thus, companies need to be selective to maximize their impact. Tackling complex issues related to their primary industry is a good starting point because businesses already have expertise in dealing with customers, suppliers, and other stakeholders. Prominent examples include the Loewe Foundation&#39;s commitment to creativity and craftmanship — aligned with its identity as a luxury fashion house — and Adidas&#39; focus on expanding access to sports for all.</p><p> <strong>Structural fit:</strong> <em>Can the project be linked to the internal structure of your organization?</em> Every project needs organizational support to be integrated with the company&#39;s corporate structure and processes, which will potentially involve CSR, HR, or logistics. But one unit or department has to be in charge of providing adequate economic, human, social, and intellectual capital. We find that different corporations develop very different structural solutions to manage their philanthropic activities. Roche decided to create a whole new department, called the Corporate Donations and Philanthropy department, integrated under the CEO&#39;s office. Inditex still carries out its philanthropic activities within its sustainability department, and Visa chose to manage its donations through the Visa Foundation, as an independent entity.</p><p> <strong>Contextual fit:</strong> <em>Is the company well anchored in the local community, and does it have access to it, in order to effectively design and implement the project?</em> Gaining access to the local context is critical for success — it enhances onsite decision-making capabilities and fosters trust among stakeholders. If the organization engages in a familiar context, it can better tailor social solutions to local needs and do so more efficiently. For instance, HSBC&#39;s Hongkong Bank Foundation has distributed over HK$2.4 billion ($305.8 million) to support the Hong Kong community, its home market. Another example is the eBay Foundation, which encourages its employees to volunteer and give within their local communities.</p><p> Answering these questions helps companies craft a corporate philanthropy strategy and determine the implications of alternative pathways. (See “Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy.”) Our assessment framework can be used on individual projects and to systematically manage a portfolio. When planning and defining a potential philanthropic project, managers can answer the questions related to the three dimensions and consider the recommendations given for each option. For example, a US-based fintech company seeking to engage in research projects focused on Alzheimer&#39;s disease would have a low cognitive fit between the philanthropic project and company expertise. It would also have a low structural fit if it did not have an in-house department to support community outreach for medical issues. Additionally, the fintech firm would score low on contextual fit if it were to engage in a program in Somalia — a market in which it doesn&#39;t operate or have specific knowledge. Under these circumstances, a grant-giving strategy through an external body like a foundation would be advisable. As this case reveals, thinking about the three dimensions can help managers establish guiding principles for their corporate philanthropy strategy and set rules regarding what, how, and where to engage. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4 style="line-height:1.5;"> Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy: An Assessment Framework</h4><p class="caption"> Using a structured framework to answer key questions, companies can craft strategies that not only guide the development of potential philanthropic projects but also streamline the management of their philanthropic portfolios. </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile" style="width: 100%"><thead><tr><th style="width:23%;" class="white"> Dimension</th><th style="width:30%" class="white">评估</th><th style="width:45%" class="white">Evaluation</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Cognitive Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “What”)</p></td><td><p> <strong>Does your company have the knowledge and expertise to engage in this social issue?</strong> </p></td><td><div style="vertical-align:top"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Take an operational approach based on the company&#39;s knowledge and expertise. A corporate foundation, in-kind donations, or venture philanthropy might be the best solution. </p></div></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> Consider a grant-giving approach. Alternatively, engaging in a partnership with an expert organization can bridge the lack of cognitive fit and allow for more direct participation.</p></div></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Structural Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “How”)</p></td><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><p> <strong>Can the project be linked to the internal structure of your organization?</strong> </p></td><td style="background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Pursue this project internally; the CSR, HR, marketing, or communications teams may be suitable departments. You may choose to establish a dedicated unit focused on corporate donations and philanthropy. </p></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:rgba(224,224,224,1.00);"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> The missing structural fit suggests that establishing an external entity such as a corporate foundation may be a better option to pursue this project.</p></div></td></tr><tr><td><p> <strong style="font-size:larger;"><span class="blue">Contextual Fit</span></strong><br /> (the “Where”)</p></td><td><p> <strong>Is the company well anchored in the local community, and does it have access to it, in order to effectively design and implement the project?</strong> </p></td><td><div style="vertical-align:top"><div style="background-color:#43BD29; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p><span class="white"><strong>是的</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p>Take an operational approach to the project. Your onsite team will be able to provide support, contextual understanding, and access to the local network for effective implementation. </p></div></div></td></tr><tr><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"></td><td style="border-top:hidden; background-color:white;"><div style="background-color:crimson; width:15%; text-align:center; float:left;"><p> <span class="white"><strong>No</strong></span></p></div><div style="width:85%; float:right; padding-left:10px;"><p> A grant-giving approach is recommended in this case. Alternatively, engage in a partnership with an expert (local) organization. </p></div></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Casajus-Burutaran-Table.png" alt="Designing a Corporate Philanthropy Strategy: An Assessment Framework" class="no-desktop" /></p></article></aside></div><p> Our study of the Adecco Group, a Fortune Global 500 company and leader in HR solutions based in Switzerland, offers a prime example of the strategic decision-making process in corporate philanthropy. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> In 2017, the Adecco Group established a global foundation, and leaders took a proactive approach to create synergies between the company&#39;s social and business strategies.</p><p> The Adecco Group&#39;s foundation has a clear purpose closely aligned to the corporation&#39;s mission: <em>Making the future work for everyone.</em> Initially, many of its social programs were transferred to the foundation. Over time, however, the Adecco Group&#39;s philanthropic portfolio grew and became very diverse, requiring a detailed assessment across the cognitive, structural, and contextual fit of the programs. In 2021, the management team carefully selected the foundation&#39;s priority projects based on the questions provided in our assessment framework. Accordingly, other initiatives were given back to the company (and integrated into the respective departments), and some were entrusted to better-suited nonprofits to take forward. This strategic move allowed the Adecco Group&#39;s foundation, now called the Innovation Foundation, to redefine its corporate philanthropy strategy and develop a decision-making framework rooted in three principles:</p><p> <strong>Industry expertise (cognitive fit).</strong> The foundation now focuses exclusively on the domains of employment, skills, and the future of work — the business&#39;s areas of expertise. In addition to receiving financial support, it benefits from the knowledge, data, experience, and ecosystem of the Adecco Group. This mutually beneficial relationship ensures that the valuable outcomes and insights generated by the foundation are shared back to the company.</p><p> <strong>Tailored social innovation lab methodology (structural fit).</strong> The foundation developed a proprietary operating model that blends data-driven analysis, design thinking, and innovation to deliver user-centric solutions following an acceleratorlike process. Thus, projects that did not align with that format — such as grant giving and fundraising — were given back to the business. These projects were run in the marketing or sustainability department, contingent on their structural fit and their knowledge, personnel, and network needs.</p><p> <strong>Local knowledge (contextual fit).</strong> Because the Innovation Foundation focuses on projects with long-term impact — those that address the source of a problem rather than the symptoms — local partners and end users are involved at every stage. One example is the foundation&#39;s Women Back to Work project in Spain, where the continuous involvement of local organizations and beneficiaries ensures that the program incorporates a deep understanding of the real problems of women reintegrating into the workforce in that context. Once a project has been developed and tested in-house, it is spun off for a local partner organization to scale and create maximum impact.</p><p></p><p> In the year following the foundation&#39;s restructuring, the team pursued three projects aimed at boosting employability for women, young adults, and older employees. These initiatives have provided the company with insights and real-time data on the unmet needs and potential solutions for underserved populations in the labor market.</p><p></p><p> The Adecco Group&#39;s case demonstrates the power of a well-crafted corporate philanthropy strategy that is grounded in guiding principles. As corporate giving becomes increasingly important in today&#39;s business landscape, it&#39;s critical for companies to focus their efforts on maximizing their social impact as well as their competitive position. A well-executed philanthropic strategy not only benefits society but also strengthens an organization&#39;s market position by providing access to new knowledge and expanding the organization&#39;s network.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-you-have-a-corporate-philanthropy-strategy/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Making Investments in AI: Samsung&#39;s Hina Dixit</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startup Financing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Venture Capital]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Hina Dixit’s interest in supporting people and solving problems has its roots in her family’s call office business, where she helped people place telephone calls when she was growing up in India. Later, after earning her bachelor’s degree in computer science, she was quickly recruited into the tech space, where her problem-solving and customer service [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Hina Dixit&#39;s interest in supporting people and solving problems has its roots in her family&#39;s call office business, where she helped people place telephone calls when she was growing up in India. Later, after earning her bachelor&#39;s degree in computer science, she was quickly recruited into the tech space, where her problem-solving and customer service skills have served her well as both a software engineer and tech investor. From a developer role at Symantec, to project leader at Apple, to an AI investor role at Samsung Next, Hina continues to leverage her communication and connection skills in seeking out and supporting innovations in artificial intelligence, as well as robotics, Web3, and other tech sectors.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Hina shares the criteria she considers when making investments in new entrepreneurial ventures. She also highlights the focus areas that are of most interest right now, explains why she enjoys mentoring other technologists, and shares her views on what the future of AI looks like. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-s7-e4-Dixit-Instagram-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="希娜迪克西特"></p><h4> Hina Dixit, Samsung Next</h4><p> Hina Dixit is a venture capitalist and software engineering leader with more than 13 years of experience. She is currently an investor at Samsung Next, focusing on the AI, augmented reality, Web3, and infrastructure sectors.</p><p> Before she joined Samsung Next, Dixit led a team at Apple that worked on a variety of projects, including security, iCloud, artificial intelligence, developer tools, and data integrity, for eight years. She is an investor in several companies, including Stability AI, MosaicML, and Space and Time.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-dixit"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How does one technology leader approach AI investments? Find out her five criteria on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I&#39;m Hina Dixit from Samsung Next, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> On today&#39;s episode, we have Hina Dixit, an investor at Samsung Next. Hina, thanks for joining us.欢迎。</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Thank you so much. It&#39;s a pleasure being here with you.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Most of our listeners are likely familiar with Samsung — giant South Korean multinational, lots of consumer electronics — but people may be less familiar with Samsung Next, so let&#39;s start there. Can you describe what Samsung Next is and what your role is?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. Samsung Next is the private equity or venture capital arm of Samsung. We tend to be stage-agnostic, but at the same time, we have six focus areas where we invest. AI is one of them. We also invest in fintech, blockchain, and infrastructure, and media tech as well, along with health tech.</p><p> Along with these six focus areas, we tend to make more and more learned investments about the ever-changing, dynamic world as well. So if you or anyone has a cool idea, please feel free to reach out.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I should&#39;ve prepared more and had a few pitches ready so that we could&#39;ve put you on the spot here while we were recording and get you on record there. So, what, exactly, do you do, though?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I currently lead the AI investment segment area. If there is any deal which is associated with AI, I tend to lead that deal and also work on the investment strategy for Samsung Next.</p><p> When you head out to these startup demos, to these pitches and expos, you will see thousands of startups. Now, how do you ensure that you are focused on the right areas which matter to Samsung? It should also propel innovation further; [instead of simply] furthering the innovation, it should also be usable. So that&#39;s why having a paradigm will help you make those sound decisions, where you can actually prioritize certain areas ahead of time compared to other investors, and understand which of the current technologies will be booming, say, a few years from now. And accordingly, you tend to segment and understand that, OK, these are my top-priority areas.</p><p> At the same time, I&#39;m very, very passionate about mentoring entrepreneurs, mentoring fellow people in tech. I come from a tech background, so I can always understand the hiccups people face when they are moving from individual-contributor roles or management roles in these big techs and moving forward to a startup entrepreneurial journey. I love connecting with them and helping them out.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s really wonderful, Hina. So I want to talk about both things you said, both the mentoring, but also I want to go back to how you pick an investment. I mean, obviously, where you&#39;re sitting, you are looking at thousands of opportunities probably, right? And so you mentioned there are some guiding principles in terms of how you prioritize where to focus and what fits strategically with Samsung, but tell us more about how you pick an investment once you&#39;ve already gone through that filter, that “OK, it&#39;s the right thing for the company. We want to do it.” Now you&#39;re actually evaluating an AI company. Tell us how you pick. What are the factors you consider?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I tend to focus on very important factors for me personally. Every investor out there has a very different way of investing. Some people are very intuition-driven, and I have seen such investors make really great decisions. Some people are very theory-driven, and some people tend to take it as they go.</p><p> I am a mix of all of them. I tend to make these sound, learned decisions where I&#39;m very comfortable and I know the space very well. One thing that is always very important for me is the team. Is there a right product-team fit here? Are these individuals capable of building these great products that they&#39;re promising? I think that is an essential parameter for me.</p><p> And then, moving on to the problem itself: Is this pain point really [going to be] valid in few years? The pain point has to be there. The next thing is the technical innovation. Now, that is important, because that serves as a mode for you, or mode for these entrepreneurs, right? Otherwise, any big tech [company] can just go in and create what they have created. We want to have a solid mode around these products that they&#39;re building and some sort of novelty.</p><p> And then, moving from technical innovation and the mode, obviously there has to be a decent market size. You might be building an awesome product, but at the same time, the market sizing [might be] very small. It becomes really hard to scale that kind of product. Even if it&#39;s not monetizable, it should be solving a very solid pain point, plus the impact of that particular solution has to be global. And that&#39;s another factor for me, where I tend to make my own decision that, OK, this is something which is going to change everything that we do today.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Tell us more about the team, because technology is one aspect, but how do you suss out both the capability of the team itself and then how well the team works with each other? I mean, a lot of startups have team issues, right?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> How do you look into that?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Sure. I think it&#39;s a very deep question, and I think it comes from my days at Apple. Apple has a very startuplike culture in some of their organization, and here I&#39;m speaking about the culture because there were so many learnings from them. When I started, there was a very open culture where people would come on the weekends to support and mentor you and help you. They wouldn&#39;t even ask for any kind of credit. They would help you move forward, and at the same time, they will not just stop there. They will empower you. They will connect you with the right connections across the organization.</p><p> I kind of felt that it is very difficult for people to be that selfless and just focus on making the product great, but I think that&#39;s what the spirit of Apple is, and I tend to see a similar spirit in founders if I know that they&#39;re very, very product-driven, or they&#39;re very, very goal-driven in terms of [their] team. Then I tend to get that sense, OK, these guys will support each other.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You&#39;ve got some extensive experience in this area. You mentioned Apple a couple of times. Tell us a bit about how you got to where you are now from where you started.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I come from a very humble family background. So while my dad would work very hard, I would help them out with our family business, which was a small public call office, or a PCO, where people [went] and used to make telephone calls. So I used to sit there, and I used to make those calls for people, handle the customers, and enable them to make these phone calls, and that was a very good learning point for me because I learned how to talk to people.</p><p> From being a very introverted child, I became very public-facing, right then and there. … Like, OK, these are my customers. They are top priority. I need to serve them, help them, and that&#39;s where I think some of these qualities that I [espouse] or these passions that I have — that I love helping people, I love solving conflicts — probably arise.</p><p> I did my high school from Kanpur [City in India], which is Mercy Memorial School, and after my high school, I went to a women&#39;s college because my parents were a bit conservative yet. I was the first girl in the entire family of my dad&#39;s side who went outside of the city in order to get an education.</p><p> It was immensely fun. It was a very safe and secure environment. Obviously, it was very competitive — we women tend to be very competitive — and at the same time, I made great friends there, and I learned so much from my classmates at that time. We used to trade on these various ideas, and we used to create these JavaServer Pages-based applications, web applications for online quizzing, test banks, writing educational articles.</p><p> I remember, even buying a Starbucks coffee at that time used to be a very, very far-off thought because it was so expensive for me, and I used to work multiple jobs at the same time. And then I was placed at Symantec six months ahead of graduation. So that took some pressure off of me, and Symantec was a great starting point for me. I was in their data loss prevention team. I learned significantly from all the mentors there. I still share great relationships with all of them. And then Apple happened, and the rest is history.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing that&#39;s fascinating: As you were saying that, I was thinking about how you tied your exposure to customer service through that very early call office job.</p><p> At the same time, much of what we&#39;re talking about with artificial intelligence ... it strikes me that the kind of job that would be suspect or likely to be replaced, and I have to wonder, how does the next Hina Dixit come along without that experience if we don&#39;t have those introductory customer service-oriented jobs to learn those skills?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, I get the question. This has been a grave thought, and a lot of people are coming forward and discussing it. But I think AI is not going to replace people. AI is going to empower people, and that&#39;s the thought process I come from. Just because phones became relevant, it didn&#39;t mean that [the mail was] not relevant anymore. We still order Amazon packages, and we still get our bills in the mail and whatnot, and that&#39;s how I think we will be able to push mankind. That&#39;s how we keep on pushing each and every … mile toward the ultimate goal of humankind&#39;s future, right?</p><p> Moving to the ultimate goal there, I think nobody should blindly trust that, OK, AI is going to replace their job, but they should be able to learn about AI. And that&#39;s one of the things where I&#39;ve been focusing on: finding these really cool technologies which can help people ramp up on AI.</p><p> Like, why do people need to write any single piece of code in order to use AI? Why can&#39;t this be as simple as looking at an Excel sheet? Why can&#39;t this be as accessible [as a] user interface, which is very easily programmable by just any business user out there? So finding that kind of interface between AI and the current users, that is a very critical piece where I think investors should focus on, because the ultimate goal here is to normalize the usage of AI and make that publicly available and at the same time accessible as well.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I think this is a very, very good point. That vision you painted is actually quite appealing. It used to be, the human element of AI was around making the technology better, faster, cheaper, or [writing] the next-generation algorithm, which of course, we still do, but that&#39;s going to be more and more in the R&amp;D and innovation zone. I think, as you&#39;re saying, the usage of AI will go from humans&#39; role as programmers and writers of code to more working at that interface, of having these building blocks and connecting those building blocks that AI provides to solve existing problems, but more importantly, as you&#39;re saying, thinking about “What else can we do with this? How do you innovate, now that you have all this at your fingertips?”</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah. I kind of think the same way, because anybody ... you know, think of Excel. Anybody can just jump into Excel and make applications out of it. I know there are a bunch of cool apps coming around productivity right now which are backed by AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Share with us a bit your view on the coolest areas of technology that you are looking at right now. What piques your interest these days with everything that&#39;s going on with cyber and Web3 and quantum computing and everything else? Can you share specific investments or areas you&#39;re looking at?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Sure. We are focused a lot on infrastructure pieces of Web3, and at the same time, we are also focusing a lot on the AI aspect of Web3. So can we use these decentralized systems in order to make compute efficient? That&#39;s a question that we are trying to … answer right now. We are also trying to dive in deeper on the health-tech side, where we want to digitize the normal health paradigm, and we want to empower users out there and give them more proper feedback, maybe in their diet, maybe connect them to the right agents or doctors or nurses.</p><p> The focus is on empowering the humans. That&#39;s where I think we are trying to focus. And then obviously there is meta-tech aspect, which is the metaverse. We&#39;re trying to understand, how easy would it be to convert any image into a 3D asset and place it in the metaverse? And then, how do we make this metaverse accessible, just like the real world?</p><p> It seems surreal, but at the same time, there&#39;s so much hard work and research for each and every aspect of this. We are also focusing a lot on the fintech perspective and trying to empower these LatAm [Latin American] countries, finding a way they can build very sustainable and safe credit-scoring systems in Asia, for example, [and in] India, East Asia, and LatAm countries. So building a lot of infrastructure around fintech in LatAm countries and Asian countries is another thing that we are focusing on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah, I think that infrastructure&#39;s particularly interesting because that is an area where artificial intelligence can make a difference, when you can get some scale through an infrastructure. It&#39;s one of those situations that it seems like it opens up new possibilities when the economics change — when things that were no longer possible become possible. Are there other things that you&#39;re working on that are next in the portfolio? What are we going to see from Samsung Next next?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> We are moving into robotics as well. I did invest in one of the companies, called Integral AI, and they are trying to use these large AI models or foundation models [to train] their robots. But at the same time, robotics is another area where we want to focus on the consumer robotics aspect, so any cool startups out there building these cool consumer robots, please feel free to reach out to us, and we&#39;ll be happy to jump in and help out.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Hina, we&#39;ve got a segment where we ask you a series of questions, and these are supposed to be rapid-fire. Just give us the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> OK.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You&#39;ve got a past career that&#39;s over a decade of being involved in these technologies. What&#39;s your proudest AI moment? What&#39;s the thing in this portfolio that you&#39;re proudest of that involves AI?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I think I&#39;ll have to say Stability AI because before that, there were a lot of research communities around, but at the same time, there was no way that somebody could go and commercialize those research works. And I really value Emad Mostaque&#39;s work there — that he recognized this problem and he got these research facilities together in order to start commercializing and build more solid consumer end products.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> We&#39;ve been very positive about artificial intelligence today, but is there anything that worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I think one thing that worries me is that we have seen a recent burst of these large language model-based apps, and that does include ChatGPT. I love their work, but at the same time, there are other pain points. And then, obviously, there are copyright issues that we need to solve, there are security issues. So those are some of the other areas we are trying to focus on, and trying to understand how those pain points can be resolved.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> It&#39;s basically gardening in my house. I just find that very therapeutic, and, secondly, I love playing with my dog, Jimmy. He&#39;s absolutely adorable.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What was the first career you wanted? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> I have always wanted to be a startup founder. I was 8 when I manifested that … I would be a founder, I would be building great products, and I would be helping out other people. So ever since I was 8, [I&#39;ve been] chasing that dream.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for artificial intelligence in the future? What are you hoping we can gain from this?</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> My biggest wish for AI would be enabling common sense in some way, because these large AI models, they do have some AI capabilities when they can be put together in conjunction. We know from the recent <a href="https://doi.org/10.48550/arXiv.2204.02311">PaLM research paper that Google published</a> that, OK, there is a way of having these multiple multimodels work together in order to create more sensible information and reliable information out there for users to believe in, and they basically used it to train their robots.</p><p> So that&#39;s one application, but a lot can come forward from that particular research work that Google published, including chain-of-thought prompting as well. How do you use these several models to work together in order to perform better in real-world and unstructured environments? So that would be very cool to see.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK, yeah, that seems so exciting to me, too, because we originally had the generative AI adversarial models, where, yes, we learned how to play chess really quickly, or we learned through a game, but the universe that has expanded from the idea that we can have bazillions of these models working kind of with and against each other — that seems very natural to, well, the way that we as humans or current biology works. It seems like there&#39;s a lot of potential for that.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Yeah, yeah.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, Hina, thanks for taking the time to talk with us today. I think that there&#39;s lots — actually, particularly from your background — that is inspiring to people. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah, thank you so much.</p><p> <strong>Hina Dixit:</strong> Thank you so much for having me. It was a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. On our next episode, Shervin and I speak with Elizabeth Anne Watkins, research scientist at Intel Labs. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/making-investments-in-ai-samsungs-hina-dixit/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>