<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 7 日星期五 12:24:02 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title> 2023 年 10 篇最受欢迎的文章（迄今为止）</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Workplace]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Three-plus years after COVID-19 interrupted office-based operations with a sudden transition to remote work, managing hybrid teams remains a pressing issue for leaders. Hybrid culture has its own pitfalls to manage, with risks like feelings of disconnection among employees and “productivity paranoia.” Based on the most-read articles in the first half of 2023, readers of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MostPopular2023-tile-angleREV-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>在 COVID-19 中断办公室运营并突然过渡到远程工作三年多后，管理混合团队仍然是领导者面临的紧迫问题。混合文化有其自身需要管理的陷阱，其中存在诸如员工之间的脱节感和“生产力偏执”等风险。根据 2023 年上半年阅读量最大的文章， <cite>《麻省理工斯隆管理评论》</cite>的读者似乎热衷于解决这些问题。改进工具可以在有关基于技能的文化变革、有效的一对一会议和知识诚实的文章中找到。读者还关注 ESG、可持续性以及人工智能在绩效管理和战略中日益重要的作用等宏观问题。</p><p>以下是迄今为止今年最受欢迎的 10 篇文章。我们希望他们将继续帮助领导者管理和支持员工以及建立蓬勃发展的创新组织。</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#1</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/work-from-home-regulations-are-coming-companies-arent-ready/" style="border-bottom:none;">在家工作法规即将出台。公司还没有准备好。</a></h4><h6>希梅纳·穆里略·查瓦罗</h6><p>世界各地管理灵活工作安排的监管细节网络不断扩大，这对跨国公司构成了严峻的挑战。这些公司现在必须应对不同司法管辖区的不同合规要求，具体取决于政府如何定义和解释<em>远程工作</em>、<em>远程办公</em>和<em>在家工作</em>等术语。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#2</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-to-make-your-one-on-one-meetings-more-effective/" style="border-bottom:none;">让一对一会议更有效的五种方法</a></h4><h6>杰西卡·威德姆</h6><p>经理与其团队或直接下属之间的每周汇报会议是建立信任的经理与员工关系的关键机会。通过采取五个有科学依据的步骤并提出五个关键问题，管理人员可以更好地组织一对一的沟通，从而提高签到的效率。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#3</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-innovation-depends-on-intellectual-honesty" style="border-bottom:none;">为什么创新取决于知识诚实</a></h4><h6>杰夫·戴尔、内森·福尔、柯蒂斯·勒弗兰特和塔亚·豪厄尔</h6><p>仅促进心理安全不足以成功推动创新；领导人还必须创造有利于健康辩论的条件。作者描述了在心理安全与公开、诚实的辩论之间建立平衡最重要的因素，并概述了领导者可以采取哪些措施来创建高绩效的学习和创新文化。</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#4</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt" style="border-bottom:none;">使用 ChatGPT 讨论战略的三个教训</a></h4><h6>克里斯蒂安·斯塔德勒和马丁·里夫斯</h6><p>由于对 ChatGPT 等大型语言模型的潜在用例感到非常兴奋，两位业务战略家决定测试这些工具是否可以支持构思、实验、评估和讲故事，作为战略创建过程的一部分。在本文中，他们分享了在进行一系列实验时得出的三个教训，在这些实验中，他们向 ChatGPT 提出了策略问题，并随后进行了迭代查询。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#5</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-is-helping-companies-redefine-not-just-improve-performance/" style="border-bottom:none;">人工智能正在帮助公司重新定义绩效，而不仅仅是提高绩效</a></h4><h6>迈克尔·施拉格、大卫·基隆、弗朗索瓦·坎德隆、谢尔文·科达班德和迈克尔·朱</h6><p>对组织使用人工智能的研究为推动绩效的因素以及如何最好地衡量绩效提供了新的视角。 KPI 重新定义战略衡量的三种实用且有价值的方法包括使用具有学习能力的智能 KPI、衡量 KPI 本身的绩效以及增强组织与 KPI 的一致性。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#6</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/esg-is-going-to-have-a-rocky-2023-sustainability-will-be-just-fine" style="border-bottom:none;">ESG 2023 年将遭遇坎坷。可持续发展会很好。</a></h4><h6>安德鲁·温斯顿</h6><p>公司的环境、社会和治理活动面临两种反弹：“反觉醒”政治戏剧和投资界关于 ESG 基金是否会优于“常规”基金的噪音。尽管 ESG 受到这些风浪的冲击，可持续发展的<em>真正</em>工作仍在继续。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#7</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-toxic-culture-gap-shows-companies-are-failing-women" style="border-bottom:none;">有毒的文化差距表明公司正在辜负女性</a></h4><h6>唐纳德·索尔和查尔斯·索尔</h6><p>企业文化的哪些元素对女性最重要？哪些文化缺陷导致女性走向出口？在分析 Glassdoor 评论中 300 万美国员工用来描述其雇主的语言时，作者发现有毒文化对女性的影响尤为严重，在包容性和尊重方面的性别差距最大。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#8</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-the-cultural-pitfalls-of-hybrid-work" style="border-bottom:none;">管理混合工作的文化陷阱</a></h4><h6>克里斯汀·摩尔曼和凯蒂·辛克弗斯</h6><p>尽管混合工作模式已在许多企业中广泛采用，但它所带来的涉及同事关系和联系的复杂性仍然存在。这里提出的一组策略可以帮助领导者在这个数字化转型时代驾驭组织文化和新员工的社交。</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#9</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change" style="border-bottom:none;">采用基于技能的方法进行文化变革</a></h4><h6>佩尔·胡甘德</h6><p>采用基于技能的方法，而不是实施典型的文化变革举措，可以带来持久的行为积极变化，特别是在培养<em>观点采择</em>和创造心理安全等软技能方面。作者解释了基于技能的文化变革方法的关键属性，以及组织如何利用它来加速流程并提高长期绩效。</p><h4> <span class="blue">#10</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-ways-to-build-a-culture-of-honesty-and-avoid-productivity-paranoia/" style="border-bottom:none;">建立诚实文化并避免“生产力偏执”的四种方法</a></h4><h6>帕梅拉·迈耶</h6><p>远程和混合工作环境可能会在经理和员工之间、或者远程和现场同事之间滋生不信任或生产力偏执。作者描述了当人们无法面对面互动和发展关系时，管理者可以采取四个步骤来培养信任和诚实的文化。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>监管人工智能创新：Aboitiz Data Innovation 的 David Hardoon</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulate-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulate-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Chief Executive Officer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[As CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation, David Hardoon oversees the operations of a technology conglomerate focused on using data science and AI to support its businesses in a range of sectors, including banking, financial services, utilities, agriculture, and construction in Singapore and the Philippines. In his role, David is leading some unexpected — but practical [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>作为 Aboitiz Data Innovation 的首席执行官，David Hardoon 负责监管一家技术集团的运营，该集团专注于利用数据科学和人工智能来支持其在新加坡和菲律宾的银行、金融服务、公用事业、农业和建筑等一系列领域的业务。 David 在其职位上领导了人工智能的一些意想不到但实际的应用，包括使用语音和图像识别来检测牲畜的压力，以及分析物联网数据以减少水泥研发过程中的废物和 CO <sub>2</sub>排放。</p><p> David 加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客的这一集，讨论他所负责的组织的广泛范围、人工智能监管和治理在帮助刺激创新方面的作用、人类在塑造人工智能输出方面有时会出现问题的角色，以及如何一次高中留校经历让他开启了人工智能职业生涯。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MMAI-S7-E3-Hardoon-Aboitiz-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="大卫·哈顿"></p><h4> David Hardoon，Aboitiz 数据创新</h4><p>David Hardoon 是 Aboitiz Data Innovation 的首席执行官，也是菲律宾联合银行的首席数据和人工智能官。他兼任 Aboitiz Group 首席数据和创新官、UnionDigital Bank 首席数据官。此前，他是新加坡金融管理局首位任命的首席数据官和数据分析小组负责人，以及人工智能特别顾问。 Hardoon 拥有南安普顿大学计算机科学（机器学习）博士学位以及伦敦大学皇家霍洛威学院计算机科学和人工智能学士学位。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>混凝土生产？家畜？苏格拉底式的方法？不知何故，我们谈论这三个。在今天的节目中了解它们如何与人工智能联系起来。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>我是来自 Aboitiz Data Innovation 的 David Hardoon，你们正在听的是<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天，Shervin 和我很高兴 David Hardoon 加入，他在 Aboitiz 集团担任多个高级职位。大卫，感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>非常感谢山姆、谢尔文。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您能先向我们介绍一下 Aboitiz 集团吗？你在哪里工作？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong> Aboitiz 集团是一家拥有 100 多年历史的企业集团，起源于西班牙加泰罗尼亚，后来迁至菲律宾。它始于大麻业务，但现在相当多元化，从主要业务（菲律宾各地的发电和配电）到金融服务、水泥、建筑、公用事业、房地产、机场、食品、农业。我们现在正在经历一场转型，正在成为——顺便说一下，我喜欢这个词——科技集团。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Aboitiz 数据创新是什么？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>大约七年前，该银行开始实现银行服务的全部数字化。正如您所想象的那样，这会产生大量数据。您以数字方式吸引消费者的次数越多，您拥有的数字服务就越多——嗯，惊喜，惊喜——您拥有的数据就越多。</p><p>问题也随之而来，我们如何真正使用它？我们在使用它吗？充分利用它的最佳方法是什么？正如你可以想象的那样，这个问题也超出了银行的范畴，涉及到其他企业。电源有很多数据；农业、机场等，都有大量的数据。</p><p>我们生来就有一个非常切题的使命：操作数据，操作人工智能。确实如此，我们该如何充分利用它呢？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>其中有哪些用途？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>我的意思是，在通常的金融方面，我们都从超个性化和金融犯罪中学习。别误会我的意思——那些东西……总是让我兴奋不已。我在新加坡的金融监管机构度过了几年美好的时光。</p><p>但让我告诉你一个奇怪的事情：水泥，一个你不会真正与数据或人工智能联系在一起的行业。我们当时与首席执行官坐下来，我们说：“看，即使在水泥领域，你也有很多数据。”</p><p>这怎么行？那么，让我向您介绍一下水泥世界是如何运作的。这对我来说是新鲜事。基本上，这就像烘焙一样。我不知道你是否烘焙，但这就像烘焙。基本上，你有混合物。你有了这些类型的配方，最终得到了具有不同类型特性的水泥。这些房产绝对至关重要，具体取决于您计划建造的内容，无论是购物中心、高层建筑、低层建筑、住宅等。</p><p>话虽如此，就像烘焙一样，你需要进行一些尝试和错误。您需要尝试这些不同的混合物，以确保它产生正确的混合物。这会导致运营开销。这会导致浪费。我的意思是，就像烘焙一样，你把这些东西放进窑里——字面意思是一个熔炉——来烘烤它。使用数据，使用来自所有设备的信息，物联网，使用人工智能，能够在面包师开始之前实际告诉面包师，或者在这种情况下，化学工程师这种混合物的输出是什么，同时保持质量控制，这绝对至关重要。顺便说一句，这不仅仅是假设。去年，该系统已在所有工厂（菲律宾约六家工厂）投入运行，提高了运营效率，减少了浪费，实现了我所说的可量化的 ESG（环境、社会） 、治理]：CO <sub>2</sub>排放量减少35万吨。这是一个关于如何使用数据的很好的、不寻常的例子。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>嗯，我可以告诉你，Sam 和我会喜欢这个。我们都是化学工程师。</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>哦，好吧，就这样。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>实际上，当你说烘焙时，我已经获得了博士学位。在催化剂合成方面，所以我花了很多时间烘烤各种铝硅酸盐来制造催化剂。你是完全正确的：你尝试了所有这些事情。一些工作;有些不起作用。如果我有能力提前知道，我可能会获得博士学位。在十分之一的时间内。</p><p>但说真的，这很有趣。现在，如果你从个性化、网络和欺诈开始，并且你也有烘烤水泥的这个例子，那么我们必须相信你正在考虑的事情有如此广泛的组合。请告诉我们更多有关该投资组合的内容，因为您可以做的事情是没有止境的。哪些事情会让你感到兴奋？</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>你说得完全正确。幸运的是，在一家企业集团工作，你每天醒来都会发现新的东西。所以它有两个维度。一方面——我要回到<em>操作化</em>这个术语，操作化数据和人工智能——它必须对业务有意义。所以收入、运营效率、风险管理。然后我们必须看看即将发生的事情。我们必须进行实验。但这些可能不会立即部署。就像，在农业建设者中，我们有动物；我们有猪、猪和家禽。作为这一过程的一部分，我们希望确保动物得到尽可能最好的照顾。在实验方面，我们说，“好吧，我们如何使用已经可用但可能尚未完全应用于特定环境（而不是东南亚）的技术？”因此，我们对猪使用语音识别和图像识别来帮助识别压力和检测疾病，以便向护理人员自动发出警报。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>基本事实是什么？知道这一点会很有趣。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个很好的问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>训练数据是什么？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>这真是太神奇了。这是一种非常富有表现力的动物。因此，当你真正和照顾它们的人一起去那里时，他们可以直接指着它们说：“这只动物很痛苦”，然后你就可以不断地录音。</p><p>我们会说，“好吧，这真的是相关的吗？是否有意义？”比如，我们可以和面包师、化学工程师进行对话吗？当我们处理电缆时，我们可以与动物饲养员、兽医等或电线杆工程师进行对话吗？这非常重要。</p><p>这是我在从事数据工作的整个职业生涯中意识到的一件事，就是事情失败的地方，你突然在探索科学研究方面出现了这种分歧——你知道，我来自科学世界，就像前学术界的人一样——没有真正看到了这种连通性。如果我们一直追溯到雷达发明之时，事情崩溃的原因就在于“嗯，它还不完全存在；它不存在；它不存在；它不存在”。哦，不太好用。”这是第一部分。</p><p>然后，第二个层次是看到，嗯，这是否会尽可能地真正对我们的内部用户产生影响——因为这非常重要——对于集团内的许多企业来说，这实际上是B2B，就像电力行业一样，本质上我们提供电力和批发[电力]？因此，就预测性资产维护而言，我们的内部用户至关重要。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这真是太棒了。我的意思是，你所说的在很多层面上都很鼓舞人心。一是，让你的想象力成为极限，对吧，因为“某件事可以做得更好、更有效吗？”这个问题。你能看到拐角处吗？”那么，是的，有数据。这是您给出的所有这些例子中固有的一件事。</p><p>你从大多数人认为非常先进和有趣的事情开始，我们的嘉宾一直在谈论这些：个性化、欺诈、网络。所有这些都非常重要。然后你就去水泥了。然后你就去养猪了。然后你谈到了人类和人工智能……</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这也很关键。我只是觉得这非常非常充满活力。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>嗯，这是人类和人工智能之间的联系。我认为有两件事必须齐头并进——必须。虽然这种情况未来可能会在某种程度上发生变化——我的意思是，谁知道即将发生什么？事情变化如此之快。但我将是第一个承认这一点的人：当我为监管机构工作时，我确实意识到了将治理与创新相结合的重要性——令人惊讶，令人惊讶。我过去经常被问到这个问题，“哦，但是你不认为治理会抑制创新吗？它让我们窒息。”我认为，我强烈反对这种观点。</p><p>我认为它不仅不会扼杀它——它会带来更多、甚至更好的创新。从本质上讲，这只是简单地拥有常识。我很荣幸能够参与这个过程并提出 FEAT 原则。这就是新加坡金融管理局的<em>公平</em>、<em>道德</em>、<em>问责</em>和<em>透明度</em>。</p><p>我记得当它出来时——我们故意让它变得非常简单——我把它展示给我们的州长、我们的总经理，他就像是，“大卫，这不是常识吗？”我只是笑了笑，然后说：“好吧，不；”即使是常识也必须......它并不总是那么常见。必须写下来。”但这很关键。那是第一。</p><p>第二，你提到的是，是的，虽然人工智能和数据可以做看似神奇的事情，但至关重要的是，这种与我们人类的结合以及我们<em>如何</em>使用它从一开始就被考虑在内。即使是现在，显然每个人都在谈论 ChatGPT，但请记住：它训练的所有数据在某种程度上都来自<em>我们</em>。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>是的。你不能把人类从循环中剔除，因为一段时间后，他们就会失去人类的本质。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>但我们有这样的例子。我的意思是，在某些地方这是可以的。我的意思是，我猜你们俩都不知道如何通过星星导航，除非，谢尔文，你有一些我还没有学会的技巧。我的意思是，大多数人不开手动变速箱；他们驾驶的是手动变速箱。这似乎是一项技能……好吧，也许我们这里有一两个人会这样做。但关键是，我们不必保留所有可能的技能。我们只需要了解我们应该坚持哪些。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>这正是你所说的：只是一些，而不是全部。但有时你会发现你看到了这样的趋势，“哦，看看它能做什么。<em>一切都</em>变得自动化。”我记得，如果我早年担任顾问 - 你知道，我曾经是一名从事人工智能的顾问 - 你会发现很多时候，潜在客户和与你交谈过的人，即使他们没有说明确地说，他们想要实现的目标是，“哦，用人工智能自动完成所有事情。”</p><p>你需要有这种自然的倾向，说：“好吧，如果它符合上下文，如果它有意义。”就像你说的，也许我想学习星空导航，因为我对它感兴趣。我想学习占星学或天体物理学或诸如此类的知识。伟大的。但你看，它现在变成了一些人开始关注的小众话题。普通公众不需要知道如何去做。但我们需要能够确定那个决策点，而不是陷入“不，现在一切，人工智能盛行”的情况。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>嗯，我的意思是，你所说的是，正在进行的对话是有价值的。持续的挑战是有价值的。我的意思是，每次对话时，即使是在苏格拉底时代，对话也是对话的提升。你正确地指出，当你说人工智能是一切的那一刻，你就没有充分发挥人工智能的作用，那么你肯定也没有充分发挥人类的潜力。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>好吧，你正在失去一个潜在的答案。让我举两个例子。在金融领域，我们有菲律宾联合银行等。虽然人工智能治理监管<em>还不</em>是一项要求，比方说，在菲律宾，我们已经设立了一个工作组，这是一个有趣的人员组合，包括风险官、法律人员、合规人员，然后还有营销人员、客户参与度、体验。所发生的情况是，虽然仍然有模型验证等传统过程，但从统计、数学、数据的角度来看，模型已在该工作组中呈现给我们进行辩论。因为一个模型可能会通过所有的统计测试，但如果这个模型出了问题——即使是 10% 或 5%——就会产生重大的声誉风险，或者对消费者产生潜在的影响。这场争论很重要，因为如果你只是从统计数据来看，即使是一个潜在的自动化流程，你也会错过它。</p><p>现在，有趣的是——我诚实地告诉你，到目前为止，可能十分之八的解决方案——不是数据，不是人工智能。很多时候，解决问题的关键在于流程，即人。这让我们实际上变得更加明智和理解，“好吧，我们如何使用它，我们如何参与它？我们什么时候允许”——山姆，就你的观点而言——“自动化？”当我们说“不”时，我在一定程度上保留否决权。这就是一个例子。</p><p>另一个是如果我回到我的水泥[例子]，事实上，我们从一开始就非常有意地这样做，因为我们不想让我们的同事和化学工程师认为，“哦，太棒了。你为什么需要我？你只需要把整个事情自动化就可以了。”</p><p>不。重点是，我们绝对需要它们，因为可能有我们没有考虑过的新型混合物。你仍然需要进行这样的实验。整个目标是提供信息。</p><p>它带来的结果是效率。如果我再次向另一个人挥手——当 ChatGPT 出现时，一些论坛立即问我，“这是什么意思？”我的本能反应是，我没有对解放进行冗长的解释，而是回答说：“这意味着我们每个人都可以拥有 10 个人的生产力。”</p><p>这就是这些东西的含义，这就是联系、对话、整合、增强的含义——我们现在有能力提高生产力，无论“生产力”在这种情况下意味着什么。对于某些人来说，他们可能会说，“我只想工作两个小时，但[看起来]好像我工作了一整天。”有些人可能会说：“我想工作一整天。” ……可能会有所不同。但这就是它的意义，因为现在我们能够获取所有这些数据。</p><p>我相信你们中有些人还记得，早在 2000 年，网上就有这样的表情包：“从互联网上获取信息就像从消防水龙带里喝水一样。”这仍然是事实。我们被信息和数据淹没，但这就像将其提炼成与我相关、可用的东西，我可以用它做一些事情并从本质上获得收益。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为从这次谈话中可以得出一件事——谢尔文使用了<em>“苏格拉底式”</em>这个词，而大卫，你使用了<em>“对话”</em>这个词。这样做的好处是它消除了我在很多机器学习中看到的傲慢态度。机器学习似乎是关于人类教导机器。所以这就是“我们知道一切。我们让机器模仿我们，如果它们这样做了，它们就通过了图灵测试，是的，一切都是黄金。”但随后你会遇到阻力，你会说：“哦，不。机器可以教<em>给我们</em>以前从未了解过的东西。”好吧，这只是改变了方向。它仍然具有相同的方向性傲慢，但你们所谈论的事情更多地[围绕]苏格拉底和对话。</p><p>当你思考这个群体可以共同组成什么时，舍文和我从去年的研究中得到了一些结果，该结果表明大约 60% 的人正在将人工智能视为同事。我觉得这是一种关系，因为在两者之间，是的，你会发现一些可能有人不会尝试的新化合物。我不知道化学工程中福斯伯里失败的等价物是什么。你还记得福斯伯里的失败吗？他学会了一种不同的跳过高栏的方法，然后突然其他人都采用了这种技术？这种想法似乎可以从这种方法中产生。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>您提出这个问题实际上非常有趣。我的意思是，我很想说，“哦，是的，我们一开始就有这一切的打算，”但我会很诚实地说，我认为这更多的是一个并非完全有意为之的美好结果在某个时间点。</p><p>但我想回到那个 FEAT 原则。其中一项原则引起了很多讨论——我的意思是<em>很多</em>讨论——我们在所有人中发表了一份声明，表示我们应该让人工智能至少遵循与人类决策相同的标准。因此，基于人工智能的决策至少应遵循与基于人类的决策相同的标准。辩论非常激烈，[人们]说，“哦，不，我们应该把它提高到一个更高的水平”，等等。</p><p>但该原则的意图是，如果您现在正在使用……那么让我再次回到金融[示例]：贷款拨备。如果[你]使用人工智能算法并且你发现“哦，我们在歧视”，好吧，是的，绝对，这是需要解决、审查和纠正的问题。但请把你的马放在那里。退后一步。将人工智能排除在外。在人工智能出现之前你有歧视吗？这确实是一个问题，因为……我记得我与许多监管机构进行了长时间的辩论。也许辩论这个词用得不恰当：与许多监管机构<em>进行讨论</em>。我实际上有点反对监管人工智能，我会解释我的意思。</p><p>我并不反对监管。但当他们说“监管人工智能”时，我有点防御性。我说，“我担心的是，我们会说，‘好吧，既然人工智能现在向我展示了所有我不想知道的东西，那么我就不会使用人工智能。我们将回到之前的相同程序，猜猜看，这是同样的问题。你只是没有注意到它，因为这些信息、知识没有浮出水面。”</p><p>所以，我一直争论的是，是的，监管必须发挥作用。是的，在某些情况下，人工智能可能需要更严格的审查。但监管仍以结果为准。该规定仍然是事实，例如，这是一个歧视案件。你不应该歧视；无论您使用的是基于人类的流程还是基于人工智能的流程，这都不是重点。但我只是想强调这一点，萨姆，因为它确实可以追溯到你所说的，它现在正在教<em>给我们</em>一些我们可能有时有意识地无知，有时无意中没有意识到的东西。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>大卫，请告诉我们您的背景。你是怎么走到现在这个位置的？</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同（David Hardoon）：</strong>如果我一路回滚到最开始，我自己会笑着再说一遍，我是怎么走到现在这个位置的？拘留。我就是这样来到这里的。</p><p>我一定是，什么，14、15、16岁，我因为拘留而被送到图书馆。而且，你知道，如果你在图书馆，你就没有更好的事情可做。我拿起一本关于 Prolog 的书。不要问我为什么，在我能找到的所有书籍中，我选择了一本关于 Prolog 的书。这确实是在了解整个世界之前，我想在这种情况下，这将是基于专家的系统。我开始阅读，但我就是爱不释手。这引发了我们如何更好地获取知识的探索？我们怎样才能更好地学习呢？</p><p>这显然导致了对神经网络、人工智能的更多了解。事实上，我是最早获得人工智能计算机科学学位的两名学生之一。从这个角度来看，它确实是全新的。</p><p>我的博士学位论文是关于语义模型的，顾名思义，就是知识、有效和信息的表示和封装； [它]是关于学习音乐模式/音乐，或者从大脑模式生成音乐。如果你以这种方式思考的话，整个想法本质上是为那些不能坐在钢琴前弹奏但具有完全认知能力的人提供基于专家的系统知识。</p><p>这就是我来到这里的原因。我知道这是一次非常奇怪的旅程。但是，是的，我需要感谢我的识字老师：谢谢你把我送进拘留所。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>好的，我们有一个部分会问您一些简单的问题。在人工智能方面，您最自豪的是什么？你做过什么让你最自豪的事情？</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>从哪里开始？我最自豪的是我们能够从学术界毕业到工业界的方式——我的字面意思是这样。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>人工智能让您担心的是什么？你今天提到了一些担忧。但你担心什么？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>令我担心的是，我认为我们并没有完全欣赏我们正在创造的东西。我认为我们需要集中精力认识到我们正在创造的东西以及我们正在播种的可能性，无论好坏。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动是什么？</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong> SUP：站立划桨。在水面上，只是划桨离开。它非常舒缓。对于那些没有尝试过的人来说，这实际上是一种非凡的锻炼。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我已经尝试过了，但我错过了单口喜剧部分。我可以划桨，但站立似乎会带来麻烦。您在拘留期间第一个想要从事的职业是什么？你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>我想成为一名天体物理学家。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>未来您对人工智能最大的愿望是什么？您希望我们能从中得到什么？</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>我不知道。自我实现？我希望我们更多地了解自己。它已经赋予了我们能力。我的意思是，例如，我有阅读障碍。感谢老天有自动拼写检查器！</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>好的，谢谢您抽出时间。我想你提到的有很多。我想我们甚至可以回到 100 年前的食物例子。我们的食品清洁度很差[问题]，但现在我们拥有了值得信赖的供应链。也许我们可以用数据建立同样类型的供应链。感谢您今天抽出时间与我们交谈。这是我的荣幸。</p><p><strong>大卫·哈同：</strong>谢谢山姆、谢尔文。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>是的。谢谢。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon：</strong>也许，如果我可以添加另一条注释，我认为这确实是关键的事情：这是人工智能<em>信任</em>。这是关于信任。非常感谢。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>感谢您的聆听。下次，我和 Shervin 与 Airbnb 信托产品和运营主管 Naba Banerjee 讨论该旅行平台如何利用人工智能和机器学习来让旅行体验变得更安全。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulate-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>在人工智能不断发展的背景下，人性化沟通以加强关系</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-grinding-ai- humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-grinding-ai- humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cole Clark. <p>科尔·克拉克 (Cole Clark) 是<a href="https://www.amygdalaunch.com/">AmygdaLaunch</a>的总裁。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[AI entered a new era when artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT became available to the public this year. These technologies are taking over more and more aspects of business as they seep into the collective consciousness. As Vox put it, generative AI is “suddenly everywhere,” and it’s poised to profoundly change daily life within organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Clark-Handwritten-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>随着 ChatGPT 等人工智能工具今年向公众开放，人工智能进入了一个新时代。随着这些技术渗透到集体意识中，它们正在接管商业的越来越多的方面。正如 Vox 所说，生成式人工智能“ <a href="https://www.vox.com/recode/2023/1/5/23539055/generative-ai-chatgpt-stable-diffusion-lensa-dall-e">突然无处不在</a>”，并且它将在许多方面深刻改变组织内的日常生活，特别是在通信领域。</p><p>当人们收到短信、电子邮件或其他数字信息时，他们比以往任何时候都更有理由怀疑这些信息是否是真人所写。 ChatGPT 甚至被用来在 LinkedIn 上向个别高管编写<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/08/chatgpt-is-being-used-to-write-emails-big-companies-are-embracing-it.html">自定义消息</a>。作为回应，人们正在创建工具来帮助人们确定消息是否真的是<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90830518/tools-to-detect-ai-generated-text-chatgpt">由人写的</a>。其中一些工具是由使用技术生成此类文本的同一家公司制造的。但很少有人可能在短期内使用这些检测器，即使他们这样做，基于人工智能的文本生成器也会不断地工作，以智取检测器。</p><p></p><p>最终结果很明显：在数字通信方面，我们在未来一段时间内不太可能信任大多数“个人”数字消息。这就是为什么在努力建立真实的关系时，完全回避技术具有新的力量。</p><h3>手写信息呈现新价值</h3><p>如今，很少有人接听来自无法识别的电话号码的电话。高管们越来越意识到人工智能也被用来<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/11/why-chatgpt-ai-are-taking-over-the-cold-call-salesforce-leader.html">安排此类电话</a>，这会让他们感觉自己只是名单上的另一个名字。</p><p>为了与决策者建立联系，我最近尝试了一条不同的路线：我手写笔记给几位高管，然后将其邮寄给他们。其中一些引起了非常积极的个人反应和会议，甚至合同讨论。这些关系建立在<a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-susan-mcpherson-on-building-meaningful-relationships-in-business-and-in-life">有意义的基础</a>上，可以带来长期的业务增长。</p><p>一直有人喜欢手写商务笔记，但它从未具有如此重要的内涵——一个真正的人花时间写下个性化的信息，而不是选择一个更容易的选择。最近的一项研究表明，这一点的威力有多大：马里兰大学和韩国延世大学商学院的研究人员发现，“出示一张<a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/10949968221102306?journalCode=jnma">手写便条</a>对客户支出有积极而显着的影响”，并且“热情是关键发现。”</p><h3>人性化沟通</h3><p></p><p>类似的原则也适用于内部沟通。一些经理现在使用技术来进行员工识别等工作，并转向生成式人工智能来创建并向团队成员发送赞美信息。虽然这可能对不知所措和疲惫不堪的管理者有帮助，但它也会降低员工可能寻求的意义感和个性化。这就是为什么手写笔记可以成为管理者向员工（尤其是不在办公室面对面接受这种认可的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-create-belonging-for-remote-workers/">远程员工）</a>表达真诚谢意的有效方式。</p><p>手写笔记可能并不适合每个人——例如，如果某人的笔迹特别难以阅读。但还有其他方法可以实现个性化沟通，包括创建针对特定个人的视频或语音备忘录，甚至在电话无人接听时留下语音邮件。有些人在他们的日程安排中划出一个时间并说：“我将保留这两个小时的时间，希望你可能想聊天。在这段时间内随时伸出援手，我就会放弃我正在做的事情。”</p><p>关键是要始终寻找在沟通中强调人性的方法。我们做得越多，人工智能在我们的人际关系中的闯入就越少，而且它们也会变得更加真实和有价值。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-grinding-ai- humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>每周工作四天：如何让它在您的组织中发挥作用</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Barnes. <p>安德鲁·巴恩斯 (Andrew Barnes) 是新西兰最大的企业信托公司 Perpetual Guardian 的创始人。他也是 4 Day Week Global 的联合创始人，也是<cite>《The 4 Day Week》</cite> （Piatkus，2020）一书的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[As cofounder of 4 Day Week Global, Andrew Barnes has a front-row seat to the world’s largest experiment on the effects of scaling back the workweek. It started with Barnes’s own New Zealand company, Perpetual Guardian, when he wondered whether his staff members could do their jobs better if they worked the equivalent of four [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA01_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>作为 4 Day Week Global 的联合创始人，安德鲁·巴恩斯 (Andrew Barnes) 参与了全球规模最大的实验，该实验旨在探讨减少每周工作时间的影响。</p><p>它始于巴恩斯自己的新西兰公司 Perpetual Guardian，当时他想知道如果他的员工工作四天而不是五天，是否可以更好地完成工作。他知道，保持相同的产出、客户服务和盈利能力至关重要。他提出了所谓的 100-80-100 规则：“只要我们获得 100% 的产出，我们就在 80% 的时间内支付 100% 的收入。”</p><p>这次审判成为了全球头条新闻——“当人数超过 14,000 人时，我们就不再统计了”——巴恩斯收到了大量的咨询请求。他创办了一个非营利组织，并开始帮助公司进行自己的试点，提供虚拟研讨会、指导他人和交流机会。目前，研究结果包括来自 91 家公司和 3,500 名员工的数据，并已由学术团队进行了分析。</p><p></p><p>这些结果普遍是积极的。 “不仅 90% 以上的员工表示他们喜欢每周工作四天——而且事实上，他们真的不想回去——而且公司还看到了生产力方面的实质性好处，”巴恩斯说。</p><p></p><p>巴恩斯在 2023 年 5 月举办的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>上谈论了这些实验及其发现。他无法在活动期间回答与会者提出的所有问题，因此他在下面回答了其中一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>是否有任何研究比较每周工作四天与减少五天工作（例如每天工作六小时）？结果是否表明四天是更好的方法？</h6><p>我们将两者视为每周四天！标题诱饵是“每周工作四天”，但实际上，我们谈论的是<em>减少工作时间</em>——100-80-100 规则。关键是员工可以获得对<em>他们</em>来说很重要的休假时间。在我的公司，有些人休一整天假，另一些人休两天半假，还有一些人（通常是工作父母）每周压缩工作五天。这个时间表有助于解决儿童保育问题，而这一问题单靠一天的休息是无法解决的。</p><p></p><h6>当涉及生产力与收入等公司业绩时，您如何从员工和团队的角度衡量每周四天工作的成功？</h6><p>显然，更容易看出公司业绩（例如盈利能力和收入）是否有所改善。我们经常发现人们问我们如何衡量员工的生产力。当然，这提出了<em>目前</em>如何衡量生产率的问题。很多时候，人们很快就会发现，许多组织都用时间来衡量生产力。</p><p>我们计划的一部分是帮助组织制定其他生产力衡量标准，以便更清楚地评估改进情况。其中一个关键部分是帮助员工识别一天中效率低下的部分。根据定义，简单地消除非生产性活动就会增加生产性活动。</p><h6>我发现战术工作之外的大部分时间都是私人对话和建立关系。当您改为每周工作四天时，这些事情会减少吗？</h6><p>不会。事实上，有证据表明这些情况有所改善。通过结合安静时间（深度工作）、更少和更短的会议以及更好的社交设施（在我们的例子中，更好的员工休息区）等政策，我们发现员工凝聚力和团队建设实际上得到了提高。通过强调工作人员需要共同努力，让每个人都能实现减少工作时间的目标，通常会有更多的时间进行这些互动，而不是更少。</p><h6>盖洛普 2020 年美国面板数据显示，每周工作四天的员工比每周工作五六天的员工幸福感更高。然而，盖洛普的数据还显示，工作天数较少的人中<a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/358346/gallup-workplace-insights-learned-2021.aspx">主动脱离工作的比例有所上升</a>。盖洛普表示，那些已经感觉与雇主脱节的员工可能会与雇主疏远得更远。您建议公司采取什么措施来解决这个问题？</h6><p>在许多员工在家工作并因此与通常的工作场所文化分离的社会背景下，减少工作时间的影响实际上很小。还有必要区分每周工作四天的旧模式（只有少数人工作四天，大多数人工作五天，前者的工资往往较低）和新模式，即每个人都减少工作时间不减薪。参与我们试验的公司报告称，参与度分数显着提高。就我们自己的公司而言，分数提高了 40%，达到研究人员所说的他们在新西兰见过的最高水平。</p><h6>您认为每周四天工作制对从事不同工作的人们（例如软件开发人员、创意工作者与销售人员）的影响有何差异？</h6><p>显然，工作的实际完成方式存在实际差异，但在我们的各种试验中，对各公司员工的影响似乎是一致的。员工表示工作效率更高、休息更充分、压力更小、更快乐。我的论点是，更健康、更快乐、休息得更多的员工生产力更高。谁曾想到！</p><h6>公司为实行四天工作周做了哪些培训和准备？</h6><p>我们鼓励组织在开始为期六个月的试用之前花几个月的时间进行计划和准备。准备和试验都允许组织灵活调整流程，找出适合他们的方法。大部分效率和改进来自于赋予员工权力并创造一种文化，使个人认识到他们必须共同努力以减少浪费的时间。因此，在我自己的组织和许多其他组织中，培训是有限的，而且基本上没有必要。</p><h6>在实施减少工作周时，如何建立员工信任以成功实现既定目标？</h6><p>简而言之，如果在实施四天工作周之前不存在信任，那么实施就不可能成功。</p><h6>我们实行 24 小时运营。您是否在此类组织中看到过这样做，这对员工数量有什么影响？不需要增加员工数量吗？</h6><p>从许多方面来说，将每周工作四天的工作方式引入到 7 天 24 小时的工作方式中会更容易，因为该组织已经在实行轮班模式。每周工作时间减少只需要重新配置轮班即可。请记住，我们的论点是生产力实际上会提高，因此在某些操作中，每个班次可以配备更少的员工。</p><p>另外，在医疗机构等人员密集的组织中，可能需要招聘更多的员工。不过，这里的节省来自于减少招聘时间和人员流动、减少病假（根据试验数据，减少 67%）以及减少对生产力的影响，以及降低昂贵的临时员工的成本。证据还表明结果有所改善。</p><h6>您是否与咨询行业的客户做过这项工作？你在那里取得了哪些成功？计费时间受到怎样的影响？</h6><p>是的。公关公司、律师事务所和咨询公司都已改为每周工作四天。计费工时经常被认为是一种障碍，但它只是一种分配成本的机制。客户根据价值和结果付费。如果您现在可以在四天模型下更快地完成工作，只需调整成本分配单位即可。客户不在乎。一个简单的例子：两个顾问完成了一件相同的工作。一个需要一个小时，一个需要半小时。为什么客户要为前者支付两倍的费用？实际上，计费时间会进行调整，以使账单与客户将支付的金额保持一致。</p><p></p><h6>在转为每周工作四天时，您遇到了哪些障碍？</h6><p>主要的障碍是，我的领导团队成员即使不是敌对的，也是高度怀疑的，而我的董事会普遍讨厌它。在这一过程中发挥领导作用并帮助他们言行一致对于项目的成功至关重要。我在<a href="https://www.4dayweek.com/">4dayweek.com</a>网站和我的书<cite>《The 4 Day Week》</cite>中列出了常见的障碍。</p><h6>您能提供公司使用的政策样本吗？</h6><p> 4dayweek.com 网站提供了大量有用的材料，包括研究报告和白皮书。该白皮书包括我们在 Perpetual Guardian 推出的用于实施缩短的时间表的政策。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>沟通是积极员工关系的核心</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Laker. <p>Ben Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) 是雷丁大学亨利商学院的领导学教授，也是<cite>《Too Proud to Lead: How Hubris Can Destroy effective Leadership and What to Do About It》</cite> （Bloomsbury，2021 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment. Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Laker_Communication-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>在当今竞争激烈的就业市场中，公司不仅要注重寻找最佳候选人，还要注重与他们建立积极的关系，从招聘流程的第一步开始，一直到就业的每个阶段。</p><p>沟通是成功建立这些联系的关键。领导者如何与未来和现任员工沟通可以极大地影响其组织作为人们愿意工作的地方的声誉。毕竟，拥有一种包含透明和开放沟通的文化对于建立信任和忠诚度至关重要。</p><p></p><h3>沟通技巧在招聘中的重要性</h3><p>研究表明，口头和书面<a href="https://newmanu.edu/top-5-skills-employers-look-for">沟通技巧</a>是潜在新员工最抢手的五项品质之一：雇主希望员工能够有效地表达自己的想法、观点和知识。</p><p>沟通能力强的员工能够清晰地表达自己的想法和情感，使他们在工作中更有效率。此外，他们能够通过认真倾听、提供准确反馈和解决冲突的能力，更好地管理与客户或同事之间具有挑战性的对话或谈判。</p><p>良好的沟通技巧还可以培养更好的公司文化：当员工能够有效地相互沟通时，他们会建立更牢固的联系。这不仅创造了一个有凝聚力和富有成效的工作环境，而且还提高了他们对组织的忠诚度。</p><p></p><p>招聘经理应筛选简历的清晰简洁的写作能力，并注意候选人在面试中的说话方式，以评估他们的沟通技巧。如果合适，他们应该在面试前索取书面作品样本，以评估候选人的写作能力。能够有效地以书面形式表达自己的资历和技能的候选人可能能够在面试过程中更好地以口头方式表达出来。</p><p></p><h3>招聘流程：明确的期望和公开的对话</h3><p>招聘过程中涉及的所有各方在传达信息时都需要清晰、简洁。招聘经理在与潜在候选人交谈时必须明确界定期望、角色和责任：一项研究发现，48% 提前离职的员工是因为雇主的<a href="https://www.hrdive.com/news/study-48-of-workers-have-left-a-job-because-it-didnt-meet-expectations/551179/">期望不明确</a>。</p><p>在招聘过程中与候选人建立公开对话对于建立信任和深入了解他们的沟通方式至关重要。通过结合使用开放式问题、角色扮演场景和注重沟通的练习，雇主可以更好地了解每位候选人的工作方法，并为牢固的工作关系奠定基础。</p><p>一旦新员工入职，提供有关其沟通技巧的反馈可以帮助他们了解自己在哪些方面已经做得很好以及哪些方面可以改进。</p><h3>应对裁员：透明度、同理心和合规性</h3><p>在经济衰退和裁员的时代，公司如何处理裁员可能对其声誉和员工士气产生深远影响。为了在裁员期间与员工保持积极的关系，雇主应优先考虑清晰、诚实和及时的沟通。这意味着尽可能提前向所有员工发出通知，解释决定背后的理由，并向受影响的员工提供支持，例如职业咨询、简历准备和求职帮助。通过尊重和同情员工，公司可以最大限度地减少负面影响并保持良好的声誉。</p><p>此外，组织必须遵守有关裁员的法律，以确保员工得到公平待遇并避免法律后果。雇主应了解其州和地方法律，以确保满足最低通知要求和其他法规。以 Bed Bath &amp; Beyond 为例，该公司最初决定绕过<a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bed-bath-beyond-to-pay-out-severance-to-1300-workers-after-initially-bypassing-law/ar-AA1aKgBG">遣散费法律</a>导致了诉讼，从而为一家最近宣布破产的公司带来了更多负面宣传，随后又撤销了该决定。</p><h3>创造开放沟通的文化</h3><p></p><p>与候选人和员工建立积极关系的关键在于营造开放沟通的文化。这意味着无论处于哪个就业阶段，都重视透明度、诚实和同理心。公司还应鼓励组织各层级之间的公开对话，为员工提供表达担忧和想法的机会。这有助于建立信任感，促进协作的工作环境，并最终为公司的整体成功做出贡献。</p><p>除了促进开放式沟通之外，雇主还应该投资培训和发展计划，帮助员工提高沟通技巧。这对个人有利，有助于营造更有效、更有凝聚力的工作环境，并最终为组织带来更大的成功，并在整体上创造更高效的工作环境。通过在员工生命周期的每个阶段优先考虑沟通，管理者可以培养积极的工作文化，让员工感到受到重视、支持并被赋予成功的权力。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>是时候面对学习的三大挑战了</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) 是伦敦商学院管理实践教授，也是咨询实践 HSM 的创始人。她的最新著作是<cite>《重新设计工作：如何转型您的组织并为每个人提供混合工作》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Virtual Teams]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Austin/theispot.com Most executives acknowledge that learning is crucial to the performance of their business. But at a recent research workshop that my team and I ran with executives from over 40 companies, it became clear that organizations’ traditional learning models are facing pressure from the emergence of new work models. The participants identified these [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023-0626_Gratton_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">迈克尔·奥斯汀/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>大多数高管承认学习对其业务绩效至关重要。但在我和我的团队与来自 40 多家公司的高管最近举办的一次研究研讨会上，我们发现组织的传统学习模式正面临着新工作模式出现的压力。参与者认为这三个学习挑战是最严峻的：</p><p> <strong>1.工作量增加，学习时间减少。</strong>我们研讨会上 88% 的高管选择工作压力作为他们面临的最大挑战之一。他们表示，许多员工，尤其是那些管理他人的员工，感觉近年来他们的工作量显着增加。一些人分享的敏感内部数据表明，在此期间，倦怠有所增加。工作量增加的最终结果是，员工不仅缺乏学习的空间，而且还感到有压力将工作任务置于学习活动之上。应对这一挑战需要领导者最大限度地利用任何可用学习时间的价值。</p><p></p><p> <strong>2.混合工作增加了学习的复杂性。</strong>三分之二 (66%) 的高管表示，员工工作地点和时间的灵活性是一个重要的挑战。高管们担心，员工在正式和非正式学习的重要时刻可能无法保持联系。经理们表示，他们发现为远程员工寻找发展机会变得更加困难，并且他们担心远程工作会对人们共享隐性知识的方式产生负面影响。事实上，研究表明 47% 的员工担心在家工作时<a href="https://newsroom.poly.com/English/press-releases/news-details/2021/Poly-Evolution-of-the-Workplace-Report-Highlights-Need-for-Work-Equity-and-Total-Meeting-Equality-for-Hybrid-Workers/">错过非正式学习机会</a>。应对这一挑战需要领导者在混合业务环境中制定稳健的学习策略。</p><p> <strong>3.劳动力市场趋紧带来技能短缺。</strong> 65% 的高管认为寻找具有专业技能的员工是一项重大挑战。我们采访的许多高管表示，他们的公司历来都在外部劳动力市场上寻找这些专业人才。然而，随着市场收紧，特别是对于难以找到的数字技能，重点已转移到提高内部员工的技能。重新培训一直被认为很重要，但现在变得至关重要。应对这一挑战需要领导者将业务战略与熟练执行的技能提升和再培训计划结合起来。</p><p>尽管这些都是严峻的挑战，但高管们也承认解决这些挑战是多么重要。技能短缺是原因之一，但成功的企业学习也具有重大的激励作用。</p><p>在当今动荡的劳动力市场中，员工会迅速从一份工作转向更有利的工作机会，学习未来有价值的新知识的机会是他们留下来的主要原因。事实上，研究表明，76% 的员工表示，如果能够从学习和发展支持中受益，他们会<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work-is-just-work">在工作岗位上呆更长时间</a>。</p><p>此外，面对对工作场所不平等现象日益增长的担忧，人们认为<a href="https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/files/5552_en.pdf">基于技能的学习</a>有助于显着减少不平等现象。对于那些不胸怀大志、没有大学学位或教育证书、或者历史上被排除在外的员工来说尤其如此。</p><p></p><h3>公司如何重新学习如何学习</h3><p>因此，这是一个悖论：当学习被视为许多公​​司业务战略的重要组成部分时，那些负责实施学习议程的人却描述了重大的艰苦战斗。</p><p>尽管如此，我还是看到管理者们所做的实验，他们通过尝试新的学习方式和新的学习方式来应对这种情况，这些方式可以为处于类似情况的其他人树立榜样。以下是他们解决三个基本问题的方法。</p><h4> 1.他们利用个性化来最大化学习时间的价值。</h4><p>确保学习的每一个小时都有意义的一种方法是使学习与学习者的具体需求紧密结合。这种个性化通常很难大规模提供。但虚拟和在线教学的实验开辟了个性化学习的途径。</p><p>一种方法是制定学习计划或途径。总部位于都柏林的 Matheson 律师事务所的学习团队提供 12 种学习途径（每年变化）供员工选择，例如客户体验或环境、社会和公司治理问题。每个途径都融合了参与核心项目和由主题专家员工提供的教程。一项重要的创新是律师和商业服务员工都可以使用这些途径。学习团队的一名成员告诉我，该方法旨在打破这些社区之间的传统孤岛，并将学习嵌入到工作的自然流程中。</p><p></p><p>其他组织已经通过使用人工智能驱动的职业诊断来完成个性化学习的任务。埃森哲开发了一款名为 Job Buddy 的人工智能工具，帮助员工根据自身、团队和外部劳动力市场的数据制定个人学习计划。该工具旨在使用机器学习算法根据个人当前的工作、技能和经验来建议职业道路和技能提升机会。在进行个人诊断后，学习平台提供了在线课程、研讨会和指导计划等资源。</p><h4> 2.他们倾向于混合体验。</h4><p>这场大流行增加了混合工作的流行，并为学习和工作一样灵活创造了条件。</p><p></p><p>在全球在线市场 Etsy，同伴学习始终是重中之重。 Etsy 战略和运营副总裁 Zofia Ciechowska 告诉我，学习被视为员工甚至供应商与社区分享知识、技能或工艺的机会。员工开设的课程涉及广泛的主题，包括如何乘坐东京地铁系统以及如何制作蜡烛等。种类繁多的课程反映了 Etsy 的文化和使命，即通过让人们展示自己的才能并相互教育来保持商业“人性化”。</p><p>至关重要的是，本着混合工作的精神，Etsy 的研讨会以面对面和在线形式进行。员工无论工作安排如何，都能够充分参与。这个丰富的基于社区的学习计划成功地推动了非正式联系，激发了好奇心，并提高了员工敬业度。</p><p>学习团队表示，看到双向学习流的好处（对于受教者和授课者来说）是令人着迷的。员工有机会展示自己的热情，并通过分享他们引以为豪的知识与同事互动。</p><h4> 3. 他们通过关注可转移技能来减少技能短缺。</h4><p>面对劳动力市场趋紧和技能短缺，最明显的学习策略是专注于对现有员工进行再培训，而不是招聘新员工。正如许多高管所分享的那样，挑战在于这是极其困难的，尤其是在规模上。</p><p>作为一家国际银行，汇丰银行正在不断变化，而重新培训对于实现其战略计划至关重要。该银行正在努力确保所有员工都具备职业发展所需的技能和知识，以便他们现在和未来都能取得成功。</p><p>该银行最近为想要从事财富服务职业的内部候选人推出了一项基于技能的发展计划。通过在三到九个月的时间里花费 20% 的工作时间，参与者能够识别、评估和发展他们在银行财富和私人银行服务业务中担任关系经理角色所需的可转移技能。</p><p></p><p> “这一开创性计划正在帮助我们为我们业务的一个非常重要的部分建立战略人才管道，”汇丰银行财富和个人银行及全球职能全球人力资源主管劳拉·鲍威尔(Laura Powell)表示。汇丰银行计划在今年晚些时候将该计划扩展到外部候选人。</p><p></p><p>在参加我们的学习研究研讨会的高管中，只有 2% 的人表示他们相信讲师主导的学习将是他们组织未来发展的优先事项。相反，39% 的人表示“在工作流程中”学习更为重要。</p><p>显而易见的是，虽然一些更传统的学习形式正在减少，但实验和新项目正在证明如何克服重大挑战。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何帮助患有多动症的员工应对远程工作的挑战</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maria Hamdani, Najma Hamdani, and Maitraye Das. <p>Maria Hamdani 博士是阿克伦大学商学院管理学教授。 Najma Hamdani 博士是一位在俄克拉荷马州和德克萨斯州执业的精神科医生。 Maitraye Das 博士是东北大学 Khoury 计算机科学学院和艺术、媒体与设计学院的助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Neurodiversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Editor’s note: In consultation with the authors, this article was updated June 26, 2023, to better reflect the views of the neurodiversity movement. Flexible work arrangements, such as hybrid and remote models, have become important for talent acquisition and retention in the post-pandemic world. As organizations refine their virtual work practices, it is important to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hamdani-ADHD-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p><em>编者注：经与作者协商，本文于 2023 年 6 月 26 日更新，以更好地反映神经多样性运动的观点。</em></p><p>灵活的工作安排，例如混合和远程模式，对于大流行后世界的人才获取和保留变得重要。随着组织完善其虚拟工作实践，重要的是要确保它们包容神经分歧的员工。注意力缺陷/多动障碍 (ADHD) 是最常见的神经发散病症之一。虽然一些患有多动症的人可能会发现远程工作非常适合他们的需求，并使他们能够更好地控制自己的工作环境，但其他人可能会发现远程工作带来了独特的挑战。远程工作通常缺乏具体的时间线索，并且可能会引入与面对面办公室环境不同的干扰和共享信息的方法，这对于一些患有多动症的人来说可能是一个挑战。如果这些挑战得不到有效管理，可能会导致一系列问题，例如倦怠、焦虑、生产力下降、缺乏动力，并最终导致辞职。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>经理可以与患有多动症的员工合作实施简单的策略，以更好地根据他们的需求定制远程工作。由于员工可能未被诊断或选择不透露他们的神经分歧状况，因此我们在下面建议的五种基于证据的干预措施可以帮助促进更好的远程工作实践，从而造福所有员工。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>但在我们更详细地讨论这些之前，让我们先简单讨论一下多动症。</p><p></p><h3>了解多动症</h3><p>ADHD 源于大脑区域的结构差异以及细胞和神经机制的变化，这些变化对目标导向行为的日常自我调节提出了挑战。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>因此，多动症患者的注意力、时间管理、工作记忆、反应抑制和奖励心理处理等执行功能的运作方式存在不同程度的差异。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>这些执行流程共同作用，帮助我们将更大的目标、愿景、知识和技能转化为生活各个方面（包括工作）的日常目标导向行动。一些患有多动症的人可能会发现他们的差异会扰乱这些以目标为导向的行动，即使他们拥有清晰的愿景、知识、技能和动机。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>虽然药物可以帮助调节注意力、抑制力和工作记忆，但涵盖五个日常行为维度的包容性工作实践和调整可以帮助释放潜力并为成功创造条件。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>成人多动症常常未被充分诊断，因为人们错误地认为这只是一种儿童时期的诊断，或者是所有儿童最终都会长大后摆脱的诊断。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>诊断不足的性别和种族差异会带来额外的并发症。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>未经诊断和治疗的多动症可能会导致继发性焦虑和抑郁，以及在个人和集体层面造成重大甚至有时是毁灭性的损失，包括生产力损失、医疗保健费用、失业、司法系统影响以及家庭成员的溢出成本。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>正确的多动症诊断和包容性工作实践可以降低这些成本，并使多动症患者能够过上更充实的工作和个人生活。</p><p></p><p> ADHD 的性别差异经常被忽视，这扩大了女性的诊断和治疗差距。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>男性被诊断为多动症的可能性是女性的三倍，而且他们通常在更年轻的时候被诊断出来。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>许多早期教育工作者错误地认为多动症主要是针对男孩的诊断，因此对女孩的诊断不足。男性通常表现出多动症和问题的外在表现（例如课堂混乱或与同龄人打架），而女性通常将注意力不集中的症状内化，表现出低自尊、焦虑和抑郁。这使得女性的检测和转诊更具挑战性，她们可能被误诊为焦虑或抑郁，而不是多动症。在工作场所，患有注意力缺陷多动症的女性可能会感到不知所措和得不到支持，随之而来的自卑和对截止日期或项目细节的焦虑，或担心犯错误，可能会导致生产力下降、绩效下降和错失职业机会。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>多动症资源用于更好地理解</h4><ul><li>美国国家心理健康研究所：“<a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/adhd-what-you-need-to-know">成人注意力缺陷/多动症：您需要了解的内容</a>”</li><li>患有注意力缺陷/多动症的儿童和成人：“<a href="https://chadd.org/for-adults/diagnosis-of-adhd-in-adults/">成人多动症的诊断</a>”</li><li>疾病控制和预防中心：“<a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/adhd/diagnosis.html">多动症的症状和诊断</a>”</li><li> Russell A. Barkley 和 Christine M. Benton： <cite><a href="https://www.guilford.com/books/Taking-Charge-of-Adult-ADHD/Russell-Barkley/9781462546855">掌控成人多动症：在工作、家庭和人际关系中取得成功的行之有效的策略</a></cite></li></ul></article></aside></div><h3>实施包容性虚拟工作实践</h3><p>以下包容性虚拟工作实践使用简单的工具和可行的管理策略来创建一个工作环境，让员工能够坚持做他们已经知道如何做的事情。围绕这些建议调整虚拟工作实践可以提高所有员工的生产力。也就是说，神经分歧的员工通常知道什么条件最有利于他们的工作效率，并且应该就影响他们的工作实践的改变进行咨询。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>提高生产力的包容性虚拟工作实践</h4><p class="caption">在远程工作环境中，领导者可以采用这些方法来提高所有员工的工作效率，无论他们是否被诊断出患有多动症。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023-06-22_Hamdani_Figure.png" alt="提高生产力的包容性虚拟工作实践"><br /></article></aside></div><p></p><h4> 1. 时间管理和计划</h4><p>虽然患有注意力缺陷多动症的人可以有效地制定一个大目标或愿景，但他们中的一些人可能会在日常细节中挣扎，这在很大程度上是由于<em>时间盲目性</em>，这是一种对时间的扭曲认知。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a>这可能会导致难以及时组织活动来完成日常任务和满足需求，以及拖延、错过最后期限、忘记和未完成的任务以及多任务处理困难。在远程工作模式中，时间管理尤其具有挑战性，因为缺乏外部时间线索（例如开车上班或午休时间），并且这些环境中的日常监督和问责制较弱。</p><p>为了支持计划和时间管理，管理者应该使用易于访问的日常计划工具，结合他们的报告，将大目标转化为日常的、可操作的部分。他们还可以创建每日问责系统，例如同行签到或每日进度图表。使用有形的时间标记来标记时间的流逝，例如在家庭办公桌上放一个时钟，安排每日提醒来开始一项任务，以及设置计时器来完成任务，然后休息，也有帮助。只要有可能，管理者就应该考虑延长最后期限，以解决时间感知方面的困难。</p><p>与虚拟团队合作时，经理应平衡会议安排和生产力期望。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>仔细考虑每周需要举行多少次团队会议，并在可能的情况下使用异步通信来帮助员工在他们喜欢的时间执行分配的任务。实施一种混合模式，让人们有时去办公室参加会议，其他时间留在家里（或在无干扰的办公空间）专注工作，这可能是平衡生产力与会议安排的可行选择。</p><h4> 2. 心理组织和工作记忆</h4><p>由于工作记忆的差异，一些患有注意力缺陷多动症的成年人可能会受益于使用外部工具进行简单的计算，在解决问题时牢记多条信息，在沟通时整理思绪，并记得回电话或赴约。为了支持心理组织，鼓励使用外部工具将重要信息带入视野，例如每日清单、便利贴、书面说明、颜色编码的视觉提示和清晰可见的截止日期。</p><p>由于信息共享的速度和数量，远程工作可能会造成精神负担，并让人感到不知所措。必须在一天内参加多个虚拟会议（其中可以包含视频、音频、文本聊天和文件共享的组合）可能特别困难，特别是对于神经分歧的员工而言。</p><p>与其营造一种每个人都争夺发言机会的竞争氛围，不如考虑如何使虚拟会议更加包容和包容。例如，会议组织者可以正式制定轮流例程，让人们在发言前有时间整理思绪；安排提问和回答的暂停时间；并关闭大型群体的聊天功能，以尽量减少分散注意力的串扰。提前分享材料并在事后分发笔记、录音和文字记录对于那些发现很难在记笔记的同时注意对话的人特别有帮助。</p><h4> 3.长期任务的自我激励</h4><p>某些患有注意力缺陷多动症的人可能会发现，在没有立即奖励的情况下，在漫长的任务中很难保持积极性和专注力。管理者可以鼓励这些员工将较大的任务分解为较小的步骤，并设定最小的期限和奖励。例如，设定 30 分钟或一小时的目标，并用小奖励来庆祝每一项成就，例如一杯咖啡或到外面散步。为这些休息时间设置计时器以返回工作非常重要； <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-managers-can-help-workers-tackle-digital-distractions/">番茄工作法</a>可以作为一个有用的模型。</p><p>为了对抗“Zoom 疲劳”，在连续会议之间留出过渡时间，并在较长的会议期间提供休息时间以调节注意力。这种方法将有助于防止员工走神，并帮助他们补充精神能量。</p><h4> 4.抑制冲动</h4><p>患有多动症的人可能难以控制冲动，导致他们做出不恰当的反应、做出冲动的评论、打断别人、说话过多、情绪反应、等待困难或不能迅速识别和纠正错误。在社交线索有限的偏远环境中，这些挑战可能更加突出。</p><p>采用辅导和反馈模式可以提高员工对冲动行为的自我意识。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a>建立融洽关系的做法，例如使用工作方式偏好调查，可以帮助管理者找到提高生产力并最大程度地减少神经分歧员工的挫败感的方法。 <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a>记住要富有同情心，给予员工恩典；走神或说话不按顺序等行为并不是由于懒惰或恶意，而是源于信息处理方式的差异。</p><p></p><p>考虑在显眼的位置张贴最佳实践指南，以提供清晰的行动框架。同样，纳入数字<a href=" https://chadd.org/adhd-news/adhd-news-adults/could-a-body-double-help-you-increase-your-productivity/">身体加倍</a>等生产力策略，员工可以通过虚拟协同办公应用程序（例如 Flown 或 Focusmate）与其他人一起工作来完成他们觉得令人沮丧的任务，以帮助保持对手头任务的专注。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>此外，在日常生活中鼓励定期体育锻炼和平静练习对于帮助人们补充自我控制和抑制冲动所需的精神资源至关重要。</p><h4> 5.注意力、集中力和焦点</h4><p>远程工作充满<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-managers-can-help-workers-tackle-digital-distractions/">干扰</a>，需要特殊考虑才能提高注意力。为了增强注意力并减少无聊，可以考虑提供可调节的桌子、膝椅、摇椅和活动座椅。安排休息时间可以帮助人们避免走神，并且当他们在办公室时，提供安静的空间以尽量减少干扰。考虑提供辅助技术来帮助完成任务，例如听写工具、录音软件和降噪耳机，这可以帮助所有员工在远程和混合环境中提高工作效率。</p><p></p><p>我们的研究发现了其他策略，可以帮助减少虚拟工作空间中的干扰。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a>让与会者使用统一或模糊的背景有助于最大限度地减少背景噪音并减少视觉触发。为员工提供关闭摄像头的选项（至少在会议的某些部分）可能会对那些可能过度担心自己的面部表情或因自己的面部表情而分心的人有所帮助。经理们还应该注意在线会议期间提供的大量信息，并且应该允许员工要求澄清，以便在分散注意力后重新集中注意力。</p><p></p><p>多动症会影响人们在生活的许多方面的表现能力，包括在线工作环境。患有诊断的个人有不同的需求，从不需要任何便利到需要合理的个性化便利。诊断中的性别和种族差异、获得护理的障碍以及耻辱加剧了多动症对个人和职业领域整体福祉的成本。通过采用包容性工作实践，组织可以更好地支持和利用多元化劳动力的人才，否则这些人才可能会被边缘化和未得到充分利用。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>专注于培养员工队伍的技能</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aneesh Raman and Elyse Rosenblum. <p>Aneesh Raman 是 LinkedIn 副总裁兼机会项目负责人。 <a href="https://gradsoflife.org/team-members/elyse-rosenblum/">Elyse Rosenblum</a>是 Grads of Life 的创始人兼董事总经理。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[As the threat of an economic downturn looms, we are entering the fourth consecutive year of uncertainty and rapid change. Three years ago, a global pandemic upended supply chains, and quarantines transformed how we work. Months later, a racial justice reckoning compelled businesses to make unprecedented commitments to building inclusive organizations. Sustained remote work again [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Raman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>随着经济衰退的威胁迫在眉睫，我们正在进入不确定性和快速变化的连续第四年。三年前，一场全球大流行颠覆了供应链，隔离改变了我们的工作方式。几个月后，种族正义的清算迫使企业做出前所未有的承诺，<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/inclusive-hiring-to-build-better-teams-period/">建立包容性组织</a>。持续的远程工作再次挑战了工作场所的现状，并在某些情况下成为了无障碍的工具。持续紧张的劳动力市场迫使企业重新考虑并调整其吸引顶尖人才的努力。现在，人工智能的进步将重塑每个行业几乎所有工作所需的技能组合。</p><p>所有这些变化使人力资源成为高管对话的中心，雇主对如何发现、培养和发展人才有了不同的思考。很快，技能就开始主导对话。从 2021 年 10 月到 2022 年 10 月，LinkedIn 网络平台上提到技能优先相关主题的帖子平均数量大约增加了一倍。雇主正在努力将技能置于其人才战略的中心——从招聘到晋升——这一点可以证明<a href="http://www.oneten.org/">OneTen</a>和<a href="https://www.businessroundtable.org/workforceskills">商业圆桌会议</a>等团体。由于许多商界普遍谈论可能出现的经济衰退，一个关键问题悬而未决：雇主如何保持对技能优先方法不断增长的投资，以最大限度地提高工人和企业的投资回报？</p><p></p><p> LinkedIn 的新数据为加倍努力以技能为先提供了令人信服的案例。 《 <a href="https://learning.linkedin.com/resources/workplace-learning-report">2023 年职场学习报告》</a>显示，Z 世代和千禧一代员工最有可能重视职业发展和技能建设的机会，甚至比他们重视工作与生活的平衡更重要。调查结果还显示，内部流动性已成为最高管理层领导者的第二大劳动力优先事项，学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 领导者表示与高管的合作比以往任何时候都更加密切。</p><p>随着最年轻的员工要求技能驱动的职业道路和高管的关注，未能维持对技能优先人才战略投资的企业将被抛在后面。然而，在经济放缓期间，人们有一种倾向，即退缩并恢复到旧的、可预测的模式和策略。从本质上讲，企业的生存本能迫使许多人选择停滞而不是创新。在 2008 年经济大衰退期间，以前要求教育程度较低的工作坚持要求大学学位的做法（即所谓的<a href="https://www.hbs.edu/managing-the-future-of-work/Documents/dismissed-by-degrees.pdf">学位膨胀</a>）加速了。这种倒退通过增加招聘成本和流动率直接损害了企业的利润，同时加剧了少数人受益而多数人失去机会的经济格局。</p><p></p><h3>扩大多元化人才的机会</h3><p>如今，即使经济前景仍然不确定，企业领导者有机会以不同的方式做事，而且他们在扩大技能优先战略方面处于更有利的地位。无论您仍在努力吸引人才，还是您的招聘已显着降温，都有一些方法可以将技能优先的方法嵌入到您业务的各个方面，即使在经济放缓期间，也可以推动更强劲的长期成果。</p><p>寻找人员来填补空缺职位过去是一个繁琐的手动过程。如果没有复杂的方法来根据实际技能寻找和培养人才，大学学位就成为雇主用来验证候选人是否具备某些技能和能力的少数生硬工具之一，但它却将<a href="https://www.bls.gov/cps/cpsaat07.htm">大多数美国人排除在外。劳动力</a>，尤其是有色人种工人。</p><p>如今，我们可以使用比以往更多的数据来准确确定我们所需的技能，然后找到拥有这些技能的人员（无论是内部人员还是外部人员）。 <a href="https://economicgraph.linkedin.com/research/skills-first-report">LinkedIn 的数据</a>显示，接受这种转变并注重技能的组织可以看到巨大的影响：LinkedIn 上采取技能优先方法的组织可以将其人才管道扩大近 10 倍。雇主已经开始意识到这一点：LinkedIn 上超过 45% 的企业现在<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/skills-new-currency-ryan-roslansky/">明确使用技能数据</a>来填补空缺职位。</p><p></p><p>为了建立未来所需的多元化、高职能团队，雇主必须关注技能——这种方法对人才管道多元化也产生巨大影响。当雇主要求某职位拥有大学学位时，他们会自动排除 60% 的美国人，其中包括 76% 的非裔美国人和 83% 的拉美裔美国人。</p><p>从职位描述中删除不必要的学位要求是基于技能的人才获取的基础，但这还不够。人才招聘领导者还必须投资扩大采购渠道并修改招聘材料中的语言，以确保其包容性和吸引力。此外，面试问题和招聘流程应以第一天的职位所需的基本技能为基础，而不仅仅是证书或经验，并且应有意且公平地制定这些技能，以揭示这些技能。</p><h3>投资学习和内部流动</h3><p>虽然聘用具备合适技能的新员工是技能投资的一种方式，但我们有机会重新关注支持现有员工的成长和发展，尤其是在招聘降温的行业。 LinkedIn 工作场所学习报告的最新调查结果表明，鉴于有效地将人才重新部署到优先业务领域的紧迫性再次凸显，2023 年可能成为扩大技能提升和内部流动计划的重要一年。事实上，调查结果显示，预算预测依然强劲，41% 的 L&amp;D 领导者预计今年的消费能力更强，只有 8% 的人预计预算会减少。</p><p>现在为员工投资技能和基于技能的职业道路可以带来回报。 LinkedIn 的调查结果显示，公司在三年内<a href="https://business.linkedin.com/talent-solutions/global-talent-trends">学习了工作技能的</a>员工保留率提高了近 7%。根据工作场所学习报告，在两年内进行过内部调动的员工有 75% 的可能性留在公司，而角色没有改变的员工有 56% 的可能性继续留在公司。</p><p>与技能优先的招聘类似，技能优先的人才管理要求公司对现有流程进行一系列补充性改变并投资新流程。推动技能优先的内部流动性的关键一步是定义特定角色所需和首选的技能以及跨角色的技能如何重叠。从那里，领导者可以帮助他们的团队建立稳健的职业道路，使员工能够通过培养和应用与其目标相符的技能来实现职业发展。最后，整个企业——更重要的是直接与员工——就可用的职业道路和获得这些职业道路所需的技能进行沟通和透明度，对于提高保留率和晋升率至关重要。</p><p>虽然技能提升和再技能计划的势头正在增强，但显然需要加快进展。 LinkedIn的调查结果显示，40%的公司仍处于早期阶段，向利益相关者出售他们的项目并组建他们的团队； 54% 处于中期阶段，正在开发和启动项目；只有 2% 的人表示他们已经完成了一个项目。百分之四的人根本没有开始。</p><p></p><p>除了运营变革之外，培育包容性、以学习为导向的文化也是公司正在做出的核心转变。通过与领先雇主客户的合作，Grads of Life 了解到，要确保代表性不足群体的员工留在公司并在公司内成长，需要的不仅仅是对 L&amp;D 的财务投资。该组织的研究揭示了黑人人才与白人人才<a href="https://gradsoflife.org/equity-career-advancement-insights-from-underrepresented-employees/">在薪酬和晋升方面存在差异</a>。至关重要的是，除了运营变革之外，组织还应投资变革管理并消除薪酬和晋升系统中的偏见，以加强组织文化。对于大多数雇主来说，采用基于技能的方法来招聘和保留人才与现状有很大不同，而面临将其付诸实践的实施团队需要指导、培训和支持才能取得成功。</p><p></p><p></p><p>在阴云密布的经济预测中，首席执行官们正在谨慎地平衡哪些方面要撤退，哪些方面要加倍努力。投资于技能优先的方法来培养优秀人才并培养他们已有的优秀人才不仅可以帮助他们度过当前的风暴。将技能作为公司战略的核心将使您的员工队伍在所有工作不断变化的世界中保持长期的适应力。</p><p> LinkedIn 的数据显示，自 2015 年以来，<a href="https://linkedin.github.io/future-of-skills/#explore">工作技能组合已经发生了约 25% 的变化</a>，到 2027 年，这一比例将翻倍——这意味着今天的工作所需的核心技能与仅仅几年前的同一份工作看起来非常不同前。今天，我们即将进入的人工智能新时代可能会进一步加速这一变化，82% 的领导者承认他们的员工将需要新技能来<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/will-ai-fix-work">采用人工智能的新工作</a>方式。</p><p>现在，当大海波涛汹涌时，那些准备在这个新的工作世界中取得成功的企业领导人将展示如何做到这一点。现在不是等待更好的条件来做出改变的时候。对于企业来说，现在是更新思维、通过关注技能型劳动力来应对挑战的最佳时机。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>人工智能的社会科学：英特尔的 Elizabeth Anne Watkins</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Relationships]]></category><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Elizabeth Anne Watkins started her doctoral program, she landed a research role studying journalists’ use of security and privacy technologies — but she found the security tools confusing and difficult to use. Today, as a research scientist in the social science of AI at Intel Labs, she advocates for other end users faced with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins) 开始她的博士课程时，她获得了一份研究记者使用安全和隐私技术的研究职位，但她发现这些安全工具令人困惑且难以使用。如今，作为英特尔实验室人工智能社会科学的研究科学家，她倡导其他最终用户理解和使用新技术。</p><p>伊丽莎白利用社会科学来了解执行复杂芯片制造流程的技术人员所关心的问题，以便开发新的人工智能系统，更好地为这些人类专家服务。在此过程中，她还帮助技术人员认识到人工智能作为支持技术（甚至是同事）的角色，而不是人类的替代品。</p><p>她加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客的这一集，讨论了她作为一名从事技术工作的社会科学家的角色，以及英特尔应用计算机视觉和自然语言处理等人工智能技术来改进半导体制造工艺的一些方式。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-s7-e2-Watkins-intel-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯"></p><h4>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯，英特尔</h4><p>Elizabeth Anne Watkins 是英特尔实验室的研究科学家，也是负责任的人工智能咨询委员会的成员。她推动社会科学方法的战略和执行，以放大人类在人类与人工智能协作中的潜力，并在计算机视觉、自然语言处理等人工智能工具的设计、部署和治理中进行可信度、可解释性、透明度和代理性的研究。机器人技术。</p><p>沃特金斯是数据与社会研究所 AI on the Ground 的附属机构，曾与学术界和工业界的研究中心合作、咨询和合作。她在哥伦比亚大学获得了博士学位，在麻省理工学院获得了硕士学位，并且是普林斯顿大学信息技术政策中心及其人机交互小组的博士后研究员。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-watkins"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们知道人工智能工具正在增强人类的表现，但人们对此有何真实感受？在今天的节目中，了解一家公司如何在开发人工智能工具时考虑到最终用户。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>我是来自英特尔的伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯，您正在聆听<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天我们有一位伟大的客人：伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins)，英特尔的研究科学家。伊丽莎白，感谢您今天加入我们。让我们开始吧。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>非常感谢您今天邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>作为全球最大的半导体制造商，英特尔可能是大多数人都知道的公司，但您能否向我们介绍一下英特尔实验室的概况，以及您的具体角色？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>就像你说的，在目前围绕人工智能、人工智能行业和人工智能领域的大型讨论中，我们并不总是最受关注的，但英特尔内部正在开展许多令人着迷的工作，而且我们有这样的工作对这个领域的独特视角以及进入该领域的独特方式，我很高兴今天在我们的谈话中透露其中的一些内容。</p><p>我于去年八月刚刚加入英特尔，与如此多不同的团队会面真是一次令人难以置信的经历。我加入英特尔，担任人工智能社会科学领域的研究科学家，并在英特尔实验室的 Lama Nachman 手下工作。该小组称为智能系统研究。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>伊丽莎白，您提到英特尔实验室正在利用人工智能做一些独特的事情。您介意与我们分享您正在做的一些事情吗？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>我特别兴奋的一个项目叫做 MARIE，是工业环境中多模式活动识别的缩写。基本上，我将从一个比喻开始：想象一下，你的计算机可以看着你组装，比如说，你在互联网上订购的一件家具。当你读到手册的困难部分时，或者你拿着螺丝刀，你拿着一块胶合板，而你无法回到手册，想象一下你的计算机可以看到你在做什么，知道手册将告诉您做什么，然后帮助您将这两者联系起来。想象一下，你的计算机实际上可以告诉你，“嘿，我想你要把架子 A 拧到支架 B 上”，或者类似的东西。我知道，每次我收到他们说里面有一把扶手椅的扁平包装时，从 A 地到 B 地对我来说都是一段非常艰难的时期。</p><p>我们的员工正在我们的工厂内进行类似的流程，他们实际上是在工厂中构建和制造半导体芯片。因此，在我们工厂内部工作的人们，我们的技术人员，正在做非常复杂和非常精细的工作，处理工厂车间发生的各种手动操作的零件和工具。因此，他们所做的所有工作都与将扁平包装放入扶手椅一样复杂，有时甚至更复杂。涉及到很多工具。 There are all kinds of different processes, different pieces of equipment, different sizes of equipment. And so we are building computer systems a little bit like the one that I described that said, “Hey, did you mean to put screw A into bracket B?” We&#39;re building systems to help the people inside of our factories do this kind of really careful and really complicated work.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Actually, that&#39;s a fun analogy. I mean, I think we all find flat packs challenging, perhaps, though I have to admit I kind of enjoy them. But I&#39;m sure it&#39;s much more complicated within Intel. And what I liked about that example is, I feel like so often we&#39;re talking about automation: Can we get machines to learn how to do something that humans do? That&#39;s machine learning [ML] at its core. And then we talk about augmentation and, well, how can machines help humans make a decision? This strikes me as a little bit different. This is going the next step.</p><p> So in this case, we&#39;re not trying to get the machine to assemble the flat pack. We&#39;re not trying to get the machine to assemble the semiconductor. It&#39;s still the humans doing it. And so it&#39;s the humans who are needing to learn here. That seems like pushing that a little bit further than we&#39;ve talked [about] before.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> I&#39;m so glad you picked up on that, Sam. That&#39;s exactly what we talk about inside Intel Labs, is that the human is the expert. The human is the one who knows how to interact with these systems, and they know how to screw the bits together. And they know all of the physical and dynamic intricacies of what it takes to put these tiny and very delicate components together.</p><p> We don&#39;t want to train a computer to do that. A computer <em>cannot</em> do that. The way that this both assembly and cleaning process — because, of course, all of these processes take place within these super-clean rooms, where everyone has to wear hazmat suits and gloves … we want to support the humans who are doing it. There is no computer who could do this. It takes human judgment; it takes human expertise to do these processes in a way that is comprehensive and truly dynamic and can respond to new pressures.</p><p> If a larger piece of a machine bends in a particular way, or if a screw falls into a hole in a particular way — it&#39;s going to be many, many years before computers are able to assess and diagnose and fix these kinds of constant dynamic problems. But you know who&#39;s really good at doing that is humans. And so we&#39;re trying to center humans and center human expertise. And that points to this dual reason that I&#39;m really excited about MARIE, is that there&#39;s both a tech side and there&#39;s a human side. And on the tech side, I think MARIE is really exciting because it&#39;s multimodal. It combines a lot of different kinds of AI systems through ambient sensing. It combines computer vision, which uses activity recognition, with audio sensing, combined with natural language processing [NLP] in a way that can help build an ambient environment around the technician, ultimately to help them [with] what they do.</p><p> But before the system can help them [with] what they do, the system has to actually learn, and it&#39;s the human experts that are teaching the system how to learn and teaching the system what it needs to know. And so this is, as far as I know, a brand-new way to deploy AI systems into new domains and apply them to new problems. … We are confronting and tackling one of the big challenges of AI development, which is data collection.</p><p> You need a lot of data to get into a new domain. You need a lot of data that&#39;s labeled the appropriate way, labeled according to the kinds of problems that you&#39;re trying to solve. And so we&#39;ve kind of flipped the script: Instead of trying to get all the data we can <em>before</em> a system is deployed, we go ahead and deploy a system that then works in partnership with the experts on the ground, and they teach the system — through speaking aloud and through dynamic data labeling — they teach the system what it needs to know. And so, hopefully, the data that is going to be used to help people to do these tasks down the line is going to be produced by the very first batches of people who are using the tool.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That seems like a great analogy because as you&#39;re saying that, it reminded me of what you would do if it was a new human partner joining the project. You&#39;d go through those same steps.</p><p> Shervin and I have some research where we find that <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/achieving-individual-and-organizational-value-with-ai/">60% of the people out there are thinking of AI as a coworker</a> , and that&#39;s exactly the sort of relationship that you&#39;re describing. But it made me think of a little danger here. Let&#39;s say that when you put that system out there, it doesn&#39;t know much, and you&#39;ve got the human training them. All right; I&#39;m a human. I feel like I&#39;m a little bit annoyed. I&#39;m like, “Why am I having to work so hard to train this coworker?” How do you keep that dynamic? You mentioned there being a technical side of this project, but the social side as well. That strikes me as maybe harder on the social side than on the technical side.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That&#39;s precisely what I want to talk about next because that&#39;s precisely what I get to do. I get to talk to the people about what they actually think about these systems — and you are right on the money. Sometimes they do perceive it to be annoying, where they&#39;re asking, “Wait — so I&#39;m putting together this really complex instrument, and the system asks me what I&#39;m doing, and it&#39;s <em>wrong</em> ? So how am I supposed to spend time not only doing my job but also teaching this machine how to do my job?”</p><p> And so I am really gratified that I get to be the social scientist who is there right on the ground. We&#39;re still deep in development, and it&#39;s common for companies to do as much testing as they can, of course, before something is deployed and then, when the actual tenets of deployment come — things such as user experience and user interface designs — those typically come closer to the end of a development process. But here, the social science and the understanding of what people need and what people might find annoying and what they need to trust a machine that is a coworker with them is right in the DNA of the development. And so I get to consistently speak with the technicians that we are building the system for and ask them questions just like the one that you described, asking them, “Do you think this is annoying? How might this be more helpful? What are some other affordances that we can build into the system to make it more helpful for you?”</p><p> And also asking deeper questions, not just about their dyadic relationship with the system but also about their larger sociotechnical context of work. Asking about, like, “What does your schedule look like?” and, “What have your bosses said about the system?” and, “Is there a way that we could try to facilitate more productive relationships, not just with your bosses but also with your other coworkers, through this system?” And so our goal is to build a very deep understanding, not just of one task but an entire space of work, and ask how our system can help in the best way it can to amplify human potential by being a coworker for humans within this space, but also [asking], “How can it be built with an understanding of their work context in order to facilitate a long-term relationship?”</p><p> Because one of these things that&#39;s demanded by the fact that we&#39;re leaning on people to provide data and leaning on people to help us actually do the data labeling is that we need them to be engaged, and we need them to like interacting with the system, and we need them to find it trustworthy and reliable and useful. And understanding how all those goals can be achieved requires a deep understanding of social context and social habits and work habits and task flows. And so that&#39;s precisely what we&#39;re working on now.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I think it&#39;s really interesting how you seem to be thinking beyond just this project. There&#39;s the element of “OK, how do I get this particular project in place,” but underlying a lot of things you&#39;re talking about are things like, “How do we figure out the best way to introduce, essentially, a new system? How do we figure out the best way for how to transform and get to our overall vision?” And that transcends just a single project. How are you trying to pick up on those lessons?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That is a really great question. I am really proud of our labs and some of the big bets that we&#39;re making on human-AI collaboration and how much the input and contributions and insights drawn from social science are being picked up, and have been picked up historically at Intel, throughout their research projects. As we&#39;re doing research projects and building products across verticals like education and manufacturing and accessibility, there&#39;s deep investment across the teams that facilitates and encourages conversations with folks like me — with the social scientists.</p><p> We often get these really fantastic teams in a room where we have engineers and data scientists and policy makers and social scientists, including not just me but a wonderful team — headed up by Dawn Nafus — of anthropologists, as well as another team of social scientists that has psychologists. And we all work together really closely to ensure that the products we build are not just designs to answer one problem but that they&#39;re properly engineered around what the best solution is, that we take advantage of all the different kinds of multimodal affordances that our tools can provide, and that we&#39;re deeply understanding of the social and organizational context that all of our products are going to be deployed into.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think so often there&#39;s a transition that seems to be happening between when we were first talking about these models and tools and using data: Things were very heavily data- and tool-oriented and very heavily science-oriented. And that made a lot of sense because we didn&#39;t know how to do some of these things. And now, as a society, we&#39;re learning how to do many of these tools and model buildings. But a lot of the team you mentioned there — anthropology, psychology — these are not traditional things that we might have thought of [as] being integral to producing an AI application, but those are the ones you happened to mention. Why did you pick those? I guess that&#39;s some of your background in social science, right?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Yeah, throughout my graduate studies and postdoc work, I was always really invested in the users and in people. And I was always really fascinated by just how weird people can be and how creative and how innovative, and how folks often use technologies in ways that their developers did not anticipate and did not foresee.</p><p> And while there are some dangerous elements to that, as we&#39;ve seen in various misuse and dual-use applications, there are also a lot of really fantastic and wonderful ways that people have figured out for technology to be more suited to them in their context or to work a little bit more smoothly for them. And so seeing how Intel was different because of their history of being a semiconductor manufacturer and being deeply invested in hardware and having an ecosystem approach to the way that AI tools are deployed really showed me that they were a company that cared, just like I did, about the people who were going to be using these tools and the social structures in which these people were embedded, and building tools that could match not just the people who bought or used the tools but also the lives and the communities into which these technologies were going to be interjected.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Elizabeth, clearly a lot of your background has been coming through as we&#39;ve been talking, but could we step back for a second and ask you about how you ended up in this role at Intel Labs?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> I guess my road to this role started way back, probably at the beginning of my graduate career. After I graduated MIT and started my Ph.D. at Columbia, there was an opening for someone to contribute to a project on security and privacy behaviors among journalists. And my adviser said, “Hey, I got you an interview for this project.” And I said, “I don&#39;t know anything about security and privacy.” And she said, “Just go to the interview. I got you the interview. Just go.” And so the night before the interview, I thought, “Oh, I&#39;d better have something to talk about. PGP — Pretty Good Privacy — everyone&#39;s talking about PGP. I better download PGP so I can act like I know what PGP is.” And I tried to figure it out, and it was hard. I couldn&#39;t figure out … I went to the website and I was like, “The website doesn&#39;t really explain what&#39;s happening here. Where&#39;s the key? I download the key, but the key&#39;s also kept in a database, but I write the key on my emails? Oh, I&#39;m so … I can&#39;t do this. I&#39;m so bad at this. This is not for me.”</p><p> And I went into the interview the next day with the wonderful project lead, Susan McGregor, and I said, “You know what? This job&#39;s not for me. I tried to do PGP; it&#39;s weirdly hard. There&#39;s something about it that I just … I can&#39;t quite grok the language.” And she said, “I think that makes you perfect for this job because we are trying to figure out why security and privacy are so hard for people at work, especially journalists who are high-value targets for attack from a lot of different actors, and we are trying to figure out how we can make security and privacy protocols better for them, so it sounds like you&#39;re frustrated with how security is designed.” And I said, “Yeah, that was frustrating.” And she said, “OK, let&#39;s do some work.”</p><p> So we ended up working together for several years studying journalists. We had one particularly harrowing project studying the journalists who published the Panama Papers. And for that, they had terabytes of data. There were journalists working all over the world; none of them were colocated, and they didn&#39;t have a single breach. Never once did they have a breach and in all of that data. And so we saw that as a success story. And we said, “OK. We&#39;re always hearing the bad stories about breaches and attacks; we never hear the success stories.” And so we got to interview the journalists who contributed to the Panama Papers and talked to them about their organizational culture and how making protocols uniform across all journalists helped to instill a sense of teamwork and a sense that they were protecting each other. And seeing the power of culture and shared mission on behaviors around something as difficult as PGP and security protocols … it was really inspirational.</p><p> And around that time, I started paying attention to facial recognition, and from there it was a short bridge over to looking at AI and asking similar questions around “Why is this hard to understand? How can we communicate it to people in a more strategic way that is more understanding of the work that they&#39;re doing and the work that they need to do? And how can we bring some transparency to these systems in a way that is meaningful and understandable for real people?”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One of the things interesting about that is, security&#39;s always like that. If it&#39;s a little bit hard to do, then we all tend to not do it, because it&#39;s tomorrow&#39;s problem versus today&#39;s problem. … That&#39;s something we as humans are terrible about. And you know, I think what we&#39;ve failed [at] in many ways here is not building that into the infrastructure so it&#39;s a default. And there&#39;s a lot of analogies for artificial intelligence: We&#39;re building things, and if we don&#39;t make the defaults easy to use or easy to do the right thing, then people will do the wrong thing — or people will do the easy thing or the short-term thing. And you mentioned facial recognition: What are the kinds of things that we should be building into our infrastructure so we don&#39;t propagate AI-based mistakes?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. Something that drives my research, both throughout my graduate career and here at Intel, is a recognition that people are the experts in their own lives and that we really need to engage with the people and with the users throughout the development pipeline in order to build not just systems but solutions, and solutions for the real problems that are happening on the ground. And as close as a company can get to including the expertise of social science and what social scientists can bring about rigorous and robust tools to study how people live and the kinds of languages they use and the kinds of values they have and what&#39;s truly important to them and what they want to protect and what they want to keep safe, as well as building in different kinds of options and different kinds of pathways into the same technology that might be used differently by people of different levels of accessibility, are all things that I would love to see the entire field take up.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That <em>sounds</em> good. I mean … much like buying low and selling high sounds great. How do companies actually do this? What steps do they need to take to make progress on these?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. The way that we&#39;re doing it at Intel is that we are facilitating conversations between our technical teams — people who are building really amazing systems around robotics and accessibility tools and educational tools — and embedding social scientists across all these teams so that we can ask some questions around “Hey, what are the presumptions of this system? Have you talked to teachers? Have you talked to the folks who are going to be using this robot on the ground? What are your conversations like with the people who are going to be served by these solutions?”</p><p> And I&#39;m really lucky that I get to be in a place where we&#39;re embedding this expertise way back into the problem-formulation stage and into the project-formulation stage, all throughout the development pipeline. I&#39;ve also been really gratified that Intel established the ethical impact assessment process along with the Responsible AI [Advisory] Council. And so this is a process for robustly and rigorously building into the development pipeline that teams all across Intel and across all business units [use]. This is a way to inject the expertise, not just of social scientists but everyone who sits on the Responsible AI [Advisory] Council, including engineers and policy makers and folks from legal and folks from standards, and facilitate conversations with this multidisciplinary Responsible AI [Advisory] Council with development teams through their submission of the ethical impact assessment.</p><p> And the ethical impact assessment is a way for us to put values into practice and ensure that values around human oversights and human rights and privacy and safety and security and diversity and inclusion — these are ways for us to make sure that those values are built into the tools that Intel BUs [business units] are putting together across the organization.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK, we have a segment where we ask our guests a series of five rapid-fire questions. Just answer the first thing that comes to your mind. First: What is your proudest AI moment?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh, goodness. That&#39;s a great question. I am really proud of being able to represent the voices of the technicians who we have on the floor to these teams of engineers and data scientists who are building these systems. And because of the process that Intel has built, where I get to sit with the engineering teams who are building the computer vision and the action recognition and the NLP and choosing the phrases in the semantic frames around tasks and about how tasks are built and how they can be recognized, being able to do the interviews that I do with technicians to ask them about their concerns when this technology is introduced, what we can do to make sure that their concerns are addressed, asking what they need to know around transparency, what they need in order to trust the system, all in the service of enhancing the work that people are doing.</p><p> The fact that I get to grab that information and deliver it consistently to the engineers and to see how quickly they respond. Like, “Oh, well, we can build this and we can build that. And what if we built this into the UI? And what if we built this into the dialog?” It&#39;s such an incredibly compelling process, especially after coming from academia, where I would write a paper and then it would take a year to get published. And then …</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Oh, a year sounds fast.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Right. If I were lucky, it would take a year. I think my longest record was maybe 3½ years it took to get published.我不知道。 What&#39;s your record?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Uh, 10. So …</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Ten!</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah. Let&#39;s don&#39;t talk about it though, because I&#39;ll get all sad.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh, no.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So you mentioned concerns that people have. What worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Well, one of their biggest concerns, when I started talking to the technicians, was that they were going to get replaced.</p><p> I said, “OK, let&#39;s have a conversation. What do you think this is for?” And they said, “I&#39;ve seen the news. I know you&#39;re trying to build a robot just to do exactly what I do, so I figure I&#39;m training my replacement.” And I thought, “Oh, no! That&#39;s terrible.” And I got to have a lot of conversations with our technicians where I got to say, “That&#39;s <em>not</em> what we&#39;re doing. We are not trying to replace you. You are the expert.我们需要你。 In fact, we need you to teach the system so that the system can go and help other people like you. So by you training the system, you&#39;re actually helping a lot of other folks in Intel fabs [semiconductor manufacturing plants] across the planet, and you are ensuring that they get help in the way that you would like to get help.”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Some research that Shervin and I were involved in a couple years ago focused entirely on this <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning">organizational learning</a> aspect that you were alluding to — that this is a way for everyone to learn more quickly and to spread knowledge.</p><p> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology? What&#39;s <em>not</em> AI going on in your world?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Well, there&#39;s so much happening recently, it seems tough sometimes to figure out what&#39;s AI and what&#39;s not.</p><p> [In] my personal life, I do a lot of baking. It&#39;s been a while since I made a loaf of bread. I do a lot of cooking. I am very lucky to live with my husband in the city of New York, and so we do a lot of exploring — in fact, just getting outside. That&#39;s probably the biggest non-AI activity, is walking outside on our own two feet and looking around with our own eyes. And that always feels very refreshing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were young?你长大后想做什么？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> I wanted to be an artist, and it has been a topsy-turvy winding road. I did my undergrad at UC Irvine, and I studied video art.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> There&#39;s so much that AI can do that humans cannot, but there&#39;s also so much that humans can do that AI cannot. And I think a big challenge, at least for me, and I hope the people with whom I work going forward for the next few years, is going to be figuring out exactly what that balance is and how can we systematize “What do people really need help with that AI systems can do?” but with a really thorough understanding of what it is that people do and how they do it.</p><p> Now that the AI systems are becoming so advanced, but oftentimes in a lab or in a vacuum, as they mature into the real world, I think it&#39;s really exciting what they can do, but we&#39;re facing a lot of work in getting them there. And I think it&#39;s going to be other social scientists and multidisciplinary teams like the ones that we have at Intel all working together to make sure that these systems can really be deployed as solutions.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a good cap for the episode. Thanks for talking to us. I think one of the things that has come through [is], you&#39;re talking about projects and things you&#39;re working on, but you&#39;re also giving us a hint about what&#39;s going to happen in the future as we move off of the, let&#39;s say, tool-focused “Can we get the ML right? Can we get the model right? Can we get the data right?” You&#39;re talking a lot about what happens next, what happens once we check off some of those check marks — what are those checks? And I think a lot of people can learn from that. Thanks for taking the time to talk with us today.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh my gosh, it&#39;s been such a pleasure.</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>感谢您的聆听。 Next time, Shervin and I speak with David Hardoon from Aboitiz Data Innovation. We&#39;re once again talking about chemical engineering, so you won&#39;t want to miss this one.</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Impact of Generative AI on Hollywood and Entertainment</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) is the President&#39;s Distinguished Professor of Information Technology and Management at Babson College, a visiting professor at Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School, and a fellow of the MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy. He is coauthor of <cite>Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration</cite> (MIT Press, 2022). Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) is an industry thought leader, author, founder, and CEO and currently serves as innovation fellow, data strategy for global consultancy Wavestone. He is the author of <cite>Fail Fast, Learn Faster: Lessons in Data-Driven Leadership in an Age of Disruption, Big Data, and AI</cite> (Wiley, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Knowledge Workers]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[One of the many topics involving generative AI that is receiving a lot of attention is its potential effects on Hollywood and the entertainment industry. It’s an obvious concern because generative AI can create the types of outputs that the industry uses — text (in the form of stories, scripts, ad copy, and reviews), marketing [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Davenport-Bean-Hollywood-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> One of the many topics involving generative AI that is receiving a lot of attention is its potential effects on Hollywood and the entertainment industry. It&#39;s an obvious concern because generative AI can create the types of outputs that the industry uses — text (in the form of stories, scripts, ad copy, and reviews), marketing campaigns, and moving and static images. Segments of the industry are facing economic pressures, which increases the demand for productivity and less-expensive “product.” And a high percentage of current entertainment is derivative of past content, which makes it well suited for generative technologies that are trained on … past content.</p><p> It&#39;s still early days for generative AI-created entertainment, but it&#39;s clear that something big is happening. A recent <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-hollywood-intellectual-property-spongebob-81fd5d15"><cite>Wall Street Journal</cite> article</a> noted that widely available AI tools can suggest storylines, character arcs, and dialogue; it even includes an interactive module that lets readers see for themselves how easily ChatGPT can write a basic script when given a few prompts. The article also raises questions about image intellectual property: “If a user prompts an AI tool to build a new character influenced by say, SpongeBob, should the original creators have to grant permission? Who owns it? Can the new work itself be copyrighted?”</p><p></p><p> Generative AI was used in <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/05/05/runway-generative-ai-chatgpt-video">making the 2022 film <cite>Everything Everywhere All at Once</cite></a> , and <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/oscars-2023-everything-everywhere-all-at-once-most-awards/">we know how that turned out</a> . Tom recently wrote about the use of generative AI to create <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2023/03/13/cuebric-generative-ai-comes-to-hollywood/">movie and TV backdrop images</a> . There are already generative AI systems that can create videos, although they are short and relatively primitive. AI is being used to provide data-driven predictions about <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/democratizing-data-in-hollywood-jumpcuts-kartik-hosanagar/">how unusual storylines will land with viewers</a> .</p><p> So, what does this mean for the industry? There are many different components to this question, as a new <a href="https://variety.com/vip-special-reports/generative-ai-entertainment-a-special-report-1235564989/">report from Variety Intelligence Platform</a> suggests. In May, the Writers Guild of America (WGA) went on strike, primarily over film and TV writers&#39; <a href="https://time.com/6277158/writers-strike-ai-wga-screenwriting/">income from streaming services programming</a> , but it also demanded that production companies “<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/29/business/media/writers-guild-hollywood-ai-chatgpt.html">regulate use of material produced using artificial intelligence</a> or similar technologies.” Because there are so many uncertainties about what will happen when and how with the technology, we spoke with two experts on the topic. Both are based in — not surprisingly — Los Angeles, and both are involved with centers at the University of Southern California (USC). However, they don&#39;t work together, and they have very different approaches to the technology.</p><p></p><h3> Resolutely Against Generative AI</h3><p> Jonathan Taplin is director emeritus at the <a href="https://www.annenberglab.com/">Annenberg Innovation Lab</a> at USC. He&#39;s had a long career in the entertainment industry and was previously a tour manager for musicians, including Bob Dylan and The Band. In addition, he&#39;s been a film producer, a banker, and a writer. His latest book, <a href="https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/jonathan-taplin/the-end-of-reality/9781541703155/?lens=publicaffairs"><cite>The End of Reality: How Four Billionaires Are Selling a Fantasy Future of the Metaverse, Mars, and Crypto</cite></a> , will be released in September. As you might infer from the title, he&#39;s not a fan of how big tech firms&#39; generative AI tools are being developed or promulgated.</p><p> “The way they train their models is by ingesting everything on the internet, with no concern for copyright,” Taplin told us. “Google has a music-generation AI trained on every audio file on YouTube. You can issue a prompt like &#39;Write me a song that sounds like Taylor Swift, sad ending, up-tempo,&#39; and the resulting song sounds somewhat like her. Someone could include it in a video game or a bar scene in a movie for free.” Generative AI could do the same kind of repurposing with video content owned by the studios, he added.</p><p> Taplin&#39;s primary concern is that generative AI will replace some of the work done by human writers, artists, photographers, and other creative professionals in the arts and entertainment industry. He also believes that it will exacerbate problems that are already bringing the film and TV industry down. “The biggest problem in the movies is too many formulas. There is a lack of originality, and that&#39;s why the industry isn&#39;t performing,” he said. Generative AI, he added, is only capable of producing even more formulaic content and will make the predictability worse. “Entertainment relies on new ideas, and this technology can&#39;t produce them,” Taplin added.</p><p> He said he&#39;s concerned that generative AI will continue to reduce the number of performers who can make a living in their fields. The majority of entertainment revenue already goes to a very small percentage of artists. This is the <a href="https://www.digitalmusicnews.com/2014/03/05/toponepercent/">reality for musicians</a> , especially on <a href="https://themusicnetwork.com/few-artists-generate-most-streams/">streaming services</a> , and is echoed in Hollywood in the huge <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/655480/all-time-top-grossing-actors-box-office/">box office revenues</a> generated by a handful of leading actors in blockbuster films. When you get an “algorithmic economy,” Taplin said, “the algorithms narrow the funnel, with outsize paychecks for a few.” He&#39;s hopeful that a collective licensing regime — similar to what&#39;s in place for music sampling — will emerge to protect artists when their content is used to train generative AI.</p><h3> Embracing Generative AI, With Some Concerns</h3><p> Yves Bergquist is director of the AI &amp; Neuroscience in Media Project at USC&#39;s <a href="https://www.etcenter.org/">Entertainment Technology Center</a> , which is funded by Hollywood studios. You can guess that his opinion of generative AI is probably much more favorable than Taplin&#39;s. It is, although he said he does have some concerns about AI&#39;s potential effects on the media and entertainment industry: “It&#39;s a completely revolutionary technology” characterized by misinformation and “some insanity.”</p><p> We asked Bergquist whether movie studios would embrace generative AI. Parts of them are already doing so, he said. “Some groups within the studios are highly technologically savvy, such as the chief technology officers and all of the visual effects artists and technicians. They are very sophisticated and are already working with generative AI companies. The studios do a lot of the postproduction work in films — particularly in animation — and there is a lot of pressure to bring costs down. The postproduction companies have a software development culture, so they will embrace generative AI.”</p><p> He also believes that many production companies will embrace the technology because they are already shooting on large LED-based screens and will need generative images for them. Bergquist said he expects that tools offering virtual actors and voice synthesis will be most aggressively adopted by short-form creators who distribute their work on TikTok or YouTube and by video game producers. “Streaming channels, digital ads, games — that&#39;s what kids watch these days,” he noted. “The media industry no longer has a monopoly on entertainment.” Makers of hardware (such as cameras) are experimenting with generative in-camera visual effects as well.</p><p></p><p> The business side of traditional movie studios is sometimes more reluctant to embrace AI, Bergquist observed, simply because they don&#39;t have the same kind of culture of data or software. “It&#39;s being bolted onto organizations and people who aren&#39;t ready,” he said. Even the new streaming studios, like Netflix and Prime Video, have experienced a lot of growing pains in their AI journeys.</p><p> Bergquist said that before the WGA strike started in May, many screenwriters told him that they view the likes of ChatGPT as a “great creative assistant tool” but not something that will replace human writers. “It&#39;s good at brainstorming ideas, but it will output only average content,” Bergquist asserted. “It&#39;s nowhere near capable of the symbolic abstraction necessary for script development, and it can&#39;t output a script with narrative structure and character arcs.” At least not now. Future language models with higher levels of intelligence and new paradigms for AI might be able to do so.</p><p></p><p> Bergquist thinks generative AI will have enormous effects not only on entertainment but also on education. He believes that schools, including the School of Cinematic Arts at USC, need to quickly ramp up their teaching to keep pace with the frenzy of new generative AI tools that are released nearly every week. Bergquist is preparing courses himself on the technology for the Society of Motion Pictures and Television Engineers, an organization that represents technologists in media.</p><h3> Are Both Experts Right?</h3><p> Although Taplin and Bergquist seem to have very different views on generative AI, they might both be right about its impacts. Economic pressures may entice the industry — at least some sectors of it — to embrace these new tools. Generative AI will lead to dramatic changes in production and postproduction, distribution, and intellectual property ownership. The technology may not be good for traditional artists and the companies that employ them, but it is likely to lead to significant changes in the industry over the next few years — hopefully some for the better along with some for the worse. Perhaps the only purely good news is that neither expert expects that humans will be entirely replaced anytime soon.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Recapping Work/23: The Big Shift</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:09:56 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Career Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Download the Event Summary Download (PDF) The pandemic irrevocably changed the how, why, and where of work. At Work/23: The Big Shift, a half-day summit held May 4, 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review brought together company executives and academic experts in talent management, hybrid work, employee well-being, and workplace culture. Together, they explained how organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> <strong>Download the Event Summary</strong></h5><p class="is-button"> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cb2792f94c.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Download (PDF)</a></p></aside><p> The pandemic irrevocably changed the how, why, and where of work. At Work/23: The Big Shift, a half-day summit held May 4, 2023, <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> brought together company executives and academic experts in talent management, hybrid work, employee well-being, and workplace culture. Together, they explained how organizations are pivoting to innovate, improve productivity, and achieve balance in this changed world.</p><p> <cite>MIT SMR</cite> editor in chief Abbie Lundberg and editorial director Elizabeth Heichler co-moderated the event.</p><p> The full video of the half-day event is here. Work/23 included these topics and speakers:</p><h4 class="work23-title" id="nalbantian"> Dismantle Career Roadblocks for More Equitable Outcomes</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Haig R. Nalbantian, Workforce Sciences Institute</h5><p> Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Nalbantian outlined ways companies are tackling the obstacles women and people of color continue to face — obstacles that are often due to situational factors, such as the roles people are in or whom they report to.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:02</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="berwick"> The Why, What, and How of Skills-Based Talent Practices</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Beth Berwick, Grads of Life</h5><p> More jobs than ever now require a four-year college degree, including many that never did in the past. But that criterion excludes 64% of the population — including 76% of Black Americans and 80% of Latinos. Berwick is among those calling for a retreat on the degree requirement. She explained how organizations can instead hire effectively based on the skills they need.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 33:24</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="smith"> The New World of Accessing Talent</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Mike Smith, Randstad Enterprise; David Kiron, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> Companies are changing how they approach and apply technology to find the people they need. <cite>MIT SMR</cite> &#39;s Kiron and our presenting partner&#39;s chief executive discussed the ways that innovative organizations are designing their own talent pools, building their talent brands, and expanding DEI initiatives beyond their own boundaries.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 54:44</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="dervin"> Flexible <em>and</em> Effective: Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workplace</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Julie Dervin, Atlassian; Brian Elliott, Future Forum; N. Sharon Hill, George Washington University School of Business; Abbie Lundberg, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> It&#39;s possible to have a healthy workplace culture and high performance in a hybrid workplace; it just requires a deliberate management approach. The speakers in this session expanded on their research and their real-world experience configuring hybrid work arrangements and discussed how to get to the right mix of worker autonomy and organizational alignment.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:07:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="kellerman"> Thriving in the New World of Work</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Gabriella Rosen Kellerman, BetterUp; Martin Seligman, University of Pennsylvania; Elizabeth Heichler, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> Workforce well-being is an urgent issue for leaders who recognize that stress is driving out talented workers. The speakers, who coauthored the book <cite>Tomorrowmind</cite> , detailed the skills that help individuals flourish in pressure-filled work environments, including <em>prospection</em> — the ability to imagine our options, plan for the future, and restore our agency.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:42:29</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="gigliotti"> How to Deliver Career Development for All</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Tony Gigliotti, UPMC; Lani Montoya, Pernod Ricard North America; George Westerman, MIT Sloan</h5><p> The speakers in this session outlined how forward-leaning companies are helping all employees — not just a select few — chart rewarding career paths. They explained that companies are doing it by providing ways to learn and practice new skills and by delivering rich feedback. Companies are also making pathways visible, showing opportunities at and above an employee&#39;s current level.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 2:13:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="altman"> An Integrated Approach to Workforce Ecosystems</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Elizabeth J. Altman, UMass Lowell; David Kiron, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> The speakers&#39; research, featured in the book <cite>Workforce Ecosystems</cite> , found that most leaders consider their workforces to be broader than full-time employees, encompassing gig workers, professional services firms, and even technologies like customer service chatbots. Altman and Kiron explained what it takes to coordinate and successfully manage that expanded workforce.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 2:49:49</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="barnes">每周工作四天：如何让它在您的组织中发挥作用</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker">Andrew Barnes, 4 Day Week Global</h5><p> Barnes has had a front-row seat at the world&#39;s largest trial of what happens when you scale back the workweek from five days to four. It started with an experiment at his own company, where, he said, “we pay 100% income, for 80% time, as long as we get 100% output.” He started a nonprofit to help other companies try it themselves and now has data from 91 participating organizations.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 3:14:02 </h6><p></p><style>.work23-title {margin-bottom:0!important;}.work23-speaker {margin-top:0!important;}.work23-timestamp {margin-bottom:25px!important;color: #005b9c!important;text-transform: uppercase;letter-spacing: 1px!important;font-size: 1.4rem!important;margin-bottom:25px!important;}</style> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>