<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>星期二，2023年8月8日14:26:05 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>取缔大学平权法案将如何影响美国企业界</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Derek R. Avery. <p>德里克·R·艾弗里 (Derek R. Avery) 是休斯敦大学鲍尔商学院包容性领导力 CT Bauer 主席。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Recruiting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equality]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avery-Extension-a4312ir2142-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">迈克尔·格伦伍德·吉布斯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> 2023 年 6 月 29 日，美国最高法院以 6 比 3 的裁决支持禁止在大学招生中使用种族和族裔因素。这是一项重大决定，将产生广泛的社会和组织影响。尽管该裁决的范围仅限于大学招生，但我们可以利用现有数据来预测对美国企业界的影响。证据清楚地指出了两个关键结果：首先，种族多样性的大学模式将发生相当大的变化；其次，这些变化将对工作场所构成以及一系列其他措施中的种族不平等模式产生相当大的下游影响。</p><p>尽管人们可能会认为这些结论有些夸张，但对三十年来州级平权行动禁令的研究强烈表明事实并非如此。事实上，消除平权行动已经导致本科和研究生课程中代表性不足的学生（黑人和西班牙裔）比例下降，特别是在科学、技术、工程和数学领域；它还导致医学院和法学院入学和毕业的代表性不足的学生减少。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这些影响往往是持久的，而且重要的是，实施不明确考虑种族和族裔的替代政策对应对这些影响效果甚微。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p>将这些州级研究结果扩展到国家级表明，雇主在填补职位空缺时，可以利用的种族多元化程度较低的受过大学教育的人才，尤其是来自一流院校的人才。另外，申请人群体中的黑人和西班牙裔候选人被选中的可能性较小，因为他们的学位较少或毕业于排名较低的大学，因此资历较低，而他们更有可能申请并被录取。 -平权行动。一个不太直观的结果是，更有声望的学院和大学的白人（和亚洲人）毕业生与其他种族背景的人的接触会更少。这对他们的多元文化能力（与与自己不同的人建立联系的能力）产生了影响，并且可能有助于解释为什么雇主倾向于向种族多元化的商学院和大学的毕业生支付更高的起薪。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>黑人和西班牙裔社区的影响将是毁灭性的。最值得注意的是，帮助满足种族相似的少数族裔客户需求的少数族裔专业人士将会减少。尽管这似乎更方便，但在医学或法律（雇用律师和执法人员）等领域尤其令人不安，在这些领域，少数族裔代表性不足往往被认为是有据可查的种族民族医疗保健的一个促成因素和刑事司法差异。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>从更有声望的学校毕业或根本毕业的几率较低也会对组织内的种族不平等产生影响。首先，代表性不足的少数族裔不太容易找到工作，或者更有可能找到质量较低的工作。它会继续影响从进入到退出的整个人力资源管理领域的结果，因为最初的安置会对薪酬、晋升、培训/发展、保留/离职和部署等方面产生持久的影响。例如，即使是获得就业机会的黑人和西班牙裔专业人士也可能更有可能发现自己面临“最后受聘、最先被解雇”的现象。此外，起薪过低会影响其他公司的加薪规模或竞争性报价，并对个人的退休储蓄产生有害的复合效应。</p><p></p><p>那些寻求更具体证据证明禁止大学平权行动可以影响美国企业多样性的人只需看看哈佛商学院教授张乐天最近的研究即可。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>他利用平等就业机会委员会 1985 年至 2015 年间 11,000 多家美国私营企业的数据，研究了平权行动禁令对不同种族背景的人是否成为管理者的影响。他预计高管们可能会将禁令解读为一种歧视的许可，因此不太可能雇用黑人经理或提拔黑人候选人。结果显示，“在一个州采取平权行动禁令后，公司总部位于该州的企业中，黑人经理的比例增长放缓超过50%，这种放缓主要集中在首席执行官政治保守的公司。”</p><p>通过扩大大学成绩差距，大学禁止平权行动实际上进一步推动了众所周知的机会平等，因为在财富和获得优质学前教育和 K-12 教育方面现有的种族差异增加了更大的高等教育差异，这也不利于代表性不足的少数群体。具有讽刺意味的是，这进一步增强了为维持种族现状而采取工作场所平权行动策略的必要性。也就是说，任何此类努力几乎肯定会受到法律依据的挑战，而最高法院（至少目前的组成）已表明自己极不可能赞成此类努力。</p><p></p><p>事实上，13 个州总检察长最近以先发制人的方式通知苹果、微软和 Uber 等公司，他们应该期待对任何被认为促进员工选拔中基于种族的偏好的政策进行更严格的审查。他们继续承诺对“违规者”采取法律行动，表明他们打算将最高法院裁决的范围扩大到美国工作场所。这就提出了一个问题，仍然致力于种族平等就业机会的组织可以采取哪些措施来限制他们在这个新的、不断变化的就业格局中可能遭受的损失？下面，我提供四项建议来帮助从业者、管理者和组织应对这一挑战。</p><p></p><h3>不要在场边等待</h3><p>西奥多·罗斯福总统经常被认为有这样一句话：“在任何决策时刻，你能做的最好的事情就是正确的事情，其次最好的事情就是错误的事情，而你能做的最糟糕的事情就是什么都不做。”在最高法院的裁决之后，人们可能会倾向于维持一切照旧，观望事态的发展，并在尘埃落定后采取反动的做法。然而，这样做肯定会产生相当大的后果。也就是说，继续从同一所学校寻找申请者，而不根据学生群体构成的可预测变化进行调整，会使组织完全依赖大学招生人员重新调整策略来解决很少有人能够解决的问题。过去30年。</p><p>因此，像许多组织历史上那样，继续使用学位和学位授予机构作为人力资本的代表，可能会导致几乎所有就业结果中的种族差异扩大，并对非就业结果产生连锁效应。例如，最近的一项研究表明，在平权行动禁令实施后，代表性不足的少数族裔青年往往会立即增加危险行为（吸烟、饮酒和酗酒）。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>简而言之，预计代表性不足的少数族裔员工将会减少，种族不平等将会加剧，包括收入和晋升方面的更大差异。</p><h3>质疑一切</h3><p>好吧，你可能不必质疑一切，但如果一个组织想要在某件事上做得更好，它需要以不同的方式做一些事情，并检查它们过去是如何做的。例如，一位人力资源主管曾经告诉我，公司的政策是只从全国排名前十的工程项目中进行招聘。这种做法的一个意想不到的后果是，新员工来自与公司所在地完全不同的地理区域，而且新员工的流动率对于该行业来说异常高。 10号程序和12号程序没有质的区别，都位于100英里以内。为什么不从 12 号计划中招募员工，以减少新员工在第一年内经历极端文化冲击并离职的机会？</p><p>在当前背景下应用这一逻辑，公司可能需要扩大其搜索参数，以吸引在人口统计上与最近的申请人群体一致的申请人群体。在历史悠久的黑人学院和大学以及为西班牙裔服务的机构进行招聘是进行定向招聘的好方法——这一策略目前在法律上是允许的。在代表性不足的少数群体经常光顾的地方放置在线广告，表明您的组织有兴趣接收这些群体成员的申请。此外，在选择和薪酬方面，企业需要重新评估授予学位机构的隐性和显性权重。从一流大学毕业的好处已经分配得不一致，白人毕业生的好处比黑人学位持有者的好处更大。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>为什么不减少每个人的受益，同时为更大的群体提供更多就业机会？</p><h3>深入研究数据</h3><p>为了解决质疑一切所带来的问题，组织可以求助于他们的数据所揭示的内容。例如，尽管惰性和针对竞争对手的基准可能表明某项工作需要大学学位，但数据是否支持这一论点？与种族差异相关的工作要求，例如获得学位和从著名学校获得学位，往往会对代表性不足的群体产生不利影响——这是一种统计歧视的形式。在选择的背景下，当特定的决策工具使一个种族群体（或任何其他受法律保护的类别）的成员相对于另一个种族群体的成员有利时，就会产生不利影响。虽然如果这种差异与工作相关，则这种差异并不违法，但需要数据来确定这种相关性。</p><p>当要求学位、偏向精英学校毕业生以及使用最低 GPA 分数线时，当这些要求与工作表现没有直接关系时，可能会对代表性不足的少数群体产生不利影响。在过去的几年里，关于消除此类要求的讨论越来越多，不仅是为了加强种族正义，也是为了在紧张的就业市场中挖掘更多的高潜力候选人。尽管有些人可能将其解释为一种“降低标准”以增强多样性的形式，但应该指出的是，与绩效无关的标准是不必要的，而且可能是非法的，并可能导致员工资格过高，这可能对员工的态度产生负面影响，以及存在和表现。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>使用您的数据（以及相关其他人的数据）来确定工作相关性并消除不会提高您利润的障碍。</p><h3>选择潜力，训练绩效</h3><p>尽管大学投入大量资源为学生的职业做好准备，但毕业生所拥有的能力水平和雇主所期望的能力水平不可避免地存在不足。例如，全国大学和雇主协会表示，雇主几乎一致认为沟通是最重要的能力，几乎所有学生都知道这一点。然而，尽管 80% 的学生认为自己非常擅长沟通，但只有 47% 的雇主也这样看待学生。关键是，超过一半的雇主认为毕业生缺乏最重要的能力。显然，53% 的雇主认为大学毕业生不是非常熟练的沟通者，他们不会留下空缺职位。如果是的话，2022年大学毕业生的失业率就不会是4%。相反，许多（如果不是大多数）雇主认识到，他们需要投资于培训，以使新员工能够跟上进度。</p><p></p><p>以种族中立但有效的方式识别潜力当然说起来容易做起来难。一般来说，用于选择员工的指标与员工的实际工作越接近越好。这表明高保真模拟、工作样本和行为锚定结构化访谈等工具可能特别有用。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>选择方法还应侧重于确定可培训性，以确保组织能够最大限度地提高其培训投资的回报。这可能需要为顶尖候选人提供机会，通过积极学习新的与工作相关的能力并随后展示他们的熟练程度来展示他们的可培训性。</p><p></p><p>在过去的半个世纪中，平权行动及其后代帮助改变了美国学院、大学和组织的种族面貌。这些计划是通过为那些历史表明不太可能（或至少不太可能）获得这些机会的人提供机会来实现这一目标的。选择“<em>机会</em>”这个词既是有意的，也是重要的，因为许多人常常忽视这样一个事实：这些计划只给予受益人表明他们归属的机会。尽管最高法院的裁决消除了一种有助于公平竞争的手段，但正如亚历山大·格雷厄姆·贝尔曾经说过的那样，“当一扇门关闭时，另一扇门就会打开。”尽管这条道路似乎不太明确，但创新型公司将通过寻找、吸引和选择来自<em>所有</em>种族和民族背景的最有才华的人才来创造和保持竞争优势。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>提出提升沟通技能的理由</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a>是硅谷通信公司<a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a>的首席执行官。她是六本书的作者，包括<cite>《DataStory：解释数据》和《通过故事激发行动》</cite> （Ideapress Publishing，2019 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[ROI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It’s hard to find a job posting that doesn’t mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Duarte-Upskilling-ROI-pie-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>公司表示，他们迫切需要能够有效沟通的员工——领导们在研讨会上一直告诉我这一点——但有多少人是真心实意的呢？很难找到一份<em>没有</em>提到沟通技能作为关键要求的招聘启事。然而，当面对候选人实际拥有的技能和他们薄弱的技能时，招聘经理发现自己在做出权衡，特别是为了满足紧迫的技术需求：<em>这个人可以像没有明天一样编码，但他的沟通很糟糕一个挑战。我们快点把他弄到这里来吧。我们会辅导他。它可以等待。</em></p><p>问题是，沟通技巧<em>不能</em>等待。人力资源、学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 等“人员职能”领域的高管明白，沟通和说服技巧在所有业务领域都至关重要，甚至在软件开发和会计领域也是如此。那些设计、管理、实施和跟踪员工发展计划的人已经知道善于影响组织中的同事和其他人所带来的商业利益。</p><p></p><p>那么，您如何向组织中的深刻怀疑者（例如，数据科学家们轻蔑地看待“说服”一词，将其视为<em>操纵的</em><em>委婉</em>说法）表明，在沟通技巧上进行认真投资是值得的？</p><p>您可以通过为投资回报提供可靠的理由来做到这一点。你可以从 L&amp;D 的那些人那里得到启发。他们对衡量培训计划投资回报率的方法以及传达这些人才的好处的最佳方式进行了长时间的思考。</p><h3>基于测量的案例，提高软技能</h3><p>在最近为我公司客户举办的一次活动中，我们的客户执行副总裁主持了一场小组讨论，讨论大型技术品牌建立软技能的方式以及投资回报率对他们的影响。两位 L&amp;D 高管分享了他们在组织中传达这种价值的发现：Catherine (Cat) Lang，负责为 ServiceNow 的客户和合作伙伴提供产品培训和认证，ServiceNow 是一家位于加利福尼亚州圣克拉拉的数字工作流程公司；诺埃尔·安德森 (Noelle Anderson)，Snap 的支持总监，Snap 是视觉消息应用 Snapchat 的母公司。以下是他们谈话中的五个关键见解。</p><h4>收集您在之前的培训中看到的投资回报率示例。</h4><p>一种开始方法是回顾组织中以前的学习工作，看看可以为利益相关者联系哪些点。例如，在您的组织取得重大胜利（例如获得利润丰厚的项目或赢得主要客户）之前，是否举办过有关呈现数据的内部研讨会？明确这种相关性并指出其他类似的相关性。您的某些软技能培训的投资回报率记录可能比您意识到的要多。</p><p></p><h4>帮助确定未来培训的价值。</h4><p>当您考虑或开发未来的培训时，请寻找更直接的方法来衡量技能提升的结果。例如，在 Snap，支持团队开发了一个推介辅导计划，销售人员、客户经理和创意策略师共同合作，为现有客户开发推介。参与者在制定、构建和练习自己的演讲时，会从经验丰富的沟通者那里获得大量指导和发展反馈——这是报名参加该计划的一大动力。他们还通过制作真实的推介内容来创造真实的、可衡量的价值。</p><p>回报——无论是续签合同还是销售新产品或服务——都是可以量化的。 “我们在后端所做的，”Anderson 说，“是与我们的 CRM 团队合作，在 Salesforce 中创建一个复选框，以表明每个演示是否是我们推介计划的一部分。”从那里，团队可以筛选出哪些推介带来了收入。</p><p>尽管 Snap 的 Anderson 团队向销售团队而不是公司 L&amp;D 汇报，但他们与 L&amp;D 作为“姐妹团队”合作，以确定和培养销售方面所需的软技能。这种方法可以在两个方向上带来红利：整个组织的团队可以向 L&amp;D 报告其领域的投资回报率证据，从而支持对全公司学习计划的进一步投资。就其本身而言，学习型组织可以就哪些类型的发展可以提高员工满意度和保留率分享更广泛的见解。 L&amp;D 可以根据团队认为哪些方面对日常绩效和销售影响最大来完善其技能建设计划。</p><h4>认识到质量影响——包括更好的员工保留率。</h4><p>即使有类似推介计划之类的东西，也很难用冷硬的美元来计算软技能培训的成本——尤其是当培训是由人力资源员工在内部进行或由经理和同事非正式地进行时。其好处也很难衡量，因为技能提升的大部分价值是间接的。</p><p>例如，考虑一下推介计划对员工的主要好处之一：提高高层领导的知名度。这对个人和组织都有回报，但不会立即体现在资产负债表上。安德森表示，批量的提案会分轮开发和呈现，到第三轮时，提案最好的两个小组可以向执行团队展示他们的想法，以获得更多反馈，然后再与客户分享任何内容。</p><p>当然，与高管的这些互动可以让推销本身变得更好。但想想其他好处：它们启动了指导关系，开辟了更多的发展和成长机会以及更多的晋升之门——所有这些都可以增强员工的体验、积极性和忠诚度。</p><p>你能量化这些结果吗？有时你做不到，所以你可以定性地衡量价值。这可能意味着就培训计划对员工行为、工作效率和团队合作方法的影响征求经理和团队领导的意见。从员工的角度考虑定性影响也很重要，因为人才保留对投资回报率具有重大影响。要证明这些无形资产为何重要，请考虑<a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/03/09/majority-of-workers-who-quit-a-job-in-2021-cite-low-pay-no-opportunities-for-advancement-feeling-disrespected/">皮尤研究中心 2022 年的一项调查</a>，该调查发现“没有晋升机会”和“工资太低”是美国工人离职的首要原因。或者考虑一下 LinkedIn 2022 年 3 月的《 <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220506202443/https://business.linkedin.com/glint/resources/employee-well-being-report-march-2022">员工福祉报告</a>》的调查结果，该报告发现工作文化的第一大驱动力是“学习和成长的机会”。</p><p> Lang 表示，在 ServiceNow，她的团队正在“关注员工保留率和对发展的满意度”，并将这些“与我们的员工声音调查非常非常紧密地联系起来”，以全面了解技能提升对保留率的影响。她说，“当我们开始试行新的软技能项目时，她看到了快速的采用。”人们对 Snap 的此类技能提升也表现出了浓厚的兴趣：安德森表示，员工将其视为公司重视他们的证据，因为它“通过对个人及其发展进行投资，展示了对个人的信任”。她还指出，“这些技能可以帮助人们在内心获得自己的动力、自己的行动，并以人们真正会做出反应的方式提出自己的想法。”</p><h4>制定策略，确定首先关注哪些类型的工作。</h4><p>与任何组织变革工作一样，提高员工技能需要战略规划。为了帮助这样的计划获得关注，在更广泛地推广之前，确定您将在哪里看到最大的直接回报并计划集中在那里是很有用的。</p><p></p><p> Lang 在 ServiceNow 的团队首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员，因为他们对日常工作的完成方式有很大的发言权，并负责使员工的努力与组织目标保持一致。他们越早清晰地传达这些目标并制定令人信服的绩效目标，公司就能越早获得实现这些目标的回报。首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员也会产生级联效应，使他们能够通过一对一的辅导、指导对话，甚至是课程或其他学习内容的推荐，与团队分享他们所学到的知识。</p><p>安德森说，另一方面，Snap 更愿意首先提高一线经理的技能。因为她负责监督销售组织的学习，而员工的沟通技巧对客户关系有直接影响，所以她认为第一线是投资回报最快的地方。</p><h4>正面解决时间紧迫的问题。</h4><p></p><p>即使组织的利益相关者同意，在理想的情况下，他们应该优先帮助员工掌握软技能，但时间限制也会使其变得困难。在重要事项与紧急事项之间的长期斗争中，紧急事项往往会赢得领导者的关注和资源。安德森描述了她所谓的“此时此地”有时如何妨碍 Snap 实现更广泛的学习目标：“在很多课程中，人们都会说，‘我太兴奋了。我等不及要走了。他们出现了，但随后就不得不退出。”工作承诺和最后期限常常让人心烦意乱。</p><p></p><p>从文化上解决这一挑战的一种方法是公开承认它，并展示如何在学习计划和课程设计中适应它。创造这样一种期望：人们只在力所能及的范围内参与就可以了。考虑将内容分成更短的模块或小型研讨会，以便忙碌的员工更容易消化。在工作日留出时间用于技能发展。学习者在工作场所需要这种类型的支持，组织也会受益。如果高管犹豫不决，请提醒他们，让学习变得可行可以提高投资回报率<em>，并</em>在紧张的劳动力市场中增强员工对组织的承诺。</p><p>您可能需要稍微调整项目截止日期，或者在人们进行开发工作时减少他们的任务，这样他们就不会感到在下班后做“真正”工作的压力。开发<em>是</em>实实在在的工作。作为管理者，要以这种方式对待它，并与利益相关者进行讨论。如果您已采取措施帮助他们了解投资的所有好处，那么销售就会更容易。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>首席执行官可以促成（或破坏）组织重新设计</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz. <p><a href="https://akordeon.com/who-we-are/">Herman Vantrappen</a>是 Akordeon 的董事总经理，这是一家总部位于布鲁塞尔的战略咨询公司。 Frederic Wirtz 是 The Little Group 的负责人，为全球各地的公司提供有关组织设计问题的建议。 Vantrappen 和 Wirtz 是<cite>《组织设计指南：深思熟虑、高效和成功的重新设计的实用框架》</cite> （Routledge，2023）的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com The Research This article draws on the dozens of major organization redesign exercises the authors have accompanied in the past 30 years across continents in a wide range of sectors, including B2B (such as payroll services) and B2C (such as fast-food retail), products (such as automotive) and services (such as engineering), and for-profit [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Vantrappen-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>本文借鉴了作者在过去 30 年中在各大洲的广泛领域进行的数十次重大组织重新设计实践，包括 B2B（例如薪资服务）和 B2C（例如快餐零售）、产品（例如汽车）和服务（例如工程），以及营利性和非营利性。</p></aside><p>首席执行官的基本职责之一是在认识到组织结构不再适合创造和交付价值后，领导重新配置组织的工作。有些重新设计是全公司范围内的重大改革，例如宝洁公司在 2019 年创建了六个基于行业的部门业务部门，其首席执行官将其描述为“过去 20 年来我们做出的最重大的组织变革”。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>其他重新设计工作的范围较小，侧重于特定的部门、功能或问题。</p><p>对于首席执行官来说，组织重新设计不同于其他大规模变革举措。例如，在公司战略调整中，首席执行官受董事会决策的约束，并遵循强有力的分析方法。在职能计划中，例如制定公司的数字战略，首席执行官可以将领导权委托给管理团队中的某人并承担监督角色。但在企业组织重新设计计划中，首席执行官必须积极带头，因为由此产生的变革将对文化和员工产生深远影响，也因为只有首席执行官拥有降低风险所需的全面视角。任何特定的重新设计选择都会产生严重的意外和不良后果。</p><p></p><p>多年来，我们在与组织的合作中见证了许多重新设计举措，并确认首席执行官对这些工作的领导是他们成功的关键。但令我们惊讶的是，有多少首席执行官仍在努力取得有效成果。我们发现，尽管管理文献中提供了大量且往往明智的建议，但计划经常会误入歧途或陷入死胡同。这里有些例子：</p><ul><li>商业服务提供商的新任首席执行官希望更广泛地重新考虑公司中心和组织的角色。管理团队的每个成员都有自己喜欢的重组想法：一个人受自组织团队的影响，另一个人坚持他们以前雇主使用的框架，第三个人认为公司应该只是一家小型企业的控股公司。区域性企业。即使是最小的对齐也需要很长时间。</li><li>多边机构的首席执行官发起了一项活动，以减少组织的孤立性。与管理团队的激烈辩论和几次异地会议导致了许多重大决策，包括共享资源和扩大首席执行官控制范围的计划。但经过一些幕后操纵后，决定被撤销了。</li><li>一家家族工程和建筑公司的创始人兼首席执行官退休，将权力移交给了他的一个孩子。新领导者计划使公司的业务流程和治理专业化，但退休的创始人却不断想方设法绕过首席执行官，破坏改善公司运作的任何努力。</li></ul><p>当我们回顾过去 30 年来所进行的重大组织重新设计（参见“研究”）并反思为什么某些举措不如其他举措有效时，我们认识到首席执行官可能会陷入以下两个陷阱之一：使用适当的框架，而且很简单，未能在整个过程中保持足够的领导力。在本文中，我们将提出首席执行官可以遵循的组织重新设计的系统方法，并解决高管如果要在整个组织重新设计和实施过程中保留完全所有权就必须防止的特定行为。</p><h3>应对组织重新设计的框架</h3><p>许多学者和顾问开发了支持组织设计系统思考的框架。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>我们在此介绍的框架强调了两个经常被忽视的方面。</p><p>首先，该框架认识到管理者在重新设计组织时永远不会从零开始。总有一个现有的组织可以为任何重新设计提供重要信息。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>即使现有设计已变得功能失调，最初采用它通常也有充分的理由，并且这些理由不应被忽视。因此，一个好的框架需要包含过去和未来之间的动态联系。</p><p>其次，管理文献中当前的大部分建议都集中在计划的上游方面（例如，确定公司的目的、价值观和愿景）或下游方面（例如执行和变革管理）。关于该学科的中游核心——即结构、流程和系统等硬性内容——的讨论较少。一个好的框架应该恢复这个重要的中游部分，同时将其与上游部分（通过考虑变革的驱动因素）和下游部分（通过确保第一天上线做好准备）无缝集成。</p><p>我们通过工作逐步开发的框架旨在通过尊重变革的动态本质并关注硬组织设计变量来克服这两个缺点。从第一条原则出发，它将组织设计思维的各个组成部分整合成一个逻辑流程，从理解组织<em>变革的驱动因素</em>到<em>概念设计</em>的选项、<em>详细设计的</em>可操作性、<em>过渡</em>阶段的实施以及重组的实际<em>执行</em>过程中必要的路线修正。 （参见“组织重新设计指南”。） </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>组织重新设计指南</h4><p class="caption">该框架将熟悉的构建块集成到逻辑流程中，以指导重组计划。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig1.jpg" alt="组织重新设计指南"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>处于组织重新设计前端的首席执行官需要了解此框架中突出的五个总体原则：</p><p> <strong>1. 组织是达到目的的手段。</strong>管理者改变组织设计，期望新的设计能够更好地帮助公司实现其业务目标。该期望基于以下假设：这些目标将明确、得到管理团队的接受、利益相关者的认可，并保持相当稳定。一家目标模糊或波动的公司很可能会经历破坏性的组织重组，而其业绩却没有太大改善。这就是为什么我们的设计框架首先要确定变革的外部和内部驱动因素。</p><p> <strong>2. 最好的设计是不可知的。</strong>可以说，做出组织设计选择比做出业务战略选择更困难。战略选择归结为从各种替代方案中选择一种能够最大化既定目标（例如 EBITDA 增长）的方案。通过战略，领导者权衡可用信息、假设和不确定性、资源限制以及他们自己的风险偏好。组织选择则不然。它们不是来自数学优化，而是来自对支持和反对多种设计方案中每一种的论据权重的判断。这就是为什么设计框架鼓励首席执行官考虑替代组织概念。</p><p> <strong>3.概念设计先于详细设计——只有后者才是参与性的。</strong>在概念阶段，定义了新设计的原则。这些涉及基本的组织变量，特别是架构（例如，集中什么和分散什么）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>在考虑替代设计概念后，选择一个并进行详细设计（例如，端到端业务流程中各种功能的角色）。详细设计可以而且应该在管理者和直接相关人员的广泛参与下完成：他们最了解什么是有效的，必须在设计结果范围内运作，并且可以充当变革大使。然而，很少建议在概念设计中采用这种参与式方法，因为概念设计往往需要熟悉公司的（通常仍然是机密的）愿景和战略选择，避免与公司各种职能的命运和速度有关的利益冲突。</p><p> <strong>4. 组织设计通过故意跳跃和紧急跳跃的模式演变。</strong>深思熟虑的战略和紧急战略的概念在战略制定的学科中根深蒂固：在公司深思熟虑的战略的指导下，组织中各级经理每天都会做出无数的决策，逐渐改变该战略的具体形式。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>在组织设计中也观察到类似的模式：高级管理层有意决定对组织进行重大重新安排（飞跃），之后进行一系列调整（跳跃）以弥补原始设计中不可避免的缺陷。这种跳跃式的模式是完全正常的，甚至是可取的，因为完美的设计是难以捉摸的，而且公司的环境一直在变化。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>这就是为什么设计框架会显示循环，将缺陷反馈回设计中，以便解决这些问题。</p><p> <strong>5. 设计的证明仅在第一天后才会公布。</strong>第一天是指批准的详细设计投入使用的那一刻，重新设计开始对大量人员的日常运作产生直接影响：他们做什么、如何做以及与谁一起做。为了管理信誉、尊重员工以及对业务的影响，错误应该尽可能少。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>因此，在第一天之前就开始仔细的变革管理流程至关重要。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>任何员工都不应该对自己在重新设计的组织中的地位一无所知。</p><p></p><h3>为什么首席执行官的持续参与很重要</h3><p>在战略制定过程中，首席执行官通过一段时间内的临时干预措施来保持参与可能是完全足够的，例如参加异地高管会议、领导指导委员会或向董事会汇报。另一方面，在组织设计练习中，我们发现最高效的首席执行官几乎每天从开始到结束都密切关注流程的脉搏。</p><p>他们这样做的原因之一是，这为他们提供了形成自己关于适合目的的设计的想法的机会，并可能从根本上改变他们的思维模式。他们花时间让自己的想法成熟，因为没有单一的最佳设计，最终的选择很大程度上是对许多有效替代方案的定性判断。</p><p>他们还始终如一地参与，因为他们意识到组织设计过程是相当无情的。每个阶段都建立在前一阶段做出的选择的基础上，逐渐涉及越来越多的人。在此过程中做出的明确或隐含的微观承诺的数量——关于角色、边界、界限、人员、人数和其他因素——不断增加。不得不回头是痛苦的，部分原因是它是广泛可见的。如果说战略制定就像种树，那么组织设计就像种草：其效果立竿见影、遍及各处，需要引起重视。</p><p></p><p>日常参与的第三个原因是帮助组织内部建立对新设计的认可。高效的首席执行官坚持充分参与有关设计活动结果的沟通，与其说是通过众所周知的“致全体员工的备忘录”，不如说是通过与现场人员交谈。只有全身心投入到实际的设计工作中，他们才能做到可信和令人信服。</p><p>最重要的是，首席执行官每天都会参与这个过程，因为他们认识到人员和互动最终将成就（或破坏）组织。充分参与设计过程为首席执行官提供了独特的机会，可以观察和影响直接报告之外的企业人员方面。</p><h3>领导力弱点如何破坏重新设计</h3><p>在我们观察到的领导者无法完全控制上述重新设计过程的情况下，他们的弱点往往反映出以下四个特征之一：三心二意、绥靖、优柔寡断或无能。我们根据对组织重新设计工作的观察，提炼出以下四种原型：</p><p><strong>半心半意的首席执行官。</strong>虽然战略制定活动的触发点往往很明确，但组织设计活动可能是由某些利益相关者的游说而不是明确的业务需求推动的。在某些情况下，管理团队或董事会成员可能会提出疑虑。首席执行官可能最初并不认为这种担忧很重要，或者倾向于发起变革，但他们可能希望让利益相关者满意，结束辩论，从而同意考虑组织重新设计——私下里认为这些计划不会有任何进展。或者，首席执行官可能对重新设计的动机感到困惑、不清楚或守口如瓶，让项目团队来填补空白。在其他情况下，首席执行官可能会自愿或非自愿地离职。在所有这些情况下，首席执行官在项目开始时都缺乏充分的承诺，导致项目开局不利。</p><p><strong>绥靖的首席执行官。</strong>每一次转型都需要仔细的变革管理，通过深思熟虑的活动将公司从目前的状态转变为期望的未来状态，并帮助人们采用变革。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>然而，首席执行官在邀请人们参与时可能会太过分，这可能会导致流程过于复杂，步骤、参与者和审批点过多。例如，邀请更多评论而不是做出决定并冻结流程可能会拖延设计阶段。旨在表现出倾听意愿的安抚行为通常是出于好意，旨在发挥利益相关者管理的作用，但它也可以反映出首席执行官自己对设计概念的不确定性。</p><p><strong>优柔寡断的首席执行官。</strong>决策无能、无法做出决策或坚持坚定决策的首席执行官虽然很少见，但并未绝迹。一个典型的症状是，首席执行官在后期“在我的尸体上”威胁屈服，而经理不同意经过深思熟虑的执行团队决策。由于担心产生负面影响，首席执行官有时会在最后阶段做出妥协。在这样的组织中，不管首席执行官如何，事情都会发生。</p><p><strong>丧失行为能力的首席执行官。</strong>有缺陷的治理可能会让首席执行官很难在整个过程中掌控重新设计。在首席执行官不兼任董事会主席的公司中，董事会可能会干扰首席执行官对组织重新设计的处理。在私营公司中，退休创始人等有权势的董事会成员可能会干预设计并让首席执行官短路，保护旧的最爱或以其他方式扰乱有序的流程。这种对首席执行官的损害——无论是在概念设计、详细设计还是过渡阶段——通常在较低层次上是可见的，并且具有很高的破坏性。</p><p>计划重新设计组织的首席执行官最好考虑这些领导力薄弱的模式。他们应该根据自己的特质和阻碍其领导力的背景因素来评估自己的脆弱性，然后考虑如何克服这些脆弱性。</p><p>他们可以首先问自己四个问题：</p><ol><li>我完全相信这个倡议吗？</li><li>我会听取正确的人的意见而不让流程偏离正轨吗？</li><li>我是否准备好在需要时做出艰难的决定并坚持下去？</li><li>我能控制我需要拉动的所有杠杆吗？</li></ol><p>这种反省很重要，因为一旦首席执行官了解他们在这一关键变革工作中的领导力可能薄弱的地方，他们就可以努力减轻这些弱点。 （参见“首席执行官如何减少他们的脆弱性。”）想象一下，一位知道自己倾向于安抚的首席执行官。他们可能认识到，在概念阶段，他们应该咨询有限的高级管理人员，在过渡阶段，他们应该采用一种“遵守或解释”流程（当任何与概念设计的偏差必须得到解释和解释时）只有在获得批准该概念的治理机构批准后才能接受）并冻结设计，向员工保证公司将在启动后根据需要进行路线修正。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性</h4><p class="caption">倾向于四种可能破坏组织重新设计的行为原型中的任何一种的首席执行官可以在流程的每个阶段采取行动来加强他们的领导力。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig2.png" alt="首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>我们与一家工业公司的首席执行官合作，他承认自己有一些无能力和优柔寡断的典型特征。他能够通过一些聪明的、具体的方式来弥补可能导致进程脱轨的倾向：</p><ul><li>由于首席执行官几乎经常出差，他任命了一位具有互补技能的首席变革官，与他密切合作，负责总部的日常项目事务。然而，首席执行官仍然负责这项工作。</li><li>首席执行官提议让公司的提名和薪酬委员会在概念设计阶段充当指导委员会。这为董事会主席提供了一个受管理的渠道，董事会主席对运营事务的频繁干预有时会损害首席执行官的利益。</li><li>在概念设计阶段的结果得到提名和薪酬委员会正式认可并得到董事会批准后，首席执行官能够在详细设计阶段更轻松地实施“遵守或解释”规则。为了避免概念蔓延，任何偏离概念的行为都必须再次通过委员会。</li><li>首席执行官鼓励公司各部门和职能部门各自任命一名过渡阶段大使。这些代表属于各自部门和职能的管理团队，并参与了详细设计阶段。他们每月与首席变革官会面，分享双向进展信息。</li><li>在上线之前，使用一个简单的跟踪器来监控一系列特定过渡目标的进展情况。完成百分比统计数据由首席执行官定期审核，并根据部门和职能公开发布。这产生了一些健康的同行压力，并帮助该过程保持吸引力。</li></ul><p></p><p>这个例子表明，首席执行官对他们明显的行为倾向以及可以防止重新设计工作脱轨的行动进行一些预先、明确和诚实的反思是值得的。</p><p></p><p>持续的组织重新设计是企业生活的一个事实。在大多数情况下，考虑重新设计有充分的商业理由，尽管它往往会消耗大量的额外时间、资源和情感能量。但要使重新设计取得成功，需要首席执行官的全力参与。然而，即便如此，重新设计工作也常常会误入歧途。首席执行官可能缺乏适当的设计框架，或者根本无法在整个过程中保持足够的领导力。他们应该首先评估自己的弱点——包括自己的行为倾向和与治理相关的限制。他们应该找到方法来证明他们是全心全意的、结论性的、果断的，并且最终是掌控一切的。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>向人工智能学习并利用人工智能学习：Duolingo 的 Zan Gilani</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Cognitive Technologies]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gamification]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Zan Gilani came to the U.S. from Pakistan to complete his undergraduate studies, he chose to study Chinese because it was rumored to be a difficult language. At the time, the tech industry was booming, and he quickly became interested in applying his passion for foreign languages and learning more generally in a technology-rich [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当赞·吉拉尼从巴基斯坦来到美国完成本科学业时，他选择学习汉语，因为据传汉语是一门很难的语言。当时，科技行业正在蓬勃发展，他很快就对运用自己对外语的热情产生了兴趣，并在技术丰富的环境中进行更广泛的学习。</p><p>这些兴趣促使 Zan 加入了 Duolingo，他在产品管理领域工作了八年，现在负责管理该应用公司的体验式人工智能团队。在这家语言学习应用公司工作，令他兴奋的是他能够帮助构建实现大规模个性化教育的解决方案：该应用拥有超过 1600 万的日常活跃用户，人工智能驱动的功能通过频繁的通知激励他们，个性化学习体验通过在练习中调整试题难度，观察和批评学习者的表现。</p><p> Zan 加入了<cite>Me、Myself 和 A​​I</cite>播客，概述了 Duolingo 使用 AI 和机器学习来推动用户参与的具体方式，并讨论了如何使用该技术来支持更广泛的学习。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E5-Gilani-Duolingo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="赞吉拉尼"></p><h4>赞吉拉尼，多邻国</h4><p>Zan Gilani 是 Duolingo 的首席产品经理。在过去的八年里，他通过致力于亚洲地区的保留、获取、增长、游戏化和新用户体验，帮助公司的学习者基础从 300 万增加到 1600 万。</p><p>他目前领导 Duolingo 的实验人工智能团队，该团队使用生成式人工智能来构建能够更有效地教授学习者的功能。更广泛地说，吉拉尼正致力于通过外部合作伙伴关系和内部教育，利用生成式人工智能让 Duolingo 取得成功。</p><p>吉拉尼在巴基斯坦卡拉奇长大，目前居住在纽约市。他拥有哥伦比亚大学政治学和东亚研究学士学位。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-gilani"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>学习一门新语言是一个复杂的过程。一家应用程序公司希望人工智能能够帮助实现个性化、情境和动机。了解更多今天的节目。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我是来自 Duolingo 的 Zan Gilani，你们正在听的是<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天，我和 Shervin 与 Duolingo 首席产品经理 Zan Gilani 进行了交谈。我个人对今天的节目感到非常兴奋，因为 Duolingo 的处境非常有趣。在我们的很多节目中，我们最终都会讨论组织如何使用人工智能来增强或改进人类决策，这很棒。但 Duolingo 更进一步，专注于人类如何利用人工智能学习——大规模个性化教育，这对我很有吸引力。无论如何，这对我来说已经足够了。让我们听听Zan的说法。赞，感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>谢谢。很高兴来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Zan，首先，您能给我们介绍一下 Duolingo 和公司吗？您的角色是什么？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>当然。 Duolingo 基本上是一个教授语言的应用程序。我们目前教授 40 多种语言。顺便说一句，这些人中的大多数人都在学习英语，而我们的大多数学习者也在手机上学习，因此 Android 和 iOS 设备也是如此。我们是下载次数最多、使用最多的教育应用程序，无论是语言还是其他方面。我们拥有约 1600 万 DAU（日活跃用户）和 40 多万月活跃用户。我在公司工作刚刚八年，担任实验人工智能团队的首席产品经理。</p><p>我的主要职责是领导这个团队，致力于利用生成式人工智能更有效地进行教学，而且更广泛地说，我帮助公司在生成式人工智能方面取得成功。</p><p>我们现在专门针对生成式人工智能的主要用例之一是新的订阅层。 Duolingo 是一款免费增值产品。使命是提供尽可能最高质量的教育[并]让尽可能多的人[尽可能]获得教育；您所需要的只是互联网连接。所以我们有这个应用程序的免费版本，这是大多数人使用的。这非常好;公司的大多数人都花时间在这上面。然后我们有订阅级别。</p><p>我们最近刚刚推出了一个新的人工智能订阅层，名为 Duolingo Max，我也很高兴介绍其功能。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以实验性人工智能……它有点像你的研发实验室，如果你愿意的话？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>嗯，我想说的是，实际上公司一半以上的人都在广泛地从事研发工作——所有从事产品工作的人，以及致力于有效学习或教学的人，你可以认为是的，它作为一个实验室。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>太棒了。也许，对于我们的观众来说，您可以列出正在使用人工智能的各种用例或场所。当然，我的意思是，[除了]许多应用程序都具有的显而易见的个性化和游戏化功能。但请告诉我们人工智能是如何被使用的。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong> Duolingo 自该应用程序问世以来就一直在使用人工智能，距今已有十年之久。事实上，它是由卡内基梅隆大学计算机科学教授 Luis von Ahn 和他当时的研究生 Severin Hacker 创立的。目前，它有多种不同的使用方式。例如，在增长方面，大量工作都用于优化通知。</p><p> Duolingo 与其他应用程序的不同之处在于，它确实试图帮助您保持动力。对于我们来说，从教学角度来说，我们认为学习语言最困难的事情实际上是保持动力，因为请记住：这是一件很难做到的事情。自己用手机来做这件事尤其困难——这确实是一件困难的事情。因此，通知以及收到通知的时间、通知所传达的信息确实会影响某人长期坚持使用通知的能力。因此，我们在通知的机器学习上投入了大量精力。</p><p>我们还在内容生成方面使用它，因此我们正在尝试创建有用的、合适的内容；我们也在那里使用它。然后，在该公司的一个独立部门中，即 Duolingo 英语测试，这基本上是学生上大学时必须参加的英语水平测试——有点像托福、托业或雅思的竞争对手；大多数美国人没有经历过这种情况——我们用它来检测作弊行为。我们还使用它在许多不同的地方生成内容。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这很有趣。该应用程序的实际核心是教你语言，它的动态程度如何？当它适应一个人的学习方式时，它的个性化程度如何？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>个性化发挥了一定作用，但很多体验是由学习科学家和教育内容开发人员策划的。对于大多数人来说，您想要学习的顺序大致相似。例如，每个人都会先学习现在时，然后再学习其他复杂时态。但是，我们使用人工智能进行个性化的地方是专门用于“Birdbrain”的系统，这基本上是我们拥有的一个系统，它针对您将在练习中看到的问题的难度进行优化。</p><p>关于 Duolingo 需要注意的一件事是它是完全互动的。这意味着感觉就像一场游戏。所以每次你学习的时候，你都在回答一个小练习，然后你就会做对或做错。你总是会得到反馈。所以 Birdbrain 的重点是尝试提出一个金发姑娘级别的难度，因为基本上，如果某件事太难，你就会感到沮丧，并且会失去动力。如果某件事太简单了，它就会变得无聊，你就会失去动力。 Birdbrain 是我们特别用于个性化练习的东西之一。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Shervin，我认为有趣的一件事是，在描述他的产品时，我们只是认为语音合成、语音识别是理所当然的。这些在10年前都是前卫的东西，而现在昝，你连AI的应用都懒得提了。我认为这有点后退一步，看看现在的情况是正常的。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。我认为你拥有的一件非常有趣而且可能是独一无二的事情就是你必须拥有的反馈循环的数量。我的意思是，通常，在许多其他应用程序中，当您考虑企业、零售、银行和电信等时，需要一些时间才能获得反馈。而且你几乎可以从很多人那里得到关于如此多的实验或小型实验的即时反馈。也许可以告诉我们更多关于学习速度和算法适应速度的信息。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>这里有一个很好的反映，那就是我们试图将一些有效学习的原则传递到产品本身中。然后，作为一家公司和一个组织，我们也试图按照这些原则运作。当您学习语言时，获得快速反馈确实很重要。但当你致力于产品本身时，这一点也很重要，而且，从很早的时候起，我们基本上就构建了自己的 A/B 测试基础设施，它是产品流程的核心；这是我们在 Duolingo 生产产品的核心组成部分。</p><p>在任何给定的时刻，您都会在非常细粒度的事物上运行数百个实验 - 按钮的位置[指示]页面上我们订阅价格的定价，您经典的面包和黄油实验 -还有巨大的新功能、新标签。基本上，如果这不是一个错误，那么我们可能正在以实验的形式运行它。我们在这方面做得非常非常好、非常老练。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Shervin 会翻白眼，因为我要讲一点学术知识，但你是体验式学习的典型案例。事实上，我将在这里给大家介绍一下你们的<a href="https://blog.duolingo.com/duolingo-max/">Max 产品</a>，因为我认为其中有两个非常令人兴奋的部分。有角色扮演，它涉及体验式学习的学术、具体经验部分，然后是解释我的答案，这是一种反思性观察和批评。请告诉我们一些关于这两者的信息以及它们如何与学习成果联系起来。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>当然。我认为讨论一下在添加这两个功能之前我们所处的位置是有用的。在教学上，Duolingo 一直致力于隐性学习，因此无需明确告诉您“这就是您要学习的内容，这就是它的运作方式”。这就是体验的本质，因为我们认为当你这样做时，它会更加自动化。人们还被复杂的语法表等变得非常振奋，并推迟了，第二个是您在应用程序上学习的，而您正在做这种交互式的事情 - 这些几乎是游戏性的练习。</p><p>缺失或限制的两件事是，第一，有些人确实想要解释，如果以正确的数量和方式进行解释，这可能会非常高效和有效。因此，“解释我的答案”是该问题的解决方案，而“解释我的答案”的好处确实只有在现代大型语言模型的帮助下才能发挥作用，即大型语言模型非常擅长为您所犯的错误提供通俗易懂的简明解释。制作。即使对于老师来说，在不使用行话且不花钱的情况下尝试做到这一点也确实很困难。因此，我们可以通过“解释我的答案”很好地做到这一点。它可以给你后续的插图，它可以给你例子——所有这些都可以构成大型语言模型，顺便说一句，对任何试图自学任何东西的人来说都是有好处的。对我来说，这改变了我的生活。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>或者任何想要发表演讲的人。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>或者任何想要发表演讲的人，是的。第二个，角色扮演，最终对大多数人来说，语言学习不是一项学术活动。他们试图将其用作现实世界中的一种技能，而这本身就是一种技能。那么如何赋予人们实践这一能力的能力呢？你如何让他们模拟这个？聊天机器人正是做到这一点的一种方法，因为现在，你所拥有的东西可以在你所处的难度级别上与你交谈，具有无限的耐心，然后也可以在事后真正给你反馈。</p><p>即使人们可以接触到以英语为母语的人（他们通常不会这样做），您仍然需要一个具有无限耐心并且真正能够理解您正在寻找的内容的以英语为母语的人。所以 Roleplay 基本上是在尝试在应用程序中提供这种体验，而不是仅仅拥有像 ChatGPT 这样的文本界面，然后让你来回说话。基本上，我们所做的就是将对话或场景分解为这些小规模的体验，你正在与一个聊天机器人交谈，他将成为咖啡师或你要借东西的朋友，然后你尝试经历一个非常具体、短暂的经历。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>山姆，我有一个问题要问你，因为山姆，如你所知，是一位杰出的教授，他一直在教人们——包括像我这样不在他班上的人——很多东西。所以我的问题，萨姆，是......不过，严肃地说，在你看来，什么才是一个好老师？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>实际上，Zan 突然提到了几件事，这就是为什么我在他的谈话中感到有些内疚的部分原因。他所说的无限耐心——这非常重要，但也非常困难。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>不切实际。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>是的。与他们见面的人是我们在教育方面遇到的一个基本问题。我的意思是，我坐在一个有35、40个人的房间前，他们不是同质的。与Zan所说的正是他们所在的人。所以，是的，您必须很好地了解材料，您必须保持人们的参与，但是您还必须跟踪人们的位置和他们所知道的 - 现在的东西并不容易，也不是太难了 - 我对此模型非常吸引人。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>那么，下一步是什么？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，是的，这正是我要去的地方。下一步是什么？我的意思是，如果我们可以用语言做到这一点，我们还能做什么？它在哪里工作？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我的意思是语言。因此，会见他们所在的人，对学生及其进步有很好的了解，然后能够做角色扮演和大量的体验学习，并能够以更无术的方式解释和指导和指导您可以重复的方式，我不必急于做笔记。我的意思是，所有这些事情，对吗？缺什么？我听到这一点，这比普通老师更好，听起来像是。但是，您认为，这是一位完美的老师，这是什么缺少的？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>出于多种原因，我认为我们仍然是一个完美的老师，还有很长的路要走。我还说，我们不相信，我当然不相信，归根结底，您所需要的只是一个聊天界面，大多数人都将能够与他们相处得很远试图学习。因此，要回答第一部分，为什么我们离老师很远，我认为其中一些是未知的，但是在学习时与另一个人建立关系有真正的影响。</p><p>学习新知识有一个情感的一部分，并且有一种人类的联系可以像您出现在辅导约会的情况下一样简单，因为您不想让老师失望，也可以导师可以通过他们的声音节奏，可以说出他们可以说出的插图，与他们可能与自己的生活有关的方式来真正与他们的面部表情相关。</p><p>这样，我们仍然远离。然后，当谈到“嘿，为什么聊天机器人不能教你一切？”对于大多数人来说，您仍然必须组织起来，并且组织起来很累。例如，仅仅决定接下来要吃什么是您所有时间都在做的事情，或者决定要看什么电影。同样，决定接下来要学习什么也很艰难。因此，产品方面的某人必须弄清楚事物的正确测序供您学习。</p><p>同样，创造力也很累。对于现实生活中的老师来说，他们真的很难扮演许多不同的角色并做很多角色扮演。然后，您需要一个也是一位出色演员的导师。 AI使您有能力与虚拟老师一起做到这一点，但是即使那样，我们也不希望学习者一直想出这些情况。</p><p>我要提到的最后两件事是，学习也是多感觉的。这也是上下文。理想情况下，您想要的是某种学习和上下文也发生的，而不仅仅是聊天机器人。</p><p>要提到的最后一件事是，人们确实确实需要一种进步感才能保持学习语言，因为实际的进步是如此慢，如此逐渐，因此很难看到。因此，您必须要做的是，您必须向人们展示正在填补的人，并且必须签入。我认为您可能会在导师的体验中模拟某些方法，但是这些是其中的一些方法我认为我们也关心在此之外建立经验并建立您走的道路的原因，以及使Duolingo成为现实的所有其他事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Zan，我想回到您所吸引的一件事，[]这就是弄清楚您需要学习的下一件事的想法。我的意思是，从历史上看，我在语言中所拥有的每个班级，我们都有一本书，我们从第1章转移到第2章。有人在某个地方真正地思考了这一顺序。</p><p>但是与此同时，我不知道这对所有学生来说都是最佳的。我们考虑推荐系统和Netflix或音乐中；你知道，我们已经与Spotify，Shervin进行了交谈。这似乎是一个很好的机会。我现在能学到的一件事是最大的差异？还是我不知道的一件事是让我无法打开下一节？这似乎是一个巨大的机会。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>是的。我也会将其分成两块。通常，其中一个是什么有效学习的命令，什么是有效的教学命令？对于那些先前熟练程度的人来说，这特别有用，大多数人试图在Duolingo学习一种语言，尤其是英国学习者，因为他们以某种方式在学校做到了，而且他们的知识是零散的，正如我们喜欢说的。</p><p>在这种情况下，由于经历不同的经历，该命令将与一个人完全不同。然后，第二个方面是您需要专注于更多的事情，您特别遇到了麻烦。也许您只是为特定概念犯了更多错误。也许是动词偶像是问题所在，或者您只是不知道如何很好地介绍自己。因此，实际上有机会在这部分经验中花费更多的时间。</p><p>并不是说每个课程都是为一个独特的学生定制的，而是您将注意力和注意力以及投入的数量以及您所做的顺序进行的，由某种导师执导。我会说这是一件艰难的事情。这确实是一件艰难的事情。我们不在那儿，但这当然是梦的一部分。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以演出是<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite> ，我们对您和您自己的了解很多。因此，也许会告诉我们一些有关您的背景的信息 - 您最终如何担任这个角色，以及旅程的样子。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>是的。我应该走多远？我从祖父母开始吗？父母？我？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>由您决定。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>好的。我会跳过扩展的传记。我在巴基斯坦卡拉奇长大。那是我长大的地方，我来到美国进行本科学习。我实际上在大学学习了政治学和东亚研究，因为我对语言很感兴趣，所以我接受了中文，当我在大学学习语言时，最令人兴奋的事情之一总是在尝试工具来看看什么是否有效。</p><p>因此，这是对语言的兴趣，这是对技术的兴趣使我进入了Duolingo。实际上，我之所以开始营销，是因为在此之前我进行了一些营销和广告实习。当时，我们在Duolingo大约有50人，我们从只有一支从事该应用程序工作的团队到拥有货币化，学习和成长的团队。因此，我开始从事营销人员的成长，然后大约一年半，我转向了产品经理。在我在Duolingo的大部分时间里，我一直从事增长，也就是说，无论是新用户还是现有用户，都可以保留用户，这使我们在亚洲的存在。那非常有趣。像这样的东西。和动力，什么使人们动机以及使他们动机的动力一直是我的兴趣。</p><p>然后，转向在AI上工作的转移，因为重点并领导这支实验AI团队是去年年底的，因为基本上，我们最终与Openai合作，供其GPT-4发布。而我们之所以最终建立这种伙伴关系的原因实际上是因为我知道Openai的GPT-4发布产品经理，当我们聚在一起时，我们很快意识到Duolingo是发布的理想用例，因为在发布会上，他们真正想要的是证明公司实际上正在使用它来改变自己的业务，这些公司也是试图为世界做好有益的公司，因此我们作为一家公司，基于该伙伴关系并获得访问权限提早向GPT-4转移了一大堆优先事项，然后开始真正地倾向于AI，其中之一是启动该团队试图从事实验功能。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>非常令人兴奋。实际上，从动力的角度来看，您很高兴知道我儿子为他的西班牙语条纹感到自豪，所以…</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>很棒。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们有一个部分，我们问您一系列问题，而这些问题只是快速的。说出您想到的第一件事。您在AI中最骄傲的时刻是什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>作为一家公司，我们推出Duolingo Max一直非常令人兴奋，只是为新的教学时代铺平了道路。实际上，它是由Duolingo的Max Team创建的，Duolingo由Edwin Bodge和Bill Peterson领导，这非常令人兴奋。</p><p>我个人说，实际上，我的团队一直在开发的第一个产品实际上是 - 实验即将上线。您可以将其视为用于阅读的Tiktok，但这是GPT-4生成的所有内容。它为您提供了巨大的内容，因为人们需要在许多不同的品种中阅读练习，并且也在听。因此，我很高兴看到情况如何。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>非常酷。您对AI的担心是什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我通常非常乐观，但是我认为担心我的事情只是变化的步伐是如此之快，以至于它会破坏它的稳定。作为一个社会，我们的目标是确保面对非常非常快速的变化，我们可以保持稳定，因为实际上，快速变化是我们想要的。我们希望进步迅速，但没有所有破坏稳定的效果。这就是恐惧。我认为这是一个可解决的问题，但这就是恐惧。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动是什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我踢了很多足球。有趣的是，事实证明，这涉及到这一点，但是，是的，我踢了很多足球。那是我最喜欢做的活动之一。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>那么，您想要什么职业？ poli-sci，我想你提到。小时候长大后想成为什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>很多不同的事情。从来没有一个答案。我想成为一名作家，一名记者，板球运动员 - 板球运动员，并从事国际发展工作；我什至想成为一名建筑师。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您在那里跑了桌子。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>是的，很多不同的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您对AI的最大愿望是什么？您希望我们能从中得到什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我认为AI是我们可以创造最快进步的方式，在这里，“进步”我只是指（尽可能多的人）过着他们选择的生活 - 他们是他们选择的生活 - 他们是他们选择的生活 -芊芊。我认为这是最高的目标，这是大多数人的生活意义。我很高兴能成为这项努力的一部分。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，听起来像您。 Zan，感谢您抽出宝贵的时间与我们交谈。我真的觉得这是我们作为人类如何变得更好的一个截然不同和令人兴奋的机会。听起来Duolingo正在做很多事情。感谢您加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>非常感谢。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您加入我们。下次，我和我与Pinterest高级副总裁兼工程主管Jeremy King交谈。回头见。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德（Allison Ryder）：</strong>感谢您听<cite>我，我自己和AI的话</cite>。我们相信，像您一样，关于AI实施的对话不会开始并停止此播客。这就是为什么我们专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个专门为LinkedIn创建组的原因。它称为领导者的AI，如果您加入我们，您可以与表演创作者和主持人聊天，提出自己的问题，分享您的见解，并从<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和BCG获得有关AI实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">MITSMR.com/aiforleleders</a>访问它。我们将在展示笔记中放置该链接，我们希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>驯服伪造的流行病</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-taming-counterfeiting-eptemic/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-taming-counterfeiting-epidemic/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Handfield, Anand Nair,  and Thomas Y. Choi. <p>罗伯特·汉德菲尔德（Robert Handfield）（ <a href="https://twitter.com/robhandfield">@Robhandfield</a> ）是美国银行大学北卡罗来纳州立大学普尔管理学院的供应链管理杰出教授。 Anand Nair是东北大学D&#39;Amore-McKim商学院的供应链和信息管理教授。 Thomas Y. Choi是亚利桑那州立大学WP Carey商学院的AT＆T教授和供应链管理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted research into the state of counterfeiting from 2017 through early 2020. Funding was provided by CAPS Research, a joint venture of Arizona State University and the Institute for Supply Management. During the discovery phase, they ran an in-person workshop and attended the October 2017 annual strategic summit of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Handfield_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Neil Webb/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者从2017年至2020年初进行了对伪造状态的研究。亚利桑那州立大学和供应管理研究所的合资企业Caps Research提供了资金。</li><li>在发现阶段，他们举办了一个面对面的研讨会，并参加了密歇根州立大学反遭受罚款和产品保护中心2017年10月的年度战略峰会。</li><li>作者在2017年和2018年对20多位主题专家进行了个人访谈。</li><li>作者还在2018年6月和8月与21名供应链高管进行了深入的调查。</li></ul></aside><p>不管他们的领导人是否知道，许多公司都会为伪造者和不道德的供应链合作伙伴失去可观的收入。任何在街头市场上仔细阅读手袋的人都知道找到看起来与真实事物相同但可能并不相同的方式的假产品是多么普遍。在某些情况下，这可能会使消费者处于危险之中：例如，一家制药公司在黑市上发现了其产品的伪造版本，而没有活跃的药品成分。同样，公司的合法产品可能会因未经授权的销售而转移，就像一家全球电子公司发现其网络中的分销商（订购了据称用于客户维修的零件）在灰色市场上出售它们一样。</p><p>每个行业的高需求产品都是欺诈性犯罪活动的有利可图的目标。不幸的是，伪造产品是许多公司不想承认或提高其董事会或股东的问题。高级管理人员经常试图解释这个问题，合理化造假者总是会找到一种复制产品的方法，或者盗版仅代表销售的一小部分，而不值得。这正是伪造者想要企业做的事情的手中：忽略它们。</p><p></p><p>当公司确实开始量化假冒者影响其底线的水平时，他们可能会以零碎的方法来攻击问题，以防止其增长。但这还不够。</p><p>我们的研究表明，成功打击伪造需要广泛收集组织功能的关注。它可以很好地处理多层策略，包括各种方法并吸引整个组织及其合作伙伴。</p><p></p><p>我们建议组织通过识别，包含和防止它的凝聚力计划来解决伪造的伪造。这个全面的过程意味着通常将合同制造商的标签保留在供应链中如何移动产品。它包括在消费市场中搜索出售的东西，部署秘密标记，审查保修索赔，教育客户以及与主要机构和竞争对手合作。</p><h3>传统策略不起作用</h3><p>传统上，对伪造的任何关注的公司都依靠品牌安全功能来追踪犯罪活动。这些团队通常使用诸如在合法产品上应用秘密和明显标记的策略，附加跟踪产品位置的RFID标签以及使用序列化结合区块链来创建对抗篡改的交易记录，从而检测出伪造的伪造。例如，符合GS1全球可追溯性标准的条形码用于跟踪Covid-19疫苗。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>对于许多组织来说，这些策略还不够。</p><p>产品的伪造和非法转移仍然普遍存在：我们2018年对21名供应链高管的调查显示，将近一半的问题发生了一个正在进行的问题或在上一年遇到了事件。超过70％的人表示他们在过去五年中发生了一个事件。 （请参阅“研究”。）一位高管告诉我们，他的公司发现，相当于整个工厂的每月生产其产品的生产正是将其送入黑市，这在很大程度上是由于从其自己的供应商之一转移了。</p><p>伪造已成为一个问题，即经济合作与发展组织称，2019年价值4640亿美元，占世界贸易的2.5％。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>曾经认为，造假者只追随高价值或豪华物品，例如药品，设计师手袋或香水。但是现在，市场上到处都是假鞋类，农药，化妆品，玩具，汽车零件和医疗设备。假冒者的目标是可以轻松获利的任何行业和任何产品线。</p><p>尽管公司可能永远不会完全消除不良行为者从复制产品或从授权渠道转移商品，但它们可以大大减少造假者的市场渗透率并恢复损失的收入。成功的方法可能涉及切断造假者进入市场的机会，消除其未经授权的商品的供应或使产品更难复制。在这里，我们将详细介绍一项强大的行动计划所包括的三项活动：身份证明，遏制和预防。</p><h3>识别：了解问题的程度和性质</h3><p>对假冒问题的严重性获得基准是关键的第一步。随着问题的规模变得很明显，关闭其关闭的潜在投资回报也开始了。这可以帮助建立可以与业务目标和成果保持一致的反企业团队的绩效指标。指标的示例包括由于非法产品交易，收回的总收入总收入（以前在不知不觉中损失的损失的美元），每年损失的收入的美元金额或百分比，以及确认的非法贸易事件的数量和篡改。</p><p><strong>创建一个跨职能的品牌安全团队。</strong>制定当前问题的现实度量通常需要进行深入的调查，该调查涉及应用市场渠道分析，以探索来自组织内部和外部的多个销售数据源和其他信息。为了有效，品牌安全团队应包括来自销售，营销，运营，采购，物流，财务和会计以及核心品牌安全功能的参与者。这些团队通常由全球品牌保护官领导，在许多情况下，他们具有执法背景，通常向首席运营官报告。</p><p><strong>检查内部和市场数据以冲洗可疑活动。</strong>鉴于线索通常被埋葬在有关销售，保修，收益和其他产品指标的数据中，公司可能会难以找到更少的衡量措施，伪造活动。除非有人在寻找它，否则异常活动很容易被忽略。</p><p>一个好的第一步是首先查看在线销售的东西。电子商务已成为推动伪造商品行业的理想渠道。消费者可能会不知不觉地从在线零售商那里购买产品，这些零售商不会验证其平台上产品的来源以及是否合法。尽管伪造的网站被亚马逊定期关闭（在中国，阿里巴巴），但第二天，经营者以定期以不同的名字再次开放​​的假货人交易。亚马逊报道说，仅2020年，它就会阻止100亿个伪造的清单，并销毁了200万个假冒产品。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>由于电子商务网站经常是造伪人的主要销售来源，因此公司可以通过调查其产品（真正的或假货）在网上出售的地方开始。寻找伪造者网站的常见属性可以缩小可疑活动池。例如，一家公司可能会在亚马逊上找到四个不同的卖家，提供其手袋的精确副本，列出相同的详细信息甚至照片。潜在假冒者的指标可能包括拼写或语法错误，模糊的照片或其他看起来不太正确的细节。</p><p>另一个重要的数据源是保修申报表。当消费者因为有缺陷（经常伪造）而将产品寄回时，侦探工作可以追踪购买的位置以及如何购买。这可以导致伪造商品市场进入市场的起源，并成为找到其下游来源的起点。我们研究的一家全球医疗产品公司雇用了一名全球品牌保护官，该官员检查了保修并返回数据，现场服务请求和销售数据。在他的头100天内，他发现了1,000起已确认的非法贸易事件，伪造，转移和篡改。每年损失了14亿美元（占收入的2％），每年损失非法产品交易。</p><p>估算假冒销售是一项艰巨但必不可少的任务：公司必须建立一个基准，以衡量反遭受措施的影响。准确地了解问题的范围是决定投资多少以及对反遭受反对措施的投资回报率的先决条件。在许多情况下，商业决策者没有意识到其收入和声誉受到危险的程度。</p><p><strong>映射供应和分销链。</strong>许多公司惊讶地发现，不良演员在自己的供应链中活跃。过量生产，黑市销售和未经授权的分销是可能导致产品或副本的常见泄漏来源，该公司通过公司一无所知的渠道出售。这就是为什么重要的早期步骤是确定公司产品旅行的制造和分销渠道的原因。</p><p></p><p>一家大型全球服装公司的品牌所有者告诉我们，他通过分销商网络听到该品牌在墨西哥出售，即使该公司在那里没有批准的零售业务。为了跟踪这些产品的来源，导演搜寻了前往墨西哥的海运货运账单和运输记录。纸质步道表明，这些货物是从以色列港口运输的，这是由在美国生产该公司品牌产品的同一授权制造商。这家服装公司最终追踪了根据相同规格和相同材料制造的真正产品的衣服，但在双方之间的合同协议之外被非法分配。当服装公司建立全球品牌安全功能并绘制其整个供应网络时，发现类似的产品转移案件也在全球范围内发生。</p><p>分析上游供应链中的原材料上花费了多少是开始绘制供应基础的好地方。采购可以与会计团队联系，以跟踪代表公司进行的所有第三方购买（通常称为<em>支出分析的</em>文件）。如果供应商购买更多的原材料并以比公司订购更高的生产水平运行，这是一个明显的迹象，即附加产品可能正在进入黑市。这需要对供应链的全面可见性，而不仅仅是第1级供应商（由于其他原因，这越来越重要，尤其是管理与劳动或环境违规有关的风险）。有些供应商可能出于竞争原因不愿透露其上游供应商，但可以放心，查询是出于安全目的而不是试图将其从链条中删除的。</p><p></p><h3>遏制：限制问题的传播</h3><p>有了一个敬业的团队，对问题的范围有最初的感觉，以及对最容易受到伪造和转移风险的理解，公司可以开始系统地管理问题以控制问题。</p><p><strong>分析产品段。</strong>调查团队的关键任务之一是按渠道，保证金，数量和伪造活动的风险进行细分产品。这确保了团队的注意力首先针对最脆弱的市场渠道。</p><p>在许多情况下，对公司供应和分销过程的当前国家分析有助于揭示造假冒商追随的一系列共同的产品细分。特别是，我们的研究发现，基于各种成品，成品定制的水平，供应商的地理跨度，供应链中的层数，需求的可预测性以及制造量的变化，具有高复杂性的产品线。此类别中项目的示例包括飞机和汽车替换零件，玩具，高端服装，品牌制药产品和消费电子产品。假冒者更有可能在机会主义的产品细分市场上以更高的复杂性为特征，并利用这种复杂性来发挥其优势。</p><p>我们采访了一家生物技术制造商的高管，他们知道假冒产品出现在市场上，但不知道来源。品牌保护团队首先将产品细分为那些是造假者的主要目标（在这种情况下为高利润项目），并分析数据以估计每个品牌的事件数量。该团队是通过特许经营，品牌所有者和地区销售经理之间的密切合作组成的，然后制定了一项计划，以特许合作伙伴和乡村业务部门的计划。这一确立的品牌保护优先级是按产品线进行的，并提供了一个系统，可以通过品牌跟踪客户报告的事件，并每六个月进行一次数据评论。</p><p>同时，分析师开始收集有关供应链漏洞的市场情报，包括潜在的物流中断和监管干预的威胁，这对业务计划和增长目标构成了重大风险。累积地，这些努力帮助制造商优先考虑品牌保护可以最好地保护市场收入免受突然中断的企业和地区的优先级。在此过程中，团队确定了影响大量伪造药物的重大假冒和转移活动，这使许多患者处于危险之中。该公司表示，它最终能够将事件数量从每年100减少到零。这需要持续的努力来通过详细的分析和引入对策来推断每次事件的来源，包括向造伪人发送信息，警告他们将被追捕，以期使他们说服他们去寻找一个更容易的目标。</p><p>这种分析始于识别初始线索并遵循活动线程。最初的问题可能会表现为一个小问题，例如客户保修问题，似乎正在订购太多替换零件的经销商，或者在特定产品品牌上的客户回报率一连串。这些问题中的任何一个都可能导致伪造活动的渠道。</p><p><strong>从电子商务网站开始，然后与海关和其他当局联系。</strong>一组分析师应持续在电子商务网站上寻找开放式伪造的运营，并将其报告给平台运营商，例如亚马逊和执法部门。至少，这将更多的摩擦引入了一些坏演员的业务，以减慢他们的速度。</p><p>假冒产品几乎总是必须跨越边界，并通过执法实体监督的转运点和海关检查。这些是供应链中的关键参与者，组织必须将它们视为与收入损失和知识产权盗窃的斗争中的合作伙伴。这些关系在高度监管的环境中尤为重要，例如药品，食品，航空航天和汽车制造业，假冒产品可能会危害其用户。</p><p>美国海关和边境保护局（CBP）的一名官员告诉我们，让品牌所有者了解CBP的流程并在帮助该机构解决问题方面发挥作用可能是一项挑战。他说：“我们在现场检查集装箱。” “如果CBP官员打开一个容器并看到看起来可疑的东西，他们将首先查看我们的注册品牌的内部数据库。如果军官没有看到任何东西，那么他们什么都无能为力。”在CBP和美国专利商标局注册品牌是包含伪造的关键一步。</p><p><strong>教育（和警告）客户。</strong>必须对消费者进行购买伪造商品的可能性和风险的教育。公司应通过品牌营销使客户意识到，如果他们从未经验证的在线第三方卖家那里购买，他们承担着没有保修产品覆盖产品的风险 - 或更糟糕的是，由于可怕的后果而失败。我们知道的一家公司开始在其亚马逊网站上添加声明，警告未获得许可的产品将不受保修。公司还应向客户强调为保修目的注册产品序列号的重要性，如果他们购买的合法产品被证明是有缺陷或错误的，则可以保护它们。如果客户试图为假冒产品注册序列号，它将显示为错误并提醒品牌安全团队的问题。</p><h3>预防：在开始之前停止未来的伪造行动</h3><p>Once an organization discovers how the spread of counterfeit products in its market channels works and has taken initial steps to contain the problem, it must continue to monitor criminal activity and establish strong preventive measures. There are important roles for numerous functions in the company to play at this stage.</p><p> <strong>Product packaging experts should explore digital tracing technology.</strong> Features in current tracing technologies offer positive product authentication, can indicate tampering, can increase the difficulty of replication, and permit product tracking and tracing. Secure markings — which use a variety of packaging, blockchain, and serial marking technologies — are one method for tracking products. Many industries are working with standards organizations like ASTM International or GS1 to develop common methods for verifying products. This can help avoid the problem where counterfeiters try to copy not just the product but the digital marking, too.</p><p> In the biotech example mentioned previously, the brand protection team worked with the business to identify covert and overt authentication capabilities, which created automatic alerts when counterfeit products were being sold through market channels. The team also created a comprehensive customer communication plan using web advertisements, targeted email and Twitter campaigns, and retailer alerts about the dangers of buying from unauthorized sources. The campaign created awareness in the company&#39;s sales partner network and set the stage to identify where new counterfeit sales were occurring.</p><p> <strong>Quality assurance should review data to track down instances of product problems and returns.</strong> QA can create triggers in its data collection processes that flag potential illegitimate activities. We know of a company that noticed an uptick in its product returns, discovered that the products were not legitimate, and tracked them down to the point of sale — which revealed the source of the counterfeiting.</p><p> <strong>Supply management should step up efforts to audit suppliers.</strong> It can be particularly fruitful to track overproduction by suppliers, as well as how they dispose of products that don&#39;t conform to quality standards — products that can end up moving through black market channels and thus avoiding trade compliance policies. One large apparel company began monitoring the inventory levels within its supplier&#39;s facilities and noticed that the supplier&#39;s inbound raw-material inventories were much greater than the volume of finished goods it was shipping to the company. This was an indication that product was being produced and sold elsewhere through other channels.</p><p> <strong>Logistics should map supply routes to document compliance on the part of transportation providers.</strong> This can help ensure chain of custody along global supply chains, particularly at handoff points such as ports, warehouses, and distribution centers. Companies with multitier distributor channels should document every logistics handoff and conduct random audits to determine whether there are proper security personnel and locked gates at all distribution centers.</p><p> <strong>Human resources might want to consider monitoring employees who are dealing directly with targeted products.</strong> This may include conducting background checks, as well as increasing training to enhance staff awareness. If there is a high level of missing inventory or a sudden increase or drop in product sales, investigations may be required.</p><p> <strong>Aftermarket sales should track warranty claims and parts sales to identify product-quality problems.</strong> As with the quality assurance team, those at the front line of aftermarket sales are in a position to learn that products aren&#39;t performing as expected, which, again, may indicate that counterfeits are entering market channels. For example, a large retailer made the decision to limit its distribution channels and authorized resellers, recognizing the high potential for counterfeit products in these particular sales channels, especially e-commerce.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Counterfeiting and product diversion are not crimes that a single organization can combat. They require the diligence of brands, retailers, packaging companies, and logistics businesses. This is a rare instance where joining with competitors can yield important insights. Companies should consider joining a consortium and partnering with industry counterparts. Industry-specific groups include the Automotive Anti-Counterfeiting Council for vehicle manufacturers and Rx-360 for pharmaceutical companies. Members of React, a large anti-counterfeiting network, include Marvel Entertainment, Mattel, Pfizer, Philips, Prada, and Timberland.</p><p> Counterfeiting is also not just a private-sector supply chain problem. Labor and human rights advocates, consumer education agencies, customs agents, federal and state law enforcement agencies, local police, and consumers of counterfeit products all have an interest and role in ferreting out unauthorized activity. While counterfeiting and product diversion cannot be eliminated, dedicated efforts can curtail both significantly.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Dismantle Career Roadblocks for More Equitable Outcomes</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian is a cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts. That was the message from [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/W23-QA03_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts.</p><p> That was the message from Haig R. Nalbantian, cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute, during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023. Nalbantian helps organizations apply evidence-based, empirical methods to strengthen their DEI efforts and retention strategies and asserts that “the surging use of analytics in the HR domain to inform work and workforce management” is a big part of the future of work.</p><p></p><p> While talent and drive are important in shaping careers, situational factors profoundly affect what happens to employees at work. They include employees&#39; access to “accelerator” roles, such as customer-facing jobs; how employees navigate flexible work arrangements, such as part-time status; and employees&#39; reporting relationships, such as whether they report to higher-level or high-performing supervisors. Nalbantian noted that these easy-to-identify circumstances, which he called <em>explained differences</em> , are prevalent.</p><p></p><p> Many organizations also have pervasive and sizable <em>unexplained disparities</em> regarding who gets chosen for promotions. Nalbantian said that in both his own studies and others, “women are actually more likely to be highly rated” by their managers at elite, large employers — all things being equal — “but in the majority of companies, they&#39;re less likely to be promoted.”</p><p> He said it is critical that companies address the explained differences and explore the unexplained disparities.</p><p> Nalbantian wasn&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the event, so he answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> Does your research address intersectionality in its analysis? You talked about women and people of color, but what about women of color and other people with multiple intersecting minority identities?</h6><p> In many of the client cases covered in my study, we did indeed examine intersectionality directly. We&#39;ve done this quite a bit in larger US-based organizations that have adequate populations of these demographic groups for modeling purposes.</p><p> One of the areas of particular interest to client organizations is intersectionality with respect to reporting relationships. That is, do the specific demographics of one&#39;s supervisor affect whether the employee is promoted, is highly rated, or gets higher pay increases? For example, do White male supervisors treat Black female reports worse than White male or White female reports? Do White female supervisors help the prospects of their female reports, regardless of color?</p><p> I can say that there are few regularities in these results — certainly far less than the results I&#39;ve reported with respect to performance ratings, roles, supervisor performance and level, and flexible working.</p><p></p><h6> Has this research mapped across socioeconomic status as an intersectional influence?</h6><p> Unfortunately, we&#39;ve had much more limited data on socioeconomic factors, in part because most of our clients focus these studies on their salaried populations, ignoring their hourly workers. This concerns me, as it reveals a tendency to discount front-line workers. I try to remind organizations that what happens in their front-line ranks can have a major impact on business results. I&#39;ve seen and documented this in client assignments. Still, the tendency of organizations is to prioritize their salaried employees — professionals, managers, and executives.</p><h6> You mentioned that being younger than comparable peers is an attribute favorable to success. Can you elaborate more on what your studies have found regarding age inequalities?</h6><p> The negative impact of age is close to universal among our analytical findings with client organizations. The simple fact is that once an employee gets beyond the median age of their cohort, all things turn negative: They&#39;re less likely to be promoted, they&#39;re less likely to receive a high performance rating, and their pay growth levels off or declines.</p><p> The one positive is that there is less turnover with older employees, often substantially less. Indeed, it may be that it is precisely because older employees tend to stay that employers don&#39;t feel the need to promote, pay, or recognize them in the same way as they do their younger employees. The latter have more outside opportunities, so they may need to be constantly wooed.</p><p></p><p> These negative signals about older workers can be very misleading. We often find that groups with more older workers actually outperform those with more younger workers. There&#39;s a discordance between what&#39;s found at the individual level compared with the group or organizational level.</p><p> This suggests that the productivity of older workers shows up not in their own measures of individual performance but in the performance of those with whom they work. We call this a <em>spillover effect</em> . So, for example, if older workers are less likely to turn over, they can cause their younger colleagues to follow suit, thereby bringing more stability to their work groups and making them more productive. For more evidence about the productivity of older workers, see the recent study I conducted with Richard A. Guzzo and Nicholas L. Anderson, which we discuss in the article “ <a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">Age, Experience, and Business Performance: A Meta-Analysis of Work Unit-Level Effects</a> ” in the journal <cite>Work, Aging and Retirement</cite> .</p><h6> How can organizations ensure that age diversity and inclusion are integrated into their equity and diversity initiatives?</h6><p> Again, it is a common view among business leaders that older workers are less productive. And because they tend to cost more, they are viewed more as a liability than an asset, despite significant evidence to the contrary. For some reason that I find hard to explain, combating ageism is not high on the DEI agenda, certainly not as compared with efforts to address gender and racial inequity. I fault the DEI community for not being more aggressive on this front.</p><p> The aging workforce is a fact of life almost everywhere. Organizations that don&#39;t deal effectively with the repercussions of this secular trend and ensure that they are managing their older workers effectively run the risk of undermining organizational performance. In effect, they may make their unfounded stereotypes a self-fulfilling outcome.</p><p></p><p> I always urge my clients to undertake the kind of disciplined diagnostic work to evaluate the realities of their own workforce — to determine whether spillover effects are indeed at work in their organization, and to respond accordingly. Through this process, many of them will find that they have an asset to protect rather than a liability to discard.</p><h6> Is there any analysis done on the correlation between company performance or share price and the situations demonstrated by the survey?</h6><p> I&#39;ve undertaken client studies in which we link workforce characteristics and management practices to various business outcomes, including profitability, financial and operational productivity, revenue growth, and customer retention, among others. Our results have been mixed. In some, we&#39;ve seen that greater diversity in work group or unit composition improves business performance; in others, we&#39;ve found no effect or statistically negligible results. The most robust review and synthesis of the results of these studies is the meta-analysis of the effects of age and tenure noted above. That study did not focus on the effects of race and gender.</p><h6> What concrete steps can organizations take to battle these biases?</h6><p></p><p> My article in the summer 2023 issue of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/">Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</a> ,” speaks directly to this question. I explain how organizations can use the results of this kind of modeling to help eliminate or reduce the influence of demographics on how well employees are positioned to succeed at work. The reality is that all too often, situational factors inordinately affect the ability of employees to succeed and that women and people of color are situationally disadvantaged.</p><p> Employers who recognize that they are not positioning this talent to succeed can deploy an approach I call <em>proactive career management</em> to change this reality on the ground. This may involve getting more women and people of color into supervisory or other accelerator roles, changing reporting relationships, and neutralizing the negative effects of flexible working, among other things. I share a case study in my article to illustrate this approach in action.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do Consumers See Your Business as a Force for Good?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cynthia E. Clark. <p>Cynthia E. Clark, Ph.D., is a professor of management at Bentley University. She is also a coauthor of <cite>Business and Society: Ethical, Legal, and Digital Environments</cite> (Sage Publications, 2020) and the author of <cite>Giving Voice to Values in the Boardroom</cite> (Routledge, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[The public’s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s efforts to impose fines on businesses for greenwashing, point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald’s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Clark-Eco-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> The public&#39;s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the US Federal Trade Commission&#39;s efforts to impose <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/04/13/ftc-is-expected-crack-down-greenwashing/">fines on businesses for greenwashing</a> , point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald&#39;s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic waste. Last year, <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/blog/2022/04/55-million-total-ftc-settlements-kohls-and-walmart-challenge-bamboo-and-eco-claims-shed-light">both Kohl&#39;s and Walmart</a> reached settlements of $2.5 million and $3 million, respectively, for falsely claiming that dozens of rayon textile products were actually made from environmentally friendly bamboo.</p><p> When such large, visible companies issue false claims or fail to act, it results in missed opportunities, a growing performance-expectation gap, and, eventually, reputational damage among consumers. So, what makes a business a force for good when it comes to the future of our environment? To find out, Bentley University and Gallup recently conducted a survey of 5,757 Americans to assess how they feel about business and its potential to have a positive impact on society and the environment. The <a href="https://www.bentley.edu/news-Announcing-the-Bentley-Gallup-Force-for-Good-survey-results">results of the Force for Good survey</a> highlight areas in which businesses, small and large, are failing to meet people&#39;s expectations — and how they can do better.</p><p></p><p> The public&#39;s expectations of large companies like Kohl&#39;s, McDonald&#39;s, or Walmart were made clear in our research. A slight majority of our respondents (53%) said that businesses overall have a negative environmental impact. Almost two-thirds (65%) said they feel this way about <em>large</em> businesses, whereas 16% said that <em>small</em> businesses have a negative impact on the planet/environment. Younger respondents in our study had higher expectations of businesses overall, with a whopping 81% of those age 18 to 29 saying that large businesses have a negative impact on the planet, compared with 54% of respondents age 70 or older.</p><p> Drilling down into the data, we found that more than 9 in 10 respondents rated four social and environmental concerns that businesses could act on as extremely or somewhat important: practicing sustainable manufacturing (92%); promoting increased access to education and training (92%); investing time and money into local communities (92%); and operating in a way that is sustainable for the environment (91%). Just 1 in 3 people surveyed said that businesses are currently doing an excellent or good job in any of these areas, and about 1 in 4 (26%) said that businesses are doing an excellent or good job of operating in an environmentally sustainable way.</p><h3> The T-Shirt Experiment</h3><p> One perspective on sustainability is that companies should practice environmental responsibility for the greater good — the “doing good to do good” perspective. Another approach focuses on the importance of “doing good to do well” so that both business and society benefit from leaders&#39; actions. But are these approaches in tension? Need they be?</p><p> One section of the Force for Good survey — what we called our T-shirt experiment — was aimed at getting a better read on how people think about this tension. Amid rising prices for almost everything, we asked whether respondents would be willing to pay extra for a T-shirt depending on a variety of company characteristics. Sixty-three percent of respondents said they would be willing to pay extra — 82% more — for a T-shirt if the company that made it was known for having a positive impact on the environment. The numbers are even higher for respondents age 18 to 29 and for women: Young people were most likely to say they would pay more — about 8 in 10 — and almost 7 in 10 women. (See “Results of the T-Shirt Experiment.”) Both of these consumer groups are key markets for many companies.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Results of the T-Shirt Experiment</h4><p class="caption"> To differing degrees, depending on age and gender, respondents indicated their willingness to pay more for the same product based on a business&#39;s sustainability practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig1-1.png" alt="Results of the T-Shirt Experiment" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> When people were asked how much they would pay for the T-shirt without being given any additional information, the median response was $10. This held true for those with personal incomes between $24,000 and $179,000. In other words, personal income had little effect on the value they assigned to the product.</p><p></p><p> Respondents were then asked how much more they would pay if the company were known for various attributes: having a positive environmental impact, making a positive impact on the local community, treating employees well, and contributing to charities. Among the four attributes, the premium was highest for companies known to have a positive environmental impact, with a median response of $7.</p><p> Our data indicates that Americans are, in fact, willing to reward companies for doing good. A company known for positive environmental performance can charge more for its products — evidence that “doing good to do well” works.</p><p></p><h3> A False Dichotomy?</h3><p> Most of the respondents didn&#39;t see a trade-off between good environmental performance and good financial performance. In other words, they believe that both can happen concurrently, despite business leaders&#39; arguments that sustainable practices harm financial performance. About 7 in 10 respondents (69%) said businesses that prioritize making a positive impact on society are just as profitable (47%) or more profitable (22%) than their competitors. People who said they have expertise in owning, leading, or managing a business were no less likely than those without such expertise to say that businesses that prioritize making a positive impact are at least as profitable as their competitors.</p><p> Members of different political parties had notable differences of opinion regarding the importance of sustainability. For example, 84% of Democrats said it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner, compared with 31% of Republicans and 59% of independents. However, a large majority of Republicans (80%) said that sustainability is at least <em>somewhat</em> important. These perspectives might affect a host of company actions, such as choosing content and spending amounts for advertising in red versus blue states and the very design of their products.</p><p></p><p> Likewise, we found significant differences across ethnic identities. Seventy percent of Black respondents, 82% of Asian respondents, 65% of Hispanic respondents, and 59% of White respondents said they believe it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner. When asked how they feel about focusing on long-term benefits like those for the environment versus short-term benefits like profits, 77% of Asian respondents said they are likely to support that focus — compared with 56% of respondents overall. The figures for both Black and Hispanic respondents hovered around 60%.</p><p> Even when we asked the question in a slightly different way, respondents did not see it as a trade-off but as more of a “both and” situation. For example, when asked about meeting the financial goals of investors, 79% said they believe it is somewhat or extremely important. Eighty-eight percent of respondents also said that making the world a better place is somewhat or extremely important.</p><h3> How Can Your Company Become a Force for Good?</h3><p> Results from this deep dive into what a broad and varied set of Americans believe suggest several actions companies can take or plan for.</p><p> <strong>Pay attention to your local footprint.</strong> Small companies are perceived as better at most stakeholder-related activities. Respondents were twice as likely to say small businesses positively impact people&#39;s lives than large businesses (82% and 41%, respectively). What&#39;s more, respondents are more likely to think large businesses have a negative impact on Americans&#39; lives in general (38%) than they are to say the same about small businesses (4%). This data, combined with the results across age and gender in the figure below (see “Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?”) on positive community impact, suggests that companies — particularly large ones — should improve their relationships with their surrounding communities.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize that younger Americans expect more.</strong> Millennials (born between 1981 and 1996) and Gen Zers (born between 1997 and 2012) expect more from businesses in terms of both social and environmental responsibility than older respondents do. In our T-shirt experiment, 82% of respondents age 18 to 29 were willing to pay more for a T-shirt from a company known for having a positive impact on their local community. Again, young respondents (73%) agreed more than any other age group that businesses&#39; efforts to reduce their carbon footprints and/or emissions are important. Companies will need to account for their environmental stewardship among their customers and future employees.</p><p> <strong>Mind the performance-expectation gap.</strong> Environmental stakeholders and regulators are on the lookout for any discrepancy between expectations of a company&#39;s responsible environmental management and what it is actually doing — the performance-expectation gap. The vast majority of respondents (89%) said businesses have “a great deal” or “some” power to make a positive impact on people&#39;s lives, but just 57% said that businesses are very or somewhat effective at doing so. In terms of the environment, the findings revealed performance-expectation gaps of at least 30 percentage points between “the importance of” and “the performance of” several environmental goals. On questions about reducing businesses&#39; carbon footprints, engaging in sustainable manufacturing, and making the world a better place, we found considerable gaps: On those three points, 52% to 57% of respondents indicated that it is extremely important for businesses to do so, but only 24% to 28% thought they are excellent or good at it.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?</h4><p class="caption"> There is a considerable gap between respondents&#39; opinions on the importance of sustainability practices and their perceptions of businesses&#39; actual practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig2.png" alt="Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> While having a dedicated sustainability leader, support from senior management, and education for employees and executives is necessary, it&#39;s important to stay vigilant in addressing the widening performance-expectation gap. In what has become a hypercritical business environment, leaders must pay greater attention to how perceptions of what their company is doing compare with what they are actually doing.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Set sustainability goals.</strong> Think carefully about how to measure what you&#39;re doing. This is a logical next step after gaining the support of senior management, and it can help your company determine the progress it has made and where it has soft or blind spots. In fact, regulators have proposed requiring companies to disclose how they set climate-related targets and measure their progress toward meeting them. Consider signing on to broadly recognized and accepted goals like the United Nations Global Compact&#39;s (UNGC&#39;s) <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals</a> , which can help your company publicly commit to a plan of action, step by step. The UNGC also requires annual statements on progress to help ward off greenwashing.</p><p></p><p> With increasing attention on environmental sustainability, gaining an understanding of how various stakeholders perceive your statements and actions is vital. By identifying and understanding current perceptions and their implications, as the Bentley-Gallup study does, companies can amend their environmental commitments and processes to ensure that they invigorate their efforts to be a force for good, which will benefit the company, its stakeholders, and, most importantly, the environment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Myth of the Mainstream</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus Collins. <p>Marcus Collins is a clinical marketing professor at the University of Michigan&#39;s Ross School of Business and former head of strategy at Wieden+Kennedy New York. He is the author of <cite>For the Culture: The Power Behind What We Buy, What We Do, and Who We Want to Be</cite> (PublicAffairs, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com For years, McDonald’s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension. The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Collins_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> For years, McDonald&#39;s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension.</p><p> The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about its updated menu, which offered healthier alternatives more in line with contemporary diet trends — but to no avail. Year over year, McDonald&#39;s sales declined, and its brand perception continued to spiral downward.</p><p></p><p> Finally, the company decided to go on the offensive. Instead of combating the opposition&#39;s hate and attempting to win over those in the middle, McDonald&#39;s decided to focus on its fans — the people who self-identify as McDonald&#39;s devotees despite the vitriol directed at the brand. The company&#39;s tactics included launching its Famous Orders campaign, which celebrated the favored menu items of superstar fans (like hip-hop mogul Travis Scott and K-pop megastars BTS); creating adult-targeted Happy Meals; and promoting fans&#39; own menu hacks. In doing so, it tapped into what these devotees love about McDonald&#39;s and not only activated their collective consumption but also inspired them to spread the word on behalf of the brand. The result of this strategy was a 10.4% increase in global revenue for McDonald&#39;s from 2018 to 2021 and the return of dormant customers: more than a quarter of those who came in to buy the Travis Scott meal, for example, hadn&#39;t visited the chain in over a year. Seemingly overnight, McDonald&#39;s went from being a cautionary tale to the darling of brand marketing and a case study for advertising effectiveness.</p><p></p><p>这里发生了什么？ Conventional wisdom would tell us that in a world of increasingly polarized opinions, our best bet is to appease the middle, if only because that&#39;s where the majority of the market is. That also seems like a safe bet to many companies, as a middle-of-the-road position is less likely to alienate potential customers. But McDonald&#39;s demonstrated what can happen when you dismiss this conventional approach. Instead of trying to speak to the mass market, it chose a side. It chose to embrace the love instead, fighting the hate, and it abandoned the notion of enticing the large but indifferent middle of the market. By doing so, McDonald&#39;s marketing efforts activated a legion of fans who not only consumed but also won over others as well. What McDonald&#39;s realized is an important lesson for contemporary marketers: If you want to get people to move, you must choose a side. The notion that you can win by playing to the middle is a misleading myth.</p><p></p><h3> Choose a Side</h3><p> The core function of marketing is to influence people to adopt a desired behavior. That is to say, we go to market to get people to move — to buy, to vote, to recycle, to subscribe, to download, to watch, to evangelize, to wear a mask — and to drive a host of other desirable behavioral outcomes that will benefit our organization or interests. And what influences people the most? Well, according to everything we know about human behavior, we are most influenced by other people — not ads, not value propositions, but other people. More specifically, we are most influenced by <em>our</em> people: the individuals who abide by the same culturally established conventions and expectations that dictate what is considered acceptable behavior for people like us. These individuals typically share a similar worldview and, therefore, adhere to a shared way of life in an effort to promote social solidarity among themselves — their subculture. They consume the way the subculture consumes, vote the way it votes, and behave the way it behaves, because that is what is expected of people like them.</p><p> If these people are against you because of the shared conventions and expectations of people like them (their culture), then the likelihood of getting them to take action on your behalf will be slim. That&#39;s why right-wing Republicans won&#39;t bother trying to convert left-leaning Democrats. Instead, Republicans speak to their base — the collective of people who see the world similarly, express a similar set of cultural characteristics as the brand, and are more inclined to move in step with the brand as an act of social solidarity. They identify as members of this group and follow its behavioral norms.</p><p> Those in the unaffiliated middle of the population, on the other hand, are by nature indifferent and risk averse. While they may have opinions, they lack strong convictions in either direction and are therefore less likely to take action. In politics, they don&#39;t vote in primaries or campaign for candidates; instead, they sit on the sidelines and wait to see how things shake out. Their behavior is the same when it comes to brands.</p><p> The middle doesn&#39;t adopt new products with any urgency. They are not the first to respond to marketing communications, nor are they likely to weigh in on a debate between advocates and detractors. They mitigate their own risk of moving out of step with what might be considered generally acceptable by stepping back and observing other people&#39;s responses first.</p><p> The red herring is that we perceive this indifference as an opportunity to persuade them to one side or the other. But the truth is, they are not typically convinced by any marketing communications. Instead, they, too, take cues from other people — sometimes those who are for you, and at other times those who are against you.</p><p></p><p> With this in mind, it becomes abundantly clear that in a polarized scenario, the chances of marketers getting people to move are far greater when we activate the collective of the willing as opposed to trying to convince detractors or even persuade the indifferent. And yet, historically, marketers have focused their efforts on the middle because it represents the biggest market opportunity. However, our chances of successfully influencing behavior increases when we choose to address the people who are most likely to take action. When we do so effectively, we catalyze a propagation effect that causes the product, behavior, or idea to cascade throughout the population, thanks to the process of social contagion — the spread of affects, behaviors, cognitions, and desires due to direct or indirect peer influence of people “like us.”</p><h3> The Power of Propagation</h3><p> The idea of propagation demands that marketers leave behind the conventional approach of targeting the middle, where the majority of the population resides. Besides being of questionable effectiveness, as discussed above, reaching the middle requires costly media spending (think prime-time TV and Super Bowl ads) and places marketing messages in an arena that is noisy and saturated with competing messages. Marketers pay little attention to the fringe, a population that conventional wisdom tells us is too small and too niche. But everything that is now mainstream once started on the fringe: It started within a subculture and propagated out to become popular culture.</p><p> For instance, if you were into comic books 20 years ago, you would have been considered a nerd. Today, however, many of the most-viewed movies across the globe, such as Marvel&#39;s <cite>Avengers</cite> series, originated from comics. Twenty years ago, if you were into video games, you would have been perceived as an immature adult. Today, gaming is not only considered cool but is also a multibillion-dollar industry. Indeed, what is now normal was once fringe. Thanks to social contagion, the cultural characteristics of a community propagate from the fringe to the middle — from the subculture to popular culture. It happens from the outside in, not the inside out.</p><p></p><p> Unlike traditional marketing communications, the reach and subsequent adoption that is achieved through this kind of propagation does not rely on people hearing a message from a company or brand. (It helps, but it&#39;s not necessary.) Instead, people hear about it from someone they trust — someone like them — which increases their likelihood of adoption. As the network scientists Nicholas Christakis and James Fowler contended, “When a small group of people begin acting in concert — displaying similar visible symptoms — the epidemic can spread along social network ties via emotion contagion and large groups can become quickly emotionally synchronized.” This is the network effect that is catalyzed when you activate the collective of the willing. Don&#39;t focus on the middle: Focus on the people who see the world the way you do. Choose a side, and they will convince the bystanders, the passive, the indifferent.</p><p></p><p> Although broadcast messaging might get our attention, it&#39;s the influence of people like us, people with whom we identify, that changes our outlook and, subsequently, our behaviors. This provides a new perspective, and corresponding strategies, for marketers who aim to communicate with consumers in a culture where ideological binaries seem to divide the market. Like McDonald&#39;s did, marketers benefit from choosing a side that is most likely to move and then activating its members so that they might convert people on the brand&#39;s behalf. Status quo practices position the middle as a safe bet. However, the dynamics of cultural diffusion subvert these long-standing best practices for connecting with consumers and influencing behavioral adoption, and demand that today&#39;s practitioners develop new strategies and accompanying tactics.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sustainability Progress Is Stalled at Most Companies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[CB Bhattacharya and Rob Jekielek. <p>CB Bhattacharya is director of the Center for Sustainable Business and the HJ Zoffer Chair in Sustainability and Ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business at the University of Pittsburgh. Rob Jekielek is managing director of The Harris Poll.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Sustainability & Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability-Driven Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else’s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual.1 On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bhattacharya-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else&#39;s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming their business models to be more sustainable have embedded sustainability into their corporate DNA. This means that they have endowed their employees with a sense of sustainable ownership, spurring them to engage in more sustainability-supporting behaviors. When every employee integrates environmental and social concerns into every business decision, sustainability progress is accelerated — an aspirational goal for all companies.</p><p> To shed light on the state of play in embedding sustainability and identify key bottlenecks, the Center for Sustainable Business at the University of Pittsburgh collaborated with The Harris Poll to conduct a survey of US employees. We wanted to find out whether their employers were taking measures that our earlier research had identified as important to prompting employees to conduct business through a sustainability lens. Our survey drew responses from 1,056 employees, representative of the US employee base. We defined sustainability for the respondents as “integrating environmental and societal concerns into business decisions and actions.”</p><p></p><p> We asked respondents to rate their level of agreement with a series of 19 statements about the status quo, such as “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance,” on a 4-point Likert scale (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”). We also presented respondents with a series of 12 issues that could pose challenges to sustainability progress, such as “Sustainability is not built into our business strategy,” and asked them to rate the extent to which that is an actual challenge at their company (from “major challenge” to “not at all a challenge”).</p><p> Roughly one-third of the respondents asserted that their employers have made significant strides in their sustainability journeys. Although that number might sound low given the enormity of the task facing us, the good news is that there is momentum, which we can help accelerate by pointing out the roadblocks as perceived by employees. Below, we provide six key recommendations that emerged from our data for managers seeking to embed sustainability in the organizational culture and business models.</p><p> <strong>Establish a purpose based on values.</strong> Purpose is a business&#39;s raison d&#39;être — the answer to the all-important question, “Why do we do what we do?” Paul Polman, former CEO of Unilever and a leader in the corporate sustainability movement, has said, “Sustainability is totally driven by purpose.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Organizations that are successful at embedding sustainability articulate the societal benefit they aim to deliver to their stakeholders, and this overarching purpose guides everything the organization does.</p><p> In our study, 36% of the respondents strongly agreed with the statement “My company wants to make a difference in people&#39;s lives, not just make profits,” while 33% strongly agreed with “My company has a higher purpose beyond profit maximization.” If purpose is the starting point for sustainability, we aren&#39;t doing very well; it is apparent that the profit-maximization narrative is alive and well. Consistently, 43% of employees cited short-term focus, a lack of investor interest, and, importantly, “Our leaders don&#39;t believe in sustainability,” as challenges. Unless CEOs and top management teams realize that profit is the <em>consequence</em> of value creation for all stakeholders and not the starting point for strategy development and execution, progress will be stifled. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p></p><p> <strong>Bake sustainability into corporate strategy.</strong> Academic researchers and others have noted that efforts to make meaningful progress toward sustainability must be driven by corporate strategy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Doing so increases the likelihood that, over time, “doing the green thing” will be seen as a normal part of employees&#39; jobs, and more and more decisions will be made through the lens of sustainability. With only 29% of respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance” and 27% with “Sustainability is core to how my company executes our business strategy,” it appears that we have a long way to go. Consistent with the status quo, 43% agreed that their company&#39;s failure to build sustainability into its business strategy represents a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Train employees, and incentivize actions that advance sustainability.</strong> Companies that are successful in engaging their workforce have invested in training that gives employees guidance on how to improve sustainability. With only 30% of employees surveyed strongly agreeing with the statement “I understand how I can improve my company&#39;s sustainability performance through my role,” there seems to be a dearth of role-specific knowledge at the individual employee level. Lack of training was cited as a major/moderate challenge by 44%, while a similar number (45%) indicated that they don&#39;t know what actions to take to improve sustainability performance. Companies need to invest more in training and sustainability knowledge creation so that employees know <em>what</em> they can do in their roles and <em>how</em> to do what needs to be done.</p><p> Managers must also do more to provide employees with incentives to advance the sustainability agenda: Forty-nine percent of those surveyed found the lack of such incentives to be a major or moderate hurdle to improving sustainability performance. Leaders should also consider whether the management culture encourages engagement and intrinsic motivation by giving employees the autonomy to solve sustainability challenges, which often require creative thinking. However, when we asked survey respondents to rate their level of agreement with the statements “My company allows me to make a lot of sustainability-related decisions on my own” and “My company gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out sustainability initiatives,” we found that, at most, 29% of respondents strongly agreed.</p><p> <strong>Create a sustainability culture in your organization.</strong> Managers can keep sustainability salient in the organizational culture by communicating progress, celebrating milestones, recognizing achievements, and collaborating on solutions both internally and with industry partners. Our research has identified the lack of a sustainability culture as one of the biggest impediments to progress, with 48% of respondents indicating that that is a major or moderate impediment at their organization. Communicating sustainability progress to employees is a key component of a sustainability culture, because it keeps issues top of mind. Celebrating successes will pique employee interest and legitimize the importance of sustainability to the organization — but only 31% of respondents strongly agreed that their company celebrates sustainability successes.</p><p></p><p> Collaborating with traditional competitors — which is increasingly necessary to address those complex “ <a href="https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/tragedy-of-the-commons-impact-on-sustainability-issues">tragedy of the commons</a> ” problems — signals to employees that the company is serious about transformational change and reinforces the culture to employees. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> With only 25% of survey respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company collaborates with other organizations to address complex sustainability issues,” it is evident that much work is required to open corporate leaders&#39; eyes to the potential of progress via collaboration.</p><p> <strong>Conduct business through a sustainability lens.</strong> Imagine the progress we would make if every employee in every company — from the mailroom to the boardroom — integrated environmental and social issues into every business decision they made. This, in our view, is conducting business through the lens of sustainability — an aspirational but necessary goal to reach if we are to surmount our existential crises. As previous research has shown, employees taking individual ownership of sustainability is a key driver for engaging in sustainability behaviors. In our survey, 28% of respondents strongly agreed with the statement “Employees at my company take ownership of improving sustainability performance,” while 45% identified a belief among employees that “sustainability is someone else&#39;s responsibility” as a challenge. This lack of personal ownership of sustainability performance is reflected in our survey results: Only 27% of respondents strongly agreed that they “invested ideas and creativity” to help their company be more sustainable, and just 24% strongly agreed that every business decision they make is viewed through the lens of sustainability.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Bridge the last mile.</strong> We noted a significant difference between how corporate and front-line employees responded to our questions. Compared with front-line nonmanagers working in roles such as customer support, managers working in corporate roles were, on average, about 15% more likely to see sustainability as embedded.</p><p> To ensure that their commitment to sustainability is real and provides tangible benefits to their organizations, leaders must address this last-mile gap between corporate and front-line employees. Broadly communicated messaging about the corporate purpose and environmental, social, and governance targets might not suffice in this instance; there is a real need to drive sustainability through practical initiatives and actions that can be integrated into daily tasks and routines that employees perform across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> Interestingly, perceiving sustainability as more embedded in the organization also opens employees&#39; eyes to the roadblocks and challenges that impede progress. Our data shows that employees who are more engaged and perceive sustainability to be more embedded also perceive more roadblocks, on average, than those who are less engaged.</p><p> The implication here is that as companies bridge the last-mile gap in embedding sustainability, they should be prepared to field more questions and listen to more opinions as employee engagement on the issue increases. Companies should use one-on-one coaching, action playbooks, and tailored communication to make sustainability everyone&#39;s job. Companies need to be prepared to invest more resources into embedding sustainability — and get the entire organization to conduct business through the sustainability lens.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Robots Can Enhance Performance Management for Humans</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Hong and Lynn Wu. <p>Bryan Hong is associate professor of entrepreneurship and management at the Bloch School of Management at the University of Missouri-Kansas City. Lynn Wu is associate professor of operations, information, and decisions at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Efficiency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to invest in robotics for their business. Our research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Wu-Robots-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/advanced%20electronics/our%20insights/growth%20dynamics%20in%20industrial%20robotics/industrial-robotics-insights-into-the-sectors-future-growth-dynamics.ashx">invest in robotics</a> for their business. Our research has found an equally and perhaps more important transformation taking place: The adoption of robots is improving companies&#39; ability to recognize and reward good employee performance.</p><p> Within every organization, leaders face a fundamental question: How do we get the best from our people? One of the most common methods is offering monetary rewards — usually, periodic bonuses — that are linked to performance. This practice is grounded in the idea that better performance should be more highly rewarded. But that approach is rarely simple to implement in practice because it requires that performance be measured well enough to be evaluated effectively. This is challenging to accomplish for most roles and even more so for individual employees. Because so much work is done in teams and managers can&#39;t monitor the specific activity of each employee or accurately measure individual performance, many organizations choose to pay bonuses based on team or company performance rather than on individual performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p></p><h3> Measuring Human Performance When Colleagues Are Robots</h3><p> What does all this have to do with robots? In our research, we have found that companies that adopt robots improve their ability to measure human performance. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> To illustrate, let&#39;s say you&#39;re working in a team of two. Your manager can see and evaluate your combined productivity as a team but not what each of you is doing individually at all times. In theory, both of you are supposed to be contributing equally; in practice, you&#39;re doing far more of the work, which isn&#39;t visible to your busy manager.</p><p> Then, let&#39;s say your teammate is replaced with a robot. As a machine, the robot is much more precise and consistent in doing its work tasks and might even provide data about its performance while operating. Because it&#39;s so consistent and transparent, any disruptions or spikes in productivity can much more clearly be identified as coming from either the robot or from you. If there are others in your organization who work with the same type of robot in a similar way, then it&#39;s much easier to see how their individual productivity varies from yours.</p><p> In other words, because robots are, by their very nature, much more consistent and transparent than humans, human activity becomes easier to observe if robots join the team. The more robots there are relative to humans, the easier it is to distinguish and measure individual human performance.</p><p></p><p> In one real-world example, a repair facility at a major US-based electronics company experienced a dramatic improvement in its ability to observe employee productivity after robots were implemented to assist workers in the repair process. Because robots, unlike humans, do not get physically tired while performing repetitive tasks, they were able to perform more consistently. This reduced variance in the production process and allowed managers to more clearly observe individual employee behaviors. Many employees followed a regular pattern of being more productive in the morning than in the afternoon, with substantial variance in their afternoon productivity. As a result, many workers ended up with more repairs to finish later in the day as they rushed to meet their daily quotas. This “cramming” of work was especially problematic because it typically resulted in more errors due to the workers having rushed.</p><p> Integrating robots into the repair process eased the tracking of individual employee productivity in two ways. First, robots made different types of errors than humans. The robots&#39; errors were consistent, which made human errors easier to distinguish. Second, the robots themselves provided precise data about their own performance, which made it easier to isolate performance outcomes, both positive and negative, caused by human behavior. This data generation capability allowed managers to better monitor productivity overall and to more easily detect weaknesses in the production process. Managers at the repair facility, for example, hadn&#39;t been aware of the extent of the afternoon cramming behavior until robots were incorporated into the production process. Once the problem was clearly identified, they were able to reorganize the work process to reduce errors; overall error rates at the facility have since improved.</p><p></p><p> These types of improvements in performance measurement can have especially dramatic effects on productivity in combination with performance-based incentives. If it&#39;s easier to observe and measure the performance of individual employees within organizations, good performers — who may have received little reward or recognition because of measurement challenges — become easier to identify and reward, and leaders really can do better in getting the best from their teams. And this is exactly what we find in our research: Companies that adopt robots are also more likely to adopt bonus incentives tied directly to individual performance as opposed to team or organizational performance. With better measurement comes increased rewards for an organization&#39;s good performers, and a more productive workplace. Using robots is fairer for the people who work at an organization.</p><p></p><p> Robots are changing the nature of work. Beyond eliminating some jobs and creating new ones, robots are also changing organizations&#39; ability to get the best from their people, as well as the way we experience work itself. Robots offer an exciting opportunity for businesses to redesign the roles and responsibilities of the humans that work with them, giving those companies a competitive edge over rivals not because of superior technology but because of better processes. The robot revolution isn&#39;t going to eliminate the need for humans. Rather, it&#39;s bringing both new challenges and opportunities for identifying, rewarding, and managing human talent.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Detecting the Good and the Bad With AI: Airbnb&#39;s Naba Banerjee</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operational Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Predictive Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Psychological Safety]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Naba Banerjee’s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Naba Banerjee&#39;s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to let curiosity be her guide as she applies her previous data science experience to the travel industry.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Naba joins hosts Shervin Khodabandeh and Sam Ransbotham to talk about how she and her team use AI and machine learning to increase the safety of the guests and hosts who use Airbnb&#39;s platform. She also discusses collaboration between humans and machines and the importance of recognizing that neither is an infallible decision maker. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-S7-E1-Banerjee-Airbnb-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Naba Banerjee"></p><h4> Naba Banerjee, Airbnb</h4><p> Naba Banerjee is the director of trust product and operations at Airbnb, overseeing the company&#39;s efforts to combat fraud, build trust between hosts and guests, and stop bad actors from using the platform. Her most recent work includes the development of Airbnb&#39;s reservation screening technology, which helps to identify users making potentially high-risk reservations and prevent them from taking advantage of the platform.</p><p> Banerjee has over two decades of experience building products that deliver innovative, customer-centric solutions. She joined Airbnb after spending 13 years at Walmart.com, where she played an instrumental role in the evolution of product management, including shipping packages to customers more quickly and building mobile apps to enable customers to check out faster.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-banerjee"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Machine learning can detect fraudulent activity, but it may also miss good behavior. Find out how one platform company manages these risks and trade-offs on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m Naba Banerjee from Airbnb, and you are listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Today, Shervin and I are speaking with Naba Banerjee, director of trust product and operations at Airbnb. Naba, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you; a pleasure to be here.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think most people know Airbnb, but maybe tell us a brief overview of the company and what you do.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Airbnb stands for a place which fosters connection and belonging. Millions and millions of hosts open up their homes to complete strangers, and you and I and our families get to travel to an exotic destination, and instead of staying at a hotel, you actually get to truly immerse yourself in the local culture. And at times, if you&#39;re really lucky, you get to stay at the house of a host and actually experience hosting as it&#39;s meant to be, thereby creating and fostering connection and belonging.</p><p> And in this world that is increasingly becoming insular and connection is becoming a rare thing, I am so glad to be part of a company that is trying to create more connection. And what my team does, the trust and safety team at Airbnb, is along the entire customer journey, right from the time that you create an account on Airbnb throughout the journey. At times, it is possible that something could go wrong: A fake account could get created, or your account could get taken over. The listing you&#39;re trying to stay at could be a fake listing; the reviews you&#39;re looking at may not be exactly genuine. But our job is to make sure that you can focus on your magical stay, the host can focus on being the perfect host, and we try to anticipate some of these risks, and we minimize the risk of those kinds of issues from happening. And using technology and data to enable that magical user journey is what my team does.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think we all hear headlines where something goes wrong. How much goes wrong in the course of the gazillions of transactions that you do?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. In 2021, we had around 70 million trips that happened on Airbnb, and less than 0.1% of those trips resulted in a host or a guest reporting potentially an issue that happened in that stay. And when our team went in and investigated and actually looked at where the real harm happened or somebody had to be removed from the platform, that number is even smaller.</p><p> I know that even one bad incident is probably too bad and should not be happening, but in the bigger scale of things, what you come back to realize is the majority of people are actually good. Ninety-nine point nine percent of people are meaning to just go about their daily business, enjoy a great stay, or be a great host. But sometimes, [on] that very rare occasion when that bad thing happens, we want to make sure that we reduce the risk of that.</p><p> If you really look at where a person is causing harm to another person, those incidents are like a fraction of a fraction of a fraction. But when we talk about safety, we&#39;re looking at [things like] a carbon monoxide gas leak. It could be slip and fall; it could be property damage, where glass broke and you probably had a stain on your carpet. We are also looking at those kinds of issues.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I&#39;m hearing from what you&#39;re saying is, your role is, No. 1, a good role. You&#39;re the protector of the good and the “warder-offer” of evil, right?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I love that. You should be part of our branding team.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s a good thing, right? It&#39;s a very purposeful role. And the second part of it is, you&#39;re talking about microscopically small incidents.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, needles in a haystack.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Right? And those are fun problems. Tell us more about under the hood — what happens?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I would say it&#39;s three parts. One is, we start with the “why,” which is — you framed it really well — that we are the protector of the good and trying to ward off the bad. We can never say that we stop everything bad. Like, to Sam&#39;s point, you cannot do that. But how are we learning and getting better? And that&#39;s where AI and ML [machine learning] comes in, where [we ask], “How can we use [the] power of data and technology to learn and get better?” And every year, the risks don&#39;t stay the same; the data keeps growing.</p><p> And then the second thing is, “How do we use technology responsibly?” Which is, you could go too blunt and try to block as much as possible to specifically look at fraud and safety incidents and keep them down, but then, if the data that you are using to make these decisions has bias in it, is potentially creating unfairness, then you could close off your doors to a lot of good people who genuinely are just trying to have a good stay. So [it&#39;s about] using technology responsibly. … It is having self-governing mechanisms, which is, we have our privacy team, our data privacy team, our infosec team, our anti-discrimination teams, which are … almost like mirrors to the trust team. [There are also] other teams in Airbnb, where every time we are really laser-focused on this particular fraud vector, this bot detection, this account-takeover detection or party detection, they are constantly making sure that are we using the data in a safe way and a transparent way, giving users control and then not introducing bias.</p><p> And then, lastly, having ways for us to give people a path back, which is, we are going to — based on the data available to us, and the technology available to us, and the maturity of that technology — make our best possible decision. But if we get it wrong, can we create transparency and a process for users to appeal and get back on the platform when we do block them or remove them so that, again, we can learn and get better? So that, at the highest level, is how my team is working under the hood.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And what are some of the use cases?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> One of the use cases that we have talked about quite a bit is, you know … I&#39;ll take you on a little story, which is, when I joined the trust team in 2020, the world had just shut down; the pandemic was raging. And very similar to how the world was waiting for a vaccine, while waiting for a vaccine, we went into lockdown mode.</p><p> That was a blunt instrument … to prevent people from exposing themselves to situations which would make them unsafe. Similarly, Airbnb became an unfortunate product-market fit for unauthorized house parties. When the hotels and bars shut down, unfortunately that less than 1% or 0.1% of users who were looking for places where they could throw these parties, they started renting out Airbnbs. And as a result, we realized that it was causing a lot of pain to our communities of hosts and guests who use this platform, which was based on a foundation of trust. So initially, we had to use some very blunt instruments.</p><p> We first instituted our global party ban, saying that Airbnb does not allow for any kind of party whatsoever. Second, we started looking at some patterns and found that someone under 25 booking an entire home for just one night or two nights less than 50 or so miles away from their home — those seem to be all signals that lead to parties. When parties happen, we usually find … that account was created yesterday. Then we implemented a blunt rule called “under 25,” and we put that in place. Now, we had to be careful, because those rules don&#39;t exactly work globally. But that worked in North America, and we saw right away that there was a reduction in the number of unauthorized parties.</p><p> But over time, just as it happens with rules, we saw that people started to game those rules. They would get an older friend to book the reservation for them. And instead of one night, they would book it for three nights, and so on and so forth. [And] the impact on good users was so high that we said, “We kind of need to move to machine learning. We need to get smarter.” And so we did our first pilot in Australia, where we segmented the place and looked at the place that had this new party model that we&#39;d built versus the other. Do we see a reduction? And again, this is like looking for a needle in the haystack, but we still saw 35% fewer parties in the area that had the party model versus not. And when we started experimenting in North America, we did see that it was as effective as the heuristic, with lesser impact to good users.</p><p> And that kind of gave us the confidence to keep moving forward, because not doing anything was not an option. We had to do something and had to be smart about it. That was one of the use cases where we could go out and talk about it — not claiming that we are stopping all parties, but at least Airbnb is taking a strong stance about it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> One common thread that I&#39;m hearing in how you&#39;re describing the problem and the solution is a need for constant adaptability and ongoing learning, and using the right instrument for the right job. At times it&#39;s a rule, then maybe its unsupervised learning, then there&#39;s a human intervention. It does sound quite multidisciplinary, including the part where the rules change, or the fraudster&#39;s mode of operation changes, and you also have the issue of “Is it too blunt? Does it limit some unintended but good or benign behaviors?” How does the human and machine collaboration or interaction work in these situations?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You summarized it really well, Shervin, which is, it&#39;s not a one-and-done thing. You build it, and then you have to constantly learn and optimize from even the kind of decisions you are making, as well as how the world around you is evolving. And that is an area [that] humans are really good at, which is, you do have to have the discipline of training your models with the latest data, with the right data, making trade-off decisions on what is the optimal threshold at which you are going to say, “OK, this is risky, and we are ready to use that risk.”</p><p> At Airbnb, we have been constantly on this journey of how to leverage humans in the loop. I have a trust operations team in addition to the product and planning teams. This operations team constitutes full-time employees as well as agents globally. And whenever we build a new model, in the beginning we often have the model make a risk threshold-based decision: “This is the top 1%. This is the next tranche. This is the next tranche.” And at times, we will route that to human beings to then create labels on top of that to say, “I agree with the model&#39;s decision,” or, “I don&#39;t agree with the model&#39;s decision,” which then serves as training data back to the model.</p><p> And then, when we have more confidence in the decision-making capability of the model, we would go toward auto-decisioning. This party model, to your point, right now it&#39;s completely auto-decisioned. But what ends up happening is, when we get an appeal back from a user saying, “I was incorrectly blocked,” that then serves as data that&#39;s coming by the customer telling us. And then an agent looks at that appeal and says, “Actually yes, this decision was incorrect.” And if the agent made a correct decision, that customer appealed correctly, and no incident happened, we know that that was a false positive.</p><p> But let&#39;s say the agent approved, and then that customer went on to throw a party; that was a false negative. We are learning from that continuously, but we do it iteratively. First, we try to have the model direct to a human. And again, there is no guarantee that the human is better at decision-making than the model, but we constantly measure the performance. Then we go toward higher-order decisioning [with less] human decisioning. And sometimes we will also have … let&#39;s say the party model makes decisions. People go about their merry way, have the reservation. Sometimes after the reservation has been booked, we will also still have humans look at the top 1% risky reservations to try and correct anything that they can.</p><p> So it is either trying to balance that out as to, when are humans the right people to make the decision? When should the machine make the decision? It&#39;s been a not-easy, nonlinear journey that we have been on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned at first you&#39;re maybe reviewing more cases and then learning from those cases. But at the same time, you have people … these 70 million transactions are happening constantly. And, for example, when you gave the illustration of the hotel … shutdown at the beginning of the pandemic, that&#39;s a time where it&#39;s happening to individual hosts and customers. How do you balance that trade-off of needing to get something in place quickly [while] at the same time needing to go through a process?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That probably is the hardest thing, and the hardest thing in my entire career I would say that I have dealt with. Before this, I was managing all of product for Samsclub.com, which is part of Walmart, and I thought my job was hard then. And while we were serving customers, helping them check out, it still felt like we were on a growth path, and we could choose how fast we grew or how slowly we grew. And I always had teams that were looking at people who were trying to check out [but] couldn&#39;t and serving them while we were building longer-term architecture, but people&#39;s lives were not at stake; [it was] people&#39;s money — fraudsters using stolen credit cards and swindling the company of millions of dollars.</p><p> There is a team at Airbnb that is trying to protect the good and ward off the bad. What we do is that you have to get really good at prioritization, which is also very hard to do in the world of trust and safety.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And in many ways, I mean, the choices are what, Sam, you said in the beginning: These kinds of economies are not risk-free. They cannot be risk-free. And the good collectively outweighs the evil, so then it becomes all about prioritization. But I have to say, we&#39;ve talked to many people in analogous roles that you have, in other organizations — you mentioned Sam&#39;s Club, others — where they&#39;re using technology, digital AI/ML to drive a variety of use cases. I think yours stands out in the sense that it is a continuous balancing act, and the stakes are high. And then you have this sort of thread of purpose and the humility of saying, “Well, we believe that we&#39;ll make mistakes, and the system cannot be mistake-free.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But over time, things are getting better. Which brings me to my next question: How do you measure this, your effectiveness? Is it in terms of number of incidents, and some severity and frequency of bad things happening?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m glad you asked this question, because I was naturally going to go toward this, which is, at the highest level, the metrics that we measure ourselves on are number of fraud incidents per million trips, number of safety incidents per million trips, as well as good user impact. That&#39;s the balancing metric to see “How many good listings did we block? How many good hosts and good guests did we prevent from moving forward to truly understand our false positives and false negatives?” But at the end of the day, it&#39;s good trips that we are looking at across the board.</p><p> We are also looking at dollars in terms of fraud loss that is potentially happening. We are looking at customer support tickets that are coming in, user NPS [Net Promoter Scores] resulting from anyone who encounters a friction that is thrown by our teams. So at a basic level, we are looking at these metrics. But one of the challenges that, for the first time, again, in my career I&#39;ve run into — not so much in the fraud world, where we can A/B test — we are constantly iterating our models.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You are probably also, when you do that, preventing quite benign behaviors and intentions as well. But as you said, there is a point where the human judgment needs to trump and say that this is something where even the risk to one person might be too high. And yes, I mean, we always talk about exploration and exploitation when it comes to machine learning, and sort of ongoing feedback loops, but there&#39;s a cost to learning, always, right? But when I send you a marketing message you may not like, the cost of learning is very minimal, so I will send you many of them, and I&#39;ll do all kinds of A/B/X testing. But when I do that kind of A/B testing to groups or populations where the stakes are higher, then you might as well make that human judgment call of not doing it and relying on retrospective data.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I think you elucidated that point quite well for us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And one question that we ask ourselves is, what makes a human being trust another human being? What makes a human being trust Airbnb? And we are realizing that we can [train] all kinds of models in the background, and you wouldn&#39;t even know whether you were in the risk threshold 1% or 2%, or marked as a good user.</p><p> But there is also a dialogue that needs to happen between Airbnb and you as a guest or you as a host, or between the host and the guest, that truly instills trust. Like when we ask someone, “Would you be comfortable sending your 17-year-old girl to a stranger&#39;s house in Greece, when she wants to backpack before joining college?” You can probably tell this is a personal experience. I have a 17-year-old who&#39;s about to go to college. And I realized that the first thought is, “No — not happening,” and I run trust and safety at Airbnb. But then when I think, “Well, if I could talk to the host; if she&#39;s going to stay with someone else in a house; if that person is a mom like me …”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And we as Airbnb could say, “We are running all these models in the background; don&#39;t worry, your daughter is safe” — I don&#39;t think that&#39;s going to fly. I think as a parent, you will want to have the information you need to see, even though your judgment may not be better than the machine&#39;s. So we are also working on, what is it that we need to say, that we need to do? And sometimes when we say things like, “Airbnb is not going to allow one-night stays that are booked at the last minute within the same neighborhood,” I think it makes a lot of parents feel better too, that OK, at least this option is gone. They will probably figure something else out. And that message cannot be convoluted. That message has to be simple. That message has to be clearly understood. And in addition to asking people what not to do, we also need to encourage people on what good behaviors they should do, like, talk to the host, talk to the guest, ask questions.</p><p> We have launched a program for solo female travelers because we were starting to see a slightly higher rate of maybe personal safety incidents in private rooms with solo female travelers. We started encouraging [women to] find out, is there going to be a lock in your room? Is that lock going to be working? Will you have access to the bathroom just by yourself? Which spaces are shared?哪些不是？ So this was not a model that was stopping anything. This was simply an educational module that we had published in multiple languages, which was really helpful for our solo travelers. Part of my team&#39;s work is not just to build invisible defenses but also to create trust and the perception of trust upfront through education and messaging.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. I have to say, you mentioned you&#39;re a mother of five. And I have to say, I think you stand on very solid ground when it comes to telling your kids what they can and cannot do, because you have so much data and so much experience, versus me when I say something and they&#39;re like, “Well, how would you know?” And you could say, “Well, trust me; I do 70 million transactions a year, and I know what&#39;s going on.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And growing.是的。 I&#39;m happy to talk to your kids, by the way.任何时候。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes, that would be great. I&#39;ll take you up on that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing about your measurements that I thought was interesting, maybe come back a little bit to that. You mentioned some positive metrics, too. So I think it&#39;s a little tempting, and I think even in this conversation we&#39;ve done that, is we titrate toward the negative. And that&#39;s the news problem in general — is that bad news sells papers. Well, I think in the course of this conversation, we&#39;ve shifted toward that. But some of the metrics you mentioned I thought had a more positive ring to them, didn&#39;t they?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And this was an epiphany that we have been having over the past few years, because any kind of machine learning model typically does well when there is a lot of data to learn from. And with these kinds of cases, where out of 70 million-plus trips, when 0.1% of those result in even a report, and a fraction of a fraction of those results in an actual incident where someone gets removed, there is very little to learn from, and as a result, these models take time to mature. Of course, with technology evolving, that is going to get better, but we realized that we have a lot more data about good user behavior.</p><p> We have a lot more users who are actually coming in, booking their stay months in advance; they are probably checking in on time, leaving the property even better than they found it, communicating with the host and the guests, leaving honest reviews. So if we can actually flip the switch, and while we need to continue to look for the anomalies and the trends and the bad actors, if we can get really good at learning what good behavior looks like while making sure that we are also measuring for potential bias or discrimination and privacy compliance in how we collect and use this data, then that can be really powerful in informing when something does look risky. For example, if an account typically is accessed from the US, [and] suddenly we see that that IP is now accessing from the Philippines, and it feels like “Oh, this is an account takeover.” But if this is a good user who has typically been traveling around the world quite a bit, maybe this is not an account takeover, and there is history there from the good user behavior for us to be smarter about “What does normal look like and what does an anomaly look like?” Not broadly, but very specifically, based on the user segment.</p><p> So this is not new stuff, but I think we sometimes tend to obsess about just really learning what bad behavior looks like and getting good at detecting that, as opposed to complementing what an anomaly looks like [compared] to what normal behavior looks like.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. And you have such a wealth of insights and information in a field that is really an evolving field. I mean, it&#39;s not like a typical collaborative filtering situation where “users like you also bought this.” I mean, so much more goes on in terms of matching. This must be a very interesting and worthwhile problem to get your arms around.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And it requires us to get out of our trust and safety silo and work really closely with our search, relevance, and personalization teams because our job — unlike my job when I used to work in e-commerce — is not just to do the collaborative filtering and say, “People like you bought this, so you should buy this,” or, “You traveled to Paris, so maybe next you want to go to Rome.”</p><p> It&#39;s about … you&#39;re traveling with the family this time. You have little kids; you probably want day care, and we know that this host offers day care, and this location might be great for you. Or with the same customer maybe traveling alone, maybe we need to offer up different recommendations. And having these trust and safety signals embedded into our search-relevance algorithms can get really powerful in matching the right person with the right listing.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Naba, you didn&#39;t start at Airbnb. Tell us a bit about how you got there. You referenced Walmart and some background there, but how did you end up in your current role?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I was the first female engineer in my family. My father took a chance on me and said, “You&#39;re curious. You&#39;re a forever learner. Do you want to do engineering?” And I had no idea what engineering was at that time, but I signed up anyway and went on to become the first female engineer in my family.</p><p> I worked with Tata Consultancy Services, then went on to join Cognizant, came through Cognizant to the US, and worked for some time at AAA. I would just keep going to different projects and different jobs that would help me learn something completely new.</p><p> Walmart happened around 2006. I was asked to work on supply chain at Walmart, which is probably, if you want to learn supply chain at a company, that&#39;s the company to go to. And while I was doing supply chain, every year I kept getting bigger and bigger responsibilities and projects until I found myself, from Walmart, leading almost all of the supply chain teams to going to Sam&#39;s Club, which is a part of Walmart — leading all of product and front end and cart and checkout and marketing and pricing, which I had never done before. But it gave me a chance to get a well-rounded experience learning how the back end of a large retailer works, as well as [how] front-end customer experience works.</p><p> And right after Sam&#39;s Club, I was asked to lead search. Right around that time, I was starting to get really interested in a world that runs on machine learning and AI, and search was a great landing ground for me. I did a course from MIT, interestingly, to learn about the application of AI and ML, and that gave me the courage to take on the search job.</p><p> And from there, Airbnb happened, after 13 years, almost, at Walmart. I was so curious about the travel industry and this marketplace that was so different from anything I had done in Walmart. So the theme here is that I have always gravitated toward something that helps me leverage the skills that I have but then use my curiosity and learning to do something completely new and build myself up as I go along. That&#39;s kind of my background.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Naba, we have a section now where we ask you a series of rapid-fire questions, and just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind. What is your proudest AI/ML moment?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You&#39;re asking me to choose between my different teams, which is career-limiting for me. But I will say that the work that we did on party detection and party risk reduction was groundbreaking, and there&#39;s no one else in the industry who did it the way we did, so that is [a] really proud [moment for me]. But I am proud of all my teams, just for the record.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer. What worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> What worries me is how powerful it is. We had a chance to get to see [OpenAI CEO] Sam Altman up close and in person as he came to Airbnb. And just how fast this technology is improving and how much capability it has … I worry about it falling into the wrong hands. I worry that while my team has this technology, the fraudsters have this technology too, and so I worry about, if today we are worried about fake IDs and fake spam messages being sent to our hosts and guests, how much more advanced this technology is going to get and how much more difficult it is going to get for us to detect the good from the bad. And I think it&#39;ll be AI to the rescue as well in detecting fake AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Your favorite activity that involves no technology?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Painting with watercolors. I love painting nature. And so paper, watercolors, and just peace and tranquility, no technology, is my favorite thing to do. And of course hugging my kids and spending time with them just listening to their day, trying to make them not be on their cellphones while they talk to me. Those two.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I wanted to be a teacher. I come from a family of teachers, and I feel so much joy when I&#39;m seeing someone&#39;s eyes light up with the gift of knowledge. I am a forever learner. Every job that I take has been completely different from my previous job; it&#39;s because I love to learn. And so, yeah, that&#39;s what I wanted to be.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And you probably do a fair amount of teaching in your current role anyway.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I do a lot of mentoring.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;ve taught us quite a lot.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, thank you. I do do a lot of mentoring, because I feel like if someone else can see me do what I do, that will make them feel that they can do it too. So if I can just do that, that&#39;s my life&#39;s mission accomplished.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> My greatest wish for the world, actually, is to not be so afraid; to give it a chance. Because I think sometimes our fear of the bad holds us from embracing the good. There is so much wasted effort that goes into activities that should be automated through AI — so many patients who are not getting treatment; so many companies that probably need help and need so much funding to stand up basic things that can be done by AI; so many countries, probably, who are underdeveloped [but could] get so much advantage. I know that when it falls into the wrong hands, it can be used for bad, but the world has more good people than bad people, and I believe in the power of us using AI for good — using our collective goodness.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think everyone will probably resonate with your idea that the world is better than it is bad. We do tend to hear most of the negative stories, but it&#39;s refreshing to hear how, one, how much attention you&#39;re paying to try and to prevent those, but also to hear something about the good stories too that your platform enables. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. We&#39;ve enjoyed it.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, Sam. Thank you, Shervin. My pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, we&#39;re joined by Zan Gilani, principal product Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>