<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 12 月 19 日星期二 12:00:36 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator><item><title>火星上的人工智能：NASA 的 Vandi Verma</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Systems]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Vandi Verma saw the Spirit and Opportunity rovers land on Mars while she was working toward a Ph.D. in robotics, it set her on a path toward working at NASA in space exploration. Perhaps unsurprisingly, today, as chief engineer for robotic operations at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL), Vandi sees the biggest opportunities for [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当万迪·维尔玛 (Vandi Verma) 攻读博士学位时，看到勇气号和机遇号火星车登陆火星。在机器人技术领域，这让她走上了在美国宇航局从事太空探索工作的道路。也许并不奇怪，今天，作为 NASA 喷气推进实验室 (JPL) 机器人操作的首席工程师，Vandi 看到了机器人和自动化领域人工智能的最大机遇。</p><p>在<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客的这一集中，她描述了火星漫游者依赖人工智能的方式，包括该技术在数字孪生模拟中的使用，使喷气推进实验室的科学家能够在实际控制火星漫游者之前练习驾驶技能。她还与主持人 Shervin Khodabandeh 和 Sam Ransbotham 讨论了 NASA 对人工智能的使用及其应对风险的方法如何为那些希望模拟地球上真实场景的组织提供经验教训。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E6-Verma-NASA-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="万迪·韦尔玛"></p><h4>万迪·维尔马，美国宇航局</h4><p>Vandi Verma 是 NASA 喷气推进实验室移动与机器人部门的首席工程师兼副部门经理。她还担任 Mars 2020 Perseverance 漫游车的机器人操作总工程师。曾任移动与机器人科室助理科长、科员组主管、可操作机器人组主管。</p><p> Verma 致力于新的机器人技术能力，包括研发；任务设计；原型制作；飞行开发、测试和发射；以及着陆和地面操作。自 2008 年以来，她一直在火星探索漫游车任务中参与火星机器人操作，包括勇气号和机遇号、好奇号漫游车、毅力号漫游车和独创号直升机。</p><p>在加入喷气推进实验室之前，她领导了 NASA 艾姆斯研究中心团队，开发了用于操作自主系统的 PLEXIL（计划执行交换语言），并开发了已部署在漫游车和载人航天项目上的技术。</p><p>维尔玛获得了博士学位。 2005年获得卡内基梅隆大学机器人学博士学位。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我们可以从人工智能在火星上的应用中学到什么？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我是来自 NASA JPL 的 Vandi Verma，你们正在听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能</cite>。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嘿，大家好，欢迎。今天，谢尔文和我真的非常兴奋能够与美国宇航局喷气推进实验室的总工程师万迪·维尔马交谈。这真的是很酷的东西。 Vandi，从我们的先睹为快来看，我们非常高兴您能参加演出。感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。</p><p><strong>万迪·维尔玛：</strong>谢谢你邀请我来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我承认我对你的工作非常着迷——我相信每个人都是如此——但让我们向每个人介绍一下你所做的事情。您能否首先概述一下喷气推进实验室以及您的具体角色？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我是 NASA 喷气推进实验室移动与机器人系统的副经理，我还与 2020 年火星任务的总工程师一起工作，该任务包括毅力号火星车和独创号直升机。</p><p> JPL 是 NASA 的一个中心，专门制造用于太空探索的机器人。 NASA 的使命是探索、发现和扩展知识，造福人类，而我们所做的就是机器人技术方面的工作。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>当你说“机器人”时，我想到的是人工智能，但火星任务对于人工智能等新技术来说似乎是一个非常具有挑战性的地方。您和喷气推进实验室如何在机器人技术领域使用人工智能？</p><p><strong>万迪·维尔玛：</strong>对。在一段时间内，人工智能已经改变了我们所说的，有些事情是我们在地面上做的，有些事情是我们在机器人上做的，所以我将谈谈其中的一些。因此，总的来说，我们更倾向于自主能力——更接近你所认为的自动驾驶汽车所使用的——并且其中大部分可能不是经典机器学习本身，尽管我们用它来告知我们的很多工作。</p><p>事实上，通过 Perseverance，我们所做的驾驶中有 88% 是自动驾驶。所以流动站有相机：它正在拍摄图像；它可以探测地形并找出危险区域并绕过障碍物。它实际上非常有趣，因为它在人类从未见过的地形上行驶，所以我们甚至无法向它提供此类信息。所以这绝对是自主导航的一种形式。</p><p>在驱动器结束时，我们也正在努力取得很大进展，因为我们处于这个非常恶劣的环境中，我们的使命是通过毅力收集和缓存一定数量的样本，因为这是我们第一次实际上将把他们带回地球。但我们希望他们来自尽可能不同的地方，所以我们想要进行大量的驾驶。如果你一直停下来，你就不会取得那么大的进步。但谁知道一路上是否有一些真正令人兴奋的事情我们会错过呢？在我们的世界里，我们称之为恐龙骨头。</p><p>我们的漫游车具有人工智能功能，它将拍摄广角图像，观察大片地形，然后尝试找出其中最有趣的特征是什么。我们有很多仪器，但其中一个仪器是<a href="https://mars.nasa.gov/mars2020/spacecraft/instruments/supercam/">SuperCam 仪器</a>，它的功能很多。它有一个激光，你可以从远处向岩石发射激光，它会产生等离子体，我们用望远镜头来研究它。这是一个非常狭窄的视野——你知道，一毫弧度——所以如果你尝试对你看到的整个视图进行这种操作，你会在那里待上几天。</p><p>因此，本质上，我们使用人工智能来找出“我们应该放弃的最有趣的事情是什么？”然后你可以将数据发回并告诉地球上的科学家。这也是非常有价值的。所以我们就这么做了。</p><p>然后，你知道，还有计划。我们使用很多资源，例如……主要是在火星上，当你拥有航天器时，环境很恶劣。所以[我们]正在考虑“如何加热东西——保持在合适的温度？我们有多少力量？”你需要与地球沟通；地球在哪里？我们也有船上计划，更多地从更大的角度来考虑事情。所以所有这些事情都是我们所做的事情的例子。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这样的例子有很多。事实上，你主要是自动驾驶——这似乎是一个令人着迷的世界。你提到发现一些有趣的东西。那里的目标函数是什么？你如何发现某件事很有趣？我知道我认为什么是有趣的，但请告诉我让机器找出什么是有趣的过程。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为定义有趣的最有趣的事情之一是它把它放在人类身上。事实上，我们很难告诉机器我们希望它们做什么，对吧？为了让我们知道什么是有趣的，我们有很多不同的参数，科学家可以使用它们来指定“我正在寻找该地区有趣的特定尺寸、特定反照率和形状的浅色调岩石。 ”我们可以改变这一点。因此，根据我们所处的地形，我们有这些不同的模板，实地科学家可以帮助我们确定这些模板。我们将其发送给机器人说：“我们正在寻找这种东西。”</p><p>我们也做了一些研究，我们告诉它，“你现在跟踪我们看到的所有东西”——这被称为新颖性检测，我们实际上还没有部署它，但是“找到我们还没有看过的东西”在。”那是另一件事。</p><p>但这里有两件事。当我们进行探索时，我们正在寻找新的事物，但我们也尝试用多种不同的仪器来描述我们所看到的事物的特征，因为我们正在尝试为我们的假设收集大量具有统计意义的数据。我们试图弄清楚“火星上是否可能存在生命，尤其是古代生命？”</p><p>所以这个难题......有假设，你试图回答特定的问题，然后科学家会告诉机器人他们感兴趣的问题。我们实际上已经使用超级计算机将其转换为我们可以的参数然后上传到机器人。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以人们粗略地描述了他们想要什么，然后你有一些超级计算机，地球上的东西，试图将其转换成一组参数，然后将其发送到流动站以找出什么寻找。我理解正确吗？</p><p><strong>万迪·维尔玛：</strong>没错。我认为，这是人工智能可以提供很大帮助的领域，因为我们仍然处于机器人技术的那个阶段，在很多领域我们都有很多旋钮。我们可以做很多事情，但艺术在于调整这个多变量空间。事实上，你知道，仅就 Perseverance 而言——我们称之为软件参数，[而且]这甚至没有考虑到硬件设计和其他因素——我们就有超过 64,000 个显式参数。它们保存在非易失性存储器中。这甚至没有考虑您可以发送的命令的参数。因此，您可以通过多种方式来表达您要说的话，这就是我们可以使用大量功能来了解我们想要做的事情的正确组合的地方。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>是的，类似的组合看起来像是会爆炸，所以它似乎是机器学习的一个很好的工具，当你有这么多参数时，可以找出正确的一组最佳参数或下一个参数来选择。从中选择。就像你说的，你无法用激光照射整个火星表面。嗯，您也无法同时探索 64,000 个参数。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>是的，你说得完全正确。然而，挑战和美丽——是什么让它成为一个如此有趣的环境——出错的幅度非常低，所以当航天器成功登陆火星如此困难时，你不能进行实验。这是国家资产。所以我们说，“你不温顺”，但你却在尽一切努力确保它会成功。您不能将车辆置于危险之中。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>嗯嗯。大多数听的人显然不会去探索火星，但当我们考虑你可以做的类比时，人们现在正在决定风险投资组合，关于他们将多少交给机器来决定，在你的情况下，决定新奇或决定开车去哪里。其他人也在做出同样的风险决策。现在，考虑到资产及其所在位置，您对风险的容忍度似乎极低。但我觉得其他拥有人工智能和新技术的人也必须做出类似的风险决策。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为你完全正确。事实上，我认为在某些方面，你可能认为我们有风险承受能力，但我们必须如此频繁地做出这些决定，如果我们实际上非常厌恶风险，我们将什么也不做，根本不会采取任何行动。制定一个评估流程，并了解特定情况下的阈值在哪里，是团队中每个人在他们所做的工作中都要学会做的事情。所以我认为这实际上可以很好地推广到其他领域。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>回到您之前谈到自动驾驶时所说的话：您确实无法在从未去过的地方练习驾驶，那么在到达那里之前如何练习？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>这有两个要素。一是我们如何进行自主能力实践，然后我们如何让在某种程度上仍然需要指导自主能力的人类进行实践？所以我们两者都做。就为行星体建造机器人而言——这是非常不同的，对吧？火星上的重力、压力、温度，所有这些都是不同的——我们创建了模拟。我帮助编程了毅力号上运行的一些软件，而且，实际上从一开始，我们就开发软件模拟，因为我们实际上可能没有完整的地球复制品。我们在地球上创建了一个全尺寸模型进行测试，但这也在任务的早期阶段不断发展。所以我们正在构建硬件，他们也在试验这些硬件——“最好的车轮设计是什么？最好的材料是什么？” ——当我们编写软件时。</p><p>关于“如何构建这些模拟，以便它们帮助我们正确地表示我们所处的环境？”有很多想法。但随后我们也开始剥离某些硬件接口。因此，我们将在更多类型的商业接口机器人部件上运行真正的飞行软件，但在我们的火星场中。我们有一个火星庭院。它不是火星，但我们尝试有斜坡和基岩等特征。然后我们构建完整的复制品，运行我们将在火星上使用传感器进行的实际计算，并对其进行测试。之后，我们进行具体测试。因此，我们将对某些零件进行热真空室测试，并且我们会一点一点地进行。</p><p>当我们进入大气层时，我们用地球上的飞机进行了一些测试，因为我们必须考虑如何登陆火星。但除此之外，一旦我们到达火星，我们就会分阶段进行。因此，我们实际上可能让自主导航告诉我们它将做什么，但实际上并没有进行导航。</p><p>我们实际上会让人类来指挥驱动器，正如我们所说的那样，但我们实际上是让它影子并说，“让我们看看你会做什么。”所以我们分阶段进行。</p><p>我们确实希望进展非常快，因为如果你这样做太久……这就是在火星上宝贵的时间。这就是我们推出自主能力的方式。现在，就人类而言，自 2008 年以来，我一直在火星上驾驶机器人执行多个不同的任务。你开始了解火星，这需要时间。所以我们一直在缩短时间。我们有学员，我们有课堂课程，所以我们从火星和数据中获取驱动器，并让他们离线计划。然后我们就有了阴影。所以现在的大多数驾驶，我实际上有其他人在键盘上进行训练，你在训练他们成为飞行员时就在观察他们。所以我们这样做，实际上仍然需要数年时间。</p><p>我们中的一些帮助建造机器人的人将从 Sol 0 开始，这是我们登陆火星任务的开始。然后，很快，在半年到一年之内，我们开始让下一批人来。因为如果你看一下任务，它们可能会在火星上停留很长时间，所以你必须对人员进行培训才能做到这一点。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>实际上，就其他人正在做的事情而言，有很多有趣的方面。但你提到模拟和构建数字孪生。你不想在火星上练习。你想在地球上练习，或者你以数字方式练习，特别是，正如你提到的——我没有意识到这一点——即使你可以练习，甚至不存在可以练习的硬件；这是同时发生的。而且，人类也在这个过程中学习这一理念，并且你不会让任何人在开车的第一天就放松驾驶；你也不会在第一天就关闭漫游车自行驾驶。所以这个学习的过程也是很有趣的。</p><p>我也觉得这很有趣。 ......你在谈论缩短时间——当你获得更多经验时，你可以缩短那个时间。由于世界上有很多人部署人工智能解决方案来完成不同的事情，我猜很多人一开始都会非常仔细地观察它们，但后来逐渐越来越信任它们。我猜你和你正在谈论的另一个人在键盘上工作的方式也是一样的——可能第一天看着他们打字，但现在在键盘上的时间减少了。所以我认为，尽管火星看起来像是一个陌生的环境，但其他人如何使用人工智能也有很多相似之处。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>是的，我认为你完全正确。有趣的事情之一是，你可以从地球上完全不同的地方、完全不同的机器人（实际上可能具有不同的移动特性）中获得什么？但人类能够很好地提取模式。因此，如果您是执行一次漫游车任务的漫游车驾驶员，您实际上会花费更少的时间，就像您所说的那样。但也有一部分原因是，我们的用户界面变得更加复杂。</p><p>如果你看看我们用来操作和驱动机器人的界面——操作机械臂并实际采样，这在某些方面甚至更加复杂——它们也发生了显着的演变。我们过去常常发送指令——就像字面上的命令行指令一样，就像您对程序上的函数调用所做的那样。现在我们以图形化的方式进行操作，您实际上是在地图上选择航路点。所以我认为这也非常有帮助，因为我们已经开始让人类关注人类直觉和我们积累的丰富经验可以带来问题的方面。 ……因为人工智能，尽管它变得非常复杂，但我们拥有的能力，仍然受到我们创造它时的想象力的限制。通过在火星上操作机器人数十年，我们非常清楚这一点。我们总是告诉自己，“什么是超出我们想象的？”因为它会发生——它每次都会发生。我们总是对这些令人惊奇的东西感到惊讶，但最终却以一种我们没有想到的方式使用它。这有点像你一直看到的——你可能为各种其他地球应用开发的技术。人们还会想出其他什么东西并将其用于什么目的？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>人们都很疯狂。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我的意思是，我认为它们很创新！</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>对。这确实是你想要的，因为你不只是试图一遍又一遍地做同样的事情。</p><p>你提到了<em>惊喜</em>这个词，我认为这是一个有趣的事情。我们讨论的一件事是，您进行所有这些模拟，并且希望某些东西能够正常工作，但您不希望它完全完美地工作，因为您试图发现一些您没有预料到的东西。那么请告诉我们一些关于这个过程如何运作的信息：“嘿，我们希望事情按照我们希望的那样进行，但我们也对发生我们没有预料到的事情持开放态度？”</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>您提出的观点非常好……模拟不会完全按照事物的执行方式进行。事实上，它几乎从来都不是。我们自动驾驶的部分原因是因为详细级别的表面信息（火星车将从其火星相机中获取的图像）我们无法足够精确地模拟它。因此，我们在地面上模拟的任何路径都是对地形的采样。你知道，我们有一个抽象；我们有一张轨道图。但它是在非常粗略的水平上进行的。如果我们已经有了详细地图，我们甚至不需要自主导航。我们实际上只是编写脚本来驱动。</p><p>一旦它行驶了 5 [或] 10 米，它就会比我们发送此命令之前获得更多的环境信息。因此，到那时，它比我们所能做的任何事情都更有能力做出决策并做正确的事情。所以我们要学会不要过度约束它。这实际上是很难教新人的事情之一：你已经在模拟中完善了它，但你必须预测你的模拟实际上是模拟。这不是现实。如果你不给它足够的回旋余地，你实际上会让它惨败。</p><p>因此，我们有这些我们称之为“放在盒子里”的东西，对于自主能力，我们有点希望人类说，“我有一些洞察力，我希望你留在这个区域内。”可以有一百米吧？就像，一个非常大的区域。因此，我们创造了这些皮带来限制这种行为，但皮带的长度是一门艺术。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Vandi，这是一次非常有趣的讨论。你能分享一下你是如何最终担任这个角色的吗？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我记得观看火星探索漫游者着陆。我当时在读研究生。我正在攻读博士学位。在机器人技术方面，实际上当时是因为我已经上了一门课——这是一门编程课，我们正在对移动机器人进行编程。这太有趣了，我想我把所有的业余时间都花在了我们在课程结束时举行的比赛上，我们必须让这些机器人在迷宫中导航。</p><p>让我着迷的是，你可以将理论应用到实际机器上，并看到它在环境中做一些事情。事实上，我一直在研究人工智能；我的硕士专业是人工智能，这很有趣。但在这里，机器人有一些令人满足的东西，你可以实际看到机器人在物理世界中运行。我喜欢太空探索；太空和机器人技术的结合堪称完美。机器人最终坚持了很长时间，火星探索漫游者的任务激发了一个机会——本来应该是 90 天——我毕业了，而且还在火星上。所以我实际上从未想过我会真正开始研究它们，而我做到了。</p><p>所以我认为这就是它的产生方式，我对它很着迷，当我在大学时，美国宇航局与大学进行了很多合作，因为使命的很大一部分是教育。这样你就可以接触到这一点。你可以研究 NASA 感兴趣的问题，我的论文与此非常一致，这就是我进入它的方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>非常酷。您要感谢一些工程师，让您介入并完成任务，使您的任务得以长久延续。</p><p>我们有一个环节想问您一些快速问题。只需回答我们这样做时您想到的第一件事即可。</p><p>您认为目前人工智能最大的机遇是什么？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为最大的机会……实际上是在机器人领域。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>令人震惊。</p><p><strong>万迪·维尔玛：</strong>是的。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>好的。人们对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为他们最大的误解是它无法推断。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>嗯。那么，您想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我想开飞机。我的父亲是一名飞行员。我想成为一名丛林飞行员。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，从那时起你就获得了飞行员执照，所以你已经实现了这一点。</p><p><strong>万迪·维尔玛：</strong>是的，我做到了。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您是否认为在某些地方我们过于努力地让人工智能适应它不适合的解决方案？我们是否将该工具应用在错误的地方？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>我认为有时在某个阶段你可以这样说神经网络。所以我其实有点不好意思说，是不是走错地方了？鉴于现阶段的技术，这取决于您的酒吧所在的位置，以了解是否值得这样做。我认为这取决于你的门槛和视野。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>好的，这很公平。您认为如果人工智能现在能够做到但目前还无法做到的一件事，那就太好了？你可以改变的一件事是什么？</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>你知道，其中一件事是我们确实拥有大量数据。将其应用于某些太空探索的限制之一是，您仍然需要对代币或其提取的内容进行大量审核。所以我认为仍然有很多调整。我认为这就是它的挑战。如果你能克服这个问题，我认为你的潜力就会被释放出来。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>很棒的讨论。当然，我猜我们的听众中没有一个人在火星上驾驶机器人，但我认为人们可以从通过这个过程学到的东西中学到很多东西。人们可能不是为了模拟火星而构建数字孪生，而是为了模拟地球上的过程而构建数字孪生。我们越来越多地通过这些设备和人工智能传感来体验世界。即使我们不在太空环境中工作，我认为我们也可以从您和您的团队所学到的知识中学到很多东西。感谢您今天抽出时间与我们交谈。</p><p> <strong>Vandi Verma：</strong>非常感谢您与观众分享我们所做的一些事情。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabadenh：</strong>感谢您的聆听。下次我和 Sam 会见第一资本公司首席科学家兼企业人工智能主管 Prem Natarajan 时，请加入我们。新的一年，请与我们一起。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/ai-on-mars-nasas-vandi-verma/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>无处不在的商店是零售业的新面貌吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David R. Bell, Santiago Gallino, and Antonio Moreno. <p>David R. Bell ( <a href="https://twitter.com/davidbnz">@davidbnz</a> ) 是纽约 Idea Farm Ventures 的总裁兼联合创始人。圣地亚哥·加利诺 (Santiago Gallino) 是沃顿商学院运营、信息和决策副教授，也是查尔斯·W·埃文斯杰出学者。 Antonio Moreno ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tmorenog">@tmorenog</a> ) 是哈佛商学院工商管理学 Sicupira Family 副教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Business Models]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Omnichannel Retailing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Retail Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Nearly 30 years ago, a fledgling startup called Amazon made its first online sale, and a retail revolution began. Dubbed “the Everything Store” by Brad Stone in his book of the same name, Amazon leveraged digital technologies to expand the very nature of retail, demonstrating that selling physical goods [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Bell-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>近 30 年前，一家名为亚马逊的新兴初创公司首次进行在线销售，一场零售革命开始了。布拉德·斯通在其同名书中将亚马逊称为“万物商店”，它利用数字技术扩展了零售的本质，表明销售实体商品不再需要实体店面。</p><p>但如今，零售业的基石——地点——再次扩大，我们所说的“<em>无处不在的商店”</em>的出现正在影响全渠道战略，并为新进入者和现有企业释放潜在价值。</p><p></p><p>卓越的零售需要通过体验与客户进行最佳互动，并以最小的摩擦实现产品交付，而从历史上看，这两种情况都发生在商店中。<em>无处不在的商店</em>指的是一种新的零售体验，其中客户参与和产品履行发生在本地环境中，也就是说，它们不依赖于专门建造的商店或仓库。它们使品牌和零售商能够更广泛地思考客户互动应该在哪里进行以及库存应该放在哪里。</p><p></p><h3>全渠道现在是什么样子</h3><p>全渠道零售包括四种不同的客户参与和履行方式：传统零售店；在线销售加上实体展厅，客户可以在其中与产品互动；网上销售，店内提货；纯电子商务，其中履行和参与都发生在网上。</p><p>如今，通过商店进行的传统零售仍占美国销售额的 80% 以上<a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>当然，该比例因<a href=" https://www.statista.com/statistics/203043/online-share-of-total-us-retail-revenue-projection/">产品类型</a>而异：可以轻松在线描述的不太复杂的商品与电子商务非常吻合，而消费者更喜欢在购买前看到和触摸，例如浓缩咖啡机和烤架，可能会受益于展示空间，从而有利于某种形式的线下购物体验。</p><p>混合模型将数字技术用于一种功能，将物理技术用于另一种功能。对于电子商务引入之前的传统零售商来说，“在线购买，店内提货”是必须的，并且会产生额外的好处，即在零售地点提货的顾客可能会增加购买其他产品当他们来访时。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>特别是对于直接面向消费者的零售商来说，Warby Parker 商店和 Bonobos 的 Guideshops 等陈列室可以提高品牌知名度，并允许顾客在购买前检查产品或试穿。他们擅长为首次客户和需求更复杂的客户提供服务。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p>下一波全渠道零售浪潮由创新者引领，例如总部位于洛杉矶的户外家具品牌 Outer，该品牌进入市场后直接向消费​​者销售，无需建立实体店。 Outer 的联合创始人 Jiake Liu 和 Terry Lin 看到了分类零售的机会：他们没有创建传统的陈列室，而是将顾客的后院变成了陈列室。潜在客户访问现有客户的家中，以脱机方式体验和与其他客户互动。将客户的场所变成陈列室的主要优点是，鉴于他们可能会具有社会人口统计学特征，因此附近的其他人可能是良好的销售前景。</p><p>这种分类的零售方法也可以作为独立业务的模型。例如，由风险投资的平台Minoan使短期住宿空间的所有者（例如酒店和Airbnb租赁）可以从特定品牌购买，向其客人提供这些品牌的产品，然后邀请客人购买这些商品待在酒店的同时。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Minoan联合创始人Marc Hostovsky呆在Airbnb时有一个灯泡时刻，他欣赏舒适的床，厨刀和其他家具。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Marc和Minoan联合创始人Shobhit Khandelwal发生了这种情况，在非商店环境中有机地体验新产品令人信服。 Hostovsky是Walmart.com和Jet.com的校友，告诉我们：“最佳产品体验不会在屏幕上发生。”</p><p>如上所述，我们还在跟踪无处不在的存储的出现。 WareClouds是一家由风险投资的城市物流初创公司，位于智利，通过使用住宅地点存储库存来分类品牌的零售，旨在明年在美国推出。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>这种方法将使品牌能够绕过传统仓库，并利用房主的未使用空间。与使用传统仓库空间相比，该策略可能会节省成本，允许品牌根据需求波动调整容量，并将库存更接近更多客户。后者使当地司机的交付速度更快，反过来又可以通过避免仓储费用来增强客户体验并为品牌节省资金。</p><p></p><p></p><p>虽然对于无处不在的商店和无处不在的存储仍然是早期的日子，但零售商应该开始探索这些策略所提供的可能性，并考虑随之而来的挑战。品牌将如何确保本地空间按预期展示其产品？分布式存储系统将如何管理数十个单独房屋的库存？零售商和品牌可能会选择与Minoan和WareClouds等专业企业合作，将执行元素委托。</p><p>零售商还必须牢记，在非传统空间中与客户会面会带来一些风险：重要的是，客户不要将这些举措视为侵入性，而且是否会大规模接受他们还有待观察。如果品牌可以正确地做到这一点，那么一些最伟大的面对面零售创新将根本不需要商店。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-everywhere-stores-the-new-face-of-retail/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>技能优先的人才策略</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 14 Dec 2023 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aneesh Raman, Elyse Rosenblum, and Abbie Lundberg. <p>Aneesh Raman是LinkedIn机会项目的副总裁兼主管。机会项目与私营和公共部门的领导者合作，在AI时代建立了更透明，动态和公平的全球劳动力市场。 Elyse Rosenblum是Life的创始人兼董事总经理，这是一家人才战略咨询公司，与领导雇主一起实施技能优先的人才实践，既可以带来商业利益和社会影响。 Abbie Lundberg是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>的总编辑。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Management Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading A. Raman and E. Rosenblum, &#8220;Focus on Skills to Grow Your Workforce,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, June 21, 2023. Skills dominate current conversations about how to spot, foster, and grow talent. A skills-first talent strategy sets your workforce up for long-term resilience in a world where jobs keep changing, and artificial intelligence increasingly [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>A. Raman和E. Rosenblum，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">专注于发展您的员工的技能</a>”， <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> ，2023年6月21日。</p></aside><p>技能主导着有关如何发现，培养和发展人才的当前对话。在这个工作不断变化的世界中，技能优先的人才策略为长期的韧性设定了您的劳动力，而人工智能越来越多地影响工作。成功的公司将他们的技能优先实践与整个员工旅程保持一致。</p><p>在本网络研讨会中，您将学习：</p><ul><li>为什么在人工智能时代，现在技能优先的实践比以往任何时候都重要。</li><li>关于如何建立技能优先人才策略的三个大想法。</li><li>在您的技能优先努力中重点介绍的10个主要测量值。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/a-skills-first-talent-strategy/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>好问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:23:35 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Elizabeth Heichler是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>的杂志编辑总监。</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko One of the enduring challenges of leadership is avoiding being persuaded that you have all the answers. When anxious employees seek certainty, it might feel like it’s your job to deliver. But numerous articles in this issue of MIT Sloan Management Review remind us how much more important it can be to ask [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-EditLetter_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p>领导层的持久挑战之一是避免说服您有所有答案。当焦虑的员工寻求确定性时，可能会觉得您要交付的工作。但是，在本期<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>中的许多文章提醒我们提出问题可能更重要。</p><p>质疑传统智慧：您可以发现“每个人都知道”不再成立。电子商务的真实性之一可能是这种情况：在线购买体验应尽可能无摩擦。<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/">马可·贝蒂尼（Marco Bertini），迭戈·阿帕里西奥（Diego Aparicio）和艾琳·阿丁利</a>。他们解释了推出正确类型的摩擦类型如何减慢买家的速度，并给他们更多时间评估他们的购买决定并提高他们的忠诚度。</p><p></p><p>质疑您从常规支出中获得的价值，例如您在领导培训中的投资。 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/">Hannes Leroy，Moran Anisman-Razin和Jim Detert</a>的研究发现，在众多领导力发展计划中缺乏严格的教育程度，并且缺乏有意义的结果。对公司购买这些计划的责任是为了确切询问自己需要发展哪些技能以提高战略优先级，然后询问提供者的更多尖锐问题。作者认为，如果客户采用更严格的标准来选择这些程序，则可能会促使提供者收紧课程和教学方法。</p><p>质疑您的员工对他们对业务和员工经验的看法。 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/">Ayse Karaevli和SerdenÖzcan</a>在研究德国的前50家公共公司及其与董事会成员互动的不同方法时，发现那些寻求员工投入的人在广泛的主题上的投入更好，在管理劳动力竞争方面做得更好支持变革。作者指出，使用更具包容性决策过程的公司领导者赋予了员工战略责任，并确定了共同的目标和利益，避免了与其劳动力的争议和公共冲突。所有这些策略都要求领导者不仅提出问题，而且还准备好聆听答案。</p><p></p><p>质疑您对他人的信念的理解，以建立有关有争议问题的对话。我很有趣地听到首席执行官担心即将举行的2024年总统大选以及工作场所意识形态的分裂潜力。 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/">Kenji Yoshino和David Glasgow</a>旨在为他们提供策略和策略，以尊重其他人在艰难的话题上互动。在他们最近的书《<cite>说正确的话：如何谈论身份，多样性和正义》</cite>中汲取的文章中，他们为面对深刻分歧的勇敢对话提供了一个框架。他们定位适当的对话切入点的方法可以改变我们面对看似棘手的差异的方式。为了准备这样的对话，至关重要的是要以开放的思想研究对方的立场，并提出可能提供有关形成人们意见的经验，世界观和环境的问题。这种明智的建议不仅可以帮助领导者为他们的团队建模文明，而且提醒所有人，通常，良好的领导才是从提出好的问题开始。</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/good-questions/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>我们的2024年冬季指南</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:22:31 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Decision-Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Set Ambitious but Realistic Environmental Goals Kate Isaacs, Jason Jay, Jeremy Gregory, and Elsa Olivetti Key Insight: Business leaders should judiciously set interim targets to get early wins and build momentum for sustainability goals. Top Takeaways: Companies need to grapple with setting critical goals to reduce carbon emissions while continuing to meet business demands. Moving [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-EXECSUM-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/" class="no-underline">设定雄心勃勃但现实的环境目标</a></h4><h6>凯特·艾萨克斯，杰森·杰伊，杰里米·格雷戈里和艾尔莎·奥利维蒂</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>商业领袖应明智地设定临时目标，以获得早期胜利并为可持续性目标增强动力。</p><p><strong>首选：</strong>公司需要努力设定关键目标，以减少碳排放，同时继续满足业务需求。在解决重大可持续性问题上进行方向发展，需要设定足够雄心勃勃的目标，以反映组织的愿景，但也足够现实。作者引导读者完成五步过程，以识别和设定环境意图，并管理迫切需要气候行动和维持商业健康之间的张力。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/" class="no-underline">悖论中的隐藏机会</a></h4><h6>斯科特·D·安东尼</h6><p><strong>关键洞察力：</strong>采用一种思维方式，将显然不可调节的目标视为促进创造力和组织绩效。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>业务领导者将面临无尽的选择。尽管有些决定很简单，但其他决定尤其难以做出，因为它们涉及悖论 - 与彼此相关的问题，例如“倾听和忽略您最好的客户”，并“维持和破坏您当前的商业模式”。研究表明，解决甚至包含看似矛盾的选择的组织扩大了可能的范围。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/" class="no-underline">准备更透明的可持续性报告</a></h4><h6>理查德·巴克（Richard Barker）</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>强制性可持续性报告将帮助公司向投资者展示他们打算如何管理风险和创造价值。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>如果组织可以将即将到来的监管革命视为合规性的练习，那么与可持续性相关的严格财务披露要求代表了机会。新的报告将揭示领导者如何看待未来，计划如何满足它以及他们期望为公司创造什么价值。专注于投资者想要的东西可以为公司规划和风险管理提供有用的视角。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/" class="no-underline">解决AI的气候变化问题</a></h4><h6>尼克拉斯·桑德伯格（Niklas Sundberg）</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>大型AI模型是大型能源消费者和碳发射器，但可持续性人工智能的最佳实践可以减少其环境影响。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>训练和运行大型语言模型所需的专门硬件和数据中心消耗大量的电力，并产生大量的碳排放和电子废物。例如，单个chatgpt查询可能会导致碳比常规的Google搜索高100倍。但是，AI领导者可以采取一些步骤来使技术更可持续，包括权利的模型，选择更有效的机器学习体系结构以及减少存储但从未使用过的组织数据量。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/" class="no-underline">摩擦可以改善客户的体验吗？</a></h4><h6> Marco Bertini，Diego Aparicio和Aylin Aydinli</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>当电子商务网站使购买产品过于快速，轻松时，他们可能会错过加深的客户关系。</p><p><strong>顶级要点：</strong>许多公司都在寻求使购物尽可能轻松的麻烦 - 尤其是在线购物者，购物者的耐心较低并且注意力较短。但是放慢购买过程，让客户有时间考虑购买决策实际上可以产生长期的福利。事实证明，当摩擦实现更好的决策时，客户满意度和忠诚度都会提高。作者提供了一项评估，以帮助公司确定将对这些优势发挥作用的摩擦程度。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/" class="no-underline">领导力发展使我们失败。这是解决它的方法</a></h4><h6>Hannes Leroy，Moran Anisman-Razin和Jim Detert</h6><p><strong>关键见解：</strong>有效的领导力发展计划将具有特定的目标，使用最合适的课程和教学方法，并产生与组织需求直接相关的结果。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>领导力发展计划昂贵，但通常无法产生有意义的结果。为了改变，购买这些计划的公司必须更重要的是。这意味着提出提供者的更多相关问题，并要求提供更好的答案。这也意味着阐明其特定的发展需求以及如何更清楚地与组织的战略重点联系在一起。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/" class="no-underline">使您的劳动力更好</a></h4><h6>Ayse Karaevli和SerdenÖzcan</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>做出故意措施的公司在做出决定时会经历更少的劳资纠纷并更好地管理变革。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>过去几年，劳动力冲突的增加，例如罢工和争议，工资，工作条件，多样性，均等机会以及健康与安全，以及员工脱离接触的水平不断上升。对德国顶级公共公司的分析发现，减少冲突最重要的是C套件和董事会领导人在多大程度上积极参与重要战略决策。领导者可以用来包括员工的三种方法正在确定共同的目标和兴趣，促进包容性决策过程并赋予员工的战略责任。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/" class="no-underline">各地的经理都必须了解种姓</a></h4><h6>Hari Bapuji，Kamini Gupta，Snehanjali Chrispal和Thomas Roulet</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>种姓，南亚社会文化经济等级，可能会影响人们获得资本，商业联系和工作机会的机会，并在全球范围内导致工作场所偏见和歧视。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>被称为种姓的社会经济分层体系可以在工作场所塑造不平等和更广泛的互动 - 不仅在印度和巴基斯坦等国家，而且在许多南亚居民，包括美国，英国，加拿大和澳大利亚等南亚居民中。领导者需要了解种姓的工作方式，以充分保护员工免受其有害影响。亚马逊，苹果和戴尔等公司通过在其公司政策中解决基于种姓的歧视来认识到这一问题的重要性。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-managers-everywhere-must-know-about-caste/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/" class="no-underline">如何有效地不同意艰难的主题</a></h4><h6>Kenji Yoshino和David Glasgow</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>领导者可以采用特定策略来促进有关身份，多样性和正义的棘手工作场所对话。</p><p><strong>最高点：</strong>分裂的工作场所互动范围从预期甚至庆祝的最安全的主题到有争议的主题，在这些主题中，对话可能会变得丑陋。处于权力地位的人是通过促进同理心而不是激发恐惧和分裂的最大机会来改变这些互动的动态。作者推荐的几种策略中有两种谨慎地研究他人的观点，并在争端之外找到共同点，以引起对话和愤怒和防御性的尊重。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/" class="no-underline">幽灵场景如何困扰策略执行</a></h4><h6>Trudi Lang和RafaelRamírez</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>高管必须面对战略计划盲点：关于其组织未来业务环境的假设。</p><p><strong>首要关注：</strong>战略规划师通常会忽略商业环境的社会经济状态可能会发生变化以及新环境如何影响其预期结果。表面上的情景心态幻想场景承认了这些隐式假设，确定了潜在的破坏，然后开始考虑它们。例如，参与幽灵场景可能意味着探索对特定技术的信任可能不断发展或监管变化如何影响特定目标的不同方式。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-ghost-scenarios-haunt-strategy-execution/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><hr /><h4><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/" class="no-underline">驱动护理危机的真正问题</a></h4><h6>唐纳德·萨尔和查尔斯·萨尔</h6><p><strong>主要见解：</strong>在人员员工机构工作的护士平均比其他护士更满意 - 医疗保健领导人需要问为什么。</p><p><strong>首要好处：</strong>美国医院面临的最大问题是员工短缺和倦怠，护理短缺是一个特别急性的疼痛点。作者对雇主评论的分析发现，护士之间高水平的工作不满是由经理与患者护理的日常现实保持联系的观点。一个明亮的观点是，为人员工作机构（有时被称为旅行护士）工作的护士报告了更好的工作条件，沟通和信任。作者的研究详细介绍了其他提供商可以学习的工作满意度的驱动力。</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">阅读文章</a></p><p></p>]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-winter-2024-issue/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>解决AI的气候变化问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Niklas Sundberg. <p>Niklas Sundberg是<cite>技术领导者可持续IT剧本</cite>（Packt Publishing，2022年）的作者，也是可持续发展的董事会成员，这是一个致力于通过技术领导力推进全球可持续性的非营利组织。他是全球运输和物流公司Kuehne+Nagel的首席数字官，此前曾是Assa Abloy的CIO兼全球企业架构负责人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko In an era defined by both the promise of technological innovation and the threat of climate change, artificial intelligence has emerged as both a valuable tool and a difficult challenge. As we use AI to tackle tough problems, we must also grapple with its hidden environmental costs and consider solutions that will allow [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Sundberg_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p>在技​​术创新的希望和气候变化的威胁所定义的时代中，人工智能既是一种有价值的工具，又是一个困难的挑战。当我们使用AI来解决棘手的问题时，我们还必须努力应对其隐藏的环境成本，并考虑解决方案，使我们能够在减轻气候影响的同时发挥其潜力。</p><p>由Microsoft支持的Openai的ChatGpt语言模型的成功引发了技术军备竞赛，技术巨头在构建自己的自然语言处理系统方面进行了巨大的投资。但是，寻求更智能的机器正在迅速遇到可持续性挑战的网络。 AI具有快速增长的碳足迹，这是由于其对能源的食欲和制造使用硬件的碳成本而引起的。自2012年以来，最广泛的AI培训运行一直在使用指数级的计算能力，平均每3.4个月增加一倍。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><h3> AI的环境成本</h3><p>即使数据中心和传输网络占全球用电的1％至1.5％，信息技术的环境影响也经常被忽略。根据国际能源机构的数据，他们还占全球碳排放量的0.6％，需要将其切成两半才能到2050年以达到零排放量。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>一个平均数据中心每年消耗50,000户房屋。电子废物是世界上增长最快的废物流，相当于每年产生的5700万吨惊人的废物流，与中国长城的重量大致相同。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>在整个生命周期中，有几个因素有助于AI系统的碳足迹：</p><p><strong>大型且复杂的模型：</strong>大型语言模型（LLM）需要数万个尖端的高性能芯片来训练和响应查询，从而导致高能消耗和碳排放。模型的复杂性越大，任务时间就越多，从而导致更多的能耗。像Chatgpt这样的<a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4个</a>LLM是最复杂和计算上最昂贵的AI型号之一。 OpenAI的GPT-3 LLM的功能由其1750亿参数模型成为可能，这是该模型的推出最大的模型之一。据估计，仅它的培训就使用了1.3吉瓦小时的能源（相当于平均120个美国家庭的年度消费），并产生了552吨的碳排放量（相当于120辆美国汽车的年度排放）。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Openai的最新型号GPT-4，据传大10倍。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p><strong>数据存储和处理：</strong>训练和运行AI模型所需的数据集是大而复杂的，导致高能消耗和碳排放。数据存储，CPU操作和芯片操作消耗数据中心中的大部分能量。此外，数据中心使用的电力中约有40％是为大型空调提供动力，这对于保持服务器凉爽且正确运行是必要的。 Falcon 180B是最近推出的开放式LLM，具有1800亿参数（类似于GPT-3的计数），并接受了3.5亿亿英里的数据集（与GPT-3的4.99亿个标记相比）。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>培训该模型对如此大的数据集估计产生了估计的1,870吨碳排放，假设美国典型的美国能量混合物，相当于一年加热350个家庭。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p><strong>能源：</strong>用于动力AI系统的能源的碳强度决定了其碳足迹。可以利用可再生能源的数据中心的碳足迹可能比没有能源消耗的数据中心具有较低的碳足迹。</p><p><strong>用水：</strong> AI和其他信息技术的环境影响超出了碳排放量。数据中心在冷却塔和HVAC系统中使用大量水，以防止服务器和其他重要设备过热。 AI模型的强烈计算和数据要求只会增加数据中心的用水量。微软在其最新的环境报告中透露，其全球用水从2021年到2022年增长了34％（约为17亿加仑，或超过2500个奥运会大小的游泳池）。 Google报告说，同期用水量增加了20％，这是外部专家与其AI开发有关的增加。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>对于设定了雄心勃勃的环境，社会和治理（ESG）目标的公司来说，这是一个令人关注的趋势，其中包括到2030年到2030年具有碳阴性和水阳性。</p><p><strong>硬件：</strong> AI硬件的生产和处置有助于碳排放和日益增长的电子废物问题。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>预计到2050年，全球电子废物每年将每年达到1.2亿吨，这是今天的两倍。同一电子废物的物质价值（只有20％的正式回收）约为625亿美元。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>回收这些资源并捕获更多的价值，可以为更健壮，可持续的经济打开大门，从而最大程度地减少了更多用于制造它们的材料并使它们远离垃圾填埋场的需求。</p><p>这并不意味着我们应该停止开发和使用AI模型来保护气候。尽管有这些巨大的环境成本，但AI也被证明是促进可持续性和应对气候变化的重要工具。 AI被用来最大化风能和太阳能等可再生能源的利用，并开发平衡能源供求的智能网格。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a> AI驱动的解决方案正在帮助农民提高农业产量，同时施用较少的农药和肥料，从而产生更环保的农业方法。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>和AI被用来优化物流和减少供应链中的废物，监视和执行环境法规，并通过机器学习算法优化数据中心操作，该算法动态调整温度设置，工作负载分布和服务器利用率。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p></p><p> AI对解决气候危机的贡献可能超过其负面的气候影响，但是只有当AI行业采用强调ESG可持续性的实践，使可持续性使其AI伦理准则的核心核心，并积极寻求减少AI技术的环境足迹的机会。 AI的用户还必须意识到有助于这些工具的环境影响的因素，以指导自己使用它，并为评估AI供应商的标准列表增加可持续性。</p><p>透明度至关重要，必须发表新模型的能源使用和碳排放的可靠测量，以提高人们对它们的认识，并鼓励AI开发人员竞争模型的可持续性。关于AI模型的碳排放和能源使用，我们所知道的大部分是通过第三方计算的估计，而不是模型本身开发人员报告的数字，这必须改变。如今可用的工具，例如<a href="https://mlco2.github.io/impact/">机器学习排放计算器</a>，可以帮助AI工程师基于硬件，小时数，提供商和位置等变量上的AI模型模拟碳排放。 Google的研究人员建议探索四种技术最佳实践，它们称为4MS，即模型，机械，机械化和地图优化，从而分别减少能量和碳排放。他们声称，遵循这些最佳实践可以将机器学习培训能源减少100倍，而二氧化碳排放量最多可将1,000倍减少。 <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p></p><h3>搬迁，权利和重新构造</h3><p>尽管4MS从技术角度解决了AI的能源使用和碳排放，但可持续AI的最佳实践可以更广泛地表示为三个R：搬迁，权利和重新构造。</p><p><strong>搬迁：</strong>并非所有能量都是平等的。我们可以通过过渡到可再生能源（例如太阳能或风能）来减轻与AI能源消耗相关的碳排放。在过去的10年中，太阳能和风的电力成本分别下降了89％和70％，现在比使用煤炭和天然气等化石燃料的替代品便宜。尽管风和太阳能的价格急剧下降，但最大的限制仍然是访问全天候可再生能源的需求。在加拿大魁北克放置计算工作量，在加拿大魁北克，可再生能源的访问几乎为100％，平均碳强度为每千瓦时32克，可能会导致碳排放量减少16倍，而美国平均水平为每千瓦时519克-小时。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>一些云供应商使用碳偏移来证实其净零索赔，但这与无碳能量运行并不相同。它只是将问题推向其他人。</p><p>如果构造良好，则从本地转变为基于云的计算可以节省1.4倍至2倍。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17个</a>基于云的数据中心是为能源效率而定制设计的仓库。云的灵活性还允许选择工作负载的位置时有很大的自由。比较基于本地和基于云的数据中心的PUE（功率使用效率）值：值越低，中心效率就越有效。还可以选择主要在可再生能源上运行的数据中心。</p><p><strong>权利：</strong>公司通常使用比他们需要更多的计算和存储资源。他们可以通过权利的AI模型和应用以及使用足够的归档程序来减少碳足迹。当使用用于机器学习训练的处理器和系统时，性能和能源效率可以提高2倍至5倍，而不是运行未针对AI工作负载进行优化的通用服务器。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a>优化涉及在范围，模型大小，模型质量和高效/可持续资源使用之间达到理想平衡。图形处理单元制造商提供了限制GPU允许绘制的功率的方法，从而可以减少能源消耗以换取较慢的性能 - 这在许多情况下可能是可以接受的。 <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a>要考虑的另一种策略是时间转移：在碳强度倾向于较低的时候，执行苛刻的工作量，例如训练期。</p><p><strong>重新构造：</strong>构建功能良好的AI模型需要强大的软件/硬件体系结构，旨在扩展和微调模型，同时保持低延迟响应时间。选择有效的机器学习模型体系结构（例如稀疏模型）可以提高机器学习质量，同时将计算降低3倍至10倍。 <a id="reflink20" class="reflink" href="#ref20">20</a>一旦AI模型达到生产，从绩效，安全性和最终用户体验的角度来管理技术债务至关重要。管理不善或忽略技术债务而支持功能改进可能会导致其迅速积累并带来严重的技术风险，包括性能缓慢，质量不佳，意外停机时间，数据丢失甚至安全漏洞。只有某些应用程序或AI模型才能重新设计。不过，当机会出现时，至关重要的是，研究更有效的机器学习模型体系结构以确保质量更好的同时减少计算。</p><h3>其他AI可持续性实践</h3><p>除了三个R之外，AI领导者还必须注意以下途径，以提高可持续性。</p><p><strong>数据管理：</strong>数字数据生产正在迅速加速。在2022年，世界估计有97个Zettabytes或97万亿千兆的数据。到2025年，这个数字可能几乎翻了一番，达到181个<a id="reflink21" class="reflink" href="#ref21">Zettabyt。21</a>大多数数据都是用于一次使用的，再也不会被使用，但可以保存在占用空间并使用大量电力的服务器上。因此，减少不必要的“黑暗数据”的负责数据管理实践对于可持续的AI开发和部署至关重要。较大的模型不一定等同于更好的模型；随着时间的流逝，性能会恶化。通过将数据存储和处理重新定位到实施更节能的冷却并由可再生能源供电的数据中心，以及实施数据压缩，重复数据删除和归档性数据的数据，可以将能源消耗和环境影响最小化。</p><p><strong>教育和意识：</strong> AI领导者可以通过教育员工，合作伙伴，客户和公众对AI的环境影响来促进对环境负责的AI实践。这些影响尚未得到广泛的理解，即使单个chatgpt查询可以比常规的Google搜索产生的碳多100倍，诸如ChatGpt这样的工具的简易可用性看起来等同于查询搜索引擎。 <a id="reflink22" class="reflink" href="#ref22">22</a>组织和决策者应对AI的环境后果，他们就越会寻找具有较低环境影响和压力AI提供者的解决方案，以采用更可持续的实践。</p><p></p><p><strong>合规性：</strong> AI领导者将需要关注围绕能源效率和电子废物管理及其对技术投资的影响的新兴法规和最佳实践。总部位于美国的非营利性贸易协会scultableIt.org发布了针对其业务可持续性影响的有史以来的第一个标准。一般性和注重人工智能立法都正在出现，例如欧盟公司的可持续发展指令及其<a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/headlines/society/20230601STO93804/eu-ai-act-first-regulation-on-artificial-intelligence">人工智能法案</a>，该法预计将在2024年完成并生效。在美国，美国证券交易委员会的碳披露规则is pending, and California recently passed two laws that will require companies to file annual public reports disclosing their direct, indirect, and supply chain greenhouse gas emissions, and to have them verified by an independent and experienced third-party provider.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The widespread adoption of generative AI models comes with an urgent need for all players in the industry, including managers and users of AI, to take greater responsibility for the environmental and social impacts of this promising technology.</p><p> Following the sustainable AI practices outlined in this article can help build a more sustainable AI ecosystem. By finding ways to minimize the energy and natural resources consumed by our AI development and deployment processes and drawing more attention to sustainability issues in discussions about AI, we can harness the power of this technology while minimizing its negative impact on our planet and society.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/tackling-ais-climate-change-problem/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Get Ready for More Transparent Sustainability Reporting</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:55:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Barker. <p>Richard Barker is a full-time member of the International Sustainability Standards Board, on leave from the University of Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School. This article expresses the personal views of the author, not the official positions of the ISSB.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Reporting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko Rigorous sustainability-related financial disclosure is coming. The era of inconsistent, voluntary disclosure is giving way to mandatory reporting — but don’t treat this regulatory revolution as simply an exercise in compliance. It is instead essential work to gain greater visibility into your business’s exposure to risk and long-term prospects for success — for [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Barker_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><p> Rigorous sustainability-related financial disclosure is coming. The era of inconsistent, voluntary disclosure is giving way to mandatory reporting — but don&#39;t treat this regulatory revolution as simply an exercise in compliance. It is instead essential work to gain greater visibility into your business&#39;s exposure to risk and long-term prospects for success — for the benefit of both investors and management.</p><p> Action has been brisk this year on the regulatory front. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plans to issue its climate disclosure rules by the end of 2023. In June, the International Sustainability Standards Board (ISSB) issued its first global standards; the European Union issued its European Sustainability Reporting Standards (ESRS) in August. The ESRS reporting requirements will be mandatory for large European companies starting in 2024 and in due course for international companies with European operations. Corporate reporting hasn&#39;t changed this much since the SEC was created in the wake of the 1929 stock market crash.</p><p></p><p> How should senior executives and boards respond to, and take advantage of, these changes? In this article, I will explain why focusing on what investors want from sustainability reporting is a critical lens for understanding how to act. Through that lens, I examine how best to navigate the evolving landscape of mandatory reporting.</p><h3>投资者需要了解什么</h3><p>Investors seeking gains via either growth or lasting value know that the energy sources that built the global economy are not those that will sustain it. Economic value will therefore be created by serving new and existing markets in different ways. Investors are looking to these different market conditions that lie ahead, where sustainability builds resilience and increases the capacity for growth.</p><p></p><p> Smart investors also know that if global warming is not slowed, and if natural resources continue to be depleted at the current rate, economic activity will suffer. Insurers are experts in anticipating and managing risk, and they are ahead of the game, rethinking where and how they do business. A consequence is that the costs of catastrophes related to climate change will increasingly be borne more directly by businesses and private citizens. The summer of 2023 saw New Yorkers sheltering inside from the smoke of Canadian forest fires; increasing damage from hurricanes in Florida; record high temperatures across the southern US; and dangerous, damaging flooding from summer rains in the Northeast. These are the scouting parties for the effects of climate change; the main forces will be along later.</p><p> In the broader global context, investors want to know how you see the future, how you are planning to meet it, and what value you expect to be able to create. Current financial reporting alone cannot offer this; in a disruptive world, investors cannot evaluate your prospects based on past performance. Investing is making choices. Sustainability informs returns.</p><p> This is not just compliance, any more than accurately tracking revenue and expenses is done purely for the benefit of regulators. Nor is it a PR exercise afforded by selective voluntary disclosures. It is instead the recognition that in a world roiled by wicked, systemic problems, what is material to sound investment decisions is changing; corporate reporting must change as well.</p><h3> How Mandatory Reporting Is Taking Shape</h3><p> For public companies in the US, the primary consideration has to be the <a href="https://www.mwe.com/insights/october-forecast-a-busy-month-for-climate-change-related-regulation-and-insurers/">SEC&#39;s forthcoming rules</a> , which will address investors&#39; demands for climate-related disclosures. At a minimum, the rules will likely require reporting on greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions generated from a company&#39;s directly controlled operations (Scope 1) and from its purchased electricity (Scope 2). More contentious is Scope 3 emissions, which occur as part of the value chain process by which the company makes its money, be that upstream in the production of inputs to the company&#39;s operations or downstream in the use of the company&#39;s products. The significance of these emissions varies enormously by industry. In some cases, where direct operations involve high emissions, Scope 3 might be relatively low. In other cases, Scope 3 might account for more than 90% of a company&#39;s carbon footprint.</p><p> From an investor&#39;s perspective, Scope 3 emissions are a risk factor because a business with a high carbon footprint is relatively vulnerable to transition-related risks. Such potential risks include regulations that restrict sales of carbon-intensive products (or make them more expensive), the loss of business or employees to competitors with stronger sustainability credentials, and the reduced availability of finance or the increased cost of capital. At the same time, a high carbon footprint can be seen as an opportunity for transition that reduces these risks and thus could increase the valuation of a company in relation to its peers. It is hard to make the case that information about significant Scope 3 emissions is not material to investors. It follows that — whether or not the SEC decides to mandate Scope 3 — companies that have Scope 3 in hand are better placed to be resilient than those that do not. It is inevitable that investors will seek this disclosure and that companies will increasingly provide it.</p><p> However, preparation for mandatory disclosure goes beyond keeping track of SEC requirements. This is because other regulators have extraterritorial reach and because sustainability reporting is inherently global, given international supply chains: Data is collected from your suppliers, who will in turn collect it from their suppliers, and so on up the supply chain. For a large corporation, this can easily amount to data from thousands of entities in many different countries. Good luck aggregating this data if it is not all measured in the same way. Meanwhile, your customers will be requiring sustainability data from you (and you from them, in order to understand downstream emissions). These customers will also be spread across different geographies. They might include unlisted and public-sector enterprises, because all are part of the value chain of listed companies. You don&#39;t want each of them to be asking you to measure different things, using different units of measurement.</p><p> It therefore makes sense to align with the global standards of the ISSB, which have been endorsed by the International Organization of Securities Commissions. Fortunately, the SEC climate proposal closely aligns with the ISSB&#39;s, and the agency “recognized the importance of global alignment and of drawing on existing frameworks that have enjoyed significant voluntary market uptake,” according to Allison Herren Lee, former SEC acting chair and commissioner. The widely used standards of the Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB) have been subsumed within the ISSB&#39;s, and both the Task Force on Climate-Related Financial Disclosures (TCFD) and the World Economic Forum have formally announced that they will sunset their guidance on climate disclosure and sustainability metrics, respectively, in favor of the ongoing work of the ISSB. Meanwhile, CDP — the global reporting platform for more than 50% of global market capitalization, formerly known as the Carbon Disclosure Project — will base its future data-capture work on ISSB standards. Overall, there is a clear direction of travel toward having the ISSB set the global baseline of investor-oriented sustainability disclosure standards that can be used across markets.</p><p> In addition — though not immediately obvious — voluntary alignment with global sustainability reporting practice will itself influence the rule-making of the SEC. The role of the SEC is to help ensure that markets are supplied with the material information that investors need and to do so in a way that passes a cost-benefit test. Where consensus has already formed around measurement and reporting, costs of reporting are lower, benefits to investors are greater, and material information is more readily available.</p><p> As noted above, business leaders must also be alert to the extraterritorial reach of some regulations. In early September, California passed legislation to mandate climate-related disclosures by any outside company doing business in the state and generating more than $1 billion in annual revenue. Meanwhile, international attention is currently focused on the EU&#39;s ESRS requirements, which are far deeper and broader than the SEC&#39;s are expected to be. There are 12 standards, covering a range of environmental, social, and governance disclosures in detail. And the scope of ESRS extends to “double materiality,” which means reporting not just to investors but also to all other stakeholders on issues material to them.</p><p></p><h3> Step Up to Meet Demands for Rigorous Sustainability Reporting</h3><p> As mandated corporate reporting expands to include sustainability issues, the following guidance can help you develop a plan to build the necessary capabilities.</p><p> <strong>Don&#39;t stop what you&#39;re already doing.</strong> You might be doing sustainability reporting in some form already, applying SASB, TCFD, or the Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) and/or reporting to CDP. You will need to build on these practices, but you are on the right road already.</p><p> <strong>Don&#39;t let perfect be the enemy of good.</strong> In the realm of voluntary disclosures, what investors want is whatever you can reasonably provide. Keep in mind that sustainability data is only indirectly relevant. Investors don&#39;t want to know your GHG emissions so much as they want to know how their presence affects your financials. For that purpose, reasonable estimation of emissions is typically good enough and, by such means as using industry averages, it is generally not hard to achieve. You should be careful to communicate the basis of your estimation, and you should not overstate the confidence you have in your measurements. Take advantage of safe harbor provisions, as appropriate. What your investors don&#39;t want is nothing, which would convey that you aren&#39;t being transparent, that you don&#39;t have material information about your business, or both. Either would be a good reason for investors not to invest.</p><p> <strong>Align with financial reporting.</strong> If your sustainability report is separate from your financial reports and investor presentations, then you&#39;re missing a trick. Investors want to understand how your sustainability-related position and performance affect your financial prospects. The more you can express your sustainability-related metrics and targets in the language of finance, the better. For example, it is one thing to have a target for net-zero GHG emissions; it&#39;s another to set out a transition plan that quantifies the capital expenditure that will be required and that guides investors in understanding current and prospective income statement effects.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on climate, and be ready for the SEC requirements.</strong> Because climate is the dominant sustainability issue, emissions are appropriately the focus of the SEC&#39;s regulation. If you are not on top of climate-related reporting already, at some point you will need to be, including being prepared to have your data audited externally. Moreover, climate is most likely your best starting point in sustainability reporting. It affects all companies, measurement practices are relatively established, and market understanding is relatively high. And if you can do climate reporting well, you will have built the capabilities needed for most other aspects of sustainability reporting, such as relationships and data systems throughout your value chain, and the art of translating sustainability data into financial implications for evaluation by your investors 。 To have this foundation, you will need to extend your data and control systems beyond your directly controlled operations, because your sustainability performance can be understood only in a value chain context. You should therefore develop your (material) Scope 3 GHG emissions reporting regardless of whether it is mandated by the SEC. This will become easier to do once Scope 1 and 2 disclosure is widespread.</p><p> <strong>Tighten systems and controls throughout your value chain.</strong> You should expect greater influence and control from your finance and legal functions as sustainability reporting evolves from being voluntary to being mandatory, and ownership of sustainability reporting migrates away from existing homes, such as communications, external relations, and dedicated sustainability teams. This migration will come with a higher hurdle for systems and data quality, and so it will almost certainly mean additional costs. But, as ever, focus on the business case, which means thinking about benefits as well as costs.</p><p> A comparison with financial accounting is again helpful. Your finance function is expensive — maybe too expensive. And maybe it could be more efficient. But is anyone suggesting that your company would be better off without it? No doubt there was pushback on cost when the SEC first introduced disclosure requirements. But then the world moved on, and the net benefit from reporting has become well understood. The same is true for sustainability reporting. If you build an authentic sustainability story, the benefits will exceed the costs. In addition, and relatedly, you should stay ahead of the curve. In a world of satellite data and artificial intelligence, your sustainability performance will increasingly be reported <em>to</em> you rather than <em>by</em> you — a scenario in which the best legal and reputational protection is to be in control and transparent. Don&#39;t allow your sustainability story to be an apologetic response to having breached the conditions of your social license to operate.</p><p> <strong>Align with the ISSB global baseline (and require your supply chain to do likewise).</strong> Your regulatory obligation is determined by the SEC. There is little reason to expect the SEC&#39;s investor-oriented focus to diverge from that of the ISSB. Yet there is good reason to expect regulation to become tighter and faster in major jurisdictions elsewhere in the world. You operate in a global economy, where the benefits of investment decisions are greater and the costs of gathering reliable data are lower if everyone shares the same measurement and disclosure standards. Aligning with the ISSB is the most effective way to align with the SEC while also reducing costs and improving data quality.</p><p> <strong>Use ISSB standards as a baseline for ESRS.</strong> The fundamental difference between ISSB and ESRS is that the former requires reporting to investors (consistent with the SEC) while the latter also requires reporting on issues that are material to all other stakeholders. If your operations draw you into the extraterritorial reach of ESRS, your optimal response is simple: Do what you would do anyway to report in the US and globally to your investors, and then separately include the additional disclosures required for ESRS compliance.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Contribute to the development of industry norms.</strong> Sustainability issues vary by industry. Companies are categorized by industry in the capital markets, to better enable like-for-like comparisons and to analyze shared exposures to industry-specific risks and opportunities. This is why the SASB standards are industry-based and why the ISSB has likewise committed to this standard-setting approach. Given that industry expertise sits within the industry and sustainability reporting remains a young practice, companies should participate proactively in discussions on best-practice reporting in their sectors, directly and indirectly helping to shape future standards.</p><p></p><p> Above all, ensure that your sustainability reporting has an authentic connection with value creation. If it feels like an exercise in compliance, then your company is missing opportunities. There should be alignment between information that is valued by your investors and that which is valuable to you in leading the business. Investors might see the company as being at greater risk of being left behind in a rapidly changing and increasingly perilous world, and your reputation in the marketplace could suffer. Consider instead how a willing embrace of tracking and disclosing sustainability performance can not only win support from the market but also, via focus and accountability, help you manage your company through the profound transitions that the planet and society demand of us all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-more-transparent-sustainability-reporting/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Hidden Opportunity in Paradoxes</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/#comments</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:45:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott D. Anthony. <p>Scott D. Anthony ( <a href="https://www.twitter.com/scottdanthony">@scottdanthony</a> ) is a clinical professor at the Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth College and a managing director and managing partner emeritus at growth strategy consultancy Innosight. He is a coauthor of <cite>Eat, Sleep, Innovate</cite> (Harvard Business Review Press, 2020).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Management Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko The Research The author reviewed relevant academic literature; conducted in-depth interviews with executives, advisers, and intrapreneurs with firsthand experience in organizational paradox; and conducted analysis using systems psychodynamics (a set of tools to study the interaction between structures, norms, and practices of groups and the cognitions, motivations, and emotions of group members) as [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-Anthony_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>The author reviewed relevant academic literature; conducted in-depth interviews with executives, advisers, and intrapreneurs with firsthand experience in organizational paradox; and conducted analysis using systems psychodynamics (a set of tools to study the interaction between structures, norms, and practices of groups and the cognitions, motivations, and emotions of group members) as part of INSEAD&#39;s Executive Master in Change program.</p></aside><p> Leading an organization demands that we confront a constant array of choices. Should we invest in this market or that one? Should we offer luxury products or mass-market goods? Should we provide incentives to individuals or teams? Should we recruit university graduates exclusively or look for nongraduates with specialized skills? While these choices can require careful consideration, they are essentially straightforward. The really hard choices that leaders will face in our increasingly complex world, argue some management thinkers, represent a different kind of problem altogether: the paradox.</p><p> Many of us are likely to have encountered the idea of paradox primarily in the context of art or philosophy. Defined by the <cite>Oxford Pocket Dictionary of Current English</cite> as “a seemingly absurd or self-contradictory statement or proposition that when investigated or explained may prove to be well founded or true,” the word <em>paradox</em> might bring to mind examples like the Socratic statement “I know that I know nothing.” Paradoxes can be interesting to ponder, but we don&#39;t often consider how they might expand our thinking as organizational leaders. That is changing in important ways.</p><p></p><p> In their book <cite>Both/And Thinking</cite> , business scholars Wendy K. Smith and Marianne W. Lewis define paradoxes as “persistent, interdependent contradictions.” <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> That means they contain at least two elements that relate to each other but appear to contradict. London Business School professor Herminia Ibarra described the “ <a href="https://hbr.org/2015/01/the-authenticity-paradox">authenticity paradox</a> ”: Leaders are told to be authentic in order to succeed, but an authentic leader can struggle to develop because they get fixated on being true to themself instead of what is required to succeed. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Some scholars assert that the very idea of an organization has a seeming paradox at its heart <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0018726702555001">because</a> “on the one hand it contains free, creative, independent human subjects; on the other hand, the relation between these subjects aspires to be one of organization, order, and control.” <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Innovation seems acutely paradoxical. To resolve Clayton Christensen&#39;s famous innovator&#39;s dilemma, you need to both listen to and ignore your best customers. Sustain and disrupt your current business model. Support and undermine your current value network. More broadly, today&#39;s leaders have to build inclusive and unique cultures that empower and direct employees while striking work-life balances for employees with very diverse desires.</p><p></p><p> Such apparent paradoxes can arise at the level of an individual, team, organization, and even the larger context in which an organization operates, like an industry, a state, or an entire society. But if a paradox is something that is fundamentally unresolvable, does that mean these business challenges are insurmountable?</p><h3> A Paradoxical Industry</h3><p> The energy industry seems to be in a particularly acute moment of paradox. A <a href="https://www.shell.com/business-customers/lubricants-for-business/perspectives/under-pressure-leading-in-paradox-industries.html">report</a> from Royal Dutch Shell called sectors like commercial transport, power, manufacturing, and energy “paradox industries” with “huge pressures to increase their output <em>and</em> reduce their impact on our planet. To grow in size <em>and</em> shrink their footprint. To automate <em>and</em> create jobs.” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> The stakes are high. Activist investors have suggested that these tensions are so intractable that Shell ought to split into three companies. In June 2023, Shell&#39;s newly appointed CEO announced plans to be “ruthless” in capital allocation, cutting some investments in renewable technologies and increasing investment in fossil fuels. “Ultimately what we need to do is to be able to generate long-term value for our shareholders,” said CEO Wael Sawan. “The answer cannot be, &#39;I am going to invest [in clean energy projects] and have poor returns and that&#39;s going to vindicate my conscience.&#39; That&#39;s wrong.” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p> What options do Shell and other energy companies have in the face of a seeming unreconcilable paradox? Consider the contrasting approaches taken by two other major energy companies.</p><p> In the late 1990s, oil and gas giant BP attempted (and failed) to rebrand itself as “Beyond Petroleum” and invested billions in wind and solar projects, many of which were later <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bp-solar/bp-turns-out-lights-at-solar-business-idUSTRE7BK1CC20111221">shut down</a> or spun off. In February 2020, BP attempted another push toward clean energy, as CEO Bernard Looney <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/bp-gambles-big-fast-transition-oil-renewables-2021-09-20/">announced</a> plans to slash the company&#39;s oil output by 40%, sell $25 billion in fossil-fuel assets, and boost its capacity to generate electricity from renewable sources twentyfold. It acknowledged that its clean energy business was losing money and would continue to lose money until at least 2025. But when energy prices surged three years later, Looney <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/inside-bps-plan-reset-renewables-oil-gas-boom-2023-03-07/">announced</a> plans to slow the planned cuts and scale back spending on renewables. While BP&#39;s leaders stressed that the company was reviewing, not ending, its commitment to shifting its portfolio, the story seemed eerily reminiscent of its first foray into clean energy. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> BP&#39;s recent history may be said to typify an either/or mindset in action. That is, when you see the apparent tension between two parts of a paradox, you choose one or the other. BP approached renewable energy as fundamentally opposed to fossil fuels, aggressively ramping up (or marketing) the former at the expense of the latter — an approach that was doomed to snap back when circumstances changed.</p><p> In contrast, Danish energy company Ørsted has taken a both/and approach, wading right into the contradictions of a paradox to find a solution that unites parts that seem to be in tension. In 2009, management announced that the company (then known as DONG Energy) would seek to generate 85% of heat and power from renewable sources by 2040. It explored investment in offshore wind and began to wean itself off coal. By 2019, it had become the world&#39;s largest offshore wind-energy producer, achieving its aggressive target 21 years ahead of plan. In 2019, it sold off its coal business and its liquified natural gas unit. While it no longer produces gas, it continues to play in the space as an infrastructure provider and trader, with a spokesperson <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/articles/read/rsted-sells-lng-unit-says-its-natural-gas-business-is-going-nowhere">noting</a> in 2019, “There&#39;ll be a long transition period leading up to a 100% green energy system, during which society can&#39;t do without gas. Gas is the least harmful fossil fuel available to support the transition to green energy, and we&#39;ll continue to trade gas for years to come.” <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Companies should, of course, dynamically adjust their strategies based on market conditions. But, more broadly, they ought to rethink the limiting perception that there is a tension between pursuing short-term returns and longer-term strategic reorientation. A stream of academic research has repeatedly shown that the perceived trade-off between pursuing planet-friendly policies and maximizing financial returns is a false one. In his book <cite>Purpose + Profit</cite> , Harvard Business School professor George Serafeim describes a study that showed purpose-driven companies that took an integrated view of sustainability issues received a risk-adjusted boost of 6% in their share returns. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> A proven path to beating the market. And one that also does good for the planet.很简单，对吧？很不幸的是，不行。</p><p></p><h3> The Polarizing Power of Paradox</h3><p> Paradoxes are complex, adaptive, system-level issues with rampant uncertainty. That&#39;s <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-leaders-delude-themselves-about-disruption">why</a> the innovator&#39;s dilemma has proved to be so stubborn despite two decades of work by practitioners and thought leaders. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Humans suffer from a predictable range of biases and blind spots that make pursuing both/and solutions challenging. Confirmation bias causes leaders to ignore evidence that goes against their existing beliefs. Loss aversion and the status quo bias means people prefer avoiding risks over taking them. Hierarchy and groupthink make it hard for groups to see their way through complexity.</p><p> One recurrent finding from academic research conducted over the past two decades is that paradox produces polarizing reactions. My own research has corroborated this finding. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> I conducted a dozen in-depth interviews with business leaders who found themselves confronting paradoxes that scholars like Smith and Lewis have identified, such as the tension between pursuing profits and purpose, sustaining current operations and driving disruptive growth, and rewarding individual performance and encouraging公平。 (See “The Research.”)</p><p> On the positive side, these kinds of paradoxes produced feelings of curiosity, excitement, and engagement. One of my research subjects, who confronted paradox daily in his role leading an innovation unit within a highly conservative company, described how even <em>discussing</em> paradox makes him feel “stimulated, like in the middle of a great chess game.” An executive who helped launch two billion-dollar businesses within a large consumer goods company described how finding a “point off the line” (data that didn&#39;t conform to expectations) was exciting because it opened up the possibility of a new path to a解决方案。 Another executive described how, as a university president, he confronted the seeming paradox between high-quality, campus-based education and accessible, affordable online programs. The executive formed and led several special-purpose teams. One ensured that both on-campus and online offerings met rigorous academic standards. Another helped on-campus professors learn from online educators and vice versa. Beyond transforming his institute, the executive noted how the effort sparked personal growth: “At an organizational level I&#39;m more effective, and at a personal level I&#39;m either a better person or I&#39;m at least a more self-aware person ”。</p><p> However, <a href="https://journals.aom.org/doi/10.5465/19416520.2016.1162422">research</a> also suggests that paradoxes can foster “anxiety, uncertainty, and ambiguity, leaving individuals feeling threatened and defensive.” <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a> A former CEO who drove strategic transformation at two organizations described how confronting paradox raised fundamental questions about the organization&#39;s identity: Having to make choices that invalidate aspects of that identity could have a cascading impact on individuals who connect to the organization&#39;s old identity.</p><p> One practitioner described the paradox of seeking to innovate within a law firm. “The work that I do is paradoxical in nature,” the lawyer said, “because we&#39;re meant to be doing innovation, which by definition is new, but if it&#39;s too new, nobody actually wants to do it because they want to see some proof, or they want some reassurance that it&#39;s going to work.” While a lawyer breaking from the practice of making decisions based on past precedent may seem trivial, such a break would require the lawyer to question a fundamental piece of themselves and their organization. The lost-in-paradox lawyer was left demotivated and frustrated: “I&#39;m stuck in the middle. I&#39;m not in a position to say, &#39;Let&#39;s go and change these structures that are impeding our work&#39; … [or] to say, &#39;Let&#39;s be honest about what we&#39;re doing and clearly state that … we&#39;re not actually doing groundbreaking stuff,&#39; so it feels disempowering.”</p><h3> Is It Really a Paradox?</h3><p> While classic philosophical paradoxes are unsolvable within their logical constraints, paradoxical problems in business can yield to solutions when leaders think beyond apparent constraints — or “out of the <em>para</em> -box,” if you will. Christensen called his first book <cite>The Innovator&#39;s Dilemma</cite> , not <cite>The Innovator&#39;s Paradox</cite> . The challenges of disruptive change are vexing, but like the perceived paradoxes facing modern executives, they are solvable. There&#39;s no law of nature that says law firms have to use past precedent when looking at innovation projects. Individuals can change a group and remain a part of it; individuals can change themselves without losing their sense of self.</p><p> Consider some of the other seemingly irreconcilable tensions that have been resolved:</p><ul><li> It was generally accepted that profitable manufacturing required making trade-offs between cost, quality, and speed — until Toyota showed that those trade-offs were false.</li><li> It was common knowledge that manufacturing had inherent randomness that required extensive quality control — until the Six Sigma movement showed that a tightly designed and managed process could produce highly predictable outputs.</li><li> Leaders believed they naturally had to adopt stricter control mechanisms as organizations grew in order to prevent employee malfeasance — until Netflix showed that “no rules rules.” <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></li><li> Environmental activists and business leaders knew that sustainability and profitability were incompatible goals — until Unilever&#39;s Sustainable Living Plan delivered on its commitment to double revenue while halving the company&#39;s environmental footprint.</li></ul><p> Executives can, of course, choose to follow either/or approaches. Or they can use the following techniques to seek opportunities to find both/and solutions.</p><p> <strong>Shift perspectives.</strong> Consider the concept of work-life balance. In the exact minute that you read this sentence, you can&#39;t be in balance, because you are doing one thing or another. Now, zoom out and imagine that you estimate that your life expectancy is 80 years. That&#39;s about 700,000 living hours. Let&#39;s say you are a <em>really</em> hard worker, averaging 50 hours a week, 50 weeks a year, for 50 years. That&#39;s 125,000 hours. So you work only 18% of your living hours.平衡！ Those extreme answers are not particularly useful, but consider the possibilities opened up by taking a quarterly perspective. That time frame allows rituals such as a weekend family retreat, decision rules such as having no more than 10 days of travel in a quarter, or more rigorous time-boxing, such as dedicating blocks of time for family activities.</p><p> Similarly, a shift in time horizon can reframe the renewable-energy tensions described previously. Consider one <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/43663662">study</a> contrasting five organizations operating in the oil sands of Alberta, Canada. <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a> All of the companies faced apparent paradoxical tensions in terms of their temporal (short- versus long-term) and philosophical (business versus society) orientations. Some companies viewed these issues as either/or poles that forced a choice. They prioritized practices that favored efficiency, such as quantitative planning, and minimized interactions with stakeholders, which led to what the researchers described as “temporal myopia” that resulted in the “narrowing of the solution space.”</p><p> Those that stepped back, shifted perspectives, and considered the interconnections between issues engaged multiple stakeholders and sought avenues for cross-collaboration. This approach allowed them to develop integrated solutions with greater potential for long-term benefits for all relevant stakeholders — including themselves.</p><p> One way to shift perspectives and find those points off the line that point to novel solutions to a problem is to run a series of thought experiments that play with constraints. That can involve <em>removing</em> a constraint, such as asking how you would approach an apparent paradox differently if you had infinite time or infinite resources, or <em>imposing</em> a constraint, such as imagining what you would do if the government suddenly outlawed the use of a particular raw材料。 While it might feel like imposing constraints would limit creativity, research consistently shows that constraints can focus problem-solving energy and boost creativity. One technique that can help spur these thought experiments is what Hal Gregersen <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/03/better-brainstorming">calls</a> a “question burst,” where you brainstorm not for answers, but for provocative questions. <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p> <strong>Adopt a paradox mindset.</strong> Adopting a mindset that views apparent paradoxes as opportunities boosts creativity and organizational performance, according to <a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2018-20753-002">research</a> . <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a> People who demonstrate a <em>paradox mindset</em> agree with statements such as “Tension between ideas energizes me” and “I am comfortable working on tasks that contradict each other.” The paradox mindset can be approached in three ways. First, leaders can be <em>screened</em> to identify those predisposed to have a paradox mindset by having them complete a short <a href="https://paradox.lerner.udel.edu/">diagnostic</a> . <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a> Second, the items on the diagnostic can be used as <em>prompts</em> before a group discussion to help people consider multiple possibilities when discussing an apparent paradox. Research shows that simply starting a meeting by stating that tensions create possibilities helps a group adopt more of a paradox mindset.</p><p></p><p> Finally, there can be conscious efforts to help people <em>develop</em> a paradox mindset. Experience in dynamic circumstances or on challenging problems builds what is <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/smj.3415">known</a> as <em>cognitive complexity</em> (the ability to consider multiple possibilities with nuance), a key enabler of a paradox mindset. <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a> Development plans that give high-potential leaders experience launching new products, working in emerging markets, or building new organizational capabilities help to prepare them to confront future paradoxes. More broadly, individuals can consider going on a paradox quest, consciously doing something that would be unusual for them, such as the following:</p><ul><li> Taking an art class, learning a musical instrument, or learning a new language.</li><li> Doing an extreme activity, such as skydiving.</li><li> Volunteering or participating in a socially oriented activity.</li><li> Enrolling in an online program to develop a new skill, like coding.</li></ul><p> <strong>Hold a paradox sparring session.</strong> Boxers use sparring sessions to train. The goal isn&#39;t to knock their opponent out but to practice form and response. A paradox sparring session is a purposeful place to bat around ideas and challenge assumptions. For example, in the early 2000s, a reorganization led to confusion within the iconic Danish toymaker Lego. Managers were being asked to do things that felt contradictory, such as simultaneously focusing on developing people and meeting stringent production targets. Lewis and fellow academic Lotte S. Lüscher led the group through a series of sparring sessions to discuss the apparent tensions. <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p> Sparring sessions <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/smj.3415">should</a> challenge participants with four types of questions:</p><ul><li> <em>Linear</em> questions, such as “What are your concerns?” encourage explanation and bring logic to the surface.</li><li> <em>Circular</em> questions, such as “What do you think others think?” explore other perspectives and home in on polarities.</li><li> <em>Reflexive</em> questions, such as “What does what you say imply?” seek opportunities to critique and connect existing options.</li><li> <em>Strategic</em> questions, such as “Is what you say realistic?” motivate more expansive solutions.</li></ul><p> This approach helps to tease a perceived paradox out of a seeming mess, creating opportunities to explore potential novel solutions to transcend it. For example, Lego challenged managers to drive performance and allow teams to be more self-managed. A sparring session devoted to the seemingly paradoxical question of how managers could both let go of and retain control led to specific solutions, such as alignment around goals and degrees of freedom for teams, more regular dialogue between managers and teams, and focused investment to teach teams how to solve problems. Lego ultimately created a list titled “11 Paradoxes of Leadership” to help future leaders develop practical solutions to vexing challenges on their own.</p><p></p><p> Organizational paradoxes are ultimately illusions. They are artificial constructs, sometimes of a system, many times of the mind. They fail to meet the definition of a paradox because they are not irreconcilable. Yet these illusionary obstacles persist as groups and individuals protect themselves from the perceived challenges of addressing them. They demand engagement because the process of engagement reveals the illusion, develops a deeper sense of self, and builds an organization&#39;s capabilities. One of my research subjects, a former Silicon Valley executive researching the human side of transformational change, began our interview by saying, “Continual creativity comes from paradox. … All great meaning comes from grappling with paradox.”</p><p></p><p> Leaders who feel like they are facing a paradox should ask themselves four questions:</p><ol><li> Is the perceived paradox truly a law of nature, or a difficult choice?</li><li> Am I imposing a constraint that is creating the perceived paradox?</li><li> Am I hesitating to act because the perceived paradox is the result of the system I helped to construct, perpetuate, and potentially benefit from?</li><li> Does a different frame reveal the paradox as an illusion?</li></ol><p> There&#39;s no doubt that tackling perceived paradoxes presents challenges and requires work. It may feel easier for leaders to collectively shrug their shoulders and say, “What can I do? It is just too hard.”他们可以做得更好。 Perceived paradoxes can be dissected and transcended, turning helplessness into empowerment. Make the paradox choice to turn either/ors into both/ands.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-hidden-opportunity-in-paradoxes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Set Ambitious but Realistic Environmental Goals</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 12 Dec 2023 12:25:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kate Isaacs, Jason Jay, Jeremy Gregory, and Elsa Olivetti. <p>Kate Isaacs and Jason Jay are senior lecturers at the MIT Sloan School of Management. Jeremy Gregory is executive director of the MIT Climate and Sustainability Consortium. Elsa Olivetti is associate dean of engineering, the Jerry McAfee (1940) Professor in Engineering, and a professor of materials science and engineering at MIT.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Climate Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[Traci Daberko The Research The authors held a series of focus groups with experienced sustainability leaders at a dozen large companies. They investigated how leaders go about setting goals, adapting them, and communicating them to stakeholders. In particular, they sought to learn how much companies engage with internal and external stakeholders, how goals drive performance, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/2024WINTER-Isaacs_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Traci Daberko</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>The authors held a series of focus groups with experienced sustainability leaders at a dozen large companies. They investigated how leaders go about setting goals, adapting them, and communicating them to stakeholders. In particular, they sought to learn how much companies engage with internal and external stakeholders, how goals drive performance, and what happens when they don&#39;t reach their goals or they decide to change them.</p></aside><p> In the years since the 2021 round of global climate negotiations, more than 2,600 companies have responded to alarms raised by scientists and policy makers by setting aggressive targets to reduce carbon emissions. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Walmart aims to become powered by 100% renewable energy by 2035; Ikea has made a commitment to produce as much renewable energy as it consumes by 2030; General Electric aims to transform itself into a net-zero company by 2050; and American Electric Power plans to reduce its carbon emissions 80% by 2030, with a goal of net-zero emissions by 2045. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> These sustainability goals address demands from a broad array of stakeholders that companies disclose material risks and improve their environmental and social impacts. They also serve to focus the attention and resources that are required within organizations to drive social and environmental progress on the ground.</p><p></p><p> However, setting appropriately ambitious sustainability goals that can pull a steady line of progress through today&#39;s uncertain business landscape is an exceedingly difficult task. Economic volatility, evolving stakeholder demands, scientific and technological developments, and variable sociopolitical pressures mean that the ground is constantly shifting under leaders&#39; feet.</p><p> Activist stakeholders in particular are watching company performance on these issues closely, demanding corporate transparency around goals and progress, and faulting companies that fail to follow through on their pledges. A 2022 study published by the nonprofit organizations <a href="https://newclimate.org/news/press-release-corporate-climate-responsibility-monitor-2022">NewClimate Institute and Carbon Market Watch</a> identified 25 large corporations with net-zero commitments and rated 21 of them as having “low integrity” or worse because their plans would reduce emissions by only 40% on average, not the 100% implied by net zero.</p><p> Companies also provoke criticism for tiptoeing forward with too much hesitancy and leaping ahead too far too fast. Sustainability goals that are perceived by employees and other stakeholders as insufficiently ambitious can draw internal and public criticism and activist ire. And goals that are very ambitious could provoke resistance from stakeholders who prioritize short-term financial gains, view the technical challenges of complex issues like decarbonization as insurmountable, or are simply unprepared for or unwilling to change. For company leaders who are trying to mediate in the middle, it can feel impossible to get goals just right.</p><p> Climate goals must also take into account current business realities. Chief sustainability officers (CSOs) are focused on environmental and societal concerns but must square their goals in these areas with their companies&#39; dependence on problematic resources such as plastic, fossil fuels, and cheap labor, as well as with the company&#39;s material issues, its purpose and strategic priorities, and the mindset of its leaders.</p><p> Our research, which included focus group discussions with leaders of corporate sustainability initiatives, found that in this atmosphere of both uncertainty and heightened scrutiny, many leaders are grappling with how far to go in setting environmental sustainability goals and what level of disclosure they should achieve. The more ambitious the goals, the stronger the creative tension between an envisioned future and the current reality. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The role of leaders is to manage this tension carefully to inspire their people, engage them in action, and grow stakeholder trust.</p><p> The question at the heart of our research is how this tension can be managed, both intentionally and productively, to drive tangible progress and increase stakeholder trust over time. To do this, leaders must attend to where their company is now and what resources are available to them while also attending to stakeholder input about the social and ecological system of which they are a part. They must aim for integrity at every step in the process: meeting the goals they set for themselves, communicating proactively when they fail to do so, and helping lead systemic changes that supersede any one company&#39;s ability when working alone.</p><h3> No Clear Path to Net-Zero Goals</h3><p> All of the companies in our focus group have publicly committed to reaching carbon neutrality or net zero by 2050. But in our discussions, leaders expressed serious doubts about whether they will be able to achieve their goals, especially those in industries that consume a great deal of industrial process heat, such as petrochemicals, steel, and cement.</p><p> Our participants expressed confidence that they could meet Scope 1 goals — that is, achieve net-zero emissions from sources that their organization directly owns or controls. Most also have what they feel are realistic plans to achieve Scope 2 goals, which cover emissions from the generation of electricity that they purchase (to power a fleet of electric vehicles, for example). These goals can be reached by improving energy conservation and shifting to sources of clean, renewable energy in competitive energy markets, or via power purchase agreements with developers of renewable energy projects.</p><p> Achieving Scope 3 goals is much more challenging across industries, and none of our participants had a predictable road map for doing so. Scope 3 goals include all other indirect emissions associated with an organization&#39;s supply chain; its customers&#39; use of its goods or services, including disposal of packaging and products; and employee commuting. Achieving Scope 3 emissions reductions will require systemic changes at scale toward low-carbon fuels and electrification in transport and logistics. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Changes like these will require new policies, new technologies, and new collaborations within industries and across sectors. To find a path forward on goals that are well beyond what they can achieve on their own and create systemic solutions, companies must reach far outside their own walls to partner with many kinds of stakeholders.</p><p> Based on the experiences and insights of the companies in our study, what follows is a developmental path for organizations that want to set and achieve increasingly ambitious goals and manage the creative tension of the journey in an intentional way.</p><h3> Step 1: <span class="normal">Engage stakeholders to determine the highest-priority areas for sustainability goals.</span></h3><p> Leaders must start by answering two questions: “What are the most meaningful and material sustainability issues where setting goals will matter most?” and “Are there issues we should be working on that we are not?” It&#39;s hard enough to achieve one big, hairy, audacious goal; it is folly to try and achieve 20. To make progress, companies must focus on a small number of issues.</p><p> Companies often center this process on external scanning and sensemaking, which are critical for staying abreast of society&#39;s rapidly changing expectations of company actions and impacts. Public awareness of issues like climate change, racial justice, and public health can rise in response to crises and other events, during which stakeholders identify companies as focal points to take action and create change. This process will always be dynamic and noisy, and if sensemaking is not proactive enough, companies might miss the mark.</p><p> Therefore, companies can and should try to understand what issues are on the minds of external stakeholders (prospective employees, customers, investors, suppliers, and communities) as well as the <em>shapeholders</em> who influence business conditions, such as standards bodies, regulators, scientific experts, nonprofit advocacy groups, and policy makers. Proactive sensemaking happens through a variety of mechanisms, including direct meetings and regular interviews with stakeholders, permanent customer and stakeholder advisory councils, regular attendance of key industry and issue conferences and forums, and benchmark comparisons with competitors. Several of our focus group participants already use AI tools to distill public conversations about the company and industry, and this is a growing area of practice.</p><p> The problem is that this outside-in view does not converge easily with internal perspectives. It can result in an extensive wish list of actions that are hard enough to measure and report, let alone set meaningful goals for and drive progress toward. Narrowing priorities requires an inside-out view as well: clarity about the domain of purpose, mission, and values; a view of the business model and vision for its future; and strategic priorities that move the company closer to that imagined future. This means it&#39;s crucial that leaders also listen to the concerns and priorities of <em>internal</em> stakeholders, particularly the employees who hold the keys to business success, and use that information as input to goal setting.</p><p> Boeing looked to its values and its mission statement — “to connect, protect, explore, and inspire the world through aerospace innovation” — as the foundation to identify six focus areas of sustainability where it has set goals: employee safety and well-being; global aerospace safety;多样性、公平性和包容性； innovation and clean technology; sustainable operations;和社区参与。</p><p> To arrive at these goals, leaders from the company&#39;s sustainability office interviewed Boeing employees and also surveyed and conducted interviews with external stakeholders. These efforts uncovered a number of sustainability topics that connected back to the company&#39;s overall strategy and future direction. Boeing leaders reviewed the stakeholder feedback, looked for common themes, and ultimately pruned the list down to a manageable number of priorities.</p><p> “Trying to be everything to everyone is not going to be successful. We deliberately zeroed in on six areas to drive alignment and focus that employees and external stakeholders can rally to support,” explained Jill Graftenreed, Boeing&#39;s director of sustainable operations and reporting.</p><p> Finally, the company&#39;s sustainability leaders needed to get leaders in other areas of the enterprise to take ownership of these priorities, so they engaged the appropriate internal functional leaders to identify one or two targets for each priority along with metrics to measure progress. This required additional consultation and benchmarking with external stakeholders, industry peers, and standard-setting bodies.</p><p> “It was important to us that we provided metrics that are meaningful and consistent with what others in the industry are also using,” Graftenreed said. “Stakeholders want to look across companies to compare how they are doing.”</p><p></p><h3> Step 2: <span class="normal">Develop an aspirational vision of success that is informed by the science of sustainability and stakeholder expectations.</span></h3><p> Once they identify high-priority issues, sustainability leaders must generate a vision of the future they aspire to create, which can serve as a North Star for company efforts. For instance, a company&#39;s climate vision might link to the scientifically driven vision to limit global warming <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/sr15/">to 1.5 degrees</a> Celsius to avoid the most catastrophic impacts and allow for adaptation.</p><p> While many companies set goals by starting with their existing emissions footprint and calculating forward to arrive at carbon reduction goals that they believe they can reasonably achieve, aspirational companies flip this process around: They establish a vision that is aligned with scientific recommendations and stakeholder expectations and then figure out their company&#39;s contribution to achieving that vision.</p><p></p><p> Salesforce anchored its climate goals externally to a single shared planetary vision of a just transition to a 1.5-degree Celsius future and then worked backward to align its Scope 1, 2, and 3 emissions goals accordingly. This translated into a companywide goal to reduce full value-chain annual emissions by 50% by 2030 and to nearly zero by 2040, using 2019 data as a baseline. In addition, Salesforce set location-based emissions targets that pushed beyond the IT industry&#39;s standard practice of using carbon offsets and renewable energy credits from greener sites to compensate for more emissions-intensive locations.</p><p> Connecting a company&#39;s contribution to a big shared vision involves building shared commitment through extensive conversations with employees, managers, and company leaders and with external stakeholders and shapeholders. And this work is never finished, given that stakeholder views on what is a legitimate aspiration can be dynamic and noisy. For instance, one company had set ambitious emissions goals two years earlier but then became aware that the SBTi (Science Based Targets initiative) had suddenly grown very influential. In following the SBTi agenda, the company decided to set more ambitious goals around its Scope 3 emissions. As the organization&#39;s leader told us, “We set carbon-neutral goals, but what everyone wants now is net zero.”</p><p> The aspirational vision that a company sets at this stage might also need to be updated based on new scientific developments, new technological capabilities, or changes in key stakeholder concerns. Inditex, which owns seven brands, including fashion retailer Zara, started its sustainability journey in the early 2000s with its first multiyear sustainability plan. In 2013, the company published a biodiversity strategy that defined some basic principles and an aim “to embed a biodiversity agenda in our day-to-day business decisions.” Later, company leaders created a road map that included not only climate action but also critical sustainability issues such as impact on soil health, water quality and availability, and ecosystem protection and restoration. This commitment was further reinforced in July 2023, when Inditex announced the launch of new, specific targets that address external stakeholders&#39; expectations, including goals related to the promotion of preferred raw materials and biodiversity.</p><p> Inditex used standards set by organizations such as Textile Exchange to guide its 2030 goal to use only “preferred fibers” as textile raw materials in order to reduce the negative impact on the environment. The company also worked with environmental experts, third-sector organizations, unions, and nonprofits to analyze impacts on local communities of activities such as garment manufacturing or retail store operations. One of the results of this process was an ambitious target of protecting, restoring, regenerating, or otherwise improving biodiversity across 5 million hectares at locations throughout the world.</p><h3> Step 3: <span class="normal">Set midlevel goals to gain early traction on the high-level vision.</span></h3><p> Next, leaders must set achievable goals that move the company from its current state (honestly and accurately assessed) toward the future vision developed in Step 2. In order to produce the desired outcomes, goals should not be too narrow, too ambitious, or too short-term — what some have called “goals gone wild.” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Leaders must understand the business intimately enough to set goals that intentionally create productive tension between vision and current reality and move the company forward, beginning with a series of small, achievable steps and building up to larger goals over time. They must carefully consider the specificity, ambition, timing, and ethical implications of their goals, as well as the range of outcomes their intended goals might produce.</p><p> At pharmaceutical company Takeda, the CEO had set a high-level climate goal to reduce emissions by 30% by 2030 (from 2015 levels). Rich Wilner, head of business transformation and environmental sustainability, noticed that despite this goal, carbon reduction projects in the factories were not getting funded. He set out to connect the “top to the shop” by setting a goal at one plant to launch just one capital investment project that year aimed at reducing greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions. Beginning with this small goal helped that plant overcome the inertia of getting started on the journey, and the approach was quickly adopted across the network of plants.</p><p> Later, Wilner successfully advocated for important organizational changes to align behavior with the intent to reduce carbon emissions. This included changes to the company&#39;s capital allocation process that would weight GHG-reducing projects favorably, along with the implementation of monitoring and forecasting tools that plant managers could easily use. The company further incentivized progress by incorporating the successful completion of carbon reduction projects into employees&#39; annual bonuses. These moves helped set up the next 10 projects for success and got Wilner&#39;s division on track with corporate goals.</p><h3> Step 4: <span class="normal">Build momentum with willing stakeholders, and expand the goal horizon toward the vision.</span></h3><p> Once the organization has gained traction on early goals, the work of sustainability leaders should shift to accelerating uptake inside the organization and gradually extending the goals toward the aspirational vision.</p><p> In his former role as sustainability manager at the Kroger grocery chain, Vontier&#39;s senior global director of sustainability and ESG, Nate Streed, sought to build momentum around a high-level vision of zero manufacturing waste companywide, including three dozen food manufacturing facilities and thousands of retail stores across the country. Like Wilner, Streed started small, by visiting seven plants — whose pioneering leaders were early and willing adopters — to understand their waste production process. Although plant leaders initially kept him at arm&#39;s length, they came to understand that he genuinely wanted to learn rather than just dictate solutions from corporate headquarters.</p><p> Streed encouraged plant leaders to experiment with new waste-reduction strategies by reframing waste as something that retains value and prompting questions to spur innovative thinking. One plant, for example, created dedicated bins for recyclable polypropylene straps and then got the vendor to color-code the straps for easier sorting. Another was able to provide coffee grounds and burlap sacks to a local landscape contractor in South Carolina.</p><p> Streed and his team harnessed the natural dynamic of collaborative competition among plant managers, encouraging them to share successful strategies and solutions while competing on plant-level metrics. Corporate leaders reinforced his efforts by making personal visits to celebrate the progress of these creative, locally tailored waste solutions. They also assured local leaders that they wouldn&#39;t be punished for trying new things, even if the initial results negatively affected performance metrics.</p><p></p><p> From these seven early-adopter plants, Streed and his team were able to continue to build momentum toward zero waste, bringing more plants on board and identifying more waste-reduction innovations. Today, almost all of Kroger&#39;s manufacturing plants operate as zero-waste facilities (with over 90% diversion), and in 2022 Kroger achieved 79% waste diversion companywide (including stores, warehouses, offices, and other facilities). <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> This illustrates how a high-level corporate vision must be paired with on-the-ground measurement and continuous improvement and innovation efforts that expand progress toward the ultimate vision.</p><p> An organization that embraces both a vision for sustainability and an ethos of sustainability-oriented innovation sets its people up for serendipitous discovery. Researchers at Dow were working on designing minuscule hollow spheres to create a light-scattering pigment in paint. That plan fell apart when researchers discovered that a small amount of heat caused the spheres to collapse. But because innovators were thinking in terms of sustainability, they recognized that the spheres could be used in a different way. If a dark-colored paper were coated with the spheres, a thermal printer could burn away the coating to produce a printed page — an environmentally friendly alternative to coating thermal printer paper with toxic chemicals such as bisphenol A. Attuning to sustainability leads to serendipity and unexpected value.</p><h3> Step 5: <span class="normal">Scale efforts to lead systems change.</span></h3><p> When companies identify systemic challenges that make Scope 3 and other value-chain goals difficult to achieve, there is an opportunity for leadership on a larger stage. This shift involves engaging with others in the industry, in cross-sector coalitions, and in policy debates to define collective goals and set the conditions for shared success.</p><p> Salesforce realized that achieving Scope 3 goals in particular could not happen without the wider engagement of the cloud computing industry. It began scaling up its efforts to the system level by taking action along three dimensions:</p><ul><li> It identified its core competency as delivering transformational software tools to businesses of all industries, sizes, and geographies, and articulated its customer value as helping them navigate successfully into the future. Clarifying the company&#39;s purpose and the value it creates led Salesforce to the development of its Net Zero Cloud tool, which enables customers to track, report, and reduce emissions.</li><li> It identified where the leverage points were for the company to influence impacts and the value chain across scopes 1, 2, and 3. For example, Salesforce notified all of its suppliers in 2020 that climate would be part of all new standard purchasing agreements. To do business with Salesforce, suppliers must prepare emissions reduction plans that disclose their Scope 1, 2, and 3 emissions and deliver all of their products and services on a carbon-neutral basis or pay for the cost of carbon.</li><li> The company took a broader view of the systemic issues beyond its control and where it was well positioned to contribute. Salesforce led and joined consortia to promote more sustainable offices and data centers, greater adoption of high-quality renewable energy, carbon credits, sustainable aviation fuel, and nature-based solutions.</li></ul><p> Former Salesforce CSO Patrick Flynn suggests asking, “Which of the very important things that need to be done are ones that we are uniquely suited to do or, at the most extreme, that will not happen unless we do it?” This provides a starting point for a focus area for action, along with a defensible story and strategy that can be explained to company employees and external stakeholders.</p><p> Maritime shipping is another sector in which sustainability solutions will depend on many organizations and stakeholders working in concert. It is both a hard-to-decarbonize sector (heavily reliant on petroleum-based fuel) and a significant contributor to many companies&#39; Scope 3 supply chain emissions. Maersk, one of the largest players in the industry, began setting goals in 2008 to reduce carbon emissions through fleet efficiency and the pursuit of alternative fuels, and it eventually set an ambitious 2040 net-zero target. Company leaders quickly realized, however, that they could not achieve these objectives alone. Alternative fuels require systems change — the creation of new supply chains and regulatory frameworks for lower-carbon fuels like methanol, green hydrogen, and ammonia.</p><p> As a result, Maersk has engaged the United Nations&#39; International Maritime Organization on carbon policy and joined alternative-fuels consortia with a wide range of partners, including green power provider Ørsted, ammonia fertilizer leader Yara, shipbuilders like Hyundai, Sumitomo for fuel supply chain provision, and a variety of financial institutions. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Ultimately, creating supply corridors for ammonia or methanol will require engagement with ports and communities around the world along major shipping routes.</p><p> At Inditex, leaders saw that achieving the goal of having 25% of its textile materials produced by regenerative or organic farming practices was at odds with the industry reality that a mere 2% of all cotton grown worldwide is organic and the percentage grown using regenerative farming practices is even lower. Meeting its target will require its ongoing support of external projects and advocacy groups that work to meaningfully grow these practices. It has since joined Conservation International&#39;s Regenerative Fund and donated 15 million euros ($15.9 million) to help scale up regenerative farming practices. It is also working with Action for Social Advancement, together with Laudes Foundation, IDH, and WWF India, to foster regenerative agriculture, restore ecosystems, and improve community well-being in a 300,000-hectare area in the Indian states of Madhya Pradesh and Odisha 。</p><p> A number of strategies for action are available to companies that seek to promote systemic change. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Business leaders have convening power to bring diverse stakeholders to the table, provided that they have demonstrated a sincere commitment to sustainability goals and have a track record of making progress on goals. They have economic power to put direct pressure on suppliers and to make demands of policy makers, given their critical role in providing jobs and creating a functioning economy and society. Leaders can use their power wisely to convene and fund new initiatives if they have earned credibility by implementing steps 1 through 4, and if stakeholders perceive that their motivation is to create societal as well as business benefit.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Ultimately, sustainability is a team sport. The challenge that company leaders face is to set provisional/achievable corporate goals that grow organizational capabilities to reach toward the needs of the planet and its people. Those needs are incredibly high right now. But company leaders don&#39;t have to face them alone; an insular approach to managing sustainability goals will not create the future we want for business or life on planet Earth. Engage with the board, executives, and employees to manage the tension. Engage with the value chain and even competitors for joint problem-solving. Engage in the wider public policy debate to change the system and make goal setting and achievement more feasible for everyone. And help everyone understand that transformation is a journey — one that sometimes starts with a single capital expenditure project in a single factory and ultimately creates a better future for all.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/set-ambitious-but-realistic-environmental-goals/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Meet Tomorrow&#39;s Workforce: Today&#39;s Student Labor Activists</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ayanna Howard. <p>Ayanna Howard ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robotsmarts">@robotsmarts</a> ) is dean of the College of Engineering at The Ohio State University.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nick Lowndes/Ikon Images Student labor activism is on the rise in new and surprising ways. Not only do students in higher education regularly turn out to support striking staff members on college campuses, but they’re also organizing and joining unions themselves in growing numbers. This direct action sets the stage for their lives after they [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Howard_Unionization-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Nick Lowndes/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Student labor activism is on the rise in new and surprising ways. Not only do students in higher education regularly turn out to support striking staff members on college campuses, but they&#39;re also organizing and joining unions themselves in growing numbers. This direct action sets the stage for their lives after they leave higher education, because when students are involved in organizing efforts in their on-campus working lives, you&#39;d better believe these same workers will seek out unions later in their careers.</p><p> The number of student-worker bargaining units in the US grew from 54 at the beginning of 2022 to 84 in July 2023 — a <a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/news/faculty-issues/labor-unionization/2023/09/06/grad-worker-unionization-booming-even-down-south">56% increase</a> — according to the National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions. While there&#39;s been steady growth over the past few decades in the organization of graduate students, whose focus is often on teaching requirements and compensation, what is new is a surge of undergraduate student workers turning to collective bargaining around issues such as minimum-wage pay and sick leave benefits.</p><p></p><p> Business leaders would be wise to pay attention to how some universities are working with students to address these challenges. The task for schools is to ensure the rights of students to unionize for an improved on-campus work environment while also providing those same students with the educational benefits of living and learning on campus. There are parallels here to how businesses must juggle the need for both workplace productivity and employee satisfaction. Today&#39;s student organizers are building expectations for partnership that they will bring with them to their future workplaces.</p><p></p><h3> The Rise of Undergrad Unionization</h3><p> Before 2016, nearly all organized student unions were composed of graduate student employees. In fact, there was only one that wasn&#39;t: In 2002, undergraduate students who served as resident assistants at the University of Massachusetts Amherst became the <a href="https://ilr.law.uiowa.edu/sites/ilr.law.uiowa.edu/files/2023-02/Fitzpatrick.pdf">first union of student resident assistants</a> in the country. Then, after 2016, other undergraduate unionization efforts began popping up, at Grinnell College, George Washington University, and Reed College, among others.</p><p> Students — whether they are focused on the two-year associate&#39;s degree, the four-year bachelor&#39;s degree, or graduate studies — represent approximately <a href="https://cew.georgetown.edu/wp-content/uploads/Working-Learners-Report.pdf">8% of the US workforce</a> . Many work within campus environments like The Ohio State University, where I am dean of the College of Engineering, either because work-study on campus is required as part of their financial aid package or because there are few flexible part-time work opportunities available for the traditional 18-to-23-year-old student.</p><p> The kinds of issues they&#39;re organizing around are closely aligned with the issues raised by unions in the retail and service industries. A <a href="https://slu.cuny.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Union-Density-2023.pdf">2023 report</a> out of the CUNY School of Labor and Urban Studies noted that the new wave of student-worker unions “has included teaching and research assistants in both the humanities and the previously quiescent STEM fields, as well as undergraduate resident advisers, student dining hall workers, and library staff.” The 30 new student-worker collective bargaining units launched since the start of 2022 represent 35,655 workers — a number that might be getting a big boost soon: At California State University, over 19,300 student assistants are hoping to vote as early as January 2024 on their organizing efforts, which would make them <a href="https://calmatters.org/education/higher-education/college-beat/2023/10/student-workers/">one of the largest student-worker unions</a> in US history.</p><p></p><p> The year 2022 marked another change: the evolution of the student-worker strike. The CUNY report cites 20 strikes by workers in higher education in 2022 and 2023 by a mix of faculty members, postdocs, and students and states that “this explosive growth in strike activity in higher education is unprecedented within recent memory.” The most notable of these, the University of California graduate student workers&#39; strike, lasted over five weeks and is now recorded as the <a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/after-historic-strike-uc-grad-students-say-university-isn-t-honoring-pay-agreements">largest ever at a US institution of higher education</a> . It ended with an agreement for higher pay, fee waivers, and other benefits.</p><p> Some experts postulate that there&#39;s a <a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/news/faculty-issues/labor-unionization/2023/04/26/were-not-slowing-down-student-workers-say">strong correlation</a> between the growth of unions on college campuses and the growth in high-profile organization efforts off campus (most recently at Amazon, Apple, and Starbucks). In fact, union organizing among college-educated young workers has been trending up. Gallup reports the relatively high <a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/354455/approval-labor-unions-highest-point-1965.aspx">approval rate of 77% for labor unions</a> among young adults.</p><h3> Power Dynamics to Watch</h3><p> On college and university campuses, unionizing student workers represent a unique constituency. On the one hand, their relationship to the school is one of worker-employer. On the other hand, they are also paying for a service and educational product, making the relationship one of customer-provider.</p><p> Schools navigating this dual identity need to think of these student-worker activists as a new kind of stakeholder — one to engage with and ultimately keep happy. California&#39;s state superintendent of public instruction, Tony Thurmond, who also serves as an ex officio member of the California State University board of trustees, put it this way at an October press conference about that school&#39;s student unionization efforts: “The California State University is stronger today because students are rising up to hold the university system true to its mission to open the doors of higher education and a strong future to every student, no matter their background.”</p><p> Corporate organizations faced with newly organizing employees often don&#39;t initially think of them this way — as a cohort that they similarly have to engage with and ultimately keep happy. Some successful negotiations eventually bring both sides around to this understanding, if only begrudgingly.</p><p> It&#39;s worth noting that this student movement is occurring at exactly the same time that some employers in corporate America have <a href="https://time.com/6221176/worker-strikes-employers-unions/">spied on and fired workers</a> who were leading organization efforts (actions that are illegal under the National Labor Relations Act). But companies must understand that if their values do not align with this new generation of student workers who have lived the experience of political advocacy, they will have difficulty in recruiting. “I think unions are incredibly important,” a college sophomore <a href="https://www.marketplace.org/2023/11/06/campus-labor-activism-spreads-to-undergrads/">told nonprofit news organization Marketplace</a> after undergraduates at her school, Barnard College, voted to unionize in October. “I would be honored to be part of one after college.”</p><p></p><p> In their article “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-an-age-of-employee-activism/">Leading in an Age of Employee Activism</a> ,” Megan Reitz, of Hult International Business School, and John Higgins, coauthor of the book <a href="https://www.routledge.com/Leadership-Unravelled-The-Faulty-Thinking-Behind-Modern-Management/Cole-Higgins/p/book/9781032033686"><cite>Leadership Unravelled</cite></a> , noted, “We are entering an age of employee activism that may well upend our assumptions about power within organizations.” Some business leaders might see this as a passing trend, but many of us in the university environment know that student labor activism is becoming the new norm — and see learning how to address the needs of the newest generation of worker-customers as an imperative. Companies and their leaders have an opportunity to watch how these negotiations play out on college campuses and understand that they&#39;re likely to also be tasked at some point with navigating the different (and perhaps divergent) interests of established employees and management, community members, and younger employee activists.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Emotional Landscape of Leadership</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker, Natalia Weisz, Vijay Pereira, and Alfredo De Massis. <p>Benjamin Laker <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">(@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School in the UK Natalia Weisz is a professor of leadership at IAE Business School in Argentina. Vijay Pereira is a distinguished professor of international and strategic human capital management at NEOMA Business School in France. Alfredo De Massis is a professor of entrepreneurship and family business at the Free University of Bozen-Bolzano in Italy, the International Institute for Management Development (IMD) in Switzerland, and Lancaster University Management School in the UK</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managerial Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Teams]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Navigating a first-time leadership role often mirrors the balancing act of a tightrope walker. On one side, there’s a team seeking direction and inspiration; on the other, higher-ups are scrutinizing each decision. This journey isn’t just about taking on added responsibilities like managing teams and coordinating projects; it’s also about stepping into [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Laker-Emotional-Landscape-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> Navigating a first-time leadership role often mirrors the balancing act of a tightrope walker. On one side, there&#39;s a team seeking direction and inspiration; on the other, higher-ups are scrutinizing each decision. This journey isn&#39;t just about taking on added responsibilities like managing teams and coordinating projects; it&#39;s also about stepping into a heightened arena of emotions that includes joy, pride, anxiety, fear, and occasional self-doubt.</p><p> As new leaders climb the organizational hierarchy, they face both the joys of success and the burden of failure, and the significance of their decisions is magnified in their more visible role. In our research — forthcoming in the journal <cite>BMJ Leader</cite> — approximately 67% of new leaders reported feeling immense pride when their team achieved a milestone. Similarly, 72% cited joy when their guidance positively impacted a team member&#39;s growth.</p><p></p><p> On the flip side, the pressures are evident too. About 58% of respondents confessed to experiencing anxiety when faced with critical decision-making, while almost half (49%) said they felt apprehensive about potential missteps being viewed critically by superiors. Interestingly, 53% of first-time leaders expressed occasional self-doubt, emphasizing the importance of mentorship and peer support in navigating this intricate leadership terrain.</p><p> Underlying these challenges is the essential yet often overlooked domain of emotional regulation, which stands out as a key determinant in the efficacy of leadership. Whereas an individual contributor might excel with technical prowess and domain knowledge alone, leadership mandates a heightened level of emotional intelligence — not just the capacity for personal emotional regulation but also the ability to recognize and manage the emotions of others. This emotional competency in leadership plays a pivotal role in shaping team dynamics. A leader with a high level of emotional intelligence fosters motivation, morale, and performance. In contrast, those who falter in this realm risk creating a counterproductive and potentially toxic environment, hampering creativity and impeding organizational progress.</p><p> Other skills and aptitudes are undeniably essential in leadership; however, it&#39;s the adept handling and comprehension of emotions that delineates a flourishing leader from one who merely gets by or even stumbles. Recognizing this significant nuance and its implications for leadership development, our research team sought to bridge this knowledge gap. We employed a two-step methodology: an initial broad survey, followed by qualitative interviews. The online questionnaire was directed at over 2,000 new leaders, especially those with two to five years of leadership experience. Feedback was collected over three months to gather insights into their experiences with emotions at work. Then, to gain a deeper understanding, we chose 100 new leaders to participate in detailed interviews.</p><p></p><h3> Regulating Emotions at Work: A Guide for First-Time Leaders</h3><p> Our research took a comprehensive look at the practical challenges leaders face and the strategies they employ in the area of emotional regulation. We identified common trends and insights that inform the six best practices that follow.</p><p> <strong>1. Understanding the role of self-awareness.</strong> The linchpin to effective emotional regulation in leadership is self-awareness. Leaders should routinely engage in introspection, asking themselves, “How do I feel right now?” and, “Is this emotion serving or hindering my leadership?” By actively addressing these questions, leaders can better understand and regulate their emotional responses. In our research, leaders who adopted this introspective approach witnessed a 45% improvement in team morale and a 38% increase in decision-making efficiency. Further, organizations reported a 32% rise in overall productivity when their leaders practiced consistent self-awareness. Embracing this approach not only bolsters leadership capabilities but tangibly benefits the entire team and organization.</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. Enhancing vision through diverse feedback.</strong> A leader&#39;s journey is not walked alone; feedback from trusted individuals can provide invaluable waypoints. Building a circle of mentors, peers, and even receptive subordinates allows leaders to gain insights beyond their immediate perspectives. Such external viewpoints can illuminate emotional blind spots, fostering growth and adaptability. Our research underscores the significance of this collaborative approach: Leaders who actively sought and integrated feedback experienced a 60% uptick in their adaptability to change and a 45% improvement in interpersonal relationships within their teams. In the dynamic landscape of leadership, this constant dialogue proves to be a keystone for sustained success.</p><p> <strong>3. Establishing boundaries for sustainable leadership.</strong> Assuming a leadership role is accompanied by heightened responsibilities. However, perpetually being on call can lead to burnout and diminished effectiveness. Setting clear boundaries, both for themselves and their teams, ensures that leaders have dedicated moments to decompress, reflect, and return with renewed vigor. Our findings underscore the pragmatic advantages of this approach: Leaders who established and communicated clear boundaries reported a 59% increase in their own productivity and a 51% enhancement in team satisfaction levels. Furthermore, these leaders noticed a 42% decrease in their own stress-related issues. Establishing boundaries is less about creating distance than it is about cultivating an environment where leaders and teams can function optimally.</p><p> <strong>4. Embracing authenticity — the strength of vulnerability.</strong> The mantle of leadership often comes with misplaced expectations of stoicism or an emotional facade, but true leadership strength can be found in authenticity and vulnerability. By acknowledging personal feelings and judiciously sharing them, leaders can bridge gaps, foster deeper connections, and engender trust within their teams. Our research found that leaders who embraced vulnerability witnessed a 66% increase in team trust levels and a 49% rise in team cohesion. Moreover, these authentic leaders reported a 38% improvement in their own job satisfaction. In the realm of leadership, vulnerability is not a liability; it&#39;s an asset that nurtures trust and authentic relationships.</p><p></p><p> <strong>5. Having extracurricular coping strategies — the key to balance.</strong> As leadership intensifies, the need for balance becomes paramount. Developing coping mechanisms outside the professional sphere is not a luxury but a necessity. Whether it&#39;s through physical activity, putting pen to paper in a journal, engaging in creative outlets, or cherishing moments with loved ones, these pursuits offer an essential emotional reset. According to our research, leaders who actively engaged in such extracurricular coping strategies saw a 56% reduction in work-related stress levels and a 47% increase in overall well-being. Additionally, these leaders noted a 43% improvement in their problem-solving capabilities within the workplace. Cultivating effective coping mechanisms is vital for a leader&#39;s holistic growth and endurance in their role.</p><p> <strong>6. Practicing breathing and mindfulness — anchors in chaos.</strong> In the fast-paced world of decision-making, the solution sometimes lies in simplicity: taking a moment to breathe. A single deep breath can provide immediate clarity amid chaos. Incorporating mindfulness and brief meditation practices into the daily routine establishes a bedrock of calm. By anchoring themselves in the present, leaders can tackle complex scenarios without being consumed by overwhelming emotions. Our research highlights tangible benefits: Leaders who integrated regular mindfulness practices into their lives reported a 50% enhancement in their emotional resilience and a 40% increase in clarity during high-pressure situations. This focus on the here and now is a cornerstone for modern leadership success.</p><h3> The Continuous Balancing Endeavor</h3><p> We urge every emerging leader to invest in emotional intelligence training and regularly engage in self-reflection in order to master their emotions and thereby lead with clarity and conviction. Consider taking these actions, starting today:</p><p> <strong>Regularly reflect.</strong> Commit to five to 10 minutes of introspective reflection daily, actively dissecting how your emotions drive your decisions. Document your insights in a journal, and push yourself to draw connections between feelings and actions. As days turn into weeks, you&#39;ll spot recurring patterns that shape your choices. Harness this newfound self-awareness and proactively channel it to make better, more informed decisions in your daily life.</p><p> <strong>Actively listen to varied voices.</strong> Begin each month with an intention to diversify your feedback channels: Select a colleague, a team member, and a mentor for their insights. Approach these conversations with an open heart, deliberately curbing the instinct to justify or counter the other person&#39;s perspectives. By absorbing their words and understanding their viewpoints, you&#39;re granting yourself a rich, multifaceted mirror into how you&#39;re perceived. Use this invaluable feedback as a directional compass that can steer you toward personal and professional development. And share your own experiences with your team: Discussing a personal lesson you learned or how you dealt with a challenge can foster an environment where others feel safe to share and learn.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Define digital work boundaries.</strong> Prioritize your well-being by establishing unmistakable “office hours” in digital environments, such as refraining from addressing work-related emails or messages after 7 pm Clearly communicate this boundary to your colleagues: Setting an example of the importance of work-life balance might inspire team members to carve out their own digital limits and protect their personal time. This proactive approach not only upholds individual well-being but also fortifies a collective respect for boundaries within the workplace.</p><p> <strong>Discover your personal reset mechanism.</strong> Earmark a minimum of one hour every week to immerse yourself in a non-work-related hobby or passion, be it painting, running, or reading a gripping novel. Recognize this time as your sacred reset hour — a sanctuary for your mind and soul. Opening up about your experiences and the refreshing benefits you reap can motivate your team members to also find and embrace their own “reset” passions. Such proactive dedication not only enriches individual well-being but also fosters a culture of holistic balance within a team.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Commence with calming breath work.</strong> Kick-start your day or pivotal meetings by dedicating the first two minutes to deliberate deep breathing exercises. Take the lead and set an example, guiding your team through the rhythm and benefits of this calming practice. By actively promoting this ritual, you not only rejuvenate individual minds but also cultivate a collective sense of serenity. Seize this tranquil foundation to steer discussions, decisions, or tasks with heightened focus and a unified approach.</p><p></p><p> While emotional regulation might seem like a small component in the grand scheme of leadership, it&#39;s critical in determining a leader&#39;s effectiveness. Emotions, if unchecked, can cloud judgment, create conflict, or lead to impulsive decisions. Conversely, when harnessed correctly, they can inspire, motivate, and drive a team to greatness. In today&#39;s fast-paced work environment where the lines between the personal and professional often blur, it&#39;s more crucial than ever for leaders, especially those stepping into the role for the first time, to master the art of regulating emotions at work.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>