<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 18 日星期二 14:41:12 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>用人工智能检测好与坏：Airbnb 的 Naba Banerjee</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operational Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Predictive Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Psychological Safety]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Naba Banerjee’s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Naba Banerjee “永远学习者”的身份使她成为家族中第一位女工程师。这种好奇心也影响了她的职业选择，引导她加入了塔塔、高知特、AAA 和沃尔玛等各种公司。现在，作为度假租赁平台 Airbnb 的信托产品和运营总监，她继续以好奇心为向导，将之前的数据科学经验应用于旅游业。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客中，Naba 与主持人 Shervin Khodabandeh 和 Sam Ransbotham 一起谈论她和她的团队如何使用人工智能和机器学习来提高使用 Airbnb 平台的房客和房东的安全。她还讨论了人类与机器之间的协作，以及认识到两者都不是绝对正确的决策者的重要性。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-S7-E1-Banerjee-Airbnb-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="纳巴·班纳吉"></p><h4>纳巴·班纳吉，Airbnb</h4><p> Naba Banerjee 是 Airbnb 信托产品和运营总监，负责监督该公司打击欺诈、在房东和房客之间建立信任以及阻止不良行为者使用该平台的努力。她最近的工作包括开发 Airbnb 的预订筛选技术，该技术有助于识别进行潜在高风险预订的用户，并防止他们利用该平台。</p><p> Banerjee 拥有二十多年构建产品的经验，可提供创新的、以客户为中心的解决方案。她在 Walmart.com 工作了 13 年之后加入了 Airbnb，在 Walmart.com 的产品管理发展中发挥了重要作用，包括更快地向客户运送包裹以及构建移动应用程序以帮助客户更快地结账。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-banerjee"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>机器学习可以检测欺诈活动，但也可能会错过良好行为。在今天的节目中了解一家平台公司如何管理这些风险和权衡。</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我是来自 Airbnb 的 Naba Banerjee，你们正在听<cite>我、我自己和 AI 的</cite>声音。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>今天，Shervin 和我正在与 Airbnb 信托产品和运营总监 Naba Banerjee 进行交谈。纳巴，感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>谢谢；很高兴来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为大多数人都知道 Airbnb，但也许可以告诉我们该公司的简要概述以及您的业务。</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong> Airbnb 代表着一个促进联系和归属感的地方。数以百万计的主人向完全陌生的人开放他们的家，你我和我们的家人可以去一个充满异国情调的目的地旅行，而不是住在酒店，你实际上可以真正沉浸在当地文化中。有时，如果您真的很幸运，您可以住在房东的家里，真正体验到房东的本来面目，从而建立和促进联系和归属感。</p><p>在这个日益变得孤立、联系变得越来越稀有的世界里，我很高兴能成为一家致力于创造更多联系的公司的一员。我的团队（爱彼迎的信任与安全团队）的工作贯穿于整个客户旅程，从您在爱彼迎创建帐户的整个旅程开始。有时，可能会出现问题：可能会创建虚假帐户，或者您的帐户可能会被接管。您想要入住的房源可能是假房源；您正在查看的评论可能并不完全真实。但我们的工作是确保您可以专注于您的神奇住宿，房东可以专注于成为完美的房东，我们会尽力预测其中一些风险，并将发生此类问题的风险降至最低。我的团队所做的就是利用技术和数据来实现神奇的用户旅程。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我想我们都听到过出现问题的头条新闻。在您进行的无数交易过程中出了多少问题？</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>这是一个很好的问题。 2021 年，爱彼迎上发生了大约 7000 万次旅行，其中不到 0.1% 的旅行导致房东或房客报告该次住宿期间可能发生的问题。当我们的团队深入调查并实际查看真正的伤害发生在哪里或必须将某人从平台上删除时，这个数字甚至更小。</p><p>我知道即使是一件糟糕的事件也可能太糟糕了，不应该发生，但在更大范围的事情中，你回过头来意识到大多数人实际上都是好人。百分之九十九点九的人只想处理日常事务、享受愉快的住宿或成为出色的主人。但有时，在极少数情况下，当坏事发生时，我们希望确保降低这种风险。</p><p>如果你仔细观察一个人在哪里对另一个人造成了伤害，你会发现这些事件只是一小部分。但当我们谈论安全时，我们关注的是[诸如]一氧化碳气体泄漏。可能会滑倒；这可能是财产损失，玻璃破裂，地毯上可能有污渍。我们也在研究此类问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我从你的话中听到的是，你的角色是，第一，一个好角色。你是善良的保护者和邪恶的“守护者”，对吗？</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>我喜欢这个。您应该成为我们品牌团队的一员。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这是一件好事，对吧？这是一个非常有目的的角色。第二部分是，你谈论的是微观上的小事件。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的，大海捞针。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>对吗？这些都是有趣的问题。告诉我们更多关于幕后的信息——会发生什么？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我想说它分为三个部分。一是，我们从“为什么”开始，也就是说——你说得很好——我们是善的保护者，并试图抵御坏的。我们永远不能说我们阻止了一切不好的事情。就像山姆所说的那样，你不能那样做。但我们如何学习并变得更好呢？这就是人工智能和机器学习[机器学习]的用武之地，[我们问]“我们如何利用数据和技术的力量来学习并变得更好？”每年，风险都不会保持不变；数据不断增长。</p><p>第二件事是，“我们如何负责任地使用技术？”也就是说，您可能会过于直率并尝试尽可能多地阻止以专门查看欺诈和安全事件并将其控制下来，但是，如果您用于做出这些决策的数据存在偏见，则可能会创造不公平，那么你就可能对很多真正只想过得愉快的好人关上大门。所以[它是关于]负责任地使用技术。 ......它有自治机制，也就是说，我们有我们的隐私团队，我们的数据隐私团队，我们的信息安全团队，我们的反歧视团队，它们......几乎就像信任团队的镜子。 [还有] Airbnb 的其他团队，每次我们真正专注于这个特定的欺诈媒介、机器人检测、帐户接管检测或当事人检测时，他们都会不断确保我们是否使用了以下数据：一种安全的方式和透明的方式，给用户控制权，然后不引入偏见。</p><p>最后，我们有办法为人们提供一条回头路，也就是说，我们将根据我们可用的数据、我们可用的技术以及该技术的成熟度，尽我们所能决定。但如果我们错了，我们是否可以创建透明度和一个流程，让用户在我们阻止或删除他们时提出申诉并重新回到平台，以便我们能够再次学习并变得更好？因此，在最高层面上，这就是我的团队在幕后工作的方式。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>有哪些用例？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我们已经讨论过很多次的用例之一是，你知道......我将给你讲一个小故事，那就是，当我在 2020 年加入信托团队时，世界刚刚关闭；疫情肆虐。与世界等待疫苗的方式非常相似，在等待疫苗的过程中，我们进入了封锁模式。</p><p>这是一个生硬的工具……防止人们将自己暴露在不安全的情况下。同样，Airbnb 不幸成为适合未经授权的家庭聚会的产品市场。不幸的是，当酒店和酒吧关闭时，只有不到 1% 或 0.1% 的用户在寻找可以举办派对的地方，开始出租 Airbnb。结果，我们意识到这给使用这个基于信任基础的平台的房东和房客社区带来了很多痛苦。所以最初，我们不得不使用一些非常生硬的工具。</p><p>我们首先制定了全球派对禁令，称爱彼迎不允许举办任何类型的派对。其次，我们开始研究一些模式，发现 25 岁以下的人会在离家不到 50 英里左右的地方预订整个房屋一晚或两晚 - 这些似乎都是导致聚会的信号。当聚会发生时，我们通常会发现……该帐户是昨天创建的。然后我们实施了一项名为“25 岁以下”的生硬规则，并将其落实到位。现在，我们必须小心，因为这些规则并不完全适用于全球。但这在北美奏效了，我们立即发现未经授权的团体数量有所减少。</p><p>但随着时间的推移，就像规则一样，我们看到人们开始玩弄这些规则。他们会找一位年长的朋友为他们预订房间。他们不会预订一晚，而是预订三晚，依此类推。 [并且]对优秀用户的影响是如此之大，以至于我们说：“我们需要转向机器学习。我们需要变得更聪明。”因此，我们在澳大利亚进行了第一次试点，在那里我们对地方进行了细分，并比较了拥有我们建立的新派对模式的地方与其他地方。我们看到减少了吗？再说一次，这就像大海捞针一样，但我们仍然发现该地区采用派对模式的派对比不使用派对模式的派对少了 35%。当我们开始在北美进行实验时，我们确实发现它与启发式方法一样有效，但对优秀用户的影响较小。</p><p>这给了我们继续前进的信心，因为什么都不做不是一种选择。我们必须做点什么，而且必须聪明地去做。这是我们可以出去讨论的用例之一——并不是说我们正在阻止所有各方，但至少 Airbnb 对此采取了强硬立场。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>在您描述问题和解决方案时，我听到的一个共同点是需要不断适应和持续学习，并使用正确的工具来完成正确的工作。有时这是一个规则，然后可能是无监督学习，然后是人工干预。这听起来确实是一个跨学科的问题，包括规则改变的部分，或者欺诈者操作方式改变的部分，你还会有“是不是太生硬了？”的问题。它是否限制了一些无意识但良好或良性的行为？”在这些情况下，人机协作或交互如何进行？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong> Shervin，你总结得非常好，也就是说，这不是一件一劳永逸的事情。你构建它，然后你必须不断地学习和优化，甚至是你正在做出的决策，以及你周围的世界如何演变。这是人类真正擅长的领域，也就是说，你必须遵守使用最新数据、正确数据来训练你的模型的纪律，并就最佳阈值做出权衡决策。你会说，“好吧，这是有风险的，我们已经准备好冒这个风险了。”</p><p>在 Airbnb，我们一直致力于如何在循环中利用人类。除了产品和规划团队之外，我还有一个信托运营团队。该运营团队由全职员工以及全球代理组成。每当我们构建一个新模型时，一开始我们经常让模型做出基于风险阈值的决策：“这是前 1%。这是下一部分。这是下一部分。”有时，我们会将其发送给人类，然后在此基础上创建标签，表示“我同意模型的决定”或“我不同意模型的决定”，然后将其作为训练数据返回到模型。</p><p>然后，当我们对模型的决策能力更有信心时，我们就会转向自动决策。这个派对模式，就你的观点而言，现在完全是自动决定的。但最终发生的情况是，当我们收到用户的申诉，说“我被错误地阻止了”，那么该申诉就会作为客户告诉我们的数据。然后一名特工查看了该上诉并说：“实际上，这个决定是错误的。”如果代理做出了正确的决定，该客户提出了正确的上诉，并且没有发生任何事件，我们就知道这是误报。</p><p>但假设代理商批准了，然后该客户继续举办派对；那是假阴性。我们不断从中学习，但我们是迭代地进行的。首先，我们尝试将模型直接应用于人类。再说一遍，不能保证人类比模型更擅长决策，但我们会不断衡量其表现。然后我们会转向[更少]人类决策的高阶决策。有时我们也会……假设政党模式做出决定。人们继续他们的快乐方式，有保留。有时，在预订完成后，我们仍然会让人查看风险最高的 1% 预订，以尝试并纠正任何可能的情况。</p><p>因此，它要么试图平衡这一点，即人类什么时候是做出决定的合适人选？机器什么时候应该做出决定？我们经历了一段并不轻松、非线性的旅程。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您一开始提到您可能会审查更多案例，然后从这些案例中学习。但与此同时，人们……这 7000 万笔交易正在不断发生。例如，当您举例说明酒店在大流行开始时关闭时，这就是个别房东和顾客发生这种情况的时候。您如何平衡需要快速到位和需要完成流程之间的权衡？</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>这可能是最困难的事情，也是我整个职业生涯中处理过的最困难的事情。在此之前，我负责管理 Samsclub.com（沃尔玛的一部分）的所有产品，当时我认为我的工作很辛苦。当我们为客户提供服务、帮助他们结账时，我们仍然感觉自己处于增长的道路上，我们可以选择增长的速度或增长的速度。我总是有团队关注那些试图检查但无法检查的人，并在我们构建长期架构时为他们提供服务，但人们的生命并没有受到威胁; [这是]人们的钱——诈骗者利用偷来的信用卡骗取了公司数百万美元。</p><p>爱彼迎有一个团队正在努力保护好人，避免坏事。我们所做的是，你必须真正擅长确定优先级，这在信任和安全的世界中也很难做到。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>我的意思是，从很多方面来说，选择就是萨姆，你一开始就说过：这些经济体并非没有风险。它们不可能没有风险。总体而言，好处多于坏处，因此一切都取决于优先顺序。但我不得不说，我们已经与许多在其他组织中扮演类似角色的人进行了交谈——你提到了山姆会员店等——他们正在使用技术、数字人工智能/机器学习来驱动各种用例。我认为你的突出之处在于它是一个持续的平衡行为，而且风险很高。然后你就会有这样的目标和谦虚地说：“好吧，我们相信我们会犯错误，而且这个系统不可能没有错误。”</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>但随着时间的推移，情况正在变得更好。这引出了我的下一个问题：你如何衡量你的有效性？是指事件的数量、不良事件发生的严重程度和频率吗？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我很高兴你问这个问题，因为我很自然地会朝着这个方向发展，也就是说，在最高层面上，我们衡量自己的指标是每百万次旅行中的欺诈事件数、安全事件数每百万次出行，以及良好的用户影响。这是衡量“我们屏蔽了多少优质列表？”的平衡指标。我们阻止了多少好主人和好客人继续前进，无法真正理解我们的误报和漏报？”但归根结底，我们全面考虑的是美好的旅行。</p><p>我们还从可能发生的欺诈损失的角度来考虑美元。我们正在查看收到的客户支持票证、因遇到我们团队提出的摩擦而产生的用户 NPS [净推荐值]。因此，在基本层面上，我们正在研究这些指标。但在我的职业生涯中，我第一次遇到的挑战之一是——在欺诈领域，我们可以进行 A/B 测试——我们不断迭代我们的模型。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>当你这样做时，你也可能会阻止相当良性的行为和意图。但正如你所说，在某种程度上，人类的判断需要压倒一切，并说这对一个人来说风险可能太高了。是的，我的意思是，当谈到机器学习时，我们总是谈论探索和利用，以及持续的反馈循环，但是学习总是有成本的，对吧？但是当我向你发送营销信息时你可能不喜欢，学习成本非常小，所以我会给你发送很多这样的信息，并且我会做各种A/B/X测试。但是，当我对风险较高的群体或人群进行这种 A/B 测试时，您可能会做出不这样做并依赖回顾性数据的人类判断。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我认为您为我们很好地阐明了这一点。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的。我们问自己的一个问题是，是什么让一个人信任另一个人？是什么让人们信任 Airbnb？我们意识到，我们可以在后台[训练]各种模型，而你甚至不知道自己是否处于 1% 还是 2% 的风险阈值内，或者是否被标记为良好用户。</p><p>但爱彼迎与您（作为房客）或您（作为房东）或房东与房客之间也需要进行对话，以真正建立信任。就像当我们问某人“如果你 17 岁的女孩想在上大学之前背包旅行时，你愿意把她送到希腊的一个陌生人家里吗？”您可能会说这是个人经历。我有一个17岁的孩子，即将上大学。我意识到，第一个想法是“不——不会发生”，我在 Airbnb 负责信任和安全。但后来我想，“好吧，如果我能和主持人谈谈就好了；”如果她要和别人住在一起；如果那个人是像我这样的妈妈……”</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>作为 Airbnb，我们可以说，“我们在后台运行所有这些模型；别担心，你的女儿很安全”——我认为这不会成功。我认为作为父母，您会希望获得需要查看的信息，即使您的判断可能并不比机器更好。所以我们也在努力，我们需要说什么，我们需要做什么？有时，当我们说“Airbnb 不会允许在同一社区内最后一刻预订的一晚住宿”时，我认为这也会让很多家长感觉更好，那好吧，至少这一点选项消失了。他们可能会想出其他办法。这个信息不能令人费解。该消息必须很简单。必须清楚地理解该信息。除了询问人们不应该做什么之外，我们还需要鼓励人们应该做哪些良好行为，例如与主人交谈、与客人交谈、提出问题。</p><p>我们推出了一项针对单身女性旅行者的计划，因为我们开始发现单身女性旅行者在私人房间内发生的人身安全事故的发生率可能略高。我们开始鼓励[女性]弄清楚，你的房间里会有锁吗？那把锁还能用吗？您可以独自使用浴室吗？哪些空间是共享的？哪些不是？所以这不是一个阻止任何事情的模型。这只是我们以多种语言发布的一个教育模块，这对我们的独行旅行者来说非常有帮助。我团队的部分工作不仅是建立隐形防御，而且还通过教育和信息传递预先建立信任和信任感。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>说得很好。我不得不说，你提到你是五个孩子的母亲。我不得不说，我认为当你告诉你的孩子他们能做什么和不能做什么时，你的立场非常坚实，因为你有这么多的数据和丰富的经验，而当我说一些话时，他们就像，“嗯，你怎么知道？”你可以说：“好吧，相信我；我每年进行 7000 万笔交易，我知道发生了什么。”</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>并且不断成长。是的。顺便说一句，我很高兴与您的孩子交谈。任何时候。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，那就太好了。我会带你去解决这个问题。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>关于你的测量，我认为很有趣的一件事，也许回过头来谈一下。您也提到了一些积极的指标。所以我认为这有点诱人，我认为即使在这次谈话中我们也已经这样做了，我们是在向负面方向滴定。这就是新闻的普遍问题——坏消息可以提高报纸销量。嗯，我认为在这次谈话的过程中，我们已经转向了这一点。但我认为你提到的一些指标对他们来说有更积极的影响，不是吗？</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的，绝对如此。这是我们过去几年的顿悟，因为任何类型的机器学习模型在有大量数据可供学习时通常都会表现良好。在此类案例中，在 7000 万多次出行中，当其中的 0.1% 甚至导致了报告，而其中的一小部分导致了有人被驱逐的实际事件时，几乎没有什么可以解决的。因此，这些模型需要时间才能成熟。当然，随着技术的发展，情况会变得更好，但我们意识到我们拥有更多关于良好用户行为的数据。</p><p>我们有更多的用户实际进来，提前几个月预订住宿；他们可能会准时入住，让房源比他们发现时更好，与房东和房客沟通，留下诚实的评价。因此，如果我们真的能够翻转开关，虽然我们需要继续寻找异常现象、趋势和不良行为者，但如果我们能够真正善于了解什么是良好行为，同时确保我们也在衡量在我们如何收集和使用这些数据方面存在潜在的偏见或歧视以及隐私合规性，那么当某些事情看起来确实有风险时，这可以非常有效地通知我们。例如，如果一个帐户通常是从美国访问的，[并且]突然我们看到该 IP 现在正在从菲律宾访问，感觉就像“哦，这是一个帐户接管”。但如果这是一个经常环游世界的好用户，也许这不是一个帐户接管，并且良好的用户行为中有历史记录，可以让我们更聪明地了解“正常情况是什么样子，异常是什么样子的？”不是广泛的，而是非常具体的，基于用户细分。</p><p>所以这不是什么新鲜事，但我认为我们有时倾向于真正了解不良行为是什么样子并善于检测它，而不是补充异常行为与正常行为的样子。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。您在一个真正不断发展的领域拥有如此丰富的见解和信息。我的意思是，这不像典型的协同过滤情况，“像你这样的用户也买了这个”。我的意思是，在匹配方面还有很多事情要做。这一定是一个非常有趣且值得您关注的问题。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>是的。它要求我们摆脱信任和安全的束缚，与我们的搜索、相关性和个性化团队密切合作，因为我们的工作——与我以前在电子商务工作时的工作不同——不仅仅是进行协作过滤并说，“像你这样的人买了这个，所以你应该买这个，”或者，“你去了巴黎，所以也许接下来你想去罗马。”</p><p>这是关于……这次你和家人一起旅行。你有小孩；您可能需要日托服务，我们知道该房东提供日托服务，并且这个位置可能非常适合您。或者同一个客户可能独自旅行，也许我们需要提供不同的建议。将这些信任和安全信号嵌入到我们的搜索相关性算法中，可以非常有效地将正确的人与正确的列表相匹配。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Naba，你并不是从 Airbnb 开始的。告诉我们一些你是如何到达那里的。您提到了沃尔玛和那里的一些背景，但您是如何最终担任目前的职位的？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我是家里第一位女工程师。我父亲抓住了我的机会，对我说：“你很好奇。你是一个永远的学习者。你想做工程吗？”当时我不知道什么是工程学，但我还是报名了，并成为我家里第一位女工程师。</p><p>我曾在塔塔咨询服务公司工作，然后加入 Cognizant，通过 Cognizant 来到美国，并在 AAA 工作了一段时间。我会继续从事不同的项目和不同的工作，这将帮助我学习全新的东西。</p><p>沃尔玛发生在2006年左右。我被要求在沃尔玛从事供应链方面的工作，如果你想在一家公司学习供应链，那可能就是你应该去的公司。当我做供应链的时候，我每年都承担越来越大的责任和项目，直到我发现自己从沃尔玛领导几乎所有的供应链团队去山姆会员店，这是沃尔玛的一部分——领导所有的供应链团队。产品、前端、购物车、结帐、营销和定价，这是我以前从未做过的。但这让我有机会获得全面的经验，了解大型零售商的后端如何运作，以及前端客户体验如何运作。</p><p>山姆会员店结束后，我被要求领导搜索工作。就在那时，我开始对机器学习和人工智能运行的世界真正感兴趣，而搜索对我来说是一个很好的着陆点。有趣的是，我在麻省理工学院修了一门课程，学习人工智能和机器学习的应用，这给了我承担搜索工作的勇气。</p><p>从那时起，差不多 13 年后，Airbnb 在沃尔玛诞生了。我对旅游业和这个市场非常好奇，它与我在沃尔玛所做的任何事情都非常不同。所以这里的主题是，我总是倾向于一些能够帮助我利用我所拥有的技能的东西，然后利用我的好奇心和学习去做一些全新的事情，并在我前进的过程中增强自己。这就是我的背景。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Naba，我们现在有一个部分，我们会问您一系列快速问题，然后告诉我们您想到的第一件事。您最自豪的 AI/ML 时刻是什么？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>你要求我在不同的球队之间进行选择，这对我的职业生涯来说是限制。但我要说的是，我们在政党检测和政党风险降低方面所做的工作是开创性的，业内没有其他人像我们一样做到这一点，所以这对我来说是一个非常自豪的时刻。但我为我所有的团队感到自豪，郑重声明。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这是一个很好的答案。您对人工智能有何担忧？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>令我担心的是它的威力有多大。当 [OpenAI 首席执行官] Sam Altman 来到 Airbnb 时，我们有机会近距离亲眼见到他。这项技术的进步速度有多快，其能力有多大……我担心它会落入坏人之手。我担心，虽然我的团队拥有这项技术，但欺诈者也拥有这项技术，所以我担心，如果今天我们担心假身份证和假垃圾邮件发送给我们的主人和客人，那么这项技术有多先进我们将变得更加难以辨别好坏。我认为人工智能也将在检测假人工智能方面发挥作用。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>水彩画。我喜欢画自然。因此，纸张、水彩画，以及平静与安宁，没有科技，是我最喜欢做的事情。当然，拥抱我的孩子们，花时间和他们在一起，聆听他们的一天，努力让他们在跟我说话时不要玩手机。那两个。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>说得很好。你想要的第一个职业：你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>我想成为一名老师。我来自一个教师家庭，当我看到某人的眼睛因知识的恩赐而发光时，我感到非常高兴。我是一个永远的学习者。我所从事的每一份工作都与我之前的工作完全不同；这是因为我喜欢学习。所以，是的，这就是我想成为的人。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>无论如何，您可能在当前的职位上进行了大量的教学工作。</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>我做了很多指导工作。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您教会了我们很多东西。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>谢谢，谢谢。我确实做了很多指导，因为我觉得如果其他人可以看到我做我所做的事情，这会让他们觉得他们也能做到。所以如果我能做到这一点，那就是我一生的使命完成了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>未来您对人工智能最大的愿望是什么？</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee：</strong>实际上，我对世界最大的愿望就是不要那么害怕；给它一个机会。因为我认为有时我们对坏事的恐惧会阻碍我们拥抱美好。有太多浪费的精力投入到本应通过人工智能自动化的活动中——如此多的患者没有得到治疗；如此多的公司可能需要帮助并需要大量资金来支持人工智能可以完成的基本事情；可能有很多不发达的国家[但可以]获得如此多的优势。我知道，当它落入坏人之手时，它可能会被用来做坏事，但世界上好人多于坏人，我相信我们利用人工智能行善的力量——利用我们的集体善良。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我想每个人都可能会认同你的观点，即世界好于坏。我们确实倾向于听到大多数负面故事，但令人耳目一新的是，一是您付出了多少努力来尝试和防止这些故事，同时也听到了您的平台带来的好故事。感谢您今天抽出时间与我们交谈。我们很享受。</p><p><strong>纳巴·班纳吉：</strong>谢谢你，山姆。谢谢你，谢尔文。我的荣幸。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>感谢您的聆听。下次我们将邀请主创产品 Zan Gilani 加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>反对限制股票回购的理由</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Guest, S.P. Kothari, and Parth Venkat. <p>尼古拉斯·盖斯特 (Nicholas Guest) 是康奈尔大学约翰逊管理研究生院的会计学助理教授。 SP Kothari 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院会计与金融学 Gordon Y. Billard 教授，此前曾担任该学院副院长。帕斯·文卡特 (Parth Venkat) 是阿拉巴马大学卡尔弗豪斯商学院的金融学助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com Are stock buybacks as bad as they’re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Kothari-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡罗·詹巴雷西/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>股票回购真的像人们想象的那么糟糕吗？普遍存在的企业回购股票做法一直是许多政治和媒体关注的焦点。 2022 年联邦通胀削减法案包括对回购征收 1% 的消费税（拜登总统提议在 2024 年预算中将其提高至 4%）。此外，民主党高层表示有兴趣禁止高管在回购后三年内出售股票，联邦政府建议放弃回购的公司将获得优惠待遇，证券交易委员会提议大幅提高股票回购利率。回购报告的范围和频率。</p><p>迄今为止，关于股票回购的经济后果的争论往往集中在小样本或精心挑选的例子上。鉴于每年有数千家公司回购其股票，并且过去五年每年回购总额超过 5000 亿美元，我们认为有必要对回购行为进行大样本研究。我们的研究发表在<cite>《财务管理》</cite>杂志上，概述了这种做法的好处，正如其支持者所说，并提供了证据，对其批评者所称的成本提出质疑。</p><p></p><p>回购批评者通常会提出三个反对这种做法的论点。首先，他们声称股票回购使公司能够通过增加对股票的需求（从而提高股票价格）或通过夸大每股收益（EPS）来欺骗天真的投资者来操纵市场。其次，他们声称股票回购使内部人员能够通过补偿合同或以高价出售股票而受益。最后，批评者指责股票回购挤出了投资，从而牺牲了创新和长期经济增长。</p><p>与此同时，那些支持或参与股票回购的人为这种做法提供了一些理由。首先，向股东支付的股息通过减少自由现金流的潜在滥用来协调经理和股东的激励。其次，使用回购代替股息或在股息之外使用回购可以使公司在返还给股东的现金金额方面具有灵活性，能够将回购的股票奖励给员工作为股权补偿，为股东提供适度的税收优惠（自2003年股息税削减以来不太明显） ），以及向市场传达公司良好前景的能力。最后，股票回购代表自愿参与者之间按照当前市场价格进行的公开且受监管的公平交易。</p><p>鉴于监管股票回购的动力，我们希望在公共数据中可以观察到其缺点的证据。为了测试这一点，我们记录了回购趋势，并比较了回购和不回购股票的公司的交易量、股价表现、首席执行官薪酬以及公司财务活动（通过投资和盈利能力证明）。我们以两种方式对回购股票的企业进行了细分：（1）小额正回购与大额正回购（定义为低于中值与高于中值），以及（2）频繁回购者与不频繁回购者（定义为在一两个季度内回购的公司）而不是一年中的三到四个季度）。</p><p>我们对过去三十年数千家美国交易所上市公司的大样本证据表明，回购在美国是一种主流的企业金融活动，每年为股东返还数千亿美元的资本。从总体来看，我们发现这种活动既不会创造也不会破坏太多财富（也就是说，它不会导致股价发生重大变化）。此外，虽然回购与过去较高的盈利能力有关，但与首席执行官薪酬过高或投资不足无关。</p><p>随着时间的推移，回购活动总量的趋势表明，虽然回购价值迅速增长，但增长的大部分可归因于通货膨胀和市值的增加。此外，回购规模目前与股息相似，并且在相当长的一段时间内没有比股息增长得更快。然而，与股息不同，回购在公司面临压力时会急剧（且暂时）下降，这表明回购实际上为公司提供了上述支付灵活性的好处。</p><p></p><h3>仔细看看数据</h3><p>通过我们的分析，我们能够系统地解决针对股票回购的每一项批评。</p><p>首先，公司是否利用股票回购来操纵市场，通过创造过剩需求来推高股价？如果这样做，回购股票的公司的交易量应该比不回购股票的公司更高。但所有上市公司的平均交易量基本上保持相似，无论它们是否回购股票或回购股票的频率如何。事实上，近年来，不回购股票的公司的交易量大大超过了回购公司的交易量，这表明回购带来的超额交易量与其他力量相比相形见绌。</p><p>如果天真的投资者因为每股收益通胀而被诱骗购买进行回购行为的公司的股票，我们应该观察到短期价格上涨，随后长期业绩不佳。然而，无论公司是否回购股票、回购股票的强度和频率如何，我们都没有发现任何证据表明公司在回购股票的季度中表现明显优于大盘。虽然我们确实发现了一些边际证据表明，大量回购的公司在回购后的季度中表现略好，但我们没有发现未来短期或长期逆转的证据。这种表现优异的模式更符合公司利用回购来发出低估信号的情况——这对投资者有利——而不是操纵市场。</p><p></p><p>第二个批评是回购让内部人士获得不公平的利润。如果股票回购作为内部人员的寻租行为是一种普遍的、系统性的滥用行为，那么回购股票的公司的首席执行官将获得异常高的薪酬，包括工资、奖金和股权奖励的价值。使用模型生成的超额薪酬衡量标准（已在早期学术文献中经过审查），我们估计进行大量正回购的公司首席执行官的收入仅比不回购股票的公司首席执行官的收入高出 51,000 美元——从统计角度和经济角度来看，这一数字微不足道。超额工资。当我们将经常回购的公司的首席执行官与不回购的公司的首席执行官进行比较时，差异甚至更小——4,000 美元。与 CEO 数百万美元的平均薪酬相比，这些差异在经济上微不足道。令人惊讶的是，不频繁回购或回购小额正数的公司首席执行官获得的超额薪酬最少，甚至低于不回购公司的首席执行官。所有这些证据都表明公司利用回购来提高首席执行官的薪酬。</p><p>第三个也是最后一个批评是，回购降低了公司利用投资机会的能力，从而牺牲了创新和经济增长。我们发现，不回购股票的公司投资更多，但利润却明显低于回购股票的公司。频繁、大量回购的公司利润丰厚，过去一直稳定投资，并且继续进行大量投资，同时向股东返还资本。这表明盈利的公司在保持稳定的投资水平的同时回购股票，而盈利较低或亏损的公司不会（或可能无法）回购股票，而是更加密集地投资以期实现盈利。虽然可能存在一些管理不善的公司选择避免有利可图的投资，而是将资本返还给愿意的股东的孤立例子，但很难看出鼓励或激励这些经营不善的公司保留现金的指令会如何引导他们做出良好的投资。</p><p>可能受到回购规定影响的潜在利益相关者包括经理、其他员工、股东、政府和整个社会。如果公司盈利，首席执行官可以以回购或股息的形式向股东支付多余的现金，将资金保留在资产负债表上，或投资新项目。对股票回购征收少量税可能不会显着改变企业行为，并可能为政府增加少量收入。但如果税率增长得足够高，公司将选择不回购股票，而是仅通过股息支付或保留现金。在这种情况下，政府不会增加任何收入，但会实施事实上的股票回购禁令。</p><h3>回购禁令如何会适得其反</h3><p>如果公司改为只支付股息，股东将失去选择是否接受现金支付的能力，并可能面临负税收后果，因为股息作为收入征税，而资本利得通常按较低税率征税。并且只有当收益实现时。此外，该公司在困难时期将失去重要的灵活性，因为削减股息比削减回购受到的市场惩罚更大。</p><p></p><p>然而，限制股票回购的举措似乎并不是为了激励公司转向通过股息偿还股东，而是为了增加对业务的投资。有证据表明，保留现金与首席执行官做出破坏价值的决策有关，例如寻求建立帝国的合并、累积个人开支或资助宠物项目。对股票回购的限制会促使治理不善的公司的首席执行官投资于他们本来不会资助的增值项目，这似乎难以置信。</p><p></p><p>从员工的角度来看，有一些证据表明，如果雇主拥有多余的现金，工会能够更成功地进行谈判，但也有大量证据表明，限制公司筹集和分配资本的灵活性对员工不利，尤其是在经济低迷时期。建立帝国的合并也可能对员工不利，因为并购常常导致收购目标的员工被解雇以及收购公司的员工被错误分配。此外，一些回购的股票被重新发行给员工，使得任何对股东不利的行为也对持股员工不利。</p><p>总体而言，我们的结果显示，股票回购与价格操纵、回报逆转、首席执行官薪酬过高和投资不足之间不存在相关性，这使得股票回购在经济上产生重大因果影响仍然是数据背后的基础是非常难以置信的。如果公司只能依赖股息，那么它们就会失去灵活性，而且有证据表明，管理不善的首席执行官保留了现金，经常将其花在破坏价值的合并、支出或宠物项目上。旨在减少回购的政策也将减少被指控但未被观察到的不当行为，而不会给美国上市公司和其他利益相关者带来成本，这是难以置信的。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>您准备好应对下一次供应中断了吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:46:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Johnny Rungtusanatham, David A. Johnston, and Elizabeth Heichler . <p>M. Johnny Rungtusanatham 是约克大学舒立克商学院运营管理和信息系统教授以及加拿大供应链管理（一级）研究主席。 David A. Johnston 是舒立克商学院运营管理和信息系统教授，也是乔治韦斯顿有限公司可持续供应链中心的研究主席和主任。伊丽莎白·海克勒 (Elizabeth Heichler) 是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>杂志的编辑总监。她主持了会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Capabilities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &#8220;Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Nov. 7, 2022. Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &#8220;black swan&#8221; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently. M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0">相关阅读</h5><p>J. Rungtusanatham 和 D. Johnston，“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">为下一次供应中断做好准备”</a> ，《<em>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</em> ，2022 年 11 月 7 日。</p></aside><p> COVID-19 大流行引发的供应中断让许多公司措手不及。为了应对供应链未来的“黑天鹅”威胁，管理者必须以不同的方式思考。</p><p> M. Johnny Rungtusanatham 和 David A. Johnston 研究了供应中断的触发因素和绩效后果。他们的 ADDAPT 框架可以帮助领导者更好地管理中断并维持产品流程。</p><p>在本次网络研讨会中，您将了解到：</p><ul><li>为什么传统的风险管理可能不足以为下一次灾难性的供应中断做好准备。</li><li>为什么您需要开发六种功能（预测、检测、诊断、激活、保护和跟踪）来为供应中断做好准备和管理。</li><li>您需要对业务战略、实践、流程和系统做出哪些改变才能提高供应链的弹性。</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>灵活有效：混合工作场所的领导策略</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Elliott. <p>Brian Elliott 是未来论坛的执行领导者和联合创始人，这是一个研究驱动的联盟，帮助全球的高级管理人员重新构想如何将人员、流程和工具结合在一起，通过数据和对话改善工作。未来论坛是 Slack、BCG、明天管理领导力和 MillerKnoll 之间的合作伙伴关系。他是<cite>《未来如何运作：带领灵活的团队完成一生中最好的工作》</cite> （Wiley，2022 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Many leaders don’t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it’s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA02_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>许多领导者不知道如何根据结果来管理工作，而不是众所周知的“座位上的流浪者”——跟踪谁在办公室以及在办公室呆了多长时间。但在混合工作场所中，有可能拥有高绩效、健康的工作场所文化，并且人们可以灵活地工作时间和地点。只是需要以不同的方式进行管理。</p><p>这是未来论坛的 Brian Elliott 传达的信息，他在 2023 年 5 月举办的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间与乔治华盛顿大学商学院的 N. Sharon Hill 和 Atlassian 的 Julie Dervin 一起在小组中发表了演讲。</p><p>埃利奥特表示，在他的公司调查的 10,243 名知识工作者中，93% 的人表示他们希望工作时间具有灵活性。他说，那些有选择的人的<a href="https://futureforum.com/research/future-forum-pulse-winter-2022-2023-snapshot/">生产力得分比没有选择的人高出 39%</a> 。那些对工作<em>地点</em>有一定灵活性的人得分也更高（8%）。</p><p></p><p>要在员工对灵活性的渴望和组织的战略目标之间找到平衡，需要重新检查需要亲自完成的工作类型。它还可能需要同一组织内不同群体的不同工作配置，并且肯定需要不同的方法来衡量员工完成的工作。</p><p>与会者向演讲者提出的问题多于时间，埃利奥特同意在活动结束后回答一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>您如何衡量生产力？大多数员工表示，他们按照自己的时间表在家工作效率更高，但事实真是这样吗？</h6><p>这是一种异端观点：我们需要停止尝试衡量知识工作的生产力，而将所有时间和精力集中在衡量结果上。</p><p>生产力指标采用输出（发送的电子邮件、关闭的案例）并将其除以输入（活跃时间），然后根据质量调整更好的结果（重新打开的案例）。这在某种程度上可以适用于死记硬背的日常任务，随着时间的推移，这些任务会变得自动化。而且，这些指标可以被利用，人们也会利用它们——甚至包括购买<a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07VHBQQVG">鼠标摇动器</a>。正如 Atlassian 的 Dominic Price<a href="https://www.atlassian.com/blog/productivity/the-problem-with-productivity-metrics">所写</a>，“生产力一直是衡量机器和资本影响的好方法。这从来都不是衡量<em>人类</em>影响的好方法。”</p><p>在未来论坛上，我们已经涉足这一领域；我们比较了具有灵活性和不具有灵活性的人群，发现具有位置灵活性的人群的生产力得分更高，而具有日程灵活性的人群则具有更大的优势。斯坦福大学的<a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">尼克·布鲁姆（Nick Bloom）</a> 、哈佛商学院的拉杰·<a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">乔杜里（Raj Choudhury</a> ）和其他人的学术研究也表明了同样的情况。</p><p>但这是一个奇怪的问题，因为当人们在办公室时我们没有问这个问题。我们只是假设，因为人们在场，所以他们正在做一些富有成效的事情。我们都知道这不准确。</p><p>相反，让我们跳过整个混乱的过程，花时间弄清楚我们组织的目标和关键结果 (OKR)，并以一种可以按业务部门和职能向下级联到团队级别的方式来实现。从团队层面来看，很多事情都可以延伸到个人层面，以发现个人在他们所做的事情以及他们作为队友的表现方面的影响。</p><p>评估人们对团队目标的影响比较困难，但比安装更多衡量他们的投入和产出的生产力指标会让我们走得更远。</p><h6>随机碰撞似乎是推动创新的关键。在跨团队建立联系方面，您如何促进偶然性？</h6><p>联系是员工敬业度和保留率的重要组成部分，但与创新的联系充其量是虚假的。<a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4093796">多项研究</a><a href="https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=991">表明</a>，真正促成创新的是心理安全。</p><p>在我们于 2021 年进行的研究中，未来论坛发现位置（无论是完全现场、混合还是完全远程）与团队创新几乎没有相关性。相反，重要<em>的</em>是人们是否觉得自己可以提出问题以及团队是否愿意承担风险等因素——也就是说，他们是否感到心理安全。</p><p>建立联系很重要，但我们应该在组织中有意识地这样做，而不是依靠随机机会。您可以通过以下三种方式执行此操作：</p><p> <strong>1. 有意的跨团队联系。</strong>诸如开放式午餐会之类的计划，由内部专家轮流出席或主持“有问题的会议”，将其他职能部门的领导带入您的季度计划周期，并在 Slack 或 Teams 中创建公共渠道，以便根据主题分享见解（如人工智能）可以走很长的路。</p><p> <strong>2. 利用工具建立联系。</strong> Donut（一款适用于 Slack 或 Teams 的应用程序，以编程方式将团队中的个人配对）等产品有助于确保每个人都能保持联系，而不仅仅是那些在同一楼层或同一栋大楼工作的人。</p><p> <strong>3、帮助新员工建立人际网络。</strong>过去几年的一大挑战是，太多公司在雇用人员时没有重新考虑如何建立联系并了解文化。我最喜欢的建议之一来自欧洲的简柏特公司，那里的新员工会被安排在团队之外与六个人会面，无论是面对面还是在虚拟咖啡会上，每个人都应该再提供两到三个联系人。</p><p>投资新工具和流程也可以带来巨大的推动作用。在头脑风暴会议之前，像<a href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/12/using-brainwriting-for-rapid-idea-generation/">头脑风暴</a>一样思考流程：让人们有低头的空间思考一些研究结果或问题，提前写出自己的想法，然后与小组分享，同时带来更多新想法。它还降低了群体思维的可能性。</p><p></p><h6>您如何以一种鼓舞人心和包容性的方式传达这样一种期望，即人们应该每周去办公室一两天，而不是强行和独裁？</h6><p>过去两年，很多公司声称每周需要 3 天亲自办公，而实际情况是平均每周 1.5 天。这掩盖了这样一个事实：通常有一批初级员工每周来两到三天，而更多高级员工来的次数较少。</p><p>重复这一政策是行不通的，威胁要解雇那些不经常来的人也是不现实的，而且会滋生怨恨。领导层知道，一些经验更丰富、更关键的人才的加入频率较低。初级员工也知道这一点。</p><p>相反，我们所看到的工作重点是通过团队级别的协议帮助团队找出自己的节奏。例如，销售团队和工程团队的需求是不同的。销售团队最终可能会规定每周有两天是默认在办公室工作的日子，并将这些日子与更多“抬头”而不是低头的特定活动叠加在一起，例如培训课程、指导时间和一-上一个。另一方面，工程团队最终可能会在每个月中抽出一周的时间亲自进行规划、共进午餐和演示日。</p><p>鼓励高级员工每周至少有一天来参加指导课程、参加培训以及与初级员工一起喝咖啡，这比简单地告诉他们出现要更进一步。</p><p>另一个关键因素是，去办公室工作不会一直比在家工作更糟糕。人们并不总是想要免费的午餐，他们想要一个团队会议的场所，能够找到一个安静的地方来接客户电话，以及有效的 Wi-Fi。对于很多公司来说，这需要重新设计工作空间。</p><h6>管理者应该怎样做才能避免弹性工作制延续甚至夸大工作场所中现有的偏见？ “眼不见心不烦”是一个真正令人担忧的问题。</h6><p>邻近偏见和出勤主义可能带来更好的机会和回报，这是一个真正的风险。我们需要创造一个公平的竞争环境，首先要培训经理和领导者根据他们产生的结果而不是投入（办公室时间、响应速度、始终在线）来评估团队和个人的绩效。领导者及其员工合作伙伴不仅需要关注晋升和奖励周期，还需要关注他们的人才发展渠道以及谁正在获得新的、闪亮的项目。</p><p>我们与 Slack 执行团队合作，制定了一项规则，即所有高级管理人员的定期审核（例如 CMO 对新项目提案的每周审核）都完全以虚拟方式完成。这不仅有助于解决人们听不到房间另一端的谈话的常见挑战，还有助于缓解“在会议发生的房间”参加这些会议的压力，而初级员工可能每年只参加一两次。</p><h6>科技以外的许多公司和行业都存在知识型员工和需要亲自到场工作的员工（例如零售业和制造业）之间的分歧。您如何建议灵活定位，以免造成不公平的双重标准？</h6><p>办公桌（办公室）员工和无办公桌（或一线）员工之间的差异远远超出了远程工作的能力：它们包括工资、福利、设施、培训等。</p><p>无办公桌员工的人才短缺对许多公司来说是一个巨大的挑战。但我不认为答案是强迫办公桌员工回到办公室全职工作。这并不能真正解决无办公桌员工的任何问题。</p><p>这里的答案是投资于无办公桌员工的特定需求。根据<a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2022/why-deskless-workers-are-leaving-and-how-to-win-them-back">波士顿咨询集团的研究</a>，日程灵活性和选择是留住人才的首要因素。领导者正在投资一些项目，例如轮班能力以及为呼叫中心工作人员提供多种类型的日程安排。 Neiman Marcus Group 通过为销售人员提供灵活的商店和部门以及工作时间选择，将营业额减少了 20%。</p><h6>我在一家初创公司。在一家新兴公司中，随着公司的成长，管理层会非常关注工作文化。初创公司或任何企业如何在允许远程或混合模式的同时建立文化？</h6><p>我坚信文化的建立与你身在何处、墙上的标语或欢乐时光的质量无关。文化是根据员工的日常经历和你所做的决定而建立的：你作为公司的优先事项、你如何对待你的客户和员工、你资源的项目以及你奖励的对象。</p><p></p><p>也就是说，我见过一些确实有助于建立坚实基础的实践。以下是其中三个：</p><p></p><p>首先，数字优先并不意味着“永不面对面”。让人们聚集在一起，即使分布广泛，也是建设文化的重要组成部分。对于团队来说，我建议至少每季度花几天时间主要关注团队建设、社交和联系。随着初创公司的发展，这通常从每个人每季度一次变成团队每季度一次，最后每个人每年一次。</p><p>其次，弄清楚你们如何一起工作，并分享更多关于自己的信息。您的<a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/06/23/team-level-agreements/">团队级别协议</a>不应只关注人们在一起的频率，还应该涉及您的沟通方式、决策方式等。共享<a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/07/15/personal-user-manual/">个人用户手册</a>等工具也可以对建立信任文化大有帮助。</p><p>第三，在工作中创造透明度。推动文化的关键因素之一是领导力沟通，随着公司规模的扩大，在设置护栏的同时保持透明度非常重要。哪些主题对您的公司和使命最重要？我们如何彼此互动？将内部沟通从首席执行官“问我任何问题”会议扩展到知识共享的公共论坛需要时间和精力； <a href="https://slack.com/blog/transformation/a-modern-leaders-guide-to-organizational-transparency">其他人的指导</a>会有帮助。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and- effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>当不确定性很高时如何支持您的团队</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Liz Fosslien. <p>Liz Fosslien ( <a href="https://twitter.com/fosslien">@fosslien</a> ) 是工作情绪方面的专家，也是<cite>《华尔街日报》</cite>畅销书<cite>《No Hard Feelings: The Secret Power of Embracing Emotion at Work》</cite> （作品集，2019 年）和<cite>《Big Feelings: How to Be OK When》</cite>的合著者和插画家。<cite>事情不太好</cite>（作品集，2022）。她还是 Atlassian Team Anywhere 的领导团队成员，此前曾担任 Humu 的内容和传播主管。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[“My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don’t really know what’s going to happen in six months either. What can I do?” If you’ve found [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fosslien-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> “我的团队看起来真的很焦虑，”一位经理最近告诉我。 “我们刚刚经历了一次重组，对未来有很多担忧。我想给每个人某种保证，但我也不知道六个月后会发生什么。我能做些什么？”</p><p>如果您最近发现自己遇到类似的情况，那么您并不孤单。过去一年里我见过的几乎每一位人民领袖都问过我这个问题的某个版本。在最近的一项研究中，89% 的人力资源领导者表示，他们的团队表达了对<a href="https://www.humu.com/blog/the-toll-of-workplace-anxiety-and-what-to-do-about-it">工作保障、领导层变动或重组的</a>担忧。</p><p>当不确定性很高时，管理者应该致力于使工作成为一个稳定的场所，而不是另一个压力来源。 “最高效的管理者会清楚地表达出他们关心团队中的成员，”Atlassian Team Anywhere 实践主管 Molly Sands 解释道。 “研究表明，表现最好的团队的管理者一贯采取的不同做法是让他们的报告<a href="https://assets-global.website-files.com/601872ae12d42e2264ff9ac4/62d6d89b1037a1bb82393638_Infographic _ Actions that drive great management.pdf">感到有价值和舒适</a>。”</p><p></p><p>当许多重大决策以及更广泛的经济状况超出您的控制范围时，您如何提供保证？这看起来几乎不可能，但事实并非如此。管理者可以通过以下七种方式在动荡时期为团队提供支持，而不必做出无法兑现的承诺。</p><p><strong>帮助每位员工朝着梦想的工作努力。</strong>你不能总是保证某人升职（或者不幸的是，甚至不能保证工作稳定），但你可以承诺为你的员工提供各种有价值的学习机会，无论接下来发生什么，这些机会都会对他们有所帮助。</p><p>为了展示您的团队成员愿意承担的经历或项目，请他们向您展示一份他们很高兴在三到五年内担任的职位的招聘启事。一起浏览列出的职责，并指出他们认为自己缺乏技能或引人注目的经验的任何职责。然后致力于通过为他们提供相关任务或项目来帮助他们在这些领域成长。</p><p>养成职业聊天的习惯也很有用。每六周，为每份报告安排 30 分钟的时间来提出以下问题：</p><ul><li>您最喜欢什么类型的项目或任务？</li><li>您认为当前职责的哪些部分让您充满活力？</li><li>您觉得自己在角色中不断学习和成长吗？</li><li>您希望在未来发展哪些技能？</li></ul><p>重点是根据这些对话为他们创造或提供相关机会。</p><p><strong>与您的团队共同制定中期任务。</strong>当面临不确定性或频繁改变优先事项时，我们常常会感到陷入困境，或者觉得我们付出的所有努力都没有什么成果。这种无助感可能会导致冷漠和脱离。事实上，我在 Humu 的团队二月份针对持续不确定性的影响进行的研究表明，大约 40% 的<a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/web-assets-humu/eBooks/FY24 Q1 eBook - Uncertainty/eBook_Uncertainty_01.pdf">员工感觉自己的雄心壮志</a>不如一年前。</p><p>为了让您的团队成员重新焕发活力，请将他们聚集在一起，确定并努力实现共同的三个月目标。展望未来三个月可以为您的员工带来长期的稳定感，但这段时间足够短，即使您周围的情况发生变化，您也可能不必改变您的使命。例如，营销团队的目标可能是在下个季度将网站流量增加 25%，或者就如何更快地共享信息和做出决策进行实验。正如 Creativity Partners 创始人杰米·伍尔夫 (Jamie Woolf) 和海蒂·罗森菲尔德 (Heidi Rosenfelder) 建议的那样，“为了更好地让您的团队参与未来的共同创造，请尝试提出诸如‘哪些新的利润来源可以取代日益减少的利润来源？’之类的问题。”或者‘我们能做些什么来打破团队内部的隔阂？’”</p><p></p><p><strong>帮助您的团队在两周内取得胜利。</strong>通过将团队成员的注意力集中在他们<em>可以</em>控制的事情上，并为他们每个人分配一个可以在一周或两周内完成的特定任务，可以快速增强团队成员的进步感。首先将您的中期使命或长期目标划分为小里程碑，并跟踪和庆祝每个目标的实现。</p><p>工程经理莎拉最近将一项雄心勃勃的产品发布分解为一系列特定功能和更新，然后从列表中为她的报告分配单独的任务。她还在每周结束时安排了 15 分钟的团队签到，以庆祝他们所取得的成就，并跟踪团队在实现共同目标方面的集体进展。</p><p><strong>尽可能地保持清晰。</strong>在困难的情况下进行深思熟虑的解释对于赢得信任和减少焦虑至关重要。下次您要分享最新消息时，请准备好讲述如何做出决定的故事，并思考可能出现的任何疑虑或问题。计划好如何应对每一个问题。如果您不确定该说什么，请向其他领导或人力资源部寻求建议。当您与团队成员分享决定时，鼓励他们提出澄清问题。</p><p>对于管理者来说，表达自己的情绪也很重要，同时避免在团队面前情绪化地处理新闻。 “你应该说，‘我对本季度的结果感到失望’，而不是‘我对结果感到非常失望。我很害怕我们都会失业。我不知道该怎么办，”桑兹建议道。 “透明度并不意味着你必须分享你的感受或担忧的一切。”</p><p></p><p>您还可以通过与您的团队讨论最近影响他们的决定（例如新产品路线图或费用政策的变化）来进行清晰度审核。在下一系列的一对一会议中，提出以下问题：</p><ul><li>您是如何以及何时得知这个决定的？</li><li>有什么不清楚的吗？</li><li>下次与团队沟通变更时，我可以采取哪些不同的做法？</li></ul><p>这些对话可以帮助您确定如何提高透明度，并让员工清楚您正在尽力让他们了解最新情况。</p><p><strong>当您无法清晰地表达时，请提供上下文。</strong>经理们往往保持沉默，直到他们能够做出具体的决定。但缺乏沟通仍然是沟通的一种形式——它通常会滋生不信任和流言蜚语。</p><p></p><p>为了避免误解，请解释为什么您无法提供更多详细信息，并提供您希望获得更多信息的时间表。例如，您可能会这样说：“我还没有收到关于销售宣传将做出哪些改变的回复。我希望在一周左右的时间内能与大家分享更多信息，但我希望尽可能透明地了解我们目前的情况。”</p><p><strong>鼓励您的团队从福利中受益。</strong>研究表明，高达 80% 的员工对其公司提供的<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbeshumanresourcescouncil/2019/07/02/only-half-of-employees-understand-their-benefits-heres-what-hr-leaders-can-do-about-it/?sh=a4a1a578133c">福利感到困惑</a>。当预算缩减时，设计和资助支持团队的新方法可能是一场艰苦的战斗。您可能会惊讶地发现，仅仅通过让员工意识到已经存在的事情就可以极大地提高士气。例如，尽管我的前雇主为休完产假返回的女性提供了在回来的第一个月兼职工作的选择，但许多准妈妈并不知道这项政策。时任 Humu 产品负责人的 Sands 在公司范围内的 Slack 频道上标记了这一选项后，几位女性（包括我）利用了它并对这项政策表示感谢。</p><p>查看公司手册，或安排与人力资源部门的快速会议以复习知识。在即将召开的团队会议中，简要概述您的组织的优势，并鼓励您的团队成员充分利用它们。您可能想特别强调心理健康福利、假期政策或灵活的工作选择。首先可以这样说：“我知道这是一段压力很大、不确定性很高的时期，所以我想重点介绍一下我们公司提供的一些计划和福利，这些计划和福利可能会帮助您感觉更好。”</p><p><strong>帮助您的团队说不。</strong>通过介入保护团队的时间来维护他们的心理健康。设定明确合理的期望，并在报告拒绝非紧急请求时支持您的报告。</p><p></p><p>您还可以寻找方法来更清楚地了解他们被要求做的所有事情，并旨在建立友好的障碍。例如，当我得知我的团队因销售请求而不堪重负时，我创建了一个简短的表格，并建议我的报告指导所有请求者完成该表格，以便开始该流程。这具有三个功能：（1）它使我能够更好地了解我的团队正在做什么，（2）我可以帮助我的报告确定优先顺序或根据需要拒绝，（3）它减少了请求的数量，因为很少有请求人们实际上填写了表格。</p><p></p><p>不确定性会滋生焦虑，尽管管理者无法打响指，神奇地让一切完美到位，但他们可以采取措施帮助团队感到更有权力、得到支持并能够取得成功。为团队成员提供对个人有意义的成长机会并帮助他们快速获胜可以恢复他们的控制感和动力。围绕变更和更新创造透明度——或者解释为什么尚未宣布决定——可以恢复员工的信任。帮助人们投资于自己的福祉并设定健康的界限可以让他们更轻松地度过工作场所的风暴。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>利用人工智能提高关键绩效指标</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Schrage, David Kiron, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>迈克尔·施拉格 (Michael Schrage)</strong>是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院数字经济倡议的研究员。他的研究、写作和咨询工作重点关注数字媒体、模型和指标的行为经济学，作为管理创新机会和风险的战略资源。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>David Kiron</strong>是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>研究部编辑主任，也是其<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">“大创意”研究计划的</a>项目负责人。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong>是波士顿咨询集团的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 亨德森研究所的全球总监，他的研究重点是技术对商业和社会的影响。您可以通过<a href="mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong>是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 北美人工智能业务的联席领导者。他是 BCG X 的领导者，在推动人工智能和数字化业务影响方面拥有 20 多年的经验。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong>是 BCG 合伙人兼副总监，专注于将人工智能和机器学习应用于商业职能中的业务问题，包括优化定价、促销、销售和营销。您可以通过<a href="mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics and Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Prediction Tools]]></category><category><![CDATA[Smart Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In the spring of 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_1290x860-scaled.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>关于研究</h4><p>本系列文章介绍了<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团第七次年度人工智能和商业战略全球研究的结果。 2023 年春季，我们开展了一项全球调查，随后分析了来自 25 个行业和 100 个国家/地区的 3,043 名受访者的记录。我们还采访了 17 名在金融服务、媒体和娱乐、零售、旅游和运输以及生命科学等众多公司和行业领导人工智能计划的高管。</p><p>我们的研究探讨了管理者和领导者如何使用人工智能来增强战略衡量，以推进战略成果。它探讨了组织如何利用人工智能调整甚至生成新的 KPI 来定义和提供可衡量的更好绩效。</p></aside><p>提高关键绩效指标是大多数组织的明确任务。根据我们第七次年度<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">全球高管人工智能调查</a>，十分之七的受访者认为，提高 KPI（而不仅仅是提高绩效）对于他们的业务成功至关重要。正如一位高管指出的那样，“我们需要不断改进我们的 KPI，这样我们就不会根据遗留指标来运营我们的业务。”</p><p>现在，越来越多的公司以各种方式使用人工智能来加速这一演变。数字营销机构 Croud 首席战略官、前高管阿维纳什·考希克 (Avinash Kaushik) 表示：“机器学习可以帮助我们的高级领导者从回顾过去的指标转向展望未来的指标，对此我感到非常兴奋。”谷歌全球战略分析总监。</p><p></p><p>早期，Lyft 的工程师设计了一种算法，通过匹配司机供应和客户需求来最大化收入。 “它研究了乘客和司机的所有可能组合，并根据所请求的乘车、司机所在的位置以及所有系统动态，选择了能够最大化收入的组合，”前副总裁伊丽莎白·斯通 (Elizabeth Stone) 说道。 Lyft 的科学。然后，当数据科学家开始测试其他目标时，一些有趣的事情出现了。一种人工智能解决方案发现，优化转化率（用户打开应用程序后订购乘车的频率）反过来会在未来提供更多乘车请求。更多的乘车请求最终意味着更多的收入。由于使用人工智能，Lyft 将其收入 KPI 从专注于乘车和司机组合转变为也专注于优化转化率。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>在印度尼西亚最大的市场之一 Tokopedia（GoTo Group 的一部分），人工智能会筛选 PB 级的数据，以检测与可信度和可靠性相关的信号。鉴于其 1400 万商家（销售 18 亿种产品）中 86.5% 是新企业家，这些都是关键考虑因素。拥有更可信的商家可以使市场更具吸引力、更有效、更高效。 “他们可能有好的产品可以销售，但他们不知道如何管理库存，”Tokopedia 的首席技术官 Herman Widjaja 说。 “通过人工智能，我们将客户与他们想要的<em>正确商家</em>提供的正确产品联系起来。”该公司将数百万个可能的信号合成到一个评分系统中，该系统代表了围绕商家质量的新 KPI。</p><p>虽然大多数受访者了解增强 KPI 的必要性，但显然大多数受访者目前依赖不充分的工具和技术来管理其指标。即使机器学习算法和生成式人工智能改变了企业能力，人类判断仍然是提高 KPI 的压倒性主导方法。三分之二的受访者确认，管理者在调整组织的 KPI 时会做出判断。虽然这种方法很常见，但往往无法产生预期的结果：仅依靠人类判断的调查受访者中只有不到三分之一看到他们的 KPI 有所改善。</p><p></p><p>相比之下，使用人工智能来告知 KPI 的公司更有可能看到改进的指标。 90% 使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的受访者表示，他们看到自己的 KPI 有所改善。这些基于人工智能的 KPI 提供了业务优势并展示了新的功能：它们通常会带来更高的效率和更大的财务收益，并且更详细、对时间敏感并且与组织目标保持一致。 （请参阅“利用人工智能创建新的 KPI”。）我们观察到，高管们越来越意识到 KPI 需要变得更智能、更具预测性。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>利用 AI 创建新的 KPI</h4><p class="caption">在接受调查的 34% 的使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的组织中，90% 的组织看到了改进。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig1-final.png" alt="利用 AI 创建新的 KPI" /><br /></article></aside></div><p>我们在研究中采访的所有领导者都表达了增强 KPI 的类似理由。随着遗留指标变得静态和过时，它们作为定义和实现组织目标的工具的价值就会减弱。事实上，它们的用处明显降低了。无论是单独的还是集体的，KPI 都需要更新和增强，以确保它们能够推进期望的组织成果。在不提高 KPI 的情况下提高绩效会产生竞争风险。专注于或围绕次优措施进行调整的公司处于竞争劣势。只关注绩效而不相应地关注其衡量标准会造成固有的不平衡，从而破坏公司有效竞争的努力。</p><p>根据我们的研究（包括对 3,000 多名经理的全球调查结果以及对十多次高管访谈的定性分析），我们确定了利用人工智能增强战略指标的三种方法：</p><ul><li><strong style="font-size:1.25em;">我</strong>改进现有的 KPI。</li><li><strong style="font-size:1.25em;">创建</strong>新的 KPI。</li><li> <strong style="font-size:1.25em;">E</strong>在 KPI 之间建立新的关系。</li></ul><p>本文解释了这个改进-创建-建立（ICE）框架如何帮助领导者和管理者重新调整关键绩效指标（KPI）的用途，以提高他们的人员、流程和技术的效率。我们的研究表明，人工智能增强的 KPI 与具有战略价值的商业利益相关，包括提高效率、更好的一致性和更大的经济效益。将人工智能集成到战略衡量流程中对未来的资本配置、客户参与度、员工体验、EBITDA 和所有其他执行指标具有巨大影响。 （请参阅“AI 调整 KPI 的好处”。） </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> AI 调整 KPI 的好处</h4><p class="caption">与不使用 AI 创建新 KPI 的组织相比，使用 AI 创建新 KPI 的组织更有可能实现更强的一致性、增强的协作、更准确的预测和更高的效率。 </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:25%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:15%;"></th><th style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;width:60%;"></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 5x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"><strong>激励结构与目标一致：是</strong>不使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的组织的 5.13 倍（6% → 29%） </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 4x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"><strong>员工之间的协作增强：</strong>是不使用 AI 来创建新 KPI 的组织的 3.97 倍（11% → 44%） </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"><strong>更有效地预测未来绩效：</strong>是不使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的组织的 3.37 倍（13% → 45%） </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#36C68A;font-size:5em;"> 3x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"><strong>更大的经济效益：</strong>是不使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的组织的 3.27 倍（11% → 34%） </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;background-color:#02253D;padding-left:50px;border-right-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;"><p style="color:#AB64F2;font-size:5em;"> 2x </p></td><td style="border-top:hidden;border-right:hidden;border-color:#506A85;border-width:thin;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td rowspan="2" style="text-align:left;vertical-align:middle;border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;padding-right:50px;"><p style="color:white;"><strong>更高的效率：</strong>比不使用人工智能创建新 KPI 的组织高 2.31 倍 (24% → 56%) </p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr><tr><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td><td style="border:hidden;background-color:#02253D;"></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article02_fig2-fallback.png" alt="AI 调整 KPI 的好处" class="no-desktop" /><br /></article></aside></div><p>我们提供了一些关于如何使用人工智能来提高 KPI 的实用步骤。</p><p></p><h3>利用 AI 改进现有 KPI</h3><p>最初使用人工智能来提高绩效数字的公司往往会发现该技术创造了重新审视和审查关键绩效参数的机会。</p><h4> Wayfair 的替代效应</h4><p>Wayfair 的人工智能方法证明了这一点。虽然失去销售似乎是一个简单的衡量标准，但这家在线家具零售商使用人工智能重新审视其销售损失 KPI 背后的基本原理。正如首席技术官菲奥娜·谭 (Fiona Tan) 回忆的那样：“我们过去认为，如果某件产品（例如沙发）失去了销售，这对公司来说就是损失。但我们开始查看数据并意识到，50% 到 60% 的情况下，当我们失去销售时，是因为客户购买了同一产品类别中的其他商品。”</p><p>这种基于人工智能的分析使 Wayfair 能够根据客户关注的问题（例如价格点、发货时间和其他因素）尝试替代报价。对这些替代产品的需求为我们了解之前衡量和解释为销售损失的情况提供了新的视角。认识到这种“替代效应”后，Wayfair 调整了整个沙发领域的定价，改进了配送中心的产品配置，并重新确定了传统 KPI 的优先级。</p><p></p><p>在某种程度上，Wayfair 使用人工智能将其传统的销售损失 KPI 转变为更有价值的指标，以区分真正的销售损失和实际销售。但在另一个层面上，升级后的 KPI 背后的人工智能也带来了更彻底的变化。谭的团队利用替代效应开发了一个“利润意识框架”，该框架改变了公司与客户互动的方式。 Wayfair 的家具推荐在提供次佳报价时开始考虑交货时间和运输成本，以及产品事故和产品盈利能力。明确衡量和纳入替代效应将销售损失重新定义为销售机会，并导致定价变化。这种重构最终使产品布局决策与配送中心和仓库的需求和能力保持一致，从而改善了员工和客户的体验。</p><p>整个行业的公司都在寻找利用人工智能来改善现有 KPI 的方法。有些人使用人工智能来加深对推动 KPI 结果的因素的理解，而另一些人则使用人工智能来识别和优先考虑哪些 KPI 可以为组织带来最大价值。虽然我们的调查结果表明，大多数公司会对改进 KPI（即依赖人类判断）感到满意，但我们也看到公司认识到，人工智能使全新的 KPI 成为可能，从而实现并推动更高水平的绩效。</p><h3>创建新的 KPI</h3><p>除了改进现有绩效指标之外，人工智能还为管理者提供了通过算法发现和生成全新 KPI 的潜力。虽然我们的调查显示，只有 16% 的受访者组织使用人工智能来生成新的 KPI，但 90% 的组织认为人工智能的使用显着改善了他们的 KPI。</p><p>例如，寻找能够帮助医生预防心源性猝死的指标是医生和研究人员持续不断的努力，心源性猝死每年困扰着美国 30 万人。这些类型的死亡都是突然发生的。医生无法预测它们，因为患者的风险并不高。这是一种特别令人沮丧的情况，因为如果医生能够及时识别高危患者，就有一种已知的有效治疗方法——安装心脏除颤器。此次搜寻的研究人员之一、加州大学伯克利分校的医生兼教授 Ziad Obermeyer 正在与瑞典哈兰地区卫生系统合作，该系统的电子健康记录数据可以与各种政府数据相关联。他和他的合作者训练了一种算法，利用死亡证明以及从政府记录和电子健康记录中获取的各种其他数据点，预测进行心电图 (ECG) 后一年内的心源性猝死。</p><p> “该算法非常擅长预测在进行心电图检查后的一年内谁将死于心源性猝死。每次有人接受心电图检查时，它都会生成一个风险评分，衡量该人死于心脏骤停的可能性，”Obermeyer 说。心电图评分也可以像关键绩效指标一样发挥作用：有了该评分，医生可以观察如果患者服用β受体阻滞剂或血管紧张素转换酶抑制剂等药物，该评分会如何变化。虽然这项研究还处于非常早期的阶段，但有一天它可能会让医生和患者共同努力降低心源性猝死的风险，并找出可能降低风险的新干预措施。 “能够将这些非常复杂的生物信号转化为指标的能力非常强大，”奥伯迈耶说，“我认为我们将会看到更多这种技术，不仅适用于心源性猝死，还适用于糖尿病并发症以及各种其他可预防的高风险情况。”</p><p> Obermeyer 使用人工智能创建心源性猝死的新 KPI，有望改善患者治疗结果、降低成本并增强医生对自身疗效的认识。利用人工智能开发和识别新的关键绩效指标是整个商业领域和我们采访的大公司中的一种新兴现象，例如星展银行、通用电气、通用汽车、赛诺菲、施耐德电气和沃尔玛。这些公司正在使用人工智能来识别企业活动早期和早期阶段的未来绩效指标。除其他好处外，这种功能可以促进更好的态势感知和对不断变化的市场条件做出更有效的响应。</p><h3>在 KPI 之间建立新的关系</h3><p>没有 KPI 是一座孤岛。我们采访的许多高管都强调，为了更好地管理他们的业务，他们需要将本地关键绩效指标 (KPI) 整合为一组更加综合的指标。各行业的高管明确指出了最大化本地 KPI 与优化更高级别、更宏观的 KPI 之间固有的组织和计算紧张关系。随着 KPI 特征和参数的发展，预测、建模以及协调多个 KPI 与 AI 交互的重要性变得更加重要。</p><h4>星展银行将其 KPI 与人工智能集成</h4><p>总部位于新加坡的星展银行曾经依赖独立的关键绩效指标来实现涉及客户旅程中不同点的每个职能。也就是说，对于给定的产品，营销将有自己的客户参与度指标，产品将有自己的流失指标，财务将有自己的收入指标等。然而，在过去三年中，跨国银行业金融服务公司已经用水平模式取代了垂直模式。星展银行创建了一个价值图，将用例连接到一个客户旅程中，其结果分为四类：客户体验、员工体验、盈利能力和风险。 “我们称之为‘旅程管理’，”星展银行首席分析官 Sameer Gupta 说道。 “每个客户旅程都会有多个驱动因素，而每个驱动因素又会有多个衡量指标。您可以想象这些规模的扩展速度有多快，而且人力不可能优化如此大量的驱动因素和指标。人工智能是一种力量倍增器，使我们能够分析大量驱动因素和指标，并确定现在需要采取行动的因素。”</p><p>在新模型中，跨职能团队可以看到结果数据，其成员都对优化所有四个类别的结果有利害关系。 “每个人都在查看相同的数据，每个人都对相同的结果负责，”古普塔指出。这些团队利用实验、数据分析、客户沉浸和人工智能来不断审查导致不同结果的因素。此外，他们仍然高度关注选择正确的指标。</p><p>用古普塔的话说，在关键绩效指标之间建立这些相互关系是“一个根本性的转变”。他预计，随着组织继续协调其指标以推动持续改进，人工智能将发挥越来越重要的作用。 “我们开始思考，‘我们目前是否通过数据和人工智能支持做出这个决定？是否有机会通过数据和人工智能实现这一目标？如果有的话，我们该怎么做？”古普塔说。通过人工智能和其他分析技术来识别 KPI 之间的新关系可以产生新的商机、新的见解以及用于管理组织行为的一组有价值的数据。</p><h3>领导力要点</h3><p>战略衡量的未来属于更智能的 KPI。然而，我们的研究表明，很少有传统组织战略性地使用人工智能来改善其 KPI。这使得人工智能和关键绩效指标都被低估了。领导层需要进行相应的投资。使用 AI 改进 KPI、创建新的 KPI 以及在 KPI 之间建立新的关系，可以创造获得可衡量的更大价值的机会。 ICE 框架邀请高管和董事会进行讨论，这应该会导致管理层投资于改进战略衡量。</p><p>我们的研究还强调，领导者不仅需要根据要追求的 KPI 进行调整，更重要的是，还要根据这些 KPI 的目的进行调整。 KPI 主要是回顾性的，还是预测性地倾向于未来？</p><p>如果是后者，组织需要改进现有 KPI 的路线图；致力于围绕创建新的 KPI 进行探索和实验；并认识到 KPI 之间的关系可能与各个 KPI 本身一样重要，甚至更重要。智能 KPI 不应主要作为独立的绩效孤岛进行管理；相反，必须理解和解决它们的相互依赖性和相互关系。正如我们的例子所示，这些转变代表了领导力面临的运营、组织和文化挑战。</p><p>与几乎所有成功的人工智能计划一样，KPI 与构成它们的算法一样，必须是透明且可解释的。 KPI（组织上、文化上和运营上）不能被视为黑匣子。它们的设计和部署应该是值得信赖的。这种文化成分不应被最小化或视为理所当然。否则，组织中各个级别的人员都会寻求对指导他们的指标进行游戏，从而导致组织出现偏差。</p><p></p><p>这种对人工智能和关键绩效指标以及更广泛的战略衡量的新重视的基础是承认高质量的关键绩效指标取决于高质量的数据。在有偏见、不完整和有缺陷的数据集上训练或监督的 KPI 很可能是有偏见、不完整和有缺陷的。 KPI 越重要，数据质量就越重要。我们看到致力于人工智能驱动 KPI 的组织变得更加致力于将数据培养为资产。他们认为对数据的投资反映在 KPI 的改进中。</p><p>最后，随着受人工智能影响的关键绩效指标在企业中变得越来越有影响力，它们自身的绩效将需要新水平的监控和监督。领导层需要能够评估其 KPI 的个人和集体表现如何。它们是可持续成功的正确关键绩效指标吗？他们是否正确地预测了未来？他们是否做出了正确的决定——并帮助人类做出正确的决定——以实现期望和理想的结果？简而言之，KPI 将需要自己的 KPI 来帮助回答这些重要问题。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/improve-key-performance-indicators-with-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> 2023 年 10 篇最受欢迎的文章（迄今为止）</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Workplace]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Three-plus years after COVID-19 interrupted office-based operations with a sudden transition to remote work, managing hybrid teams remains a pressing issue for leaders. Hybrid culture has its own pitfalls to manage, with risks like feelings of disconnection among employees and “productivity paranoia.” Based on the most-read articles in the first half of 2023, readers of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MostPopular2023-tile-angleREV-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>在 COVID-19 中断办公室运营并突然过渡到远程工作三年多后，管理混合团队仍然是领导者面临的紧迫问题。混合文化有其自身需要管理的陷阱，其中存在诸如员工之间的脱节感和“生产力偏执”等风险。根据 2023 年上半年阅读量最大的文章， <cite>《麻省理工斯隆管理评论》</cite>的读者似乎热衷于解决这些问题。改进工具可以在有关基于技能的文化变革、有效的一对一会议和知识诚实的文章中找到。读者还关注 ESG、可持续性以及人工智能在绩效管理和战略中日益重要的作用等宏观问题。</p><p> The following are the 10 most popular articles of the year so far. We hope they will continue to help leaders in managing and supporting employees and in building thriving, innovative organizations.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#1</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/work-from-home-regulations-are-coming-companies-arent-ready/" style="border-bottom:none;">Work-From-Home Regulations Are Coming. Companies Aren&#39;t Ready.</a></h4><h6> Jimena Murillo Chávarro</h6><p> A growing web of regulatory minutiae governing flexible working arrangements around the world poses an acute challenge for multinationals. These companies must now contend with different compliance requirements in different jurisdictions, depending on how governments define and interpret terms like <em>remote work</em> , <em>teleworking</em> , and <em>work from home</em> .</p><h4> <span class="blue">#2</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-ways-to-make-your-one-on-one-meetings-more-effective/" style="border-bottom:none;">Five Ways to Make Your One-on-One Meetings More Effective</a></h4><h6> Jessica Wisdom</h6><p> Weekly check-in meetings between managers and their teams or direct reports are key opportunities to build trusting manager-employee relationships. By taking five science-backed steps and asking five key questions, managers can better structure their one-on-ones to make these check-ins more productive.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#3</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-innovation-depends-on-intellectual-honesty" style="border-bottom:none;">Why Innovation Depends on Intellectual Honesty</a></h4><h6> Jeff Dyer, Nathan Furr, Curtis Lefrandt, and Taeya Howell</h6><p> Fostering psychological safety alone isn&#39;t enough to successfully drive innovation; leaders must also create conditions that enable healthy debate. The authors describe the factors most important to establishing the balance between psychological safety and open, honest debate and outline what leaders can do to create a high-performance learning and innovation culture.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#4</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/three-lessons-from-chatting-about-strategy-with-chatgpt" style="border-bottom:none;">Three Lessons From Chatting About Strategy With ChatGPT</a></h4><h6> Christian Stadler and Martin Reeves</h6><p> Amid great excitement about the potential use cases of large language models like ChatGPT, a pair of business strategists decided to test whether the tools can support ideation, experimentation, evaluation, and storytelling as part of the strategy creation process. In this article, they share three lessons that emerged when they conducted a series of experiments in which they posed a question of strategy to ChatGPT and followed up with iterative queries.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#5</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-is-helping-companies-redefine-not-just-improve-performance/" style="border-bottom:none;">AI Is Helping Companies Redefine, Not Just Improve, Performance</a></h4><h6> Michael Schrage, David Kiron, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu</h6><p> Research on organizations&#39; use of artificial intelligence offers new perspectives on what drives performance and how best to measure it. Three practical and valuable ways KPIs can redefine strategic measurement include using smart KPIs that learn, measuring the performance of KPIs themselves, and enhancing organizational alignment with KPIs.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#6</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/esg-is-going-to-have-a-rocky-2023-sustainability-will-be-just-fine" style="border-bottom:none;">ESG Is Going to Have a Rocky 2023. Sustainability Will Be Just Fine.</a></h4><h6> Andrew Winston</h6><p> Companies&#39; environmental, social, and governance activities are facing two kinds of backlash: “anti-woke” political theater and noise from the investment community about whether ESG funds will outperform “regular” funds. But while ESG gets buffeted by these winds, the <em>real</em> work of sustainability continues.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#7</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-toxic-culture-gap-shows-companies-are-failing-women" style="border-bottom:none;">The Toxic Culture Gap Shows Companies Are Failing Women</a></h4><h6> Donald Sull and Charles Sull</h6><p> Which elements of corporate culture are most critical to women? And which cultural shortcomings are causing women to head for the exits? In analyzing the language that 3 million US employees used in Glassdoor reviews to describe their employers, the authors found that toxic culture disproportionately affects women, with the widest gender gaps in perceptions of inclusivity and respect.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#8</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/managing-the-cultural-pitfalls-of-hybrid-work" style="border-bottom:none;">Managing the Cultural Pitfalls of Hybrid Work</a></h4><h6> Christine Moorman and Katie Hinkfuss</h6><p> Although the hybrid work model has been widely adopted among many businesses, the complications involving peer relationships and connections that it has introduced linger on. A set of strategies presented here can help leaders navigate organizational culture and the socialization of new employees during this era of digital transformation.</p><p></p><h4> <span class="blue">#9</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change" style="border-bottom:none;">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a></h4><h6> Per Hugander</h6><p> Taking a skills-based approach, rather than implementing typical culture-change initiatives, can lead to positive changes in behavior that endure, particularly when it comes to cultivating soft skills like <em>perspective taking</em> and creating psychological safety. The author explains key attributes of the skills-based approach to culture change and how organizations can leverage it to speed the process and improve performance in the long term.</p><h4> <span class="blue">#10</span><br /> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-ways-to-build-a-culture-of-honesty-and-avoid-productivity-paranoia/" style="border-bottom:none;">Four Ways to Build a Culture of Honesty and Avoid &#39;Productivity Paranoia&#39;</a></h4><h6> Pamela Meyer</h6><p> Remote and hybrid work environments can breed distrust, or productivity paranoia, between managers and employees or between remote and in-person colleagues. The author describes four steps managers can take to foster a culture of trust and honesty when people aren&#39;t able to interact and develop relationships with one another in person.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-10-most-popular-articles-in-2023-so-far/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Regulating AI Innovation: Aboitiz Data Innovation&#39;s David Hardoon</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Chief Executive Officer]]></category><category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technological Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[As CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation, David Hardoon oversees the operations of a technology conglomerate focused on using data science and AI to support its businesses in a range of sectors, including banking, financial services, utilities, agriculture, and construction in Singapore and the Philippines. In his role, David is leading some unexpected — but practical [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> As CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation, David Hardoon oversees the operations of a technology conglomerate focused on using data science and AI to support its businesses in a range of sectors, including banking, financial services, utilities, agriculture, and construction in Singapore and the Philippines. In his role, David is leading some unexpected — but practical — uses of artificial intelligence, including using voice and image recognition to detect stress in livestock, and analyzing internet-of-things data to reduce waste and CO <sub>2</sub> emissions in the cement R&amp;D process.</p><p> David joins this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast to discuss the broad scope of the organizations he&#39;s responsible for, the role of AI regulation and governance in helping to spur innovation, humans&#39; sometimes problematic role in shaping AI outputs, and how a high school detention led to a career in artificial intelligence. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MMAI-S7-E3-Hardoon-Aboitiz-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="David Hardoon"></p><h4> David Hardoon, Aboitiz Data Innovation</h4><p> David Hardoon is the CEO of Aboitiz Data Innovation and chief data and AI officer of Union Bank of the Philippines. He is concurrently the chief data and innovation officer of the Aboitiz Group and chief data officer of UnionDigital Bank. Previously, he was the Monetary Authority of Singapore&#39;s first appointed chief data officer and head of the Data Analytics Group, as well as a special adviser on AI. Hardoon has a doctorate in computer science (machine learning) from the University of Southampton and a bachelor&#39;s degree from Royal Holloway, University of London, in computer science and AI.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Concrete production? Livestock? The Socratic method? Somehow, we talk about all three. Find out how these connect with AI in today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I&#39;m David Hardoon from Aboitiz Data Innovation, and you&#39;re listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome. Today, Shervin and I are excited to be joined by David Hardoon, who holds several senior positions at the Aboitiz Group. David, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Thank you very much, Sam, Shervin.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Can you first tell us a bit about the Aboitiz Group? Where do you work?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> The Aboitiz Group is a 100-plus-year-old conglomerate that originated starting in Spain — Catalonia — and relocated to the Philippines. It started in the hemp business but is now quite diversified, from the main business — power generation and distribution across the Philippines — [to] financial services, cement, construction, utilities, [real] estate, airports, food, agriculture. We&#39;re now going through a transformation and becoming — I love this term, by the way — a techglomerate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What is Aboitiz Data Innovation?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> About seven years ago, give or take, the bank started with all digitalization of the banking services. And what that had resulted in, as you would imagine, [was] a tremendous amount of data. The more you engage your consumers digitally, the more you have digital services — well, surprise, surprise — the more data you have.</p><p> And the question came as well, how are we really using it? Are we using it? What&#39;s the best way to put it to good use? And that question kind of also went beyond just the bank into the rest of the businesses, as you can imagine. Power has a lot of data; agriculture, airports, etc., have a lot of data.</p><p> We were born with a very on-point mandate: operationalizing data, operationalizing AI. Really, how do we put it to good use?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What are some of these uses?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I mean, there&#39;s the usual financial side, where we all learn from hyperpersonalization, financial crime. And don&#39;t get me wrong — that stuff … always gets me all excited. I spent a few good years in the financial regulator [space] here in Singapore.</p><p> But let me give you an oddity: cement, an industry that you wouldn&#39;t really associate with data or AI. We sat down with the CEO at the time, and we said, “Look, even in the world of cement, you have a lot of data.”</p><p> How can this work? So let me give you a little tidbit of how the world of cement works. And this is something that was new to me. So basically, it&#39;s like baking. I don&#39;t know if you bake, but it&#39;s like baking. It&#39;s basically, you have mixtures. You have these kind of formulas, and you end up with cement, which will have different types of properties. And these properties [are] what&#39;s absolutely critical depending on what you&#39;re planning to build, whether it&#39;s a mall, a high rise, a low rise, residential, etc., and so forth.</p><p> Having said that, as with baking, you kind of need to do a bit of trial and error. You need to try out these different mixtures to make sure it produces the right one. That results in operational overhead. It results in wastage. I mean, as with baking, you stick this stuff into kilns — literally, it&#39;s a furnace — to bake it. Using data, using the information that&#39;s coming from all the devices, the IoT, using AI, being able to actually tell the bakers or, in this case, the chemical engineers what is going to be the output of this mixture before they even start, while at the same time maintaining that quality control, which is absolutely crucial. Now this is, by the way, not just hypothetical. This is already operational for the past year in all the plants — about six plants in the Philippines — and results in operational efficiency, results in reduction in [the amount] of wastage, resulted in what I like to call quantifiable ESG [environmental, social, and governance]: a 35 kiloton reduction of CO <sub>2</sub> emissions. So that&#39;s a nice unusual example I like to give in terms of how data is used.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Well, I could tell you, Sam and I are going to love that. We&#39;re both chemical engineers.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Oh, well, there you go.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Actually, when you said baking, I did my Ph.D. in catalyst synthesis, so I spent a lot of my time baking various aluminosilicates to create catalysts. And you&#39;re completely right: You try all these things. Some work; some don&#39;t work. And had there been the ability for me to know ahead of time, I probably would have gotten my Ph.D. in a tenth of the time.</p><p> But seriously, this is quite interesting. Now, if you go from personalization and cyber and fraud, and you also have this example in baking cements, then we must believe that there is such a wide portfolio of things that you are considering. So tell us more about what makes it into that portfolio, because there is no end to what you could do. What are the kinds of things you get excited about?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> You&#39;re absolutely right. Being fortunate working in a conglomerate, you kind of wake up every day and discover something new. So there are kind of two dimensions to it. On the one hand — and I&#39;m going to go back to this term <em>operationalization</em> , operationalizing data and AI — it&#39;s stuff that has to make sense to the business. So revenue, operational efficiency, risk management. And then we have to look at the things around the corner. We have to experiment. But those may not be things that get immediately deployed. Like, effectively in agricultural builders, we have the animals; we have pigs, swine, and poultry. And as part of that process, we want to make sure that the animals have the best possible care provided to them. On an experimental side, we say, “OK, how can we use technology that&#39;s already available but may not have been put in exactly in this particular context, not in Southeast Asia?” So we&#39;re using voice recognition and image recognition for pigs to help identify stress and detect illnesses, so that could be automatic alerts to the caregivers.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the ground truth on that? That would be interesting to know.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a great question.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the training data?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> So this is the amazing stuff. It&#39;s a very expressive animal. So when you actually go there with the people who take care of them, they can literally point at them and say, “This animal is distressed,” and you&#39;re constantly recording.</p><p> We&#39;re kind of, “OK, is this really something that&#39;s relevant? Does it make sense?” Like, can we have that conversation with the baker, you know, the chemical engineer? Can we have a conversation with the animal keeper, the veterinarian and so forth, or the pole engineer when we&#39;re dealing with electricity cables? It&#39;s extremely important.</p><p> And that&#39;s one of the things that I realized throughout my career of doing data, is where things failed, where you suddenly had this divergence of exploring scientific research — and I came from the world of science, you know, like ex-academic — without really seeing that connectivity. And if we go all the way back, even when radar was invented, the reason things fall apart is whereby the very, very small gaps of “Well, it&#39;s not quite there; oh, it&#39;s not quite usable.” So that&#39;s the first part.</p><p> Then, the second level is seeing, well, is this something that, as much as possible, is truly going to make a difference to either our internal users — because that&#39;s extremely important — and for many of the businesses which are within the group, which are actually B2B, like in power, where, essentially, we provide power and wholesale [electricity]? So it&#39;s our internal users in terms of, let&#39;s say, predictive asset maintenance — critically important.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That is really fantastic. I mean, what you&#39;ve said is inspiring on so many levels. One is, let your imagination be the limit, right, because [of] the question of “Can something be done better, more effectively? Can you see around the corner there?” And there&#39;s data, then, yes. That&#39;s one thing that&#39;s inherent in all these examples that you gave.</p><p> You started with what most would consider quite advanced and interesting things, and we have guests who talk about those all the time: personalization, fraud, cyber. All of those are very important. And then you went to cement. And then you went to pigs. And then you talked about human and AI …</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Which is quite critical too. I just find that very, very energizing.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Well, it&#39;s the nexus between human and AI. There are two critical things that I believe have to go hand in hand — have to. While this may change in the future to some degree or extent — I mean, who knows what&#39;s going to happen around the corner? Things change so rapidly. But I&#39;ll be the first one to admit this: I truly came to this appreciation when I worked [for] the regulator — surprise, surprise — [of the] criticality of combining governance and innovation. And I used to get asked this question repeatedly, of “Oh, but don&#39;t you think governance inhibits innovation? It stifles us.” And I came to the view of, I&#39;m vehemently against that perspective.</p><p> I would argue that not only it does not stifle it — it would result in more and even better innovation. It&#39;s essentially about just simply having, you know, common sense. I was privileged in being in the process and coming up with the FEAT principle. So this was <em>fairness</em> , <em>ethics</em> , <em>accountability</em> , and <em>transparency</em> , back at the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</p><p> I remember that when it came out — and we deliberately kept it very simple — and I showed it to our governor, our managing director, and he was just like, “David, isn&#39;t this just common sense?” And I just smiled, and I was like, “Well, no; even common sense has to ... it&#39;s not always that common. It has to be written down.” But it&#39;s critical. That&#39;s No. 1.</p><p> And No. 2, what you were mentioning is that, yes, while AI and data can do what is seemingly miraculous stuff, it&#39;s critical that this combination with us humans and <em>how</em> we use it is baked in at the very beginning. And even now, obviously, everyone&#39;s talking about ChatGPT, but remember: All the data that it&#39;s trained on is from <em>us</em> to a certain extent.</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。 You can&#39;t take humans out of the loop, because after a while, they will lose what makes them human.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> But we have examples of that. I mean, that&#39;s OK in some places. I mean, neither of you know how to navigate by the stars, I&#39;m guessing, unless, Shervin, you&#39;ve got some tricks up your sleeve that I haven&#39;t learned yet. I mean, most people don&#39;t drive a manual transmission; that seems to be a skill that&#39;s … well, OK, maybe one or two of us do here. But the point is, we don&#39;t have to retain all possible skills. We just have to be savvy about which ones we hang on to.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> That&#39;s exactly [right], what you said: It&#39;s some, not all. But sometimes you find that you see this trend of like, “Oh, look what it can do. <em>Everything</em> gets automated.” And I remember, if I go to my early days as a consultant — you know, I used to be a consultant doing AI — you would find a lot of times, potential clients and people you spoke to, even if they didn&#39;t say it explicitly, what they were trying to achieve was like, “Oh, just do everything automatically with AI.”</p><p> And you need to have almost this natural inclination by saying, “OK, if it&#39;s contextual, if it makes sense.” Like you said, maybe I want to pick up star navigation because I&#39;m interested in it. I want to learn about astrology or astrophysics or whatnot. Great. But you see it now becomes a niche topic that some people pick up. The general public doesn&#39;t need to know how to do it. But we need to be able to identify that decision point rather than just go [into a] “No, everything now, AI galore” kind of situation.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Well, I mean, what you&#39;re saying is, there&#39;s value in the ongoing dialogue. There&#39;s value in ongoing challenge. And every time there is a dialogue, I mean, even back in Socrates&#39;s time, the dialogue is where it elevates the conversation. And you&#39;re rightly pointing out that the moment you say AI is the be-all and end-all is the moment that you are under-delivering on AI, and then you&#39;re for sure under-delivering on the human potential.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Well you&#39;re losing a potential answer. Let me give you two examples. In the financial section, we have Union Bank of the Philippines, amongst others. While AI governance regulation is not yet — <em>yet</em> — a requirement, let&#39;s say, in the Philippines, we&#39;ve situated a working group, which is an interesting combination of people, from your risk officer, legal, compliance, and then you have marketing, customer engagement, experience. What happens is, while you still have the traditional process of model validation, etc., from a statistical, mathematical, data point of view, the models are presented in this working group for us to have a debate. Because a model may pass all the statistical tests, but if this model goes wrong — even that 10% or 5% — there is a significant reputational risk at play or there&#39;s a potential impact to the consumers. That debate is important because if you just looked at it from that statistical, even a potentially automated process, you would miss it.</p><p> Now, the resolution, interestingly enough — and I honestly tell you, like, maybe eight out of 10 times so far — isn&#39;t data, isn&#39;t AI. The resolution a lot of times is process, which is people. And that makes us actually wiser and understanding, “OK, how do we use it, and how do we engage with it? And when do we allow” — Sam, to your point — “that automation?” And when we go “no,” I retain the veto to overrule, to a certain extent. So that&#39;s one example.</p><p> The other one is if I go back to my cement [example], and in fact, we did this very deliberately at the very beginning because we didn&#39;t want our colleagues and chemical engineers to think, “Oh, great. Why do you need me? You&#39;re just going to automate the whole thing.”</p><p> No. The whole point was, we absolutely need them because there may be new types of mixtures that we haven&#39;t considered. You will still need to have that experimentation. The whole goal is providing information.</p><p> What it has resulted in is efficiency. If I give a swing again to another one — when ChatGPT came out, I got asked straightaway from a few boards, “What does this mean?” And my instinctive reaction, rather than going into this whole lengthy explanation of liberation, I just responded by saying, “It means that every one of us can have the productivity of 10 people.”</p><p> So this is what this stuff means, and that&#39;s what that nexus, the dialogue, the integration, the augmentation means — is that we now have the ability to be far more productive, whatever “productive” means in that context. For some people, they may say, “I just want to work two hours but [appear] as if I work the whole day.” Some may say, “I want to work the whole day.” … It may differ. But that&#39;s what it means because now we&#39;re able to take all this data.</p><p> I&#39;m sure some of you remember, back in 2000, you had these memes online of “getting information off the internet is like drinking from a fire hose.” It&#39;s still true. We&#39;re inundated with information, with data, but it&#39;s like distilling it down to something that&#39;s relevant to me, usable, that I can do something with it and get that gain, essentially.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think one thing that&#39;s coming out of this conversation — Shervin used the word <em>Socratic</em> , and, David, you used the word <em>dialogue</em> . What&#39;s nice about this is it&#39;s dropped this hubris that I feel like I see in a lot of machine learning. Machine learning seems to be about humans teaching machines. So it&#39;s this sort of “We know all. We make the machines emulate us, and if they do, they pass the Turing test, and, yes, everything&#39;s golden.” But then you get pushback, and you say, “Oh, no. The machine can teach <em>us</em> things we&#39;ve never known before.” Well, that just has switched the direction. It still has that same directional hubris, but the things that you&#39;re both talking about are much more [oriented around the] Socratic and dialogue.</p><p> When you think about what that group can form together — and Shervin and I have got some results from last year&#39;s research that said about 60% of the people are thinking about AI as a coworker. And that strikes me as that sort of a relationship, because between the two, yes, you find some new compound that maybe someone wouldn&#39;t have tried. I don&#39;t know what the chemical engineering equivalent of the Fosbury flop is. Do you remember the Fosbury flop, where he learned a different way of jumping over the high bar, and then suddenly everyone else adopted that technique? That sort of idea seems like it could come out of this approach.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> It&#39;s actually really interesting you bring that up. I mean, I&#39;d love to say, “Oh, yeah, we had this all intended in the very beginning,” but I&#39;ll be very honest and say, I think it&#39;s more of a nice consequence that wasn&#39;t fully intended at a point in time.</p><p> But I want to go back to that FEAT principle. One of the principles resulted in a lot of discourse — and I mean a <em>lot</em> — where we had a statement amongst all of them that said that we should hold AI to at least the same standard as human decisions. So AI-based decisions should be held to at least the same standard as human-based decisions. And the debate was phenomenal and [people] said, “Oh, no, we should hold it to a higher one,” etc., and so forth.</p><p> But what the intention of that principle was saying is, if you&#39;re using now … so let me go back again to, let&#39;s say, a financial [example]: loan provisioning. And if [you&#39;re] using an AI algorithm and you&#39;re finding that “oh, we&#39;re discriminating,” OK, yeah, absolutely, that&#39;s something that needs to be addressed, reviewed, and corrected. But hold your horses there. Take a step back. Take the AI out of the equation. Had you been discriminating before the AI? And that&#39;s really the question because ... I remember I had long debates with many regulators. Maybe debate is the wrong word: <em>discussions</em> with many regulators. And I was actually a bit opposed to regulating AI, and I&#39;ll explain what I mean by that.</p><p> I&#39;m not opposing regulation. But when they said “regulating AI,” I got a bit defensive. I said, “What I&#39;m worried about is that we&#39;re like, &#39;OK, well, since AI now is showing me all this stuff that I don&#39;t want to know about, then I&#39;m just not going to use AI.&#39; And we&#39;re going to go back to the same procedures previously, which, guess what — it&#39;s the same problem. You just weren&#39;t paying attention to it because that information, that knowledge, wasn&#39;t bubbled up to the surface.”</p><p> So, what I kept on arguing is that, yes, the regulation has to be in play. And yes, there may be certain scenarios whereby AI requires higher scrutiny. But the regulation is still on the outcome. The regulation is still in the fact that, for example, it&#39;s a case of discrimination. You should not be discriminating; whether you&#39;re using a human-based process or an AI-based process is kind of beside the point. But I just want to emphasize that point, Sam, because it really goes back to what you were saying of, it&#39;s now teaching <em>us</em> things that we may have been, let&#39;s say, sometimes consciously ignorant of, sometimes inadvertently unaware of.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> David, tell us about your background. How did you end up where you are?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> If I roll back all the way to the beginning, and I&#39;m going to say this again with a big smile myself, how did I end up where I am? Detention. That&#39;s how I ended up here.</p><p> I must have been, what, 14, 15, 16 years old, and I got sent to the library because of detention. And, you know, if you&#39;re in a library, you have nothing better to do. I picked up a book on Prolog. Don&#39;t ask me why, from all the books I could have picked up, I picked up one about Prolog. And this is really before knowing anything about the whole world of, well, I guess in that case, it would be expert-based systems. And I started reading, and I just couldn&#39;t put it down. And that kind of triggered this exploration of, how can we better capture knowledge? How can we better learn?</p><p> And that obviously resulted in kind of learning a bit more about neural networks, AI. In fact, I was one of the first two students who took the degree of computer science with artificial intelligence. It was literally brand-new, from that perspective.</p><p> My Ph.D. thesis was about semantic models, so literally the representation and encapsulation of knowledge, effectively, and information; [it] was on learning musical patterns/music, or generating music from brain patterns. And the whole idea about that is essentially providing expert-based systems knowledge, if you think about it in that way, for people who, say, can&#39;t sit in front of a piano and play but are fully capable cognitively.</p><p> So that&#39;s kind of what brought me here. I know it&#39;s a very weird kind of journey. But yeah, I need to thank my literacy teacher: Thank you for sending me to detention.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> OK, so we&#39;ve got a segment where we&#39;re going to ask you some quick questions. What are you proudest of in terms of artificial intelligence? What have you done that you&#39;re proudest of?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Where to begin? What I&#39;m most proud of is the way we&#39;ve been able to graduate — and I literally mean that — from the academic world to the industrial world.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What worries you about AI? You&#39;ve mentioned some worries today. But what worries you?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> What worries me is I don&#39;t think we&#39;re fully appreciating what we&#39;re creating. I think we need to focus head on with the realization of what we&#39;re creating and what we&#39;re seeding for possibilities, for good and for bad.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> SUP: stand-up paddling. Being on the water and just paddling away. It&#39;s extremely soothing. It&#39;s actually phenomenal exercise, for those who haven&#39;t tried.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I&#39;ve tried and I&#39;ve missed the stand-up part. I&#39;m OK with the paddling, but the stand-up seems to lead to trouble. What&#39;s the first career you wanted while you were sitting in detention? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I wanted to be an astrophysicist.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future? What are you hoping we can gain from this?</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> I don&#39;t know. Self-actualization? I hope we learn more about ourselves. It&#39;s already giving us capabilities. I mean, for example, I&#39;m dyslexic. Thank heavens for auto spell-checkers!</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Well, thank you for taking the time. I think that there&#39;s a lot that you&#39;ve mentioned. I think we can go back to even examples of food 100 years ago. We had a terrible food cleanliness [problem], and now we have a supply chain we can trust. Perhaps we can build that same sort of supply chain with data. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. It&#39;s been a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> Thank you, Sam, Shervin.</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。谢谢。</p><p> <strong>David Hardoon:</strong> And maybe, if I may just add another note, I think that&#39;s really the critical thing: It&#39;s AI <em>trust</em> . It&#39;s about trust. Thank you very much.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, Shervin and I talk with Naba Banerjee, head of trust product and operations at Airbnb, about how the travel platform uses AI and machine learning to make travel experiences safer.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/regulating-ai-innovation-aboitiz-data-innovations-david-hardoon/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Amid Growing AI, Humanize Communication to Strengthen Relationships</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cole Clark. <p>Cole Clark is president of <a href="https://www.amygdalaunch.com/">AmygdaLaunch</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[AI entered a new era when artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT became available to the public this year. These technologies are taking over more and more aspects of business as they seep into the collective consciousness. As Vox put it, generative AI is “suddenly everywhere,” and it’s poised to profoundly change daily life within organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Clark-Handwritten-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> AI entered a new era when artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT became available to the public this year. These technologies are taking over more and more aspects of business as they seep into the collective consciousness. As Vox put it, generative AI is “ <a href="https://www.vox.com/recode/2023/1/5/23539055/generative-ai-chatgpt-stable-diffusion-lensa-dall-e">suddenly everywhere</a> ,” and it&#39;s poised to profoundly change daily life within organizations in many ways, particularly in the sphere of communication.</p><p> More than ever, when people receive texts, emails, or other digital messages, they have reason to wonder whether an actual human being wrote them. ChatGPT is even being used to write <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/08/chatgpt-is-being-used-to-write-emails-big-companies-are-embracing-it.html">custom messages</a> to individual executives on LinkedIn. In response, tools are being created to help people determine whether a message was really <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90830518/tools-to-detect-ai-generated-text-chatgpt">written by a human</a> . Some of these tools are made by the same companies whose technologies generate such text. But few people are likely to use these detectors in the short term, and even if they do, there will be a continuous cycle of AI-based text generators constantly working to outsmart the detectors.</p><p></p><p> The net result is clear: When it comes to digital communication, we&#39;re unlikely to trust most “personal” digital messages for a while to come. This is why, in working to build authentic relationships, sidestepping technology altogether has newfound power.</p><h3> Handwritten Messages Take on New Value</h3><p> Few people answer calls from unrecognized phone numbers these days. And executives are increasingly aware that AI is also being used to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/11/why-chatgpt-ai-are-taking-over-the-cold-call-salesforce-leader.html">schedule such calls</a> , which can make them feel like just another name on a list.</p><p> In an effort to connect with decision makers, I recently tried going a different route: I wrote notes by hand to several executives and dropped them in the mail. Some of these have led to very positive personal responses and meetings, and even contract discussions. These relationships are being built on <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-susan-mcpherson-on-building-meaningful-relationships-in-business-and-in-life">meaningful foundations</a> that could lead to long-term business growth.</p><p> There have always been people who prefer to write business notes by hand, but it&#39;s never before carried such a significant connotation — that a real person has taken the time to write out a personalized message rather than choosing an easier option. And a recent study shows how powerful that can be: Researchers from business schools at the University of Maryland and Yonsei University in South Korea found that “presenting a <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/10949968221102306?journalCode=jnma">handwritten note</a> has a positive and significant effect on customer spending” and that “warmth underlies the key findings.”</p><h3> Humanizing Communication</h3><p></p><p> A similar principle applies to internal communication as well. Some managers now use technology for things like employee recognition and turn to generative AI to create and send complimentary messages to team members. While this may be helpful for overwhelmed and exhausted managers, it can also reduce the sense of meaning and personalization that employees may be looking for. This is why handwritten notes can be a powerful way for managers to show employees — especially <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-create-belonging-for-remote-workers/">remote workers</a> , who aren&#39;t in the office to receive such recognition face to face — their genuine appreciation.</p><p> Writing notes by hand may not be the right move for everyone — such as if someone&#39;s penmanship is particularly difficult to read. But there are other ways to personalize communication, including creating videos or voice memos tailored to a specific individual, or even leaving a voicemail if a phone call goes unanswered. Some people block off a time in their schedule and say, “I&#39;m going to keep this two-hour block open in hopes that you might want to chat. Reach out anytime within that time frame, and I&#39;ll drop whatever I&#39;m doing.”</p><p> The key is to always be on the lookout for ways to emphasize our humanity in our communications. The more we do that, the less of an interloper AI will be in our relationships — and the more authentic and rewarding they&#39;ll become.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/amid-growing-ai-humanize-communication-to-strengthen-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Four-Day Workweek: How to Make It Work in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Barnes. <p>Andrew Barnes is the founder of Perpetual Guardian, New Zealand&#39;s largest corporate trustee company. He is also a cofounder of 4 Day Week Global and the author of <cite>The 4 Day Week</cite> (Piatkus, 2020).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[As cofounder of 4 Day Week Global, Andrew Barnes has a front-row seat to the world’s largest experiment on the effects of scaling back the workweek. It started with Barnes’s own New Zealand company, Perpetual Guardian, when he wondered whether his staff members could do their jobs better if they worked the equivalent of four [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA01_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> As cofounder of 4 Day Week Global, Andrew Barnes has a front-row seat to the world&#39;s largest experiment on the effects of scaling back the workweek.</p><p> It started with Barnes&#39;s own New Zealand company, Perpetual Guardian, when he wondered whether his staff members could do their jobs better if they worked the equivalent of four days instead of five. It would be crucial, he knew, to still deliver the same output, customer service, and profitability. He landed on what he calls the 100-80-100 rule: “We pay 100% income for 80% time, as long as we get 100% output.”</p><p> The trial made global headlines — “We stopped counting when we got over about 14,000” — and Barnes was inundated with requests for advice. He started a not-for-profit organization and began helping companies on their own pilots, providing virtual workshops, mentoring others, and networking opportunities. The results, which now include data from 91 companies and 3,500 workers, have been analyzed by a team of academics.</p><p></p><p> And those results have been universally positive. “Not only are 90%-plus of employees saying they like the four-day week — and, in fact, they really don&#39;t want to go back — but companies are seeing material benefits in productivity,” Barnes said.</p><p></p><p> Barnes talked about the experiments and their findings during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023. He wasn&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the event, so he answers some of them below. （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6> Is there any research comparing a four-day workweek versus five reduced days (at six hours a day, for example)? Do the results suggest that four days is the better way?</h6><p> Both are viewed by us as four-day weeks! The clickbait is “a four-day week,” but in reality, we talk about <em>reduced hours working</em> — the 100-80-100 rule. The key is that employees get the time off that&#39;s important to <em>them</em> . In my company, we have some people who take a full day off, others who take two half days, and others, often working parents, who work compressed hours five days a week. That schedule helps with child care issues, which a single day off would not address.</p><p></p><h6> How do you measure the success of the four-day workweek from the perspective of employees and teams when it comes to productivity versus company results like revenue?</h6><p> Obviously, it&#39;s easier to see whether there&#39;s improvement in company results such as profitability and revenue. We often find that people ask how we measure employee productivity. This, of course, raises the question of how productivity is <em>currently</em> being measured. All too often, it quickly becomes clear that many organizations use time as a surrogate for productivity.</p><p> Part of our program is helping organizations develop other productivity measures so that improvements can be more clearly assessed. A key part of this is helping employees identify the unproductive parts of their day. Simply eliminating unproductive activity will, by definition, increase productive activity.</p><h6> I find that much of what fills the time outside of tactical work are personal conversations and relationship-building. Do those things diminish when you move to a four-day week?</h6><p> No. In fact, the evidence suggests that these improve. By combining policies such as quiet hours (deep work), fewer and shorter meetings, and better social facilities (in our case, a better staff breakout area), we find that staff cohesion and team-building actually increase. By reinforcing that staff members need to work together to allow everyone to achieve the objective of reduced hours of working, there is often more time for these interactions, not less.</p><h6> Gallup&#39;s US panel data from 2020 shows that employees who work four days per week have higher well-being than those who work five or six days. However, Gallup&#39;s data also shows that the <a href="https://www.gallup.com/workplace/358346/gallup-workplace-insights-learned-2021.aspx">percentage who are actively disengaged rises</a> among those who work fewer days. Gallup says that employees who already feel disconnected from their employer are likely to drift even further away. What do you advise companies to do to address this?</h6><p> In the context of a society where many employees work from home and are therefore separated from the usual workplace culture, the impact of reduced hours working is actually minimal. It is also necessary to differentiate between the old style of four-day-week working (where only a few worked four days and most worked five, often with the former receiving lower pay) and the new model, where everyone works a reduced schedule with no reduction in pay. Companies in our trials report significant increases in engagement scores. In the case of our own company, scores increased by 40% — to levels the researchers said were the highest they had ever seen in New Zealand.</p><h6> What differences do you see in the effects of the four-day workweek on people doing different kinds of work — say, between software developers and creative workers versus salespeople?</h6><p> Obviously, there are practical differences in how the work is actually done, but the impact on employees across the companies in our various trials appears to be consistent. Employees report being more productive, more rested, less stressed, and happier. It is a thesis of mine that healthier, happier, more rested employees are more productive. Who would have thought!</p><h6> What kind of training and prep do companies do to introduce a four-day week?</h6><p> We encourage organizations to take a couple of months to plan and prepare before initiating the six-month trial. Both the preparation and trial allow organizations to flex the process to find out what works for them. The bulk of the efficiencies and improvements come from empowering staff members and creating a culture where individuals recognize that they have to work together to reduce wasted time. In my own organization and in many others, training was therefore limited and largely unnecessary.</p><h6> How do you build employee trust to successfully achieve the stated goals when implementing a reduced workweek?</h6><p> Put simply, if trust does not exist prior to the implementation of the four-day week, it is unlikely the implementation will be successful.</p><h6> We run a 24-hour operation. Have you seen this done in organizations such as this, and what is the impact on the staffing numbers? Don&#39;t you have to increase the number of employees?</h6><p> In many ways, it is easier to introduce a four-day week into a seven-day, 24-hour operation, as the organization is already running shift patterns. A reduced-hour week simply requires shifts to be reconfigured. Remember that our thesis is that productivity actually increases, so in some operations, each shift can be staffed with fewer employees.</p><p> Alternatively, in people-heavy organizations such as medical facilities, it is likely that more staff will have to be recruited. The savings here, though, come from reduced recruitment time and turnover, fewer sick days (67% fewer, according to the trial data) with reduced impact on productivity, and lower costs for expensive temporary staff. Evidence also suggests that outcomes improve.</p><h6> Have you done this work with clients in consulting industries? What kind of success have you had there? How was billable time affected?</h6><p>是的。 PR firms, legal firms, and consultancies have all moved to the four-day week. Billable hours is often quoted as an impediment, but it is simply a mechanism to allocate costs. The clients pay on value and outcomes. If you can now do the work quicker under the four-day model, just adjust the cost allocation units. The client doesn&#39;t care. A simple example: Two consultants produce an identical piece of work. One takes an hour, one half an hour. Why would the client pay twice as much for the former? In reality, billable hours get adjusted in order to align the bill with the amount the client will pay.</p><p></p><h6> What obstacles did you encounter when making the switch to a four-day workweek?</h6><p> The principal obstacle was that members of my leadership team were highly skeptical, if not hostile, and my board universally hated it. Bringing leadership on the journey and helping them to walk the talk is critical for the project&#39;s success. I have set out the usual obstacles in various papers that are on the <a href="https://www.4dayweek.com/">4dayweek.com</a> website and in my book, <cite>The 4 Day Week</cite> .</p><h6> Can you provide sample policies used by companies?</h6><p> The 4dayweek.com website has lots of helpful material, including the research and a white paper. That white paper includes the policies we introduced at Perpetual Guardian to implement the reduced schedule.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-four-day-workweek-how-to-make-it-work-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Communication Is at the Heart of Positive Employee Relationships</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Laker. <p>Ben Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School and coauthor of <cite>Too Proud to Lead: How Hubris Can Destroy Effective Leadership and What to Do About It</cite> (Bloomsbury, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment. Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Laker_Communication-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> In today&#39;s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment.</p><p> Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can significantly affect their organization&#39;s reputation as a place where people want to work. After all, having a culture that incorporates transparent and open communication is essential to building trust and loyalty.</p><p></p><h3> The Importance of Communication Skills in Hiring</h3><p> According to research, oral and written <a href="https://newmanu.edu/top-5-skills-employers-look-for">communication skills</a> are among the top five most sought-after attributes in potential new hires: Employers want workers who can effectively convey their ideas, perspectives, and knowledge.</p><p> Employees with strong communication skills are able to express their thoughts and emotions clearly, making them more efficient in the workplace. Additionally, they are better equipped to manage challenging conversations or negotiations with clients or coworkers through their ability to listen attentively, provide accurate feedback, and resolve conflicts.</p><p> Good communication skills also foster a better company culture: Employees create a stronger bond when they are able to effectively communicate with one another. This not only creates a cohesive and productive work environment but also increases their loyalty to the organization.</p><p></p><p> Hiring managers should screen resumes for clear and concise writing abilities and pay attention to how candidates speak during interviews to assess their communication skills. If appropriate, they should request written work samples before an interview to assess candidates&#39; writing capabilities. Candidates who can effectively communicate their qualifications and skills in writing will likely be able to better articulate them orally during the interview.</p><p></p><h3> The Hiring Process: Clear Expectations and Open Dialogue</h3><p> All parties involved in the hiring process need to be clear and concise when conveying information. Hiring managers must clearly define expectations, roles, and responsibilities when talking to potential candidates: One study found that 48% of employees who left a job early did so because their employer&#39;s <a href="https://www.hrdive.com/news/study-48-of-workers-have-left-a-job-because-it-didnt-meet-expectations/551179/">expectations were unclear</a> .</p><p> Establishing an open dialogue with candidates during the hiring process is essential for building trust and gaining insight into their communication styles. By using a combination of open-ended questions, role-playing scenarios, and exercises that focus on communication, employers can better understand each candidate&#39;s approach to their work and create a foundation for a strong working relationship.</p><p> Once a new hire is brought on board, providing feedback on their communication skills can help them understand what they are already doing well and where they can improve.</p><h3> Navigating Layoffs: Transparency, Empathy, and Compliance</h3><p> In an era marked by recession fears and downsizing, how companies handle layoffs can have a profound impact on their reputation and employee morale. To maintain a positive relationship with employees during layoffs, employers should prioritize clear, honest, and timely communication. This means providing as much advance notice as possible to all employees, explaining the rationale behind the decision, and offering support to those affected, such as career counseling, resume preparation, and job search assistance. By treating employees with respect and empathy, companies can minimize negative impacts and maintain a favorable reputation.</p><p> Furthermore, organizations must comply with laws governing layoffs to ensure the fair treatment of employees and avoid legal repercussions. Employers should be aware of their state and local laws to ensure that they meet minimum notice requirements and other regulations. Consider the case of Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, where the initial decision to <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bed-bath-beyond-to-pay-out-severance-to-1300-workers-after-initially-bypassing-law/ar-AA1aKgBG">bypass severance laws</a> led to lawsuits — and thus more negative publicity for a company that had recently declared bankruptcy — followed by a reversal of the decision.</p><h3> Creating a Culture of Open Communication</h3><p></p><p> The key to fostering positive relationships with candidates and employees alike lies in creating a culture of open communication. This means valuing transparency, honesty, and empathy, no matter the stage of employment. Companies should also encourage open dialogue among all levels of the organization, providing opportunities for employees to voice their concerns and ideas. This can help to establish a sense of trust, promote a collaborative work environment, and, ultimately, contribute to the company&#39;s overall success.</p><p> In addition to fostering open communication, employers should invest in training and development programs that help employees enhance their communication skills. This benefits the individuals, contributes to a more effective and cohesive work environment, and can, ultimately, lead to greater success for the organization and a more productive work environment overall. By prioritizing communication at every stage of the employee life cycle, managers can foster a positive work culture in which individuals feel valued, supported, and empowered to succeed.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>