<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 12 月 11 日星期一 17:00:52 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title>认识明天的劳动力：今天的学生劳工活动家</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ayanna Howard. <p>Ayanna Howard ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robotsmarts">@robotsmarts</a> ) 是俄亥俄州立大学工程学院院长。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nick Lowndes/Ikon Images Student labor activism is on the rise in new and surprising ways. Not only do students in higher education regularly turn out to support striking staff members on college campuses, but they’re also organizing and joining unions themselves in growing numbers. This direct action sets the stage for their lives after they [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Howard_Unionization-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼克·朗兹/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>学生劳工激进主义正在以令人惊讶的新方式兴起。高等教育的学生不仅定期支持大学校园罢工的工作人员，而且越来越多的人自己组织和加入工会。这种直接行动为他们离开高等教育后的生活奠定了基础，因为当学生在校园工作生活中参与组织活动时，你最好相信这些工人会在他们的职业生涯后期寻求工会。</p><p>根据国家高等教育和职业集体谈判研究中心的数据，美国学生工人谈判单位的数量从 2022 年初的 54 个增加到 2023 年 7 月的 84 个， <a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/news/faculty-issues/labor-unionization/2023/09/06/grad-worker-unionization-booming-even-down-south">增长了 56%</a> 。虽然研究生组织在过去几十年里稳步增长，其重点往往是教学要求和薪酬，但新的情况是，大量本科生工人转向围绕最低工资和工资等问题进行集体谈判。病假福利。</p><p></p><p>商业领袖应该明智地关注一些大学如何与学生合作应对这些挑战。学校的任务是确保学生成立工会的权利，以改善校园工作环境，同时为这些学生提供在校园生活和学习的教育福利。这与企业必须如何兼顾工作场所生产力和员工满意度的需求有相似之处。今天的学生组织者正在建立对伙伴关系的期望，他们将把这种伙伴关系带到未来的工作场所。</p><p></p><h3>本科生工会化的兴起</h3><p>2016年之前，几乎所有有组织的学生会都是由研究生员工组成。事实上，只有一个不是：2002年，在马萨诸塞大学阿默斯特分校担任住院助理的本科生成为美国<a href="https://ilr.law.uiowa.edu/sites/ilr.law.uiowa.edu/files/2023-02/Fitzpatrick.pdf">第一个学生住院助理工会</a>。然后，2016 年之后，格林内尔学院、乔治华盛顿大学和里德学院等其他本科生工会组织开始涌现。</p><p>学生——无论是攻读两年制副学士学位、四年制学士学位还是研究生——约占<a href="https://cew.georgetown.edu/wp-content/uploads/Working-Learners-Report.pdf">美国劳动力的 8%</a> 。许多人在俄亥俄州立大学这样的校园环境中工作，我是该大学工程学院的院长，要么是因为校园勤工俭学是其经济援助计划的一部分，要么是因为几乎没有灵活的兼职工作机会传统的18至23岁的学生。</p><p>他们组织的问题与零售和服务行业工会提出的问题密切相关。纽约市立大学劳动与城市研究学院<a href="https://slu.cuny.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Union-Density-2023.pdf">2023 年的一份报告</a>指出，新一波的学生工人工会“包括人文学科和之前沉寂的 STEM 领域的教学和研究助理，以及本科生住宿顾问、学生餐饮服务人员”大厅工作人员和图书馆工作人员。”自 2022 年初以来启动的 30 个新的学生工人集体谈判单位代表了 35,655 名工人——这个数字可能很快就会大幅增加：在加州州立大学，超过 19,300 名学生助理希望最早在 2024 年 1 月就他们的组织努力，这将使他们成为美国历史上 <a href="https://calmatters.org/education/higher-education/college-beat/2023/10/student-workers/">最大的学生工人工会之一</a>。</p><p></p><p> 2022 年标志着另一个变化：学生工人罢工的演变。纽约市立大学的报告列举了 2022 年和 2023 年高等教育工作者举行的 20 次罢工，其中包括教师、博士后和学生，并指出“高等教育界罢工活动的爆炸性增长在近期记忆中是前所未有的。”其中最引人注目的是加州大学研究生工人罢工，持续了五周多，目前被记录<a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/after-historic-strike-uc-grad-students-say-university-isn-t-honoring-pay-agreements">为美国高等教育机构有史以来最大规模的罢工</a>。最终达成了更高工资、费用减免和其他福利的协议。</p><p>一些专家推测，大学校园内工会的发展与校外备受瞩目的组织工作（最近在亚马逊、苹果和星巴克）的发展之间存在<a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/news/faculty-issues/labor-unionization/2023/04/26/were-not-slowing-down-student-workers-say">很强的相关性</a>。事实上，受过大学教育的年轻工人的工会组织一直呈上升趋势。盖洛普报告称，年轻人<a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/354455/approval-labor-unions-highest-point-1965.aspx">对工会的支持率相对较高，为 77%</a> 。</p><h3>值得关注的动力动态</h3><p>在学院和大学校园里，加入工会的学生工人代表了一个独特的群体。一方面，他们与学校的关系是工人与雇主的关系。另一方面，他们还为服务和教育产品付费，从而建立了客户与提供者的关系。</p><p>具有这种双重身份的学校需要将这些学生工人积极分子视为一种新型的利益相关者——一种可以参与并最终保持快乐的利益相关者。加州公共教育总监、加州州立大学董事会当然成员托尼·瑟蒙德 (Tony Thurmond) 在 10 月份关于该校学生会组织工作的新闻发布会上这样说道：“加州州立大学更强大今天，因为学生们正在奋起维护大学系统的使命，为每个学生打开高等教育的大门，为他们创造美好的未来，无论他们的背景如何。”</p><p>面对新组织的员工的企业组织最初通常不会这样看待他们——他们同样必须与他们打交道并最终保持快乐。一些成功的谈判最终使双方达成了这一谅解，尽管只是不情愿。</p><p>值得注意的是，这场学生运动发生的同时，美国企业界的一些雇主<a href="https://time.com/6221176/worker-strikes-employers-unions/">监视并解雇了领导组织工作的工人</a>（根据《国家劳动关系法》，这些行为是非法的）。但企业必须明白，如果他们的价值观与经历过政治倡导经历的新一代学生工不一致，他们将难以招聘。 “我认为工会非常重要，”一名大学二年级学生在其所在学校巴纳德学院 (Barnard College) 的本科生于 10 月份投票支持成立工会后<a href="https://www.marketplace.org/2023/11/06/campus-labor-activism-spreads-to-undergrads/">告诉非营利新闻组织 Marketplace</a> 。 “大学毕业后，我很荣幸能成为其中的一员。”</p><p></p><p>霍特国际商学院的梅根·雷茨 (Megan Reitz) 和《 <a href="https://www.routledge.com/Leadership-Unravelled-The-Faulty-Thinking-Behind-Modern-Management/Cole-Higgins/p/book/9781032033686"><cite>领导力揭秘</cite></a>》一书的合著者约翰·希金斯 (John Higgins) 在他们的文章<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-an-age-of-employee-activism/">《员工激进主义时代的</a>领导》中指出，“我们正在进入一个员工激进主义的时代，这很可能会颠覆我们的假设关于组织内部的权力。”一些商界领袖可能认为这是一种短暂的趋势，但我们大学环境中的许多人都知道学生劳工激进主义正在成为新常态，并认为学习如何满足最新一代工人客户的需求势在必行。公司及其领导者有机会观察这些谈判在大学校园中的进展情况，并了解他们在某些时候也可能面临着协调现有员工和管理层、社区成员、社区成员的不同（也许是不同的）利益的任务。和年轻的员工积极分子。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/meet-tomorrows-workforce-todays-student-labor-activists/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>领导的情感景观</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:00:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker, Natalia Weisz, Vijay Pereira, and Alfredo De Massis. <p>本杰明·莱克<a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">(@drbenlaker</a> ) 是英国雷丁大学亨利商学院的领导力教授。娜塔莉亚·韦兹是阿根廷 IAE 商学院的领导力教授。 Vijay Pereira 是法国 NEOMA 商学院国际和战略人力资本管理领域的杰出教授。 Alfredo De Massis 是意大利博岑-博尔扎诺自由大学、瑞士国际管理发展学院 (IMD) 和英国兰卡斯特大学管理学院的创业和家族企业教授</p>]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managerial Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Teams]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR Navigating a first-time leadership role often mirrors the balancing act of a tightrope walker. On one side, there’s a team seeking direction and inspiration; on the other, higher-ups are scrutinizing each decision. This journey isn’t just about taking on added responsibilities like managing teams and coordinating projects; it’s also about stepping into [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Laker-Emotional-Landscape-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡罗琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p>首次担任领导角色通常反映出走钢丝者的平衡行为。一方面，有一个团队在寻求方向和灵感；另一方面，有一个团队正在寻找方向和灵感。另一方面，高层正在仔细审查每一个决定。这段旅程不仅仅是承担管理团队和协调项目等额外责任；它还涉及到进入一个高度的情感舞台，包括喜悦、自豪、焦虑、恐惧和偶尔的自我怀疑。</p><p>当新领导者晋升组织层级时，他们既面临成功的喜悦，也面临失败的负担，他们的决策的重要性在他们更明显的角色中被放大。在我们即将发表在<cite>BMJ Leader</cite>杂志上的研究中，大约 67% 的新领导者表示，当他们的团队实现里程碑时，他们感到无比自豪。同样，72% 的人表示，当他们的指导对团队成员的成长产生积极影响时，他们感到很高兴。</p><p></p><p>另一方面，压力也显而易见。大约 58% 的受访者承认，在面临关键决策时会感到焦虑，而近一半 (49%) 的受访者表示，他们担心潜在的失误会受到上级的批评。有趣的是，53% 的首次担任领导者偶尔会表达自我怀疑，强调指导和同事支持在应对这一错综复杂的领导领域中的重要性。</p><p>这些挑战的背后是情绪调节这一重要但经常被忽视的领域，它是领导效能的关键决定因素。虽然个人贡献者可能仅凭借技术实力和领域知识而表现出色，但领导力则要求更高水平的情商——不仅是个人情绪调节的能力，还包括识别和管理他人情绪的能力。这种领导情感能力在塑造团队动力方面发挥着关键作用。具有高情商的领导者可以培养动力、士气和绩效。相比之下，那些在这个领域犹豫不决的人可能会创造适得其反和潜在有毒的环境，阻碍创造力并阻碍组织进步。</p><p>无可否认，其他技能和才能对于领导力来说至关重要。然而，正是对情绪的熟练处理和理解，才将一个蓬勃发展的领导者与一个勉强过日子甚至跌倒的领导者区分开来。认识到这一重大细微差别及其对领导力发展的影响，我们的研究团队试图弥合这一知识差距。我们采用了两步方法：首先进行广泛调查，然后进行定性访谈。在线调查问卷针对2000多名新领导者，特别是那些拥有两到五年领导经验的领导者。我们在三个月内收集了反馈，以深入了解他们在工作中的情绪体验。然后，为了更深入地了解，我们选择了100位新领导参加详细访谈。</p><p></p><h3>调节工作情绪：新手领导者指南</h3><p>我们的研究全面审视了领导者面临的实际挑战以及他们在情绪调节领域采用的策略。我们确定了共同趋势和见解，为随后的六种最佳实践提供了信息。</p><p> <strong>1.了解自我意识的作用。</strong>领导力中有效情绪调节的关键是自我意识。领导者应该经常进行内省，问自己“我现在感觉如何？”以及“这种情绪有利于还是阻碍我的领导力？”通过积极解决这些问题，领导者可以更好地理解和调节他们的情绪反应。在我们的研究中，采用这种内省方法的领导者团队士气提高了 45%，决策效率提高了 38%。此外，组织报告称，当领导者实行一致的自我意识时，其整体生产力提高了 32%。采用这种方法不仅可以增强领导能力，而且可以使整个团队和组织切实受益。</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. 通过多样化的反馈增强愿景。</strong>领导者的旅程不是一个人走的，而是一个人走的。来自值得信赖的个人的反馈可以提供宝贵的方向点。建立一个由导师、同事甚至乐于接受的下属组成的圈子，可以让领导者获得超越他们直接观点的见解。这种外部观点可以照亮情感盲点，促进成长和适应。我们的研究强调了这种协作方法的重要性：积极寻求和整合反馈的领导者的变革适应性提高了 60%，团队内的人际关系改善了 45%。在充满活力的领导力格局中，这种​​持续的对话被证明是持续成功的基石。</p><p> <strong>3. 建立可持续领导力的界限。</strong>承担领导角色伴随着更大的责任。然而，永远待命可能会导致倦怠和效率下降。为自己和团队设定明确的界限，可以确保领导者有专门的时间来减压、反思，并以新的活力回归。我们的研究结果强调了这种方法的务实优势：建立并传达明确界限的领导者表示，他们自己的生产力提高了 59%，团队满意度提高了 51%。此外，这些领导者还发现，与压力相关的问题减少了 42%。建立界限并不是为了创造距离，而是为了培养一个让领导者和团队能够最佳运作的环境。</p><p> <strong>4.拥抱真实——脆弱的力量。</strong>领导力的外衣常常伴随着错误的坚忍主义期望或情感化的外表，但真正的领导力可以在真实性和脆弱性中找到。通过承认个人感受并明智地分享这些感受，领导者可以弥合差距，培养更深层次的联系，并在团队内部建立信任。我们的研究发现，接受脆弱性的领导者的团队信任水平提高了 66%，团队凝聚力提高了 49%。此外，这些真诚的领导者报告称，他们自己的工作满意度提高了 38%。在领导力领域，脆弱并不是一种责任；而是一种责任。它是培养信任和真实关系的资产。</p><p></p><p> <strong>5. 制定课外应对策略——平衡的关键。</strong>随着领导力的加强，平衡的需求变得至关重要。在专业领域之外发展应对机制不是奢侈而是必要的。无论是通过体育活动、写日记、参与创意活动，还是珍惜与亲人在一起的时刻，这些追求都提供了重要的情感重置。根据我们的研究，积极采取此类课外应对策略的领导者的工作压力水平降低了 56%，整体幸福感提高了 47%。此外，这些领导者指出，他们在工作场所解决问题的能力提高了 43%。培养有效的应对机制对于领导者的整体成长和角色耐力至关重要。</p><p> <strong>6. 练习呼吸和正念——在混乱中锚定。</strong>在快节奏的决策世界中，解决方案有时很简单：花点时间喘口气。一次深呼吸就能让混乱中的事物立刻变得清晰。将正念和简短的冥想练习融入日常生活中，为平静奠定了基础。通过立足当下，领导者可以应对复杂的情况，而不会被压倒性的情绪所吞噬。我们的研究强调了切实的好处：将定期正念练习融入生活的领导者表示，在高压情况下，他们的情绪恢复能力提高了 50%，清晰度提高了 40%。这种对此时此地的关注是现代领导力成功的基石。</p><h3>持续的平衡努力</h3><p>我们敦促每一位新兴领导者投资于情商培训，并定期进行自我反思，以控制自己的情绪，从而以清晰和坚定的方式领导。从今天开始考虑采取这些行动：</p><p><strong>定期反思。</strong>每天进行 5 到 10 分钟的内省反思，积极剖析你的情绪如何影响你的决定。在日记中记录你的见解，并推动自己在感受和行动之间建立联系。随着日子变成几周，你会发现重复出现的模式会影响你的选择。利用这种新发现的自我意识，并主动引导它在日常生活中做出更好、更明智的决定。</p><p><strong>积极倾听不同声音。</strong>每个月开始时，都打算使您的反馈渠道多样化：选择一位同事、一位团队成员和一位导师来听取他们的见解。以开放的心态进行这些对话，刻意抑制证明或反驳对方观点的本能。通过吸收他们的话语并理解他们的观点，你就为自己提供了一面丰富的、多面的镜子，让你了解别人如何看待你。使用这些宝贵的反馈作为方向指南针，可以引导您走向个人和职业发展。并与您的团队分享您自己的经验：讨论您学到的个人教训或您如何应对挑战可以营造一个让其他人感到安全地分享和学习的环境。</p><p></p><p><strong>定义数字工作边界。</strong>通过在数字环境中建立明确无误的“办公时间”来优先考虑您的福祉，例如晚上 7 点后不要处理与工作相关的电子邮件或消息。 向您的同事明确传达这一界限：树立工作与生活平衡重要性的榜样激励团队成员突破自己的数字限制并保护他们的个人时间。这种积极主动的方法不仅维护个人福祉，而且加强了对工作场所边界的集体尊重。</p><p><strong>发现您的个人重置机制。</strong>每周至少指定一个小时让自己沉浸在与工作无关的爱好或激情中，无论是绘画、跑步还是阅读扣人心弦的小说。认识到这段时间是你神圣的重置时刻——你的思想和灵魂的避难所。公开你的经历和你获得的令人耳目一新的好处可以激励你的团队成员也找到并拥抱他们自己的“重置”激情。这种积极主动的奉献精神不仅丰富了个人的福祉，而且还培养了团队内部整体平衡的文化。</p><p></p><p><strong>从平静呼吸开始。</strong>通过在前两分钟进行深呼吸练习来开始你的一天或关键会议。带头并树立榜样，指导您的团队了解这种平静练习的节奏和好处。通过积极推广这种仪式，您不仅可以使个人思想焕发活力，还可以培养集体的平静感。抓住这个平静的基础，以高度关注和统一的方法来引导讨论、决策或任务。</p><p></p><p>虽然情绪调节似乎只是领导力宏伟计划中的一个小组成部分，但它对于决定领导者的有效性至关重要。如果不加以控制，情绪可能会影响判断、产生冲突或导致冲动的决定。相反，如果运用得当，它们可以激励、激励并推动团队走向伟大。在当今快节奏的工作环境中，个人和职业之间的界限常常变得模糊，对于领导者来说，尤其是那些第一次担任这个角色的领导者，掌握在工作中调节情绪的艺术比以往任何时候都更加重要。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-emotional-landscape-of-leadership/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>领导力发展让我们失望。这是修复方法</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hannes Leroy, Moran Anisman-Razin, and Jim Detert. <p>Hannes Leroy 是伊拉斯姆斯大学鹿特丹管理学院组织与人事管理系副教授。莫兰·阿尼斯曼-拉辛 (Moran Anisman-Razin) 是利默里克大学凯米商学院工作和就业研究系的工作和组织心理学副教授。 Jim Detert 是弗吉尼亚大学达顿商学院工商管理学 John L. Colley 教授，也是<cite>《选择勇气：工作中勇敢的日常指南》</cite> （哈佛商业评论出版社，2021 年）一书的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com Helping managers and high-potential contributors develop better leadership skills can be a critical part of building organizational capabilities — but for many companies, leadership development programs are falling far short. Those responsible for selecting such programs often struggle to show how their spending has produced significant, enduring changes in participants’ individual capacities or [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Leroy-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹尼尔·赫茨伯格/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>帮助管理者和高潜力贡献者培养更好的领导技能可能是建设组织能力的关键部分，但对于许多公司来说，领导力发展计划还远远不够。那些负责选择此类计划的人往往很难证明他们的支出如何对参与者的个人能力或集体成果产生了重大、持久的变化，但运营高管却继续为这些努力提供资金，而无需承担此类责任。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>结果是：一个巨大的领导力发展行业，其中很少有人区分蛇油和有效的治疗药水。</p><p>我们对世界各地几十所商学院的领导力发展项目（LDP）的审查揭示了这些项目的典型缺陷。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>我们调查的项目主管很少能够确定他们的领导力发展产品的设计和评估如何始终符合预期影响的科学标准。例如，大多数人 (70%) 表示，他们满足于对项目的积极反应或所获得知识的证据，而不是记录参与者能力的提高，至少在短期内 (63%)。没有人将他们的计划与参与者的职业轨迹、追随者的态度或绩效、或团队或组织层面的成果的变化联系起来。</p><p></p><p>同样，我们最近对 46 名人力资源高管的采访显示，他们对自民党的选择很少受到有效性证据的强烈指导。相反，大多数人承认，他们在信息有限的情况下做出了这样的决定，通常根据项目的“外观”（例如设计良好的网站）或教师的魅力等因素投入大量资金。正如一位高管指出的那样，领导力发展决策似乎类似于在线约会行业，向左或向右滑动更多地基于外观而不是实质。</p><p>这个问题并非不可避免。通过多年研究领导力发展、开发和交付项目以及与爱立信、微软、飞利浦、红十字会和西门子等组织的首席人力资源官和首席学习官的合作，我们得出了一个简单的前提：领导力发展需要关注三个核心要素——项目的愿景、方法和影响——以及它们之间的整合。</p><p>只需提出几个关于程序的好问题，并仔细解析答案，就可以阐明每个元素的设计以及与其他元素的协调程度，并导致显着更好的决策。本文将解释高质量计划的要素，并概述领导者和计划制定者在确定自民党有效性时应提出的问题。</p><h3>坚实的计划是三条腿站立的</h3><p>领导力发展计划从根本上应该关注参与者的成长。有效的方法将增加参与者的知识、技能或能力。对自民党的任何评估都应从其<em>愿景</em>开始：该计划旨在培养参与者的哪些能力或素质，为什么这很重要，以及它将如何满足特定的发展需求。</p><p>一个好的项目会有非常具体的目标——例如，参与者将发展他们的领导身份，或者提高他们的情商或在压力下批判性思考的能力。并且它将清楚地说明其所依据的基本思想或证据。如果程序开发人员无法告诉您他们的具体愿景是什么，为什么它适合您自己组织的需求和目标，以及它所基于的原则，那么就没有理由认为您会获得有意义的结果。</p><p>如果您没有有效的到达目的地计划，也没有理由认为您会到达理想的目的地。这就是为什么要评估的第二个关键维度是领导力发展计划的<em>方法</em>。这包括课程（例如，参与者将研究说明性案例并学习战略分析的有效技术）和教学/学习方法（例如，参与者将讨论和辩论、进行体验式练习以及建立自己的模型）。</p><p></p><p>自民党评估的第三个组成部分是其<em>影响</em>——参与者和其他利益相关者的预期结果。值得选择的项目可以阐明参与者将如何改变。这最终关系到项目是否能够清楚地解释其预期结果，包括如何评估这些结果。</p><p>我们的经验表明，大多数计划购买者至少会询问有关他们正在考虑的自民党的愿景、方法和影响的隐性问题。然而，我们断言，他们经常提出错误的问题，或者当他们提出更好的问题时，他们太容易满足于不满意的答复。 （请参阅“提出正确的问题”。）由于预算、时间或进行运营变革的权力的限制，他们会被那些承诺简单、新颖、舒适以及参与者高评价的项目所吸引，这是可以理解的。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>提出正确的问题</h4><p class="caption">负责选择有效的领导力发展计划的管理者通常不会收集最有用的信息。他们需要提出更好的问题才能产生更好的结果。 </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile" style="width: 100%"><thead><tr><th style="line-height:1.25;vertical-align:bottom;width:15%;text-align:center;">核心要素</th><th style="line-height:1.25;vertical-align:bottom;width:42.5%">你可能会问什么</th><th style="line-height:1.25;vertical-align:bottom;width:42.5%">你应该问什么</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td rowspan="2" style="vertical-align:middle;text-align:center;"><p><strong>想象</strong></p></td><td><p>参与者会经历个人成长吗？</p></td><td><p>参与者会提高领导他人的能力吗？</p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:white;"><p>参与者是否有动力参加该计划？</p></td><td style="background-color:white;"><p>他们是否有动力运用所学知识？ </p></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="background-color:#e0e0e0;vertical-align:middle;text-align:center;""><p><strong>方法</strong></p></td><td style="background-color:#e0e0e0;"><p>够容易吗？</p></td><td style="background-color:#e0e0e0;"><p>它是否适当复杂？</p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:#e0e0e0;"><p>参与者会感到舒服吗？</p></td><td style="background-color:#e0e0e0;"><p>即使参与者感到不舒服，他们会学习吗？ </p></td></tr><tr><td rowspan="2" style="border-bottom:hidden;vertical-align:middle;text-align:center;""><p><strong>影响</strong></p></td><td><p>我们会改变参与者的内心和想法吗？</p></td><td><p>我们会看到参与者的行为方式发生变化吗？</p></td></tr><tr><td style="background-color:white;"><p>我们如何证明成本的合理性？</p></td><td style="background-color:white;"><p>我们会只花我们认为合理的钱吗？ </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MAG_Leroy_RF_Winter_2024_Table-1-scaled.jpg" alt="提出正确的问题" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p>同样的问题是程序组件之间经常出现错位。需要将愿景、方法和影响力结合成一个完整、一致的整体，才能产生有意义的结果。 （参见“一家公司改善领导力发展的方法”。）但是许多计划都缺少这种一致性。考虑一个承诺培养“具有卓越情商技能的领导者”的计划，该计划首先评估参与者当前的能力，然后提供如何改进的想法。这些组件是错位的，因为该方法不太适合行为技能发展的愿景。更强大的产品将让参与者反复尝试实时评估和管理自己和他人的情绪，并在此过程中提供指导性辅导和纠正。同样，询问参与者是否喜欢情商计划或认为自己有所提高，也无法以与提高技能的愿景相一致的方式评估影响。更有效的评估将使用多源评级来记录项目前后的情商行为能力。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>一家公司改善领导力发展的方法</h4><p class="caption">以下是欧洲一家行业领先的能源巨头如何重新设计领导力发展计划以更好地满足其需求。</p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th>想象</th><th>方法</th><th>影响</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p><strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>面对市场动态、行业监管和公众舆论的变化，首席执行官着手加强整个公司的内部创业行为。作为这一期望变革的一部分，首席执行官认识到公司现有的领导力发展计划（重点是通过有趣的主题和鼓舞人心的演讲者来开发能力）需要从根本上进行修改。</p><p> <strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>重新设计的自民党需要直接以积极实践成功的内部创业所需的行为为目标。因此，新的自民党关注的是项目后的适用性和价值，而不是项目内的福利，如项目的地点或住宿。</p></td><td><p> <strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>新的计划以不同的方式促使管理者走出他们的舒适区。例如，他们参加具有挑战性的户外培训，并与非营利组织合作以拓展他们的内部创业思维。</p><p> <strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>这些项目最初产生了阻力——他们的评价不如以前的自民党有趣和舒适——而且他们的评价也低于以前的项目。该公司将此类反馈视为具有挑战性的增长经历的预期路标，而不是软化其方法的理由。</p></td><td><p> <strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>一年之内，该计划在首席执行官启动重新设计的核心原因上取得了进展：那些愿意接受更多内部创业精神的人正在大声疾呼，那些不愿意加入的人正在离开，以及期望的新行为（追求新的想法、技术、产品和市场）在公司内部扎根。</p><p> <strong><span class="blue">•</span></strong>重新设计了衡量、奖励和其他系统，以便可以跟踪和激励计划目标。学习和发展人员使用数据将资金请求与战略成果联系起来，并要求外部顾问将费用结构与结果联系起来。 </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MAG_Leroy_RF_Winter_2024_Table-2.png" alt="一家公司改善领导力发展的方法" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p></p><h3>关于自民党要问的正确问题</h3><p>如果领导力发展计划有效性的问题源于提出错误的问题和接受糟糕的答案，那么解决方案就从提出更好的问题开始。下面，我们建议了常见查询的六种替代方案。更敏锐的询问应该有助于项目购买者更好地了解项目愿景、方法和影响的整体一致性。</p><p><strong><em>不要问</em>“参与者会经历个人成长吗？”<em>问</em>“参与者会提高领导他人的能力吗？”</strong>练习瑜伽或太极拳。写日记。锻炼身体并饮食良好。冥想。职业规划。减少混乱。成长的机会几乎是无限的。作为个人，我们中的许多人都投入了资源来学习上述活动，并声称从中发展了。但是，尚不清楚我们的能力带领他人朝着共同的目标迈进。</p><p>那么，为什么这些和许多其他类似的活动经常在领导力发展中包括？精明的供应商知道，让组织赞助据称与领导力相关的东西要比称其为什么要容易得多：值得的人类发展可能与成功领导他人所需的关键行为有任何关系。问题在于，将太多的事情与领导力发展相关联通常会使它变得越来越少，而不是更多。而且这种过于广泛的标签有助于解释为什么组织在良好时期时可能会为这些类型的学习经历提供资金 - 了解它们可能会促进更广泛的目标，例如个人福祉和领导能力的长期增长 - 但很快就削减了看起来像有趣的东西预算紧张时的特权。我们中的一位以前在一所大学教授领导技能编程的大学中，包括学习高尔夫和餐饮礼节。毫不奇怪，大多数教师都指出这样的课程是在认为领导力发展是一项不必要的不​​值得认真的教育机构的努力。</p><p>这就是为什么保持程序的远见和中心很重要的原因。所提出的计划与有效领导他人的能力以及在什么时间范围内如何相关？需要解释这项学习如何直接有助于领导的关键方面。这并不是说除了坚果和螺栓技能培训（例如设定目标和激励他人）之外，没有什么可以与领导成功联系在一起，但是需要明确建立链接。</p><p>对有效领导力发展的研究表明，将参与者学习到<em>需求分析</em>的重要性 - 对组织目标或角色需求之间的差距和学习者当前能力之间的差距进行评估。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>一些自由顾展提供商，例如咨询公司Mercuri Urval，拒绝与不会从需求分析开始的组织合作，从而确定与公司背景和战略相关的领导挑战，因为这是证明自由顾问的ROI和Impact的关键。</p><p><strong><em>而不是问</em>“他们会被激励参加吗？”<em>问</em>“他们会被激励使用他们学到的东西吗？”</strong>我们大多数人都没有动力去医疗约会，因为我们发现他们很愉快。只有当我们认为他们将帮助我们保持健康或使我们恢复健康时，我们才会去。也就是说，我们不是受到经验本身的动力，而是基于我们收到的建议和治疗方法的实用性。</p><p>我们认为，相同的逻辑应该适用于选择有限公司，但是我们已经看到，为其娱乐价值而不是其有用性选择了程序。应根据参加该计划的期望来选择程序，而不是基于设计主要诱使他们参加的功能。</p><p></p><p>当然，参加的动机是相关的 - 但与随后使用所学的东西，即<em>转移的动机</em>并不相同。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>来自与参与者的目标或问题相关的编程，以便在随后的情况下有目的地召回和应用。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>这就是为什么直接将学习和发展与在职体验之间的联系可能如此强大的原因，尽管它比课堂学习更具挑战性。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>简而言之，领导力发展计划的课程是根据参与者在参加后能够和动力做什么的证据的选择计划，而不是他们对露面的兴奋。告诉参与者该计划将如何对解决他们关心的内容有用，并确保该程序明确执行此操作。当参与者像患者一样，认为他们的处方治疗将减轻他们的困扰或促进健康，他们将受到动力保持参与。</p><p><strong><em>而不是问</em>“足够容易吗？”<em>问</em>“它适当复杂吗？”</strong>当您上飞机时，您是否希望飞行员的训练容易方便？当然不是。您希望它已经足够严格且适当地复杂，以便飞行员知道在遇到意外的天气或遇到飞行中设备故障时该怎么办。您希望对飞机飞行路径的空中交通管制员也是如此。您希望他们的培训旨在为他们做好准备，以熟练地使用他们所学到的知识，而不是最大化其他目标。相比之下，领导力发展计划经常旨在最大程度地提高参与者的便利性或最大程度地减少对被认为更重要的工作的干扰。</p><p>有效学习的科学清楚地表明，在努力时，学习更深，更耐用。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>这意味着，如果您希望参与者可靠地将他们学到的知识编码为长期记忆中的知识，并能够可靠地检索和使用他们在各种相关环境中学到的知识，则需要做所有参与者和参与者的事情教育工作者的实时吸引力较小。这包括分隔学习而不是将其纳入一个块；在整个主题中介绍了新主题，而不是坚持一个主题，直到参与者掌握为止。并改变实践条件。这些技术可以使运营最不发达国家更具挑战性，但对于支持最终目标至关重要：学习的持续转移和改善的结果。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p>事实是，如果某些事情足够重要以值得大量投资，那么它也可能会变得足够复杂，因此必须优先考虑疗效。</p><p><strong><em>而不是问</em>“参与者会舒服吗？”<em>问</em>“即使参与者不舒服，也会学到吗？”</strong>对参与者的舒适感的担忧似乎指导了太多程序的设计。很明显为什么会这样；在立即进行后图满意度调查上得分不佳的程序可能不会再次资助。但是，荟萃分析研究的证据表明，喜欢教育经验与从中学习，短期满意度与所学知识的转移之间通常没有显着的关系。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>我们从经验和文献中都知道，增长是通过审判和苦难的坩埚经历而来的，而不是目前的舒适。</p><p></p><p>例如，它已经确定，发展涉及摆脱一个人的舒适区 - 面对而不是避免挑战性的体验 - 例如，更高强度的实践（例如，身体上或情感上的征税）会带来更大的改进（只要它停止之前停止超负荷的点）。我们还从心理学中知道，避免或最小化不适的持续时间或强度实际上会干扰学习新模式并取代旧模式。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>简单地说，您不会通过隐藏对公开演讲的厌恶或对人际关系的挑战。您通过在支持性学习环境中面对他们来做到这一点。这与认知行为疗法的核心是一致的：为了可持续地改变您的行为，您必须浮出水面，挑战，重新诠释和取代目前与困难情况相关的无益思想和感觉。这并不容易或舒适，但是有效。</p><p>这就是为什么该公司大胆（超越户外领导力发展）试图通过在挑战荒野探险中扩展参与者超越舒适区域来推进传统的户外培训的原因。在新颖，高压力背景的高压煮者环境中，鼓励参与者尝试建立或磨练领导能力的新行为。大胆的设计经验，创造出来自自我成长的更深，更持久的幸福感，而不是直接但短暂的幸福感直接与享受体验本身有关。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>实际上，由于经历的增长，长期满意度得分通常很高。</p><p><strong><em>而不是问</em>“我们会改变参与者的心灵吗？”<em>问</em>“我们会看到参与者的行为方式的变化吗？”</strong>这是我们警惕的另一个指导信念：如果您改变人们的思想，就会改变他们的行为。这听起来不错，但至少有两个原因是有问题的：改变行为引导信念非常困难，而且态度与行为之间的联系总的来说，这并不是那么牢固。如果这听起来是违反直觉的，请考虑人们认为锻炼对他们有益的频率，他们的健康渴望，甚至他们每天锻炼30分钟的意图也不会可靠地导致所需的行为 - 实际上是在锻炼。</p><p>有充分的文献证明，成年后，人们在看待世界的方式上有很大差异 - 例如，他们如何优先考虑不同的价值观以及他们认可不同的信念。成人的态度深深地根深蒂固，无法改变，无法改变干预措施，以至于可能会改变他们。</p><p>即使很容易改变态度，数十年的研究表明，这可能会转化为持续行为改变的可能性很小。通常，态度不能很好地预测相关行为。仅当人们有意识地建立具体的行为承诺和问责过程并完成与新习惯相关的艰苦工作时，它们才变得更加可靠地联系。其他研究表明，将价值变化视为行为改变的期望产物（不是其原因）是有用的，因为我们对所做工作的感觉可以影响我们的信念。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p>多样性，公平和包容性的学者非常清楚，专注于DEI信念或态度的领导力计划可能会使日常行为在很大程度上保持不变。即使对态度表现出明显积极影响的计划也经常对行为影响有限。这是否反映了将态度变化与行为改变的一般挑战，还是其他可能性 - 人们经常拥护不反映其实际信念的价值观，也许是因为他们知道社会接受的立场是什么，结果是相同的。改变人们所说的话很少是最终的最终愿景，这通常是他们随后的行为的差异。那么，为什么不衡量什么趋于重要的事情：开发计划之后的人会做些不同的事情。</p><p><strong><em>而不是问</em>“我们将如何证明支出合理？”<em>问</em>“我们只花我们可以证明什么？”</strong>那些经营任何规模的运营单位的人都类似于风险投资者和贷款官：他们对（重新）投资合理的机会不感兴趣，因为他们自己的结果取决于他们的收益。 LDP的ROI的固体案例。例如，沟通顾问南希·杜阿尔特（Nancy Duarte）建议，例如，如果您认为俯仰教练是销售人员的宝贵开发领域，那么您的计划应包括一个计划，以跟踪参与者在计划期间如何使用和练习的计划，以及他们是否会增加。合同续订或新销售。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>或者，如果您要雇用合作伙伴来交付新墨西哥那样，请坚持认为它的结果也可以投资。考虑一下印度一家咨询公司大湖管理学院的例子：它具有绩效付费费用结构，其中一定比例的薪酬直接与参与者的明显后计划变更有关。</p><p>对于领导力发展中的人来说，这是一个更具挑衅性的想法：如果您不能为投资提供令人信服的案例，请不要花费您分配的钱。通过预算金额产生巨大的结果并不会迫使未来的投资；相反，它通过强化怀疑论者的信念来破坏它，认为回报不值得花钱。因此，如果您知道只有两倍的分配才能期望有意义的结果，请考虑为为什么只每隔一年运行该程序来制定令人信服的解释。拒绝花费您可能会感到冒险的事情，但是这样做的勇气可能是激发对领导力发展的长期支持所需要的。</p><p>这些都不意味着唯一有用的投资是可以直接与财务成果联系起来的投资。这是对人类发展的一种有限的观点，它忽略了员工成长和福祉也与个人和组织目标间接相关的众多方式。但这并不能消除对良好领导力发展至关重要的严格思维和声音衡量的必要性。</p><h3>与计划开发人员合作以获得更好的结果</h3><p>打破浪费资源的循环和领导力发展计划的令人失望的结果并不仅仅来自购买者对计划的更严格的评估。除非关键的利益相关者在事实之后停止互相责备并开始建设性地前期合作，否则不太可能发生。需要的是赞助领导力发展的高级管理人员与选择，管理和交付的人力资源人员和/或计划开发人员之间的更强的伙伴关系。没有其他方面都无法使视力，方法和影响保持一致。</p><p></p><p>在健康的合作伙伴关系中，双方都在桌上席位，同意承认他们对什么是什么，应该是什么，并同意在事情不起作用时进行更改。例如，领导力发展人员可能会以方便交付时间表的要求更加努力地撤回，并拒绝专注于计划满意度得分。他们可以致力于将编程及其结果链接到关键的组织目标方面做得更好。就他们而言，运营高管可能会停止抱怨发展使参与者远离他们的“现实工作”，并在评估程序时开始超越短期成果。同样，高级领导者可以停止将LDP资金与短期运营结果联系起来，这是一种常见的做法，它可能会花更多的时间来调整对可用资源的计划，而不是在最佳且明显地满足参与者需求的方式上。领导者可以通过在工作中利用新的行为时积极认识并在经济上奖励人们来支持所学到的知识。</p><p></p><p>从领导力发展计划中期望更多的时间很长。我们知道要提出的问题和期望的答案。最需要的是关键决策者的集体意愿去做所需的事情。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leadership-development-is-failing-failing-us-heres-how-to-fix-it/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>问三阴：怎样才能让会议不那么痛苦？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-make-make-meetings-less-painful/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-make-meetings-meetings-less-painful/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang是首席执行官教练，并领导杜克大学的Fuqua/Coach K领导力与道德中心（Cole）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Building]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[We love to hate meetings, and it can often seem that the one thing we all agree on is that they’re the reason we aren’t getting any real work done. But does it have to be this way? Sanyin Siang, who writes MIT Sloan Management Review’s Coaching for the Future-Forward Leader advice column, doesn’t think [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AmcDLkcHsFk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p>我们喜欢讨厌会议，似乎我们都同意的一件事是，这是我们没有完成任何真正的工作的原因。但事情一定要这样吗？写<cite>Mit Sloan Management评论</cite><a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/coaching-for-the-future-forward-leader/">为未来领导者建议专栏的教练的</a>Sanyin Siang并不这么认为。实际上，她认为在许多情况下，它们实际上可以帮助您的员工重新加入和重新连接。</p><p>在这个简短而有见地的视频中，Sanyin为为什么我们需要将人际关系和人际关系视为会议的重要组成部分，并解释了如何做到这一点。她讨论了机会会议提供了其他沟通渠道，例如Slack和Email，根本无法提供。她分享了一些关于如何更战略性地进行会议的想法，以期建立团队成员对彼此的理解并扩展自己的资源。</p><p></p><p>到本视频结束时，您将有更好的了解如何将会议转变为建立信任，促进理解和推动有意义进步的强大工具。有关如何让会议期待的更多建议，请阅读Sanyin关于此主题的专栏：“ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/">Ask Sanyin：为什么我们不能正确地开会呢？</a> ”</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-make-meetings-meetings-less-painful/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> AI的操作安全：雪佛龙的Ellen Nielsen</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulation-for-safety-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulation-for-safety-chevrons-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham（ <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ）是波士顿学院Carroll管理学院信息系统系的教授，也是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Reviews</cite>的人工智能和商业策略Big Ideas Initiative的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh是BCG的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美BCG Gamma（BCG的AI实践）的coeader。可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>与他联系。</p><p class="mt20"><cite>我，我本人和AI</cite>是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>和Boston Consulting Group的合作播客，由Sam Ransbotham和Shervin Khodabandeh主持。我们的工程师是David Lishansky，协调的制作人是Allison Ryder和SophieRüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Digital Solutions]]></category><category><![CDATA[Energy Industry]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Ellen Nielsen, Chevron’s first chief data officer, sees data as the common thread throughout a career that has spanned systems, digital data, procurement, and supply chain. In her current role, she applies what she’s learned to Chevron’s wide-ranging AI and machine learning initiatives, including the use of robots and computer vision to inspect tanks, digital [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>雪佛龙第一位首席数据官埃伦·尼尔森 (Ellen Nielsen) 将数据视为贯穿系统、数字数据、采购和供应链的整个职业生涯的共同主线。在目前的职位上，她将所学到的知识应用到雪佛龙广泛的人工智能和机器学习计划中，包括使用机器人和计算机视觉来检查储罐，使用数字孪生来模拟操作，以及使用传感器来监控炼油厂的设备。</p><p>在<cite>ME，我本人和AI</cite>播客的这一集中，Ellen分享了综合能源巨头的机器学习和生成性AI的用例，她描述了公司的公民发展计划，该计划将安全，确保AI和机器学习工具放入整个雪佛龙的雇员之手。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E5-Nielsen-Chevron-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="艾伦·尼尔森"></p><h4>埃伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen），雪佛龙</h4><p>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）是雪佛龙（Chevron）的首席数据官，她专注于创建与价值链思维合作的面向数据的文化。尼尔森（Nielsen）是多学科领导者，拥有30多年的全球经验，作为IT，数字，数据，采购和供应链的高管。她曾与石油和天然气的行业领导者合作，快速移动的消费品，汽车，制造业，零售以及银行和保险。</p><p>尼尔森（Nielsen）是行业活动的常规发言人，并获得了许多奖项和认可，包括被<cite>CDO杂志</cite>的2023年全球数据能力女性名单命名。她在2023年DataIQ 100名单中也排名第五，在美国数据中最有影响力的人中最有影响力的人。</p><p>她还在包括PIDX（石油行业数据交换）和数据和AI女性领导者的各种董事会中任职。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn领导者的AI<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite>播客，请在LinkedIn上与我们进行对话。今天加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI的AI</a> 。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入»</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple播客</a>， <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google播客</a>上订阅<cite>我，我自己和AI</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>数字双胞胎？工程生产的AI？在今天的一集中，找出一家石化公司如何系统地提高其劳动力，从而受益于《生成AI》（Generative AI）。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>我是雪佛龙（Chevron）的艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen），你在听<cite>我，我自己和人工智能</cite>。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎<cite>我，我本人和AI</cite> ，这是商业中人工智能的播客。每个情节，我们都会向您介绍与AI创新的人。我是波士顿学院分析教授Sam Ransbotham。我还是<cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite>的AI和业务战略嘉宾编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是BCG的高级合伙人Shervin Khodabandeh，也是我们AI业务的领导者之一。自2017年以来，<cite>麻省理工学院SMR</cite>和BCG一直在研究和发布AI，采访了数百名从业者，并对成千上万的公司进行调查，以建立，部署和扩展AI功能并真正改变组织的运作方式。</p><p>大家好。今天，山姆和我正在与雪佛龙公司首席数据官艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）交谈。艾伦，感谢您抽出宝贵的时间与我们交谈。欢迎来到节目。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>谢谢你有我。今天我很高兴的交谈我真的很高兴。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>让我们开始。我可以想象我们的大多数听众 - 实际上，所有这些听众都听说过人字形，但他们可能不知道的是AI在雪佛龙的所有价值链中普遍存在的程度。因此，也许告诉我们一些有关您的角色以及在雪佛龙的AI的使用方式。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>也许谈论我的角色……它始于三年前。我是雪佛龙（Chevron）的第一任数据官。这并不意味着我们（尚未一直在处理）很长一段时间的数据，但是需要更多地专注于数据开始出现，因此，我的任务是传播数据 - 驱动的决策，当然也包括任何类型的数据科学/分析。看到它随着时间的推移而增长非常非常有趣。</p><p>我们在许多地方使用AI。我们使用机器人的某些区域（例如，在坦克检查中），您可以想象这很麻烦，让人参与其中。现在我们使用机器人来做到这一点。我们基本上将人类从这些狭窄的空间中夺走，这是计算机视觉的结合 - 拍摄图像，比较图像 - 并[对该坦克和该设备的状态如何进行预测。生锈了吗？它需要维护吗？我们是否需要以非常预测的方式处理它，以便将来以更可靠和安全的方式运行？</p><p>另一个例子是，当我们谈论压缩机或任何类型的设备中的传感器时，过去，我们当然是安装它们的，但是对于这些传感器和数据收集的价格急剧下降，我最近看到了……实际上，这是一项已创建的公民开发应用程序，因为必须安装这些传感器，并且在安装它们时，您基本上采用QR码，然后单击一下，您可以将地理空间位置添加到传感器，然后您可以在地图上看到所有这些传感器，因此您实际上看到了……正在发生的事情以及事物是否实际工作以及哪些传感器已经库存。因此，我们在这里结合了计算机愿景，使用公民开发，当然，在机器学习中使用传感器，基于AI的方式来进行预测以及它们的工作方式。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我知道您做得很好的一件事是数字双胞胎。也许您可以对该示例发表一些评论。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>数字双胞胎是我们使用的众多例子之一。哪些触发了数字双胞胎的触发器？一个是，您可以想象我们在该领域里有人，因此我们希望使他们的生活更轻松，更安全。这意味着，我们可以收集的有关现场资产以及如何运营它们的数据和更多的信息将达到更安全，更可靠的目的。那是一个触发因素。</p><p>第二个触发因素是，您可以根据物联网，[工业]物联网设备，感官……收集大量信息，然后将其输入另一个信息库中，您可以在这些信息中推动这些资产中的预测性决策。因此，使用数字双胞胎，我们基本上希望两者兼而有之：我们希望变得更安全，可靠，但也可以对我们所做的事情更具预测性，这对效率和正确的时间做正确的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您能为我们提供一个使用数字双胞胎的地方的特定例子吗？这如何帮助安全？这如何帮助提高效率？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>如果您服用数字双胞胎，可以说，您基本上是“数字双人”设施，炼油厂……所以在炼油厂中，您可以想象有很多管道，有很多设备，有很多压缩机，有一些发电机 - 有些事情在机械上非常有效，人们必须维护这些产品才能将产品淘汰。</p><p>当您看到产品的价值链或材料进来并出现产品时，这之间的一切都会通过此炼油厂。而且，如果您拥有数字二线的所有内容，则可以更好地计划，您可以更好地运作。您知道什么时候进来了。您可以更好地预测如何获得更好的输出。这基本上就是我们在运营的炼油厂或设施中的工作方式 - 真正查看信息的流程和数据驱动的决策。</p><p>我们一直在通过信息进行决定，你知道吗？在过去触手可及的信息以驱动这一点。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个很好的例子。我认为长期的听众会知道Shervin和我都是化学工程师。但是您可能不知道 - 好吧，我不再是化学工程师，部分原因是我被模拟化学过程的想法所吸引。我们发现我们不必构建一些过程来测试某些东西。我们可以在计算机上构建并进行测试。而且您知道，那是很久以前的，那时确实是一些丑陋的，丑陋的工具。我猜想您比这更复杂 - 或者我希望您比这要复杂得多。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>我认为这是一个总是不断发展的空间，但我对机会感到非常兴奋。我可以想象，您知道，当您有催化剂或必须测试原材料时，您必须用生产负责人进行计划，必须停止生产，您必须进行实时测试。那带走了输出。</p><p>现在，您可以以一种更有效的方式模拟规格，而不再进行身体进行。我也曾在过去的公司中，在过去的公司中，我们不得不一遍又一遍地测试事物，甚至在实验室中进行物理测试。我认为[这些时代大多是]结束了。它变得越来越多地模拟了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>艾伦，您能给我们另一个例子，也许是在探索或提取的情况下，或者在没有数据和AI的情况下曾经是相当体验，昂贵且危险的东西吗？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>我认为我们也有一个很好的例子，实际上是从去年年底（]年底）发布的。当您考虑石油和天然气时，您会考虑一下，如何从水库中获得更多？您想从水库中获得最大的收益，并以一种非常有效，负责任的方式做到这一点。而且，通过收集数据，您可以想象，如果您没有计算机电源，而不是以数字方式的数据，那就很麻烦了。我无法想象人们过去是如何做到的。他们可能正在打印物品并将其放在上面，并提出基于假设的经验 - 当然，他们获得了很多经验。现在，我们使用机器学习，算法来做到这一点。我们了解岩石成分是如何的。我们甚至创建了一个“ Rockopedia”，以了解什么是不同的岩石条件和构图，以便我们每天都可以在需要时利用这些数据。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，我认为有一个更大的主题，随着这些技术的出现，天空的限制是极限，所以问题是，您还能应用它，您还能处理什么？而且我认为这使我提出了有关任务和目的的问题，因为显然有大量数据。显然有很多工具。用例是由任务驱动的，以及我们想对此做些什么。</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong>是的。实际上，我将其链接在雪佛龙（Chevron）上，将其与我们的战略联系起来。我们进行更高的回报，并安全地降低碳。这是我们的指导原则：我们所做的一切当然都应该使公司成功，公司的影响，但在低碳环境中也是如此。我们知道几十年来世界（看起来）不同。我们照顾甲烷，照顾温室[燃气]排放，总体上照顾了碳足迹。因此，这是我们总是要解决的问题。数据和人工智能在我们的运作方式和安全操作方式中发挥作用，但也发挥了作用。安全是雪佛龙价值系统的重要组成部分。当您思考未来并考虑AI，机器人和数字双胞胎以及所有这些时，我们可以帮助我们的员工以更安全，更加可靠的方式以及以新的方式来帮助我们的员工来做更安全，更加可靠地完成工作将来。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我对雪佛龙或主要是工程和科学公司的公司对我来说是什么有趣的是，当AI投入生产中以增强工人，工程师和科学家正在做出的一些决策和一些见解。但是，作为工程师，作为这些植物的运营商，我可能不太同意。我不知道这是否引起共鸣：您如何使科学家和工程师使用这些工具感到舒适？</p><p><strong>艾伦·尼尔森（Ellen Nielsen）：</strong> MM嗯。我认为这实际上是有帮助的，因为工程师的心态非常合乎逻辑，他们了解科学，而且我们有很多科学人员。因此，当您谈论数据科学及其背后的事物时，我们有很多人对学习数据科学非常感兴趣，我们也会说我们已经开始提供教育。所以我想，“我从哪里开始？”您从学习开始：“嘿，我不明白。”这是一种典型的工程思维方式：“我不明白；我想了解它。我正在寻找&#39;它告诉我什么？它如何影响我的解决方案？&#39;”</p><p>我们已经有一段时间的数字奖学金计划了。实际上，我们与麻省理工学院（MIT）一起做这件事，在那里我们有一年的同伙，而他们并没有从一个部门出来。他们确实从整个公司中脱颖而出，一年内经历了设计工程硕士的经历，这确实是一件艰难的事情。但是他们回来了，了解新技术，理解……我们如何以不同的方式使用它。他们是第一个回到正常环境中的人，影响着其他人从知识中参与并冒险进入不同的事物，也许他们以前从未尝试过。因此，这是影响文化的一件事。</p><p>第二件事：在数据科学领域，我们开始与赖斯大学合作。我们还有一个六个月的计划，整个公司也在整个公司中，不仅让人们了解数据科学的含义，而且还将其带回了环境。 So they are not leaving their role completely. They go in six months, seven months, and then they return back in the best way possible to influence the company: “Hey, what is possible?”</p><p> The last piece is maybe the broadest way because we call it <em>citizen development</em> . We believe that many, many people in the company get things in their hands now with the evolution of AI. And we just saw gen AI is now in the hands of … everybody who wants it. And with this kind of citizen development overall, we want to bring the technology, which has become much easier, to many people so that they can use it. And, of course, they need data for this, and that&#39;s why we provide the data in these systems — to be more self-efficient. So I would say there is a three-prong kind of approach to influence the culture, leadership, and we have really nice [use] cases over in AI citizen development. We are also publicly talking about it with certain use cases we do. I think that&#39;s the culture piece. It takes a while to get into every artery of the company, but I feel there is really excitement in the company right now to go down that road.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I like about what you&#39;re saying is that [you&#39;re] actually doubling down on the predominantly engineering and scientific culture of the company and making this a cross-disciplinary collaboration between science and engineering and AI, versus any of these replacing each other. It&#39;s an <em>and</em> , not an <em>or</em> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Is there a specific example you have where someone has gone to one of these seven-month programs or the digital scholar program and brought back something that&#39;s made some change, made a difference?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, definitely. So we have many because we are, I think, two or three years into this, and, of course, they bring it back and solve several issues. We even have this sometimes with internships; after two or three weeks, they recognized they could solve a planning issue [that] they were chewing on … and it was pretty complex, but with the new views and data and artificial intelligence, the outcomes were really stunning.</p><p> We actually have somebody also influencing the planning of our field — field development — and creating a low-code environment, and really this breaks in and it really changes the way we work.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> In terms of making the company more productive, more efficient, ensuring it&#39;s safe, ensuring that it does good for people and communities and environment and species in all different forms, what has been challenging?有什么难的？</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> I would say there definitely are some challenging parts. This is an early-stage technology, especially the gen AI. Things are moving very fast. So, what is challenging [is], whatever you do today might be different in three months. The challenging part is, you cannot work in the same way you worked maybe in the past. You have to maybe pivot faster. It&#39;s not that you build a solution. I think a company told me they built a solution and that, six months later, if they [were to] build it now again, they would do it totally differently. So you have to watch when you — I call it maybe put the eggs in a basket. You have to think about what&#39;s the right timing for what kind of use case and figure this out because you don&#39;t want to lock yourself in when the technology is still in that kind of an evolution stage. This is something that we watch.</p><p> And then the second thing is, not everything in terms of security or handling data in the right way is solved yet in generative AI. That&#39;s just … the technology&#39;s not ready. There are no solutions yet. And you can build a kind of sandbox or kind of a fenced environment, but you have to fence it by yourself. And I think the hyperscalers, like Microsoft and so on, I think they&#39;re working on also adapting those use cases in their normal landscape, where you can have an authorization process, where you have an excess process, how you&#39;re administering and governing this the right way. So this is, I would say, still missing.</p><p> I&#39;m very hopeful that this will be closed very fast, but today, you have to pull different technologies. If it&#39;s a vector database — we&#39;ll talk a little bit of tech-tech language here — it&#39;s not all ready to be used on a really wide scale very safely. And you have to imagine, if you have a corporation, there are rights in terms of what information can be shared, what should not be shared, and so on. And that&#39;s something that we think is a challenge.</p><p> The third challenge I want to mention is the policy makers, you know. So we follow this very closely with responsible AI. We are a member of the Responsible AI Institute and watching very carefully what&#39;s happening there. What kind of policies are coming around the corner? How do we incorporate that responsibly into our operations, into our productization of AI models? And that&#39;s, of course, evolution. It&#39;s not something you can buy and run it. And, yeah, we&#39;ll see how companies are filling these gaps.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Ellen, can you comment on generative AI, and if and how it&#39;s being used or planned to be used?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. We [had been] following generative AI already since two years or so, maybe a little longer. We were not totally surprised by the development. Maybe you can say, “OK, when was ChatGTP coming?” That was maybe a surprise for everybody — that it was coming so fast. But we were watching this and already did some use cases on a kind of innovative sandbox environment to see what that will be. And when it came out, we said, “OK, this is new technology. We want to understand it. We [put] it into the hands of the people and use it, and then understand the telemetry of &#39;What do we use it for, and how does it resonate?&#39;”</p><p> In May/June, we decided to put a more dedicated team on those activities, and we have hundreds of use cases now in the pipeline, which we down-select to the most prominent ones and approach them. But technologywise, we are really, I would say, very much on top of what&#39;s going on and have really super smart people working on it.</p><p> I can tell you my own use case. I use it for writing things down. You can talk about maybe writing your performance agreement with your supervisor or with your team. You check on presentations or documentation you have to do to really optimize the writing. I know that my team is using it because we are thinking in product development and product management and portfolio management. So in the past, they took much longer to write down their thinking, and I talked with one of my team members and she said, “You know, in the past, it took me maybe one or two weeks. Now it takes me one hour to get this done.” So there are lots of efficiencies in using, let&#39;s say, ChatGTP in the space.</p><p> When we look into other examples, you can imagine we have knowledge databases. We have knowledge around system engineering and other information we have available within the company on a very broad scale. And in the past, if you wanted to know how this generator works, you had to basically type in search criteria and then finally you found the document, and you had to read the document. Or this document was not enough; you need another document. OK, you find the second document, then you complete, basically, your answer, and then you go back [and] basically execute on it.</p><p> We have created a chat system where you can [more easily] collaborate with this kind of information and figure this out much faster. So these are maybe two — maybe one more on a daily thing and one more maybe related to kind of how we work in the systems approach.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> If I combine some of your ideas, I see some difficulties. So earlier on, you were talking about citizen developers and the idea of putting a lot of these tools in the hands of people. And then, later, you were talking about problems of security and policy that are not part of the infrastructure yet. Historically, security always follows features. We care about features first, and then we care about security. So we have the combination of a widespread proliferation of tools among citizen developers and low infrastructural guardrails or policies, and then concern about inability to fast-follow. Those seem like they could smash together and create a lot of tension. How do you navigate that?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, I would say maybe we have to talk about AI in general and then generative AI. So when I talk about policy makers, this was more the generative AI perspective.</p><p> When you think about citizen development, we have models, or algorithms, in the box. We have proven [them]; we have secured [them]. They have followed a review process. We checked on them in terms of responsible AI. So they are ready to use for any citizen developer who wants to use that. So they are secured and safe, and they are actually in our safe environment. So you can already start there and make it safe. But the new technology which is coming on the gen AI, with these large language models and the data behind it where the large language models learn from, that&#39;s maybe not ready yet to put into a citizen development perspective. So to make this very clear, when I talk about citizen development, everything — what is secured, kind of the telemetries there, the space is there — we have ensured that we are doing the right thing. This is made available for everyone in the company.</p><p> And the other things which are maybe not secure yet, we are not putting that into the system.我们正在等待。 So we cannot just afford to have unsecured things in our citizen development program.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah, that brings out a nice sort of differentiation between the ideas that citizen data-ship, data scientists can&#39;t just build. … There&#39;s a curation process that goes on. And it sounds like you&#39;re pretty active in that curation process in deciding what tools go to citizen developers and which tools you&#39;re still investigating and you&#39;re protecting.这就说得通了。</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, that&#39;s it;确切地。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Chevron is obviously a giant petrochemical company out there worldwide.每个人都知道。 And you&#39;re the chief data officer.你是怎么到达那里的？ Tell us a little bit about your history. How did you get to this role?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, I&#39;m happy to be in this role. It&#39;s a super exciting area I&#39;m always passionate about. When you follow the start of my career, I&#39;m from Germany. I did a system engineering degree and then ventured out into digital data — later on, to procurement and supply chain. I think the big red thread throughout my whole career is the data part, but of course in different ways. So one can say, when I ventured out into supply chain, you deal with a lot of money from the company bought by third parties. How do you organize that? And there&#39;s a lot of data and thinking and strategic thinking about how you do that. And I would say I&#39;m a learner. I&#39;m a humble learner. I like to embrace new things and very diverse perspectives for the best of the company, and it&#39;s just by coincidence maybe that I got into this role, because when I joined Chevron five years ago, I started in a procurement space because I have a procurement and a data digital leg, I would call it.</p><p> We tackled data right away because the data was not sufficient to drive these decisions, and maybe the first two years proved me right in terms of “that&#39;s possible.” I&#39;m also a big believer that data and AI will be all around us. So this is an exciting space to be in and to learn and to see what&#39;s coming next there.</p><p> So I&#39;m just happy to be there. Actually, a former executive said, when I said to him — not in Chevron — “I&#39;m so lucky at all the opportunities I&#39;ve had in my career,” and he said, “Ellen, you are not lucky.” So he sent me a book; you basically condition your path, so you&#39;re open to things even when you think it&#39;s not on your direct trajectory but it&#39;s really enhancing your skills and how you connect the dots. I like connecting the dots, and that&#39;s why I&#39;m enjoying this role.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a great story.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK, so these are a series of rapid-fire questions we ask. Just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind.</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> It&#39;s kind of a speed-dating question, maybe.好的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What do you see as the biggest opportunity for AI right now?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Health care.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What is the biggest misconception about AI?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Replacing human beings.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What was the first career you wanted?你长大后想做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> I didn&#39;t want to sit [at] a desk.我失败了。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> AI is being used in our daily lives a lot. When is there too much AI?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> I would say too much AI would be, if it guides me in the wrong direction and influences me in a way which is not based on the real facts.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> I already have too much AI in my car because I cannot open the garage, because it recognizes where I am and which thing it has to open, and if it doesn&#39;t work, I can&#39;t get in.</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> I enjoy this. We have a pretty smart home here with all kinds of voice recognition electronics, garage door opener, sprinklers, starters, and whatever. But, I would say, it helps to be more efficient, and if the network is down, that&#39;s really hard now, you know?</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s right. So last question: What is the one thing you wish AI could do right now that it can&#39;t?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Hmm;治愈癌症。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very good.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> It seems like there&#39;s a headline every week that this new AI thing is going to solve cancer, and then you look back and none of these seem to pan out. I&#39;m not saying we should quit trying, but it&#39;s always the example, and it seems like it never quite gets there.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But it&#39;s a little bit of a stochastic process, too, right? I mean, if you have enough trials at it, right? We&#39;re for sure trying a lot more things because of AI and our ability to experiment.</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Can I answer it maybe slightly differently? So I think the other thing would be what AI maybe cannot do which would be great [is] really help us with the climate transition, the climate questions we have on this planet. I think it helps here and there, but that would be fantastic if it could help more.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yep.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> At the same time, though, I don&#39;t think we can abdicate and just hope the machines solve the problems that we&#39;ve created either. I think it&#39;s going to take both of us working together on that.没关系; that&#39;s part of the hope.</p><p> Is there anything you&#39;re excited about artificial intelligence? What&#39;s the next thing coming that you&#39;re most excited about right now?</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Hmm, good question. I think we want to improve our lives, and I think where I live right now, we are very privileged. We already have AI excess in many ways, you know? We just talked about it — in our smart homes and our cars, etc. — but that doesn&#39;t count for everybody in the world. It would be great if those advances and those benefits would be [more broadly] available.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah, you didn&#39;t ask me, Sam, but I totally agree. I mean, I think that when you think about just in education and the impact that it can have on underprivileged communities and nations, they don&#39;t need to have a school setup anymore. You could just do so much and help so many people just learn and develop and build skills that normally would rely on infrastructure and physical people and teachers and all that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You&#39;d think I&#39;d be threatened by that, but I&#39;m not a bit. I mean, I think that&#39;s our biggest opportunity. We have so many people that … I mean, we just cannot get them all through education programs, and the education programs we have are not particularly optimized or fast. And if we could solve that problem and get better resources out of our brains, then that would be a huge win.</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Hey, Sam, can I ask you a question? I know I turned this around now, but if you think that the shelf life of knowledge is decreasing, right, there were some recent articles about it that maybe what you learn today is maybe worth four or five years and then it&#39;s kind of obsolete. So how do you think this will evolve in the education system?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s huge, because I think about that. I mean, I teach a class in machine learning and AI, and I am acutely aware that unless they&#39;re graduating the semester that I teach them, everything that I&#39;m … you know, the specifics that we&#39;re teaching them are likely to be quite ephemeral. We&#39;ve seen how rapidly this evolves. I think that pushes us to step back and be higher level. If we slip into teaching a tool, teaching how to click “File,” how to click “New,” how to click “Open,” how to click “Save,” those are very low-level skills. And when we think about what kinds of things we should be teaching, I mean, my university is a liberal arts university, and I think that&#39;s a big deal because, if we think about teaching technical skills within a world of liberal arts, I think这是一件大事。 We had the sexiest job of the 21st century being data science. [Regarding] the next one, [it&#39;s] not clear to me that data science is involved. And it&#39;s not that data science isn&#39;t important; it&#39;s just rapidly becoming commoditized.</p><p> And so then we have things like philosophy, which become more important, and ethics, which, as the cost of data science drops, these things become more important.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Linguistics.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Linguistics, yeah.就这样吧。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Large language models, right.精彩的。 Ellen, thank you so much. This has been so insightful, and we thank you for making the time.</p><p> <strong>Ellen Nielsen:</strong> Yeah, thank you.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for tuning in. On our next episode, Shervin and I venture into in the use of AI in outer space with Vandi Verma, chief engineer of [Mars] Perseverance robotic operations and deputy manager at NASA&#39;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory.请加入我们。</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/digital-twins-and-simulations-for-safety-chevrons-ellen-nielsen/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>为您的员工打造更好的盟友</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ayse Karaevli and Serden Özcan. <p>Ayse Karaevli is chair of corporate management and change, and Serden Özcan is chair of innovation and corporate transformation, at WHU—Otto Beisheim School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors used ESG data from Refinitiv to analyze workforce controversies in Germany’s top 50 companies that were significant enough to gain media attention over the past 10 years. They calculated an average score for each company, taking workforce size into account, and identified the companies in the top and bottom [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Karaevli-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Neil Webb/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors used ESG data from Refinitiv to analyze workforce controversies in Germany&#39;s top 50 companies that were significant enough to gain media attention over the past 10 years.</li><li>他们考虑到劳动力规模，计算了每家公司的平均分，并确定了最高和最低四分位的公司，表明与劳动力相关的争议的最高和最低水平。</li><li> To gain insights into the decision-making and governance processes of the top- and bottom-ranked companies and the outcomes of these processes, they conducted in-depth, semistructured interviews with external directors, current and former executives, and employee representatives.</li></ul></aside><p> Amid economic uncertainty, supply chain restructuring, and a new wave of automation, businesses that once engaged in extensive hiring now face significant layoffs. Many companies are rolling back flexible work arrangements prompted by the pandemic. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Meanwhile, employees increasingly want to see their own values and priorities represented in how their companies operate. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> And since the pandemic, many are redrawing the boundaries between work and their personal lives to protect their own well-being.</p><p> These trends have intensified tensions between American workers and corporate leaders, leading to a gradual erosion of trust and an increasing strain in their relationships. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> We can see this both directly, in the rise of workforce controversies, such as strikes and other disputes over wages, working conditions, diversity, equal opportunity, health, and safety; and indirectly, through employee disengagement. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p></p><p> Besides inducing costly operational disruptions and lowering the quality of work, labor controversies and disengagement pose significant challenges for businesses in attracting and retaining talent. Furthermore, such controversies hinder companies&#39; ability to navigate business challenges like cybersecurity, digitalization, and sustainability, which demand vigilance from and collaboration with employees.</p><p> Our analysis of the top 50 public corporations in Germany reveals that, despite a long-standing tradition of involving employees on company boards, management&#39;s ability to manage workforce disputes and foster employee engagement varies. We found that the structure and composition of boards have little to do with their effectiveness; rather, what matters most for reducing conflict is the extent to which C-suite and board leaders actively engage employees in critical strategic decisions. (See “The Research.”) We interviewed key stakeholders in companies that had experienced fewer workforce controversies. Through our conversations with board directors, CEOs, CFOs, and employee representatives in a range of sectors, we identified three strategies such leaders use to include employees: They identify mutual goals and interests, foster inclusive decision processes, and give employees strategic responsibilities.</p><p> The strategies facilitate active collaboration among C-suite leaders, external directors, and employees on critical issues while simultaneously fostering trust among the three groups. (See “Three Strategies to Avert Workforce Controversies.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Three Strategies to Avert Workforce Controversies</h4><p class="caption"> When companies focus on employees&#39; and leaders&#39; common interests, include employees when making decisions, and give employees responsibility for developing business strategy along with senior managers, they can increase engagement and make workforce controversies less likely. </p><p style="text-align:center;"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MAG_Karaevli_Figure-1.png" width="80%" alt="Three Strategies to Avert Workforce Controversies"></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Leaders who employ these strategies can more effectively address a broad spectrum of strategic issues, including business model transformations, restructurings, mergers and acquisitions, divestments, spinoffs, technology adoption, environmental sustainability, and social concerns. Meanwhile, establishing a solid foundation for tackling problems can set the stage for the workforce to join management in value creation.</p><p> Companies in any region can harness these benefits, even if they lack a formal structure, such as board representation, for involving employees in decisions. While the research focused on companies that have employee representation on their boards, at the end of the article we will explain how companies without such structures can incorporate these strategies into their existing decision-making processes.</p><h3> 1. Identify Mutual Goals and Interests</h3><p> Corporate leaders often overlook the fact that employees have a significant stake in their company&#39;s long-term success — after all, they depend on it for their livelihoods and, often, their future security. But the companies in our sample with the fewest workforce controversies recognize and capitalize on the inherent connection between employees&#39; interests and those of the organization. Leaders in these companies make the effort to identify shared objectives and focus on how to achieve them in ways that address both management and employee concerns. Rather than approaching potential conflicts as negotiations between two opposing sides, they frame such situations as joint problems to solve. In doing so, they create a shared sense of ownership and responsibility for finding solutions.</p><p> Moreover, these companies deviate from the conventional practice of making HR executives chiefly responsible for communication with employees. In the companies we studied, CEOs and CFOs directly engaged with employee board representatives to explain the rationale behind potentially controversial decisions before presenting those decisions to the full board. According to Herbert Hainer, a former CEO of Adidas and a director on several US and European corporate boards, open and transparent communication from the CEO can give employees the broader context for decisions and help them align with company goals.</p><p> Wolfgang Ziebart, chair of the board at wind-turbine maker Nordex and former CEO of semiconductor manufacturer Infineon Technologies, advises emphasizing the potential consequences if board members, C-suite leaders, and employee representatives focus solely on their own group&#39;s rights and agendas. “Everyone would stand to lose in the long run,” he observed.</p><p> A restructuring effort by ThyssenKrupp, an industrial engineering and steel manufacturing conglomerate, illustrates the repercussions when a coherent communication strategy is lacking. In 2019, in response to global changes in the sectors where ThyssenKrupp competed, CEO Martina Merz laid out an ambitious plan that entailed the sale of three core businesses: elevator manufacturing, marine systems, and steel. After thorough discussions, the board and employee representatives agreed to the plan.</p><p> ThyssenKrupp divested the elevator business in 2020 for $20.4 billion. Subsequent efforts to sell the steel division failed. Although management explored a range of options for both the steel and marine divisions for over two years, including sales, government equity partnerships, and an initial public offering (IPO), they never presented a concrete plan to the board.</p><p> That ambiguity prevented the employee representatives from assessing and addressing workers&#39; concerns, and their frustrations resonated with the board. In a March 2023 memo to ThyssenKrupp&#39;s 100,000 workers, the employee representatives criticized management for a lack of vision and for wasting time. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> A week later, Merz resigned. Four months later, the CFO announced his intention to leave when his contract expired.</p><p> ThyssenKrupp employees didn&#39;t resist the restructuring. On the contrary, they wanted to see the company adapt successfully to changes in its industry. They supported the initial plan even though tens of thousands of workers would be affected — 26,000 in the steel division alone. And they did not withdraw their support for the goal. Management&#39;s failure to communicate and involve employees created the controversy.</p><p> In contrast, when financial services provider Allianz changed its core business model, company leaders ensured that employees understood and were persuaded by the reasons behind the change and its timing. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> Leaders at every level in the organization participated in the communications effort, including the global heads of business transformation and strategic workforce planning, the CEOs of Allianz companies in 30 countries, and the leaders of the operating entities within those companies. They explained what the shift would mean for employees, including what current and future roles would look like under the new business model. They also provided a timeline for the change process, along with concrete milestones and how they would be evaluated.</p><p></p><p> This approach enabled company leaders to gain the crucial support of employee representatives on the Allianz board, which proved vital for the successful rollout of the reconfigured organization, products, and services.</p><p> When companies communicate with employees and involve them in decisions about sensitive issues, they gain their trust, even when an initiative does not succeed. Harald Kern, a longtime employee director at Siemens, Europe&#39;s largest industrial manufacturing company, recounted a proposed merger between Siemens Mobility and aircraft maker Bombardier. Siemens&#39;s employee representatives found it challenging to quickly comprehend management&#39;s intentions and anticipate the repercussions for the company and its workforce. To help them learn the motives behind the merger decision, management supplemented company information with insights from industry analysts.</p><p> Ultimately, external factors impeded the merger. But Kern said that management&#39;s commitment to open dialogue and sharing resources solidified employees&#39; trust in Siemens&#39;s leaders.</p><p></p><h3> 2. Foster Inclusive Decision Processes</h3><p> Corporate leaders often prioritize results over how they achieve them. However, we found that companies that take deliberate steps to include employees when making decisions experience fewer workforce controversies.</p><p> In 2020, Siemens spun off its energy business, a unit with nearly 100,000 employees that represented 40% of the company&#39;s sales. In the preliminary discussions about the decision by the board, employee representatives raised concerns that are typical in such an uncertain situation, such as potential job insecurity and changes to employee roles. Management not only responded to these concerns but also shared information about the strategic and financial challenges the energy division faced. As employees gained deeper insight, they came to view the spinoff as the most viable solution, and the potential for conflict in later stages of the process were significantly reduced. According to Robert Kensbock, the general chairman of the works council for Siemens Energy, “While there were risks, the growth opportunities outweighed them.” <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> By engaging employees from the outset, Siemens&#39;s management not only secured their support but also gained deeper insights into business operations as their plans unfolded. The employees offered recommendations for improving efficiency and reallocating those cost savings to employee training.</p><p> Moreover, they suggested and championed the transformation of a plant that specialized in building oil and gas turbines into an innovation hub that would concentrate on developing power generation and transmission technologies for plants using renewable energy sources. After the IPO, the plant introduced pioneering innovations that have earned Siemens Energy national acclaim and positioned the company as a leader in the renewable energy industry. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p></p><p> In this and other cases we studied, the behavior of the board, starting with its chair, both set the tone for employee participation and determined how it would be received. When the board chair actively invites employees to critique management plans, keeps an open mind, and seeks to understand their perspectives, employees are more likely to accept, understand, and effectively navigate the challenges of the restructuring process, according to an interviewee with experience revamping companies in multiple industries. Another interviewee, who has served on multiple German boards and was a nonexecutive director at Goldman Sachs International, emphasized that this approach should be embraced by all shareholder representatives, not only the board chair.</p><p> Additionally, our interviews indicated that board chairs in companies with the fewest workforce controversies take steps to ensure that all employees feel comfortable and respected and that their contributions are valued equally. Our interviewees identified several effective practices in companies where employee representatives have a seat on the board, including the following:</p><ul><li> Arrange directors&#39; seating in alphabetical order to prevent easy identification of their respective roles as shareholder or employee representatives.</li><li> Alternately, regularly rotate seats so that employee representatives sit next to different shareholder directors at each board meeting.</li><li> Coach new employee representatives so that they feel comfortable and learn how to be effective during board deliberations.</li><li> Assign shareholder directors as mentors to guide development of employees&#39; boardroom skills.</li></ul><p> Board chairs might go even further and require each shareholder director to have lunch or dinner with two employee representatives every three to six months, thus creating opportunities for informal discussions outside the boardroom. One board chair we interviewed holds social events like holiday dinners to foster a more inclusive atmosphere. Our interviews indicate that these practices improve social cohesion among board members who otherwise would not naturally spend time getting to know each other as individuals.</p><p> According to Stephan Gemkow, a nonexecutive director at Airbus, when the board commits to including employees in key decisions, the entire decision-making process becomes more collaborative. Instead of structuring board activity around a rigid agenda driven by the priorities of shareholder members or management, the chair becomes a facilitator who encourages open discussions, invites diverse perspectives, and cultivates an environment where all members actively contribute. Such an approach is necessary, Gemkow said, to discover innovative solutions to complex strategic problems, such as how to address layoffs during a restructuring.</p><h3> 3. Give Employees Strategic Responsibilities</h3><p> Our research reveals that companies with fewer workforce controversies strive to close the power gap between employees, leadership, and shareholder representatives by giving employee representatives strategic roles and responsibilities, both in formal committees and through informal channels.</p><p> Board committees are where the action is. Members perform rigorous research on and analysis of the issues in their domain, meet with key people in the organization, and develop recommendations for action by the full board. They have power to shape the board&#39;s agenda and influence its decisions.</p><p> In the framework of German corporate governance, boards have substantial autonomy when appointing employee representatives to committees. We found a direct relationship between the proportion of employee representatives serving on board committees and the number of workforce controversies a company has faced.</p><p> Among companies with no workforce controversies in the past five years, an average of 70% of employee representatives are on board committees. In contrast, companies that faced five or more controversies in this time frame include an average of only 38% of employee representatives on board committees. Furthermore, when employee representatives are assigned to strategic board committees such as finance or technology in addition to those that primarily focus on employee or nonstrategic matters, companies also experience significantly fewer workforce controversies.</p><p> The companies that scored highest in our analysis — with the fewest workforce controversies — include logistics provider DHL, telecommunications carrier Deutsche Telekom, and software maker SAP. At all three companies, a large majority of employee representatives served on board committees: 80% at DHL, 89% at SAP, and 100% at Deutsche Telekom. And they were members of strategic committees, such as finance and investment, technology and innovation, strategy, and sustainability, in addition to narrowly focused audit and personnel committees.</p><p> In contrast, Volkswagen and Lufthansa were among the companies with the most workforce controversies during our study period. At Volkswagen, only half of the employee representatives served on board committees, while at Lufthansa, 40% did. Furthermore, at each company, employee representatives predominantly served on less-strategic committees, such as audit. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> When employee representatives serve on a greater number and a wider range of committees, they develop a deep understanding of the company&#39;s overall strategic and financial requirements. Not only can they effectively influence decisions, but they can also assume greater responsibility for implementing them.</p><p> Such arrangements foster healthy checks and balances by promoting transparency and objectivity. They also ensure that shareholder directors obtain firsthand information from employees about potential long-term repercussions of management decisions while they are being considered. Specifically, employee representatives can alert external directors to critical risks from supply chain disruptions, production inefficiencies, investment backlogs, and employee turnover trends.</p><p> Employee and shareholder representatives we interviewed said that employees, when empowered with strategic responsibilities, can also help companies address long-term goals such as integrating sustainability into corporate systems and processes and maintaining continuity in leadership succession decisions.</p><p> For example, at Bayer, employee and shareholder representatives have equal representation on the committee that oversees key performance indicators and executive compensation, including the CEO&#39;s. Employee representatives have influenced the inclusion of incentives to encourage top executives to pursue sustainability goals. In 2021, the committee recommended that 20% of the CEO&#39;s compensation be based on progress toward six goals related to environmental, social, and governance (ESG) factors, including providing support for sustainable agriculture and the health and well-being of women globally, and addressing climate change through emissions-reduction or -offset initiatives.</p><p> The Siemens board goes further. It facilitates meetings between employee representatives and managers two levels below the C-suite who are being considered for executive roles. This practice allows employee representatives to evaluate the capabilities and profiles of potential future leaders, assess their alignment with the company&#39;s values, and establish a foundation for collaboration with them in the future. Importantly, this initiative sends a strong message to employees that they are valued partners in shaping the company&#39;s future leadership.</p><h3> Many Ways to Include Employees</h3><p> There are multiple avenues for companies to integrate employees into strategic decision-making, even when they don&#39;t have a formal structure for doing so, such as employee representation on the board. Below, we suggest some alternative approaches for executing each of the three strategies.</p><p> <strong>Committees and task forces.</strong> A committee or task force that includes employees and management can be pivotal to operationalizing our first two strategies — identifying mutual goals and interests and fostering inclusive decision processes. When a company has a defined project or problem to solve, such as deciding the fate of a business unit, such groups enable employees to communicate their concerns and suggestions directly to company leaders. In addition, the CEO and CFO get an opportunity to clarify the strategic and financial logic behind crucial decisions.</p><p> Committees should include both the senior executives who are responsible for formulating and implementing the plans under discussion and employees who represent the units most likely to be affected. The employees should be selected by their peers to ensure that they reflect the perspectives of those who are closely linked to the outcomes of leaders&#39; decisions.</p><p> Ideally, leaders will involve employees from the start of their deliberations. In this way, they demonstrate to the entire organization both the value of the committee and their commitment to inclusive decision-making. This will signal that employees are at the table and in the game.</p><p> <strong>Engagement with board members.</strong> Employees can be invited to board meetings or retreats to foster more inclusive decision processes. Doing so can expose external directors to perspectives and information that they might not get from company leaders.</p><p> For instance, at a regular board meeting, key employees can share the operational and cultural integration issues their peers are experiencing after a merger. At a special board meeting or retreat, employees from across the organization can share their insights and expertise on broader topics. If, for example, the board is meeting to explore opportunities for automation, employees can weigh in on the practicality and applicability of proposed initiatives and recommend solutions for affected roles.</p><p> <strong>Employee advisory groups.</strong> Employee advisory groups provide a way to give employees strategic responsibility. Unlike committees and task forces, advisory groups are designed to function over the long term. They typically focus on broad organizational issues, including how employees feel about the company and their jobs. Because these groups play a role in helping their organizations respond to the values, concerns, and aspirations of the workforce, they can be charged with developing and recommending solutions for both ongoing concerns and the future direction of the company.</p><p> For example, a digital transformation advisory group that includes IT, marketing, and operations employees can continuously assess the impact of emerging technologies such as artificial intelligence, oversee the implementation of digital initiatives, and advise on digital strategy, thus ensuring that the organization remains nimble and competitive.</p><p> Similarly, an advisory group of employees from business areas that are adept at environmental compliance and sustainability practices can guide the organization&#39;s approach and initiatives in those areas to ensure compliance with ESG standards.</p><p> When the board takes the recommendations of employee advisory groups seriously and incorporates them into decisions, employees become more empowered, and their perspectives become embedded into their company&#39;s long-term objectives.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Our analysis of leading German companies shows the benefits when board directors and company leaders are open to employee input into strategic decisions and are willing to give them an influential role. They can not only more effectively address workforce and labor issues but also, by tapping into employees&#39; interests in the long-term success of the business, gain insights that make them more resilient.</p><p> Employees&#39; participation on committees, task forces, and employee advisory councils, and engagement with board members can help companies foster stronger relationships between directors or corporate leaders and their workforces while gaining the benefits from the insights that employees bring to corporate decision-making and governance 。</p><p> Organizations that embrace these practices can cultivate collaborative, equitable, and inclusive decision-making at the highest levels.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-better-allies-of-your-workforce/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>大型语言模型的工作限制</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikhail Burtsev, Martin Reeves, and Adam Job. <p>Mikhail Burtsev, Ph.D., is a Landau AI fellow at the London Institute for Mathematical Sciences, former scientific director of the Artificial Intelligence Research Institute, and author of more than 100 papers in the field of AI. Martin Reeves is chairman of the BCG Henderson Institute, focused on business strategy. Adam Job, Ph.D., is director of the Strategy Lab at the BCG Henderson Institute.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com Large language models (LLMs) seem set to transform businesses. Their ability to generate detailed, creative responses to queries in plain language and code has sparked a wave of excitement that led ChatGPT to reach 100 million users faster than any other technology after it first launched. Subsequently, investors poured over $40 billion into [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER_Burtsev-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Page/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Large language models (LLMs) seem set to transform businesses. Their ability to generate detailed, creative responses to queries in plain language and code has sparked a wave of excitement that led ChatGPT to reach 100 million users faster than any other technology after it first launched. Subsequently, investors poured over <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/venture-capital-funding-plunges-globally-first-half-despite-ai-frenzy-2023-07-06/">$40 billion into artificial intelligence startups</a> in the first half of 2023 — more than 20% of all global venture capital investments — and companies from seed-stage startups to tech giants are developing new applications of the technology.</p><p> But while LLMs are incredibly powerful, their ability to generate humanlike text can invite us to falsely credit them with other human capabilities, leading to misapplications of the technology. With a deeper understanding of how LLMs work and their fundamental limitations, managers can make more informed decisions about how LLMs are used in their organizations, addressing their shortcomings with a mix of complementary technologies and human governance.</p><p></p><h3> The Mechanics of LLMs</h3><p> An LLM is fundamentally a machine learning model designed to predict the next element in a sequence of words. Earlier, more rudimentary language models operated sequentially, drawing from a probability distribution of words within their training data to predict the next word in a sequence. (Think of your smartphone keyboard suggesting the next word in a text message.) However, these models lack the ability to consider the larger context in which a word appears and its multiple meanings and associations.</p><p> The advent of the latest neural network architecture — transformers — marked a significant evolution toward modern LLMs. Transformers allow neural networks to process large chunks of text simultaneously in order to establish stronger relationships between words and the context in which they appear. Training these transformers on increasingly enormous volumes of text has led to a leap in sophistication that enables LLMs to generate humanlike responses to prompts.</p><p> This ability of LLMs hinges on several critical factors, including the model&#39;s size, denoted by the number of the trainable weights (known as <em>parameters</em> ), the quality and volume of the training data (defined by number of <em>tokens</em> , referring to word or subword units), and the maximum size of input the model can accept as a prompt (known as its <em>context window size</em> ). Every parameter in a model encapsulates some information about a relationship extrapolated from the training data, so a model with a larger number of parameters tends to be more knowledgeable and nuanced. (OpenAI&#39;s GPT-3, for example, has 175 billion parameters.) The volume of the training data also significantly influences the model&#39;s ability to generalize, with larger data sets offering more diverse representations of semantic relationships and facts. (GPT-3 was trained on approximately half a trillion tokens.) The size of the prompt that the model can accept also plays a role in its accuracy. (GPT-3 has a context window of 2,000 tokens.) The more detailed the context, the more accurate the model&#39;s prediction is.</p><p> In response to a prompt, the LLM draws on the relationships established by its training to generate a continuation of the text, token by token. Each step entails forecasting the probabilities of the next token based on the context provided, and the algorithm selects the token based on these probabilities. The degree of randomness in this selection is modulated by the model&#39;s <em>temperature</em> setting. Higher temperatures produce more “creative,” or unlikely, selections, whereas lower temperatures produce more predictable responses. To improve the accuracy of an LLM&#39;s responses to specific prompts and limit its ability to produce inappropriate, irrelevant, or toxic responses, pretrained models can be fine-tuned through techniques like <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/09/25/technology/chatgpt-rlhf-human-tutors.html">reinforcement learning from human feedback, or RLHF</a> , which has been employed to fine-tune models like ChatGPT.</p><h3> Four Important Limitations of LLMs</h3><p> Based on this understanding of how LLMs work, we can examine the false impressions they might create as we apply our human intuition to seemingly human output.</p><h4> 1. Limitations of Reasoning</h4><p> <strong>Prompt:</strong> <em>According to the cabbage-growers&#39; union report for 2007, 80% of cabbages collected were heavy (over 0.5 kg), 10% of cabbages were green, 60% were red, and 50% were big (having a diameter of over 10 cm). Which of the following statements must be false?</em></p><ol><li> <em>All red cabbages weren&#39;t big.</em></li><li> <em>30% of red cabbages were big.</em></li><li> <em>There were no cabbages that were both green and big.</em></li><li> <em>Half of the cabbages were small.</em></li></ol><p> <strong>LLM response:</strong> <em>The statement that must be false is 4. Half of the cabbages were small.</em></p><p> The correct answer would be that Statement 1 is false — at least some red cabbages must have been big.</p><p> Contrary to the impression they might create, LLMs are not built for complex reasoning. For example, studies have found that GPT-4, OpenAI&#39;s most advanced LLM, could correctly <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/over-just-few-months-chatgpt-232905189.html">verify a number as prime</a> in only 2.4% of cases, with similar weaknesses in the prediction of visual patterns. Other research has shown that <a href="https://owainevans.github.io/reversal_curse.pdf">LLMs</a> fail to understand relationships between words in the training data set: For example, GPT-4 can correctly answer the question “Who is Tom Cruise&#39;s mother?” (Mary Lee Pfeiffer) but cannot infer the answer to “Who is Mary Lee Pfeiffer&#39;s son?” — with the model correctly answering questions like the former 79% of the time, compared with 33% for the latter.</p><p> Essentially, LLMs learn only to <em>verbally simulate</em> elementary logical rules but do not possess the skills to chain them together for producing and verifying complex conclusions. Moreover, LLMs are prone to error accumulation in multistep logical reasoning because the model&#39;s fundamentally probabilistic nature means that every step has a nonzero chance of an error. Finally, LLMs cannot always outline the “chain of thought” that led to a conclusion, making it difficult for humans to determine whether or where an error occurred.</p><p></p><p> A recent field experiment conducted with more than 750 Boston Consulting Group consultants highlighted the real-life implications of this limitation. Participants using GPT-4 when trying to solve a simple business problem got the answer wrong 23% more often than the control group that did not have access to an LLM — because <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2023/how-people-create-and-destroy-value-with-gen-ai">GPT-4 not only often got the answer wrong</a> but provided such a persuasive rationale for its solution that users accepted it at face value.</p><p></p><h4> 2. Limitations of Knowledge or Expertise</h4><p> We asked an LLM to provide us with five papers in peer-reviewed academic journals on the feasibility of nuclear fusion, with paper titles, the year of publication, and the names of the main authors. The LLM returned five results, of which two were news articles, not peer-reviewed papers, and one was a paper that does not exist.</p><p> The knowledge of an LLM is dictated by its training data. If the data lacks specific domain knowledge, has insufficient instances of a particular concept, or is not up to date, the LLM might fail to surface relevant knowledge in response to a prompt. Similarly, LLMs might reproduce errors present in the training data. Finally, the models could create errors by “hallucinating” statements that were not in the training data. Researchers who tasked ChatGPT with generating treatment plans for a variety of cancer cases found that one-third of the <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/chatgpt-generates-error-filled-cancer-treatment-plans-study-2023-8">LLMs&#39; responses contained incorrect information</a> — often mixed with correct indications, and plausibly articulated in a way that made it difficult for a layperson to identify what was accurate. In another high-profile example, two lawyers and their firm were fined after submitting <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/jun/23/two-us-lawyers-fined-submitting-fake-court-citations-chatgpt">fake citations</a> generated by ChatGPT in a court filing: The LLM had hallucinated six legal cases, including judicial opinions and quotes.</p><p> Finally, limitations of knowledge can also lead to a lack of consistency, with LLMs responding to the same prompt asked at different points in time in contradictory manners. For example, Iowa educators used ChatGPT to determine the <a href="https://www.popsci.com/technology/iowa-chatgpt-book-ban/">appropriateness of books for their school&#39;s library</a> to comply with a new state law. They fed the LLM a list of all of the library books and asked it to point out those that contained content that violated the law, which resulted in the removal of 19 titles from the library. However, when journalists later queried ChatGPT on those 19 titles, it suggested that only four of them contained content inconsistent with the law.</p><h4> 3. Limitations of Understanding</h4><p> <strong>Prompt:</strong> <em>There is an apple inside a blue box. There is also a red box inside the blue box. The red box has a lid on it. How can I get the apple?</em></p><p> <strong>LLM response:</strong> <em>To retrieve the apple from the boxes, you can follow these steps:</em></p><ol><li> <em>Open the lid of the red box: Since the red box is inside the blue box and has a lid on it, you need to open the lid of the red box first.</em></li><li> <em>Remove the red box from the blue box: Once the lid of the red box is open, you can take out the entire red box from the blue box.</em></li><li> <em>Open the red box: After removing the red box from the blue box, you can open the red box to access its contents.</em></li><li> <em>Retrieve the apple: Finally, you can reach inside the red box and take out the apple.</em></li></ol><p> ChatGPT failed to understand that the apple is not inside the red box.</p><p> An LLM might not “understand” the prompt it is given. Lacking adequate context, it might falter, and its outputs might become disjointed or incoherent. <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.02312">Researchers analyzed ChatGPT&#39;s responses</a> to more than 500 human-submitted questions on the online software engineering forum Stack Overflow. They found that 52% of the model&#39;s responses were inaccurate, with more than half of those errors resulting from ChatGPT not understanding the concept or the details of the question, or focusing on the wrong part of the problem. This means that an LLM might not even be marginally helpful when users lack sufficient knowledge of a problem to supply good prompts.</p><h4> 4. Limitations of Planning and Execution</h4><p> LLMs can output clear step-by-step guidance for a requested task, creating the impression that the model can plan practical solutions. But given LLMs&#39; limited reasoning ability and limited understanding of tasks, suggested actions can be impractical or naive. For example, when asked to create a plan for <a href="https://fortune.com/recommends/mortgages/i-used-chatgpt-as-my-financial-planner/">saving toward home ownership</a> , ChatGPT provided some generally solid financial advice but did not account for potential changes in income or interest-rate shifts. Moreover, it does not consider human fallibility: It neither questions the realism of goals nor the user&#39;s belief to be aware of their exact spending habits.</p><p> For businesses, all of these limitations can undermine reliability; one cannot be sure that information provided by an LLM is complete, relevant, feasible, or true. Given these limitations, LLMs certainly cannot be counted on to make critical decisions or execute plans autonomously. However, delegating mundane tasks might still seem appealing — for example, those involving programmatic interactions with existing IT services, like web browsing and scraping, or social media monitoring and messaging. Indeed, Auto-GPT — an open-source application powered by GPT-4 that chains together LLM outputs to autonomously execute user-set goals — has allowed enthusiasts to create a number of impressive automation demonstrations, including <a href="https://lifehacker.com/you-can-try-auto-gpt-the-next-generation-of-chatgpt-r-1850343691">conducting research on products</a> , coding web pages or apps, and even <a href="https://dataconomy.com/2023/04/19/best-autogpt-examples-use-cases/">ordering pizza</a> . However, AI researcher Jim Fan suggested that the working demos are <a href="https://twitter.com/DrJimFan/status/1647616587199815684?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1647616587199815684%7Ctwgr%5E53a5539ffd940932a855d641438099af4aa992a5%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechcrunch.com%2F2023%2F04%2F22%2Fwhat-is-auto-gpt-and-why-does-it-matter%2F">“heavily cherry-picked”</a> — with research on autonomous agents indicating that, in realistic environments, they <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.13854.pdf">achieve success rates of only around 10%</a> .</p><h3> Overcoming the Limitations</h3><p> Rather than simply restricting applications of LLMs to routine cases where their limitations do not apply or mistakes are not critical (such as generating new product ideas for further consideration), businesses should design all of their implementations with the limitations in mind — by complementing them with human oversight and other technologies.</p><p> Keeping humans in the loop is critical as businesses integrate LLMs into their operations. This should include validation of AI-generated outputs in order to enhance the confidence placed in the technology. It could also be extended to having experts translate business problems into prompts for the AI, and ensuring that the information provided by the model is adequate by appropriately tailoring the context and nuance fed to it.</p><p> Beyond thinking about how to craft the optimal system of humans and AI, businesses should also explore complementary technologies that can address the limitations of LLMs. In this fast-moving space, new innovations are being made constantly that promise to enhance the technology&#39;s capabilities, so continuously updating your understanding is also crucial.</p><p> For example, to enhance <em>reasoning</em> capabilities, researchers are exploring <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.07697.pdf">augmenting LLMs with reasoning engines</a> that encode domain-specific information into <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.01157.pdf">knowledge graphs</a> representing relations between specialized concepts and facts. Researchers are also training specialized models to assess the logical coherence between premises in the prompt and the LLM&#39;s output. To augment <em>knowledge</em> and <em>expertise</em> , LLMs are being trained on domain-specific databases — such as <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/chatgpt-can-help-doctors-and-hurt-patients/">Google and DeepMind&#39;s Med-PaLM model</a> , which has been shown to significantly outperform general-purpose LLMs on the United States Medical Licensing exam. LLM reliability might also be improved through reinforcement learning with <a href="https://github.com/opendilab/awesome-RLHF">feedback collected from human experts</a> . LLMs can also improve their understanding of a user&#39;s initial prompts by being programmed to ask clarifying follow-up questions before providing an answer.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The promise of LLMs&#39; near-universal applicability means that businesses are right to be excited about exploring this powerful new technology. However, these models&#39; uncanny ability to generate humanlike text outputs can easily lead us to ascribe to them capabilities that they do not possess. A proper understanding of their limitations should guide the manner and context in which they are implemented.</p><p> Businesses should be particularly wary in areas where logical reasoning is involved, facts are important, replicability is crucial, or the stakes are high. In these situations, companies need to explore using complementary technologies that address the limitations of LLMs — such as knowledge graphs, reasoning engines, and specialized domain models — and ensure that there is appropriate human input and oversight.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-working-limitations-of-large-language-models/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>引领透明爆炸时代</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/#comments</comments><pubDate> Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Melissa Swift. <p>Melissa Swift ( <a href="https://twitter.com/meswift">@meswift</a> ) leads Capgemini Invent&#39;s Workforce &amp; Organization practice for North America. She is the author of <cite>Work Here Now: Think Like a Human and Build a Powerhouse Workplace</cite> (Wiley, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Frank is having a terrible morning. The seasoned CIO wakes up groggy to a flurry of texts from his team, who found out about the CEO’s retirement from LinkedIn because the internal announcement got stuck in everyone’s spam filters. As Frank huffs and puffs around the park during his [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Swift-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>弗兰克度过了一个糟糕的早晨。</p><p>这位经验丰富的首席信息官在他的团队发来的一连串短信中昏昏沉沉地醒来，他们发现首席执行官从 LinkedIn 退休，因为内部公告被困在每个人的垃圾邮件过滤器中。弗兰克在晨跑时在公园里气喘吁吁，他的老板通过电话询问他全新仪表板上的一些令人不安的数字。 Arriving at the office already feeling beleaguered, he spits iced coffee all over his keyboard when an email alerts him that another leader in the organization dramatically documented her departure on “ <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/quittok?lang=en">QuitTok</a> ” — racking up half a million views already.</p><p> He spends much of the morning fielding questions from a group of software engineers who found roles similar to theirs listed on job sites for 20% more than their current salaries, while his marketing leadership team goes back and forth about whether the numbers from the new dashboards or the old spreadsheets are correct. Just before lunch, his daughter texts him: “Dad. Have u seen ur Glassdoor lately?” She screenshots an abysmal rating for his company with comments like “I can&#39;t decide if management are stupid, criminals, or just criminally stupid.”</p><p></p><p> By the time he staggers to the company cafeteria, Frank has had a week&#39;s worth of misery. And it&#39;s only noon.</p><p> Welcome to leadership in a hyper-transparent world. Frank is fictional, but his challenges are real. The hoary cliché is true: Information flows today at the speed of light … and it&#39;s moving far too fast for many leaders to grapple with. Whether it&#39;s social media channels making company dirty laundry public (or even displaying “clean underwear” information — not scandalous, but not intended to be seen broadly) or internal technology systems throwing an array of decontextualized data onto the screens of folks unprepared to interpret it, technology is meaningfully eroding the information advantage leaders have enjoyed since the dawn of the working world.</p><h3> Goodbye Watercooler Grumbling; Hello QuitTok</h3><p> Knowledge is power — and today, everyone seems to have it.</p><p> Unfortunately, greater availability of information on <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/">workforce issues like pay</a> , layoffs, or diversity, as well as business performance metrics at the micro and macro scales, means that the average worker is getting hit with more bad, or at least uncomfortable, news. For leaders and employees alike, this is prompting tough conversations that create a meaningful source of stress: I hear from clients over and over that even the most seasoned leaders often struggle to engage in these challenging conversations, causing both parties to walk away more unsettled than when they started.</p><p> Today, leaders&#39; actions are immediately discussed across internal and external platforms in writing and on a massive scale. The internal messaging app Slack alone boasts 300,000 messages sent <em>per second</em> , and 145 million people log onto Microsoft Teams for similar discussions each day. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Fifty-five million people use company feedback platform Glassdoor every month, and 774 million are on LinkedIn to talk about work. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Social media content tagged with the #QuitTok hashtag had been viewed an astounding 41 million times as of April 2023. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> The days when reactions to strategic leadership decisions were confined to a bit of watercooler grumbling are long gone.</p><p></p><p> So how can leaders stay sane — and effective — in a world where it can feel like everyone knows everything and talks about it all of the time? What can organizations do to ensure that appropriate signals pop through a cacophony of noise, and that the noise doesn&#39;t challenge the well-being of everyone they employ, from the top down?</p><p></p><h3> Four Practical Strategies for Leaders</h3><p> Here are four pathways to sanity and clarity in a hyper-transparent world.</p><p> <strong>1. Ease leaders&#39; burden by dialing up the right kind of organizational honesty.</strong> It might seem impossible to stanch the flow of difficult conversations — but a client illuminated a simple strategy for me recently: “It&#39;s easier for our leaders when we&#39;re more honest. That way, they just don&#39;t have to have as many tough conversations.” There&#39;s such truth to this statement. If people will see the reality of a given situation anyway, communicating about that reality from the jump means that individual leaders won&#39;t have to scramble and backpedal when confronted by their teams.</p><p> Now, does this entail communicating every single detail of every situation to every audience?绝对不。 What it does mean is changing the frame of every communication from “What is it that we want people to believe?” to “What are the basic facts and pieces of context that people will need to make smart decisions in this situation?” This changes the nature of the information cascade.</p><p> In the old model, leaders would be equipped with a static set of messages that the organization assumed would travel undisturbed into teams&#39; hands and be acted upon unquestioningly (or at least politely). In the new model, the organization is more focused on establishing context for a series of emerging facts — with the implicit understanding that challenging or even contradictory information might come through unbidden. The goal shifts from imposing a set of ideas to creating a discussion that minimizes interpersonal friction and maximizes productive action, even when there&#39;s disagreement or the information is evolving.</p><p> <strong>2. Reframe communications on a “one world” basis — ending the internal/external distinction.</strong> It&#39;s often said that we live in a world of context collapse, where information travels instantly through seemingly disparate circles of communication that would have been disconnected or at least time-sequenced in the past. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Leaders used to have the luxury of communicating internally in steps before taking the message to select outside figures in a thoughtful progression. Today, once something happens, they can reasonably assume that it will be known internally and externally in short order, across a broad array of audiences. To address this reality, many organizations have merged internal and external communications functions, or have tasked heretofore externally focused communications departments with ensuring consistency in messaging to internal stakeholders as well. Shaping communications in a unified manner not only creates stable messaging in a leak-prone world but also generally raises the standard of internal communications efforts — as internal messages are pressure-tested with the same rigor as statements released to the outside world.</p><p> Even if an organization has not reorganized its communications function accordingly, individual leaders can work to ensure that their messaging remains consistent across internal and external audiences. While a worthwhile exercise, it can be a delicate balancing act: Leaders are challenged to mimic the language of, say, social media posts while simultaneously nudging their colleagues and supervisors to ensure that enough information is released to sate the needs of curious internal stakeholders.</p><p> <strong>3. Go “back to the future” on basic communication skills — but add 21st-century emotional intelligence.</strong> Although the hyper-transparent world is the outgrowth of a host of quickly evolving technologies, the ultimate leadership superpower in this context is a distinctly low-tech one: being able to speak or write a simple, clear sentence. Like a bell cutting through the chatter in a crowded town square, leaders with excellent basic communication skills are simply better at making themselves heard through the noise. Pithy verbal communications are particularly demanded in situations where a stimulus is coming through quickly and frenetically (such as via social media or internal chat channels) and information might range from somewhat to completely inaccurate. We need the ability to shout “Freeze!” and have everyone stop and think.</p><p></p><p> Leaders who have historically been allowed to hem and haw or bloviate at length will find themselves quickly overrun by the punchiness of contemporary communication streams — whether or not those streams are true or helpful to business progress. All of that said, being factual and logical isn&#39;t enough on its own. A great sentence is as it ever was (the classic writing guide <cite>The Elements of Style</cite> holds up pretty well after more than 100 years), but science has taught us a great deal about how people absorb information. For instance, information that triggers an emotional response is more likely to be reposted on social media, causing it to often circulate faster and more broadly. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Leaders who were taught to communicate coolly and unemotionally might find that their messages don&#39;t move through the organization as fast as peers&#39; more emotionally inflected statements.</p><p> In a hyper-transparent world, we might even want to look to the neuroscience findings that caution us that separating rational and emotional thinking is a false dichotomy altogether, and thus, we should stop trying to craft completely emotionless leadership messages. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p> <strong>4. Build your judgment muscle — and your team&#39;s.</strong> Let&#39;s take as a given that the transparent nature of the world and workplace will only increase from here on out. In such an environment, your ability to quickly and sensibly decide what to do with a piece of information — your judgment — becomes a critical tool for survival and success. Leaders will want to consciously work on this skill themselves, but given that they cannot be in every one of a multiplying set of conversations all the time, they&#39;ll also want their teams to get better at judgment. A bank that I worked with some years ago started to offer front-line workers some of the same leadership development opportunities it had historically reserved for top executives, based on the rationale that with greater availability of information, those workers would be making the same kind of calls that used to be made many steps up the chain.</p><p> There is huge value in being able to trust your team to do the right thing, even when confronted with strange and conflicting information, when you&#39;re not around. Practicing scenario planning is a helpful tool in this regard, even for team members who might not come to the table with an innately strong sense of judgment. It can also be helpful for teams to practice evaluating the veracity of information in order to make better decisions. That&#39;s a critical skill in a world in which generative AI is emerging.</p><p></p><p></p><p> When leaders have some practical strategies in hand, leading in a hyper-transparent world doesn&#39;t have to feel like piloting a rickety spacecraft through an asteroid belt of conflicting, incomplete, and often emotion-laden information. We might all sometimes have a version of Frank&#39;s morning, but we can also have Frank&#39;s afternoon – where he cleared his calendar and started focusing on having the right discussions with the right folks, inside his company and beyond.</p><p> Six months later, someone posts about Frank&#39;s company on a social media channel: “Management is not perfect, but they try to be pretty honest, which I totally appreciate. They&#39;re really working on doing the right things, and you can see it day to day.”</p><p> Frank likes and shares the message.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/leading-in-the-age-of-exploding-transparency/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title>为未来的工作构建神经多样性人才管道</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodiversity-talent-pipeline-for-the-future-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodiversity-talent-pipeline-for-the-future-of-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maureen Dunne. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/maureen-n-dunne-ph-d-a2609a45/details/experience/">Maureen Dunne</a> , Ph.D., is a globally recognized neurodiversity expert and the former president of the Illinois Community College Trustees Association, the third-largest consortium of community colleges in the United States. She is the author of the forthcoming book <cite>The Neurodiversity Edge: The Essential Guide to Embracing Autism, ADHD, Dyslexia, and Other Neurological Differences for Any Organization</cite> (Wiley, 2024).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Neurodiversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition & Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images During recent economic policy updates, Jerome Powell, chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve, announced that the American labor market is suffering from a structural labor shortage. Its origins are varied — demographic variables such as an aging population and early retirements, the tragic loss or persistent absence of many [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Dunne-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>During recent economic policy updates, Jerome Powell, chair of the US Federal Reserve, announced that the American labor market is suffering from a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/01/11/briefing/labor-shortage.html">structural labor shortage</a> .其根源各不相同——人口老龄化和提前退休、COVID-19大流行导致许多工人的悲惨损失或持续缺勤以及移民历史性下降等人口变量——但现在的数字太大了忽略。 At the end of last year, there were approximately two job vacancies for every available worker, expanding the labor gap to around 10 million workers. Political economist <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2022/09/20/american-post-pandemic-labor-shortage-explained/">Nicholas Eberstadt framed it</a> this way: “Yes, the United States has a Depression-scale work problem.”</p><p> Meanwhile, an estimated 30% to 40% of neurodivergent adults are <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/20/-neurodivergent-workers-help-companies-meet-the-demand-for-talent.html">currently unemployed</a> . Unemployment rates for college-educated autistic individuals might be <a href="https://www.benefitnews.com/news/how-to-create-equitable-workplace-experiences-for-autistic-talent">as high as 85%</a> . An estimated 50 million people in the United States and <a href="https://dceg.cancer.gov/about/diversity-inclusion/inclusivity-minute/2022/neurodiversity">15% to 20% of the global population</a> fall under the neurodivergence umbrella today.</p><p></p><p> The neurodiversity paradigm advocates for a strengths-based approach to understanding, including, and valuing neurodivergent individuals with cognitive typologies such as autism, attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder, dyslexia, dyscalculia, synesthesia, and dyspraxia, to name a few. Far too many neurodivergent people are falling through the cracks. This failure is not just a question of ethics. The paucity of successful and authentic neurodiversity-inclusive pathways in higher education, our workplaces, and our communities has tangible implications and hampers the success of organizations everywhere. With so many job openings unfilled and so many possible candidates unfulfilled, the theoretical win-win solution to these imbalances is certainly worth exploring.</p><h3> Cognitive Diversity and the Workplace of Tomorrow</h3><p> Harnessing the potential of neurodivergent individuals could help employers build a more future-ready workforce. Creativity, lateral (or nonlinear) thinking, reverse engineering to solve problems, complex visual-spatial skills, systems thinking, intuitive insights, hyperfocus, and multisensory pattern recognition — distinct areas in which neurodivergent candidates might excel — all stand to become increasingly important as artificial intelligence embeds itself into our daily lives.</p><p> Neurodivergent leaders already occupy top positions in every industry, including the military, though many are reluctant to disclose their status. There is ample evidence to suggest that these same individuals — when situated in an effective and suitable working context — can perform as well as or even better than their neurotypical peers in a range of positions. According to James Mahoney, head of the Autism at Work program at JPMorgan Chase, an internal study found that autistic employees — when correctly onboarded — demonstrated <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/viewpoint-how-to-become-a-champion-for-employees-with-autism.aspx">up to 140% greater productivity</a> than neurotypical peers hired for the same positions.</p><p></p><p> No two neurodivergent people are the same, and it is important to value the richness and diversity of all kinds of minds, given that different individuals exhibit their own unique strengths and challenges. That said, there is a growing body of evidence that suggests that there is a correlation between different divergent neurotypes and uncommon skills, such as a heightened capacity for originality or innovative ideation. The results of numerous studies suggest that neurodivergent cognition is positively correlated with enhanced creativity and innovative thinking and that autistic people are less prone to cognitive biases and <a href="https://psyche.co/ideas/autistic-people-challenge-preconceived-ideas-about-rationality">more consistent in making rational decisions</a> than the general population. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These unique perspectives and skills are inherently valuable to employers on an individual level while providing additional group-level value as a critical hedge against groupthink.</p><p></p><h3> The Community College Talent Pipeline</h3><p> A large percentage of neurodivergent individuals begin their higher education journeys at community colleges; one 2015 study found that of those with autism who attend college, as many as 80% enroll in a community college. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Efforts to bring the neurodivergent into the business economy should begin at — or at least in partnership with — these kinds of institutions and could be a game changer in crafting neurodiversity-friendly employment opportunity pathways.</p><p> This might be especially true given the tone set by the US Supreme Court&#39;s recent ruling on <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/">diversity in college admissions decisions</a> , which stands to disproportionately strip diversity from elite university student bodies. Companies committed to the notion that diversity of all kinds is a priceless asset might need to think more creatively about where that diversity can be found.</p><p> The burden then falls on expanding opportunity pathways for students at community colleges. During my time as president of the Illinois Community College Trustees Association, we looked to incentivize collaboration between community colleges, local and regional economic development organizations, and employers. The first statewide Future of Work committee was designed to facilitate direct industry partnerships with employers to create new opportunity pathways for students, communities, and businesses and to facilitate conversations about emerging industries and careers.</p><h3> Building Bridges With Industry</h3><p> Pound for pound, the community college system is our most efficient means of producing qualified candidates to meet the needs of the largest end user of the education system: the corporate economy. However, employers will be able to tap into the full depth and breadth of this talent pool only if neurodiversity-friendly opportunity pathways are cultivated and sustained from the outset.</p><p> Community colleges already serve as powerful partners in meeting the needs of local employers. If they provide wraparound supports such as mental health support, specialized tutoring, time management tools, executive function coaching, and peer navigators, neurodivergent students will be far more likely to navigate a path toward degree completion and subsequent employment.</p><p> Apprenticeships, paid internships, and job-shadowing opportunities with community employers also play critical roles in bridging gaps between earned skills and successful employment. Many community colleges offer an apprenticeship “earn and learn” model, such as the Project Hire-Ed Apprenticeship Program at the College of DuPage, where employers pay for students&#39; tuition to help shepherd them toward learning new skills while they develop on-the-job experience working in a related role.</p><p></p><p> Cybersecurity offers a good example of a target industry for such programs, given the pervasiveness of neurodivergent people working in the field. Per the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, information security analyst jobs are expected to grow by <a href="https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/information-security-analysts.htm">32% from 2022 to 2030</a> . Community colleges around the country, including the City Colleges of Chicago and Nassau Community College, offer more affordable cybersecurity certificate programs that position candidates on a career path with immediate local demand. Competency-based education, such as the welding technology program at Lewis and Clark Community College, represents a similarly attractive framework with flexible options for learners with diverse needs, paving a path to earned credits through skill mastery.</p><p> The neurodiversity movement has raised awareness of the talents of neurodivergent job seekers and developed stronger collaborative initiatives between postsecondary education and industry. For example, Bloomberg has reported that US intelligence services have started to look to the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-18/people-on-the-autism-spectrum-may-be-ideal-for-some-ai-work#xj4y7vzkg">neurodivergent community</a> to supercharge their machine learning and cybersecurity practices. Companies in completely different sectors are following suit after witnessing the likes of <a href="https://businesschief.com/human-capital/top-7-companies-hiring-and-nurturing-neurodiverse-talent">EY, JPMorgan, Microsoft</a> , and other high-profile firms harness the advantages of prioritizing diversity of thought.</p><p> These efforts provide a road map. Collaborations between industry partners, economic development associations, and community colleges that leverage neurodiversity-friendly wraparound support programs, apprenticeships, paid internships, and job-shadowing initiatives represent a new feature in the labor market ecosystem. By leaning into this trend, we have the opportunity to cultivate a work-ready neurodivergent talent pipeline capable of challenging outdated, unproductive assumptions about what a qualified candidate looks like.</p><h3>在办公的地方</h3><p>To truly capitalize on the neurodivergent talent pool, job placement coordinators and employers must implement the right processes. On the employer side, human resources departments should review recruitment and hiring practices, with a strong emphasis on inclusion. They should also work to further institutionalize onboarding strategies for both colleagues and management that promote a deeper understanding of how to support neurodiverse teams.</p><p> On a practical level, this might entail mentoring neurodivergent personnel during onboarding — providing clear success metrics, avoiding ambiguity, and allowing universal access to noise-canceling headphones and other accommodative tools and practices. In addition, some neurodivergent people are much more productive in familiar environments, so demonstrating an openness to hybrid or remote workplace protocols could signal a more receptive attitude toward their needs.</p><p></p><p> But these steps have little impact when an organizational culture fails to embrace psychological safety, trust, anti-bullying policies, and clear communication standards. In other words, no matter how much sunlight and water you make available, a garden won&#39;t grow in toxic soil. The stakes are high, and the payoff is potentially huge for forward-looking organizations willing to embrace authentic neurodiversity inclusion and belonging. But a cosmetic effort will have little impact.</p><p> By combating stereotypes; permitting flexible, results-driven work arrangements; and fostering welcoming organizational cultures where people don&#39;t feel the need to mask their cognitive differences, we can start to collectively harness the full potential of our neurodiverse workforce.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/building-the-neurodiversity-talent-pipeline-for-the-future-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>数据科学中连接器角色的兴起</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas C. Redman and Thomas H. Davenport . <p>Thomas C. Redman is president of Data Quality Solutions and the author of <a href="https://www.koganpage.com/hr-learning-development/people-and-data-9781398610828"><em>People and Data: Uniting to Transform Your Organization</em></a> (Kogan Page, 2023). Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) is the President&#39;s Distinguished Professor of Information Technology and Management at Babson College, a visiting professor at Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School, and a fellow of the MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy. He is coauthor of <a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047241/working-with-ai/"><em>Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration</em></a> (MIT Press, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Science]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images For all of the current focus on using data, analytics, and AI to improve organizational decisions and operations, too many data science projects fail. Even for those that succeed, progress is often slow and expensive. Why? Organizational gaps between teams are wreaking havoc with the ability to develop, apply, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Redman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>For all of the current focus on using data, analytics, and AI to improve organizational decisions and operations, too many data science projects fail.即使对于那些成功的人来说，进展往往也是缓慢且昂贵的。为什么？团队之间的组织差距正在严重影响开发、应用和扩展数据科学项目的能力。需要一种新型角色来弥合这些差距。</p><p> Let&#39;s not minimize the many aspects of data science that can trip a company up — from defining the right business problem to developing a solution and then supporting it properly. However, our diagnosis of the situation, researched in part with our colleagues Roger Hoerl and Diego Kuonen, shows that many companies struggle less with the solution and more with the organizational issues.</p><p></p><p> We&#39;ve identified three root causes for this. First, data science has been <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone">“bolted on” to the organizational chart</a> . This might have been acceptable a generation ago, when data science was reserved for relatively few problems, but it needs to be built in now that data science matters to every team.</p><p> Second, data science aims to improve day-to-day operations and decision-making, and that means disruption. But most line managers strive for control, predictability, and no surprises. Given that disruption and control are polar opposites, there is a far greater-than-normal tension between line management and data science.</p><p> Third, many companies seem to expect data scientists to do it all: magically understand the business and all its nuances, deal with data quality issues, and convince recalcitrant managers and staff members to change their long-cherished processes. Many data scientists prefer to simply create better algorithms, which means those other tasks often receive short shrift.</p><p> There is no minimizing these issues — they are deep, structural, and often political and may well demand additional management strategies. Here, we will address one critical aspect of the organizational problem, namely the gaps between the various departments that inhibit the development and deployment of data science models.</p><h3> Closing the Gaps With Connectors</h3><p> The obvious way to close organizational gaps is to fill them with people. We generically call people in these roles <em>connectors</em> . For some time, companies have assigned people who have job titles such as systems analyst, business analyst, coverage officer, and systems engineer to close gaps between business and technical departments. They&#39;ve also tried to close gaps that crop up in data science projects, labeling the people tasked with doing so data wranglers, data engineers, purple people, and translators.</p><p> While many such efforts have helped move data science projects along, it often feels like an elaborate game of whack-a-mole: Close one gap, and another pops up. Also, these efforts alone don&#39;t resolve some of the related issues:</p><ul><li> Line managers and data scientists often don&#39;t understand each other. This makes it particularly difficult for both parties to agree on the problem to be solved and for data scientists to obtain and understand the nuance in needed data.</li><li> Implementing a model requires extensive changes within the business: redesigned processes, training on how the models work, and upskilling to run them.</li><li> The two sides might not see eye to eye on IT infrastructure decisions, such as those related to technical debt.</li></ul><p> For those reasons, we recommend that companies approach the issue in a more disciplined manner, following these three steps.</p><p> <strong>1. Define the data science project process and identify the people involved.</strong> While the specifics might vary, the process should start with framing the problem and understanding the business context and end with monitoring/updating the new model in production. The critical work: identifying who, outside the data science team, must be involved in each step.</p><p> For example, when framing the problem and selecting a project, companies want to involve both senior leaders and middle managers whose teams will be affected. When it&#39;s time to obtain and prepare data, business domain experts who understand the data nuances and IT professionals who prepare data should be in the room. When developing the model, external software providers should be consulted. When it&#39;s time to insert the model into processes, business and process analysts, managers of the affected processes, trainers, and change professionals should all be involved. Finally, as an organization deploys the model into the IT infrastructure and then monitors and updates it, IT professionals, people building the data pipes, and supply chain managers should contribute.</p><p> <strong>2. Evaluate where connectors can help.</strong> Essentially, this step aims to clarify the gaps. Ask, “Are all of the people involved fully connected — that is, do they understand their roles, and is there sufficient communication such that work gets done in a reasonably effective manner?”</p><p> We find that most often the answer is “no.” Indeed, we find that connectors are often essential in the following ways:</p><ul><li> Framing the problem to be solved with data science: For example, executives might have heard some of the hype surrounding AI but lack a deep enough understanding of what problems it can help solve, or the technology&#39;s potential across the organization.</li><li> Translating between business and technical people — an age-old gap that has yet to be closed.</li><li> Dealing with data quality issues.</li><li> Communicating requirements, progress, and issues within the team — in other words, tying the many pieces of a data science project together and being the connector between diverse teams.</li><li> Keeping track of progress toward the overall goal of deployment and organizational change when nobody else sees the big picture.</li></ul><p> <strong>3. Clarify specific roles for connectors and put them in place.</strong> This step is generally straightforward for individual projects. We recommend that companies also consider having connectors between the entire data science program and the rest of the business. There is a <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/to-succeed-with-data-science-first-build-the-bridge/">natural tension</a> between line managers, who work hard to establish a measure of control in their everyday work, and data science professionals, who aim to disrupt things.</p><p></p><p> Left unchecked, this tension makes it extremely difficult for a data science team to establish itself within a company. Connectors at the program level aim to ease this tension: They help senior business leaders understand both the potential and challenges of data science, help data science leaders understand the top problems facing the business, and establish a portfolio of data science projects that aligns with business需要。</p><p></p><h3> What Companies Are Trying Now</h3><p> Given that building the organizational capabilities to succeed with data is so important, we are delighted to see companies experimenting and enjoying success with a wide range of connector roles. For example, Regions Bank and many other organizations make use of data product managers, who take an end-to-end perspective. Forty percent of organizations now take a data product management approach, according to a recent <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/data/cdo-report/">survey of chief data officers</a> .</p><p> Gulf Bank in Kuwait has created a network of data ambassadors to lead quality and data science projects at the department level. The Federal Statistical Office of Switzerland employs a “data science bridge” to coordinate its many statistical functions. Kroger&#39;s data science subsidiary, 84.51º, has a set of what it calls solution design consultants — people with business backgrounds who mediate between data scientists and business stakeholders. (84.51º refers to the longitudinal location of the subsidiary&#39;s Cincinnati office, and like early purveyors of longitude maps, the company makes sense of complex data problems.) Kroger&#39;s 84.51º also uses technology in the form of machine learning operations tools to monitor the status of data science projects from inception to ongoing management and keep all parties informed. Many other organizations have also adopted such connector roles and tools.</p><p> Let&#39;s examine the work at Regions Bank and the Federal Statistical Office of Switzerland in more detail.</p><h4> Data Product Partners at Regions Bank</h4><p> Manav Misra, chief data and analytics officer of Regions Bank, observed that many data science projects were not being successfully implemented, so he established the concept of <em>data products</em> and the new connector role of <em>data product partner</em> to manage them.</p><p> Misra defines a data product as an end-to-end software solution to a problem that the business has. “A data product leverages data and advanced analytics heavily in order to deliver that solution,” he said. Data product partners function as both data product managers and partners with the business who bring products to fruition and manage them over time.</p><p> Each data product partner is assigned to a particular business or support unit of the bank and attends staff meetings with their business partners in order to better understand their priorities. Most partners come from the business side of the bank, though some also have analytics backgrounds.</p><p> The job of the data product partner includes understanding what the business unit and end users need and starting the development cycle with a minimum viable product. During the early stages of the process, data product partners serve as bidirectional translators, connecting the opportunities of analytics and AI with business needs. At the later stages, they are responsible for assessing how the complete solution is adopted and used, monitoring how well the user interface is working, keeping track of how many people use it, and ensuring that the product delivers or exceeds the value promised in the original business case.</p><h4> The Data Science Bridge in Switzerland</h4><p> The Federal Statistical Office in Switzerland recognized that it needed to improve its core data science processes if it was to meet the growing needs of the Swiss government, so it created a data science competence center, a type of center of excellence. To make sure the competence center was fully connected to the rest of the Swiss government, leaders staffed a “data science bridge” — a group of connectors specifically charged with <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-data-science-management-process/">managing six high-level processes</a> :</p><ul><li> Driving collaboration.</li><li> Developing human capital.</li><li> Ensuring data quality.</li><li> Managing the project portfolio.</li><li> Ensuring a positive business impact.</li><li> Ensuring a human-centric and trustworthy application of data science.</li></ul><p> The bridge is paying real dividends. It has facilitated communities of practice in the customer base, helping people become more effective users of data tools and reports and encouraging them to exchange their experience with data science and AI, based on a common language and understanding. The bridge is reducing chaos in the six processes listed above.</p><p> Moreover, “most important decisions are taken on the bridge,” noted Kuonen, who serves as an adviser to the Swiss government on data science. (Kuonen is also head of Statoo Consulting, a Switzerland-based consultancy, and professor of data science at the Geneva School of Economics and Management at the University of Geneva.) Kuonen believes that the bridge will deliver more value as it matures.</p><h3> Connector Management Challenges: Five Questions to Ask</h3><p> Despite the apparent advantages of connectors, managing them presents some tough issues. In some respects, connectors operate in “white space” in the org chart, where management is always tough. For example, companies have not had much luck managing data stewards as they seek to align the definitions of various data elements across a company.</p><p> Companies should think through the following questions as they define their connector roles. The answers will vary by organizational circumstance, but some patterns are beginning to emerge.</p><p></p><p> <strong>1. Where should connectors sit, organizationally?</strong> Most commonly, connectors sit under the chief data and analytics officer or the data science organization, but they are sometimes found in business-side groups. If the company has been successful at matrix management for other roles, connectors could report to both areas.</p><p> <strong>2. How should companies attract, evaluate, and retain connectors?</strong> As data expert <a href="https://tdan.com/how-to-find-the-right-tweener-for-your-organization/31029">Theresa Kushner has pointed out</a> , connector roles are challenging, given that they require knowledge of both the business and data, as well as considerable soft skills. There are now several hundred analytics and data science degree programs in business schools, which are a good place to recruit connectors. Organizations putting together a team of connectors often ask business leaders to evaluate candidates for such roles; Procter &amp; Gamble, for example, asked leaders to identify one “breakthrough business result” that each candidate helped to achieve. Retention will depend in large part on offering these hires a viable career path.</p><p> <strong>3. What is the connector career path?</strong> Experienced technical people may very well recognize the need for connectors but fear that if they take such a role, they will lose their technical edge. Experienced business people might not want to fall off their current career path within their business unit or function. In the short run, companies should establish roles of increasing responsibility in the data science organization, such as senior and well-compensated data product managers. We believe that in the long run, many organizations will want every senior executive to have data science experience in their background.</p><p> <strong>4. Is more than one type of connector needed?</strong> Since some connecting is performed at very high levels, while other connecting is focused on the detailed technical level, the logical answer is “yes.” But a company might not be able to afford to hire more than one for a project, so some companies are asking data product managers to play a lower-level connector role as well. Other organizations ask connectors to play their roles across two or more projects at once.</p><p> <strong>5. What exactly are a connector&#39;s responsibilities?</strong> Since connectors might have the best overall view of a project, it is common to charge them with managing it end to end (as in the role of data product manager). This is appropriate if connectors are experienced and if they understand and value the technical roles on a data science project. If they don&#39;t, their connector responsibilities should be more circumscribed, such as translator roles that don&#39;t involve end-to-end responsibility for project success.</p><p> More detailed answers to these questions will emerge for your organization over time.</p><p></p><p> In our work with companies that have successfully employed connector roles, the software vendors and data science leaders involved have told us that the deployment percentage of data science projects has increased as connectors have proliferated. We believe that this is an important and ongoing set of roles that needs further institutionalization in almost every large company. Otherwise, data science might become a dismal science with a low deployment percentage and a poor record of improving business performance.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-connector-roles-in-data-science/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>问三阴：我怎样才能说服自己我属于领导者？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-in-leadership/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-in-leadership/#comments</comments><pubDate> Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang is a CEO coach and leads the Fuqua/Coach K Center on Leadership &amp; Ethics (COLE) at Duke University.需要建议吗？ Send an <a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">email to Sanyin</a> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managerial Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Dynamics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Pinnolis/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images I have just moved up to an executive job, and while I know I’m ready, I don’t feel very confident in front of my team. I was the first in my family to go to college and still carry the feeling of having to prove I belong, even though [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AskSanyin_Col05_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Dan Pinnolis/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question">I have just moved up to an executive job, and while I know I&#39;m ready, I don&#39;t feel very confident in front of my team.我是家里第一个上大学的人，尽管我在这家公司取得了很多成就，但我仍然怀着必须证明自己属于自己的感觉。我如何抑制冒名顶替综合症并感觉自己像一个领导者？</p><p>不要因为经历冒名顶替综合症而责备自己。 Some self-doubt is normal when taking on a more senior role. Instead of trying to banish it, you can transform it into something powerful as you build new relationships with your team members.</p><p> Impostor syndrome is seen as concern about our capabilities, but I think that concern arises from whether we feel that we belong in a particular space. Insecurity about being seen, included, and accepted is a relational issue that others on your team likely also feel at times.</p><p></p><p> One of the best antidotes for impostor syndrome, especially for someone in a leadership position, is to build a sense of belonging and community. By creating connection and fostering inclusion for others, we can also create a greater sense of belonging and confidence for ourselves. There are three practices that managers can use to increase inclusion and inspire confidence among their team members.</p><p> <strong>Acknowledge contributions.</strong> It can take courage for people to speak up in meetings. But when we fail to adequately recognize the speaker, or adopt their idea without giving credit, they might leave the meeting feeling unheard or unappreciated. Make a habit of acknowledging people in the moment: “That&#39;s a new idea — thank you,” or “To build on Tom&#39;s idea … ,” for instance. Managers can and must create an atmosphere where team members feel their contributions are welcome.</p><p> <strong>Make good introductions.</strong> Build a sense of belonging by introducing people with some comments about their strengths, expertise, and history. Good introductions help others know the role the person plays and the value they bring, but they also reinforce the person&#39;s sense of self and confirm their ownership of their responsibilities. As a leader, it can be especially meaningful to introduce members of your team in this way to people outside the company. It shows respect for them and confirms that they matter.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Emphasize superpowers.</strong> I believe everyone has one inimitable and intrinsic gift — their superpower — and it&#39;s important to acknowledge a person&#39;s superpower when you see it in practice. These abilities are often invisible, undiscovered, or minimized by the individual. Many of us don&#39;t recognize them in ourselves until a perceptive leader or colleague points them out. Helping employees see their gifts can quiet the inner voices telling them they don&#39;t belong.</p><p> The leaders who experience impostor syndrome most acutely are often those who came to the role from less privileged backgrounds, have followed a nontraditional path, or are from underrepresented demographic groups. Those experiences can build our awareness of our own vulnerability and an understanding of the limits of what we&#39;re able to control on our own — that is, humility. Add genuine empathy for team members to those qualities, and guess what: You possess the traits of the kind of leader who can be most effective in these challenging times. And you&#39;ll be embraced for your leadership by your team.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-how-can-i-convince-myself-i-belong-in-leadership/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>