<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 10 日星期四 15:40:41 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>在新的工作世界中蓬勃发展</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriella Rosen Kellerman. <p>Gabriella Rosen Kellerman 是 BetterUp 的首席创新官，也是<cite>《Tomorrowmind: Thriving at Work With Resilience, Creativity, and Connection — N​​ow and in a Uncertain Future》</cite> （Atria Books，2023 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Wellness]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book Tomorrowmind, have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled. During Work/23, an MIT Sloan [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>劳动力福祉是一个紧迫的问题：压力和倦怠限制了员工的敬业度并驱逐了有才华的员工。但<cite>《Tomorrowmind》</cite>一书的合著者加布里埃拉·罗森·凯勒曼 (Gabriella Rosen Kellerman) 和马丁·塞利格曼 (Martin Seligman) 发现了五种技能，可以帮助个人在充满活力的工作环境中蓬勃发展，即使是在压力特别大的环境中。</p><p>在 2023 年 5 月举行的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间，凯勒曼和塞利格曼解释说，他们使用缩写词<em>PRISM</em>来指代这五种技能。它始于<em>展望</em>——想象我们的选择、规划未来和恢复我们的能动性的能力——凯勒曼将其描述为“我们时代的元技能”。其他的是<em>韧性</em>、<em>创新</em>、<em>社会联系</em>和<em>重要性</em>。合著者表示，所有这些都是可以学习的，领导者可以帮助员工做到这一点。</p><p></p><p></p><p>凯勒曼和塞利格曼的工作建立在塞利格曼与美国陆军进行的开创性研究的基础上，该研究旨在了解哪些士兵最有可能患上创伤后应激障碍。他发现，极度悲观的人——相信坏事发生时一切都会崩溃的灾难论者——最容易受到伤害。他的研究还发现，在第一天表现出高积极情绪、低消极情绪和高乐观情绪的士兵能够更好地承受环境，甚至会因英雄主义而获得奖章。</p><p> “我在心理学领域工作了 60 年，一直致力于研究复原力，”塞利格曼说。 “那些刀枪不入、坚韧不拔的人都是乐观主义者。”</p><p>他们解释说，韧性依赖于自我意识和自我同情。 “从某种程度上来说，情绪调节是成年人成熟的基本技能，”凯勒曼指出。 “这是我们识别自己情绪的能力，停下来回应它们，重新评估它们，然后选择回应。”她补充说，这种反应最好来自深思熟虑、集中的地方，而不是情绪反应的地方。</p><p> Kellerman 和 Seligman 无法回答 Work/23 活动期间与会者提出的所有问题，因此 Kellerman 在下面回答了其中一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><p></p><h6>为什么在某些情况下，无论知识或技能如何，自我效能和自信都被视为负面特征？</h6><p><em>自我效能</em>是我们对自己以所需方式行动以实现目标的能力的信念。当我们在特定领域建立精通时，我们通过见证自己的成功来建立自我效能。数十年的研究表明，自我效能感与幸福感和成就感之间存在正相关关系。</p><p>相比之下，<em>自尊</em>——通常被定义为对自己能力的信心——是一个不太稳健的结构，可能会被错误地夸大。它可能与实际成就相关，也可能无关。正如我们的同事罗伊·鲍迈斯特（Roy Baumeister）所证明的那样，<a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1111/1529-1006.01431">自尊并不能预测绩效或幸福感</a>。</p><p>自我效能感高的人可能不会给别人留下自信的印象，而那些给人自信的人可能有也可能没有很高的自我效能感。当自信是错误的或自恋的时，它就会成为一种负面特征，但这两种特征都不适用于自我效能。</p><h6>是否有研究将悲观主义、创伤后应激障碍和自杀联系起来？</h6><p>是的。悲观是抑郁症的常见特征，也是自杀的重要危险因素。例如，请参阅“ <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/257552463_An_Examination_of_OptimismPessimism_and_Suicide_Risk_in_Primary_Care_Patients_Does_Belief_in_a_Changeable_Future_Make_a_Difference">对初级保健患者的乐观/悲观和自杀风险的检查：对可变未来的信念会产生影响吗？”</a> ”</p><p><em>灾难化</em>是悲观主义的一种极端形式，可以预测 PTSD 风险。灾难化也被证明与 PTSD 严重程度存在因果关系。请参阅“<a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32479704/">灾难化变化与创伤后应激障碍症状严重程度变化之间的顺序关系</a>”。</p><h6>您建议人们首先选择什么技能来实现成长？</h6><p>这对每个人来说都会有所不同。对于那些缺乏复原力的人，可以从这里开始。具体来说，重点关注以下五种能够提高复原力的技能：情绪调节、自我效能、认知敏捷性、自我同情和乐观。您对这五个中的哪一个感到最不舒服？了解它并寻找将其应用到日常生活中的方法。</p><p></p><p>我们的书《 <cite><a href="https://www.gabriellarosenkellerman.com/book">Tomorrowmind》</a></cite>在第 4 章中包含了构建这些能力的练习。对于那些已经感到有弹性的人，可以选择 PRISM 的另一种力量（前景、弹性、创新、社会支持和重要性）作为开始。 [编者注：Kellerman 和 Seligman 在最近的 MIT SMR<em>文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reimagining-hr-for-better-well-being-and-performance/">重新构想 HR 以实现更好的福祉和绩效</a></em>”<em>中也探讨了 PRISM 的元素</em>。]</p><h6>公司如何培训员工这些技能？</h6><p>所有这些技能都可以教授和发展。最好的培训形式是个性化和纵向的，包括学习和实践的结合。如果有的话，人类专家，如导师或教练，是理想的资源。</p><p>您可以从大型团体体验开始，例如演示或研讨会，但不要就此止步。向管理者传授这些技能，并教导管理者如何向他们的下属传授这些技能。寻找方法将这些技能融入您的文化中。所有这些都需要长期练习才能维持。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>应对企业多元化的强烈反对</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Victor Ray and Tsedale M. Melaku. <p>维克多·雷 (Victor Ray) 是爱荷华大学社会学、犯罪学和非裔美国人研究系的 F. 温德尔·米勒 (F. Wendell Miller) 副教授，也是<cite>《论批判种族理论：为什么重要和为什么你应该关心》</cite> (兰登书屋，2022 年)一书的作者。 Tsedale M. Melaku 博士是巴鲁克学院 (CUNY) 齐克林商学院管理学助理教授，着有<cite>《你不像律师：黑人女性和系统性性别种族主义》</cite> （Rowman 和利特菲尔德，2019）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com Corporate diversity is facing a backlash. Target, a company that has carried merchandise celebrating LGBTQ+ pride for over a decade, ordered some stores to remove such products after conservative activists accused the company of sexualizing children and organized a boycott. Anheuser-Busch lost sales in response to a promotion with trans influencer Dylan Mulvaney, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Ray_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>企业多元化正面临强烈反对。 Target 公司十多年来一直销售庆祝 LGBTQ+ 骄傲的商品，在保守派活动人士指责该公司对儿童进行性化并组织抵制后，该公司下令一些商店下架此类产品。由于跨性别影响者迪伦·马尔瓦尼 (Dylan Mulvaney) 的促销活动，安海斯-布希 (Anheuser-Busch) 的销售额下降，百威淡啤 (Bud Light) 失去了美国最畅销啤酒的地位。即使是福来鸡（Chick-fil-A），也许是企业保守主义的原型，反对同性婚姻和周日关门政策，最近也因聘请一位高管来领导其多元化、公平和包容性（DEI）而受到保守派的攻击努力。</p><p>大学也面临着多元化的强烈抵制。美国最高法院最近驳回了哈佛大学和北卡罗来纳大学教堂山分校的种族意识招生计划。结束种族意识招生可能会产生连锁反应，因为不明确的监管环境可能会阻碍组织实施当前的多元化努力，同时促使一些组织明确排除黑人、拉丁裔和土著群体。</p><p></p><p>最近的这些事件表明，边缘化或代表性不足群体成员对民权进步的抵制仍然根深蒂固，反对改善公平的努力也更加大胆。</p><p>多元化的强烈反对使公司陷入困境。屈服于反多元化团体的压力可能会让他们失去在其他消费者中试图培养的善意；塔吉特公司屈服于保守派压力，遭到进步积极分子的反击。退缩还可以鼓励保守派活动人士进一步提出他们的要求。虽然这可能会暂时减轻公司的压力，但从长远来看，屈服于反多元化势力可能会伤害他们。人口结构正在发生变化，非白人在令人垂涎的青年市场中所占的比例越来越大，对 LGBTQ+ 美国人的法律保护得到了广泛的<a href="https://thehill.com/changing-america/respect/equality/599240-support-for-lgbtq-rights-on-the-rise-poll/">支持</a>。消除歧视和增加机会对于确保丰富的人才渠道至关重要。对于许多管理者和员工来说，反歧视只是道义上的责任。</p><p>多元化举措很容易受到攻击，因为许多举措都是试探性的。一次性的长达数小时的培训课程、不受支持的新员工，或者随着反种族主义抗议的消退而消亡的项目，远远达不到使组织结果真正公平所需的变革性结构变革。真诚致力于多元化的领导者必须为捍卫包容性组织的成本做好准备，并采取难以逆转多元化成果的政策。</p><p></p><h3>不温不火地拥抱多样性</h3><p>当林登·约翰逊总统在马丁·路德·金在场的情况下签署 1964 年民权法案时，他是在回应几十年来全面经济包容性的呼声。根据该法案第七章，美国工作场所普遍存在的种族歧视变成了非法。大多数采用多元化政策的组织之所以这样做，是因为社会运动迫使他们采取行动，而不是出于对平等机会的崇高承诺。</p><p>许多组织回顾性地认识到，更大的多样性有助于<a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2019/04/business-case-for-diversity-in-the-workplace/">他们</a>开拓利基市场或促进创新。但关于多样性有益于盈利的论点并没有导致美国工作场所种族隔离和种族分层的根本转变。如果经济收益没有实现，领导者可以依靠多元化的商业案例来撤回对这些举措的支持。</p><p>虽然民权法推动了工作场所的真正变革，但它们在很大程度上是边缘化的。尽管黑人和拉丁裔就业在早期取得了进展，但工作场所废除种族隔离在<a href="https://www.russellsage.org/publications/documenting-desegregation">20 世纪 80 年代</a>基本停止，此后对黑人<a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1706255114">男性的</a>雇佣歧视一直相对持续。在受聘时，有色人种通常被指定担任与组织核心职能隔离的多元化职位，限制了他们的职业发展和流动机会。反歧视法的执行情况因政治风向而异，通常（但不完全）在民主党总统领导下加强，在共和党总统领导下减弱。正如社会学家弗兰克·多宾（Frank Dobbin）和亚历山德拉·<a href="https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/abs/10.1146/annurev-soc-090820-023615">卡列夫（Alexandra Kalev）</a>在他们的研究中发现的那样，试图遵守不确定的监管环境会导致公司采取有效性可疑的多元化政策。人力资源专家经常提出一些被法院视为善意反歧视努力的政策，尽管这些政策效率低下，有时甚至适得其反。</p><p>多元化的组织很少破坏白人规范和塑造这些规范的<a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0003122418822335">权力</a>。同质性仍然是标准，多样性是偏差。尽管承认民权运动给工作场所带来的变化，金伯利·克伦肖 (Kimberlé Crenshaw) 及其<a href="https://thenewpress.com/books/critical-race-theory">同事</a>在其 1996 年出版<cite>的《批判种族理论》</cite>一书中强调了多样性政策播下的不平等基础：“正是那些执行明确的种族隔离和种族统治政策的白人，他们是公司就业办公室、学校招生办公室、银行贷款办公室等决策者的工作。”</p><p>组织对多样性的不温不火的历史使他们没有准备好应对当前的强烈反对。在对警察谋杀乔治·弗洛伊德引发的大规模抗议做出集体反应短短三年后，公司却违背了他们的多元化<a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/esg/host-of-companies-sued-alleging-unmet-diversity-equity-pledges">承诺</a>。承诺包括增加边缘群体和妇女在高级职位和董事会中的代表性；解决留任、晋升和薪酬差距问题；与高级领导者和管理者合作，提高包容性领导行为的技能。公司增加了专注于 DEI 的职位，以表明他们解决不公正问题的意图，但没有以支持长期组织变革的方式进行转变。</p><p></p><p>我们怀疑，经济放缓以及多元化的强烈反对导致公司以比其他职位更快的<a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/diversity-roles-disappear-three-years-george-floyd-protests-inspired-rcna72026">速度</a>削减这些新的 DEI 职位。对 DEI 的攻击导致一些组织背弃了他们的承诺，即制定旨在解决针对面临持续不平等的群体的组织政策、实践和文化的举措。整合实质性 DEI 项目的尝试也遭到了强烈反对， <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/business-and-practice/coca-cola-scraps-diversity-requirements-for-outside-law-firms">可口可乐</a>放弃了针对外部律师事务所提出的 DEI 政策就证明了这一点。一些维权股东攻击公司的 DEI<a href="https://www.mvalaw.com/media/news/15112_WLT_McDowell.pdf">干预措施</a>，并针对有助于减轻工作场所歧视的 DEI 审计做法。</p><h3>对抗抵抗</h3><p>尽管我们描述了一个悲观的故事，但多元化计划可以成功。研究<a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/000312240607100404">表明</a>，当组织专门设立专门职位来管理和监控公平目标和计划时，多元化计划就会发挥作用。</p><p>问责制是维持有效的 DEI 政策和计划的<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/02/dei-initiatives-are-futile-without-accountability">关键</a>。虽然股权工作应涉及所有员工，但 DEI 专业人员必须有权追究领导层的责任。组织领导者必须负责设计、建模和实施重塑组织政策的公平计划。研究表明，战略性 DEI 举措是可行的，包括建立激励员工赞助边缘群体成员的辅导计划、展示招聘和晋升流程的透明度以及让员工对多元化目标负责。</p><p>最近针对多元化的强烈反对应该让组织领导者做好准备，应对内部利益相关者和外部反多元化活动人士可能抵制多元化举措的情况。发表支持 DEI 的公开声明有助于建立问责目标，但不幸的是，似乎越来越多的领导人在回应反多元化活动人士时选择沉默或投降。</p><p>我们看到了类似的现象，即右翼对气候科学的拒绝导致一些领导人淡化可持续发展目标，这种做法被称为<em>“环保”</em> 。最近的一项<a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/0047287520930087">研究</a>研究了酒店业的这一动态，发现消费者更喜欢酒店传达其企业社会责任努力，而不是参与“环保活动”。有趣的是，研究发现，此类沟通还促使消费者考虑自己选择的道德规范。同样，我们认为，公开讨论组织通过问责制解决系统性问题的承诺，可以减少对能够改变行为和态度并带来进步的举措的抵制。</p><p></p><p>组织应该直面多元化的强烈抵制，以及肤浅的多元化政策的空洞本质。随着多样性培训受到越来越多的批评，以及白人疲劳破坏了对种族主义的严肃讨论，组织中的种族包容性面临着生存威胁。抵制这种多样性倒退需要组织对为应对公认的种族不公正而做出的广泛承诺负责。</p><p>对于致力于将公平融入其使命、价值观、文化和实践的组织，我们建议采取战略规划方法。对隔夜结果的期望必须受到以结果为导向、可衡量的现实目标的控制，并有目标完成日期。该流程必须包括反馈循环设计，允许在计划、实施和执行中进行修正，从而为管理者提供检查影响和进度的机会。最近发生的事件使各组织有机会重申和加强其致力于通过消除不平等来创建公平组织的承诺。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>取缔大学平权法案将如何影响美国企业界</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Derek R. Avery. <p>德里克·R·艾弗里 (Derek R. Avery) 是休斯敦大学鲍尔商学院包容性领导力 CT Bauer 主席。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Recruiting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equality]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avery-Extension-a4312ir2142-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">迈克尔·格伦伍德·吉布斯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> 2023 年 6 月 29 日，美国最高法院以 6 比 3 的裁决支持禁止在大学招生中使用种族和族裔因素。这是一项重大决定，将产生广泛的社会和组织影响。尽管该裁决的范围仅限于大学招生，但我们可以利用现有数据来预测对美国企业界的影响。证据清楚地指出了两个关键结果：首先，种族多样性的大学模式将发生相当大的变化；其次，这些变化将对工作场所构成以及一系列其他措施中的种族不平等模式产生相当大的下游影响。</p><p>尽管人们可能会认为这些结论有些夸张，但对三十年来州级平权行动禁令的研究强烈表明事实并非如此。事实上，消除平权行动已经导致本科和研究生课程中代表性不足的学生（黑人和西班牙裔）比例下降，特别是在科学、技术、工程和数学领域；它还导致医学院和法学院入学和毕业的代表性不足的学生减少。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这些影响往往是持久的，而且重要的是，实施不明确考虑种族和族裔的替代政策对应对这些影响效果甚微。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p>将这些州级研究结果扩展到国家级表明，雇主在填补职位空缺时，可以利用的种族多元化程度较低的受过大学教育的人才，尤其是来自一流院校的人才。另外，申请人群体中的黑人和西班牙裔候选人被选中的可能性较小，因为他们的学位较少或毕业于排名较低的大学，因此资历较低，而他们更有可能申请并被录取。 -平权行动。一个不太直观的结果是，更有声望的学院和大学的白人（和亚洲人）毕业生与其他种族背景的人的接触会更少。这对他们的多元文化能力（与与自己不同的人建立联系的能力）产生了影响，并且可能有助于解释为什么雇主倾向于向种族多元化的商学院和大学的毕业生支付更高的起薪。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>黑人和西班牙裔社区的影响将是毁灭性的。最值得注意的是，帮助满足种族相似的少数族裔客户需求的少数族裔专业人士将会减少。尽管这似乎更方便，但在医学或法律（雇用律师和执法人员）等领域尤其令人不安，在这些领域，少数族裔代表性不足往往被认为是有据可查的种族民族医疗保健的一个促成因素和刑事司法差异。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>从更有声望的学校毕业或根本毕业的几率较低也会对组织内的种族不平等产生影响。首先，代表性不足的少数族裔不太容易找到工作，或者更有可能找到质量较低的工作。它会继续影响从进入到退出的整个人力资源管理领域的结果，因为最初的安置会对薪酬、晋升、培训/发展、保留/离职和部署等方面产生持久的影响。例如，即使是获得就业机会的黑人和西班牙裔专业人士也可能更有可能发现自己面临“最后受聘、最先被解雇”的现象。此外，起薪过低会影响其他公司的加薪规模或竞争性报价，并对个人的退休储蓄产生有害的复合效应。</p><p></p><p>那些寻求更具体证据证明禁止大学平权行动可以影响美国企业多样性的人只需看看哈佛商学院教授张乐天最近的研究即可。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>他利用平等就业机会委员会 1985 年至 2015 年间 11,000 多家美国私营企业的数据，研究了平权行动禁令对不同种族背景的人是否成为管理者的影响。他预计高管们可能会将禁令解读为一种歧视的许可，因此不太可能雇用黑人经理或提拔黑人候选人。结果显示，“在一个州采取平权行动禁令后，公司总部位于该州的企业中，黑人经理的比例增长放缓超过50%，这种放缓主要集中在首席执行官政治保守的公司。”</p><p>通过扩大大学成绩差距，大学禁止平权行动实际上进一步推动了众所周知的机会平等，因为在财富和获得优质学前教育和 K-12 教育方面现有的种族差异增加了更大的高等教育差异，这也不利于代表性不足的少数群体。具有讽刺意味的是，这进一步增强了为维持种族现状而采取工作场所平权行动策略的必要性。也就是说，任何此类努力几乎肯定会受到法律依据的挑战，而最高法院（至少目前的组成）已表明自己极不可能赞成此类努力。</p><p></p><p>事实上，13 个州总检察长最近以先发制人的方式通知苹果、微软和 Uber 等公司，他们应该期待对任何被认为促进员工选拔中基于种族的偏好的政策进行更严格的审查。他们继续承诺对“违规者”采取法律行动，表明他们打算将最高法院裁决的范围扩大到美国工作场所。这就提出了一个问题，仍然致力于种族平等就业机会的组织可以采取哪些措施来限制他们在这个新的、不断变化的就业格局中可能遭受的损失？下面，我提供四项建议来帮助从业者、管理者和组织应对这一挑战。</p><p></p><h3>不要在场边等待</h3><p>西奥多·罗斯福总统经常被认为有这样一句话：“在任何决策时刻，你能做的最好的事情就是正确的事情，其次最好的事情就是错误的事情，而你能做的最糟糕的事情就是什么都不做。”在最高法院的裁决之后，人们可能会倾向于维持一切照旧，观望事态的发展，并在尘埃落定后采取反动的做法。然而，这样做肯定会产生相当大的后果。也就是说，继续从同一所学校寻找申请者，而不根据学生群体构成的可预测变化进行调整，会使组织完全依赖大学招生人员重新调整策略来解决很少有人能够解决的问题。过去30年。</p><p>因此，像许多组织历史上那样，继续使用学位和学位授予机构作为人力资本的代表，可能会导致几乎所有就业结果中的种族差异扩大，并对非就业结果产生连锁效应。例如，最近的一项研究表明，在平权行动禁令实施后，代表性不足的少数族裔青年往往会立即增加危险行为（吸烟、饮酒和酗酒）。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>简而言之，预计代表性不足的少数族裔员工将会减少，种族不平等将会加剧，包括收入和晋升方面的更大差异。</p><h3>质疑一切</h3><p>好吧，你可能不必质疑一切，但如果一个组织想要在某件事上做得更好，它需要以不同的方式做一些事情，并检查它们过去是如何做的。例如，一位人力资源主管曾经告诉我，公司的政策是只从全国排名前十的工程项目中进行招聘。这种做法的一个意想不到的后果是，新员工来自与公司所在地完全不同的地理区域，而且新员工的流动率对于该行业来说异常高。 10号程序和12号程序没有质的区别，都位于100英里以内。为什么不从 12 号计划中招募员工，以减少新员工在第一年内经历极端文化冲击并离职的机会？</p><p>在当前背景下应用这一逻辑，公司可能需要扩大其搜索参数，以吸引在人口统计上与最近的申请人群体一致的申请人群体。在历史悠久的黑人学院和大学以及为西班牙裔服务的机构进行招聘是进行定向招聘的好方法——这一策略目前在法律上是允许的。在代表性不足的少数群体经常光顾的地方放置在线广告，表明您的组织有兴趣接收这些群体成员的申请。此外，在选择和薪酬方面，企业需要重新评估授予学位机构的隐性和显性权重。从一流大学毕业的好处已经分配得不一致，白人毕业生的好处比黑人学位持有者的好处更大。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>为什么不减少每个人的受益，同时为更大的群体提供更多就业机会？</p><h3>深入研究数据</h3><p>为了解决质疑一切所带来的问题，组织可以求助于他们的数据所揭示的内容。例如，尽管惰性和针对竞争对手的基准可能表明某项工作需要大学学位，但数据是否支持这一论点？与种族差异相关的工作要求，例如获得学位和从著名学校获得学位，往往会对代表性不足的群体产生不利影响——这是一种统计歧视的形式。在选择的背景下，当特定的决策工具使一个种族群体（或任何其他受法律保护的类别）的成员相对于另一个种族群体的成员有利时，就会产生不利影响。虽然如果这种差异与工作相关，则这种差异并不违法，但需要数据来确定这种相关性。</p><p>当要求学位、偏向精英学校毕业生以及使用最低 GPA 分数线时，当这些要求与工作表现没有直接关系时，可能会对代表性不足的少数群体产生不利影响。在过去的几年里，关于消除此类要求的讨论越来越多，不仅是为了加强种族正义，也是为了在紧张的就业市场中挖掘更多的高潜力候选人。尽管有些人可能将其解释为一种“降低标准”以增强多样性的形式，但应该指出的是，与绩效无关的标准是不必要的，而且可能是非法的，并可能导致员工资格过高，这可能对员工的态度产生负面影响，以及存在和表现。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>使用您的数据（以及相关其他人的数据）来确定工作相关性并消除不会提高您利润的障碍。</p><h3>选择潜力，训练表现</h3><p>尽管大学投入大量资源为学生的职业做好准备，但毕业生所拥有的能力水平和雇主所期望的能力水平不可避免地存在不足。例如，全国大学和雇主协会表示，雇主几乎一致认为沟通是最重要的能力，几乎所有学生都知道这一点。然而，尽管 80% 的学生认为自己非常擅长沟通，但只有 47% 的雇主也这样看待学生。关键是，超过一半的雇主认为毕业生缺乏最重要的能力。显然，53% 的雇主认为大学毕业生不是非常熟练的沟通者，他们不会留下空缺职位。如果是的话，2022年大学毕业生的失业率就不会是4%。相反，许多（如果不是大多数）雇主认识到，他们需要投资于培训，以使新员工能够跟上进度。</p><p></p><p>以种族中立但有效的方式识别潜力当然说起来容易做起来难。一般来说，用于选择员工的指标与员工的实际工作越接近越好。这表明高保真模拟、工作样本和行为锚定结构化访谈等工具可能特别有用。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>选择方法还应侧重于确定可培训性，以确保组织能够最大限度地提高其培训投资的回报。这可能需要为顶尖候选人提供机会，通过积极学习新的与工作相关的能力并随后展示他们的熟练程度来展示他们的可培训性。</p><p></p><p>在过去的半个世纪中，平权行动及其后代帮助改变了美国学院、大学和组织的种族面貌。这些计划是通过为那些历史表明不太可能（或至少不太可能）获得这些机会的人提供机会来实现这一目标的。选择“<em>机会</em>”这个词既是有意的，也是重要的，因为许多人常常忽视这样一个事实：这些计划只给予受益人表明他们归属的机会。尽管最高法院的裁决消除了一种有助于公平竞争的手段，但正如亚历山大·格雷厄姆·贝尔曾经说过的那样，“当一扇门关闭时，另一扇门就会打开。”尽管这条道路似乎不太明确，但创新型公司将通过寻找、吸引和选择来自<em>所有</em>种族和民族背景的最有才华的人才来创造和保持竞争优势。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>提出提升沟通技能的理由</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a>是硅谷通信公司<a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a>的首席执行官。她是六本书的作者，包括<cite>《DataStory：解释数据》和《通过故事激发行动》</cite> （Ideapress Publishing，2019 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[ROI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It’s hard to find a job posting that doesn’t mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Duarte-Upskilling-ROI-pie-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>公司表示，他们迫切需要能够有效沟通的员工——领导们在研讨会上一直告诉我这一点——但有多少人是真心实意的呢？很难找到一份<em>没有</em>提到沟通技能作为关键要求的招聘启事。然而，当面对候选人实际拥有的技能和他们薄弱的技能时，招聘经理发现自己在做出权衡，特别是为了满足紧迫的技术需求：<em>这个人可以像没有明天一样编码，但他的沟通很糟糕一个挑战。我们快点把他弄到这里来吧。我们会辅导他。它可以等待。</em></p><p>问题是，沟通技巧<em>不能</em>等待。人力资源、学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 等“人员职能”领域的高管明白，沟通和说服技巧在所有业务领域都至关重要，甚至在软件开发和会计领域也是如此。那些设计、管理、实施和跟踪员工发展计划的人已经知道善于影响组织中的同事和其他人所带来的商业利益。</p><p></p><p>那么，您如何向组织中的深刻怀疑者（例如，数据科学家们轻蔑地看待“说服”一词，将其视为<em>操纵的</em><em>委婉</em>说法）表明，在沟通技巧上进行认真投资是值得的？</p><p>您可以通过为投资回报提供可靠的理由来做到这一点。你可以从 L&amp;D 的那些人那里得到启发。他们对衡量培训计划投资回报率的方法以及传达这些人才的好处的最佳方式进行了长时间的思考。</p><h3>基于测量的案例，提高软技能</h3><p>在最近为我公司客户举办的一次活动中，我们的客户执行副总裁主持了一场小组讨论，讨论大型技术品牌建立软技能的方式以及投资回报率对他们的影响。两位 L&amp;D 高管分享了他们在组织中传达这种价值的发现：Catherine (Cat) Lang，负责为 ServiceNow 的客户和合作伙伴提供产品培训和认证，ServiceNow 是一家位于加利福尼亚州圣克拉拉的数字工作流程公司；诺埃尔·安德森 (Noelle Anderson)，Snap 的支持总监，Snap 是视觉消息应用 Snapchat 的母公司。以下是他们谈话中的五个关键见解。</p><h4>收集您在之前的培训中看到的投资回报率示例。</h4><p>一种开始方法是回顾组织中以前的学习工作，看看可以为利益相关者联系哪些点。例如，在您的组织取得重大胜利（例如获得利润丰厚的项目或赢得主要客户）之前，是否举办过有关呈现数据的内部研讨会？明确这种相关性并指出其他类似的相关性。您的某些软技能培训的投资回报率记录可能比您意识到的要多。</p><p></p><h4>帮助确定未来培训的价值。</h4><p>当您考虑或开发未来的培训时，请寻找更直接的方法来衡量技能提升的结果。例如，在 Snap，支持团队开发了一个推介辅导计划，销售人员、客户经理和创意策略师共同合作，为现有客户开发推介。参与者在制定、构建和练习自己的演讲时，会从经验丰富的沟通者那里获得大量指导和发展反馈——这是报名参加该计划的一大动力。他们还通过制作真实的推介内容来创造真实的、可衡量的价值。</p><p>回报——无论是续签合同还是销售新产品或服务——都是可以量化的。 “我们在后端所做的，”Anderson 说，“是与我们的 CRM 团队合作，在 Salesforce 中创建一个复选框，以表明每个演示是否是我们推介计划的一部分。”从那里，团队可以筛选出哪些推介带来了收入。</p><p>尽管 Snap 的 Anderson 团队向销售团队而不是公司 L&amp;D 汇报，但他们与 L&amp;D 作为“姐妹团队”合作，以确定和培养销售方面所需的软技能。这种方法可以在两个方向上带来红利：整个组织的团队可以向 L&amp;D 报告其领域的投资回报率证据，从而支持对全公司学习计划的进一步投资。就其本身而言，学习型组织可以就哪些类型的发展可以提高员工满意度和保留率分享更广泛的见解。 L&amp;D 可以根据团队认为哪些方面对日常绩效和销售影响最大来完善其技能建设计划。</p><h4>认识到质量影响——包括更好的员工保留率。</h4><p>即使有类似推介计划之类的东西，也很难用冷硬的美元来计算软技能培训的成本——尤其是当培训是由人力资源员工在内部进行或由经理和同事非正式地进行时。其好处也很难衡量，因为技能提升的大部分价值是间接的。</p><p>例如，考虑一下推介计划对员工的主要好处之一：提高高层领导的知名度。这对个人和组织都有回报，但不会立即体现在资产负债表上。安德森表示，批量的提案会分轮开发和呈现，到第三轮时，提案最好的两个小组可以向执行团队展示他们的想法，以获得更多反馈，然后再与客户分享任何内容。</p><p>当然，与高管的这些互动可以让推销本身变得更好。但想想其他好处：它们启动了指导关系，开辟了更多的发展和成长机会以及更多的晋升之门——所有这些都可以增强员工的体验、积极性和忠诚度。</p><p>你能量化这些结果吗？有时你做不到，所以你可以定性地衡量价值。这可能意味着就培训计划对员工行为、工作效率和团队合作方法的影响征求经理和团队领导的意见。从员工的角度考虑定性影响也很重要，因为人才保留对投资回报率具有重大影响。要证明这些无形资产为何重要，请考虑<a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/03/09/majority-of-workers-who-quit-a-job-in-2021-cite-low-pay-no-opportunities-for-advancement-feeling-disrespected/">皮尤研究中心 2022 年的一项调查</a>，该调查发现“没有晋升机会”和“工资太低”是美国工人离职的首要原因。或者考虑一下 LinkedIn 2022 年 3 月的《 <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220506202443/https://business.linkedin.com/glint/resources/employee-well-being-report-march-2022">员工福祉报告</a>》的调查结果，该报告发现工作文化的第一大驱动力是“学习和成长的机会”。</p><p> Lang 表示，在 ServiceNow，她的团队正在“关注员工保留率和对发展的满意度”，并将这些“与我们的员工声音调查非常非常紧密地联系起来”，以全面了解技能提升对保留率的影响。她说，“当我们开始试行新的软技能项目时，她看到了快速的采用。”人们对 Snap 的此类技能提升也表现出了浓厚的兴趣：安德森表示，员工将其视为公司重视他们的证据，因为它“通过对个人及其发展进行投资，展示了对个人的信任”。她还指出，“这些技能可以帮助人们在内心获得自己的动力、自己的行动，并以人们真正会做出反应的方式提出自己的想法。”</p><h4>制定策略，确定首先关注哪些类型的工作。</h4><p>与任何组织变革工作一样，提高员工技能需要战略规划。为了帮助这样的计划获得关注，在更广泛地推广之前，确定您将在哪里看到最大的直接回报并计划集中在那里是很有用的。</p><p></p><p> Lang 在 ServiceNow 的团队首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员，因为他们对日常工作的完成方式有很大的发言权，并负责使员工的努力与组织目标保持一致。他们越早清晰地传达这些目标并制定令人信服的绩效目标，公司就能越早获得实现这些目标的回报。首先关注总监和高级总监级别的人员也会产生级联效应，使他们能够通过一对一的辅导、指导对话，甚至是课程或其他学习内容的推荐，与团队分享他们所学到的知识。</p><p>安德森说，另一方面，Snap 更愿意首先提高一线经理的技能。因为她负责监督销售组织的学习，而员工的沟通技巧对客户关系有直接影响，所以她认为第一线是投资回报最快的地方。</p><h4>正面解决时间紧迫的问题。</h4><p></p><p>即使组织的利益相关者同意，在理想的情况下，他们应该优先帮助员工掌握软技能，但时间限制也会使其变得困难。在重要事项与紧急事项之间的长期斗争中，紧急事项往往会赢得领导者的关注和资源。安德森描述了她所谓的“此时此地”有时如何妨碍 Snap 实现更广泛的学习目标：“在很多课程中，人们都会说，‘我太兴奋了。我等不及要走了。他们出现了，但随后就不得不退出。”工作承诺和最后期限常常让人心烦意乱。</p><p></p><p>从文化上解决这一挑战的一种方法是公开承认它，并展示如何在学习计划和课程设计中适应它。创造这样一种期望：人们只在力所能及的范围内参与就可以了。考虑将内容分成更短的模块或小型研讨会，以便忙碌的员工更容易消化。在工作日留出时间用于技能发展。学习者在工作场所需要这种类型的支持，组织也会受益。如果高管犹豫不决，请提醒他们，让学习变得可行可以提高投资回报率<em>，并</em>在紧张的劳动力市场中增强员工对组织的承诺。</p><p>您可能需要稍微调整项目截止日期，或者在人们进行开发工作时减少他们的任务，这样他们就不会感到在下班后做“真正”工作的压力。开发<em>是</em>实实在在的工作。作为管理者，要以这种方式对待它，并与利益相关者进行讨论。如果您已采取措施帮助他们了解投资的所有好处，那么销售就会更容易。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>首席执行官可以促成（或破坏）组织重新设计</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Herman Vantrappen and Frederic Wirtz. <p><a href="https://akordeon.com/who-we-are/">Herman Vantrappen</a>是 Akordeon 的董事总经理，这是一家总部位于布鲁塞尔的战略咨询公司。 Frederic Wirtz 是 The Little Group 的负责人，为全球各地的公司提供有关组织设计问题的建议。 Vantrappen 和 Wirtz 是<cite>《组织设计指南：深思熟虑、高效和成功的重新设计的实用框架》</cite> （Routledge，2023）的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Human Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Structure]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Dan Page/theispot.com The Research This article draws on the dozens of major organization redesign exercises the authors have accompanied in the past 30 years across continents in a wide range of sectors, including B2B (such as payroll services) and B2C (such as fast-food retail), products (such as automotive) and services (such as engineering), and for-profit [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Vantrappen-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹·佩奇/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>本文借鉴了作者在过去 30 年中在各大洲的广泛领域进行的数十次重大组织重新设计实践，包括 B2B（例如薪资服务）和 B2C（例如快餐零售）、产品（例如汽车）和服务（例如工程），以及营利性和非营利性。</p></aside><p>首席执行官的基本职责之一是在认识到组织结构不再适合创造和交付价值后，领导重新配置组织的工作。有些重新设计是全公司范围内的重大改革，例如宝洁公司在 2019 年创建了六个基于行业的部门业务部门，其首席执行官将其描述为“过去 20 年来我们做出的最重大的组织变革”。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>其他重新设计工作的范围较小，侧重于特定的部门、功能或问题。</p><p>对于首席执行官来说，组织重新设计不同于其他大规模变革举措。例如，在公司战略调整中，首席执行官受董事会决策的约束，并遵循强有力的分析方法。在职能计划中，例如制定公司的数字战略，首席执行官可以将领导权委托给管理团队中的某人并承担监督角色。但在企业组织重新设计计划中，首席执行官必须积极带头，因为由此产生的变革将对文化和员工产生深远影响，也因为只有首席执行官拥有降低风险所需的全面视角。任何特定的重新设计选择都会产生严重的意外和不良后果。</p><p></p><p>多年来，我们在与组织的合作中见证了许多重新设计举措，并确认首席执行官对这些工作的领导是他们成功的关键。但令我们惊讶的是，有多少首席执行官仍在努力取得有效成果。我们发现，尽管管理文献中提供了大量且往往明智的建议，但计划经常会误入歧途或陷入死胡同。这里有些例子：</p><ul><li>商业服务提供商的新任首席执行官希望更广泛地重新考虑公司中心和组织的角色。管理团队的每个成员都有自己喜欢的重组想法：一个人受自组织团队的影响，另一个人坚持他们以前雇主使用的框架，第三个人认为公司应该只是一家小型企业的控股公司。区域性企业。即使是最小的对齐也需要很长时间。</li><li>多边机构的首席执行官发起了一项活动，以减少组织的孤立性。与管理团队的激烈辩论和几次异地会议导致了许多重大决策，包括共享资源和扩大首席执行官控制范围的计划。但经过一些幕后操纵后，决定被撤销了。</li><li>一家家族工程和建筑公司的创始人兼首席执行官退休，将权力移交给了他的一个孩子。新领导者计划使公司的业务流程和治理专业化，但退休的创始人却不断想方设法绕过首席执行官，破坏改善公司运作的任何努力。</li></ul><p>当我们回顾过去 30 年来所进行的重大组织重新设计（参见“研究”）并反思为什么某些举措不如其他举措有效时，我们认识到首席执行官可能会陷入以下两个陷阱之一：使用适当的框架，而且很简单，未能在整个过程中保持足够的领导力。在本文中，我们将提出首席执行官可以遵循的组织重新设计的系统方法，并解决高管如果要在整个组织重新设计和实施过程中保留完全所有权就必须防止的特定行为。</p><h3>应对组织重新设计的框架</h3><p>许多学者和顾问开发了支持组织设计系统思考的框架。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>我们在此介绍的框架强调了两个经常被忽视的方面。</p><p>首先，该框架认识到管理者在重新设计组织时永远不会从零开始。总有一个现有的组织可以为任何重新设计提供重要信息。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>即使现有设计已变得功能失调，最初采用它通常也有充分的理由，并且这些理由不应被忽视。因此，一个好的框架需要包含过去和未来之间的动态联系。</p><p>其次，管理文献中当前的大部分建议都集中在计划的上游方面（例如，确定公司的目的、价值观和愿景）或下游方面（例如执行和变革管理）。关于该学科的中游核心——即结构、流程和系统等硬性内容——的讨论较少。一个好的框架应该恢复这个重要的中游部分，同时将其与上游部分（通过考虑变革的驱动因素）和下游部分（通过确保第一天上线做好准备）无缝集成。</p><p>我们通过工作逐步开发的框架旨在通过尊重变革的动态本质并关注硬组织设计变量来克服这两个缺点。从第一条原则出发，它将组织设计思维的各个组成部分整合成一个逻辑流程，从理解组织<em>变革的驱动因素</em>到<em>概念设计</em>的选项、<em>详细设计的</em>可操作性、<em>过渡</em>阶段的实施以及重组的实际<em>执行</em>过程中必要的路线修正。 （参见“组织重新设计指南”。） </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>组织重新设计指南</h4><p class="caption">该框架将熟悉的构建块集成到逻辑流程中，以指导重组计划。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig1.jpg" alt="组织重新设计指南"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>处于组织重新设计前端的首席执行官需要了解此框架中突出的五个总体原则：</p><p> <strong>1. 组织是达到目的的手段。</strong>管理者改变组织设计，期望新的设计能够更好地帮助公司实现其业务目标。该期望基于以下假设：这些目标将明确、得到管理团队的接受、利益相关者的认可，并保持相当稳定。一家目标模糊或波动的公司很可能会经历破坏性的组织重组，而其业绩却没有太大改善。这就是为什么我们的设计框架首先要确定变革的外部和内部驱动因素。</p><p> <strong>2. 最好的设计是不可知的。</strong>可以说，做出组织设计选择比做出业务战略选择更困难。战略选择归结为从各种替代方案中选择一种能够最大化既定目标（例如 EBITDA 增长）的方案。通过战略，领导者权衡可用信息、假设和不确定性、资源限制以及他们自己的风险偏好。组织选择则不然。它们不是来自数学优化，而是来自对支持和反对多种设计方案中每一种的论据权重的判断。这就是为什么设计框架鼓励首席执行官考虑替代组织概念。</p><p> <strong>3.概念设计先于详细设计——只有后者才是参与性的。</strong>在概念阶段，定义了新设计的原则。这些涉及基本的组织变量，特别是架构（例如，集中什么和分散什么）。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>在考虑替代设计概念后，选择一个并进行详细设计（例如，端到端业务流程中各种功能的角色）。详细设计可以而且应该在管理者和直接相关人员的广泛参与下完成：他们最了解什么是有效的，必须在设计结果范围内运作，并且可以充当变革大使。然而，很少建议在概念设计中采用这种参与式方法，因为概念设计往往需要熟悉公司的（通常仍然是机密的）愿景和战略选择，避免与公司各种职能的命运和速度有关的利益冲突。</p><p> <strong>4. 组织设计通过故意跳跃和紧急跳跃的模式演变。</strong>深思熟虑的战略和紧急战略的概念在战略制定的学科中根深蒂固：在公司深思熟虑的战略的指导下，组织中各级经理每天都会做出无数的决策，逐渐改变该战略的具体形式。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>在组织设计中也观察到类似的模式：高级管理层有意决定对组织进行重大重新安排（飞跃），之后进行一系列调整（跳跃）以弥补原始设计中不可避免的缺陷。这种跳跃式的模式是完全正常的，甚至是可取的，因为完美的设计是难以捉摸的，而且公司的环境一直在变化。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>这就是为什么设计框架会显示循环，将缺陷反馈回设计中，以便解决这些问题。</p><p> <strong>5. 设计的证明仅在第一天后才会公布。</strong>第一天是指批准的详细设计投入使用的那一刻，重新设计开始对大量人员的日常运作产生直接影响：他们做什么、如何做以及与谁一起做。为了管理信誉、尊重员工以及对业务的影响，错误应该尽可能少。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>因此，在第一天之前就开始仔细的变革管理流程至关重要。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>任何员工都不应该对自己在重新设计的组织中的地位一无所知。</p><p></p><h3>为什么首席执行官的持续参与很重要</h3><p>在战略制定过程中，首席执行官通过一段时间内的临时干预措施来保持参与可能是完全足够的，例如参加异地高管会议、领导指导委员会或向董事会汇报。另一方面，在组织设计练习中，我们发现最高效的首席执行官几乎每天从开始到结束都密切关注流程的脉搏。</p><p>他们这样做的原因之一是，这为他们提供了形成自己关于适合目的的设计的想法的机会，并可能从根本上改变他们的思维模式。他们花时间让自己的想法成熟，因为没有单一的最佳设计，最终的选择很大程度上是对许多有效替代方案的定性判断。</p><p>他们还始终如一地参与，因为他们意识到组织设计过程是相当无情的。每个阶段都建立在前一阶段做出的选择的基础上，逐渐涉及越来越多的人。在此过程中做出的明确或隐含的微观承诺的数量——关于角色、边界、界限、人员、人数和其他因素——不断增加。不得不回头是痛苦的，部分原因是它是广泛可见的。如果说战略制定就像种树，那么组织设计就像种草：其效果立竿见影、遍及各处，需要引起重视。</p><p></p><p>日常参与的第三个原因是帮助组织内部建立对新设计的认可。高效的首席执行官坚持充分参与有关设计活动结果的沟通，与其说是通过众所周知的“致全体员工的备忘录”，不如说是通过与现场人员交谈。只有全身心投入到实际的设计工作中，他们才能做到可信和令人信服。</p><p>最重要的是，首席执行官每天都会参与这个过程，因为他们认识到人员和互动最终将成就（或破坏）组织。充分参与设计过程为首席执行官提供了独特的机会，可以观察和影响直接报告之外的企业人员方面。</p><h3>领导力弱点如何破坏重新设计</h3><p>在我们观察到的领导者无法完全控制上述重新设计过程的情况下，他们的弱点往往反映出以下四个特征之一：三心二意、绥靖、优柔寡断或无能。我们根据对组织重新设计工作的观察，提炼出以下四种原型：</p><p><strong>半心半意的首席执行官。</strong>虽然战略制定活动的触发点往往很明确，但组织设计活动可能是由某些利益相关者的游说而不是明确的业务需求推动的。在某些情况下，管理团队或董事会成员可能会提出疑虑。首席执行官可能最初并不认为这种担忧很重要，或者倾向于发起变革，但他们可能希望让利益相关者满意，结束辩论，从而同意考虑组织重新设计——私下里认为这些计划不会有任何进展。或者，首席执行官可能对重新设计的动机感到困惑、不清楚或守口如瓶，让项目团队来填补空白。在其他情况下，首席执行官可能会自愿或非自愿地离职。在所有这些情况下，首席执行官在项目开始时都缺乏充分的承诺，导致项目开局不利。</p><p><strong>绥靖的首席执行官。</strong>每一次转型都需要仔细的变革管理，通过深思熟虑的活动将公司从目前的状态转变为期望的未来状态，并帮助人们采用变革。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>然而，首席执行官在邀请人们参与时可能会太过分，这可能会导致流程过于复杂，步骤、参与者和审批点过多。例如，邀请更多评论而不是做出决定并冻结流程可能会拖延设计阶段。旨在表现出倾听意愿的安抚行为通常是出于好意，旨在发挥利益相关者管理的作用，但它也可以反映出首席执行官自己对设计概念的不确定性。</p><p><strong>优柔寡断的首席执行官。</strong>决策无能、无法做出决策或坚持坚定决策的首席执行官虽然很少见，但并未绝迹。一个典型的症状是，首席执行官在后期“在我的尸体上”威胁屈服，而经理不同意经过深思熟虑的执行团队决策。由于担心产生负面影响，首席执行官有时会在最后阶段做出妥协。在这样的组织中，不管首席执行官如何，事情都会发生。</p><p><strong>丧失行为能力的首席执行官。</strong>有缺陷的治理可能会让首席执行官很难在整个过程中掌控重新设计。在首席执行官不兼任董事会主席的公司中，董事会可能会干扰首席执行官对组织重新设计的处理。在私营公司中，退休创始人等有权势的董事会成员可能会干预设计并让首席执行官短路，保护旧的最爱或以其他方式扰乱有序的流程。这种对首席执行官的损害——无论是在概念设计、详细设计还是过渡阶段——通常在较低层次上是可见的，并且具有很高的破坏性。</p><p>计划重新设计组织的首席执行官最好考虑这些领导力薄弱的模式。他们应该根据自己的特质和阻碍其领导力的背景因素来评估自己的脆弱性，然后考虑如何克服这些脆弱性。</p><p>他们可以首先问自己四个问题：</p><ol><li>我完全相信这个倡议吗？</li><li>我会听取正确的人的意见而不让流程偏离正轨吗？</li><li>我是否准备好在需要时做出艰难的决定并坚持下去？</li><li>我能控制我需要拉动的所有杠杆吗？</li></ol><p>这种反省很重要，因为一旦首席执行官了解他们在这一关键变革工作中的领导力可能薄弱的地方，他们就可以努力减轻这些弱点。 （参见“首席执行官如何减少他们的脆弱性。”）想象一下，一位知道自己倾向于安抚的首席执行官。他们可能认识到，在概念阶段，他们应该咨询有限的高级管理人员，在过渡阶段，他们应该采用一种“遵守或解释”流程（当任何与概念设计的偏差必须得到解释和解释时）只有在获得批准该概念的治理机构批准后才能接受）并冻结设计，向员工保证公司将在启动后根据需要进行路线修正。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column callout-highlight--transparent"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性</h4><p class="caption">倾向于四种可能破坏组织重新设计的行为原型中的任何一种的首席执行官可以在流程的每个阶段采取行动来加强他们的领导力。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MAG_Vantrappen_Fig2.png" alt="首席执行官如何减少自己的脆弱性"></p><p class="attribution">来源：Herman Vantrappen 和 Frederic Wirtz</p></article></aside></div><p>我们与一家工业公司的首席执行官合作，他承认自己有一些无能力和优柔寡断的典型特征。他能够通过一些聪明的、具体的方式来弥补可能导致进程脱轨的倾向：</p><ul><li>由于首席执行官几乎经常出差，他任命了一位具有互补技能的首席变革官，与他密切合作，负责总部的日常项目事务。然而，首席执行官仍然负责这项工作。</li><li>首席执行官提议让公司的提名和薪酬委员会在概念设计阶段充当指导委员会。这为董事会主席提供了一个受管理的渠道，董事会主席对运营事务的频繁干预有时会损害首席执行官的利益。</li><li>在概念设计阶段的结果得到提名和薪酬委员会正式认可并得到董事会批准后，首席执行官能够在详细设计阶段更轻松地实施“遵守或解释”规则。为了避免概念蔓延，任何偏离概念的行为都必须再次通过委员会。</li><li>首席执行官鼓励公司各部门和职能部门各自任命一名过渡阶段大使。这些代表属于各自部门和职能的管理团队，并参与了详细设计阶段。他们每月与首席变革官会面，分享双向进展信息。</li><li>在上线之前，使用一个简单的跟踪器来监控一系列特定过渡目标的进展情况。完成百分比统计数据由首席执行官定期审核，并根据部门和职能公开发布。这产生了一些健康的同行压力，并帮助该过程保持吸引力。</li></ul><p></p><p>这个例子表明，首席执行官对他们明显的行为倾向以及可以防止重新设计工作脱轨的行动进行一些预先、明确和诚实的反思是值得的。</p><p></p><p>持续的组织重新设计是企业生活的一个事实。在大多数情况下，考虑重新设计有充分的商业理由，尽管它往往会消耗大量的额外时间、资源和情感能量。但要使重新设计取得成功，需要首席执行官的全力参与。然而，即便如此，重新设计工作也常常会误入歧途。首席执行官可能缺乏适当的设计框架，或者根本无法在整个过程中保持足够的领导力。他们应该首先评估自己的弱点——包括自己的行为倾向和与治理相关的限制。他们应该找到方法来证明他们是全心全意的、结论性的、果断的，并且最终是掌控一切的。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ceos-can-make-or-break-an-organization-redesign/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>向人工智能学习并利用人工智能学习：Duolingo 的 Zan Gilani</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Cognitive Technologies]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gamification]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Zan Gilani came to the U.S. from Pakistan to complete his undergraduate studies, he chose to study Chinese because it was rumored to be a difficult language. At the time, the tech industry was booming, and he quickly became interested in applying his passion for foreign languages and learning more generally in a technology-rich [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当赞·吉拉尼从巴基斯坦来到美国完成本科学业时，他选择学习汉语，因为据传汉语是一门很难的语言。当时，科技行业正在蓬勃发展，他很快就对运用自己对外语的热情产生了兴趣，并在技术丰富的环境中进行更广泛的学习。</p><p>这些兴趣促使 Zan 加入了 Duolingo，他在产品管理领域工作了八年，现在负责管理该应用公司的体验式人工智能团队。在这家语言学习应用公司工作，令他兴奋的是他能够帮助构建实现大规模个性化教育的解决方案：该应用拥有超过 1600 万的日常活跃用户，人工智能驱动的功能通过频繁的通知激励他们，个性化学习体验通过在练习中调整试题难度，观察和批评学习者的表现。</p><p> Zan 加入了<cite>Me、Myself 和 A​​I</cite>播客，概述了 Duolingo 使用 AI 和机器学习来推动用户参与的具体方式，并讨论了如何使用该技术来支持更广泛的学习。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E5-Gilani-Duolingo-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="赞吉拉尼"></p><h4>赞吉拉尼，多邻国</h4><p>Zan Gilani 是 Duolingo 的首席产品经理。在过去的八年里，他通过致力于亚洲地区的保留、获取、增长、游戏化和新用户体验，帮助公司的学习者基础从 300 万增加到 1600 万。</p><p>他目前领导 Duolingo 的实验人工智能团队，该团队使用生成式人工智能来构建能够更有效地教授学习者的功能。更广泛地说，吉拉尼正致力于通过外部合作伙伴关系和内部教育，利用生成式人工智能让 Duolingo 取得成功。</p><p>吉拉尼在巴基斯坦卡拉奇长大，目前居住在纽约市。他拥有哥伦比亚大学政治学和东亚研究学士学位。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-gilani"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>学习一门新语言是一个复杂的过程。一家应用程序公司希望人工智能能够帮助实现个性化、情境和动机。了解更多今天的节目。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我是来自 Duolingo 的 Zan Gilani，你们正在听的是<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天，我和 Shervin 与 Duolingo 首席产品经理 Zan Gilani 进行了交谈。我个人对今天的节目感到非常兴奋，因为 Duolingo 的处境非常有趣。在我们的很多节目中，我们最终都会讨论组织如何使用人工智能来增强或改进人类决策，这很棒。但 Duolingo 更进一步，专注于人类如何利用人工智能学习——大规模个性化教育，这对我很有吸引力。无论如何，这对我来说已经足够了。让我们听听Zan的说法。赞，感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>谢谢。很高兴来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Zan，首先，您能给我们介绍一下 Duolingo 和公司吗？您的角色是什么？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>当然。 Duolingo 基本上是一个教授语言的应用程序。我们目前教授 40 多种语言。顺便说一句，这些人中的大多数人都在学习英语，而我们的大多数学习者也在手机上学习，因此 Android 和 iOS 设备也是如此。我们是下载次数最多、使用最多的教育应用程序，无论是语言还是其他方面。我们拥有约 1600 万 DAU（日活跃用户）和 40 多万月活跃用户。我在公司工作刚刚八年，担任实验人工智能团队的首席产品经理。</p><p>我的主要职责是领导这个团队，致力于利用生成式人工智能更有效地进行教学，而且更广泛地说，我帮助公司在生成式人工智能方面取得成功。</p><p>我们现在专门针对生成式人工智能的主要用例之一是新的订阅层。 Duolingo 是一款免费增值产品。使命是提供尽可能最高质量的教育[并]让尽可能多的人[尽可能]获得教育；您所需要的只是互联网连接。所以我们有这个应用程序的免费版本，这是大多数人使用的。这非常好;公司的大多数人都花时间在这上面。然后我们有订阅级别。</p><p>我们最近刚刚推出了一个新的人工智能订阅层，名为 Duolingo Max，我也很高兴介绍其功能。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以实验性人工智能……它有点像你的研发实验室，如果你愿意的话？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>嗯，我想说的是，实际上公司一半以上的人都在广泛地从事研发工作——所有从事产品工作的人，以及致力于有效学习或教学的人，你可以认为是的，它作为一个实验室。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>太棒了。也许，对于我们的观众来说，您可以列出正在使用人工智能的各种用例或场所。当然，我的意思是，[除了]许多应用程序都具有的显而易见的个性化和游戏化功能。但请告诉我们人工智能是如何被使用的。</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong> Duolingo 自该应用程序问世以来就一直在使用人工智能，距今已有十年之久。事实上，它是由卡内基梅隆大学计算机科学教授 Luis von Ahn 和他当时的研究生 Severin Hacker 创立的。目前，它有多种不同的使用方式。例如，在增长方面，大量工作都用于优化通知。</p><p> Duolingo 与其他应用程序的不同之处在于，它确实试图帮助您保持动力。对于我们来说，从教学角度来说，我们认为学习语言最困难的事情实际上是保持动力，因为请记住：这是一件很难做到的事情。自己用手机来做这件事尤其困难——这确实是一件困难的事情。因此，通知以及收到通知的时间、通知所传达的信息确实会影响某人长期坚持使用通知的能力。因此，我们在通知的机器学习上投入了大量精力。</p><p>我们还在内容生成方面使用它，因此我们正在尝试创建有用的、合适的内容；我们也在那里使用它。然后，在该公司的一个独立部门中，即 Duolingo 英语测试，这基本上是学生上大学时必须参加的英语水平测试——有点像托福、托业或雅思的竞争对手；大多数美国人没有经历过这种情况——我们用它来检测作弊行为。我们还使用它在许多不同的地方生成内容。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这很有趣。该应用程序的实际核心是教你语言，它的动态程度如何？当它适应一个人的学习方式时，它的个性化程度如何？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>个性化发挥了一定作用，但很多体验是由学习科学家和教育内容开发人员策划的。对于大多数人来说，您想要学习的顺序大致相似。例如，每个人都会先学习现在时，然后再学习其他复杂时态。但是，我们使用人工智能进行个性化的地方是专门用于“Birdbrain”的系统，这基本上是我们拥有的一个系统，它针对您将在练习中看到的问题的难度进行优化。</p><p>关于 Duolingo 需要注意的一件事是它是完全互动的。这意味着感觉就像一场游戏。所以每次你学习的时候，你都在回答一个小练习，然后你就会做对或做错。你总是会得到反馈。所以 Birdbrain 的重点是尝试提出一个金发姑娘级别的难度，因为基本上，如果某件事太难，你就会感到沮丧，并且会失去动力。如果某件事太简单了，它就会变得无聊，你就会失去动力。 Birdbrain 是我们特别用于个性化练习的东西之一。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Shervin, one thing I think that&#39;s funny about that is that, in describing his product, we just took for granted the speech synthesis, speech recognition. These were avant-garde things 10 years ago, and now, Zan, you didn&#39;t even bother to mention those as applications of AI. I think that&#39;s sort of stepping back [and] seeing what now is normal.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s right. And I think one thing you have that&#39;s quite interesting and maybe unique is just the number of feedback loops you must have. I mean, usually, in a lot of other applications, when you think about corporations and retail and banks and telecom, etc., it takes some time to get feedback. And you&#39;re almost getting instantaneous feedback on so many experiments or mini experiments from so many people. Maybe tell us a little bit more about just the speed of learning and the speed of adaptation of your algorithms.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> There&#39;s a nice bit of mirroring over here, which is that there are principles for learning effectively that we try to impart into the product itself. And then, as a company and as an organization, we are trying to operate on those principles as well. Getting fast feedback really matters when you&#39;re learning a language. But it also matters when you are working on the product itself, and, from a very early time, we basically built out our own A/B testing infrastructure, and it&#39;s pretty core to the product process; that&#39;s the central component of how we do product at Duolingo.</p><p> At any given moment in time, you have hundreds of experiments being run on things that are very granular — the positioning of buttons [indicating] the pricing on the page for the price of our subscriptions, your classic bread-and-butter experiments — to also huge new features, new tabs. Basically, if it&#39;s not a bug, it&#39;s probably the case that we&#39;re running this in the form of an experiment. We&#39;ve gotten very, very good and very, very sophisticated at doing this.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Shervin&#39;s going to roll his eyes because I&#39;m going to go academic for a minute, but you&#39;re a classic case of experiential learning. And actually, I&#39;m going to give you a little bit of segue to talk about your <a href="https://blog.duolingo.com/duolingo-max/">Max product</a> here, because I think there are two pretty exciting parts of that. There&#39;s Roleplay, which is getting to the academic, concrete experience part of experiential learning, and then this Explain My Answer, which is a reflective observation and critique. So tell us a little bit about both of those and how those are tied to learning outcomes.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Definitely. I think it&#39;s useful to talk about where we were before adding those two features. Pedagogically, Duolingo has always been about implicit learning, so learning without telling you explicitly, “This is what you&#39;re going to learn, and this is how it works.” And that is the DNA of the experience, because we think it&#39;s just more automatic when you do it that way. People also get really demotivated and put off by complicated grammar tables, etc. And then, the second is that you&#39;re learning on an app, and you&#39;re doing this interactive thing — these almost gamelike exercises.</p><p> The two things that have been missing or limited is that, one, some people do actually want explanations, and that can be really efficient and effective when done in the right amount and in the right way. So Explain My Answer is a solution to that problem, and the nice thing about Explain My Answer that really only works thanks to modern large language models is that the large language models are really good at providing jargon-free, concise explanations of the mistakes you make. It&#39;s really tough, even for teachers, to try to do that without using jargon and also without being right on the money. And so we are able to do that with Explain My Answer pretty well. It can give you follow-up illustrations, it can give you examples — all of these things that make large language models, by the way, just good for anyone trying to learn anything by themselves. For me, it&#39;s life-changing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Or anyone trying to give a speech.</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani:</strong> Or anyone trying to give a speech, yes. And then the second one, Roleplay, is that, ultimately, for most people, language learning is not an academic exercise. They&#39;re trying to use it as a skill in the real world, and that&#39;s a skill in and of itself. So how do you give people the ability to practice that? How do you get them to simulate this? Chatbots are exactly one way to do so, because now, what you have is something that can speak to you at the level of difficulty that you&#39;re at, has infinite patience, and can then actually give you feedback afterward as well.</p><p> Even if people had access to native speakers, which they don&#39;t generally, you&#39;d still need a native speaker who has infinite patience and who really, really can understand what you&#39;re looking for. So Roleplay is basically trying to provide that experience in the app, rather than just having a text interface like ChatGPT and just having you speak back and forth. Basically, what we&#39;ve done is we&#39;ve broken down conversations or scenarios into these bite-size experiences, where you&#39;re talking to a chatbot who&#39;s going to be a barista or a friend that you&#39;re borrowing something from, and then you try to go through a very specific, short experience.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Sam, I have a question for you because, Sam, as you know, is a distinguished professor, and he&#39;s been teaching people — including people that are not in his class, like me — a lot of things. So my question, Sam, is … in all seriousness, though, what makes a good teacher, in your opinion?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Actually, Zan hit on a couple things right there, and that&#39;s part of why I was feeling somewhat convicted in his conversation. This infinite patience that he talks about — that&#39;s really important, and it&#39;s also really hard.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Impractical.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah.在人们所在的地方与他们见面是我们教育中面临的一个基本问题。我的意思是，我坐在一个有 35、40 人的房间前面，他们并不相同。就地与人见面正是赞所说的。所以，是的，你必须很好地了解材料，你必须让人们参与进来，但你也必须跟踪人们在哪里以及他们知道什么——呈现不太容易也不太难的东西——我非常被这个模型所吸引。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>那么，下一步是什么？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，是的，这正是我要去的地方。下一步是什么？我的意思是，如果我们可以用语言做到这一点，我们还能用什么来做到这一点？它在哪里起作用？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我的意思只是为了语言。因此，与人会面，对学生及其进步有很好的了解，然后能够进行角色扮演和大量的体验式学习，并能够以更通俗易懂的方式和更深入的方式进行解释和指导。这样你就可以重复它，而我不必急于记笔记。我的意思是，所有这些事情，对吗？ What is missing?我听到这个，听起来比普通老师要好。但在你看来，在赞看来，这位完美的老师还缺少什么？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>我认为，由于多种原因，我们距离成为完美老师还有非常非常非常长的路要走。我还想说，我们不相信，而且我当然不相信，到最后，你所需要的只是一个聊天界面，大多数人将能够真正做到他们想要的一切努力学习。因此，要回答第一部分关于为什么我们远离老师的问题，我认为其中一些是未知的，但在学习时与另一个人建立关系确实会产生影响。</p><p>学习新东西有情感的一部分，也有一种人际关系，这可以很简单，比如你去参加辅导预约，因为你不想让你的老师失望，也可以是这样一个事实：导师可以真正地关注他们的面部表情、他们声音的节奏、他们可以讲述的插图，以及他们与自己生活的联系方式。</p><p>所以说，我们距离还很远。然后，当谈到“嘿，为什么聊天机器人不能教你一切？”对于大多数人来说，你还是得有组织性，而有组织性是相当累人的。例如，决定接下来吃什么通常是您花费所有时间做的事情，或者决定看什么电影。同样，决定接下来要学什么也很困难。因此，产品方面的人员必须找出正确的学习顺序。</p><p>同样，有创造力也很累人。对于现实生活中的导师来说，扮演很多不同的角色并进行大量的角色扮演确实很困难。那么你需要一位导师，他也是一位出色的演员。人工智能让你能够通过虚拟老师来做到这一点，但即便如此，我们也不希望学习者必须一直自己想出这些场景。</p><p>我要提到的最后两件事是学习也是多感官的。这也是上下文相关的。理想情况下，您想要的是某种学习和情境发生，而不仅仅是聊天机器人。</p><p>最后要提到的是，人们确实需要一种进步感，才能坚持学习一门语言，因为实际的进步是如此缓慢且渐进，真的很难看到。所以你要做的是，你必须向人们展示正在填满的进度条，并且你必须检查。我认为你可能有一些方法可以在导师体验中模拟这一点，但这些是其中的一些我认为我们也关心在这之外构建体验并构建一条你可以走的路，以及所有其他使 Duolingo 成为现实的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Zan，我想回到你正在谈论的一件我非常感兴趣的事情，[这]就是弄清楚你接下来需要学习什么的想法。我的意思是，从历史上看，我上的每一堂语言课，我们都会有一本书，然后从第一章转到第二章。有人在某个地方真正思考了这一切的顺序。</p><p>但与此同时，我不知道这对所有学生来说一定是最佳的。我们会考虑推荐系统和 Netflix，或者音乐；你知道，我们已经和 Spotify 谈过，Shervin。这似乎是一个很好的机会。我现在可以学到的最能带来改变的一件事是什么？或者我不知道的一件事是什么阻止我打开下一部分？这似乎是一个巨大的机会。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>是的。我也会把它分成两部分。其中之一就是，一般来说，什么是有效的学习顺序，什么是有效的教学顺序？它对于那些已经具备一定熟练程度的人特别有用，也就是大多数试图在 Duolingo 中学习语言的人，尤其是英语学习者，因为他们已经在学校以某种方式做到了这一点，而且他们的知识是零散的，正如我们喜欢说的。</p><p>在这些情况下，由于经历不同，每个人的顺序会完全不同。第二个方面是你在需要更多关注的时刻特别遇到麻烦的事情。也许你只是在某个特定概念上犯了更多错误。也许问题出在动词变形上，或者也许你只是不知道如何很好地介绍自己。因此，我们有机会实际上花更多的时间在这部分体验上。</p><p>并不是说每门课程都是为一个独特的学生定制的，而是你的注意力和焦点放在哪里，你投入的数量以及你做的顺序都是由某种导师指导的。我会说这是一件很难做到的事情。这确实是一件很难做到的事情。我们不在那里，但这当然是梦想的一部分。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以这个节目是<cite>我、我自己和人工智能</cite>，我们对你和你自己了解不多。所以也许可以告诉我们一些你的背景——你是如何最终担任这个角色的，以及这段旅程是怎样的。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>是的。我应该回溯到多远？我是从祖父母开始吗？ Parents? Myself?</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>由你决定。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>好的。我将跳过扩展的传记。我在巴基斯坦卡拉奇长大。那是我长大的地方，我来到美国读本科。事实上，我在大学里学习了政治学和东亚研究，因为，第一，我对语言感兴趣，所以我选了中文，当我在大学学习语言时，最令人兴奋的事情之一就是总是尝试使用工具来看看能做什么。是否有效。</p><p>所以，正是对语言和技术的兴趣让我选择了 Duolingo。事实上，我开始从事营销是因为我之前做过一些营销和广告实习。当时，Duolingo 大约有 50 名员工，我们从只有一个开发应用程序的团队发展到拥有致力于盈利、学习和成长的团队。因此，我开始以营销人员的身份致力于增长，然后，大约一年半后，我转而担任产品经理。在 Duolingo 的大部分时间里，我都致力于增长，也就是说用户保留，无论是新用户还是现有用户，从而扩大我们在亚洲的影响力；那太有趣了。 Things like that.动机以及什么能够激发人们的积极性以及什么能够让他们保持积极性一直是我的兴趣所在。</p><p>然后，去年年底我们开始以人工智能为重点并领导这个实验性人工智能团队，因为基本上我们最终与 OpenAI 合作推出了 GPT-4。我们最终建立这种合作伙伴关系的原因实际上是因为我认识 OpenAI 上 GPT-4 发布的产品经理，当我们聚在一起时，我们很快意识到 Duolingo 是该发布的完美用例，因为对于该发布，他们真正想要的是表明公司实际上正在利用这一点来改变他们的业务，这些公司也是试图为世界做好事等等。所以我们，作为一家公司，基于这种伙伴关系并获得访问权很早就转向了 GPT-4，改变了一系列优先事项并开始真正倾向于人工智能，其中之一就是组建了一个尝试研究实验性功能的团队。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>非常令人兴奋。事实上，从动机的角度来看，你会很高兴知道我儿子为他的西班牙语天赋感到非常自豪，所以……</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>太棒了。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们有一个环节会问你一系列问题，这些问题都是连珠炮般的；说出你想到的第一件事。在人工智能领域，你最自豪的时刻是什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>作为一家公司，我们推出 Duolingo Max 非常令人兴奋，并且为新的教学时代铺平了道路。实际上，它是由 Edwin Bodge 和 Bill Peterson 领导的 Duolingo Max 团队创建的，非常令人兴奋。</p><p>我个人想说，实际上，我的团队一直在开发的第一个产品实际上是——实验正在上线。你可以把它想象成用于阅读的 TikTok，但它的所有内容都是由 GPT-4 生成的。它为您提供了广泛的内容，因为人们需要多种不同类型的阅读练习，而且它还需要听力。所以我很高兴看到事情进展如何。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>非常酷。您对人工智能有何担忧？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我总体上非常乐观，但我认为让我担心的是变化的速度太快以至于会破坏稳定。作为一个社会，我们的目标是确保我们能够在面对非常非常快速的变化时保持稳定，因为实际上快速变化正是我们想要的。我们希望快速取得进展，但又不产生任何破坏稳定的影响。这就是恐惧。我认为这是一个可以解决的问题，但这就是恐惧。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动是什么？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>我经常踢足球。有趣的是，事实证明这涉及到技术，但是，是的，我踢了很多足球。这是我最喜欢做的活动之一。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>那么，您想要的第一份职业是什么？政治科学，我想你提到过。当你还是个孩子的时候，你长大后想做什么？</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>很多不同的事情。从来没有一个答案。我想成为一名作家、记者、板球运动员——一名板球运动员——并从事国际发展工作；我什至想成为一名建筑师。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你在那里管理桌子。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>是的，有很多不同的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>您对人工智能最大的愿望是什么？您希望我们能从中得到什么？</p><p> <strong>Zan Gilani：</strong>我认为人工智能是我们能够创造最快进步的方式，这里的“进步”我指的是尽可能多的人[尽可能]过着他们选择的生活——他们是芊芊。我认为这是最高层次的目标，这就是大多数人生命的意义。我很高兴能成为这项努力的一部分。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>嗯，听起来你是的。 Zan，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。我真诚地觉得，对于我们人类如何变得更好来说，这是一个非常不同且令人兴奋的机会。听起来 Duolingo 正在做很多这样的事情。感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>赞·吉拉尼：</strong>非常感谢。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您加入我们。下次，Sam 和我将与 Pinterest 高级副总裁兼工程主管 Jeremy King 进行交谈。 See you then.</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/learning-from-and-with-ai-duolingos-zan-gilani/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>遏制假货泛滥</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Handfield, Anand Nair,  and Thomas Y. Choi. <p>Robert Handfield ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robhandfield">@robhandfield</a> ) 是北卡罗来纳州立大学普尔管理学院供应链管理美国银行大学杰出教授。阿南德·奈尔 (Anand Nair) 是东北大学达莫尔-麦金商学院供应链和信息管理教授。 Thomas Y. Choi 是 AT&amp;T 教授，也是亚利桑那州立大学 WP Carey 商学院供应链管理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted research into the state of counterfeiting from 2017 through early 2020. Funding was provided by CAPS Research, a joint venture of Arizona State University and the Institute for Supply Management. During the discovery phase, they ran an in-person workshop and attended the October 2017 annual strategic summit of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Handfield_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼尔·韦伯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者对 2017 年至 2020 年初的假冒状况进行了研究。资金由亚利桑那州立大学和供应管理研究所的合资企业 CAPS Research 提供。</li><li>在发现阶段，他们举办了现场研讨会，并参加了密歇根州立大学防伪和产品保护中心 2017 年 10 月的年度战略峰会。</li><li>作者于 2017 年和 2018 年对 20 多名主题专家进行了单独采访。</li><li>作者还于 2018 年 6 月和 8 月对 21 名供应链高管进行了深入调查。</li></ul></aside><p>无论领导者是否意识到，许多公司正在因造假者和不道德的供应链合作伙伴而损失大量收入。任何在街头市场仔细观察手袋的人都知道，找到看起来与真品一模一样但功能可能不同的假货是多么常见。在某些情况下，这可能会让消费者面临风险：例如，一家制药公司在黑市上发现了不含活性药物成分的假冒产品。此外，一家公司的合法产品可能会被转用于未经授权的销售，例如一家全球电子公司发现其网络中的分销商在灰色市场上销售这些部件，这些分销商原本订购了据称用于客户维修的组件。</p><p>每个行业的高需求产品都是欺诈犯罪活动的有利可图的目标。不幸的是，许多公司不愿意承认或向董事会或股东提出假冒产品的问题。高级管理人员经常试图用借口来解释这个问题，认为造假者总会找到复制产品的方法，或者盗版只占销售额的一小部分，不值得追究。这正中了造假者希望企业做的事情：忽视他们。</p><p></p><p>当公司开始量化造假者对其利润的影响程度时，他们可能会采取零敲碎打的方法来解决问题，试图防止问题进一步扩大。但这还不够。</p><p>我们的研究表明，成功打击假货需要广泛的组织职能部门的关注。它最适合包含多种方法并让整个组织及其合作伙伴参与的多层战略。</p><p></p><p>我们建议各组织制定一个一致的计划来识别、遏制和预防假冒行为。这一全面的流程意味着定期密切关注合同制造商并绘制产品如何在供应链中移动的图表。它包括确定消费者市场上销售的产品范围、部署隐蔽标记、审查保修索赔、教育客户以及与主要机构和竞争对手合作。</p><h3>传统策略不起作用</h3><p>关注假货的公司传统上依赖品牌安全功能来追踪犯罪活动。这些团队经常使用一些策略来检测假冒行为，例如在合法产品上应用隐蔽和公开的标记、附加跟踪产品位置的 RFID 标签，以及使用序列化与区块链相结合来创建防篡改的交易记录。例如，符合 GS1 全球追溯标准的条形码用于追踪 COVID-19 疫苗。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>但对于许多组织来说，这些策略还不够。</p><p>产品假冒和非法转移仍然普遍存在：我们 2018 年对 21 名供应链高管进行的调查显示，近一半的高管存在持续存在的问题或在前一年经历过事件。超过 70% 的人表示他们在过去五年中发生过事故。 （参见“研究”。）一位高管告诉我们，他的公司发现相当于整个工厂每月生产的产品被送往黑市，这主要是由于从其自己的供应商之一转移。</p><p>经济合作与发展组织表示，假冒伪劣问题已发展为 2019 年价值 4,640 亿美元的问题，占世界贸易额的 2.5%。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>人们曾经认为造假者只追求高价值或奢侈品，例如药品、名牌手袋或香水。但现在市场上充斥着假鞋、农药、化妆品、玩具、汽车零部件和医疗设备。造假者瞄准任何容易获利的行业和产品线。</p><p>虽然公司可能永远无法完全消除不良行为者复制产品或从授权渠道转移商品的行为，但它们可以显着减少造假者的市场渗透并挽回收入损失。成功的方法可能包括切断造假者进入市场的机会，消除他们对未经授权的商品的供应，或者使产品更难以复制。在这里，我们将详细介绍强有力的行动计划所包含的三项活动：识别、遏制和预防。</p><h3>识别：深入了解问题的范围和性质</h3><p>获得关于假冒问题严重性的基线是关键的第一步。随着问题的严重程度逐渐明朗，关闭该问题的潜在投资回报也开始显现。这可以帮助为防伪团队建立与业务目标和成果相一致的绩效指标。指标示例包括每年因非法产品贸易而损失的收入金额或百分比、收回的总收入（之前因假冒销售而不知不觉损失的美元）以及已确认的非法贸易、假冒、转移事件的数量和篡改。</p><p><strong>创建跨职能的品牌安全团队。</strong>针对当前问题制定切合实际的措施通常需要进行深入调查，其中涉及应用市场渠道分析，探索来自组织内部和外部的销售数据和其他信息的多个来源。为了发挥作用，品牌安全团队应包括销售、营销、运营、采购、物流、财务和会计以及核心品牌安全职能部门的参与者。此类团队通常由全球品牌保护官领导，该官在许多情况下具有执法背景，通常向首席运营官报告。</p><p><strong>检查内部和市场数据以清除可疑活动。</strong>鉴于线索通常隐藏在有关销售、保修、退货和其他产品指标的数据中，公司可能很难发现假冒活动，更不用说衡量假冒活动了。除非有人在寻找，否则异常活动很容易被忽视。</p><p>良好的第一步是首先查看网上销售的商品。电子商务已成为助长假货行业的完美渠道。消费者可能会无意中从在线零售商那里购买产品，而这些零售商不会验证其平台上产品的来源以及是否合法。 Despite counterfeit sites being shut down regularly by Amazon (and, in China, Alibaba), operators trading in fake goods regularly open up again under a different name the next day. Amazon reported that it blocked 10 billion fake listings and destroyed 2 million counterfeit products in 2020 alone. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> Since e-commerce sites are frequently a counterfeiter&#39;s primary source of sales, companies can begin by investigating where their products — either genuine or fake — are being sold online. Looking for common attributes of counterfeiter websites can narrow down the pool of suspicious activity. For instance, a company might find four different sellers on Amazon offering an exact copy of its handbag, listing the same details and even photos. An indicator of potential counterfeiters might include spelling or grammatical errors, blurry photos, or other details that don&#39;t look quite right.</p><p> Another important data source is warranty returns. When a consumer sends a product back because it is defective (and counterfeits often are), detective work can track down where it was purchased and how. This can lead to the origin of market entry for counterfeit goods and a starting point to find their downstream source. A global medical products company we looked at hired a global brand protection officer who examined warranty and returns data, field service requests, and sales data. In his first 100 days, he found 1,000 confirmed incidents of illicit trade, counterfeiting, diversion, and tampering. This amounted to $1.4 billion — 2% of revenue — lost annually to illegal product trade.</p><p> Estimating counterfeit sales is a difficult but essential task: Companies must establish a baseline against which to gauge the effects of anti-counterfeit measures. Having an accurate understanding of the scope of the problem is a prerequisite for deciding how much to invest and what ROI to expect from anti-counterfeiting measures. In many cases, business decision makers are unaware of the extent to which their revenue and reputation are in jeopardy.</p><p> <strong>Map the supply and distribution chain.</strong> Many companies are surprised to learn that bad actors are active within their own supply chains. Overproduction, black-market sales, and unauthorized distribution are common sources of leakage that may result in a product, or copies of it, being sold through channels that a company knows nothing about. That&#39;s why an important early step is to identify the manufacturing and distribution channels through which the company&#39;s products travel.</p><p></p><p> The brand owner at a large global apparel company told us that he had heard through his distributor network that the brand was being sold in Mexico even though the company had no authorized retail presence there. To track where these products were coming from, the director hunted down bills of lading and shipping records for the ocean freight shipments that were going to Mexico. The paper trail showed that the goods were shipped from a port in Israel — by the same authorized manufacturer that was producing the company&#39;s branded product in the United States. The apparel company eventually tracked down the clothes, which were genuine products, made under the same specifications and from the same materials, but were being illicitly distributed outside of the contractual agreement between the parties. When the apparel company set up a global brand security function and mapped its entire supply network, it found that similar cases of product diversion were occurring all over the world.</p><p> Analyzing how much is being spent on raw materials in the upstream supply chains is a good place to start mapping a supply base. Procurement can reach out to the accounting team to track all third-party purchases being made on the company&#39;s behalf (a document generally known as a <em>spend analysis</em> ). If a supplier is buying more raw materials and is operating at a higher production level than what the company is ordering, this is a telltale sign that the additional product may be moving into the black market. This requires full visibility into the supply chain, beyond just Tier 1 suppliers (which is increasingly important for other reasons, in particular to manage risk related to labor or environmental violations). Some suppliers may be reluctant to disclose their upstream suppliers for competitive reasons but can be reassured that the query is for security purposes and not an attempt to cut them out of the chain.</p><p></p><h3> Containment: Limit the Problem&#39;s Spread</h3><p> With a dedicated team in place, an initial sense of the problem&#39;s scope, and an understanding of the particular counterfeiting and diversion risks that it&#39;s most vulnerable to, a company can begin to manage the problem systematically in order to contain it.</p><p> <strong>Analyze product segments.</strong> One of the key tasks for the investigation team is segmenting products by channel, margin, volume, and risk of counterfeit activity. This ensures that the team&#39;s attention is being directed toward the most vulnerable market channels first.</p><p> In many cases, a current-state analysis of a company&#39;s supply and distribution processes helps reveal a common set of product segments that counterfeiters go after. In particular, our research found that product lines with high complexity based on the variety of finished products, level of finished-product customization, geographical span of suppliers, number of tiers in the supply chain, predictability of demand, and variation in manufacturing volumes. Examples of items in this category include aircraft and automotive replacement parts, toys, high-end apparel, branded pharmaceutical products, and consumer electronics. Counterfeiters are more likely to opportunistically target product segments characterized by a greater level of complexity and exploit this complexity to their advantage.</p><p> We interviewed executives at a biotech manufacturer who knew that counterfeit products were showing up in the market but did not know the source. The brand protection team started by segmenting products into those that were big targets for counterfeiters (in this case, high-margin items) and analyzing data to estimate the number of incidents per brand. The team — formed through a close collaboration among franchises, brand owners, and regional sales managers — then rolled out a plan to franchise partners and country business units. This established brand protection priorities by product line and provided a system to track customer-reported incidents by brand and conduct data reviews every six months.</p><p> At the same time, analysts began collecting market intelligence on supply chain vulnerabilities, including potential logistics disruptions and the threat of regulatory intervention, that posed significant risks for business plans and growth targets by region. Cumulatively, these efforts helped the manufacturer prioritize those businesses and regions where brand protection could best safeguard market revenue from sudden disruptions. In the process, the team identified a significant counterfeit and diversion activity affecting a blockbuster infusion drug that was putting many patients at risk. The company said it was able to eventually reduce the number of incidents from 100 per year to zero. This required persistent efforts to deduce the source of each incident through detailed analysis and the introduction of countermeasures — including sending a message to counterfeiters warning that they would be pursued, in hopes of convincing them to go look for an easier target.</p><p> This kind of analysis begins with identifying an initial clue and following the thread of activity. The initial problem may manifest itself as a minor issue such as a customer warranty problem, a dealer who seems to be ordering too many replacement parts, or a spate of customer returns on a particular brand of product. Any of these issues may be a hint that leads to a channel of counterfeiting activity.</p><p> <strong>Start with e-commerce sites, and reach out to customs and other authorities.</strong> A team of analysts should be hunting down in-the-open counterfeit operations on e-commerce sites on an ongoing basis and reporting them to the platform operator, such as Amazon, and to law enforcement. At the very least, this introduces more friction into some bad actors&#39; businesses to slow them down.</p><p> Counterfeit products almost always have to cross borders and pass through transshipment points and customs inspections overseen by law enforcement entities. These are critical players in the supply chain, and organizations must think of them as partners in the battle against revenue loss and intellectual property theft. These relationships are particularly important in highly regulated environments, such as pharmaceuticals, food, aerospace, and automotive manufacturing, where counterfeit products can endanger their users.</p><p> An official with US Customs and Border Protection (CBP) told us that it can be challenging to get brand owners to understand the CBP&#39;s process and play their part in helping the agency fight the problem. “We are in the field, inspecting containers,” he said. “If a CBP officer opens a container and sees something that looks suspicious, they will first look in our internal database of registered brands. If the officer doesn&#39;t see anything, there is nothing they can do.” Registering brands with the CBP and US Patent and Trademark Office is a critical step in containing counterfeiting.</p><p> <strong>Educate (and warn) customers.</strong> It is imperative that consumers are educated about the possibility and risks of buying fake goods. Companies should make customers aware, through brand marketing, that if they buy from an unverified online third-party seller, they bear the risk of not having the product covered by warranty — or, worse yet, having it fail with dire consequences. One company we know of began adding a statement on its Amazon website warning that products returned to it that were not licensed would not be under warranty. Companies should also emphasize to customers the importance of registering the product serial number for warranty purposes, which protects them if a legitimate product they&#39;ve purchased turns out to be flawed or faulty. If a customer tries to register the serial number for a counterfeit product, it will show up as an error and alert the brand security team to a problem.</p><h3> Prevention: Stop Future Counterfeit Ops Before They Start</h3><p> Once an organization discovers how the spread of counterfeit products in its market channels works and has taken initial steps to contain the problem, it must continue to monitor criminal activity and establish strong preventive measures. There are important roles for numerous functions in the company to play at this stage.</p><p> <strong>Product packaging experts should explore digital tracing technology.</strong> Features in current tracing technologies offer positive product authentication, can indicate tampering, can increase the difficulty of replication, and permit product tracking and tracing. Secure markings — which use a variety of packaging, blockchain, and serial marking technologies — are one method for tracking products. Many industries are working with standards organizations like ASTM International or GS1 to develop common methods for verifying products. This can help avoid the problem where counterfeiters try to copy not just the product but the digital marking, too.</p><p> In the biotech example mentioned previously, the brand protection team worked with the business to identify covert and overt authentication capabilities, which created automatic alerts when counterfeit products were being sold through market channels. The team also created a comprehensive customer communication plan using web advertisements, targeted email and Twitter campaigns, and retailer alerts about the dangers of buying from unauthorized sources. The campaign created awareness in the company&#39;s sales partner network and set the stage to identify where new counterfeit sales were occurring.</p><p> <strong>Quality assurance should review data to track down instances of product problems and returns.</strong> QA can create triggers in its data collection processes that flag potential illegitimate activities. We know of a company that noticed an uptick in its product returns, discovered that the products were not legitimate, and tracked them down to the point of sale — which revealed the source of the counterfeiting.</p><p> <strong>Supply management should step up efforts to audit suppliers.</strong> It can be particularly fruitful to track overproduction by suppliers, as well as how they dispose of products that don&#39;t conform to quality standards — products that can end up moving through black market channels and thus avoiding trade compliance policies. One large apparel company began monitoring the inventory levels within its supplier&#39;s facilities and noticed that the supplier&#39;s inbound raw-material inventories were much greater than the volume of finished goods it was shipping to the company. This was an indication that product was being produced and sold elsewhere through other channels.</p><p> <strong>Logistics should map supply routes to document compliance on the part of transportation providers.</strong> This can help ensure chain of custody along global supply chains, particularly at handoff points such as ports, warehouses, and distribution centers. Companies with multitier distributor channels should document every logistics handoff and conduct random audits to determine whether there are proper security personnel and locked gates at all distribution centers.</p><p> <strong>Human resources might want to consider monitoring employees who are dealing directly with targeted products.</strong> This may include conducting background checks, as well as increasing training to enhance staff awareness. If there is a high level of missing inventory or a sudden increase or drop in product sales, investigations may be required.</p><p> <strong>Aftermarket sales should track warranty claims and parts sales to identify product-quality problems.</strong> As with the quality assurance team, those at the front line of aftermarket sales are in a position to learn that products aren&#39;t performing as expected, which, again, may indicate that counterfeits are entering market channels. For example, a large retailer made the decision to limit its distribution channels and authorized resellers, recognizing the high potential for counterfeit products in these particular sales channels, especially e-commerce.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Counterfeiting and product diversion are not crimes that a single organization can combat. They require the diligence of brands, retailers, packaging companies, and logistics businesses. This is a rare instance where joining with competitors can yield important insights. Companies should consider joining a consortium and partnering with industry counterparts. Industry-specific groups include the Automotive Anti-Counterfeiting Council for vehicle manufacturers and Rx-360 for pharmaceutical companies. Members of React, a large anti-counterfeiting network, include Marvel Entertainment, Mattel, Pfizer, Philips, Prada, and Timberland.</p><p> Counterfeiting is also not just a private-sector supply chain problem. Labor and human rights advocates, consumer education agencies, customs agents, federal and state law enforcement agencies, local police, and consumers of counterfeit products all have an interest and role in ferreting out unauthorized activity. While counterfeiting and product diversion cannot be eliminated, dedicated efforts can curtail both significantly.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Dismantle Career Roadblocks for More Equitable Outcomes</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian is a cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts. That was the message from [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/W23-QA03_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts.</p><p> That was the message from Haig R. Nalbantian, cofounder and coleader of the Workforce Sciences Institute, during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023. Nalbantian helps organizations apply evidence-based, empirical methods to strengthen their DEI efforts and retention strategies and asserts that “the surging use of analytics in the HR domain to inform work and workforce management” is a big part of the future of work.</p><p></p><p> While talent and drive are important in shaping careers, situational factors profoundly affect what happens to employees at work. They include employees&#39; access to “accelerator” roles, such as customer-facing jobs; how employees navigate flexible work arrangements, such as part-time status; and employees&#39; reporting relationships, such as whether they report to higher-level or high-performing supervisors. Nalbantian noted that these easy-to-identify circumstances, which he called <em>explained differences</em> , are prevalent.</p><p></p><p> Many organizations also have pervasive and sizable <em>unexplained disparities</em> regarding who gets chosen for promotions. Nalbantian said that in both his own studies and others, “women are actually more likely to be highly rated” by their managers at elite, large employers — all things being equal — “but in the majority of companies, they&#39;re less likely to be promoted.”</p><p> He said it is critical that companies address the explained differences and explore the unexplained disparities.</p><p> Nalbantian wasn&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the event, so he answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> Does your research address intersectionality in its analysis? You talked about women and people of color, but what about women of color and other people with multiple intersecting minority identities?</h6><p> In many of the client cases covered in my study, we did indeed examine intersectionality directly. We&#39;ve done this quite a bit in larger US-based organizations that have adequate populations of these demographic groups for modeling purposes.</p><p> One of the areas of particular interest to client organizations is intersectionality with respect to reporting relationships. That is, do the specific demographics of one&#39;s supervisor affect whether the employee is promoted, is highly rated, or gets higher pay increases? For example, do White male supervisors treat Black female reports worse than White male or White female reports? Do White female supervisors help the prospects of their female reports, regardless of color?</p><p> I can say that there are few regularities in these results — certainly far less than the results I&#39;ve reported with respect to performance ratings, roles, supervisor performance and level, and flexible working.</p><p></p><h6> Has this research mapped across socioeconomic status as an intersectional influence?</h6><p> Unfortunately, we&#39;ve had much more limited data on socioeconomic factors, in part because most of our clients focus these studies on their salaried populations, ignoring their hourly workers. This concerns me, as it reveals a tendency to discount front-line workers. I try to remind organizations that what happens in their front-line ranks can have a major impact on business results. I&#39;ve seen and documented this in client assignments. Still, the tendency of organizations is to prioritize their salaried employees — professionals, managers, and executives.</p><h6> You mentioned that being younger than comparable peers is an attribute favorable to success. Can you elaborate more on what your studies have found regarding age inequalities?</h6><p> The negative impact of age is close to universal among our analytical findings with client organizations. The simple fact is that once an employee gets beyond the median age of their cohort, all things turn negative: They&#39;re less likely to be promoted, they&#39;re less likely to receive a high performance rating, and their pay growth levels off or declines.</p><p> The one positive is that there is less turnover with older employees, often substantially less. Indeed, it may be that it is precisely because older employees tend to stay that employers don&#39;t feel the need to promote, pay, or recognize them in the same way as they do their younger employees. The latter have more outside opportunities, so they may need to be constantly wooed.</p><p></p><p> These negative signals about older workers can be very misleading. We often find that groups with more older workers actually outperform those with more younger workers. There&#39;s a discordance between what&#39;s found at the individual level compared with the group or organizational level.</p><p> This suggests that the productivity of older workers shows up not in their own measures of individual performance but in the performance of those with whom they work. We call this a <em>spillover effect</em> . So, for example, if older workers are less likely to turn over, they can cause their younger colleagues to follow suit, thereby bringing more stability to their work groups and making them more productive. For more evidence about the productivity of older workers, see the recent study I conducted with Richard A. Guzzo and Nicholas L. Anderson, which we discuss in the article “ <a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">Age, Experience, and Business Performance: A Meta-Analysis of Work Unit-Level Effects</a> ” in the journal <cite>Work, Aging and Retirement</cite> .</p><h6> How can organizations ensure that age diversity and inclusion are integrated into their equity and diversity initiatives?</h6><p> Again, it is a common view among business leaders that older workers are less productive. And because they tend to cost more, they are viewed more as a liability than an asset, despite significant evidence to the contrary. For some reason that I find hard to explain, combating ageism is not high on the DEI agenda, certainly not as compared with efforts to address gender and racial inequity. I fault the DEI community for not being more aggressive on this front.</p><p> The aging workforce is a fact of life almost everywhere. Organizations that don&#39;t deal effectively with the repercussions of this secular trend and ensure that they are managing their older workers effectively run the risk of undermining organizational performance. In effect, they may make their unfounded stereotypes a self-fulfilling outcome.</p><p></p><p> I always urge my clients to undertake the kind of disciplined diagnostic work to evaluate the realities of their own workforce — to determine whether spillover effects are indeed at work in their organization, and to respond accordingly. Through this process, many of them will find that they have an asset to protect rather than a liability to discard.</p><h6> Is there any analysis done on the correlation between company performance or share price and the situations demonstrated by the survey?</h6><p> I&#39;ve undertaken client studies in which we link workforce characteristics and management practices to various business outcomes, including profitability, financial and operational productivity, revenue growth, and customer retention, among others. Our results have been mixed. In some, we&#39;ve seen that greater diversity in work group or unit composition improves business performance; in others, we&#39;ve found no effect or statistically negligible results. The most robust review and synthesis of the results of these studies is the meta-analysis of the effects of age and tenure noted above. That study did not focus on the effects of race and gender.</p><h6> What concrete steps can organizations take to battle these biases?</h6><p></p><p> My article in the summer 2023 issue of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/">Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</a> ,” speaks directly to this question. I explain how organizations can use the results of this kind of modeling to help eliminate or reduce the influence of demographics on how well employees are positioned to succeed at work. The reality is that all too often, situational factors inordinately affect the ability of employees to succeed and that women and people of color are situationally disadvantaged.</p><p> Employers who recognize that they are not positioning this talent to succeed can deploy an approach I call <em>proactive career management</em> to change this reality on the ground. This may involve getting more women and people of color into supervisory or other accelerator roles, changing reporting relationships, and neutralizing the negative effects of flexible working, among other things. I share a case study in my article to illustrate this approach in action.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do Consumers See Your Business as a Force for Good?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cynthia E. Clark. <p>Cynthia E. Clark, Ph.D., is a professor of management at Bentley University. She is also a coauthor of <cite>Business and Society: Ethical, Legal, and Digital Environments</cite> (Sage Publications, 2020) and the author of <cite>Giving Voice to Values in the Boardroom</cite> (Routledge, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[The public’s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s efforts to impose fines on businesses for greenwashing, point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald’s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Clark-Eco-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> The public&#39;s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the US Federal Trade Commission&#39;s efforts to impose <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/04/13/ftc-is-expected-crack-down-greenwashing/">fines on businesses for greenwashing</a> , point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald&#39;s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic waste. Last year, <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/blog/2022/04/55-million-total-ftc-settlements-kohls-and-walmart-challenge-bamboo-and-eco-claims-shed-light">both Kohl&#39;s and Walmart</a> reached settlements of $2.5 million and $3 million, respectively, for falsely claiming that dozens of rayon textile products were actually made from environmentally friendly bamboo.</p><p> When such large, visible companies issue false claims or fail to act, it results in missed opportunities, a growing performance-expectation gap, and, eventually, reputational damage among consumers. So, what makes a business a force for good when it comes to the future of our environment? To find out, Bentley University and Gallup recently conducted a survey of 5,757 Americans to assess how they feel about business and its potential to have a positive impact on society and the environment. The <a href="https://www.bentley.edu/news-Announcing-the-Bentley-Gallup-Force-for-Good-survey-results">results of the Force for Good survey</a> highlight areas in which businesses, small and large, are failing to meet people&#39;s expectations — and how they can do better.</p><p></p><p> The public&#39;s expectations of large companies like Kohl&#39;s, McDonald&#39;s, or Walmart were made clear in our research. A slight majority of our respondents (53%) said that businesses overall have a negative environmental impact. Almost two-thirds (65%) said they feel this way about <em>large</em> businesses, whereas 16% said that <em>small</em> businesses have a negative impact on the planet/environment. Younger respondents in our study had higher expectations of businesses overall, with a whopping 81% of those age 18 to 29 saying that large businesses have a negative impact on the planet, compared with 54% of respondents age 70 or older.</p><p> Drilling down into the data, we found that more than 9 in 10 respondents rated four social and environmental concerns that businesses could act on as extremely or somewhat important: practicing sustainable manufacturing (92%); promoting increased access to education and training (92%); investing time and money into local communities (92%); and operating in a way that is sustainable for the environment (91%). Just 1 in 3 people surveyed said that businesses are currently doing an excellent or good job in any of these areas, and about 1 in 4 (26%) said that businesses are doing an excellent or good job of operating in an environmentally sustainable way.</p><h3> The T-Shirt Experiment</h3><p> One perspective on sustainability is that companies should practice environmental responsibility for the greater good — the “doing good to do good” perspective. Another approach focuses on the importance of “doing good to do well” so that both business and society benefit from leaders&#39; actions. But are these approaches in tension? Need they be?</p><p> One section of the Force for Good survey — what we called our T-shirt experiment — was aimed at getting a better read on how people think about this tension. Amid rising prices for almost everything, we asked whether respondents would be willing to pay extra for a T-shirt depending on a variety of company characteristics. Sixty-three percent of respondents said they would be willing to pay extra — 82% more — for a T-shirt if the company that made it was known for having a positive impact on the environment. The numbers are even higher for respondents age 18 to 29 and for women: Young people were most likely to say they would pay more — about 8 in 10 — and almost 7 in 10 women. (See “Results of the T-Shirt Experiment.”) Both of these consumer groups are key markets for many companies.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Results of the T-Shirt Experiment</h4><p class="caption"> To differing degrees, depending on age and gender, respondents indicated their willingness to pay more for the same product based on a business&#39;s sustainability practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig1-1.png" alt="Results of the T-Shirt Experiment" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> When people were asked how much they would pay for the T-shirt without being given any additional information, the median response was $10. This held true for those with personal incomes between $24,000 and $179,000. In other words, personal income had little effect on the value they assigned to the product.</p><p></p><p> Respondents were then asked how much more they would pay if the company were known for various attributes: having a positive environmental impact, making a positive impact on the local community, treating employees well, and contributing to charities. Among the four attributes, the premium was highest for companies known to have a positive environmental impact, with a median response of $7.</p><p> Our data indicates that Americans are, in fact, willing to reward companies for doing good. A company known for positive environmental performance can charge more for its products — evidence that “doing good to do well” works.</p><p></p><h3> A False Dichotomy?</h3><p> Most of the respondents didn&#39;t see a trade-off between good environmental performance and good financial performance. In other words, they believe that both can happen concurrently, despite business leaders&#39; arguments that sustainable practices harm financial performance. About 7 in 10 respondents (69%) said businesses that prioritize making a positive impact on society are just as profitable (47%) or more profitable (22%) than their competitors. People who said they have expertise in owning, leading, or managing a business were no less likely than those without such expertise to say that businesses that prioritize making a positive impact are at least as profitable as their competitors.</p><p> Members of different political parties had notable differences of opinion regarding the importance of sustainability. For example, 84% of Democrats said it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner, compared with 31% of Republicans and 59% of independents. However, a large majority of Republicans (80%) said that sustainability is at least <em>somewhat</em> important. These perspectives might affect a host of company actions, such as choosing content and spending amounts for advertising in red versus blue states and the very design of their products.</p><p></p><p> Likewise, we found significant differences across ethnic identities. Seventy percent of Black respondents, 82% of Asian respondents, 65% of Hispanic respondents, and 59% of White respondents said they believe it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner. When asked how they feel about focusing on long-term benefits like those for the environment versus short-term benefits like profits, 77% of Asian respondents said they are likely to support that focus — compared with 56% of respondents overall. The figures for both Black and Hispanic respondents hovered around 60%.</p><p> Even when we asked the question in a slightly different way, respondents did not see it as a trade-off but as more of a “both and” situation. For example, when asked about meeting the financial goals of investors, 79% said they believe it is somewhat or extremely important. Eighty-eight percent of respondents also said that making the world a better place is somewhat or extremely important.</p><h3> How Can Your Company Become a Force for Good?</h3><p> Results from this deep dive into what a broad and varied set of Americans believe suggest several actions companies can take or plan for.</p><p> <strong>Pay attention to your local footprint.</strong> Small companies are perceived as better at most stakeholder-related activities. Respondents were twice as likely to say small businesses positively impact people&#39;s lives than large businesses (82% and 41%, respectively). What&#39;s more, respondents are more likely to think large businesses have a negative impact on Americans&#39; lives in general (38%) than they are to say the same about small businesses (4%). This data, combined with the results across age and gender in the figure below (see “Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?”) on positive community impact, suggests that companies — particularly large ones — should improve their relationships with their surrounding communities.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize that younger Americans expect more.</strong> Millennials (born between 1981 and 1996) and Gen Zers (born between 1997 and 2012) expect more from businesses in terms of both social and environmental responsibility than older respondents do. In our T-shirt experiment, 82% of respondents age 18 to 29 were willing to pay more for a T-shirt from a company known for having a positive impact on their local community. Again, young respondents (73%) agreed more than any other age group that businesses&#39; efforts to reduce their carbon footprints and/or emissions are important. Companies will need to account for their environmental stewardship among their customers and future employees.</p><p> <strong>Mind the performance-expectation gap.</strong> Environmental stakeholders and regulators are on the lookout for any discrepancy between expectations of a company&#39;s responsible environmental management and what it is actually doing — the performance-expectation gap. The vast majority of respondents (89%) said businesses have “a great deal” or “some” power to make a positive impact on people&#39;s lives, but just 57% said that businesses are very or somewhat effective at doing so. In terms of the environment, the findings revealed performance-expectation gaps of at least 30 percentage points between “the importance of” and “the performance of” several environmental goals. On questions about reducing businesses&#39; carbon footprints, engaging in sustainable manufacturing, and making the world a better place, we found considerable gaps: On those three points, 52% to 57% of respondents indicated that it is extremely important for businesses to do so, but only 24% to 28% thought they are excellent or good at it.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?</h4><p class="caption"> There is a considerable gap between respondents&#39; opinions on the importance of sustainability practices and their perceptions of businesses&#39; actual practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig2.png" alt="Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> While having a dedicated sustainability leader, support from senior management, and education for employees and executives is necessary, it&#39;s important to stay vigilant in addressing the widening performance-expectation gap. In what has become a hypercritical business environment, leaders must pay greater attention to how perceptions of what their company is doing compare with what they are actually doing.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Set sustainability goals.</strong> Think carefully about how to measure what you&#39;re doing. This is a logical next step after gaining the support of senior management, and it can help your company determine the progress it has made and where it has soft or blind spots. In fact, regulators have proposed requiring companies to disclose how they set climate-related targets and measure their progress toward meeting them. Consider signing on to broadly recognized and accepted goals like the United Nations Global Compact&#39;s (UNGC&#39;s) <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals</a> , which can help your company publicly commit to a plan of action, step by step. The UNGC also requires annual statements on progress to help ward off greenwashing.</p><p></p><p> With increasing attention on environmental sustainability, gaining an understanding of how various stakeholders perceive your statements and actions is vital. By identifying and understanding current perceptions and their implications, as the Bentley-Gallup study does, companies can amend their environmental commitments and processes to ensure that they invigorate their efforts to be a force for good, which will benefit the company, its stakeholders, and, most importantly, the environment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Myth of the Mainstream</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus Collins. <p>Marcus Collins is a clinical marketing professor at the University of Michigan&#39;s Ross School of Business and former head of strategy at Wieden+Kennedy New York. He is the author of <cite>For the Culture: The Power Behind What We Buy, What We Do, and Who We Want to Be</cite> (PublicAffairs, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com For years, McDonald’s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension. The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Collins_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> For years, McDonald&#39;s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension.</p><p> The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about its updated menu, which offered healthier alternatives more in line with contemporary diet trends — but to no avail. Year over year, McDonald&#39;s sales declined, and its brand perception continued to spiral downward.</p><p></p><p> Finally, the company decided to go on the offensive. Instead of combating the opposition&#39;s hate and attempting to win over those in the middle, McDonald&#39;s decided to focus on its fans — the people who self-identify as McDonald&#39;s devotees despite the vitriol directed at the brand. The company&#39;s tactics included launching its Famous Orders campaign, which celebrated the favored menu items of superstar fans (like hip-hop mogul Travis Scott and K-pop megastars BTS); creating adult-targeted Happy Meals; and promoting fans&#39; own menu hacks. In doing so, it tapped into what these devotees love about McDonald&#39;s and not only activated their collective consumption but also inspired them to spread the word on behalf of the brand. The result of this strategy was a 10.4% increase in global revenue for McDonald&#39;s from 2018 to 2021 and the return of dormant customers: more than a quarter of those who came in to buy the Travis Scott meal, for example, hadn&#39;t visited the chain in over a year. Seemingly overnight, McDonald&#39;s went from being a cautionary tale to the darling of brand marketing and a case study for advertising effectiveness.</p><p></p><p>这里发生了什么？ Conventional wisdom would tell us that in a world of increasingly polarized opinions, our best bet is to appease the middle, if only because that&#39;s where the majority of the market is. That also seems like a safe bet to many companies, as a middle-of-the-road position is less likely to alienate potential customers. But McDonald&#39;s demonstrated what can happen when you dismiss this conventional approach. Instead of trying to speak to the mass market, it chose a side. It chose to embrace the love instead, fighting the hate, and it abandoned the notion of enticing the large but indifferent middle of the market. By doing so, McDonald&#39;s marketing efforts activated a legion of fans who not only consumed but also won over others as well. What McDonald&#39;s realized is an important lesson for contemporary marketers: If you want to get people to move, you must choose a side. The notion that you can win by playing to the middle is a misleading myth.</p><p></p><h3> Choose a Side</h3><p> The core function of marketing is to influence people to adopt a desired behavior. That is to say, we go to market to get people to move — to buy, to vote, to recycle, to subscribe, to download, to watch, to evangelize, to wear a mask — and to drive a host of other desirable behavioral outcomes that will benefit our organization or interests. And what influences people the most? Well, according to everything we know about human behavior, we are most influenced by other people — not ads, not value propositions, but other people. More specifically, we are most influenced by <em>our</em> people: the individuals who abide by the same culturally established conventions and expectations that dictate what is considered acceptable behavior for people like us. These individuals typically share a similar worldview and, therefore, adhere to a shared way of life in an effort to promote social solidarity among themselves — their subculture. They consume the way the subculture consumes, vote the way it votes, and behave the way it behaves, because that is what is expected of people like them.</p><p> If these people are against you because of the shared conventions and expectations of people like them (their culture), then the likelihood of getting them to take action on your behalf will be slim. That&#39;s why right-wing Republicans won&#39;t bother trying to convert left-leaning Democrats. Instead, Republicans speak to their base — the collective of people who see the world similarly, express a similar set of cultural characteristics as the brand, and are more inclined to move in step with the brand as an act of social solidarity. They identify as members of this group and follow its behavioral norms.</p><p> Those in the unaffiliated middle of the population, on the other hand, are by nature indifferent and risk averse. While they may have opinions, they lack strong convictions in either direction and are therefore less likely to take action. In politics, they don&#39;t vote in primaries or campaign for candidates; instead, they sit on the sidelines and wait to see how things shake out. Their behavior is the same when it comes to brands.</p><p> The middle doesn&#39;t adopt new products with any urgency. They are not the first to respond to marketing communications, nor are they likely to weigh in on a debate between advocates and detractors. They mitigate their own risk of moving out of step with what might be considered generally acceptable by stepping back and observing other people&#39;s responses first.</p><p> The red herring is that we perceive this indifference as an opportunity to persuade them to one side or the other. But the truth is, they are not typically convinced by any marketing communications. Instead, they, too, take cues from other people — sometimes those who are for you, and at other times those who are against you.</p><p></p><p> With this in mind, it becomes abundantly clear that in a polarized scenario, the chances of marketers getting people to move are far greater when we activate the collective of the willing as opposed to trying to convince detractors or even persuade the indifferent. And yet, historically, marketers have focused their efforts on the middle because it represents the biggest market opportunity. However, our chances of successfully influencing behavior increases when we choose to address the people who are most likely to take action. When we do so effectively, we catalyze a propagation effect that causes the product, behavior, or idea to cascade throughout the population, thanks to the process of social contagion — the spread of affects, behaviors, cognitions, and desires due to direct or indirect peer influence of people “like us.”</p><h3> The Power of Propagation</h3><p> The idea of propagation demands that marketers leave behind the conventional approach of targeting the middle, where the majority of the population resides. Besides being of questionable effectiveness, as discussed above, reaching the middle requires costly media spending (think prime-time TV and Super Bowl ads) and places marketing messages in an arena that is noisy and saturated with competing messages. Marketers pay little attention to the fringe, a population that conventional wisdom tells us is too small and too niche. But everything that is now mainstream once started on the fringe: It started within a subculture and propagated out to become popular culture.</p><p> For instance, if you were into comic books 20 years ago, you would have been considered a nerd. Today, however, many of the most-viewed movies across the globe, such as Marvel&#39;s <cite>Avengers</cite> series, originated from comics. Twenty years ago, if you were into video games, you would have been perceived as an immature adult. Today, gaming is not only considered cool but is also a multibillion-dollar industry. Indeed, what is now normal was once fringe. Thanks to social contagion, the cultural characteristics of a community propagate from the fringe to the middle — from the subculture to popular culture. It happens from the outside in, not the inside out.</p><p></p><p> Unlike traditional marketing communications, the reach and subsequent adoption that is achieved through this kind of propagation does not rely on people hearing a message from a company or brand. (It helps, but it&#39;s not necessary.) Instead, people hear about it from someone they trust — someone like them — which increases their likelihood of adoption. As the network scientists Nicholas Christakis and James Fowler contended, “When a small group of people begin acting in concert — displaying similar visible symptoms — the epidemic can spread along social network ties via emotion contagion and large groups can become quickly emotionally synchronized.” This is the network effect that is catalyzed when you activate the collective of the willing. Don&#39;t focus on the middle: Focus on the people who see the world the way you do. Choose a side, and they will convince the bystanders, the passive, the indifferent.</p><p></p><p> Although broadcast messaging might get our attention, it&#39;s the influence of people like us, people with whom we identify, that changes our outlook and, subsequently, our behaviors. This provides a new perspective, and corresponding strategies, for marketers who aim to communicate with consumers in a culture where ideological binaries seem to divide the market. Like McDonald&#39;s did, marketers benefit from choosing a side that is most likely to move and then activating its members so that they might convert people on the brand&#39;s behalf. Status quo practices position the middle as a safe bet. However, the dynamics of cultural diffusion subvert these long-standing best practices for connecting with consumers and influencing behavioral adoption, and demand that today&#39;s practitioners develop new strategies and accompanying tactics.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sustainability Progress Is Stalled at Most Companies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[CB Bhattacharya and Rob Jekielek. <p>CB Bhattacharya is director of the Center for Sustainable Business and the HJ Zoffer Chair in Sustainability and Ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business at the University of Pittsburgh. Rob Jekielek is managing director of The Harris Poll.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Sustainability & Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability-Driven Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else’s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual.1 On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bhattacharya-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else&#39;s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming their business models to be more sustainable have embedded sustainability into their corporate DNA. This means that they have endowed their employees with a sense of sustainable ownership, spurring them to engage in more sustainability-supporting behaviors. When every employee integrates environmental and social concerns into every business decision, sustainability progress is accelerated — an aspirational goal for all companies.</p><p> To shed light on the state of play in embedding sustainability and identify key bottlenecks, the Center for Sustainable Business at the University of Pittsburgh collaborated with The Harris Poll to conduct a survey of US employees. We wanted to find out whether their employers were taking measures that our earlier research had identified as important to prompting employees to conduct business through a sustainability lens. Our survey drew responses from 1,056 employees, representative of the US employee base. We defined sustainability for the respondents as “integrating environmental and societal concerns into business decisions and actions.”</p><p></p><p> We asked respondents to rate their level of agreement with a series of 19 statements about the status quo, such as “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance,” on a 4-point Likert scale (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”). We also presented respondents with a series of 12 issues that could pose challenges to sustainability progress, such as “Sustainability is not built into our business strategy,” and asked them to rate the extent to which that is an actual challenge at their company (from “major challenge” to “not at all a challenge”).</p><p> Roughly one-third of the respondents asserted that their employers have made significant strides in their sustainability journeys. Although that number might sound low given the enormity of the task facing us, the good news is that there is momentum, which we can help accelerate by pointing out the roadblocks as perceived by employees. Below, we provide six key recommendations that emerged from our data for managers seeking to embed sustainability in the organizational culture and business models.</p><p> <strong>Establish a purpose based on values.</strong> Purpose is a business&#39;s raison d&#39;être — the answer to the all-important question, “Why do we do what we do?” Paul Polman, former CEO of Unilever and a leader in the corporate sustainability movement, has said, “Sustainability is totally driven by purpose.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Organizations that are successful at embedding sustainability articulate the societal benefit they aim to deliver to their stakeholders, and this overarching purpose guides everything the organization does.</p><p> In our study, 36% of the respondents strongly agreed with the statement “My company wants to make a difference in people&#39;s lives, not just make profits,” while 33% strongly agreed with “My company has a higher purpose beyond profit maximization.” If purpose is the starting point for sustainability, we aren&#39;t doing very well; it is apparent that the profit-maximization narrative is alive and well. Consistently, 43% of employees cited short-term focus, a lack of investor interest, and, importantly, “Our leaders don&#39;t believe in sustainability,” as challenges. Unless CEOs and top management teams realize that profit is the <em>consequence</em> of value creation for all stakeholders and not the starting point for strategy development and execution, progress will be stifled. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p></p><p> <strong>Bake sustainability into corporate strategy.</strong> Academic researchers and others have noted that efforts to make meaningful progress toward sustainability must be driven by corporate strategy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Doing so increases the likelihood that, over time, “doing the green thing” will be seen as a normal part of employees&#39; jobs, and more and more decisions will be made through the lens of sustainability. With only 29% of respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance” and 27% with “Sustainability is core to how my company executes our business strategy,” it appears that we have a long way to go. Consistent with the status quo, 43% agreed that their company&#39;s failure to build sustainability into its business strategy represents a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Train employees, and incentivize actions that advance sustainability.</strong> Companies that are successful in engaging their workforce have invested in training that gives employees guidance on how to improve sustainability. With only 30% of employees surveyed strongly agreeing with the statement “I understand how I can improve my company&#39;s sustainability performance through my role,” there seems to be a dearth of role-specific knowledge at the individual employee level. Lack of training was cited as a major/moderate challenge by 44%, while a similar number (45%) indicated that they don&#39;t know what actions to take to improve sustainability performance. Companies need to invest more in training and sustainability knowledge creation so that employees know <em>what</em> they can do in their roles and <em>how</em> to do what needs to be done.</p><p> Managers must also do more to provide employees with incentives to advance the sustainability agenda: Forty-nine percent of those surveyed found the lack of such incentives to be a major or moderate hurdle to improving sustainability performance. Leaders should also consider whether the management culture encourages engagement and intrinsic motivation by giving employees the autonomy to solve sustainability challenges, which often require creative thinking. However, when we asked survey respondents to rate their level of agreement with the statements “My company allows me to make a lot of sustainability-related decisions on my own” and “My company gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out sustainability initiatives,” we found that, at most, 29% of respondents strongly agreed.</p><p> <strong>Create a sustainability culture in your organization.</strong> Managers can keep sustainability salient in the organizational culture by communicating progress, celebrating milestones, recognizing achievements, and collaborating on solutions both internally and with industry partners. Our research has identified the lack of a sustainability culture as one of the biggest impediments to progress, with 48% of respondents indicating that that is a major or moderate impediment at their organization. Communicating sustainability progress to employees is a key component of a sustainability culture, because it keeps issues top of mind. Celebrating successes will pique employee interest and legitimize the importance of sustainability to the organization — but only 31% of respondents strongly agreed that their company celebrates sustainability successes.</p><p></p><p> Collaborating with traditional competitors — which is increasingly necessary to address those complex “ <a href="https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/tragedy-of-the-commons-impact-on-sustainability-issues">tragedy of the commons</a> ” problems — signals to employees that the company is serious about transformational change and reinforces the culture to employees. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> With only 25% of survey respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company collaborates with other organizations to address complex sustainability issues,” it is evident that much work is required to open corporate leaders&#39; eyes to the potential of progress via collaboration.</p><p> <strong>Conduct business through a sustainability lens.</strong> Imagine the progress we would make if every employee in every company — from the mailroom to the boardroom — integrated environmental and social issues into every business decision they made. This, in our view, is conducting business through the lens of sustainability — an aspirational but necessary goal to reach if we are to surmount our existential crises. As previous research has shown, employees taking individual ownership of sustainability is a key driver for engaging in sustainability behaviors. In our survey, 28% of respondents strongly agreed with the statement “Employees at my company take ownership of improving sustainability performance,” while 45% identified a belief among employees that “sustainability is someone else&#39;s responsibility” as a challenge. This lack of personal ownership of sustainability performance is reflected in our survey results: Only 27% of respondents strongly agreed that they “invested ideas and creativity” to help their company be more sustainable, and just 24% strongly agreed that every business decision they make is viewed through the lens of sustainability.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Bridge the last mile.</strong> We noted a significant difference between how corporate and front-line employees responded to our questions. Compared with front-line nonmanagers working in roles such as customer support, managers working in corporate roles were, on average, about 15% more likely to see sustainability as embedded.</p><p> To ensure that their commitment to sustainability is real and provides tangible benefits to their organizations, leaders must address this last-mile gap between corporate and front-line employees. Broadly communicated messaging about the corporate purpose and environmental, social, and governance targets might not suffice in this instance; there is a real need to drive sustainability through practical initiatives and actions that can be integrated into daily tasks and routines that employees perform across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> Interestingly, perceiving sustainability as more embedded in the organization also opens employees&#39; eyes to the roadblocks and challenges that impede progress. Our data shows that employees who are more engaged and perceive sustainability to be more embedded also perceive more roadblocks, on average, than those who are less engaged.</p><p> The implication here is that as companies bridge the last-mile gap in embedding sustainability, they should be prepared to field more questions and listen to more opinions as employee engagement on the issue increases. Companies should use one-on-one coaching, action playbooks, and tailored communication to make sustainability everyone&#39;s job. Companies need to be prepared to invest more resources into embedding sustainability — and get the entire organization to conduct business through the sustainability lens.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>