<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 11 月 15 日星期三 20:41:17 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator><item><title>联合利华的人工智能道德：从政策到流程</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) 是巴布森学院信息技术与管理学校长杰出教授、牛津大学赛德商学院客座教授以及麻省理工学院数字经济项目研究员。他是<cite>《Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）一书的合著者。 Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) 是一位行业思想领袖、作家、创始人兼首席执行官，目前担任全球咨询公司 Wavestone 的创新研究员、数据战略部门。他是<cite>《快速失败，更快学习：颠覆、大数据和人工智能时代数据驱动领导力的教训》一书</cite>的作者（Wiley，2021 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Many large companies today — most surveys suggest over 70% globally — have determined that artificial intelligence is important to their future and are building AI applications in various parts of their businesses. Most also realize that AI has an ethical dimension and that they need to ensure that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Davenport-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">卡洛琳·吉森-贝塞尔/麻省理工学院 SMR |盖蒂图片社</p></figcaption></figure><p>如今，许多大公司（大多数调查显示全球超过 70% 的公司）已经确定人工智能对其未来很重要，并正在其业务的各个部分构建人工智能应用程序。大多数人还意识到人工智能具有道德维度，他们需要确保他们构建或实施的人工智能系统是透明、公正和公平的。</p><p>到目前为止，许多追求道德人工智能的公司仍处于解决这个问题的早期阶段。他们可能会劝告员工采取符合道德的方法来开发和使用人工智能，或者起草一套初步的人工智能治理政策。大多数人连这一点都没有做到。在<a href="https://www.conversica.com/conversation-automation-resources/report/ai-ethics-survey/">最近的一项调查</a>中，73% 的美国高级领导人表示，他们认为人工智能道德准则很重要，但只有 6% 的人制定了这些准则。</p><p></p><p>我们看到人工智能道德流程的五个阶段：<em>传福音</em>，公司代表谈论人工智能道德的重要性；<em>制定政策</em>，公司审议并批准围绕人工智能道德方法的公司政策；<em>记录</em>，公司收集每个人工智能用例或应用程序的数据（使用<a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2021/05/27/the-future-of-work-now-ethical-ai-at-salesforce/?sh=312432713eb6">模型卡</a>等方法）；<em>审查</em>，公司对每个用例进行系统分析（或将其外包给合作伙伴公司），以确定该案例是否符合公司的人工智能道德标准；和<em>行动</em>，公司要么按原样接受用例，要么将其发送回提议所有者进行修改，要么拒绝它。</p><p>只有在更高级别的阶段（审查和行动），公司才能真正确定其人工智能应用程序是否符合其制定的透明度、偏见和公平标准。为了使这些阶段到位，它必须拥有大量用于收集信息的人工智能项目、流程和系统，以及用于对特定应用程序做出决策的治理结构。许多公司尚未具备这些先决条件，但随着公司表现出更大的人工智能成熟度和重视度，这些先决条件将是必要的。</p><h3>联合利华的早期政策</h3><p>联合利华是英国消费品包装公司，旗下品牌包括多芬 (Dove)、第七代 (Seventh Generation) 和本杰瑞 (Ben &amp; Jerry&#39;s)，长期以来一直注重企业社会责任和环境可持续发展。最近，该公司已将人工智能作为一种显着改善其全球业务运营和决策的手段。联合利华的企业数据执行官（一个治理委员会）认识到，公司可以通过将人工智能的负责任和合乎道德的使用嵌入到公司的数据战略中，建立强大的隐私、安全和治理控制。目标是利用人工智能驱动的数字创新，最大限度地发挥公司的能力，并促进社会更加公平和公正。成立了一个多功能团队，其任务是探索这在实践中意味着什么，并制定行动计划来实现该目标。</p><p>联合利华现在已经实施了上述所有五个阶段，但回顾过去，其第一步是制定一套政策。例如，一项政策规定，任何会对个人生活产生重大影响的决定不应完全自动化，而应最终由人类做出。其他采用的特定于人工智能的原则包括“我们永远不会责怪系统；我们永远不会责怪系统”的法令。必须有联合利华所有者负责”并且“我们将尽最大努力系统地监控模型和人工智能的性能，以确保其保持其有效性。”</p><p>委员会成员很快意识到，仅制定广泛的政策不足以确保人工智能的负责任发展。为了建立对人工智能采用的信心并真正释放其全部潜力，他们需要开发一个强大的工具、服务和人力资源生态系统，以确保人工智能系统能够按预期工作。</p><p></p><p>委员会成员还知道，联合利华的许多人工智能和分析系统是与外部软件和服务供应商合作开发的。例如，该公司的广告代理商经常使用程序化购买软件，该软件使用人工智能来决定在网络和移动网站上放置哪些数字广告。该团队的结论是，其人工智能道德方法需要包括对外部来源能力的关注。</p><p></p><h3>开发强大的人工智能保障流程</h3><p>在联合利华使用人工智能的早期，该公司的数据和人工智能领导者注意到，该技术的一些问题根本不涉及道德——它们涉及的系统在完成预期任务时效率低下。联合利华全球数据科学总监 Giles Pavey 主要负责人工智能道德规范，他知道这是人工智能用例的重要组成部分。 “例如，预测现金流的系统可能不涉及公平或偏见风险，但可能存在一些无效的风险，”他说。 “我们决定将功效风险与我们评估的道德风险一起纳入其中。”该公司开始使用<em>“人工智能保证”</em>一词来广泛涵盖其对工具有效性和道德规范的概述。</p><p>联合利华人工智能保证合规流程背后的基本理念是检查每个新的人工智能应用程序，以确定其在有效性和道德方面的内在风险有多大。该公司已经制定了明确的信息安全和数据隐私方法，目标是采用类似的方法，确保人工智能应用程序在未经审查和批准的情况下不会投入生产。将合规流程整合到联合利华已有的合规领域（例如隐私风险评估、信息安全和采购政策）将是成功的最终标志。</p><p> Debbie Cartledge 担任公司数据和人工智能道德战略负责人，她解释了团队采用的流程：</p><blockquote><p>当规划新的人工智能解决方案时，联合利华员工或供应商会在开发之前提出概述的用例和方法。这是内部审查的，更复杂的案例则由外部专家手动评估。然后，提议者被告知潜在的道德和功效风险以及需要考虑的缓解措施。人工智能应用程序开发完成后，联合利华或外部方会进行统计测试，以确定是否存在偏见或公平问题，并检查系统实现其目标的有效性。随着时间的推移，我们预计大多数案例都可以根据项目提案人提供的项目信息进行全面自动评估。</p></blockquote><p>根据系统在公司内部的使用位置，系统还可能需要遵守当地法规。例如，所有简历检查现在都是由人工审核员完成。如果简历检查完全自动化，审查可能会得出这样的结论：系统需要有人参与其中，以做出是否让候选人参加面试的最终决定。如果存在无法缓解的严重风险，人工智能保证流程将拒绝该申请，理由是联合利华的价值观禁止这样做。人工智能用例的最终决定由高级执行委员会做出，其中包括来自法律、人力资源、数据和技术部门的代表。</p><p>举个例子：该公司在百货商店设有销售其化妆品品牌的区域。开发了一个项目，利用计算机视觉人工智能通过日常自拍照自动记录销售代理的出勤情况，其延伸目标是查看代理的外表是否合适。由于人工智能保证流程，项目团队拓宽了他们的思维范围，超越了法规、合法性和有效性，还考虑了全自动系统的潜在影响。他们认为需要人工监督来检查标记为不合规的照片，并对任何后续行动负责。</p><h3>与外部合作伙伴合作，整体人工智能</h3><p>联合利华在人工智能保证流程中的外部合作伙伴是总部位于伦敦的 Holistic AI 公司。创始人 Emre Kazim 和 Adriano Koshiyama 自 2020 年以来一直与联合利华 AI 团队合作，Holistic AI 于 2021 年成为 AI 风险评估的正式合作伙伴。</p><p> Holistic AI 创建了一个平台来管理 AI 保证审查流程。在这种情况下，“人工智能”是一个广泛的类别，涵盖任何类型的预测或自动化；甚至用于对人力资源候选人进行评分的 Excel 电子表格也将包含在该流程中。联合利华的数据道德团队使用该平台审查人工智能项目的状态，并可以查看哪些新用例已提交；信息是否完整；以及他们收到的风险级别评估，编码为红色、黄色（在英国称为“琥珀色”）或绿色。</p><p>交通信号灯状态在三个点进行评估：分类时、进一步分析后以及最终缓解和保证后。最后一点，评级有以下解释： 红色评级表示人工智能系统不符合联合利华标准，不应部署；黄色表示人工智能系统存在一些可接受的风险，企业主有责任了解并承担责任；绿色意味着人工智能系统不会给流程带来任何风险。迄今为止，联合利华的数百个用例中只有少数获得了红色评级，包括上述化妆品。所有提交者都能够解决其用例的问题并将其提升到黄色评级。</p><p>对于人工智能项目的领导者来说，该平台是开始审核流程的地方。他们提交了一份拟议的用例，其中包含详细信息，包括其目的、业务案例、项目在联合利华内部的所有权、团队组成、使用的数据、所采用的人工智能技术的类型、是否是内部开发的还是由外部供应商开发的、自治程度等。该平台使用这些信息对应用程序的潜在风险进行评分。风险领域包括可解释性、稳健性、有效性、偏见和隐私。机器学习算法会被自动分析，以确定它们是否对任何特定群体存在偏见。</p><p></p><p>整体人工智能平台中越来越多的评估是基于欧盟拟议的人工智能法案，该法案还将人工智能用例分为三类风险（不可接受、高和不足以监管）。欧盟国家正在就该法案进行谈判，希望在 2023 年底之前达成协议。Kazim 和 Koshiyama 表示，尽管该法案仅适用于欧洲企业，但联合利华和其他公司可能会在全球范围内采用该法案，就像他们在欧盟的通用数据保护条例。</p><p></p><p> Kazim 和 Koshiyama 预计整体人工智能未来能够汇总各公司的数据并进行基准测试。该软件可以评估收益与成本、同一用例的不同外部提供商的效率以及最有效的人工智能采购方法。 Kazim 和 Koshiyama 还考虑在某些情况下公开风险评级，并与保险公司合作，确保人工智能用例免受某些类型的风险。</p><p>我们仍处于<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">确保公司对人工智能采取道德方法</a>的早期阶段，但这并不意味着仅仅发布声明和政策就足够了。人工智能是否符合道德将取决于用例。联合利华的人工智能保证流程及其与 Holistic AI 的合作来评估每个用例的道德风险水平，是确保人工智能系统符合人类利益和福祉的当前唯一方法。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-ethics-at-unilever-from-policy-to-process/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>中国出境禁令和劫持人质事件的兴起</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-takeing-in-china/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-takeing-in-china/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jack Wroldsen and Chris Carr. <p>杰克·沃尔德森 (Jack Wroldsen) 是加州圣路易斯奥比斯波加州理工学院奥法利商学院商业法和公共政策助理教授。他是智利的NSEP学者，也曾在阿根廷和墨西哥学习和工作。克里斯·卡尔 (Chris Carr) 是圣路易斯奥比斯波加州理工学院奥法利亚商学院的商业法和公共政策教授。他还是四次富布赖特奖获得者（意大利、突尼斯、巴基斯坦和蒙古）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[China]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Austin/theispot.com Foreign entities doing business in China are facing increasingly grave risks. On top of the high-level geopolitical and economic risks to consider, the growing incidence of exit bans, which prevent foreign executives from leaving China if their company becomes involved in a dispute, imposes a very individual human risk. While there has been [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2024WINTER-Carr_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">迈克尔·奥斯汀/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>外资企业在华经营面临的风险日益严峻。除了需要考虑的高级别地缘政治和经济风险之外，越来越多的出境禁令（如果公司卷入纠纷，外国高管就无法离开中国）也带来了非常个人化的风险。尽管媒体对一些案例进行了广泛报道——美国调查公司Mintz Group的一名新加坡高管被禁止出境，并<a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-65061116">拘留了该公司的五名中国员工</a>； <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/huawei-s-meng-wanzhou-2-michaels-what-next-china-u-n1280229">两名加拿大商人被针锋相对地拘留，</a>以报复美国对一名在加拿大被捕的华为高管提出的欺诈指控——许多在国际上开展业务的公司都相对默默无闻地面临着出境禁令和商业劫持的现实。</p><p>这种风险正在增加，而且不太可能很快减弱。在正常的业务过程中，没有什么比公司高管或员工被拘留在国外更具破坏性和波动性的了。在中国运营的公司应该提前为这些潜在情况做好准备。</p><p></p><p>出境禁令可能源于民事商业纠纷以及更严重的法律纠纷。 <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-chinese-law-raises-risks-for-american-firms-in-china-u-s-officials-say-cf62c1a0">中国最近对反间谍法的修订</a>，包括对拥有“与国家安全有关的文件、数据、材料或物品”的模糊、开放式禁令，很容易涵盖任何行业的日常商业活动，使外国高管面临更大的被捕风险。 <a href="https://travel.state.gov/content/travel/en/traveladvisories/traveladvisories/china-travel-advisory.html">美国国务院最近警告说</a>，中国政府“任意执行当地法律，包括对美国公民和其他国家公民发布出境禁令，没有根据法律规定公平和透明的程序。”</p><p>因商业原因而受到出境禁令的人在被阻止在机场登机之前通常不会收到提前通知。该人通常会受到讯问，但不会被告知有关出境禁令的原因或如何提出异议的信息。</p><p>发生商业纠纷时，出境禁令通常只有在外国人同意中国对方的要求后才会解除——中国对方通过限制个人自由，在纠纷中获得了巨大的影响力。即使外国人愿意在被困在中国的情况下花费必要的时间和金钱在法庭上追诉案件，中国法院也不太可能做出有利于外国当事人的裁决。</p><p></p><p>以亨利·蔡（Henry Cai）为例，他是土生土长的中国人，在 20 世纪 80 年代与妻子搬到加利福尼亚州，并成为美国公民。 2012年，蔡投资了一家中国科技初创公司，持股8%，并担任该公司董事。几年后，当这家初创公司面临现金流问题并拖欠贷款时，蔡多次前往中国处理这种情况。 2017年，蔡在机场被拦截并被拒绝出境，此时他意识到自己卷入了该公司债权人提起的诉讼。六年后，他仍然<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-us-exit-ban-diplomacy-11668357015">滞留在中国</a>，无法支付解除出境禁令所需的数百万美元。对于在中国的他以及在加州的妻子和两个孩子来说，人员、情感和经济损失都很高。</p><p></p><p>另一个例子是加州商人布莱恩·霍洛维茨(Brian Horowitz)，他从一家中国制造商那里购买了燃气搅拌机。由于搅拌机不符合加州空气质量标准而引发合同纠纷后，霍洛维茨前往中国与供应商会面。当他试图回国时， <a href="https://www.latimes.com/archives/la-xpm-2011-jan-28-la-fi-china-horowitz-20110128-story.html">在上海机场被拘留</a>；供应商对其公司提出了合同索赔，法院在霍洛维茨不知情的情况下实施了退出禁令。两周后，他的妻子向中国供应商电汇了 25 万美元，让她的丈夫回家。</p><p>尽管因商业纠纷而实施的出境禁令在中国是合法的，但外国高管也面临着成为非法商业劫持事件受害者的风险。在这种情况下，他们可能会被限制在酒店房间或公司设施（例如办公室或工厂）内。劫持商业人质最高可判处三年监禁。然而，在实践中，除非发生暴力，否则中国<a href="https://foreignpolicy.com/2017/08/08/chinas-police-think-hostages-arent-their-problem/">执法部门往往拒绝</a>干预这些情况。</p><p>在一个案例中，一家美国珠宝公司的高管前往中国与一家制造商讨论产品订单和<a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3692138">65 万美元付款的</a>纠纷。该高管进入制造商工厂后，她的钱包和护照被没收。随后她被带回酒店，并由制造商的员工看守了五天。她在一名精通中文的美国律师的帮助下逃脱，该律师前往中国，帮助她躲避警卫，并将她带到大使馆。</p><p>另一个案例是，一家美国公司派两名中层管理人员参观为其生产产品的中国工厂。这家美国公司已经向制造商支付了货款，但其高管了解到，工厂工人拒绝发货，因为他们的工资已经几个月没有支付了。工人们将这些高管锁在工厂内，并要求支付赎金才能释放他们。为了释放人质并获得货物，美国公司必须向制造公司和工人支付费用。</p><p>商业劫持人质事件通常会在几天或几周内得到解决，而出境禁令可能需要数月或数年才能解除。这两种情况都没有得到官方追踪，商界人士往往对他们的困境保密。尽管如此，根据六个国家（美国、加拿大、英国、德国、荷兰和澳大利亚）政府的数据和媒体报道，我们记录了大约过去<a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/tie.22261">100 多起企业出境禁令和商业人质事件</a>十年。鉴于政府关于这一现象的文件并不全面，而且并非每个案例都会受到媒体关注，这可能是一个严重的低估。</p><h3>采取多方面的方法，为最坏的情况做好准备</h3><p>这些情况的尖锐的个人性质和地缘政治动态使得规划和解决它们特别具有挑战性。您应该支付多少钱才能使您的同事（或您自己）免于被扣为人质？您如何与员工的配偶谈论其伴侣被拘留的原因以及您计划就其返回进行谈判？与媒体接触以施加政治压力以释放员工是您工作的一部分吗？</p><p>为了应对这种情况，企业领导者必须承认前往中国的员工发生这种情况的风险，并进一步了解情况，例如与经历过这种情况的其他人建立对话，这一点至关重要。他们还应与美国驻外领事官员、公司所在城市的中国官员和警察局长、美国联邦和州政府领导人、地方和国家媒体成员以及适用的行业团体（例如美中贸易全国委员会。</p><p>企业应预先组建危机处理小组并制定行动计划，为中国及其母国的关键员工和顾问分配具体职责。该计划应包括外部沟通，例如利用社交媒体引起人们对被困员工困境的关注。公司应咨询其商业保险公司，了解是否有相关保险可减轻出境禁令或商业人质事件的财务影响。</p><p>在中国有商业利益的高管还应密切关注应付账款、合同义务和业务关系的基调，以识别潜在的冲突或分歧来源。他们应该尽力在问题出现之前预见到问题，并且应该特别警惕任何未偿债务或产品已交付但由于任何原因尚未完全付款的情况。</p><p></p><p>如果已经或疑似已经提起诉讼，或者欠中国实体任何债务，公司应避免让员工前往中国。如果此类旅行不可避免，员工应保持经常沟通，以便其他人了解他们的行踪和日程安排，并应避免单独旅行。如果争议已经发生但尚未具体化为诉讼，并且员工必须前往中国，请考虑在美国先行提起诉讼，假设美国法院对中国企业拥有管辖权。例如，如果美国公司在美国法院指控违反合同，那么员工在国外时应携带翻译成中文的美国诉讼文件。</p><p></p><p>领导者还必须准备好支持和帮助员工及其家人。提前成立的危机小组应该有一个计划，与被困海外的员工及其家人以及整个公司的员工进行诚实和敏感的沟通。表现出你的关心。保持透明和诚实。这些情况会让人精神疲惫、迷失方向、令人恐惧；它们也是建立信任、团结和关爱文化的机会。与金钱相比，更重要的是人。</p><p>当然，重要的是继续致力于以切实的方式帮助受影响的员工及其家人。安排向受影响的家庭提供个性化的护理包；拜访他们的家，并与他们面对面交流。在可能的情况下，还向被困在国外的员工寄送爱心包，并方便与家人通话。</p><p>出境禁令和商业人质事件等情况是人权和地缘政治问题，也是对个人商业的强烈挑战。商业领袖明智地通过制定全面的战略方法来应对此类挑战。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-rise-of-exit-bans-and-hostage-takeing-in-china/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> RAI 项目是否为第三方和生成式人工智能做好了准备？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Infographic]]></category><category><![CDATA[Policy Making]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[In 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review and BCG completed their second year of researching responsible AI (RAI). In addition to producing a series of articles that draw on insights from an expert panel and a survey-based research report, the team has highlighted its key findings in this infographic. Although many organizations are prioritizing RAI and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> 2023 年，<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和 BCG 完成了<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">负责任人工智能 (RAI) 研究</a>的第二年。除了根据专家小组的见解和基于调查的研究报告撰写一系列文章外，该团队还在该信息图中强调了其主要发现。</p><p>尽管许多组织正在优先考虑 RAI 并开发程序来负责任地管理人工智能工具，但大多数公司依赖第三方 AI 工具（他们购买、访问或许可的工具，包括 ChatGPT 和 Bard 等生成式 AI 工具）具有重大风险。显然，大多数组织还没有准备好应对这些新风险，但我们的研究使我们能够制定一套建议来帮助他们正确实施 RAI。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/are-rai-programs-prepared-for-third-party-and-generative-ai/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何在棘手的话题上有效地表达不同意见</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 13 Nov 2023 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kenji Yoshino and David Glasgow. <p>Kenji Yoshino ( <a href="https://twitter.com/kenji_yoshino">@kenji_yoshino</a> ) 是纽约大学法学院首席大法官厄尔·沃伦宪法学教授，也是梅尔策多样性、包容性和归属感中心的教职主任。 David Glasgow ( <a href="https://twitter.com/dvglasgow">@dvglasgow</a> ) 是梅尔策多样性、包容性和归属感中心的执行主任，也是纽约大学法学院的兼职教授。他们是<cite>《说正确的事：如何谈论身份、多样性和正义》</cite> （Atria Books，2023 年）的合著者，本文正是基于该书。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Cultural Differences]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com &#160; Conversations about identity, diversity, and justice are some of the thorniest human interactions of our time. Consider Uber’s head of diversity, who hosted a workplace event titled “Don’t Call Me Karen” to highlight the “spectrum of the American White woman’s experience” and foster an “open and honest conversation about race.” Following backlash [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Yoshino_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼尔·韦伯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p></p><p>关于身份、多样性和正义的对话是我们这个时代最棘手的人类互动之一。以 Uber 的多元化负责人为例，他举办了一场名为“别叫我凯伦”的工作场所活动，以强调“美国白人女性的经历范围”，并促进“关于种族的公开和诚实的对话”。由于有色人种员工的强烈反对，她被安排休假。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>或者想想斯坦福大学法学院负责多样性的副院长，他在保守派法官凯尔·邓肯的演讲中试图“缓和”学生抗议。院长试图安抚因法官的反 LGBTQ+ 观点而愤怒的学生，同时给法官完成演讲的空间。但她的干预引起了公众的愤怒，因为人们认为她将学生的感受置于法官的言论自由权之上。她也被安排休假。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p>如果这些对话阻碍了高级多元化、公平和包容性 (DEI) 专业人士的发展，那么普通领导者还有什么希望呢？比你想象的还要多。</p><p>我们领导纽约大学法学院的一个研究中心，致力于研究多样性、包容性和归属感问题。我们共同或单独教导了来自各行各业的数以万计的人如何跨越差异进行更有意义和有效的对话。我们集中精力指导掌权者，因为他们有最大的机会改变这些互动的动态——培养同理心，而不是引发恐惧和分裂。</p><p>虽然我们辅导的人在多种类型的身份对话中遇到困难，但分歧往往是最令人痛苦的。当你和对方意见一致时，参与身份对话相对容易。当你不同意时，你可能会充满焦虑和自我怀疑。你可能会想：<em>我真的像我想象的那样开明吗？人们会感到被我伤害或背叛吗？</em></p><p>你可能会想通过屈服于谈话伙伴所说的任何内容来应对这种焦虑。然而这种做法往往并不可取，因为它损害了你的尊严和真实性。我们相信，即使在当今两极分化和过热的政治气候下，在身份问题上仍然可能存在分歧。关键是要尊重地去做。就是这样。</p><h3>在争议等级上找到对话</h3><p>我们都是同性关系——Kenji 于 2009 年与他的丈夫结婚，David 于 2014 年与他的丈夫结婚——而且我们在许多论坛上参与了有关同性婚姻的辩论。我们从来不喜欢这些讨论，但我们发现其中的一个特点特别糟糕：我们的对手很少承认这场辩论对我们或其他 LGBTQ+ 人群意味着什么。</p><p>在一本反对婚姻平等的著名著作中，作者坚持认为，人们可以拒绝同性婚姻，“但不要诋毁受同性吸引的人，或忽视他们的需求”。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>他们在现场对话中采取了相同的立场。在一场有关同性婚姻的电视辩论中，主持人要求作者之一瑞安·安德森（Ryan Anderson）向女同性恋财务顾问苏兹·奥曼（Suze Orman）解释“她出了什么问题”。 “我不认为你有什么问题，”安德森告诉奥曼。 “问题是，什么是婚姻？我认为婚姻本质上是……一男一女的结合。” <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>尽管这听起来很外交，但这种回应并没有意识到，从许多同性恋者的角度来看，安德森反对同性婚姻在逻辑上意味着他认为奥曼是二等公民。然而，在我们关于这个话题的无数次对话中，我们可以用一只手数出对方认识到我们可能会认为他们的观点是对我们基本人性的攻击的次数。这种方法并不要求他们改变观点。它只是要求他们承认这种观点可能会如何传播到另一方。</p><p>部分由于这种挫败感，我们开发了一个争议量表，将分歧的主题沿直线绘制出来。左边是最安全的话题，在这些话题中存在分歧是可以预料的，甚至是值得庆祝的。右边是最有争议的话题，对话最有可能变得丑陋。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>如何表达不同意见</h4><p class="caption">在这种争议规模上定位对话主题可以帮助您在更有可能进行尊重性讨论的层面上构建一个困难的主题。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MAG_Yoshino_Essay_Winter_2024_Figure-1.png" alt="如何表达不同意见" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p>关于个人品味的分歧通常是温暖而善意的。当朋友嘲笑我们喜欢垃圾电视节目时，这些分歧会加强而不是削弱我们的关系。对事实的分歧也相对舒服，只要这确实是关于事实的辩论（例如谁、什么、何时、何地或如何），而不是关于价值观的几乎不加掩饰的辩论（被定义为“另类事实”或“假新闻”） ）。当话题在争议规模上进一步向右漂移时，真正的危险就来了。最激烈的对话是其中一方或双方都感到他们的平等人性受到质疑的对话。</p><p>想象一下，您是工作场所多元化和包容性倡议的拉丁裔支持者，而您正在与反对该计划的非拉丁裔同事进行辩论。我们认为，讨论该倡议是否成功地提高了拉丁裔在工作场所的代表性（事实），您会觉得不舒服，但可以控制。您会发现很难争论是否应在晋升决策（政策）中考虑多样性因素。你会发现争论心理学家理查德·赫恩斯坦和政治学家查尔斯·默里臭名昭著的假设，即智商在种族和族裔群体之间存在差异（人性平等）是令人痛苦的。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>身份分歧的问题在于，特权较高的对话伙伴几乎总是将问题定位在争议规模上的不同位置，而不是特权较少的对话伙伴。如果您认为您的公司过于关注反种族主义，您可能会将这场争议视为关于组织应如何优先考虑其使命的不同方面的政策辩论。你的谈话对象是一位亚裔美国同事，她可能会认为你轻视了她对公司的归属感。毕竟，她是那个必须与工作场所的反亚裔偏见作斗争的人。您将该问题定位在“政策”争议范围的中间位置。 She locates it at the rightward extreme of “equal humanity.”</p><p></p><p> You might find that after you recognize where the other person is on the controversy scale, you&#39;ll reassess the nature of the disagreement, moving the issue closer to where they&#39;ve positioned it. But you might not, and we&#39;re not pushing you to do so. All we ask is that you explicitly acknowledge your counterpart&#39;s position. At the outset of the conversation, you might say something like, “To me this is a policy debate, but I see how it could be deeply personal for you, and I&#39;ll do my best to respect that reality when sharing my views.” There might also be times during or after a conversation where you realize you treated the topic as a purely intellectual exercise and need to recognize the impact the discussion might have had on the other person: “I&#39;ve been bringing policy arguments to the table, but can I ask how you&#39;ve been experiencing this discussion as someone whose life might be more directly affected by this issue?”</p><p> We think you&#39;ll be shocked at how much acknowledging your relative subject positions can take the hurt or heat out of a disagreement. This holds true even if those positions seem obvious to both parties. Often, what&#39;s needed is not more knowledge but more acknowledgment of shared knowledge.</p><p></p><h3> Find Uncommon Commonalities</h3><p> In the 1987 movie <cite>Predator</cite> , the character of Dutch (played by Arnold Schwarzenegger) and the character of Dillon (Carl Weathers) greet each other with what&#39;s come to be known as an epic handshake. “Dillon, you son of a bitch,” Dutch says as they walk up to each other and clasp their hands together with their hulking arms in a V-shape like they&#39;re about to arm-wrestle. They refuse to let go of each other&#39;s hand. Then the handshake turns into an actual arm-wrestling match. It&#39;s an almost parodic display of over-the-top masculinity.</p><p> The scene might have been forgotten but for a viral meme. When social media users want to show two seemingly unrelated people, groups, or concepts that share a surprising commonality, they post a picture of Dutch and Dillon shaking hands. They put one label over Dutch&#39;s arm, another over Dillon&#39;s arm, and the commonality in the middle. In one instance, revenge and ice cream shake hands over the phrase “best served cold.” The epic handshake has also spawned other attempts at highlighting unpredictable overlaps using Venn diagrams. We learn that bank robbers, DJs, and preachers share “put your hands up.” These images help us see the handshake hidden in each arm-wrestling match.</p><p> This capability is critical, and cultivating it is harder than it looks. It&#39;s conventional wisdom that offering points of agreement is an effective strategy when disagreeing with someone. But as philosopher Daniel Dennett has noted, it&#39;s particularly helpful to find points that “are not matters of general or widespread agreement.” <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> The idea is to find uncommon commonalities that surprise you out of your defaults. Too often, people settle for the bland ones that feel like empty gestures. It&#39;s like posting the bank robbers, DJs, and preachers meme and making the commonality “occupations.”</p><p> Instead, try to find uncommon commonalities that can liberate you as well as your conversation partner and help make even the most inflammatory of subjects easier to discuss. In recent years, hordes of concerned parents have streamed into usually sleepy town hall meetings to express outrage over the conversations about race being held in their children&#39;s classrooms. One such parent is Bart Glasgow (no relation to David), a conservative evangelical Christian White man from Canton, Georgia, who spoke up at a school board meeting to oppose the hiring of a DEI administrator in his local district.</p><p></p><p> Bart and his wife, Coley, decided to speak with four experts on the subject of race. One was Carol Anderson, a professor and chair of African American studies at Emory University and author of several books, including <cite>White Rage</cite> . On the surface, Anderson and the Glasgows have little in common. Yet in their hour-long conversation, both sides made considerable effort to find points of connection. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Bart Glasgow noted that he wrote his senior college thesis on the topic of civil disobedience, examining figures like Henry David Thoreau, Mahatma Gandhi, and Martin Luther King Jr. “I think what Dr. King did was amazing,” he said. “To take that biblical principle of turning the other cheek and to show love when hate&#39;s being shown to you.” Anderson noted that her father was “career military” and described being raised in the church and in a “God-fearing” community. They all bonded over their experience of growing up with the <cite>World Book Encyclopedia</cite> in their homes and with parents who would take them “to the woodshed.” They continued by sharing experiences of being in the minority in an educational setting. Anderson, who is Black, talked about being bussed to a majority-White high school. Coley Glasgow, who is White, shared that she completed her higher education at two historically Black colleges.</p><p> This exploration of common ground paid dividends. As the conversation continued, they aired disagreements. Bart Glasgow argued against an emphasis on systemic racism; Anderson disagreed. Later, Bart advocated for school vouchers that would allow parents to move their children out of underperforming local schools, and again Anderson disagreed. Yet these disagreements were remarkably civil. When the conversation concluded, Bart said to Anderson, “I could talk to you for hours. I really could.” Anderson replied, “Thank you so much for being here and asking these wonderful questions and engaging in this great conversation.谢谢。 I love it.”</p><p> The next time you are confronted with a disagreement, try asking yourself what you have in common with your conversation partner that might surprise them. If you&#39;re debating same-sex marriage, you might point out that many people — straight and gay — think marriage is an antiquated institution. So, despite your differences, you both believe in the importance of marriage as an institution. Finding those uncommon commonalities requires a bit of ingenuity, and it might feel taxing at times. But the payoff is big: Finding them can jolt both of you out of the reflexive and unconscious sense that you are adversaries in the conversation.</p><h3> Show Your Work</h3><p> Shortly after we launched the Meltzer Center for Diversity, Inclusion, and Belonging, we received an unnerving email from a respected colleague. She asked us to use our platform as diversity and inclusion scholars to advocate for people who don&#39;t fully vaccinate themselves or their children. In her view, excluding people from schools and workplaces for defying vaccine mandates had “troubling” implications for the values of diversity, inclusion, and belonging. She invited us to discuss the issue with her so it could be addressed university-wide.</p><p> We received this request before the COVID-19 pandemic turned vaccines into a white-hot issue. Even so, we knew this conversation might be difficult. We passionately disagreed with her perspective, but we feared that neither acknowledging her position on the controversy scale nor offering an epic handshake would suffice.</p><p> So we shared our reasoning in depth. We stated politely but firmly that we didn&#39;t believe opposition to vaccines fit within the scope of our center&#39;s work. We explained that the center&#39;s primary function was to address bias against marginalized social groups, like people of color or women. We acknowledged that some groups, like religious minorities, were mistreated because of their beliefs rather than because of their physical characteristics. But particularly as a newly launched center, we weren&#39;t eager to stretch the definition of a marginalized group to people defined by their views on a single issue. We also noted that the topic of vaccine hesitancy raised complicated medical, ethical, and public health questions outside our expertise.</p><p> We had no illusions that this approach would change our colleague&#39;s mind. But it showed we&#39;d given her viewpoint real consideration, and it also offered her an opportunity to point out where we might be wrong. She thanked us for the thoughtfulness of our response, noted that she completely understood our position, and invited us to participate in an event on a separate topic.</p><p> Our approach to our colleague&#39;s inquiry was an example of showing your work — that is, explaining a disagreement in as much detail as possible to demonstrate to the other person that you&#39;ve thought carefully about the subject. The advice to highlight points of disagreement might seem out of step with our previous emphasis on finding common ground. But you can and should do both — look for points of agreement and share points of disagreement in detail. Paint a complete picture of the facts and values on which you&#39;re basing your disagreement, any research and conversations that have informed your current thinking, and any remaining doubts or uncertainties you hold. Over your conversation partner&#39;s lifetime, they&#39;ve probably encountered many people who have reflexively opposed their views based on shoddy or incomplete work. Showing the effort you&#39;ve made will distinguish you from those opponents. It will help them respond to you rather than to all those voices from their past.</p><p> A word of caution: When showing your work, don&#39;t offer a slapdash summary of the opposing argument before immediately dismissing it. Writer Moira Weigel has likened this mistake to “the first sentence of the last paragraph” of a high school essay: “I have thought of the other side already. Do not accuse me of not having thought of the other side!” <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Rather than taking that cursory approach, take the time to research and understand the opposing view, and then share that understanding generously before you explain why you continue to see the issue differently. Show your work to show your respect.</p><h3> Manage Expectations</h3><p> Many people have a low tolerance for disagreement in general. If a contentious identity issue comes up at a conference room table, they immediately change the subject. If they have an argument with someone, they replay the conversation in their mind for weeks. David, unfortunately, is one such person. He&#39;ll run away from voicing a disagreement to avoid conflict, then stew alone in frustration that the other person doesn&#39;t agree with him. For whatever reason, he seems to have an unrealistic expectation that identity conversations should always end in a group hug.</p><p> People sometimes ask us anguished questions along these lines: “I&#39;m an atheist and staunch liberal, but a colleague on my team at work is a conservative evangelical Christian. How can we work together despite our disagreements?” Our answer: Lower your expectations. We admit this advice probably won&#39;t make its way onto a motivational poster. But we think it&#39;s completely appropriate to scale the intensity of the passion you bring into the disagreement to the intensity of the relationship.</p><p></p><p> A cartoon by Randall Munroe shows a stick figure furiously tapping away at a computer keyboard while a voice from the other room calls out, “Are you coming to bed?” The stick figure responds, “I can&#39;t. This is important. Someone is <em>wrong</em> on the internet.” <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Most people have enough perspective not to care fiercely about disagreements with random internet trolls. But it&#39;s worth cultivating that healthy instinct in other situations, too. Each of us would struggle if we had a major disagreement with our spouse about issues of identity. Nevertheless, we&#39;ve both supervised and advanced the careers of students who disagree with us, because the teacher-student relationship is less intense than the marital one. The same goes for colleagues, neighbors, and acquaintances. When the relationship isn&#39;t as close, the need for agreement should be lower.</p><p> You can also manage your expectations of what can be achieved in a single conversation. As with any dispute over a heavy subject, identity conflicts often aren&#39;t neatly resolved in one encounter. The first conversation might go poorly, but the second might go better and the third better still. You might need to take multiple off-ramps and on-ramps to and from a conversation before you make progress.</p><p></p><p> When people engage in conversations about identity, diversity, and justice with someone who has opposing views, we encourage them to practice the four strategies we&#39;ve described:</p><ul><li> Locate the conversation on the controversy scale. To you, the conversation might be a factual or policy debate, but to the other person, it might be a debate over their equal humanity.</li><li> Find uncommon commonalities — points of agreement that are not matters of widespread agreement.</li><li> Show your work on the remaining disagreements to demonstrate that you&#39;ve thought carefully about the subject.</li><li> Manage your expectations. Scale the intensity with which you care about the disagreement to the intensity of the relationship.</li></ul><p> Despite the examples we&#39;ve shared, you might think we&#39;re being unrealistic about your ability to disagree agreeably on matters of identity by practicing these strategies. It&#39;s true that they can&#39;t ensure positive outcomes in all conversations. But we&#39;re confident that you&#39;ll see an immediate improvement in the quality of your conversations if you follow these guidelines.</p><p></p><p> Sometimes, of course, the rift between you and the other person will be too wide. Sometimes an attempt at conversation will end without a resolution. Sometimes the relationship itself will end. As awful as that outcome can feel, it&#39;s sometimes a necessary one. We&#39;re not here to guarantee that every disagreement will end happily. Rather, we want to help you ensure that a divide is truly unbridgeable before you walk away from it.</p><p> Other times, of course, you might be surprised in a positive way. Few, if any, meaningful relationships are devoid of conflict. When handled well, moments of tension can deepen a bond. Rather than nodding along insincerely or offering fake opinions, sharing a thoughtful difference of opinion can show the other person that you value them enough to be honest with them. Moreover, by modeling how to productively disagree, you can set the tone for how others throughout your organization can navigate today&#39;s thorniest conversations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-productively-disagree-on-tough-topics/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Real Measure of Presentation Success</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a> is the CEO of <a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a> , a communication company in the Silicon Valley. She&#39;s the author of six books, including <cite>DataStory: Explain Data and Inspire Action Through Story</cite> (Ideapress Publishing, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Historically, it’s been tough to quantify the success of events, presentations, and speeches. We’ve long known that the spoken word is a powerful tool for influence and action, but how do you measure that power? When many organizations flipped from in-person to virtual and hybrid meetings and events, presentation [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Duarte-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Historically, it&#39;s been tough to quantify the success of events, presentations, and speeches. We&#39;ve long known that the spoken word is a powerful tool for influence and action, but how do you measure that power?</p><p> When many organizations flipped from in-person to virtual and hybrid meetings and events, presentation analytics became a whole new ballgame. Speakers used to measure impact largely by surveying people and reading the literal room. While those forms of feedback still provide useful information about whether and how a message is landing, presenters now have many other metrics they can use.</p><p></p><p> Here&#39;s a quick example: For decades, my firm built all the decks for a large company&#39;s annual software developer conference. When the conference went remote because of COVID-19, we reworked all the content — each of the breakout sessions, as well as the keynotes — for a virtual audience. After that conference, the organizers stack-ranked the most popular sessions and realized they&#39;d put the same amount of energy into creating a session that garnered 40 views as they&#39;d put into creating sessions that earned hundreds of thousands of views. The organizers also got data on the percentages of participants actively engaging with the sessions, along with related numbers on downloads and shares. Combined with the substance of attendee comments, these insights told the conference folks which topics were resonating both broadly and deeply, helped them manage their time investments, and shaped their choice to keep the conference mostly virtual.</p><p> That&#39;s just one of many ways you can slice, dice, and analyze. But to gauge a presentation&#39;s success, what should you measure <em>for</em> ? In the example above, a key organizational goal was for developers to learn and build new software features into products, so the conference folks were looking specifically at how long each attendee stayed in the critical sessions, how active they were in the learning sessions, which tools they downloaded, and, after the event, how many applications the developers rolled out. Once the event team knew which sessions had turned out to be the most useful, they could create better-targeted content for the next conference.</p><p> All of these yardsticks measured some form of action. And really, that&#39;s what all presenters should be looking for: evidence that they&#39;ve moved people to <em>do</em> something, whether it&#39;s learning a new skill, adopting a new approach to organizational culture, changing a deeply ingrained process or behavior, or treating customers differently.</p><p> To measure a presentation&#39;s success, you need to assess your audience members&#39; feelings and actions before you speak, while you speak, and after you&#39;re done.</p><p></p><h3> Before Your Talk</h3><p> To define what baseline result you&#39;re after — that is, what action you want people to take after they walk away from your talk — it helps to know your audience. In studying hundreds of powerful speeches (and even checking out business speeches from the Stanford University library all the way back to the 1950s), I found that most of their <a href="https://www.duarte.com/how-to-write-a-call-to-action-in-a-persuasive-speech/#:~:text=Who's%20in%20Your%20Audience%2C%20and,they%20bring%20to%20the%20table.">calls to action</a> targeted one of four audience types: <em>doers</em> , who could instigate activity and get things moving in the organization; <em>suppliers</em> , who could provide resources and other types of support needed to achieve a desired goal; <em>influencers</em> , who could mobilize others to adopt a new idea or approach; or <em>innovators</em> , who could generate new ideas and apply their smarts to solve a problem or seize an opportunity.</p><p> Which type of audience will you address in your talk? Once you&#39;ve sorted out that critical “who,” you can analyze the “what” and the “how” of getting people to adopt and implement your idea. Specifically, you can take one of the following approaches.</p><p> <strong>Delve into your audience&#39;s thoughts and feelings.</strong> Ask yourself about the people you want to reach: <em>What</em> do they think about your idea now? If it&#39;s not on their radar yet, <em>how</em> will they feel about it when they hear what you have to say? And how do you want their thoughts and feelings to <em>change</em> as a result of your talk?</p><p></p><p> This isn&#39;t just a hypothetical stepping-into-their-shoes exercise. Gathering that information in advance — and articulating the points of view you want to move people <em>from</em> and <em>to</em> — will determine the way you frame an issue and possible responses to it. That could mean doing some research or surveying the audience to assess what people currently know about your topic and how they feel about it. For example, you might interview the people closest to your customers or culture. Are they excited about your idea, or skeptical of it? What questions do they have about it? Not only will you figure out what baseline you&#39;re starting from — you&#39;re also likely to gain insights about your audience that will help you <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/four-storytelling-techniques-to-bring-your-data-to-life/">craft your message</a> . You can also identify a benchmark to measure against later on, after your presentation — say, one of your organization&#39;s KPIs or an important talent-recruitment metric.</p><p> <strong>Anticipate emotional sticking points.</strong> The bigger the transformation you&#39;re trying to trigger in your audience, the more difficult it can be to quantify, especially if it&#39;s an emotional shift. As you research what&#39;s currently going on in your audience members&#39; heads, consider their hearts as well. What&#39;s going to be the hardest part of your message for people to accept or process, no matter how logical the argument or solid the evidence? What sources of potential resistance can you identify? If you do win over people&#39;s heads, how will you know when you&#39;ve won over their hearts, too?</p><p> Emotional change often won&#39;t show up on a dashboard. Even technologies that allow organizations to <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/employee-emotions-arent-noise-theyre-data/">track customer or employee sentiment</a> won&#39;t collect data on everything you need to know. Sometimes you&#39;ll know you&#39;ve overcome emotional resistance only when you see it later in new behaviors — when employees stop pushing back on important initiatives, for example, or when customers change their minds and buy the new release of your product.</p><h3> During Your Talk</h3><p> You can gauge your talk&#39;s likelihood of success as it&#39;s happening. To do this, you&#39;ll measure audience reactions in a few ways.</p><p> <strong>Observe audience behavior in the room or online.</strong> The most immediate form of measurement is to watch how people respond to a presentation in real time. When everyone takes out their phones to snap pictures of slides, you know something&#39;s grabbing their attention. Notice, too, when people laugh, gasp, or applaud — these basic behavioral cues signal <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-data-insights-visually-consumable/">which moments in your talk are resonating</a> . Tech comes in really handy here. If your talk (whether delivered in person or remotely) is recorded, you can easily go back and look for places where the audience visibly or audibly responded.</p><p> <strong>Look at the number of attendees.</strong> If you&#39;re addressing a crowd at a big event such as an industry gathering, another useful metric is the number of people who showed up to hear you speak when they could have attended other sessions instead. If you&#39;ve packed a physical or virtual room, that means you&#39;ve teed up your talk effectively before even opening your mouth. When I spoke this year at Dreamforce, a Salesforce conference, most of my audience members skewed young and weren&#39;t familiar with my work, but the talk was still oversubscribed, with overflow attendees clustered in the doorway. My name wasn&#39;t the draw — rather, it&#39;s the way I&#39;d titled and framed the message that hit a nerve. When attendees rated the talk, the data showed that it had lived up to the promise in the title and program description.</p><p> <strong>Spark and track social engagement.</strong> If your talk is getting everyone buzzing, especially at a large event, they might share quotes or images from your presentation in real time on social channels. Be sure to add your social handles and event-specific hashtags to your slides so it&#39;s easier for your audience to tag you and for you to track the ideas they&#39;re engaging with most. (Those posts, comments, likes, reshares, and other in-the-moment social reactions can later be captured in a post-event report.) You can also accelerate and measure the spread of ideas by providing repackaged presentation content in easily shared formats like infographics or <a href="https://www.duarte.com/resources/books/slidedocs/">Slidedocs</a> (slides that have more text because they are meant to be read by the audience rather than simply presented by the speaker). One of our tech customers has us build their keynote speeches into skimmable e-books with the script and slide visuals as well as trackable links to additional material.</p><h3> After Your Talk</h3><p> Your post-talk metrics can track both satisfaction with the presentation and some of the steps audience members have taken to implement the ideas.</p><p> <strong>Use surveys to assess audience satisfaction.</strong>许多演讲者在演讲后使用调查来衡量观众的情绪。如果您在演讲之前也对人们进行了调查，您将能够了解您的演讲是否使听众中的实干家、供应商、影响者或创新者更加接近您的观点。我们合作的一家财富 100 强科技公司也使用观众收视率作为管理工具来激励演讲者表现出色。每个人都想获得尽可能高的分数，而那些得分不好的人可能会在下次演讲时努力提高分数，或者不会被邀请回来。</p><p><strong>检查说话者自己的满意度。</strong>在没有强大衡量文化的公司中，有时最明显的成功标志之一就是演讲者自己认为他们的演讲进行得如何。这可能看起来有些自作多情，但这比大多数人想象的要重要。如果一个领导者不断地提高自己作为沟通者的技能和表现，并且对观众的暗示很敏感，那么他认为自己已经进行了有效的演讲，那么他们的机会实际上很大。而且，嘿，当你的首席执行官想要感觉自己像个摇滚明星，而他们走下舞台时也感觉像个摇滚明星，我称之为胜利。</p><p></p><p><strong>量化所采取的行动。</strong>在这里，您可以回到您定义的基线结果 - 您在开发演示文稿时想要引发或改变的观众行为。虽然满意度和认同等反应很重要，但行动更重要。演讲的目的是说服人们采纳并实施你的想法。因此，请看看您的倡议因您的演讲而获得的关注。您的员工是否填写了人力资源团队在福利演示中提到的注册表？您的销售团队是否下载了您在启动时推出的新公司概述？最终完成了多少笔交易？我在我的幻灯片中嵌入了二维码——大多数人都知道如何使用它们——并分享我的幻灯片。这使得与会者可以对概念进行更深入的“双击”。我的营销团队可以跟踪所有活动以进行会谈后分析。</p><p></p><p>如果您试图阻止某些行为，那么衡量这些行为也很重要。有一年，一家公司聘请了我的团队来帮助他们发布计划重组的消息，这是最难发布的演示文稿之一。高管们尤其担心两种后果：高价值员工沮丧地离职，以及生产力下降。因此，他们决定在公告发布后跟踪两个数据点：未来几个月的辞职人数，以及未来几周客户关系管理数据中反映的生产力下降情况。收到这些报告后，他们欣慰地发现这两个数字都比公司领导层的预期要好得多。在这种情况下，衡量成功意味着在传递精心设计的消息后跟踪<em>缺乏</em>（即消极）行动的情况。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-real-measure-of-presentation-success/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>化学品披露迫在眉睫的挑战</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lori Bestervelt, Colleen McLoughlin, and Jillian Stacy. <p>Lori Bestervelt 博士是前全球运营主管，Colleen McLoughlin 博士、DABT、ERT 是 Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry 毒理学总监。 Jillian Stacy 是 Enhesa Sustainable Chemistry 的业务经理。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Life Cycle]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Practices]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Sam Falconer/theispot.com New and emerging rules in the U.S. and Europe that make companies responsible for the environmental impacts of products through their entire life cycles are forcing brands to confront a striking knowledge gap: their often inadequate understanding of the chemicals found in their supply chains. The European Green Deal’s Circular Economy Action Plan, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bestervelt_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">萨姆·法尔科纳/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>美国和欧洲的新规则要求公司对产品整个生命周期对环境的影响负责，这迫使品牌面临一个巨大的知识差距：他们对其供应链中发现的化学品往往了解不足。</p><p> 2020年3月通过的<a href="https://environment.ec.europa.eu/strategy/circular-economy-action-plan_en">欧洲绿色新政循环经济行动计划</a>；新提出的影响时装和纺织品<a href="https://wwd.com/sustainability/business/legislation-moves-in-the-eu-new-laws-in-france-germany-and-the-netherlands-1235458823/">的生态设计规则</a>；拟议的<a href="https://commission.europa.eu/business-economy-euro/doing-business-eu/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence_en">企业可持续发展尽职调查指令</a>将要求公司披露对人权和环境的任何风险。它们适用于整个产品生命周期，从成分和材料的配方到产品制造、包装和分销以及回收和处置。在美国，加利福尼亚州、科罗拉多州、缅因州和俄勒冈州这四个州已经通过了<a href="https://www.packworld.com/news/sustainability/article/22419036/four-states-enact-packaging-epr-laws">针对包装材料的生产者延伸责任法</a>，该问题将成为美国证券交易委员会最终<a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-46">范围 3 供应链要求</a>的焦点。除了此类立法之外，世界各地的司法管辖区还推出了一系列新的监管行动，重点关注<a href="https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billTextClient.xhtml?bill_id=202120220SB54">材料采购和处置</a>、<a href="https://www.nysenate.gov/legislation/bills/2021/S8922">全球供应链安全</a>以及保护员工安全和人权。</p><p></p><p>这些规则对许多制造、营销和销售我们穿的衣服、我们使用的化妆品以及我们孩子玩的玩具的品牌提出了挑战，因为他们的公司对其产品的详细化学成分知之甚少。 。</p><p>面对监管的发展，时尚品牌不得不重新考虑对材料、染料和大量与森林砍伐和污染有关的化学品的使用。他们还需要能够通过供应链中的每个环节追踪这些化合物。</p><p>追踪一件衣服的化学成分并不是一件容易的事，因为一件衣服中使用的数十种物质和材料来自不同的供应商，并在不同的阶段融入到产品中。像牛仔裤这样的基本服装将由来自数十个不同供应商的面料组合、染料、柔软剂、褪色酶、杀菌剂和防腐剂制成，采用不同的配方，需要使用不同的技术来应用。所有这些因素都会在供应链和整个产品生命周期的各个环节造成环境危害。</p><p></p><h3>超越安全数据表</h3><p>销售消费品的知名品牌面临监管机构清理供应链的最大压力。尽管许多公司已公开<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/companies-rush-to-trace-sprawling-supply-chains-as-sustainability-rules-loom-11674512050">承诺</a>提高其可持续性，但获得供应商和合作伙伴所需的合作一直是一个挑战。大多数品牌都依赖其供应商提供的安全数据表 (SDS) 来获取有关产品化学成分的信息。然而，这些文件的主要目的是披露可能伤害供应链中工人或其他人的化学品和化合物的信息。它们没有提供有关产品中使用的每种材料的化学成分的详细信息，也没有提供有关其对回收和处置的影响的任何有意义的见解。</p><p>在我们为一些全球最大品牌进行化学危害评估和产品毒理学分析的过程中，我们审查的 SDS 中大约有三分之一包含有关其所涵盖的产品和材料的化学成分的不完整或不准确的信息。无论这是供应商故意遗漏信息的结果，还是 SDS 作为披露工具的局限性的反映，最终结果是负责这些产品的品牌往往对产品内部的内容一无所知。</p><p>填补 SDS 中提供的基本信息与全球当局即将要求的详细披露之间的差距，已成为许多品牌冲突和困惑的根源。一些供应商不愿意分享详细的化学配方以保护商业秘密，许多品牌也不愿意（或无法）投资于昂贵的化学评估。</p><p></p><p>我们预计这个问题将通过两种方式得到解决。首先，市场可能会转向能够证明其产品和流程安全的供应商。我们已经开始在时尚行业看到这一点：Gucci、H&amp;M、Stella McCartney 和 Zara 等品牌最近承诺从可持续纺织厂<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fashion-giants-vow-to-buy-more-recycled-fibers-in-boost-to-sustainable-textile-mills-11668451031">购买更多回收材料</a>。其次，公司必须投资于详细的化学品筛选，以提供更全面的危害评估和完整的配方披露。随着品牌寻求确定性和评估供应商的客观方法，这种方法也越来越受欢迎。</p><p>在这两种情况下，处于可持续发展转变中心的大品牌的关键目标都是透明度。品牌需要开始与供应商进行坦诚对话，了解其产品中的具体成分以及定期报告和披露的预期内容。他们可能需要增加人员，以便有足够的资源与供应商合作，特别是在寻求将工作关系扩展到第一层之外的情况下。品牌可能还必须协调组织多个部门的信息请求以获得认可。参与整个供应链可能是一项乏味而艰苦的工作。</p><p></p><p>这些并不总是轻松的对话。我们在这里看到的最常见的沟通障碍是保密问题，供应商表示他们太忙了，无法处理客户提出的一系列化学成分问题，以及对询问内容和原因的误解。品牌不一定知道向供应商提出什么要求。他们也不知道在获得信息后如何评估化学品的影响。品牌可能还必须管理多个内部化学品库存系统，并协调不同平台供应商的数据。</p><p>为了让各方达成共识，品牌需要标准化一个流程，以确定要问什么问题、要问谁以及如何管理收集到的信息。品牌还需要向供应商解释为什么这些信息对企业很重要以及他们将如何使用这些信息，以减轻隐私问题。</p><h3>通过数字评估化学品风险</h3><p>正如我们所指出的，当更多品牌无法从供应链合作伙伴那里获得可靠信息时，我们预计更多品牌会提供其产品化学成分的确凿证据。</p><p>提供产品化学风险客观确定性的唯一方法是进行化学危害评估，识别产品生产中使用的特定化学成分，并根据已知毒素的综合列表对其进行筛选，以提供危害评分。不过，它们并不便宜。 Companies can expect to spend anywhere from $3,000 to $10,000 per substance for each assessment;对于有大量必须仔细审查的科学文献的物质来说，其成本处于该范围的较高端。因为即使是最基本的服装、化妆品、玩具和消费品也含有数十种单独的化学品，因此成本也会迅速上升。</p><p>除了这些成本之外，一旦发现有毒物质，在生产过程中重新装备和更换有毒物质也面临挑战，人们开始清楚地看到，迫在眉睫的最后期限（例如欧洲绿色协议的 2050 年净零排放目标）比看上去要近得多。</p><p></p><p>从供应链中去除有毒物质的过程中关键的第一步是系统地识别它们。例如，我们最近与一个全球鞋类品牌合作开展了一个项目，该品牌的全公司使命是使其橡胶供应链更加环保可持续。首先，它建立了当前化学品库存的综合数据库，并根据其运营所在司法管辖区的已知毒素和受管制化学品清单检查所有条目。只有这样，它才能开始转向更安全的化学品。</p><p>随着品牌的进步，品牌需要将这些机构知识融入到其采购和产品开发流程中，以减轻或消除未来产品在其整个生命周期中的有害化学影响。</p><p>从长远来看，这些举措将带来更安全、更可持续的消费品。然而，在短期内，随着越来越多的品牌开始认识到，在当今以可持续发展为导向的经济中，经过考验的制造和分销方法已不再足够，预计供应链将出现大量中断和重组。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-looming-challenge-of-chemical-disclosures/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何让人们重新学习技能：语言课</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Carl Clarke, Zsófia Belovai, Michelle Davies, Nicha Surawattananon, and James Elfer. <p>卡尔·克拉克 (Carl Clarke) 是沃达丰的人才、学习、领导力、技能和人员绩效总监。 Zsófia Belovai 是 MoreThanNow 的行为科学主管。米歇尔·戴维斯 (Michelle Davies) 是沃达丰学习、绩效和再培训战略的负责人。 Nicha Surawattananon 是 MoreThanNow 的行为科学家。 James Elfer 是 MoreThanNow 的创始人兼首席执行官。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Reskilling has become an imperative rather than merely a growth opportunity. Technology advancements like generative AI have led the World Economic Forum to project that 44% of employees will experience skill disruptions in 2023. On the surface, organizations seem to be rising to this challenge: Thirty-four percent of Fortune [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Belovai-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>重新培训已成为当务之急，而不仅仅是增长机会。<a href="https://www.ilo.org/global/about-the-ilo/newsroom/news/WCMS_890740/lang--en/index.htm">生成式人工智能</a>等技术进步促使<a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2023/05/future-of-jobs-2023-skills/">世界经济论坛预测，</a>到 2023 年，44% 的员工将经历技能中断。从表面上看，组织似乎正在迎接这一挑战：财富 50 强公司中有 34% 已经进行了再培训和培训根据波士顿咨询集团的研究，提高技能是首要战略优先事项，并指定了年度预算的 1.5% 来支持这些优先事项。</p><p>然而，尽管对学习计划和人才技术平台等再培训基础设施的投资水平很高，但我们发现组织低估了通过有效的敬业度策略<em>改变员工行为的</em>必要性。如果人们不报名参加，那么即使拥有精心设计的再培训计划也对组织没有任何帮助。为了实现转变，领导者必须了解如何以鼓励人们学习的方式将人们与再培训计划联系起来。</p><p></p><p>在咨询公司 MoreThanNow 和全球电信公司沃达丰的行为科学家团队进行的一项实验中，我们发现，虽然大多数领导者将重新技能视为<em>个人</em>进步的机会和/或实现公司战略的手段，但更坦率、自信的信息让他们的技能与数字化未来相关的想法促使更多的人采取行动。我们提供了有关如何改变行为的证据，以帮助领导者将员工与组织在再培训和技能提升方面进行的大量投资联系起来。</p><p></p><h3>职业相关性引起共鸣</h3><p>我们的随机对照实验包括全球 800 名沃达丰员工的样本，旨在确定最能吸引人们探索沃达丰变革案例的语言和动机。我们比较了四种不同的消息类型，介绍了公司的学习产品以及员工应该注册的原因：</p><p> <strong>1. 个人发展：</strong>您将投资自己的职业道路并在数字化未来中蓬勃发展。<br /> <strong>2. 公司战略：</strong>您将帮助沃达丰转型为一家面向数字未来的科技公司。<br /> <strong>3. 学习乐趣：</strong>每天发现新技能和能力时，您会将学习的乐趣融入到工作中。<br /> <strong>4. 职业相关性和安全性：</strong>您将为数字化未来培养技能和能力。</p><p>虽然大多数领导者和组织在谈论再培训时倾向于使用信息 1 和 2，但我们发现，第四条更直接的“职业相关性和安全性”信息对对以技术为中心的角色进行再培训的态度具有最大的积极影响。与收到其他消息的员工相比，收到该消息的员工平均对更广泛的职业选择持更开放的态度，考虑再培训的可能性高出 4.9%，尽管该计划需要时间和精力。虽然这些数字可能看起来很小，但它们具有统计意义，来自语言的无成本变化，并且是可扩展的。</p><p>也许更值得注意的是，实验表明，收到“职业相关性”信息的人更有可能（14.7%）在沃达丰内部网站上探索再培训机会，这提供了一种切实可行的方法来衡量沃达丰员工如何实际投入时间来发展他们的技能。</p><h3>领导者的三个再培训沟通技巧</h3><p>信息 4 通过公开、诚实和明确的关于重新技能的必要性的信息产生了更大的影响。</p><p>数十年的研究表明，为什么损失比收益更大，以及如何将其用作改变思想和行为的有效语言工具。例如，当人们被要求评估失去或获得金钱的情感影响时，他们系统地<a href="https://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/document?repid=rep1&type=pdf&doi=e89e139fc94470c62f0904b69c229816bba4c2ba">认为损失具有更大的影响</a>。同样，在与经济学家进行的<a href="https://www.ssoar.info/ssoar/bitstream/handle/document/28311/ssoar-jebo-2009-3-gachter_et_al-are_experimental_economists_prone_to.pdf?sequence=1">现场实验</a>中，告诉参与者他们将因迟到的会议注册而被罚款的消息比为提前注册提供折扣的消息要有效得多。</p><p>这些研究和我们自己的研究得出了以下三个技巧，可以帮助管理者在人工智能和生成人工智能等颠覆性技术兴起的情况下更有效地与员工讨论重新培训技能的问题。</p><p><strong>设定背景：新兴技术对员工职业生涯的潜在影响要令人放心但保持透明。</strong>诚实地对待人工智能和其他技术对工作角色可能产生的影响的不确定性，而不是只传达其优点。员工常常担心人工智能会抢走他们的工作，但它更有可能改变和扩大他们的工作。谈论如何积极主动地应对这些变化，并参与技能提升和再培训机会，以驾驭变革浪潮。这可以促使员工更积极地尝试探索增加技术知识并相应发展其角色的好处。</p><p><strong>使其相关：给出个人的、具体的例子。</strong>讨论新技术对个人特定工作领域的影响，并概述可能会给团队带来哪些变化。也许您的团队开发演示文稿、处理数据或根据客户反馈采取行动的方式将会改变。确定具体场景将帮助您和您的员工思考不断发展的技术环境中所需的技能，并制定切实可行的行动计划。</p><p><strong>让它成为现实：为未来提供最佳选择。</strong>消息灵通、开放。谈论员工需要将培训计划视为未来的技能，而不是作为一种可有可无的福利。员工很容易迷失在海量的再培训计划信息中，作为经理，您有责任引导他们选择公司提供的最佳未来职业选择。例如，与其说“我希望你考虑一个培训计划来发展你的职业生涯”，不如说“我希望你考虑一个培训计划；未来你的角色的某些部分可能会实现自动化，因此我们需要确保你的技能不断发展。”</p><p></p><p></p><p>沃达丰的实验取得了成功：公司领导者改变了他们的语言，从传达“个人进步”福利改为更坦诚的“职业相关性和安全性”信息。当沃达丰推出第一批再培训计划时，它利用这种预先沟通方式成功吸引了 4,000 名意大利员工。目前，约 300 名员工已成功接受再培训，并从联络中心重新部署到其他内部职能部门。沃达丰员工总共完成了 100 万小时的学习时间。</p><p>我们鼓励领导者效仿沃达丰的做法，以更开放、更直接的方式与员工讨论再培训问题。您的数字化未来以及您的员工成功驾驭变化的世界的能力可能取决于它。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-engage-people-on-reskilling-a-language-lesson/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>利用生成式人工智能进行营销：哈佛商学院的 Ayelet Israel</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Market Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[As an associate professor at Harvard Business School and cofounder of the Customer Intelligence Lab at the school’s Digital Data Design Institute, Ayelet Israeli’s work is focused on how data and technology can inform marketing strategy, as well as how generative AI can be a useful tool in eliminating algorithmic bias. One of the products [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>作为哈佛商学院副教授和该校数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的联合创始人，Ayelet Israel 的工作重点是数据和技术如何为营销策略提供信息，以及生成式人工智能如何成为营销策略中的有用工具。消除算法偏差。她最近的工作成果之一是她与两位微软经济学家和研究人员合着的一篇<a href="https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4395751">论文</a>，内容涉及如何使用生成式人工智能来模拟焦点小组和调查以确定客户偏好。</p><p> Ayelet 加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，讨论生成式人工智能在市场研究中的机遇和局限性。她详细介绍了研究的进行方式以及人工智能技术如何帮助营销人员减少与传统客户研究方法相关的时间、成本和复杂性。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/MMAI-S8-E3-Israeli-HBS-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="阿耶莱特·以色列"></p><h4>阿耶莱特·以色列，哈佛商学院</h4><p>阿耶莱特·以色列 (Ayelet Israel) 是哈佛商学院营销部门工商管理学马文·鲍尔 (Marvin Bower) 副教授。她也是该校数字数据设计学院客户智能实验室的联合创始人。她的研究重点是数据驱动的营销，重点是企业如何利用内部数据、客户数据和市场数据来改善结果。她的研究兴趣包括零售、定价策略、渠道管理、营销分析和算法偏差。以色列拥有博士学位。西北大学凯洛格管理学院营销学博士。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>使用生成式人工智能如何帮助我们了解消费者的偏好？在今天的节目中，听听一位教授讲述她的市场研究。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我是哈佛商学院的阿耶莱特·以色列，你们正在听的是<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>大家好。今天，谢尔文和我很高兴阿耶莱特·以色列加入。她是哈佛商学院数字数据设计研究所客户智能实验室的副教授和联合创始人。 Ayelet，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。让我们开始吧。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>非常感谢您邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通常，我们首先会询问客人的职业。但作为一名教授的好处在于人们知道这意味着什么。但我仍然认为很高兴听到一些关于你的背景和简历的信息。那么您能花一点时间介绍一下自己并告诉我们您对什么感兴趣吗？</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>好的。我是哈佛商学院的营销学教授。我真正感兴趣的是我们如何更好地利用数据和人工智能来获得更好的结果，如果这对公司、客户和整个社会都有好处的话。我正在进行的一些工作是围绕人工智能以及企业如何利用它来更好地获取消费者信息和偏好。在我所做的其他工作中，我思考如何消除决策中的算法偏差。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>几个月前我看到了您关于使用生成式人工智能的演讲，这真的让我觉得很有趣，因为很多人都在谈论生成式人工智能，但我们还没有很多证据。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>证据……并不是说它不存在，而是即将到来。但你开始通过你正在进行的这项研究获得一些证据。我们可以在市场研究中使用 GPT 和生成式做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我和我在 Microsoft 的两位同事 Donald Ngwe 和 James Brand 开始思考，我们真的可以使用 GPT 进行市场研究吗？这个想法是，有些人已经证明，你可以通过向 GPT 提出问题来复制非常著名的实验，包括著名的 Milgram 实验。我们在想，“我们作为研究人员和实践者所做的工作就是为了更好地了解客户的偏好；也许我们可以使用 GPT 来实际提取这些类型的偏好。”</p><p>对于大型语言模型，其想法是它们将为您提供最有可能的下一个单词。语言就是这样产生的。我们在想，“也许如果我们要求 GPT 或诱导它在两件事之间做出选择，也许答案（最有可能的下一个词）实际上会反映人群中最可能的反应。从这个意义上说，我们本质上会查询 GPT，但会得到我们在人群中看到的偏好的潜在分布。”我们开始尝试这个想法。我们专注于消费产品——因为我们假设 GPT 所了解的数据主要围绕消费产品，可能来自评论网站或类似的东西——看看这个想法是否真的可行？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>有点！</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>那太棒了。请告诉我们更多信息。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我们的第一反应是，“好吧，让我们看看它是否能产生我们对经济学所期望的非常基本的东西。例如，当价格较高时，它是否知道拒绝报价？它知道在价格和选择之间进行权衡吗？”我们确实看到了一条向下倾斜的需求曲线，这正是我们在查询 GPT 数千次以获得答案时所期望看到的。我们还看到这样的事情，“哦，我们可以告诉它一些关于它的收入的信息，它会对此做出反应。”当它的收入较高时，它对价格的敏感度就会降低，这是有道理的——这也是我们对人们的期望。</p><p>我们还看到，它可以对有关自身的信息做出反应：“哦，上次您在这个类别中购买时，您购买了这个特定品牌”，这使得它将来更有可能选择这个品牌。所以这些是我们对“它是否真的以人类在调查中的方式做出反应？”的测试。然后我们更进一步，我们试图让人们愿意为产品或某些属性付费。然后我们基本上将价格分布与我们在市场上看到的价格分布进行比较，这非常一致。</p><p>对我们来说，真正有趣和令人兴奋的事情是能够了解为属性付费的意愿，因为这是我们作为营销人员都希望找到的东西。在我们的例子中，它是牙膏，我们试图弄清楚有多少人愿意为氟化物支付多少钱，这是我们很难考虑的事情。如果有人问你——“我不知道。”我确实知道我更喜欢买这款牙膏，但我不知道编号是多少。所以这让我们更好奇，GPT 是否可以像我们询问消费者的方式一样为我们提供这个数字。研究人员多年来已经表明，提出这些问题的最佳方法是通过联合研究。本质上，您为人们提供 10 到 15 个选择，通过他们的不同选择，您能够了解他们正在做出的权衡，并实际量化他们愿意支付的差异。</p><p>我们基本上就是这么做的。我们使用 GPT 进行了联合类型分析，并将结果与​​即将发表的论文刚刚运行的人体研究进行了比较，并得到了非常相似的结果，所以我们对此感到非常兴奋。当然，结果并不相同。我们需要做更多的工作来弄清楚一些问题出在哪里，以及这在多大程度上具有普遍性，但我们能够解决这个问题的事实就令人难以置信地令人兴奋。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这对公司来说似乎很令人兴奋，因为我猜测对很多人进行市场研究的成本比仅仅通过 ChatGPT 进行一堆 API 调用要高得多。这一定是吸引力。还有其他上诉吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>基本上，这些类型的研究非常耗时、昂贵且复杂。理想情况下，您希望要求人们做出很多权衡，但您受到人类这样做的能力的限制。使用GPT，您可以多次查询。但在这一点上，我不会告诉任何人，“用 GPT 或另一个法学硕士取代你所有的人体研究”，因为要弄清楚如何正确地做到这一点，还有很多工作要做。</p><p> GPT 的特点之一是它是经过预训练的。它会给我偏好，但这些偏好与其预训练的时间段相关。一家公司想知道“客户现在对什么感兴趣？”所以这是一种限制。</p><p>我们现在正在测试的是，也许我们仍然需要询问人员，但询问的人数比平时要少。因此，通常当您进行这些研究时，您需要数千名用户才能获得从学术或统计角度来看稳健且具有统计显着性的结果。我们正在尝试看看，也许我可以从更少的人那里收集信息，并通过微调将其与 LLM 结合起来，并生成一些有用的东西。但实际上，一个很大的优势是节省成本和时间。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这是一个重要的时刻。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。到目前为止，我们讨论的是消费品，但您可以考虑企业对企业类型的调查，这种调查成本更高，也更难进行。所以也许那里也有潜力。我们还没有测试过。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我喜欢这个主意。我的意思是，当你考虑生成式人工智能的大多数用例时，你会发现很多关于消除工作中的苦差事或创建图像和内容以及总结文本的事情。然后还有围绕计划和库存管理的更高级的内容。但你所说的实际上是用这个取代人类，对吗？我的意思是，基本上就是这样。</p><p>这是一个可能非常有趣的事情的开始，因为你至少证明了它是合理的，对吗？我的意思是，你问了所有这些问题，我想这在经济上是合理的。但是，作为一名营销人员，你就是你自己，并非所有营销策略都基于理性。事实上，其中许多都是基于完全非理性的欲望。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您对许多人做出的非理性选择有何看法，这些选择创造了这些大品牌和 20,000 美元的手袋以及诸如此类的东西？你如何利用这一点？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>在回答你的问题之前，作为一名学者，我首先感到紧张的是当你使用“<em>已证明”</em>这个词时。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>证明——我听到了！</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我看到山姆是……</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我说这话的时候笑了。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>我想说我们展示了与此相符的证据。我们也知道这些模型仍在不断发展，也许我们一个月前展示的东西在一个月后就不再相关，这也是为什么你不应该在没有测试的情况下就去实现它的原因。所以我想对此小心。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>所以你知道，对于什么是产品，人们有更理性的看法，但品牌所创造的价值对我们来说是无法衡量和难以量化的。但这几乎就像我用氟化物给出的例子一样。就像，我们不知道如何量化氟化物。如果我问你，“哦，你愿意花多少钱购买像高露洁这样的品牌，而不是我刚配制的牙膏？”我们可能会觉得很困难。</p><p>实际上，相同的联合研究模型将能够推断出这些差异。例如，我们可以看到 Mac 相对于其他计算机类型的偏好。所以它已经以某种方式嵌入其中。</p><p>现在它有多准确——这是一个经验问题。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>是的，不，你说得很对，因为当我听到你回答这个问题时，我也意识到我的假设，即你所展示的一些证据，相对于已被证明的，不一定是合理的。而是它有能力概括大多数人所做的事情——或者很多人所做的事情——并将其嵌入到它所训练的内容中。那么我的第二个问题是，如何让它更细分、更具体或更细致？因为当您进行焦点小组讨论时，您可能正在寻找特定的风味/特定的细微差别组合。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，而且，当 GPT 和其他法学硕士刚刚推出时，我们看到了很多用途，很多令人兴奋的是，“我是一名工程师。我只能问它一个问题。它给了我最常见的东西。这正是我想要的。”事实上，我们正在做的是另一面。我们不想要最常见的东西。我们想了解分布。</p><p>这就是为什么当我们查询 GPT 时，我们会多次询问每个问题 - 因为我们希望获得很多很多不同的消费者。在我们的分析中，我们仅改变了收入和您之前购买的商品。但我们可以以同样的方式改变性别、种族、任何你想要的东西……年龄。我已经看到其他研究人员这样做了。 ……</p><p>哥伦比亚大学和伯克利分校的同事发表了一篇非常有趣的论文，其中使用 GPT 来创建感知图——两个品牌彼此之间的接近程度。他们还表现出性别、年龄以及汽车等方面的差异，我们预计在汽车市场上会看到这些差异。所以你也绝对可以以类似的方式做到这一点。这也体现在政治学的政治学中。我可以给某人一种意识形态，他们的投票行为是有意义的，他们在不同主题上生成的文本是有意义的。作为一个关心异质性并了解不同消费者之间差异的营销人员，这也是非常令人兴奋的。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。如果我们能将其用于临床试验就好了。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我看到了一些关于法学硕士相对于医生更好的临床态度的论文，所以也许仍然有一些东西。 [笑。]</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>也许这就是 GPT-5。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>不过，正如你所说，我认为这些工作方式是对最有可能的下一个单词、最有可能的下一个单词进行概率估计……并且你已经细分出了“鉴于你的收入较低” ，高收入，鉴于你是这个属性，那个属性……”这很有趣，但是我们从哪里想到奇怪的地方呢？如果一切都基于“最有可能”，特别是预定义的[参数]——并不是说你不擅长想出一个好的搜索空间，而是我们如何找到我们不知道的东西，那么？这不是市场研究和焦点小组得出的结果吗？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>当然，这是挑战的一部分。显然，GPT 学习某种分布，但有些人，你知道……可以说它学习的所有内容都是来自评论。可能有很多非常极端的消费者，他们不会在网上写评论或无法访问互联网，但有这些有趣的极端想法。即使我告诉 GPT，“我想要尽可能多的随机性，非常高的变化”，我也不会去找那些人。所以这肯定会是一个问题。</p><p>我已经知道一些初创公司正在尝试解决这个问题并识别这些极端消费者，然后通过使用法学硕士来预测他们在另一种情况下会做什么，从而将他们提升到一个新的水平。但与此同时，已经有一些关于 GPT 创造力的工作，它创造了非常有创意的想法，你知道，这并不完全是你所要求的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>其中一些创意不受现实的限制。我想我们都见过其中的一些，[比如]它下棋的方式，并认为该规则有点过于限制。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。所以这也是幻觉的问题，应该在不同的环境下进行测试。但我认为我们诱导它做出选择的方式不太容易出现幻觉问题，因为它提供了一种选择，并且你不需要询问事实或类似的东西。我并不是想说 GPT 的表现会优于任何客户调查或类似的调查。我只想看看它是否和人类一样优秀。</p><p>即使是与我们交谈的人类客户，我们也必须非常努力地找到人来进行这些调查，有时我们会错过他们。我们也许能够得到一些人的分布，但仍然必须在没有人工智能而只有人类对话的极端情况下努力工作。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我发现真正有趣的是，你说过“这不如消费者调查”，现在我想挑战这一点。因为我发现你的这个想法有趣的是，当你考虑其他人工智能或一代人工智能用例时，你会说，“好吧，所以我是一个人。我是个工程师。我有一个任务。让我们问问 GPT，或者任何生成式人工智能系统，它是否是知识类工作，是否能像人类一样做得好。 OK, great.或者它能比人类编码得更好吗？或者它可以创建一个视频、文档或其他东西，让您阅读后会说：“哇，这太棒了。那么<em>你</em>就可以做到。我不需要这么做。”正确的？所以这种举证责任是非常明确的。</p><p>在这一点上，我不太确定你<em>是否需要</em>承担举证责任，因为在很多方面，我们假设一个由 500 人或 1000 人组成的焦点小组，或任何调查 - 我的意思是，没有焦点据我所知，有这么大的一个群体——但这种调查在某种程度上是福音，或者，就像 GPT 或其他人，无论什么——</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>您能和我们论文的审稿人谈谈吗？ [笑。]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>因为事实是，如果你仔细想想，那就是如果唯一知道的方法......那就回去吧。因为，你看：你的前提是，“我们将通过增强这个来在所有市场研究上节省很多钱”，这是一个真实的前提，而且肯定是这样。但我也发现负担减轻了。即使您不停止任何一项基于人类的市场研究或调查，您仍然可以通过扩大反应和选择范围来增加大量价值。</p><p>因为我会争论，你怎么知道 1,000 人或 2,000 人具有<em>代表性</em>，或者他们有所有这些细微差别？所以这件事实际上带来了事实存在的信号，否则你就不会在那里。 And I find that actually quite inspiring to a marketer.我很高兴与您的审稿人交谈。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为作为学者，我们习惯于一定程度的严谨性和稳健性，以及能够说，哦，实际证明事物的能力，而且这个工具可以提供某些东西的模拟这一事实很好，但是“它真的能取代人类吗？”是一个更高的负担，因为这个问题，它实际上给了我有意义的、更新的答案吗？它会匹配某些东西吗？你会说，“好吧，也许人类一开始就没有那么伟大，那么我们为什么要尝试……？”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>不，我实际上是在表达不同的观点。我接受过科学家培训，在科学界和学术界，我承担的举证责任要高得多。我并不是想争辩说你已经证明它可以取代人类。我不认为它会取代人类。但我想说的是，这样做的价值在于，它极大地增强了营销人员可用的信号、见解和想法，因为根据定义，没有任何调查或焦点小组是不受限制的，这不是有限，因为它拥有那里的一切。所以我的观点并不是证明举证责任已经得到满足，而是我什至不知道是否应该有这种举证责任，因为它正在解决焦点小组和传统研究的局限性。所以不一定需要更换。它们一开始就并不完美。没有人会反对这一点。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。我认为，至少，我可以放心地说，我们表明它可以提供有关偏好和正在发生的事情的非常丰富的信息，至少在它所训练的数据范围内。考虑到研究的类型以及市场研究和接触人员等方面的问题，这可能已经对很多公司产生了很大的改变。一定。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这里有多种不同的信号，我认为我们首先从以下想法解决了这个问题：这个信号是否取代了焦点小组的其他信号？但这里的因变量可能是，人们真的购买产品吗？人们买氟化物吗？他们购买[假货]产品吗？</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果这个信号为该预测添加了一些信息，那么我们就有了一个新的信息源。如果它完全取代了它，那么我们就有了不同的东西。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。现在我们要解决的问题是，对陈述的偏好与实际上基于人们行为的显露偏好进行调查。现在，我认为 GPT 的问题可能比人类少，因为它不受实验者偏见或试图安抚我等因素的影响。因此，它可能会给我一些更接近的东西，但如果它带来来自评论网站或市场研究的数据，但它仍然给我一些可能更接近所陈述的偏好的东西，而不一定[给我]人们实际会购买什么。但焦点小组和调查也是如此。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以我们认为这是一种新的信号源——那里有很多不同的信号，并且它可能与一个信号有一些重叠。而且我认为这本身就很有趣，但它也可能有一个新的信号。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我发现的另一件令人着迷的事情是，人工智能解决方案已经过数据训练，然后，当它们投入生产时，它们会接受数据训练，或者从生产中的数据中获得反馈，然后它们得到更好的。对于生成式人工智能，很多反馈也需要由人类驱动而不是数据驱动，对吗？就像，这就是它告诉你要做的事情。它引起你的共鸣吗？是的，不是，等等。所以感觉就像是一种技术，生成式人工智能可以成为另一个生成式人工智能输出的用户。</p><p>因此，让我们看一下这样的范式，看，它正在取代焦点小组中的人员，或者我们也可以替换公司中的人员，该公司是一个营销人员，负责处理生成式人工智能的响应，例如“你如何设计一个营销活动”为了这？”</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>嗯嗯。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以这个想法可能是多个生成式人工智能代理相互竞争以提高整体质量——你对此有何看法？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为这是一个有趣的想法。但我也认为，<a href="http://john-joseph-horton.com/papers/llm_ask.pdf">到目前为止的证据</a>表明，在某些时候，你仍然需要至少一个人参与其中……</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>当然。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong> ……因为所有这些幻觉，不切实际的事情出现了。但当然，如果这些模型变得越来越好、效率越来越高、质量越来越高，那为什么不呢？当我们在组织中实施这些类型的事情时，我们还需要考虑如何——我不知道这个词是否完全是<em>“验证”</em> ，但我们如何确保该过程仍然有意义并且我们不这样做这些特工互相交谈只是浪费大家的时间吗？</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>不，当然。你是100%正确的。你需要人类参与其中，而且可能至少需要几十年。但您可能不需要那么多。你知道，如果你有某种输出应该对 20,000 名客户服务代表有所帮助，并且根据反馈、根据他们在试点中的使用情况，它会变得更好，让我们比如说，三个月，也许你不需要向 5,000 人进行试点。也许你可以将其试点给一百个人加上两到三个不同的人工智能代理，这样你就可以大大加快采用时间。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，那很酷。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>虽然我不得不说，当我听到你这么说时，Shervin，它让我想到的是当人们将麦克风距离扬声器太近时，我们会得到这些反馈循环 - 放大反馈循环。我确实担心，如果这两个数据源过于一致，我们就会被压制。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>确实如此。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们不会变得疯狂。跳到本章后面：给我们答案。人们正在听这个，他们在公司工作，他们现在就可以使用这些工具，而不是 20 年后，就像我们作为学者所想的那样。人们现在应该使用这些工具做什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>和他们一起玩。弄清楚……您想了解客户的哪些信息？我们在论文中提供了完整的提示列表，详细说明了如何提示这些类型的事情并开始获取这些信息。正如谢尔文之前所说，它到底是什么？我们不确定，但这是一个信号。那里有我们可以开始查找的信息，对吧？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通过使用它，可以帮助人们发现其中包含哪些信息？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为是测试和发现。但从一个具体的问题开始确实很有帮助，因为你会陷入很多兔子洞。您可以永远进行这些对话。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Ayelet Israel，您是我们接待的唯一一位带有“AI”缩写的客人，这非常适合“<em>我”、“我自己”和“Ayelet Israel”</em> ，即<em>“我、我自己和我自己”</em> 。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong> [笑]</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>请告诉我们更多有关您自己和您的背景的信息，以及您如何最终达到现在的位置以及是什么让您对所有这些东西感兴趣。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>当然。正如我的姓氏所示，我最初来自以色列。以色列被誉为“<a href="https://www.cfr.org/book/start-nation">创业国家</a>”。当我开始思考我想在大学学习什么时，有一个特殊的项目旨在通过为人们提供某种管理工具来改善创业国家。因此，这是一个为期五年的计算机科学学士学位和 MBA 联合课程。</p><p>我开始这样做，我喜欢计算机科学。我实际上主修金融和营销，但我对营销特别感兴趣，特别是在这种背景下理解大量数据，这些数据非常有趣且实用。然后我决定获得博士学位。在营销方面。</p><p>多年来，我认为消费品或围绕客户和交易的事物对我来说很有趣。这只是一个迷人的世界。你有很多关于这方面的数据，因为随着我们更多地转向在线和数字化，我们可以看到越来越多的数据。接下来的问题是，“我们如何才能更有效、更负责任地利用这些数据？”我的研究的一部分也是关于这一点的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以我们有一个环节，我们会问您一系列快速问题，让您了解情况。只需回答您想到的第一件事即可。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>好的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>目前人工智能最大的机会是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>最大的机会。这并不快。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>下一个问题。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>是的，下一个问题。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>哦，好的。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我会考虑一下。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>通过。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>通过。您认为目前人们对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我周围的人往往从事这方面的工作，并且了解这一点，这只是一个模型，但很多人仍然不明白，仍然想象着机器人和发生的这种神奇的事情。这就是为什么我喜欢非常清楚地解释，“哦，它是预测下一个单词的可能性并在分布上选择它们，这就是所发生的一切。”所以我认为我们的情况可能仍然不像十年前那么糟糕，但仍然是这种神奇的、人为的事情发生，但事实并非如此。我想它仍然很神奇。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这真是太神奇了——或者说可以。您想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我不知道。在以色列，你参军。我在军队；我是一名情报中尉。我不认为这是我必然想要的职业。这是我做的事。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>关于人工智能有很多讨论和兴奋。人们在哪里过度使用它？人们在哪里使用它而不适用它？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我认为我看到的挑战之一实际上是用它来问事实问题，因为这不是它的目的。这不是一种真相发现机制，这只是一种错误的用法。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>好的。有没有什么事情是你希望人工智能现在就能做到但它却做不到的？接下来令人兴奋的事情是什么？明天的什么公告会让你高兴？</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我对这个问题的回答略有不同。我认为，就负责任地使用数据和算法偏差的研究而言，人工智能让我兴奋的是，是的，很多人已经表明人工智能可以产生有偏见的结果。多年来我们也知道人类会产生有偏见的结果。人工智能让我兴奋的是，机器更容易修复有偏见的结果并生成消除偏见的流程，而对人类来说要困难得多。这是我真正感到兴奋的事情。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我喜欢这一点，因为我们的世界里存在着所有这些偏见和厌女症，而不是机器造成的。首先，机器并不是让我们陷入这种境地的人。事实上，在我们训练它们之前，它们可能在一开始就做了一些这样的事情，我们不应该因为它们开始走这条路而将它们扔掉，因为我们可以调整模型中的权重。我们可以向模型提供反馈，以改进模型，而这是我们无法对无数人提供的。</p><p><strong>阿耶莱特·以色列：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以我认为这是一个重要的观点。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>我们已经看到了第一代人工智能图像模型。如果你说“医生”，我们只是[看到]男人或类似事物的照片。随着时间的推移，这种情况已经有了很大改善。这真的很令人兴奋，对吧？我们可以尝试思考如何使用这些东西解决一些社会问题，因为，是的，机器比人类更容易被操纵。当然，这是一种风险，但那是针对某些科幻播客，而不是针对这个。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>图像中医生的例子很恰当，因为我认为很多人都对这些模型的准确性着迷，因为他们感觉是对的。他们证实了我们的刻板印象。你要求这张图片，它给你的正是你所认为的那个图片，但这只是再次加剧了问题。如果我们不[阻止]，这种情况就会持续下去。但是，正如你所说，那里已经有所改善。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Ayelet，非常感谢你。这确实很有见地，也很有趣。感谢您参加节目。</p><p> <strong>Ayelet Israel：</strong>非常感谢您邀请我。这很有趣。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>感谢您今天加入我们。在我们的下一集中，Shervin 和我与 Shopify 首席产品官 Miqdad Jaffer 进行了交谈。在您进行假日购物之前，请加入我们，了解无处不在的人工智能如何为我们所有人带来巨大的价值。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/marketing-with-generative-ai-harvard-business-schools-ayelet-israeli/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>更智能的 KPI 治理</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron, Michael Schrage, François Candelon, Shervin Khodabandeh, and Michael Chu. <p class="mt20"><strong>David Kiron</strong>是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>研究部编辑主任，也是其<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/">“大创意”研究计划的</a>项目负责人。</p><p class="mt20"><strong>迈克尔·施拉格 (Michael Schrage)</strong>是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院数字经济倡议的研究员。他的研究、写作和咨询工作重点关注数字媒体、模型和指标的行为经济学，作为管理创新机会和风险的战略资源。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>François Candelon</strong>是波士顿咨询集团 (BCG) 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 亨德森研究所的全球总监，他的研究重点是技术对商业和社会的影响。您可以通过<a href= "mailto:candelon.francois@bcg.com">candelon.francois@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh</strong>是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是 BCG 北美人工智能业务的联席领导者。他是 BCG X 的领导者，在推动人工智能和数字化业务影响方面拥有 20 多年的经验。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <strong>Michael Chu</strong>是 BCG 合伙人兼副总监，专注于将人工智能和机器学习应用于商业职能中的业务问题，包括优化定价、促销、销售和营销。您可以通过<a href= "mailto:chu.michael@bcg.com">chu.michael@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Metrics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[About the Research This article series presents findings from the seventh annual global research study on artificial intelligence and business strategy by MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group. In spring 2023, we fielded a global survey and subsequently analyzed records from 3,043 respondents representing more than 25 industries and 100 countries. We also [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>关于研究</h4><p>本系列文章介绍了<em>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</em>和波士顿咨询集团第七次年度人工智能和商业战略全球研究的结果。 2023 年春季，我们开展了一项全球调查，随后分析了来自 25 个行业和 100 个国家/地区的 3,043 名受访者的记录。我们还采访了 17 名在金融服务、媒体和娱乐、零售、旅游和运输以及生命科学等众多公司和行业领导人工智能计划的高管。</p><p>我们的研究探讨了管理者和领导者如何使用人工智能来增强战略衡量，以推进战略成果。它探讨了组织如何利用人工智能调整甚至生成新的 KPI 来定义和提供可衡量的更好绩效。</p></aside><p>如果不进行调整和细化，静态业务指标会产生两种类型的战略风险。一是鼓励在错误的措施上表现。例如，2008 年全球经济危机的部分原因是银行对当时广泛使用的指标的依赖：风险价值，该指标衡量正常市场条件下单个时间点的潜在投资组合损失。金融机构没有调整这一措施，因为风险较高的次级抵押贷款和证券化违约掉期已成为其投资组合的较大部分。在严重低估潜在损失的指标（在某些情况下，低估了几个数量级）的指导下，许多金融机构破产或遭受重大损失。</p><p></p><p>机会成本是静态关键绩效指标带来的另一个风险。我们的研究令人信服地表明，有意使用人工智能来设计和创建更具动态的 KPI 的公司可以享有更强的态势感知能力、运营与战略成果之间更紧密的联系以及整体业绩的改善。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这些<em>智能</em>KPI 反映了对绩效驱动因素的更深入理解，并且比未经人工智能通知的同类 KPI 能够对未来结果做出更可靠的预测。 （请参阅“三种类型的智能 KPI”。）在波动和快速变化的市场中，“设定后忘记它们”的关键指标方法既不可取，也不可持续。</p><div class="callout-highlight callout-simple"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>三种类型的智能 KPI</h4><p class="caption"><table id="chart1" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th>关键绩效指标类型</th><th>描述</th><th>Benefits</th><th>例子</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能描述性 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>综合历史和当前数据以提供有关<em>已发生</em>或<em>正在发生的事情</em>的见解。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>更深入地了解绩效差距及其原因。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>赛诺菲的“零食人工智能”工具通过揭示不同 KPI 之间的关键相互依赖性来增强态势感知。</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能预测 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>预测未来表现，产生可靠的领先指标。提供潜在结果的可见性。识别其他技术或人类无法识别的模式，使他们能够利用更丰富的潜在违反直觉的模式。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>采取先发制人的行动，以减轻风险或利用机会。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>通用电气已将其 KPI 转变为关注领先指标，并使用人工智能通过将订单与产品和服务的安装基础进行比较来分析订单渠道，帮助准确识别增加未来订单并推动更强劲的收入和利润的机会。</ul></p></td></tr><tr><td><ul><p><strong>智能规定 KPI</strong></ul></p></td><td><ul><p>使用 AI 推荐可优化性能的操作。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>指出绩效差距并建议纠正措施。</ul></p></td><td><ul><p>赛诺菲的智能 KPI 根据供应链绩效建议对销售 KPI 进行调整，从而使运营和销售保持一致。 </ul></p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --></p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/AI-BusinessStrategy_Article04_Table.png" alt="三种类型的智能 KPI" class="no-desktop" /></p><p class="attribution">资料来源：D. Kiron、M. Schrage、F. Candelon 等人，“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/strategic-alignment-with-ai-and-smart-kpis/">人工智能和智能 KPI 的战略调整</a>”， <span style="font-style:normal">《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</span>》，2023 年 9 月 5 日。</p></article></aside></div><p>需要有效的治理来确保 KPI 不断发展、与战略愿景保持一致，并受到员工和管理者的信任。随着人工智能注入的工作流程和流程殖民并扩展业务能力，领导者需要更新和升级其关键绩效指标以跟上。从施耐德电气到沃尔玛再到马士基，我们看到战略家、技术专家和商业领袖共同努力完善和增强 KPI，以确保其与不断变化的组织目标保持一致。</p><p>在这些公司中，使 KPI 更具预测性、动态性和洞察力的责任超出了战略家和业务领导者的范围。他们鼓励技术人员为 KPI 的制定、组织和优先级排序做出实质性贡献。与公司传统上建立和更新 KPI 的方式相比，这是一个巨大的变化。</p><p>正如施耐德电气首席治理官兼秘书长 Hervé Coureil 所观察到的那样，“当流程数字化时，它们开始产生‘废气数据’，这些数据可以转化为相关的遥测指标，提供有关流程行为、缺陷等的见解。其次，数字化转型引发重大决策和投资——投资组合和投资选择、业务模式实施、新系统和基础设施——因此，有必要衡量这些决策的影响以及构成转型的各种计划的有效性。”</p><p></p><p>制定此类措施不仅仅取决于执行判断、直觉和经验。将静态的传统绩效指标转变为更智能、更动态的 KPI，需要数据、分析和人工智能发挥更大的作用。 We suggest that leaders adopt a three-pronged approach to governing the development and use of AI-driven KPIs and, more broadly, their strategic measurement systems. This governance approach rests on three factors:</p><ol><li> A solid data foundation with responsible data and analytics practices.</li><li> Organizational structures with responsibility and accountability for evolving KPIs.</li><li> Trust in KPIs trained to adapt to and learn from changes in circumstances.</li></ol><h3> Governance of Smart KPI Development: Get Your Data in Order</h3><p> Effective KPI governance requires effective data governance. Every organization participating in our research emphasized data quality and discipline as the technical enabler for its AI-driven KPI initiatives. Most legacy IT and database systems, however, aren&#39;t configured to generate or make accessible the quality data necessary for measuring or defining smart KPIs.</p><p> Pierre-Yves Calloc&#39;h, the chief digital officer at Pernod Ricard, recalls that the spirits giant realized it needed three years&#39; worth of weekly consumer sales data to enable meaningful AI interventions. A preliminary review revealed huge gaps. “When we started, we had almost no data governance,” says Calloc&#39;h. “Almost 80% of the data we needed wasn&#39;t there because it was mainly external data. Our statistical experience is that you need weekly data; if you have monthly data, it doesn&#39;t work, so you need to source the information manually. We even called it &#39;archeology&#39; because of the level of effort needed, even going into old PowerPoint and Excel files in mailboxes. In addition, you need a strong business case for the project, because without clear benefits in mind, people will not invest the time.” Essentially, the business case for AI-powered KPIs could not be made without technically reliable and robust governance that transformed data <em>archaeology</em> into data <em>architecture</em> .</p><p> Jon Francis, General Motors&#39; chief data and analytics officer, who previously oversaw Starbucks&#39;s digital transformation, echoed Calloc&#39;h&#39;s observations. “It&#39;s actually really hard to just create a KPI because of the underlying data challenges,” he says. “It takes all of your effort, usually, to create the KPI and report on it.” Poor data and metadata governance undermines an organization&#39;s ability to develop the right metrics. Francis notes that technology systems are often just “spooling data that&#39;s not defined or useable” and, as a result, “you end up with these data dumping grounds.” He candidly observes that for most organizations, the generation of data from production systems is an afterthought.</p><p> Effective KPI governance remains contingent upon a company&#39;s technological capabilities to harness data: It demands diligent data governance, a structured approach to analytics management, and a path for technologists and business unit leaders to collaborate on developing optimal KPIs on an ongoing basis.</p><p></p><h3> Embedding Governance in Teams or Functions</h3><p> Our research finds top management rethinking how to develop and continuously improve their key performance measures and metrics. While approaches vary, a common theme among interviewed executives is choosing to locate responsibility for transforming KPIs in a specific team or group of teams.</p><p> At Schneider Electric, leadership came to recognize that the company&#39;s legacy metrics could become incompatible with its aspirations to strategically collaborate and innovate with its global customers. Coureil helped sponsor the creation of a Performance Management Office within the company&#39;s data team to oversee performance measurement. The office was deliberately positioned in the governance team to ensure a neutral cross-functional perspective.</p><p> The Performance Management Office helped top management transform their portfolio of KPIs and align them with operations. It also pushed the businesses to become far more data-driven and aware of the links between improvement against a given performance metric and enhanced outcomes. “Measurement has been very core for us,” adds Coureil. “We actually tried to make metrics a complete, integral part of our digital transformation, as opposed to an afterthought.”</p><p> What&#39;s the desired outcome of a given KPI? “It&#39;s an ontology or taxonomy question at some point: What behaviors are you looking for?” asks Coureil. “I think people put a lot of things in the KPI basket, and we&#39;ve spent a lot of time trying to be extremely clear about what we&#39;re looking at: What is the desired outcome? It looks very simple, but it is not that simple, actually … being extremely sharp on what the desired outcome of a given KPI is.” That&#39;s why having a performance management office is proving to be essential to strategically coherent and consistent KPI governance, Coureil says.</p><p> Instead of using a performance management office, DBS Bank governs KPI development through cross-functional teams that create value maps linking customer journeys to desired outcomes. The Singapore-based financial services leader revisited its operating model to reflect the fact that using smarter KPIs could measurably improve outcomes for both the business and its customers. “Over the past three years, we moved to something we call a data-driven operating model,” says group chief analytics officer and managing director Sameer Gupta.</p><p> At the heart of the model are cross-functional squads. Representatives from various functions, such as product, risk, data, marketing, call center, and human resources, form a squad, Gupta explains. Every squad member is then aligned on the same set of outcomes mapped to four categories: customer experience, employee experience, profitability, and risk.</p><p> The factors driving performance on each outcome are represented in a value map that connects performance metrics with the four types of outcomes. Each squad is responsible for identifying and optimizing these factors. “The squads look at optimizing those drivers,” says Gupta. “We look at many things to optimize those drivers: experimentation, data, customer immersion, AI, machine learning — all kinds of tools to try and continuously optimize in coordination and consultation with control towers and management dashboards.”</p><p> The result, Gupta notes, is not just greater data-driven operational efficiencies and effectiveness but KPIs that expand the boundaries of the DBS client and customer experience. Revisiting processes for KPI governance have led to both better KPIs and better KPI outcomes.</p><p> While the specific approaches vary, most leaders we spoke with are in the early stages of building governance structures to help make their KPIs more intelligent, detailed, and predictive.</p><h3> Effective KPI Governance Is Based on Trust</h3><p> While these technological and organizational investments in KPI governance are crucial to enhancing KPIs, our research suggests that their practical value to teams is contingent upon people&#39;s willingness to trust them. During Schneider Electric&#39;s digital transformation efforts, Coureil recognized that “one of the changes, versus a more traditional way of doing business, is that you don&#39;t build your dashboard anymore. Somebody else does it for you. So you have to trust those metrics.”</p><p> Anecdotal evidence indicates that establishing trust in AI-sourced metrics can be challenging.</p><p> At Maersk, for instance, the long-held assumption was that getting a vessel out of port and on its way to the next one as quickly as possible was ideal. A digital twin simulation, however, showed that being on time was better than being early: With an end-to-end connected schedule, as is also the situation for commercial airlines, the port that a vessel is heading to next can&#39;t adjust its schedule to immediately accommodate earlier arrivals. In other words, “faster isn&#39;t better” was a counterintuitive assertion from the data team, and it was only after the on-time approach was put into practice that the front-line operators — and even those at the most senior levels managing the entire terminal — were finally convinced.</p><p> Cultivating the trust necessary to develop and use dynamic, AI-enhanced KPIs is a critical leadership and governance challenge. Developing data-savvy managers who are receptive to developing and embracing AI-driven KPIs is a significant part of that challenge. At one media organization, an executive interviewee noted that she&#39;d had a hard time persuading her superiors to look at KPIs and make decisions based on data. Their usual retort was that executives are “paid millions for their gut instincts” — in other words, experience and intuition were valued over data-driven insight.</p><p></p><p> Building a data-oriented management community is one way to create trust among the leaders using enhanced KPIs. At Sanofi, the most senior 150 leaders, representing various functions and businesses, are being trained in boot camps to become more data-centric and to seek out more information before making decisions. As chief digital officer Emmanuel Frenehard says, “Our goal as part of our cultural change is that these 150 people, when they leave the boot camp, are far more inclined to adopt that data-centric view and better understand the potential of AI for us. We are making sure that the core of our leadership is trained on how to use the next generation of AI-driven KPIs.”</p><h3> Further Considerations</h3><p> To ensure that their AI-enabled smart KPIs are setting them up for strategic success, leaders must prioritize the technological, organizational, and cultural dimensions of KPI governance discussed above. As they begin to do so, these related considerations should be top of mind.</p><p> <strong>Establish a steering committee to guide continuous improvement.</strong> Transforming legacy KPIs into enhanced KPIs demands regular experimentation to ensure that key performance is focused on the right outcomes. Determining where this experimentation happens, who does it, and how often are critical leadership and governance decision points. Is it in a central team, like a performance office, or is it more widely distributed? Should certain KPIs be revisited and reviewed more frequently than others? Who has decision rights when changing KPIs changes accountability? There are no one-size-fits-all answers to these questions. Leaders need flexible processes to effectively govern KPIs that might be siloed or cross-functional. We suggest establishing a cross-functional KPI steering committee with business and technical expertise to elicit necessary input and buy-in from relevant stakeholders.</p><p> <strong>Oversee investment in capabilities to optimize groups of KPIs.</strong> Does your company have the capability to assess whether its KPIs are good enough or fully optimized? Our research suggests that AI can play a valuable role in assessing KPI quality, prioritizing KPIs, and addressing trade-offs among them. AI can help determine, for example, under what conditions customer-centricity imperatives should take priority over improving operational efficiencies, or when to prioritize revenue considerations over market share investments. Integrating AI into the process for developing, setting, and prioritizing KPIs can be a disruptive change for managers who are accustomed to making these decisions themselves. To preempt or address such disruptions requires organizational, technological, and cultural investments.</p><p> <strong>Govern KPIs like assets, not tracking tools.</strong> Enhanced KPIs can redefine key performance, not just track it: That makes KPIs, and the capability to enhance them, valuable assets. As with other assets, KPIs can depreciate with time or inattention. Governing KPIs like assets, not tracking tools, ensures that they become more valuable, insightful, and predictive over time. Given a wide variety of asset management frameworks, effective governance means choosing the appropriate asset management framework for KPI assets, including relevant, underlying data assets. Some companies are already beginning to explore using KPIs for KPIs to ensure that the value of their KPI assets consistently improves.</p><p> <strong>Elevate KPI oversight.</strong> As KPIs become more intelligent and more effective proxies for corporate strategy, it becomes more important for boards to be involved with governing KPI development and use. To be sure, developing and using KPIs are management functions. However, boards sign off on strategies that KPIs both embody and inform. Signing off on strategy but not the company&#39;s approach to developing KPIs is short-sighted and can undermine strategic aspirations. Engage the board directly in efforts to develop organizational capabilities for enhancing KPIs. Investing in enhanced KPIs is just as strategically relevant as investing in improving performance itself.</p><p></p><h3>结论</h3><p>Our three-pronged approach to governing the development and use of KPIs expands on the idea that AI can transform KPIs into strategic assets that do more than track performance. They serve as a GPS for the organization, delivering greater foresight and a deeper understanding of interdependencies among key performance drivers.</p><p> Making the transition to AI-enhanced KPIs is not an incremental shift. It is a dramatic change from exclusively human, top-down approaches to setting and refining KPIs. Organizations that have made this transition are putting technology in the (KPI development) loop.</p><p> In the future, KPIs will no longer be passive tools for measurement but active agents for empowering decision makers. Ongoing innovation using generative AI promises to expand the purpose, power, and potential of smart KPIs. Holding conversations with chat-enabled smart KPIs, for instance, is already a goal for several of the executives we interviewed. With proper governance, empowering smart KPIs will empower strategists and managers alike.</p><p> <em>Editor&#39;s note: The authors would like to thank Gaurav Jha, David Zuluaga Martínez, Allison Ryder, and Barbara Spindel for their contributions to this article.</em></p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/governance-for-smarter-kpis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Make Data Monetization Everybody&#39;s Business</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:42 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, Leslie Owens, and Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Barbara H. Wixom is a principal research scientist at MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research and chair of the center&#39;s Data Research Advisory Board. Cynthia M. Beath is a professor emerita at the McCombs School of Business, University of Texas at Austin, and a research associate at MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research. Leslie Owens is the former executive director of MIT Sloan&#39;s Center for Information Systems Research and a senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management. Previously, she was vice president and research director at Forrester Research, and a manager at Abbott. Elizabeth Heichler is editorial director, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Data Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading B.H. Wixom, C.M. Beath, and L. Owens, &#8220;How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Sept. 27, 2023. Most leaders see their organization’s data as an important asset, but few have robust strategies for converting that asset into financial returns. In their new book, Data Is Everybody&#8217;s Business, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> BH Wixom, CM Beath, and L. Owens, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-have-better-strategy-conversations-about-monetizing-data/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">How to Have Better Strategy Conversations About Monetizing Data</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , Sept. 27, 2023.</p></aside><p> Most leaders see their organization&#39;s data as an important asset, but few have robust strategies for converting that asset into financial returns. In their new book, <cite>Data Is Everybody&#39;s Business</cite> , Barbara H. Wixom, Cynthia M. Beath, and Leslie Owens argue that leaders must make data monetization a core business activity.</p><p> That requires developing a broad and shared understanding of three key data monetization approaches: improving work with data, wrapping products with data, and selling information offerings. And it also requires educating and involving employees at all levels and functions across the organization.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn how to:</p><ul><li> Implement five sets of practices that convert your organization&#39;s most important data into reusable data assets.</li><li> Establish common language so that everybody can engage in building and/or harnessing data assets.</li><li> Bring business discipline to data investments by measuring financial value realized.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-to-make-data-monetization-everybodys-business/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> A Reshoring Renaissance Is Underway</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Erin McLaughlin and Dana M. Peterson. <p>Erin McLaughlin is a senior economist at The Conference Board. Dana M. Peterson is chief economist of The Conference Board.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Labor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Offshoring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Kevin Foley/MIT SMR; Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images Companies are building manufacturing facilities in the U.S. at a pace not seen in decades. A confluence of factors is driving this trend: Amid supply chain bottlenecks, rising labor and transportation costs, U.S. tariffs on China, and geopolitical tensions, companies recognize the value of reshoring production. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/McLaughlin-Reshoring1-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Kevin Foley/MIT SMR; Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> Companies are building manufacturing facilities in the US at a pace not seen in decades. A confluence of factors is driving this trend: Amid supply chain bottlenecks, rising labor and transportation costs, US tariffs on China, and geopolitical tensions, companies recognize the value of reshoring production. US industrial policies favoring domestic manufacturing are also informing these decisions, including new laws seeking to address national security threats, economic disruptions, and dwindling access to key technological components. The result is an early-stage US reshoring renaissance.</p><p> The question for executives is whether their companies should follow this trend. But first, it&#39;s important to understand the trend&#39;s scope and what&#39;s driving it.</p><p></p><p> There have been calls for reshoring since manufacturing began sharply declining in the late 1970s, but COVID-19 marked a turning point for the C-suite. Between the first quarter of 2020 and the third quarter of 2023, executives started talking about onshoring, reshoring, and nearshoring during earnings calls and conferences much more frequently than they had previously, according to an analysis by The Conference Board.</p><p> Such talk started significantly increasing in the second quarter of 2020, as the pandemic set in globally. In the second quarter of 2022, as supply chain pressures again surged, Russia invaded Ukraine, and new federal industrial policies were enacted. Overall, instances of executives mentioning these ideas increased nearly 3,000% in just three years.</p><p> New laws also helped drive this onshoring resurgence, including the 2021 Bipartisan Infrastructure Law, the 2022 CHIPS and Science Act, and the 2022 Inflation Reduction Act. Each contains stipulations regarding the production and procurement of US-made products and components that benefit companies that manufacture domestically.</p><p> Reshoring is now driving a dramatic rise in manufacturing construction activity. Companies are constructing US manufacturing facilities at a higher rate than any other property type. Such spending rose to an annual rate of $114.7 billion in 2022, according to the US Census Bureau — a 40% increase year over year and a 62% increase over the past five years.</p><p> This made manufacturing the fastest-growing asset category in 2022, as the average growth rate for <em>all</em> nonresidential buildings and infrastructure increased just 7.4% compared with 2021. And the building continues: Manufacturing spending was 74% higher in July 2023 than in the same month the previous year.</p><p></p><p> The reshoring renaissance does not apply universally. Sectors requiring large amounts of manual labor, including shoes and apparel, furniture, and home decorative items, are <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/05/business/economy/supply-chain-reshoring-us-manufacturing.html">less likely to reshore</a> . Industries with more complex and expensive products, and those that can use automation and robotics in manufacturing, are leading the US resurgence. The <a href="https://reshorenow.org/content/pdf/2022_Data_Report.pdf">five industries</a> experiencing the greatest US employment growth as a result of reshoring and direct investment are electrical equipment, appliances, and components; computer and electronic products; chemicals; transportation equipment; and medical equipment and supplies.</p><p> Our analysis shows that North America (the US, Canada, and Mexico) has the existing supplier base to support more manufacturing activity than it currently has. In fact, for electrical equipment, North America has 15% of the global supplier base and 7% of global output. Twenty-one percent of the pharmaceutical industry&#39;s global supplier base is in North America, but its share of global output is just 18%, according to <a href="https://www.conference-board.org/publications/TCB-Global-Supplier-Index">The Conference Board Global Supplier Index</a> .</p><p></p><h3> Is Reshoring Right for Your Company?</h3><p> Reshoring results from executives and senior managers reorienting from a “low cost” to a “best cost” supply chain strategy by prioritizing factors such as supply chain resiliency, sustainability, and geopolitical stability over cheap foreign labor. Although onshoring can entail higher costs from building new facilities and paying higher wages, the benefits of minimizing external risks and creating long-term efficiencies might outweigh keeping near-term costs low.</p><p> Business leaders should consider six key factors in deciding whether to adopt this model.</p><p> <strong>1. Labor costs.</strong> Global labor shortages and cost increases — including in China, where wages are rising — make it relatively more affordable to locate manufacturing in the US than it once was. China outpaced G20 countries in real wage growth from 2008 to 2022, according to the International Labour Organization&#39;s “ <a href="https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---ed_protect/---protrav/---travail/documents/publication/wcms_862569.pdf">Global Wage Report 2022-2023</a> .” China&#39;s real monthly wages in 2022 were equivalent to about 2.6 times their real 2008 value.</p><p> <strong>2. Advanced manufacturing.</strong> New automated “smart factories,” which require more engineers and skilled technicians but often far fewer workers overall, including traditional assembly-line workers, make the US labor pool attractive due to its well-educated workforce. Demand for robotics and the advanced technology that supports smart facilities is also surging. <a href="https://www.automate.org/news/robot-sales-in-north-america-have-strongest-year-ever-in-2021">North American robot sales set a record in 2021</a> , with 39,708 units sold, for $2 billion — a 14% increase over the previous high in 2017, and 28% more than the number sold in 2020, according to the Association for Advancing Automation. Plex&#39;s “ <a href="https://www.plex.com/sites/default/files/2022-05/10292_7th_State-of-Smart-Manufacturing_Supply-Chain.pdf">7th Annual State of Smart Manufacturing Report</a> ” notes that smart-manufacturing adoption rates increased 50% in 2022 year-over-year and 83% of manufacturers reported that smart factories are key to their future success.</p><p> <strong>3. Risk mitigation.</strong> The longer and more complex the supply chain, the greater the risks it faces, especially in terms of potential geopolitical instability. There is also renewed scrutiny by the federal government of its own reliance on other economies for critical public health and national defense supplies and components, such as personal protective equipment and semiconductors used in military vehicles and weaponry.</p><p> <strong>4. Sustainability</strong> With companies increasingly needing to meet sustainability goals and reduce their carbon footprints, localizing manufacturing offers several benefits. Constructing new, green facilities domestically can greatly reduce Scope 1 operating emissions from company-owned facilities and vehicles. The US has the world&#39;s largest sustainable-building market, with more than 511 million square feet <a href="https://www.usgbc.org/articles/top-10-countries-leed-demonstrate-green-building-truly-global-movement">certified under the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design</a> rating system, compared with 180 million square feet in China. Plus, manufacturing a product closer to its end customer reduces emissions from transportation.</p><p> <strong>5. Stakeholder sentiment.</strong> Many companies&#39; stakeholders — including employees, corporate boards, industry organizations, government officials, and other companies connected within a supply chain — want executives to consider <a href="https://www.kearney.com/industry/consumer-retail/article/-/insights/the-2021-reshoring-index-the-tides-are-turning">localizing manufacturing operations</a> . Walmart — the largest retailer in the United States — vowed in 2021 to spend an additional $350 billion through 2030 on items made, grown, or assembled in the US, for example.</p><p> <strong>6. Transportation costs.</strong> When deciding whether to onshore manufacturing operations, executives should weigh the benefits of lower international labor and operating costs against the greater cost of ocean freight shipping. Trans-Pacific shipping costs increased fifteenfold in 2021 from January 2020 levels, and while transportation costs have declined as the economy has slowed, the supply chain volatility of the last few years is front of mind for managers.</p><p> The growth in US manufacturing-facility construction will continue as businesses see value in focusing on aspects of risk mitigation, using automation to offset labor challenges, and even building new facilities that emit less carbon. This reshoring renaissance is just beginning; it takes a few years to plan, permit, and acquire property for new-facility construction.</p><p></p><p> Now is the time for manufacturing executives to understand how their businesses fit into this renaissance and determine whether reshoring is right for them. Using the factors above as a framework, executives should consider these five key questions:</p><ol><li> Can a new facility for my products that uses advanced automation offset higher labor costs?</li><li> Does my current supply chain involve countries that present uncertainty due to geopolitics?</li><li> Will the carbon emissions from my company&#39;s current supply chain improve significantly if we build a new facility powered by renewable energy and localize production?</li><li> Are my stakeholders, especially customers, asking for domestically manufactured products?</li><li> Is the cost savings that comes with eliminating transoceanic shipping enough to balance out a likely increase in labor and new-facility construction costs?</li></ol><p> By seeking answers to questions such as these, the C-suite can better navigate their company&#39;s operations through a changing global production landscape.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/a-reshoring-renaissance-is-underway/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>