<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 8 月 24 日星期四 21:23:17 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>如何为所有人提供职业发展</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[George Westerman and Tony Gigliotti. <p>乔治·韦斯特曼（George Westerman）是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是麻省理工学院全球机会论坛（以前称为全球机会倡议）的创始人。 Tony Gigliotti 是 UPMC 的人才管理和组织发展高级总监，该公司是一家位于匹兹堡的医疗保健提供商和保险公司。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Career Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To be competitive in today’s tough labor markets, companies need to expand career development beyond those employees who are considered “high potential.” Helping all workers build rewarding job paths benefits both individuals and organizations. But broadening the reach of career development is not simple. Traditional development programs don’t easily scale, and most managers aren’t equipped [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA05_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>为了在当今严峻的劳动力市场中保持竞争力，公司需要将职业发展范围扩大到那些被认为“高潜力”的员工之外。帮助所有员工建立有价值的工作道路对个人和组织都有好处。但扩大职业发展范围并不简单。传统的发展计划不容易扩大规模，而且大多数经理都不具备成为优秀职业顾问的能力。</p><p>具有前瞻性的公司明白这一必要性。在 2023 年 5 月举行的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间，麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的 George Westerman 指出，在<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-companies-should-help-every-employee-chart-a-career-path/">对 1,016 名员工进行的一项调查</a>中，三分之二的人表示他们希望晋升，但“其中一半人表示他们受到了阻碍”缺乏良好的职业建议。”大多数 2021 年换工作的人都认为缺乏晋升机会是原因。</p><p></p><p></p><p>韦斯特曼表示，管理者不能完全负责员工的职业发展；许多领导者不想或不知道如何提供帮助，而且许多领导者也没有动力这样做。但组织不应该认为员工可以完全拥有自己的职业道路。 “如果你相信这个故事，那么当员工没有晋升时，你往往会责怪员工而不是系统，”他说。</p><p>相反，那些成功扩大获得职业帮助的人的公司正在使机会和途径变得可见，提供学习和练习新技能的机会，并提供丰富的反馈和指导。提供获取此信息的自主路径尤其重要，因为并非所有员工都有心理安全感与经理讨论工作选择。</p><p>保乐力加北美公司首席人力资源官兼 Westerman 小组发言人拉尼·蒙托亚 (Lani Montoya) 表示，在这家优质烈酒和葡萄酒公司，全球职位评级流程让所有 18,500 名员工也能看到自己级别的职位与上面和下面一样。 “他们可以看到团队的结构，如果他们对某个角色感兴趣，他们可以看到它在哪个团队中的地位，”她说。</p><p></p><p> UPMC 人才管理和组织发展高级总监 Tony Gigliotti 也是该小组成员之一，他表示，他的组织正在努力在职业道路和工作机会方面实现类似的透明度。这家总部位于匹兹堡的医疗保健提供商和保险公司在其医院和门诊办公室拥有 95,000 名员工。 UPMC 内网上的职业资源网站提供评估和技能培养机会，其人力资本管理系统中的一项功能显示员工工作类别内外的职位发布、职位描述和职业道路。</p><p> “现在他们触手可及的信息很多，”吉利奥蒂说。 “这将赋予更多员工权力。”</p><p>下面，Westerman 和 Gigliotti 回答了 Work/23 与会者在活动期间无法回答的一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>您如何看待那些真正喜欢自己的工作、有个人贡献且不想成为经理的员工的职业发展？</h6><p><strong>乔治·韦斯特曼：</strong>许多工人不想在职业生涯中取得进步，但仍然可以从发展机会中受益。以教师为例。很少有人想成为校长，但所有人都可以从专业发展机会中受益。大多数医生可能不想进入管理层，但每年参加继续医学教育对他们（及其患者）来说是有好处的。</p><p> <strong>Tony Gigliotti：</strong>重要的是要定义职业发展，而不仅仅是垂直晋升到领导职位。否则，部分高效且可靠的员工可能会觉得他们没有职业发展的机会，这可能会导致他们脱离敬业度。</p><p>我们为 UPMC 领导者提供的资源通过参考支持职业成长和发展的许多干预措施，采取更全面的职业发展方法。其中包括培训和学习路径、指导、辅导、工作提升/丰富、延伸任务、跨职能工作团队和委员会、会议和社区参与。</p><p></p><p>此外，我们的人才审查计划使表现出色的员工对当前职位感到满意的情况正常化。该考虑的一部分必须包括员工自己的意图。在这些情况下，我们会探索就地培养员工的方法。</p><p>最后，我们提醒领导者，职业抱负可以而且经常会随着时间的推移而改变，因此他们必须随着员工职业需求和偏好的变化寻求反馈并倾听员工的意见。</p><h6>在考虑人员为了职业发展进行内部调动时，什么标准最有效？当公司的需求和个人的需求发生冲突时，调动似乎会成为一个问题。</h6><p> <strong>Westerman：</strong>如果你认为公司的需求超过了员工调动新职位的愿望，那么你就是在邀请他们离开公司。相反，他们会跳槽到另一个雇主，让你失去雇员，并且顺利过渡的机会也更少。</p><p></p><p>为了鼓励从内部招聘，您可能不需要特殊的标准或激励措施。只需让内部候选人了解机会，并让招聘经理了解候选人即可。不过，你也可以尝试其他改变来提高激励，比如先向内部候选人开放一个职位，然后再向外部列出，或者要求经理分担外部招聘的成本。</p><h6>公司如何管理人才囤积并应对那些拒绝公开分享职业道路的管理者？</h6><p> <strong>Gigliotti：</strong>我们的组织有多种方式来应对那些囤积人才、不关注员工在组织内职业发展的领导者。我们的组织与所有员工透明地共享所有职业道路，包括职位描述。因此，尽管一些领导者倾向于囤积人才，但员工仍然可以获得了解自己（和他人）职业道路所需的资源。这种方法是消费者驱动的——也就是说，我们的员工表达了对这些信息的需求，以便他们能够在组织内规划自己的职业生涯。</p><p></p><p>此外，我们的组织人才审查旨在识别新兴人才和现成人才。整个组织内人才审核讨论的结果将被汇总，然后与人力资源主管透明地共享。这些信息使人力资源部门能够识别可能对组织内的空缺职位感兴趣并准备好担任空缺职位的潜在内部人才。</p><p>增长是我们员工敬业度模型中的一个关键维度。如果领导者不培养员工、与他们分享职业资源或鼓励他们在组织内的职业发展，那么该领导者的员工敬业度得分（特别是在成长维度）将会受到影响。低分会向该领导者的主管和当地人力资源团队发出危险信号，他们可能会进行干预。这种干预的一部分是让领导者与我们责任和诚信的组织价值观保持一致，这在一定程度上期望领导者“支持员工的……职业成长和发展”。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-deliver-career-development-for-all/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>问三阴：为什么我们不能开好会？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 23 Aug 2023 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanyin Siang. <p>Sanyin Siang 是一位 CEO 教练，领导杜克大学 Fuqua/Coach K 领导力与道德中心 (COLE)。需要建议吗？发送<a href="mailto:asksanyin@mit.edu">电子邮件至三阴</a>。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Advice]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Team Building]]></category><category><![CDATA[Trust]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Your Career]]></category><description><![CDATA[As a senior leader in my company, I find meetings are crucial for keeping tabs on what’s going on and making decisions. But we seem to accomplish little, people are frequently unprepared, and they gripe about the time cost. How can I shift people’s attitudes and run more effective meetings? We’ve all been there: We [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AskSanyin-featured-column4-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"></figcaption></figure><p class="article-body-question">作为公司的高级领导者，我发现会议对于密切关注正在发生的事情并做出决策至关重要。但我们似乎收效甚微，人们常常毫无准备，并且抱怨时间成本。如何改变人们的态度并召开更有效的会议？</p><p>我们都经历过这样的情况：我们坐下来进行了一个小时的谈话，但不知何故，会议结束时的清晰度不如开始时的清晰。我们走出去，感叹时间的浪费和缺乏进展。</p><p>在生产力超高、待办事项无穷无尽、个人疲惫不堪的时代，您的团队可能将会议视为返回工作的障碍，而不是有目的的事情。将这种态度转变为热情参与意味着重新思考您想要通过会议实现的目标。随着远程工作的广泛普及，与我们的团队实时互动的机会变得更加稀有和更有价值。我们如何利用这段时间加深关系？如果我们将建立信任作为每种类型会议的主要目标怎么办？</p><p></p><p>决策会议通常是关于对一系列行动的承诺。在这里，您还可以讨论决策对员工的情感影响以及沟通变革的最佳方式。对这些问题的深入讨论可以洞察他人的价值观和方法。</p><p>头脑风暴和解决问题的会议从对建立信任的明确考虑中受益匪浅。每个人都需要轻松地分享自己的想法，同时抵制评判的冲动。在这里，你想鼓励脆弱性，因为当我们说“我不知道”时，我们承认我们在更大的团队中的局限性和相互依赖性。</p><p>还有机会将有时例行的信息共享会议转变为更丰富的联系场所。尝试设定这样的期望：这些都是更多地了解彼此的挑战和策略的机会，并鼓励提出问题。这些会议还提供了庆祝胜利或邀请其他部门帮助的机会。利用时间帮助团队成员建立彼此之间的联系（矩阵），而不是以您为中心作为首选问题解决者的轴辐式联系。</p><p></p><p>最后，尝试在定期团队会议中安排集体反思的时间。 elf Beauty 的首席执行官塔朗·阿明 (Tarang Amin) 截至 2023 年 5 月已连续 17 个季度实现增长，每次执行领导团队会议开始时都会有时间公开分享和反思。 “高管们可以在这里谈论他们个人生活中发生的事情……他们的心态、重要举措是什么、他们在组织中听到了什么，”他说。</p><p>请记住，阻碍进展的通常不是缺乏行动项目。阻碍我们前进的往往是对意图的误解、理解上的偏差以及变革带来的情感损失。解决这些问题的方法是建立能够进行良好沟通的信任关系。因此，不要深入讨论您计划的下一次会议的<em>内容</em>，而是从<em>谁</em>以及他们之间的关系开始。您的团队可能会重新发现彼此交流所带来的活力和快乐，甚至开始期待会议。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ask-sanyin-why-cant-we-get-meetings-right/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>使用联合机器学习克服 AI 规模劣势</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Yannick Bammens and Paul Hünermund. <p>Yannick Bammens 是比利时哈瑟尔特大学战略与创新教授，他是该大学 AI4Business 计划的共同领导者。 Paul Hünermund 是丹麦哥本哈根商学院战略与创新助理教授，他在那里共同组织了一年一度的因果数据科学会议。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Big Data]]></category><category><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Deep pockets, access to talent, and massive investments in computing infrastructure only partly explain why most major breakthroughs in artificial intelligence have come from a select group of Big Tech companies that includes Amazon, Google, and Microsoft. What sets the tech giants apart from the many other businesses seeking to gain an [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Bammens_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">宗晶晶/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>雄厚的财力、人才资源以及对计算基础设施的大规模投资只能部分解释为什么人工智能领域的大多数重大突破都来自包括亚马逊、谷歌和微软在内的一批精选的大型科技公司。科技巨头与许多其他寻求从人工智能中获得优势的企业的不同之处在于，他们作为平台运营商收集了大量数据。仅亚马逊每月就在其平台上处理数百万笔交易。所有这些大数据都是丰富的战略资源，可用于开发和训练复杂的机器学习算法，但对于大多数企业来说，这是一种遥不可及的资源。</p><p>访问大数据可以实现更复杂、性能更好的人工智能和机器学习模型，但许多公司必须使用更小的数据集。对于规模较小的公司以及医疗保健、制造或建筑等传统行业的公司来说，缺乏数据是冒险进入人工智能的最大障碍。由于自我强化的数据网络效应，大数据和小数据组织之间的数字鸿沟是一个严重的问题，更多的数据会带来更好的人工智能工具，这有助于吸引更多生成更多数据的客户，等等。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>这为大公司提供了强大的人工智能竞争优势，而中小型组织则难以跟上。</p><p></p><p>多个小规模公司将数据集中在一个共同控制的中央存储库中的想法已经存在一段时间了，但对数据隐私的担忧可能会阻止此类举措。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>联合机器学习 (FedML) 是一项最新的创新技术，它通过使用去中心化数据的隐私保护协作人工智能来克服这一问题。 FedML 可能会成为游戏规则的改变者，解决拥有和没有大数据的公司之间的数字鸿沟，并使经济的更大一部分能够从人工智能中获益。这项技术不仅在理论上听起来很有前途，而且已经在工业中成功实施，我们将在下面详细介绍。但首先，我们将解释它是如何工作的。</p><h3>小数据和联合机器学习</h3><p>FedML 是一种允许小数据组织训练和使用复杂的机器学习模型的方法。<em>小数据</em>的定义取决于人工智能所解决问题的复杂性。例如，在制药领域，考虑到广阔的化学空间，获得一百万个带注释的分子用于药物发现相对较小。其他需要考虑的因素包括机器学习技术的复杂性，从简单的逻辑回归到需要更多数据的神经网络，以及应用程序所需的准确性： 对于某些人工智能应用程序（例如进行医疗诊断） ），把事情做好比其他人更重要（例如当有人打字时建议表情符号）。在其他条件相同的情况下，较小的组织和传统非数字行业的组织面临着更严重的数据相关规模劣势。</p><p></p><p>人们已经构思出一些有用的策略和技术来帮助企业解决这个问题，例如跨公司数据池、迁移学习（重新利用以前训练的模型）和自我监督学习（在人工数据集上训练模型） 。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>然而，数据池的集中式方法在某些情况下可能不适合，例如当存在禁止数据传输的法律限制或涉及应保密的敏感数据的战略问题时。同样，只有当公司能够基于执行相关领域任务的机器学习模型的早期见解时，迁移学习和自我监督学习才是可行的方法，而这可能并不总是可行的。 FedML 可以成为小数据公司人工智能工具包中强大的额外工具，并作为其他小数据技术的重要补充。</p><p>在联邦学习设置中，机器学习模型在由不同组织控制的多个分散服务器上进行训练，每个服务器都有自己的本地数据。他们与中央协调器进行通信，该中央协调器聚合各个模型更新并协调训练过程。 （请参阅“联合机器学习概述”。）在最简单的情况下，学习目标是获取数据分布的基本描述性事实，例如均值或方差。例如，每家公司都可以计算其工厂某一制造流程的平均故障率，并将其提交给协调器，然后协调器将结合这些个人的贡献以形成更准确的联合估计。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>联合机器学习概述</h4><p class="caption">在联邦学习设置中，机器学习模型在由不同组织控制的多个分散服务器上进行训练，每个服务器都有自己的本地数据。他们与中央协调器进行通信，该中央协调器聚合各个模型更新并协调训练过程。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Bammens_Fig1.png" alt="联合机器学习概述" /><br /></article></aside></div><p></p><p> FedML 是一种分布式机器学习技术，可用于多种算法。例如，神经网络的权重或梯度可以以类似的方式在组织之间进行平均。协调器负责设置初始模型架构并协调训练过程，该过程通常需要多次迭代。因此，公司可以使用大量参数来训练复杂的机器学习模型，否则这些模型将超出他们的能力范围，因为本地数据的限制将导致模型准确性不佳。</p><p>重要的是，原始公司数据保持私密，并且在应用 FedML 时，只有统计数据（例如估计权重和其他参数）才会被共享和汇总。这样，10 家协作的小数据公司（每家都可以访问<em>x 个</em>数据点）可以通过其 AI/机器学习应用程序实现与一家可以访问 10 倍<em>x</em>数据点的大公司大致相似的预测能力，而不会损害数据隐私。</p><h3>制药行业的 FedML</h3><p>制药创新非常昂贵且耗时。截至 2022 年，将一种新药推向市场的<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/press-releases/deloittes-thirteenth-annual-pharmaceutical-innovation-report-pharma-r-and-d-return-on-investment-falls-in-post-pandemic-market.html">平均成本</a>约为 23 亿美元，而这个过程可能需要 10 多年的时间。药物发现的关键困难之一涉及极其大量的可能分子（数量级为 10 <sup>60</sup> ）以及在广阔的化学空间中寻找具有前景的分子的相关挑战。在如此高昂的成本和大量的分子可能性的背景下，高性能的预测机器学习模型是制药公司人工智能驱动的药物发现议程的基石。随着 Alphabet 等<a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/famga-big-tech-pharma/">大型科技</a>公司利用其在人工智能和机器学习方面深厚的专业知识冒险进入药物发现领域，制药公司也面临着压力。</p><p> Janssen Pharmaceutica 的科学总监 Hugo Ceulemans 认识到人们不愿共享药物发现数据，但也认识到协作人工智能在提高药物发现效率方面的巨大潜力，因此在 2016 年左右开始提出 FedML 想法并与同行展开讨论。最终，10 家制药公司在 2019 年成立了 Melloddy 联盟。Ceulemans 在一篇博文中指出，虽然制药公司之前已经汇集了数据来支持预测工作，但鉴于数据是一种数据，因此合作范围有限。昂贵的竞争性资产。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>他解释说，由于新的 FedML 联盟将允许基础数据贡献保持在各自数据所有者的控制之下而不是共享，因此可能会实现更雄心勃勃的范围。</p><p> Melloddy 是一个以<em>用于药物发现的机器学习账本编排命名</em>的术语，是一个为期三年的试点项目，旨在测试 FedML 的可行性和有效性。该项目由欧盟共同资助；欧盟委员会认为 Melloddy 是一个为制药以外的商业领域提供见解的测试案例。参与公司包括阿斯利康、拜耳、葛兰素史克、杨森制药、默克和诺华等。这些公司得到了技术和学术合作伙伴的支持，包括 Owkin（一家人工智能生物技术企业）和 KU Leuven（一所拥有人工智能驱动药物发现专业知识的大学）。</p><p>通过利用彼此的数据而不实际共享数据，参与的制药公司可以在世界上最大的药物发现数据集上训练他们的机器学习模型，从而能够更准确地预测有前途的分子并提高药物发现过程的效率。 Owkin 首席产品官 Mathieu Galtier 在一篇博客文章中解释说，由于 Mellody 使用联合学习，数据从未离开任何制药合作伙伴的基础设施。机器学习过程在每个参与的制药公司本地进行，并且仅共享模型。 “一项重要的研究工作致力于确保合作伙伴之间只共享统计信息，”他写道。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>于 2022 年结束的 Melloddy 试点项目的结果表明，使用去中心化数据创建用于协作人工智能的安全多方平台是可行的，并且通过使用 FedML 方法确实增强了机器学习模型的性能。</p><h3> FedML 联盟的战略考虑</h3><p>在建立 FedML 联盟时，参与规划过程的人员必须仔细考虑协调技术和激励合作伙伴的最佳方法。选定的协调器在有效管理 FedML 流程方面发挥着关键作用。小数据组织的领导者有时不愿意与大型科技公司合作，因为他们可以保持更大的战略控制，并与平等运营的小型科技合作伙伴建立更紧密的联系。一些人甚至担心大型科技公司自己会进入他们的领域，就像制药行业一样。</p><p>以 Mellody 为例，制药公司选择了初创公司 Owkin 来承担协调该联盟的 FedML 平台的责任。对于许多 FedML 计划来说，这可能是一个好方法，但考虑到初创公司的高失败率，它可能存在风险：如果初创公司失败，联盟可能会崩溃。还有一个潜在的风险是，初创公司可能会从未参加该联盟的竞争对手那里筹集资金；这是一个尴尬的情况，但并非不可能。因此，如果选择一家初创企业作为主要技术协调者，财团合作伙伴应该认真考虑投资企业风险资本（CVC）的选择。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>当合作伙伴在初创公司中拥有相当大的 CVC 联合股份并拥有优先购买权时，他们对科技初创公司的跑道长度及其未来发展轨迹拥有更强的控制力。</p><p></p><p> FedML 可能会引发激励问题，其中一些参与者无法使用所有相关的本地数据或忽视投资必要的数据基础设施以提高本地模型的准确性。他们可能选择不付出努力，而依赖其他联盟合作伙伴提供的数据贡献。这种搭便车行为会破坏善意参与者的积极性和参与性。为了解决这个问题，FedML 联盟可以在所提供数据的数量和覆盖范围方面就适当的合作伙伴承诺达成一致，并在合同协议中预先指定。协调器还可以监控本地模型更新对联合模型整体准确性的贡献，并且可以根据每个合作伙伴对联邦学习过程的贡献按比例支付 FedML 服务费。</p><p></p><p>在迈出组建 FedML 联盟的第一步时，确保合作伙伴的支持至关重要。因此，合作伙伴应参与确定联盟的目标，以换取他们的数据承诺。 AI Canvas 是一种决策工具，可用于识别和讨论机器学习用例和所需的训练数据。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>在与合作伙伴联系时，请记住，大多数 FedML 应用程序中的有效模型更新需要访问所有相关模型变量的本地数据。因此，通常会在同一行业内找到合适的合作伙伴，共享相似的业务流程和数据。与间接竞争对手（例如为其他地理市场提供服务的竞争对手）合作而不是与直接竞争对手合作可能有利于最大限度地减少潜在冲突。对于涉足 FedML 的小数据组织来说，建议从可实现的机器学习项目开始，以建立动力并在合作伙伴之间建立信任，然后再开始更雄心勃勃的项目。</p><p> FedML 仍然是一种年轻的人工智能方法，由一群 Google 工程师于 2016 年开发。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>但该领域的进展速度很快，我们可以预期其在一系列业务领域的采用将会激增。将 FedML 纳入其战略愿景的小数据组织具有前瞻性思维的领导者能够更好地利用人工智能的变革力量来塑造他们未来的成功。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/using-federated-machine-learning-to-overcome-the-ai-scale-disadvantage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>谁应该为演出定价？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jovana Karanovic, Elizabeth J. Altman, and Carmelo Cennamo. <p>Jovana Karanovic 是伊拉斯姆斯大学鹿特丹管理学院的助理教授，也是重塑工作基金会的创始人。伊丽莎白·J·奥尔特曼 (Elizabeth J. Altman) 是马萨诸塞州洛厄尔大学曼宁商学院管理学副教授； <cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》劳动力未来倡议的客座编辑；合著者<cite>《劳动力生态系统：与人员、合作伙伴和技术一起实现战略目标》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2023 年）。 Carmelo Cennamo 是哥本哈根商学院战略与创业学教授、数字市场竞争论坛主任、SDA 博科尼管理学院平台经济与监管监测副教授兼主任。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Platforms & Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Daniel Hertzberg/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted interviews with platform executives at four platform businesses — Malt, Ring Twice, Temper, and Wolt — that represent different industry sectors and price-setting models. They also conducted archival web-based research studying platform-based businesses in various regions of the world and evaluated their pricing models. They were provided with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Karanovic_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">丹尼尔·赫茨伯格/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者采访了四家平台企业（Malt、Ring Twice、Temper 和 Wolt）的平台高管，这些企业代表了不同的行业领域和定价模式。</li><li>他们还进行了基于网络的档案研究，研究世界各地基于平台的业务，并评估其定价模型。</li><li>他们获得并分析了来自服务平台的数据，该平台从平台控制的价格设置转变为允许服务提供商设定价格。这些数据是 Jovana Karanovic、Hakan Özalp、Carmelo Cennamo 和 Mark Boons 正在进行的研究项目的一部分。</li></ul></aside><p>经过一段疲惫的旅程抵达波士顿洛根国际机场后，米娅打开优步应用程序寻找回家的车。看到“您的 Uber 司机将在 3 分钟内到达”的消息后，她松了口气，但这种安慰并没有持续太久，因为司机取消了行程。在接下来的 30 分钟内，六名 Uber 司机接受了她的乘车请求，然后取消了，最后一名司机到达了。发生了什么事？</p><p>与许多平台公司一样，Uber 需要高效地匹配服务提供商（司机）和客户（乘客）。为此，它必须确保定价具有足够的竞争力，以便乘客选择服务并让司机有动力提供服务。米娅很难搭车，因为优步已经开始为司机提供更高的收入透明度，允许他们在接载乘客之前查看他们的预期报酬和路线目的地。一项旨在让司机受益的变化对乘客来说有一个重大的缺点：更多的司机开始取消他们认为无利可图的行程。</p><p></p><p>对于平台运营商来说，由谁制定价格以及交易中的其他各方有什么自由裁量权来改变价格以实现互利的结果的问题是复杂而微妙的。就优步而言，该平台设定了乘车价格，尽管司机可以在收入潜力不具吸引力的情况下选择退出，但司机和乘客都没有提出不同定价的灵活性。这是将控制权主要掌握在平台提供商手中的缺点之一。</p><p>虽然平台运营商通过算法确定价格在叫车和送餐服务中很常见，但其他类型的平台业务允许服务提供商或客户设定价格。 Fiverr 是一个在线市场，为高技能服务提供商与客户匹配编程或图形设计等任务，让自由职业者说出他们的费率。相比之下，荷兰酒店、零售和物流领域的轮班工作平台 Temper 让客户（例如餐馆和商店）决定零工的报酬。</p><p>正如 Uber 的例子所示，控制所有定价可能会给平台带来意想不到的后果，但允许其他利益相关者设定价格也可能有缺点。例如，比利时平台企业 Ring Twice 提供园艺和保姆等各种家庭服务，将定价控制权分配给客户。事实证明，客户知道他们想要什么，但不一定知道一项特定任务需要花费多少时间和精力。允许客户设定价格会导致匹配次数减少，因为许多客户提供的付款低于服务提供商愿意接受的价格。成功的工作匹配减少意味着平台的收入损失。</p><p>授予定价控制权是一项重大战略决策，最终决定价值的创造和获取，并建立平台本身、服务提供商和客户之间的权力动态。创建一个让所有三个利益相关者都认为定价模型可持续且有益的场景是平台领导者面临的主要挑战。为了帮助领导者做出这一决定，我们提供了一个框架来理解不同平台定价方法的关键权衡。除了经济考虑之外，我们强调管理者需要预测权力动态并采取混合方法来缓解它们。 （参见“零工平台的定价动态”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>零工平台的定价动态</h4><p class="caption">平台运营商必须了解将定价权交给不同利益相关者的关键权衡；通过混合方法分享这种力量往往是最可持续的选择。 </p><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%">谁控制定价</th><th style="width:25%">好处</th><th style="width:25%">风险</th><th style="line-height:1.5;width:25%">混合解决方案</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p><strong>平台</strong></p></td><td><p>基于捕获市场数据的算法定价可以最大限度地提高标准化服务的市场效率。</p></td><td><p>实时价格调整可能对提供商或客户不利。缺乏可预测性会损害信任。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>设定基本费率，使提供商能够上调价格或让客户提出报价。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>提供与生活工资相符的价格保证。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>供应商</strong></p></td><td><p>服务提供商的定价能力可以激励高质量的提供商加入。平台上更多的可变性满足了长尾需求。</p></td><td><p>定价过低会降低整个平台服务的感知价值。定价过高可能会赶走客户并限制平台的增长。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>允许客户和供应商之间进行价格和合同谈判。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>提供价格建议并与提供商分享市场数据。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p><strong>顾客</strong></p></td><td><p>客户可以控制自己的成本，这可能会增加客户对平台的参与度和感知价值。</p></td><td><p>提供太低的薪酬可能会赶走提供商，从而限制平台的增长。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>根据生活工资设定最低价格门槛。</p><p> <span class="blue">•</span>通过共享市场数据和/或提供价格建议来协助客户。 </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Karanovic_table-1.png" alt="零工平台的定价动态" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><h3>当平台发号施令时</h3><p>通过保留定价控制权，平台可以受益于众多优势，尤其是在某些细分市场。这种做法在叫车、食品配送和包裹递送领域很普遍，这些领域的服务相当标准化，数量很大，而且物流随着规模的扩大而迅速变得复杂。</p><p>通过保留控制权，平台可以优化效率，特别是当它们为大量具有类似需求的客户提供服务时。为了设定最佳价格，平台利用他们收集的大量交易数据。以最近被 DoorDash 收购的芬兰平台 Wolt 为例，该平台提供食品配送等服务。 Wolt 依赖于诸如快递员与餐厅的距离、食物准备时间以及与顾客的距离等参数。利用这些信息，它可以为快递员提供最佳路线建议，并提供相关的额外信息（例如，建筑物入口位置），以确保快速送货并节省时间。正如 Wolt 经理向我们解释的那样，该平台对效率的关注与快递员选择最佳路线的愿望是一致的，因此标准化配送流程和价格是有意义的。</p><p>控制价格还可以让平台根据市场情况快速调整，实现收入最大化：当需求高时，网约车和配送平台通常会实时提高价格。平台还可以尝试不同的定价策略。</p><p></p><p>最后，通过控制价格，平台提供商可以提供折扣和促销来吸引和留住客户。它可以选择根据客户行为、偏好和购买历史提供个性化定价。例如，亚马逊利用此类数据为某些商品设置动态定价。当客户在亚马逊上查看产品时，他们看到的价格可能与其他客户看到的同一产品的价格不同。这是因为亚马逊的定价算法会考虑客户的浏览和购买历史记录、他们的位置以及其他变量，以确定最大化购买可能性的个性化价格。</p><p>然而，平台保留定价控制权是需要权衡的，特别是当涉及到对利益相关者之间权力动态的影响时。特别是，如果平台定的价格太低，服务提供商可能会拒绝接受工作，或者如果价格定得太高，他们可能会难以吸引客户。在这两种情况下，服务提供商参与平台的动力都会减弱。一项研究检查了美国城市 Uber 司机论坛上的帖子，发现他们讨论了故意关闭自己的应用程序，让其显得不可用，以便让算法实施更高的高峰定价，旨在激励司机上路。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>司机本质上必须与系统进行博弈才能获得他们想要的价格，这反映出并加剧了供应商和平台之间缺乏信任。</p><p>平台控制的定价还与可能无法充分满足某些客户需求的标准化服务菜单密切相关。他们可以使用该平台寻找服务提供商，然后在平台外安排后续交互。最近的一项研究确实发现，提供商对平台规则和费用的不满，以及客户对更加个性化服务的渴望，是导致脱媒的主要因素之一。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>当客户和提供商对平台强加的规则不满意时，他们不太可能在平台上进行交易（收入降低），并且平台的声誉可能会在所有不满的利益相关者群体中受到损害。</p><p></p><h3>让服务提供商掌控一切</h3><p>服务提供商控制价格设定也有优势——这是 Upwork、Toptal 和 Malt 等自由职业市场的常见做法。授予这种自主权提供了一个具有竞争力和灵活的定价环境，这对于寻求特定功能以满足独特项目需求的客户来说特别有利。同样，提供者可以更有效地利用他们的技能或非凡才能货币化。</p><p>当提供商为项目设定价格时，他们可以考虑他们的成本、他们愿意付出的努力以及他们可以提供的服务质量——平台没有但需要这些信息才能设定适当的价格。定价还允许服务提供商行使创业自由，并根据无形因素（例如他们对特定项目的个人兴趣）调整价格。例如，欧洲咨询和软件开发服务平台 Malt 的一位经理表示，他们可能会以较低的价格获得一项有助于他们积累宝贵专业知识的任务。</p><p>当服务提供商能够设定自己的定价并提供差异化​​服务时，该平台就可以满足利基产品的长尾需求。 Helpling 是一个在德国、法国、瑞士、英国、爱尔兰、意大利和新加坡提供家庭清洁服务的平台，就是一个很好的例子。该平台最初有一个模型，在给定市场内，它为重复的清洁工作设定每小时的标准价格。 （一次性工作略高的价格也在市场内标准化。）然而，几年后，Helpling 改变了做法，让供应商自行设定价格。我们的研究表明，随着供应商愿意以更高的费用从事不同类型的工作（例如派对后的清理工作），某些工作的价格随后上涨。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>平台的政策变化显然暴露了附加服务需求未得到满足。</p><p>允许服务提供商设定价格还可以改善服务质量更可能因提供商而异的类别的客户体验。类似服务的不同质量水平可能会产生不确定性并降低满意度。质量较低通常是由于当客户支付平台业务设定的标准价格时，提供商缺乏动力付出所需的努力。如果提供商能够自行设定反映其真实价值的价格，他们就可以通过付出更大的努力获得回报并提供更高的客户满意度。</p><p></p><p>这种方法确实有缺点。当平台运营商放弃定价控制而供应商收费过高时，可能会降低整体匹配和交易量；如果提供商收费过低，就可能会浪费金钱。在 Malt，服务提供商可以完全控制价格设定，尽管他们对执行任务所需的条件和专业水平有深入的了解，但他们往往会低估自己的价格。但这可能会形成恶性循环，我们采访的麦芽经理表示：被低成本供应商吸引的客户可能缺乏洞察力。如果客户无法区分平台上列出的高质量和低质量的提供商，那么低价可能会越来越多地吸引寻求更基本、更低质量服务的客户。这会赶走高质量的提供商，并可能降低平台的品牌资产和声誉。它还可能导致一场逐底竞争，提供商不断降低价格以相互竞争，从而降低平台的利润和提供商的收入（以及他们留在平台上的意愿）。</p><p>对于客户来说，提供商的定价会带来其他动力。选择专注于利润丰厚的利基市场的提供商可能会导致一些需求得不到满足。提供商设定的定价的更大可变性使得客户更难公平地比较价格并找到物有所值的产品。如果选择服务提供商变得过于耗时，客户可能会完全放弃该平台。</p><h3>客户说出他们的价格</h3><p>荷兰轮班工作平台 Temper 允许客户决定他们愿意支付的费用，并将咖啡师等熟练工人与餐厅等场所相匹配。当客户是对所需服务和愿意支付的金额有明确要求的企业时，这种方法最合适。</p><p>在这种模式下，客户可以设定反映其预算和所需服务水平的价格，而服务提供商可以根据自己的定价政策和成本结构选择接受或拒绝报价。在 Temper，寻找轮班工人的餐厅有不同的成本结构——例如，位于市中心的餐厅支付更高的租金。它们还因服务质量而异（例如，精致餐饮与快餐休闲），这会影响他们所需的技能资料，从而影响他们为吸引工人而提供的薪酬。客户可以控制成本，但也可以灵活地适应竞争环境，例如，为周末轮班提供更高的报酬。该平台公开了其他企业为相同服务提供的现行费率，这也可以为定价决策提供信息。</p><p>最后，如果客户对定价流程有更大的控制权，他们可能会更有动力使用平台。如果他们有权决定他们对服务的价值，他们可能会感到更满意并在交易中投入。对平台的更多控制可能会加深主人翁意识并提高参与度和忠诚度。</p><p>当然，客户设定的定价需要权衡，这可能会影响平台运营商和提供商。如果客户将价格定得太低，服务提供商可能不愿意接受这项任务，或者他们可能会为了保持盈利而走捷径。这反过来可能导致产品或服务整体质量下降，从而降低平台的吸引力和增长潜力。同样，客户可能无法获得有关市场动态、成本和竞争格局的完整信息，从而导致提供商和客户的结果都不是最佳的。</p><h3>通过混合方法取得平衡</h3><p>无论定价是由平台、服务提供商还是客户控制，在适当的情况下，每种选择都有可能最大化价值创造和效率。尽管如此，平台不同利益相关者之间展开的动态可能会超过其中一些好处，并导致意想不到的后果。为了确保长期可持续性并提高平台业务的财务绩效，平台管理者可能希望分享一些定价控制权。</p><p>平台提供商可以考虑混合方法来做到这一点。例如，TaskRabbit 根据复杂性、持续时间和市场价格等因素为不同类型的任务设定标准价格。这些标准价格最初由平台确定，旨在为客户和零工提供一致性和指导。不过，TaskRabbit也允许服务提供商根据自己的喜好和情况调整价格，设定的价格可以高于或低于平台的标准价格。欧盟提出了一项平台工作指令，认为设定自己费率的权利是自由职业者和雇员之间的区别因素；如果被采用，它可能会推动目前决定价格的乘车和食品配送平台与提供商分享这种控制权。</p><p>控制定价的平台可以通过向服务提供商公开价格的确定方式以及他们是否可以采取任何措施来增加收入来缓解权力失衡。他们还应该为听证提供者的担忧提供一种机制，并使他们能够对影响他们在平台上收入的算法决定的决定提出上诉。</p><p>虽然在某些情况下允许服务提供商设定价格是有意义的，但这并不总是能为他们或平台带来最佳定价。例如，与新提供商相比，已建立高评级并显示大量已完成任务的提供商可能拥有更大的定价能力。这对平台来说并不有利，因为如果新的服务提供商需要很长时间才能获得工作，那么他们很快就会脱离，从而限制平台的增长。 Malt 通过提高新提供商在搜索结果中的可见性来解决这种差异。</p><p>平台还可以协助提供商制定价格，特别是对于容易出现需求波动的产品。 Airbnb 的一项研究发现，只有专业的房东（拥有多个房产的人）才会熟练地定价；大多数其他人设定的价格并不理想。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Airbnb 引入了价格建议，提醒房东注意活动和需求旺盛的时间段，并促使他们提高价格。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>此外，它还允许主机选择自动价格调整，这实际上将定价权带回平台，即使在这种服务提供商控制的模式中也是如此。</p><p>正如我们所看到的，当客户设定价格时，他们可能会向服务提供商提供低价报价，尤其是在不利的市场条件下。平台可以通过设置最低价格阈值来防止对服务提供商的剥削，例如与最低工资或生活工资相对应的价格阈值。例如，Temper 为每个服务类别设定了与最低工资相符的最低价格阈值，尽管荷兰法律并未要求这样做。此外，它还允许提供商进行谈判。该公司的一位联合创始人告诉我们，到 2022 年，Temper 上所有交易的 10% 是与客户设定的初始价格相比上涨的。平台的此类主动举措可能会导致旨在限制其权力的监管不断增加。纽约市已经对 Uber 和 Lyft 司机规定了最低工资，最近还宣布对食品配送应用程序的工人实行同样的规定。欧盟更进一步：如果某些标准不适用，例如工人有权根据自己的需要调整平台确定的费率，其拟议指令将假定零工工人是平台的雇员。换句话说，如果一个平台设定了薪酬上限，那么它就可能被视为雇主。</p><p></p><p>正如我们所指出的，客户可能并不总是完全了解情况，或者他们可能有非常具体的偏好，在这种情况下，平台可以帮助他们选择提供商。例如，在自由职业市场 Upwork 上，客户发布他们需要完成的所需任务，例如“徽标设计”或“报告撰写”，并详细描述他们正在寻找的内容以及他们愿意支付的价格。当客户有特定偏好并且需要特定类型的服务提供者时，这种定价模式很有效。然而，Upwork 最终意识到，并非所有客户都有明确的偏好；有些人只是想要完成服务，并且宁愿从产品菜单中选择它。这导致了 Upwork 项目目录的推出，该网站提供客户可以浏览和选择的预定义项目，例如“24 小时内撰写 500 字的 SEO 优化博客文章”，价格为 50 美元。供应商不会向客户详细介绍工作，而是发布他们可以以固定价格提供的服务。这使得客户可以更轻松地找到满足其需求的合适提供商，并为提供商提供更多赢得工作的机会。</p><p></p><p>平台控制其市场以实现回报最大化的需求不会消失，但其采取的方法将决定其长期可持续性。平台领导者必须认识到，平台不是一个单边的、分级管理的实体，而是一个经济和社会关系的网络。为了成功管理并确保各方满意，他们必须与其他利益相关者共享某些方面的控制权，允许妥协，并在需要时介入支持其员工。当平台关系中的各方更公平地分享控制权时，平台模式就能更惠及各方。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/who-should-price-a-gig/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>重新思考数字创新的治理</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David L. Rogers. <p>David L. Rogers 是哥伦比亚商学院数字业务战略和领先数字化转型高管教育项目的教务主任。他是<cite>《数字化转型路线图：重建组织以实现持续变革》</cite> （哥伦比亚商学院出版社，2023 年）（本文改编自该书）以及畅销书<cite>《数字化转型手册》</cite> （2016 年）的作者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Digital Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Process]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Transformation]]></category><description><![CDATA[Patrick George When global chemical company BASF launched its Onono lab in São Paulo, Brazil, its mission was to accelerate innovation through rapid collaboration with local partners and startups. But Onono’s director, Antonio Lacerda, faced an immediate hurdle from corporate governance: He was told that his lab would have to follow the same corporate data [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Rogers_1290x860.png" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">帕特里克·乔治</p></figcaption></figure><p>当全球化学公司巴斯夫在巴西圣保罗设立 Onono 实验室时，其使命是通过与当地合作伙伴和初创公司的快速合作来加速创新。但 Onono 的主管 Antonio Lacerda 面临着来自公司治理的直接障碍：他被告知，他的实验室必须遵循用于保护巴斯夫整个云基础设施的相同公司数据政策，这将使其无法快速灵活地与其他公司合作新的初创公司。 Lacerda 推迟了发布，直到他能够凭借重要的政治资本安排一个例外：为他的团队提供一个包含单独数据的“沙箱”，并获得通过 API 与新合作伙伴共享这些数据的特别许可。</p><p> Lacerda 以及许多创新冠军的经验指出了数字化转型的一个基本问题：在大公司中，创新团队在面对与他们自己的变革使命相矛盾的业务规则时只能争取豁免。但只要依赖于高层领导批准的临时例外，创新就永远不会大规模发生。相反，我们必须重新思考我们的治理方法，并设计新的管理实践，以数字化的速度进行创新。</p><p></p><p>设计可重复的创新流程对于数字时代的增长至关重要，但它却非常困难。在太多的组织中，新企业都是在单一执行发起人的基础上获得批准的。一旦启动，企业就会进展缓慢，由传统孤岛中的团队管理。资源分配也很缓慢，因为有前途的项目要等待数周或数月才能获得下一轮批准。因为每个项目都得到了一位有影响力的高管的支持，所以没有人愿意关闭它，即使它没有什么希望。</p><p>与此同时，风险规避导致企业只为他们容易实现的目标提供资金——对核心进行渐进式改进，从而带来有保证的、快速的投资回报率。这条路永远不会导致转变。相反，您需要接受不确定性并支持核心内部和外部增长的治理。 （参见“治理如何帮助或阻碍创新。”）</p><div class="callout-highlight callout"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>治理如何帮助或阻碍创新</h4><p class="caption"><table id="Chart#" class="chart-grouped-rows no-mobile"><thead><tr><th style="width:50%">治理<em>不善</em>的迹象</th><th style="width:50%"><em>良好</em>治理的迹象</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><p><span class="blue">•</span>任何新的创新都必须由高层管理人员亲自批准。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>既定的结构为创新提供资源和治理。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>新企业进展缓慢，由职能部门中的传统团队领导。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>新企业在高度独立的多功能团队的领导下行动迅速。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>年度预算周期减缓了向新企业分配资源的速度。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>通过迭代融资快速实现资源分配。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>创新仅限于少数大项目，一旦启动就很难停止。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>通过智能关闭来管理稳定的创新渠道，以释放资源。</p></td></tr><tr><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>唯一获得支持的企业是核心业务中的低风险创新。</p></td><td><p> <span class="blue">•</span>治理支持具有低不确定性和高不确定性的企业，无论是在核心还是在其他领域。 </p></td></tr></tbody></table><p><!--IMAGE FALLBACK FOR MOBILE BELOW --><br /><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MAG_Rogers_table-1.png" alt="治理如何帮助或阻碍创新" class="no-desktop"></p></article></aside></div><p>数字化转型要求精心设计治理以解决几个问题。一是<em>监督</em>。谁批准新项目？他们向谁汇报？谁关闭它们？接下来是<em>资金</em>。您将如何在企业投资组合中分配资源，以最大限度地提高成功机会？同样重要的是<em>人</em>。谁将为新企业配备员工，无论是在组织内部还是外部？如何组建具有正确技能组合的团队？治理还必须包括<em>指标</em>。您将如何衡量新企业的进展？而且，至关重要的是，如何对定期<em>关闭</em>企业进行纪律约束，这种做法在大型企业中经常被忽视？</p><p>在本文中，我们将讨论如何设计治理模型来推动任何企业的数字创新，重点关注两个关键工作组：参与建立新企业的人员以及监督和评估其工作的人员。我们将深入研究管理大规模增长的首要治理问题，包括风险投资团队和监事会如何合作。我们将探索如何管理正在进行的决策，为新企业开绿灯，为值得的企业提供额外资金，并关闭其他企业以释放资源。</p><h3>设计团队推动创新</h3><p>几十年的经验告诉我们，在老牌企业和小型初创企业中，有意义的新增长总是从一个地方开始：小团队，有效授权。这些团队进行快速、迭代的实验，这是每一种现代创新方法的核心——无论是敏捷、设计思维、精益创业还是产品管理。每个创新团队的工作都是接受拟议的新企业并快速测试其商业模式的各个方面，以验证哪些内容在市场上行得通，哪些行不通。</p><p>在任何成熟的企业中，管理创新团队的规则对于他们的成功至关重要。许多读者都会熟悉小型多功能团队的想法。但规模和组成只是团队成功重要因素的一部分。通过研究亚马逊和谷歌等数字原生代以及沃尔玛和万事达卡等数字化转型者的创新，我确定了团队治理的五个基本支柱。伟大的创新团队是：</p><p><strong>小的。</strong>研究表明，小团队的沟通、协调和决策速度比大团队快得多。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>小团队是敏捷方法的基础，敏捷方法使用快速的短冲刺节奏，每个团队都必须交付新的工作代码、测试和学习，并调整优先级。在亚马逊，创新团队被称为“双披萨团队”，因为每个团队都应该足够小，可以容纳两个披萨（最多八个人）。</p><p><strong>多功能的。</strong>优秀的创新团队拥有多元化的成员，他们跨越职能部门（例如营销、工程和设计）。每个团队的目标是拥有能够提供完成工作所需的所有基本技能的成员。多功能团队能够完全自行推进，而不是在项目中采取下一步之前不断等待另一个部门的输入。</p><p><strong>单线程。</strong>最好的创新团队的所有成员都全职致力于团队的工作。至少，创新团队的领导者必须是单线程的，这意味着他们不能将每周的工作时间分配给团队的新项目和其他项目。领导团队是他们的全部责任。</p><p><strong>自主性。</strong>成功的创新团队拥有明确的决策权，使他们有权在自己的指导下工作。他们的工作不需要获得团队之外任何人的批准——无论是产品设计、接下来要运行哪些测试，还是要追求哪些客户。自治还意味着不禁止从公司外部承包资源。</p><p><strong>负责。</strong>只有当团队也明确对其工作结果负责时，自治才有可能实现。在这里，良好的治理需要对成功有一个明确的定义，这是根据结果而不是可交付成果来定义的。该定义可能包括定量指标和定性原则，并且在团队工作开始之前必须与领导层达成一致。有效的问责制还需要透明度：在任何时候，团队的结果必须对团队内部或外部的任何人可见。每次测试运行、构建的每个 MVP 以及跟踪的每个指标都应该对公司中的任何人可见。</p><h3>与增长委员会建立监督</h3><p>创新团队最重要的合作伙伴是负责分配资金并监督和支持其工作的管理者。根据我的经验，支持企业创新最成功的模式是董事会。在董事会模式中，一个小组定期召开会议并审议，以决定是否赞助各种可能的创新企业——就像一群风险投资人听取初创公司的推介一样。一个创新委员会将赞助和支持多个并行工作的团队。</p><p>这种方法与我发现的非常常见的方法形成鲜明对比：新企业由单一发起人批准的组织。在这些公司中，一名或多名高管可能会利用他们在组织内的影响力来赞助他们认为具有战略重要性和前景的新数字企业。这种模型本质上是临时的，决策基于不同个人的直觉和判断。一旦赞助商将自己的名字和声誉投入到一个项目中，他们就很难让它消亡，无论市场验证其前景如何。相比之下，董事会模式——具有更大的多样性和决策的公正性——本质上更适合大规模管理创新。</p><p>有效的企业创新委员会（也称为增长委员会、风险投资委员会或增长委员会）的人数不应超过八人。他们应该包括具有主题专业知识和市场知识的成员。董事会应该能够挑战公司的正统观念，倡导长远观点，并引入行业外的想法。最好的董事会由来自不同部门的内部利益相关者和至少一名具有外部视角的成员组成。成员的级别应该足够高，以便在组织中拥有真正的影响力，但级别又不能高到无法将董事会工作作为优先事项。</p><p>董事会的职责是定期开会批准新企业，为团队提供战略指导，决定每个阶段的额外资金，并就何时关闭企业做出严格的决定。在这里，决策权再次至关重要。创新委员会必须对其投资组合中的每个团队拥有完整的资助权。其决策应通过与团队的公开而活跃的辩论来制定，但决策权仍由董事会决定。其他高级管理人员，包括首席执行官，可以为企业提供建议和意见，但他们不能对董事会的投资决策进行投票或否决。</p><p></p><h3>为新项目开绿灯</h3><p>董事会和团队必须合作的第一个流程是开绿灯，即批准新企业开始工作。当董事会批准一家新企业时，它应该为团队分配足够的资源（以时间、金钱和人员的形式）进行第一轮测试，以验证有关商业模式的最初问题。有效批准的关键是<em>最大限度地减少</em>每个团队的初始投资，并<em>最大限度地增加</em>批准测试的想法数量。</p><p>这种方法可能看起来有悖常理——它肯定与许多创新治理不善的组织中试图“选择赢家并下大赌注”的倾向形成鲜明对比。事实上，对于董事会来说，重要的是要克制住试图从提交的想法中挑选最佳想法的冲动。首先，董事会确实无法知道哪些想法可行。这些知识只能通过测试和验证来获得。其次，成功的企业往往源于最初有缺陷但随着测试、反馈和迭代设计而不断发展的想法。我建议董事会不要试图评估成功的可能性，而是根据问题定义、战略契合度和团队思维来判断新企业的推介。</p><p></p><p>为了批准许多创新想法，必须建立快速、廉价且有效的验证流程。这意味着引入客户的声音来快速测试该企业是否专注于解决真正的问题。在花旗银行，新企业通常以为期两天或三天的研讨会开始，员工在其中探索问题/机会陈述，并有机会与实际客户一起快速、迭代地开发自己的创新理念。随着您提高第一阶段验证的速度并降低成本，您的企业就有能力批准更多的风险团队来测试和追求更多可能的增长想法。</p><h3>通过迭代资金管理资源</h3><p>管理创新的下一个关键流程是迭代融资，这是董事会在企业获得批准后向团队分配资源的方式。基于风险投资初创企业融资方法，迭代融资被设计得极其敏捷。在每次董事会审查（通常每 30、60 或 90 天）中，董事会将审查每个团队的进度，包括市场测试的新数据，并决定是否向该团队释放下一批资源。</p><p>迭代融资与大型企业的传统预算流程截然不同。这就是为什么它是管理新创新投资的更好方法：</p><p><strong>更快地开始。</strong>在传统的预算流程中，新项目将获得一大笔初始资金，以反映对该项目的承诺。但这只有在经过长时间的分析之后才会发生，分析努力通过基准和第三方数据（误导性地）评估不确定的新企业的机会。相比之下，迭代融资为企业提供了较小的初始预算，但如果团队正在寻求的机会明确且具有战略相关性，则可以让团队快速启动。</p><p><strong>融资周期更短，更加敏捷。</strong>公司预算通常每年制定一次，项目和部门的资金通过一个需要数月的复杂过程来提供。一家有前途的新企业可能需要等待一年多的时间才能获得进行为期四个星期的测试的资源。相比之下，当董事会频繁开会并且融资轮次只为团队提供一到三个月的资源时，决策就会更加灵活。</p><p><strong>根据真实世界的数据进行投资。</strong>许多领导者会向未经测试的新企业过度投入资金，因为他们个人相信该策略是正确的，或者因为他们被团队的说服力所左右。通过迭代融资流程，董事会完全根据真实数据来决定每轮资源。每次开会时，董事会和团队都必须就团队需要在下一次审查会议上提供哪些数据达成一致。这些指标（通常是三到六个关键变量）将随着时间的推移而发生变化，具体取决于新企业仍然面临的最大不确定性来源。它们记录了风险投资团队迄今为止所学到的知识以及下一步需要学习的知识。</p><p><strong>快速扩展以推动指数级增长。</strong>在传统预算中，当资金更新时，任何增加都只是之前预算的增量。通过迭代融资，如果验证成功且风险投资取得进展，则每轮投资的规模应呈指数级增长。人力资源配置也应增加。这意味着发现有意义的增长机会的创新团队可以快速扩展，从而对公司的利润产生可衡量的影响。</p><p>显然，迭代融资要求董事会准备好快速增加对在市场上证明自己的企业的投资。这意味着企业必须提前为一组资源提供资金，以便董事会在一年内跨项目组合进行分配。</p><p>在每个投资组合中，类似的创新（例如，单个业务部门内的高风险创新组合）应该争夺资金。不要让苹果与橙子竞争。首先为特定类别的创新投资组合提供资金，然后让董事会迭代地为各种企业提供资金。</p><h3>养成智能关机的习惯</h3><p>当然，并非每个团队审查都会以继续资助的决定结束。困扰企业创新的经典问题之一是，企业学会如何启动新项目，而不是如何阻止它们。为了让创新取得成果，公司必须准备好退出那些被证明不成功或与战略不够一致的项目。</p><p>系统地、定期地关闭企业是成长委员会的一项关键工作。每次董事会开会进行迭代融资审查时，问题必须是：“我们是进一步资助该企业还是将其关闭？”</p><p></p><p>在传统公司，关闭创新项目的最大障碍往往是不愿承认失败，以及一种非理性的感觉，即任何类型的失败都会带来太大的风险。但如果通过迭代融资提前关闭，失败的成本是最小的。相比之下，如果你的团队不快速、明智地关闭企业，公司就会付出非常实际的成本。如果没有这种纪律，您的创新将缺乏重点，您的资源将分散得太薄，并且您将耗尽新实验的带宽。你将被<em>僵尸项目</em>困住——不成功的企业永远不会关闭并继续吸走资源。在强生公司，通过评估现有投资组合并关闭不再符合公司更新战略的项目来资助一系列全新的创新。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p>只有当你将其作为例行决定时，停止项目才会变得更容易，而定期进行资金审查的创新委员会将产生巨大的影响。在通用电气的石油和天然气部门，在董事会成立之前很少有项目被关闭。董事会一开始，就在第一个 90 天的周期内轻松关闭了 20% 的现有项目。随着董事会和团队开始专注于战略调整，50% 的新企业在 60 天内关闭。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>媒体巨头 Schibsted 的目标是，每当在开发渠道中添加新内容时，就会取消一项风险投资。当一个项目需要审查时，为自己设定一个高标准，问：“我们为什么不应该关闭这个项目？”</p><p>以下五种做法对于在任何组织中实现智能关闭至关重要：</p><p><strong>规划一条具有存活率的管道。</strong>大规模创新需要规划关闭大多数新企业。在与真正的客户接触后，只有三分之一到一半的明亮、闪亮的新想法能够通过第一次融资审查。存活率通常会在随后的回合中增加。了解您在不同验证阶段的存活率将使您能够规划未来的管道。例如，如果董事会预计在一年内帮助将三到四家新企业推向市场，那么它需要在一开始就播下足够的种子，以获得成功的良好机会。</p><p><strong>使用风险积压来快速重新分配。</strong>创新委员会应该保留一份已批准但尚未开始的企业创意的排名列表。在审核过程中使用此待办事项将使关闭变得更加容易。重点不再是简单地扼杀一个失败的想法，而是释放团队及其资源，从积压的工作中开发更有前途的想法。因此，当您关闭一个项目时，请快速将成员重新分配给下一个最佳想法。在许多情况下，这可能只是意味着让团队重新关注同一问题的不同解决方案。</p><p><strong>从停工中提取价值。</strong>当您决定关闭一个项目时，请寻求尽可能多的价值。在某些情况下，公司可以将合资企业出售给另一家企业。当沃尔玛的 Vudu 流媒体视频服务不再具有强大的战略优势时，沃尔玛将其剥离给媒体巨头康卡斯特。有时，一项事业很有前途，但尚未可行；通过缩减投资，您可以维持未来的选择。在谷歌眼镜作为消费产品失败后，该公司将项目缩减为专注于工厂车间应用程序的企业专用设备。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>有时，只有完全关闭才有意义，而要提取的关键价值是从实验中获得的经验教训。当亚马逊关闭其亚马逊拍卖和 zShops 服务时，它吸取了教训，为随后推出的亚马逊商城取得了巨大成功。</p><p><strong>广泛分享学习成果。</strong>分享你从失败的企业中学到的东西是最难遵循的原则之一。大多数公司更愿意放弃那些没有成功的项目。在 2014 年关于其早期数字化转型工作的内部报告中，《纽约时报》承认：“当我们关闭项目时，决策都是悄悄做出的，很少进行讨论，以保护项目运行人员的声誉。结果，教训被遗忘，相关员工变得更加厌恶风险。” <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>克服这种不情愿对于纽约时报公司及其商业模式的最终转变至关重要。国际汽车联合会 (FIA) 的德国分支机构运营着一个创新实验室，一年内 10 个项目中有 8 个被取消。它最大的胜利是什么？与世界各地在自己的市场上面临同样挑战的其他国际汽联附属机构分享这些结果。</p><p><strong>将人与项目区分开来。</strong>这是建立接受创新失败并从中学习的文化的最后一个关键部分。强有力的董事会审查流程将使团队对其结果负责。但你应该小心，不要将失败的项目与参与该项目的个人的优点联系起来。这些团队成员可以在下一个项目中为您取得巨大的成功。一定要鼓励您的创新者继续研究他们的下一个想法。</p><p>如果你的停工流程确实有效，你就会开始看到志愿服务。当团队真正专注于通过实验验证增长机会时，他们通常会向董事会建议自己关闭，并报告说：“这就是我们所了解到的情况以及我们建议现在关闭的原因。”当这些员工很快带着另一个创业想法回到董事会时，请不要感到惊讶。这可能是你的下一个重大突破。</p><p></p><p></p><p>为了让数字化转型为任何组织带来真正的增长和价值，它必须不仅仅涉及在不合适的管理下挣扎的团队的孤立创新。如果没有新的治理模式来管理新企业，数字创新的潜力将永远达不到。</p><p>创新治理需要三个关键组成部分：（1）必须授权团队快速行动并进行实验，以发现市场上有效的方法； (2) 董事会必须有权监督团队组合并为其提供建议，在最需要的地方分配资源； (3) 两者都必须遵循为新企业开绿灯的常规流程，迭代地为其提供资金，并关闭它们，为下一个新兴机会腾出资源。</p><p>有了正确的治理，各种类型的老牌公司都可以释放员工的潜力，推动业务各个层面的转型和增长。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/rethinking-governance-for-digital-innovation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> AI 的图像和灵感：Pinterest 的 Jeremy King</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Platforms]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jeremy King leads a team of 1,400 passionate engineers working on the continuous improvement of Pinterest’s image-driven platform. With a background that includes heading up a translation team at eBay and overseeing the technology behind Walmart’s U.S. retail stores and e-commerce business, Jeremy is now responsible for technology operations at Pinterest. To support the company’s [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Jeremy King 领导着一支由 1,400 名充满热情的工程师组成的团队，致力于不断改进 Pinterest 的图像驱动平台。杰里米 (Jeremy) 的背景包括领导 eBay 的翻译团队以及监督沃尔玛美国零售店和电子商务业务背后的技术，现在负责 Pinterest 的技术运营。为了支持公司的使命，激励人们“创造他们热爱的生活”，他和他的团队依靠先进的人工智能、机器学习和图形数据库来索引和构建图像网络，以便用户能够找到灵感——特别是当他们不完全确定自己在寻找什么时。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和 AI</cite> ”播客中，Jeremy 与主持人 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 一起谈论 Pinterest 在图像识别领域取得的一些最新进展，并分享了他对生成式 AI 将如何改变基于图像的内容的看法就像 Pinterest 的一样。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MMAI-S7-E6-King-Pinterest-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="杰里米·金"></p><h4>杰里米·金，Pinterest</h4><p> Jeremy King 是 Pinterest 的技术高级副总裁，负责领导公司的技术愿景和工程组织，负责构建和扩展视觉发现引擎。</p><p>在加入 Pinterest 之前，他曾担任沃尔玛的首席技术官兼高级副总裁，领导团队负责沃尔玛和 Jet 的美国零售商店和电子商务背后的技术，并监督跨云和数据的客户、商家和供应链技术平台。 King 还曾在 Walmart Labs、LiveOps 和 eBay 担任过高管级技术职务。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-hardoon"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>基于人工智能的平台如何使用生成式人工智能来吸引用户？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我是来自 Pinterest 的 Jeremy King，您正在听的是<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天我们的嘉宾是 Pinterest 工程主管杰里米·金 (Jeremy King)。杰里米，感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>很高兴来到这里。非常感谢。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>从概述开始总是好的；也许可以告诉我们一些有关 Pinterest 的业务以及您在 Pinterest 的工作的信息。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我们想说，Pinterest 是互联网上寻找灵感的目的地。每天都有数以亿计的人来找我们，询问他们想穿什么、今天下午想做什么、晚餐想做什么、或者如何装饰孩子的蛋糕或改造他们的厨房。因此，我们希望建立一个平台，让任何人都可以创造自己热爱的生活。</p><p>这是一个履行此类使命的好地方，当我告诉很多人我在哪里工作时，他们会对他们自己的 Pinterest 版块和世界上正在发生的事情感到非常高兴。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>太好了。告诉我们更多有关在 Pinterest 工作的信息。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我现在在 Pinterest 担任工程主管已经四年多了。就像任何领导者一样，我正在努力弄清楚如何解除我的团队的阻碍并雇用优秀的人才。我一直告诉人们，当我来到 Pinterest 时，我对人才水平印象深刻。这是一个相对较小的团队。我们在全球拥有 4,500 名员工和约 1,400 名工程师。因此，与世界上一些最大的公司竞争，这个团队必须具有极高的素质。我们拥有一些世界上最优秀的图数据库人才；我们拥有世界上最好的计算机视觉人才。和这些人一起工作真的很有趣。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>到目前为止，这些都没有提到人工智能，那么人工智能在这 1,400 名工程师中扮演什么角色呢？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>是的，这是一个很好的观点。 Pinterest 和现在许多其他公司的事实之一是，Pinterest 实际上是从机器学习和人工智能的基础上诞生的。没有它，它就不存在。因此，将 AI 和 ML 与 Pinterest 分开讨论几乎是用词不当。没有它，这一切都不会发生。我们所做的几乎所有事情都涉及我们的机器学习系统。我们每秒都会进行数百万次推理。每个请求都会返回图表，并向每个人发布一个非常具体的用例。</p><p>它没有被缓存。 ……每个人都有特定的结果。我提到我们大约有 1,400 名工程师。我们大约有 350 名机器学习工程师。作为一个百分比，当我告诉其他 CTO 时……他们会说，“与我的公司相比，机器学习人员的比例非常高。”在数据平台方面也是如此。我们有一位出色的领导者，戴夫·伯吉斯（Dave Burgess），他负责运营我们的数据平台。您可以想象我们的数据平台与我们能力的任何其他部分一样重要。所以我提到了图表，但它也是一种普通的 SQL 数据库和保持这个东西运行的实时系统。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>杰里米，你多次提到“图表”。什么是图表？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>从本质上讲，图表是什么，如果你采用一个实体、一个对象，然后你说，“什么与该对象相关？” - 所以，在这种情况下，我们使用最近邻图，我们在上面写了很多文档，也就是说，“嘿，在这种情况下，我有一个图像，并且我有另一个与这个图片。”这让我能够构建这种图像网络。图表在 Pinterest 上工作的原因是因为每个引脚本质上都被添加到板上，这本质上使其成为图表中的一个节点，因此它会继续增加图表。</p><p>因此，它允许您……与 SQL 数据库或关系数据库不同，您必须对标签索引和索引进行排序，而图表可以被索引。本质上任何图像都可以索引到任何其他图像。它允许您非常有效地搜索相关的事物。这就是 Pinterest 的力量。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Jeremy，你提到人工智能一直是 Pinterest 旅程的重要组成部分，并且从 Pinterest 成立之初就已经在 Pinterest 的技术堆栈中根深蒂固，所以对于你们来说，生成式人工智能一定也无处不在，我相信现在每个人都在想这个问题。所以也许可以告诉我们一些你在那里做什么的情况。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我们拥有最先进的机器学习环境，可以将所有表面上的这些数据集互连起来。我们将其称为“主页”、搜索系统、推动 Pinterest 个性化、推荐和参与的相关事物。 [并且]我们的月度活跃用户增长速度非常快。 …… Z 世代的增长速度甚至是最快的。我们每月增加了 1300 万活跃用户，因此我们真正关注的是如何提高参与度。</p><p>毫不奇怪，机器学习的许多改进，即使是在过去两年，也一直在推动这种参与。当然，我们已经构建了新功能，使 Pinterest 变得更容易购物。但是，当我们看到机器学习模型的能力有效地增强了 10 倍或 100 倍（这在今天相对常见）时，我们发现随着结果变得更加具体，我们的结果也会大幅增加。</p><p>坦率地说，Pinterest 还关注[大量]不同的事物。所以并不是每一个项目都是关于“你今晚晚餐想做什么？”这也是“我知道你上周在看生日蛋糕”或“新年即将到来”，我们将其中一些相互影响。因此，我们一直在利用一些近几年才出现的先进人工智能功能。这包括 GPU [图形处理单元] 工作以及所有使这些事情变得经济高效的事情。</p><p>因此，回到你关于生成式人工智能的问题，毫不奇怪，考虑到我们是一个图像平台，生成式人工智能对我们来说非常有趣，我通常将其分为三个部分。当我们考虑大型语言模型（法学硕士）时，我们会讨论，第一，如何提高我的团队的工作效率？我们有几个飞行员正在运行。我们还没有确切决定走哪条路，但它看起来确实很有前途，并且像许多其他 CTO 一样，我们对此感到非常兴奋。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这很有趣。告诉我们生成式人工智能如何提高效率。</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我与一些 CTO 交谈过，我认为非常有趣的一件事是，这位特定的 CTO 说，一般来说，它提高了 10% 到 15% 的生产力，但有一小部分用户的工作效率提高了 50%。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>太棒了。我只是想说，感觉就像，如果你回到十年前，有很多图像和非结构化文本以及诸如此类的东西，让人工智能训练这些数据并理解它，人类干预需要这样做，既可以标记内容，也可以确保输出有意义。现在感觉，随着人工智能时代的到来，许多类似人类的判断将越来越多地通过人工智能时代做出，特别是对于大量非结构化文本、图像、视频和此类内容。是这样吗，还是我太过分了？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>我认为这是对的。我的意思是，Pinterest 的系统是建立在嵌入的基础上的，所以你拍摄一张图像或一段文本，然后基本上给它贴上标签——本质上，就你的观点而言，这就是 Pinterest 真正擅长的。您可以利用我们的计算机视觉技术并有效地构建这些嵌入来检测人、内容、沙发或生日蛋糕。</p><p>我们在这方面非常擅长，并且在这方面长期处于行业领先地位。你没有错，所发生的事情只是变得更好；它变得更加准确、更加具体。在过去，我可以说，“嘿，我知道这是一盏灯，我知道它有吊坠，它是由水晶制成的，它是金的，”诸如此类的事情。但现在我可以说：“我确切地知道它上面有多少个尖齿；我知道它们是什么类型的灯泡；我大概知道是谁制造的”之类的东西。我可以说得更具体。</p><p>在 Pinterest，我们确实将它们视为两件不同的事情。人们来到 Pinterest 是因为他们不知道自己到底想要什么。这就是 Pinterest 蓬勃发展的地方，也是我们在市场上保持长期差异化的原因。因为如果你知道你想要什么，你总是可以去亚马逊、家得宝或 Wayfair 去购买，但如果你不知道你想要什么，你可以从 Pinterest 开始，或者进行一百万种不同的搜索，因为[你]不知道自己想要什么。我不知道如何描述，你知道，“经典的谷仓厨房”——[你]不知道这些词。</p><p>因此，即使将其放入 ChatGPT 之类的东西中，我也不知道该怎么说 - 你知道我的意思吗？我相信随着时间的推移，这会变得更好，但其中很多也将是基于图像的。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您是否发现可用的基础模型可以为您做到这一点，或者您正在构建自己的特定领域模型？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>我想，两者都是答案。我们发现——现在还相对较早——在生成图像方面，我们发现较小的模型实际上更加具体，所以我认为这就是将会发生的事情。我的 CTO 朋友们也说了同样的事情，也就是说，每一个模型都将针对特定的用例，这不仅有助于它更加准确，而且还使其实施起来便宜得多。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为您多次提到蛋糕很有趣，因为我认为装饰蛋糕实际上是我唯一使用 Pinterest 的用途。这与谢尔文关于生成的评论有关，因为我深深怀疑我在那里看到的那些蛋糕，没有人可以创造。我当然无法创造它们。那么……人们在多大程度上发布了实际上不存在的图像或不存在的产品？ Pinterest 对此有何看法？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>说得很好。我想，是的，我们在我们称之为“艺术”的最大类别之一中经常看到这种情况。艺术包括很多东西，包括传统上挂在墙上的东西、绘画等等。但它也包括人体艺术之类的东西，我们有纹身之类的东西。再说一次，很多都是很好的案例，人们需要一点灵感，而且它可以产生创造力，对吗？它可能不存在于世界上，但你想看看它在人类身上是什么样子。</p><p>你可以看到这一点的到来，你将能够打印出一些生成的东西。这已经发生了，对吧？</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>是的。这确实与灵感的理念相符。</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>是的，绝对如此。像蛋糕之类的东西很有趣。更困难的部分之一是，我见过很多关于家居和家居装修的工作，但它正在产生一大堆无法实现的想法，我可以说，“嘿，人们还没有真正拿出相机来拍一张他们房间的照片。”人们这样做，但我们称之为 1% 功能。比如，如何让人们真正使用手机或手机摄像头？</p><p>但如果你可以上传一张图片——我已经看到了一些漂亮的效果图，比如，“这就是我的房间。重新布置我房间里的家具，我已有的家具，”这样的事情变得非常有趣。或者你说，“我想用 Wayfair 的这张沙发替换这张沙发。我想用其他灯替换这盏灯，”这里有 20 种不同的组合，您可以点击查看。</p><p>这就像您正在进行虚拟体验，几乎像 AR [类似增强现实]，但您将真实的产品放入其中，而不是生成产品。但它可以让您构建更加增强的用户体验。</p><p>去年，我们开发了<a href="https://help.pinterest.com/en/article/try-on">AR Try On</a> ，它可以让你试妆，我们再次看到，虽然它没有得到大量使用，但使用它的人购买的可能性增加了 60%某物。当人们真正到达那里时，它会非常有吸引力。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong> Pinterest 的困难是什么？您提到了很多很好的用例，您正在使用这些技术做很多事情。当然，不可能一切都那么美好。有什么难的？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我们在包容性搜索和结果上花费了大量时间。 2021年，我们推出了发型搜索。这就是第一个技术：当您寻找发型时，如何识别与您相似的头发？这对于完善您正在寻找的内容非常重要。</p><p>我们在肤色方面也遇到了同样的问题，最初我们尝试使用早期模型进行肤色检测。我们发现，更多的是关于人脸检测。因此，我们的团队在皮肤检测方面做了一些出色的工作——它可以是侧面拍摄、背面拍摄、耳朵拍摄或手部拍摄。你不知道什么样的皮肤。那么如何检测是什么皮肤呢？然后您就可以检测到您正在寻找哪种语气。</p><p>同样的东西也必须应用到头发上。我们有各种各样的头发：我们有剃光/秃头、我们有直发、我们有波浪形、我们有卷发、我们有卷发、我们有保护性头发，这些类型的头发使结果显着更好。</p><p>您可以保存您的头发图案和肤色，然后我们将据此定制您的结果。正如您可以想象的那样，这是一个复杂的问题。这不仅仅是美国的事；也是美国的事。每个不同的国家都有不同类型的头发图案和肤色以及不同类型的时尚，所以这些事情确实很难，但它们是伟大的项目。</p><p>我们拥有一支出色的团队。特别是这里的先进技术团队——我们一直致力于包容性技术和所有这些先进模型，它们确实很难，但当你把它们做好时，它们会很棒。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我们这里有一个部分：五个快速问题。我只会问你一堆连珠炮般的问题。请告诉我你想到的第一件事。你最自豪的人工智能时刻是什么？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>包容性的产品功能，实际上，头发图案是我最自豪的功能，因为我不仅从一开始就参与了该产品，而且它也是行业中的第一个。我们从钉钉者那里得到的回应之多令人难以置信。所以，是的，这确实是一件好事。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>除了偏见和一些道德问题之外，您对人工智能还有哪些担忧？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>这很有趣。每个论坛上都有。它说：“嘿，你担心偏见吗？”让我们来看看。人工智能让我担心什么？唔。是的，我不担心。我不担心太多事情，但那是CTO……</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>很好。但这是一件好事，对吧？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>这是一位长期担任首席技术官的事情。如果你担心太多，你就无法在这份工作中生存。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您最喜欢的不涉及技术的活动是什么？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>山地自行车。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>非常酷。</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>我尝试每周至少去两次。周五早上我和一群硅谷科技[同事]一起去，然后通常在周末和我的兄弟和其他一些人一起去。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>你想要的第一个职业：你长大后想做什么？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我认为我 5 岁的婴儿书上写的是消防员，但我的祖父和父亲都是工程师，所以我实际上认为我会建造房屋，因为我喜欢在外面用手工作。所以这就是我想我要去的地方——建筑或房屋建造。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您希望人工智能能做哪些目前做不到的事情？</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>传送：让我更快地通过安检线！也许那即将到来。我一直对翻译感到非常兴奋。我很久以前就接管了 eBay 的翻译团队，有一些很棒的人正在从事这方面的工作。我一直认为万能翻译器会是一件非常神奇的事情。它已经如此接近，但在该设备的消费者版本出现之前似乎仍然很遥远。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>但你认为这是为什么呢？因为我们现在有了法学硕士，而且很长一段时间以来我们已经有了音频到文本的技术。这里的限制因素是什么？</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King：</strong>我认为这是外形因素；比如，我如何拿出手机，点击“从西班牙语翻译成英语”——你知道，诸如此类的事情。我不知道;如果我走到旧金山街上的一个小贩面前，我说的语言不同，但我想要一些东西。 ……它必须很接近，但这是一个外形因素。但我认为它很快就会到来。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>似乎可以解决。</p><p><strong>杰里米·金：</strong>是的，可以解决。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>杰里米，我们非常感谢您抽出时间与我们交谈。 It&#39;s been very interesting to learn, sort of behind the scenes, what&#39;s happening between all those images that we see but maybe didn&#39;t appreciate all that goes into making something that looks as easy as Pinterest work. And it&#39;s been pretty fascinating to see how much artificial intelligence and machine learning is behind that. Thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Jeremy King:</strong> Of course. It&#39;s been wonderful.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Thanks for listening today. On our next episode, Sam and I meet with Damini Satija and Matt Mahmoudi from Amnesty International. Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/images-and-inspiration-with-ai-pinterests-jeremy-king/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Identify Critical Roles to Improve Performance</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Boris Groysberg, Eric Lin, Abhijit Naik, and Sascha L. Schmidt. <p>Boris Groysberg is the Richard P. Chapman Professor of Business Administration at Harvard Business School. Eric Lin is an associate professor of business at Oberlin College and Conservatory. Abhijit Naik is senior global quantitative researcher at Quent Capital. Sascha L. Schmidt is a professor and director of the Center for Sports and Management at WHU-Otto Beisheim School of Management.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent]]></category><category><![CDATA[Executing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Brian Stauffer/theispot.com Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization’s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn’t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Groysberg_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Brian Stauffer/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Leaders like to show that they value employees. They proclaim that everyone on the team is critical to the organization&#39;s success. As uplifting as that sentiment is, it simply isn&#39;t true. Talent can be a source of competitive advantage only if great people are in the most critical roles. Having stars in jobs that aren&#39;t critical is just a waste of talent.</p><p> It&#39;s accepted wisdom in strategy execution that focused application of concentrated strength — identifying, developing, and leveraging critical capabilities — is required for success. Yet until these capabilities are translated into specific roles, with systems in place to ensure that high-quality employees occupy such positions, a strategy is just an intention. Unfortunately, too many organizations build strategy around the people they have at the time and current skill sets — when they should instead be devising the most promising strategy, developing a better understanding of the roles that will be most critical in executing it, and then staffing those roles with the best available talent. As we&#39;ll demonstrate, applying data and analytics to that problem can help you determine exactly where your top talent needs to be placed.</p><p></p><p> There are two ways to figure out which roles have the most influence on key results: using data to deduce this from the bottom up and inferring it from the top down. Where the context is appropriate and the data available, taking the bottom-up approach can yield answers that may be surprising. In such cases, leaders must be prepared to let the insights guide their decisions.</p><h3> Data Reveals the Difference Makers</h3><p> Data can be used to help tease out both who your current stars are and what positions have the greatest influence on organizational outcomes. It can help identify hidden talent in situations where performance is a team effort and point out roles that may be much more important to success than leadership has realized.</p><p> Take soccer: There is much debate around which positions on the field are the most valuable. Forwards, including strikers, are the primary scorers — they capture the limelight as well as the largest salaries by producing goals. The top 50 highest-paid athletes worldwide include six soccer players — and they are all forwards — according to a 2023 <cite>Forbes</cite> report.</p><p> Since soccer is a low-scoring game, every goal matters — so preventing an opponent&#39;s goal is an equally crucial contribution. Thus, some argue that defenders are the most valuable players. Central defenders play a critical role in coordinating the counteroffensive, as failure to stop the ball at key moments can create big opportunities for the opponent to score. It&#39;s no surprise that central defenders have been team captains more often than other position players.</p><p></p><p> Of course, goalkeepers are the last defenders on the line: Their judgment and skills in the face of extreme pressure can mean the difference between victory and defeat. Still others contend that midfielders drive the tempo of the game. Just as controlling the center of the board is critical to winning chess matches, midfielders can magnify the impact of everyone&#39;s contributions by shutting down opponent passing lanes or by initiating drives through well-timed distributions from the defensive players to the offensive strikers. Finally, the grandmaster might be the coach, who makes decisions on rosters, positions, and general strategy.</p><p> To determine each role&#39;s relative contribution, we collected and analyzed five years&#39; worth of data from the Bundesliga, Germany&#39;s top soccer league, and evaluated the importance of individual positions on the soccer field between 2014 and 2019.</p><p> By analyzing the changes in outcomes as players moved among different roles and teams, we isolated contributions by position while observing how fortunes rose and fell following such switches. Building a model of how each position contributes to the outcome, we weighted the importance of positions by measuring how much the model&#39;s win prediction deteriorated when we omitted each role from the model in turn.</p><p> Our analysis indicated that defenders and goalkeepers are the most critical for winning matches; they occupy the top three slots in two different models we developed. Four positions are always present among the top five: left fullback, right fullback, goalkeeper, and offensive left midfielder. Although defenders may not get as much fan adoration, the numbers indicate that they are the biggest difference makers for winning.</p><p> This kind of analysis works regardless of industry. Every organization or function is similarly likely to have its own underappreciated roles. While the sales team may land the account, it could be the service department that keeps that account renewing each year.</p><p> Talent scarcity matters, too. Comparing the left versus right positions for fullback, midfielder, and center defender, the roles on the left side contribute disproportionately more.为什么？ While left-footed soccer players are naturally advantaged for these roles, the number of world-class left-footed players is considerably smaller than right-footed players. In critical roles where exceptional talent is scarce, having performers in such roles is doubly important.</p><p> Organizational leadership and structure also matter. When included in the models, coaches are the third-most-important factor, behind only the fullback positions. Team organization, systems of play, and staffing govern how critical roles are deployed. In the Bundesliga, the 4-5-1 team formation — four defenders, five midfielders, and one striker — is the most successful configuration. It favors the strategy of prioritizing defense positions and is a good example of congruence between strategy and how organizations configure themselves around critical roles.</p><p></p><h3> Use Data to Fill Critical Roles</h3><p> A similar analytical approach can be applied to businesses by combining performance and HR data. For companies with multiunit structures (such as multiple stores, distribution centers, or service teams), the good news is that you don&#39;t need a soccer league&#39;s worth of data — you can do this yourself. Multiunit organizations with common roles offer the opportunity to capture data across the units and isolate difference-making roles.</p><p> First, gather the data that identifies your workers by location, role, and timing. Second, be sure to gain an understanding of contextual factors that influence outcomes but are unrelated to staffing (for example, stores may perform differently due to location, age, format, or season). This allows you to separate an individual&#39;s impact on outcomes from circumstantial factors. Third, collect performance outcome data for the unit; it&#39;s best to obtain multiple types of metrics, since outcomes are multidimensional.</p><p> In work we did with a national retailer, we gathered such data from hundreds of stores over five years. We measured monthly store performance by revenue, profit, growth, employee turnover, and breakage. We found that store managers matter a great deal: Twenty-one percent of revenue performance could be attributed to store managers — over three times more significant than store attributes — and they had an outsize impact on margins. Regional and district managers also produced measurable effects, but they were less influential than store managers. As expected, the impact of district and regional managers differed depending on the metric. While store managers had the strongest influence on revenues, margin performance was more strongly influenced by district and regional managers, who had significant input into purchasing decisions.</p><p> Just as in soccer, structure and systems matter. Our research found that stores that were closer to headquarters performed better, motivating the further exploration of how stores farther afield could be supported. There is also valuable insight to be gained from employee mobility. When people stay in their roles and locations, it is impossible to use data to disentangle the impact of people from their surrounding circumstances. Moving people through different settings not only gives them a chance to develop and grow, it also enhances the data, allowing more precise measurements of the impact of roles and the people performing them.</p><p></p><p> For the retailer we worked with, these insights changed the talent strategy. Originally, the leaders were moving toward creating a training academy program for district and regional managers, having assumed that higher-status managers with a broader scope of responsibilities would matter more to performance. After considering the results of our analysis, they pivoted to explore what behaviors and practices mattered in the critical role of the store manager. They launched a companywide effort to find out, modeling their approach on Google&#39;s internal research called Project Oxygen, to distill the attributes of managers who positively influenced company performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Once they had identified the details of this critical role, they were able to apply focused investment in developing and replicating capabilities for the job at scale.</p><h3> Talent Insights and Sustainable Competitive Advantage</h3><p> Billy Beane of the Oakland Athletics used data to build a high-performing team at a surprisingly low cost. His strategy as a general manager was to use different performance metrics to find undervalued players who contributed more to winning games than players who performed well on traditional measures. The success of this approach was quickly copied throughout the league, dissipating the A&#39;s strategic advantage. Could an advantage from data-driven talent decisions on crucial roles also be so short-lived?</p><p> There is a key difference to note. The Athletics studied measures that identified great players — but these players could be great on any team. The hallmark of a good strategy is one where the sources of competitive advantage are interlocked with other strategic commitments, making it difficult to copy. Finding key roles and building an organization around those roles may be more defensible than finding hidden stars, since the strategic advantage is tied to how organizations support these roles and develop pipelines to fill them.</p><p> The Bundesliga is known not only for its defense game but also for how it sources talent. It lacks the financial muscle of leagues such as the Premier League, with its billionaire owners. However, the German soccer system&#39;s commitment to developing young talent over relying on high-priced transfers of proven stars makes it an attractive option for young players who need to prove themselves with time on the field — including young players from outside Germany. Because other leagues that have paid dearly for high-priced transfers are obligated to play such talent for more minutes, they have diminished value propositions for younger, emerging talent. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Like Beane&#39;s winning Athletics team, there is an advantage in arbitraging on the undervalued, be it defensive players or younger players. However, unlike this Major League Baseball case, imitating the Bundesliga advantage will require a substantial adjustment to strategy — one that many teams and even leagues are not prepared to make.</p><h3> Execute Based on Differentiating Capabilities</h3><p> Strategy is about defining how to win — it requires committing to capabilities that are unambiguously the best in class. But no company can be the best at everything; a winning strategy requires focus and a keen awareness of what roles are disproportionately critical — and investing appropriately. Failing to acknowledge this puts the entire strategy at risk. By translating abstract capabilities into concrete jobs, organizations are much better positioned to make their strategies a reality.</p><p> Leaders can take a page from the soccer playbook and consider the following lessons for their own organizations:</p><p> <strong>Know your critical roles and where you need to invest.</strong> Despite being a less visible role, defenders matter more than other positions for winning soccer games. Insight into where difference-making roles exist should guide attention and investment when it comes to recruiting, developing, and retaining talent. While it is important to know your key contributors, it is just as important to know where you have deficits in critical roles.</p><p> Additionally, critical roles may change over time. As the competitive landscape evolves, difference-making positions can also change. Winning consistently requires monitoring not only what the critical roles are but how they might be shifting.</p><p></p><p> Investing in critical roles is not just about finding amazing talent — it is also about creating the required systems and practices that focus on positions first, and the people who fill them second. It&#39;s tempting to be blinded by the brightness of stars and give in to eagerly absorbing them regardless of what position they take. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Building a system around such stars makes organizations fragile: They become overdependent on them and distracted from the goal of aligning strategy with talent deployment.</p><p> <strong>Use data where you can, and invest in making it informative.</strong> When you have multiunit structures in your organization, you can exploit that to study roles systematically. Many companies have invested in systems that measure the performance of business units, products, regions, or stores. It takes additional investment to connect this information to personnel data, since most organizations do not explicitly link organizational performance and human resource information. Additionally, it&#39;s common to opt for the ease of keeping people in fixed locations instead of rotating them through different settings. But the practice of introducing some variance in how and where people work can create incredible insights into what roles drive performance. Such insights can highlight the contributions of unsung heroes and highlight where investments in training and recruiting can yield the most substantial gains in performance.</p><p> <strong>Hire for and develop based on key skills.</strong> Today, seniority and pedigree are too influential in talent markets; moreover, they have the effect of entrenching common wisdom about what matters within a role. Just as leaders can be misguided about what roles matter most, they can also be led astray about what skills and behaviors within those roles make the difference. By identifying critical capabilities within critical roles, organizations can both reward what matters and develop the blueprint for hiring, retaining, and developing employees with such skills in mind.</p><p> <strong>Align systems and structure.</strong> Talented employees in critical roles need to be supported with systems and structures that play to their strengths. Similar to the way Bundesliga teams have found that prioritizing the defense roles in field positioning increases the odds of success, organizations need to think creatively about what structure frees those in critical jobs to do their best work. These investments both enable more contributions from your critical roles and make your strategy less vulnerable to replication.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize leadership&#39;s critical role.</strong> On soccer teams, coaches are the third-most-important factor to winning games. Leaders set strategy and then build and motivate the team that supports it. Because alignment across the organization is so critical, any meaningful step to identify, invest in, and develop critical roles needs support from the top. This is especially important when a change in strategy requires building up talent in a critical role that has historically been weak. Leaders need to reinforce their commitment to supporting new key roles with their teams and with potential hires.</p><p></p><p> In soccer, winning can hinge on very small differences. While good teamwork is critical, the highly integrated nature of the sport obscures what the critical roles are. The thoughtful use of data can shed light on the critical roles within your team and uncover surprising results that challenge conventional wisdom. Having insight on critical roles may not only inform your strategy — it may be a source of competitive advantage in itself.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/identify-critical-roles-to-improve-performance/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Thriving in the New World of Work</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Gabriella Rosen Kellerman. <p>Gabriella Rosen Kellerman is chief innovation officer at BetterUp and coauthor of <cite>Tomorrowmind: Thriving at Work With Resilience, Creativity, and Connection ― Now and in an Uncertain Future</cite> (Atria Books, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Well-Being]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Wellness]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book Tomorrowmind, have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled. During Work/23, an MIT Sloan [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/W23-QA04_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Workforce well-being is an urgent issue: Stress and burnout are limiting employee engagement and driving out talented workers. But Gabriella Rosen Kellerman and Martin Seligman, coauthors of the book <cite>Tomorrowmind</cite> , have identified five skills that can help individuals flourish in dynamic work environments — even those that are especially pressure-filled.</p><p> During <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023, Kellerman and Seligman explained that they use the acronym <em>PRISM</em> to refer to those five skills. It starts with <em>prospection</em> — the ability to imagine our options, plan for the future, and restore our agency — which Kellerman described as “the meta skill of our era.” The others are <em>resilience</em> , <em>innovation</em> , <em>social connection</em> , and <em>mattering</em> . All of them can be learned, the coauthors said, and leaders can help their employees do so.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Kellerman and Seligman&#39;s work builds on seminal research Seligman conducted with the US Army to understand which soldiers are most at risk of experiencing post-traumatic stress disorder. He found that people with extreme pessimism — catastrophizers who believe that when bad events occur, everything will fall apart — are most vulnerable. His research also found that soldiers who demonstrate high positive emotion, low negative emotion, and high optimism on Day One are better positioned to withstand their environments and even go on to be awarded medals for heroism.</p><p> “I&#39;ve worked on resilience my entire 60 years in psychology,” Seligman said. “The people who were invulnerable, who are resilient, are the optimists.”</p><p> Resilience draws on self-awareness and self-compassion, they explained. “Emotional regulation is, in some ways, the foundational skill of maturing as an adult,” noted Kellerman. “It&#39;s our ability to recognize our emotions, to pause in response to them, to reappraise them, and then to choose a response.” That response, she added, ideally comes from a thoughtful, centered place rather than an emotionally reactive one.</p><p> Kellerman and Seligman weren&#39;t able to get to all of the questions from attendees during the Work/23 event, so Kellerman answers some of them below. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><p></p><h6> Why is it that, in some cases, self-efficacy and confidence are seen as negative traits, irrespective of knowledge or skills?</h6><p> <em>Self-efficacy</em> is our belief in our own ability to act in the ways we need to in order to achieve our goals. We build self-efficacy by witnessing our own successes as we build mastery in specific domains. Many decades of studies have shown the positive relationship between self-efficacy and well-being and accomplishment.</p><p> In contrast, <em>self-esteem</em> — often defined as confidence in our own abilities — is a less robust construct and can be falsely inflated. It may or may not be related to actual accomplishments. As our colleague Roy Baumeister has demonstrated, <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1111/1529-1006.01431">self-esteem does not predict performance or well-being</a> .</p><p> People with high degrees of self-efficacy may not come across as confident to others, and people who do come across as confident may or may not have high degrees of self-efficacy. Confidence becomes a negative trait when it is false or narcissistic, but neither characteristic applies to self-efficacy.</p><h6> Are there studies correlating pessimism, PTSD, and suicide?</h6><p>是的。 Pessimism is a common feature of depression, and a significant risk factor for suicide. See, for example, “ <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/257552463_An_Examination_of_OptimismPessimism_and_Suicide_Risk_in_Primary_Care_Patients_Does_Belief_in_a_Changeable_Future_Make_a_Difference">An Examination of Optimism/Pessimism and Suicide Risk in Primary Care Patients: Does Belief in a Changeable Future Make a Difference?</a> ”</p><p> <em>Catastrophization</em> , an extreme form of pessimism, is predictive of PTSD risk. Catastrophization has also been shown to have a causal relationship with PTSD severity; see “ <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32479704/">The Sequential Relation Between Changes in Catastrophizing and Changes in Posttraumatic Stress Disorder Symptom Severity</a> .”</p><h6> What skill do you recommend that people choose first for growth?</h6><p> This will vary for every person. For those who are low on resilience, start there. Specifically, focus on the five following skills that drive resilience: emotional regulation, self-efficacy, cognitive agility, self-compassion, and optimism. Which of the five do you feel least comfortable with? Learn about it and look for ways to apply it in your day-to-day life.</p><p></p><p> Our book, <cite><a href="https://www.gabriellarosenkellerman.com/book">Tomorrowmind</a></cite> , includes exercises to build each of these in Chapter 4. For those who are already feeling resilient, pick another of the PRISM powers (prospection, resilience, innovation, social support, and mattering) to start with. [ <em>Editor&#39;s note: Kellerman and Seligman also explore the elements of PRISM in their recent</em> MIT SMR <em>article “<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/reimagining-hr-for-better-well-being-and-performance/">Reimagining HR for Better Well-Being and Performance</a></em> .”]</p><h6> How can companies train their employees on these skills?</h6><p> All of these skills can be taught and developed. The best forms of training are personalized and longitudinal and include a mix of learning and practice. Human experts, like mentors or coaches, are an ideal resource, where available.</p><p> You can start with large-group experiences, like presentations or workshops, but don&#39;t stop there. Teach these skills to managers, and teach the managers how to teach those skills to the people who report to them. Look for ways to integrate practices that build these skills into your culture. All of them require practice over time in order to be sustained.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/thriving-in-the-new-world-of-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Countering the Corporate Diversity Backlash</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Victor Ray and Tsedale M. Melaku. <p>Victor Ray is the F. Wendell Miller Associate Professor in the departments of sociology and criminology and African American Studies at the University of Iowa and the author of <cite>On Critical Race Theory: Why It Matters &amp; Why You Should Care</cite> (Random House, 2022). Tsedale M. Melaku, Ph.D., is an assistant professor of management at the Zicklin School of Business at Baruch College (CUNY) and the author of <cite>You Don&#39;t Look Like a Lawyer: Black Women and Systemic Gendered Racism</cite> (Rowman and Littlefield, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human Resources]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com Corporate diversity is facing a backlash. Target, a company that has carried merchandise celebrating LGBTQ+ pride for over a decade, ordered some stores to remove such products after conservative activists accused the company of sexualizing children and organized a boycott. Anheuser-Busch lost sales in response to a promotion with trans influencer Dylan Mulvaney, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023FALL-Ray_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Egle Plytnikaite/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Corporate diversity is facing a backlash. Target, a company that has carried merchandise celebrating LGBTQ+ pride for over a decade, ordered some stores to remove such products after conservative activists accused the company of sexualizing children and organized a boycott. Anheuser-Busch lost sales in response to a promotion with trans influencer Dylan Mulvaney, costing Bud Light its spot as America&#39;s bestselling beer. Even Chick-fil-A, perhaps the prototype of corporate conservatism with its opposition to same-sex marriage and policy of closing on Sundays, recently came under attack from conservatives for employing an executive to lead its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) efforts.</p><p> Universities are also facing a diversity backlash. The US Supreme Court recently struck down race-conscious admissions programs at Harvard and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill. Ending race-conscious admissions will likely have ripple effects, as an unclear regulatory environment might discourage organizations from implementing current diversity efforts while spurring some to explicitly exclude Black, Latine, and Indigenous groups.</p><p></p><p> These recent events show that resistance to civil rights progress for members of marginalized or underrepresented groups remains entrenched, and opponents of efforts to improve equity have been emboldened.</p><p> Diversity backlash puts companies in a difficult position. Bowing to pressure from anti-diversity groups may cost them the goodwill they have tried to cultivate among other consumers; Target&#39;s capitulation to conservative pressure earned it blowback from progressive activists. Backing down can also encourage conservative activists to push their demands further. While it might temporarily reduce the pressure on companies, giving in to anti-diversity forces could hurt them over the long term. Demographics are changing, with nonWhites making up an increasing portion of the coveted youth market, and legal protections for LGBTQ+ Americans have broad <a href="https://thehill.com/changing-america/respect/equality/599240-support-for-lgbtq-rights-on-the-rise-poll/">support</a> . Rooting out discrimination and increasing access to opportunity is essential to ensuring a rich talent pipeline. And for many individual managers and employees, anti-discrimination is simply a moral imperative.</p><p> Diversity initiatives are vulnerable to attack because many have been tentative. One-off hours-long training sessions, unsupported new hires, or programs that wither as anti-racist protests recede fall far short of the transformative structural changes needed to make organizational outcomes truly equitable. Leaders who are sincerely committed to diversity must prepare for the cost of defending inclusive organizations and adopt policies that make it difficult to roll back diversity gains.</p><p></p><h3> A Tepid Embrace of Diversity</h3><p> When President Lyndon Johnson signed the 1964 Civil Rights Act, with Martin Luther King Jr. present, he was responding to decades of agitation for full economic inclusion. Under the act&#39;s Title VII, the commonplace racial discrimination foundational to American workplaces became illegal. Most organizations that adopted diversity policies did so because social movements forced their hand, not out of a high-minded commitment to equal opportunity.</p><p> Many organizations retroactively recognized that greater diversity helped <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2019/04/business-case-for-diversity-in-the-workplace/">them</a> exploit niche markets or foster innovation. But arguments that diversity can be good for the bottom line haven&#39;t led to a fundamental transformation of segregated and racially stratified American workplaces. And relying on a business case for diversity lets leaders withdraw support for these initiatives if economic gains don&#39;t materialize.</p><p> While civil rights laws drove real workplace changes, they were largely marginal. Despite early gains in Black and Latine employment, workplace desegregation essentially stopped in the <a href="https://www.russellsage.org/publications/documenting-desegregation">1980s</a> , and hiring discrimination against Black <a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1706255114">men</a> has been relatively constant since. When hired, people of color were often designated to diversity positions cordoned off from the organization&#39;s core functions, limiting opportunities for their career growth and mobility. Enforcement of anti-discrimination laws varied greatly depending on the political winds, typically (but not exclusively) increasing under Democratic presidents and waning under Republicans. As sociologists Frank Dobbin and Alexandra <a href="https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/abs/10.1146/annurev-soc-090820-023615">Kalev</a> have found in their research, attempts to comply with an uncertain regulatory environment led companies to adopt diversity policies with dubious effectiveness. Human resources experts often introduced policies that courts countenanced as good-faith anti-discrimination efforts, despite the policies being ineffective and sometimes counterproductive.</p><p> Diversifying organizations rarely undermined the White norms and the <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0003122418822335">power</a> that shaped them. Homogeneity remained the standard, diversity a deviation. Acknowledging the changes brought to workplaces by the Civil Rights Movement, Kimberlé Crenshaw and <a href="https://thenewpress.com/books/critical-race-theory">colleagues</a> nonetheless highlighted in their 1996 book <cite>Critical Race Theory</cite> the unequal ground on which diversity policies were seeded: “The very same Whites who administered explicit policies of segregation and racial domination kept their jobs as decision makers in employment offices of companies, admissions offices of schools, lending offices of banks, and so on.”</p><p> This history of organizations&#39; tepid embrace of diversity has left them unprepared to deal with the current backlash. Three short years after their collective response to massive protests over the police murder of George Floyd, companies are reneging on their diversity <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/esg/host-of-companies-sued-alleging-unmet-diversity-equity-pledges">pledges</a> . Promises included increasing the representation of marginalized groups and women in senior-level positions and boards; addressing retention, promotion, and pay gaps; and working with senior leaders and managers on upskilling inclusive leadership behaviors. Companies added positions focused on DEI to demonstrate their intentions to tackle injustice, without transforming in ways that would support long-term organizational changes.</p><p></p><p> A slowing economy and, we suspect, a diversity backlash led companies to cut those new DEI positions at a faster <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/diversity-roles-disappear-three-years-george-floyd-protests-inspired-rcna72026">rate</a> than other jobs. Attacks on DEI have led some organizations to backtrack from their commitments to create initiatives centered on addressing organizational policies, practices, and cultures that target groups facing persistent inequities. Attempts to integrate substantive DEI programs also succumbed to the backlash, as evidenced by <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/business-and-practice/coca-cola-scraps-diversity-requirements-for-outside-law-firms">Coca-Cola</a> abandoning its proposed DEI policy for outside law firms. Some activist shareholders have attacked companies&#39; DEI <a href="https://www.mvalaw.com/media/news/15112_WLT_McDowell.pdf">interventions</a> and also targeted the practice of DEI audits, which help mitigate workplace discrimination.</p><h3> Confront the Resistance</h3><p> Although we&#39;ve outlined a pessimistic story, diversity programs can succeed. Research <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/000312240607100404">shows</a> that diversity programs are effective when organizations dedicate specialized positions to manage and monitor equity goals and programs.</p><p> Accountability is <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/02/dei-initiatives-are-futile-without-accountability">key</a> to sustaining effective DEI policies and programs. While equity work should involve all employees, DEI professionals must be empowered to hold the leadership accountable. Organization leaders must take responsibility for designing, modeling, and implementing equity programs that reshape organizational policy. Research shows that strategic DEI initiatives, including establishing mentoring programs that incentivize employees to sponsor marginalized group members, demonstrating transparency in hiring and promotion processes, and holding employees accountable for diversity goals, can work.</p><p> The latest backlash against diversity should prepare organizational leaders for possible resistance to diversity initiatives from internal stakeholders and external anti-diversity activists. Making public statements in support of DEI can help establish accountability goals, but unfortunately, it seems that a growing number of leaders are choosing silence or capitulation in response to anti-diversity activists.</p><p> We see a similar phenomenon in how the right-wing rejection of climate science has led some leaders to downplay sustainability goals, a practice known as <em>greenhushing</em> . A recent <a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/0047287520930087">study</a> examining this dynamic in the hospitality industry found that consumers preferred when hotels communicated their corporate social responsibility efforts rather than engaging in greenhushing. Interestingly, the study found that such communications also prompted consumers to consider the ethics of their own choices. Similarly, we believe that openly discussing an organization&#39;s commitment to address systemic issues through accountability reduces resistance to initiatives that can change behaviors and attitudes and lead to progress.</p><p></p><p> Organizations should confront the diversity backlash, along with the empty nature of superficial diversity policies, head-on. With diversity training increasingly criticized and White fatigue derailing serious discussions of racism, racial inclusion in organizations faces an existential threat. Resisting this diversity retreat requires organizational accountability to the broad array of commitments made in response to acknowledged racial injustices.</p><p> For organizations committed to embedding equity within their mission, values, culture, and practices, we recommend taking a strategic planning approach. Expectations for overnight results must be regulated by realistic goals that are results-oriented and measurable, with targeted dates for completion. This process must include a feedback loop design that allows for corrections in planning, implementing, and executing, thus providing managers with openings to check for impact and progress. Recent events give organizations an opportunity to reaffirm and strengthen their commitments to working toward creating an equitable organization by stamping out inequality.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/countering-the-corporate-diversity-backlash/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Outlawing Collegiate Affirmative Action Will Impact Corporate America</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Derek R. Avery. <p>Derek R. Avery is the CT Bauer Chair of Inclusive Leadership at the University of Houston&#39;s Bauer College of Business.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Recruiting]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equality]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avery-Extension-a4312ir2142-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Michael Glenwood Gibbs/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> On June 29, 2023, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled 6-3 in favor of outlawing the use of race and ethnicity as factors in college admissions. This was a momentous decision that stands to have widespread societal and organizational implications. Although the scope of the ruling was limited to college admissions, we can draw upon existing data to forecast the impact on corporate America. The evidence clearly points to two key outcomes: First, collegiate patterns of racioethnic diversity will change fairly dramatically; and second, these changes will have considerable downstream consequences for workplace composition as well as patterns of racioethnic inequity across a host of other measures.</p><p> As tempting as it might be to view those conclusions as hyperbolic, research on three decades of state-level affirmative action bans strongly suggests otherwise. In fact, eradicating affirmative action has led to reductions in the proportions of underrepresented (Black and Hispanic) students in undergraduate and graduate programs, particularly in science, technology, engineering, and math; it has also led to fewer underrepresented students enrolled in and graduating from medical and law schools. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> These effects tend to be lasting — and, importantly, implementing alternative policies that don&#39;t explicitly consider race and ethnicity has done little to counter them. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p></p><p> Extending these state-level findings to the national level suggests that employers will have less racioethnically diverse college-educated talent to draw upon when filling their vacancies, particularly from premier institutions. Alternatively, the Black and Hispanic candidates within their applicant pools are less likely to be selected because they will be less credentialed as a result of having fewer degrees or having graduated from lower-ranked colleges, where they are more likely to apply and be accepted post-affirmative action. A somewhat less-intuitive consequence is that the White (and Asian) graduates of more prestigious colleges and universities will have had less exposure to people of other racioethnic backgrounds. This has implications for their multicultural competence — the ability to relate to those dissimilar from oneself — and may help account for why employers tend to pay higher starting salaries to graduates of more racioethnically diverse business schools and universities. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> The fallout within Black and Hispanic communities stands to be devastating. Most notably, there will be fewer minority professionals to help meet the needs of racioethnically similar minority clientele. Though this might seem to be more a matter of convenience, it is especially troubling in fields like medicine or law (which employs attorneys and members of law enforcement), where minority underrepresentation is often noted as a contributing factor to well-documented racioethnic health care and criminal justice disparities. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p> Lower odds of graduating from a more prestigious school or graduating at all also have implications for racioethnic inequality within organizations. This begins with underrepresented minorities being less apt to obtain a job or more likely to land a lower-quality one. It goes on to influence outcomes spanning the entire human resources management landscape, from entry to exit, because initial placements have lasting consequences for things like compensation, promotions, training/development, retention/separation, and deployment. For instance, even Black and Hispanic professionals who gain access to employment opportunities may be more likely to find themselves facing the “last hired, first fired” phenomenon. Moreover, a low starting salary can affect the size of raises or competitive offers from other companies and has deleterious compounding effects on one&#39;s retirement savings.</p><p></p><p> Those seeking even more concrete evidence that outlawing collegiate affirmative action can influence diversity in corporate America need look no further than recent research by Harvard Business School professor Letian Zhang. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> He examined affirmative action bans&#39; effect on whether people from different racial backgrounds became managers, using data from the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission on more than 11,000 private-sector US businesses from 1985 to 2015. He anticipated that executives might interpret bans as a sort of license to discriminate and, therefore, be less likely to hire Black managers or promote Black candidates. The results showed that “after a state adopts the affirmative action ban, growth in the proportion of Black managers in establishments with corporate headquarters in that state slows down by more than 50% and this slowdown is mostly concentrated in firms with politically conservative CEOs.”</p><p> By widening the collegiate achievement gap, the ban on affirmative action in colleges actually kicks the proverbial can of equal opportunity further down the road by adding larger higher education differentials to existing racial differences in wealth and access to quality preschool and K-12 education that also disfavor underrepresented minorities. Ironically, this further enhances the need for workplace affirmative action strategies just to maintain the racial status quo. That said, any such efforts will almost certainly be challenged along legal grounds, and the Supreme Court (at least as currently constituted) has shown itself highly unlikely to view such efforts favorably.</p><p></p><p> In fact, in a form of preemptive strike, 13 state attorneys general recently informed companies such as Apple, Microsoft, and Uber that they should expect greater scrutiny of any policies perceived as promoting race-based preferences in employee selection. They went on to promise legal action against “violators,” signaling their intention to extend the parameters of the Supreme Court ruling to US workplaces. This raises the question, what can organizations that remain committed to racial equal employment opportunity do to limit any losses they might suffer in this new, evolving employment landscape? Below, I provide four suggestions to help practitioners, managers, and organizations navigate this challenge.</p><p></p><h3> Don&#39;t Wait on the Sidelines</h3><p> President Theodore Roosevelt is often credited with saying, “In any moment of decision, the best thing you can do is the right thing, the next best thing is the wrong thing, and the worst thing you can do is nothing.” In the wake of the Supreme Court ruling, it is probably tempting to maintain business as usual, wait and see how things proceed, and adopt a reactionary approach as the dust settles. Doing so, however, promises to have considerable consequences. Namely, continuing to source applicants from the same schools while making no adjustments based on the predictable changes to student-body compositions leaves an organization entirely dependent on college admissions staffs to retool their strategies to solve a problem that few have been able to address in the past 30 years.</p><p> Accordingly, continuing to use degrees and degree-granting institutions as proxies for human capital, as many organizations historically have, will likely result in race differentials widening across virtually all employment outcomes, with cascading effects for nonemployment outcomes. For instance, a recent study showed that underrepresented minority youth tend to increase their engagement in risky behaviors (smoking cigarettes, alcohol use, and binge drinking) immediately following an affirmative action ban. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In short, expect to have fewer underrepresented minority employees and greater racial inequity, including larger differentials in earnings and advancement.</p><h3> Question Everything</h3><p> Well, you might not have to question everything, but if an organization wants to get better at something, it will need to do some things differently and examine how they&#39;ve been done in the past. For instance, an HR executive once told me that it was company policy to recruit only from the country&#39;s top 10 engineering programs. An unintended consequence of this practice was that new recruits came from geographic regions that were quite dissimilar to the company&#39;s locale, and new-hire turnover was unusually high for its industry. There was no qualitative difference between the No. 10 program and the No. 12 program, which was located within 100 miles. Why not recruit from the No. 12 program to reduce the chance of a new employee experiencing extreme culture shock and leaving within the first year?</p><p> Applying this logic in the current context, companies might need to broaden their search parameters to attract applicant pools that are demographically consistent with those of their recent past. Recruiting at historically Black colleges and universities and Hispanic-serving institutions is a good way of engaging in targeted recruitment — a strategy that is presently legally permissible. Placing online advertisements in places frequented by underrepresented minorities conveys that your organization is interested in receiving applications from members of these groups. Moreover, when it comes to selection and compensation, companies will need to reevaluate the implicit and explicit weights assigned to degree-granting institutions. The spoils of graduating from a premier institution are already distributed inconsistently, with larger benefits for White graduates than for Black degree holders. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a> Why not make that benefit smaller for everyone and simultaneously open more employment opportunities to a larger group?</p><h3> Lean Into the Data</h3><p> To address the issues raised by questioning everything, organizations can turn to what their data reveals. For instance, though inertia and benchmarking against competitors may suggest that a job requires a college degree, does the data support that contention? Job requirements that are linked to racial differences, like degree attainment and earning degrees from highly prestigious schools, tend to have an adverse impact on underrepresented groups — a form of statistical discrimination. In the context of selection, adverse impact occurs when a particular decision-making tool advantages members of one racial group (or any other legally protected category) relative to members of another racial group. While such differences are not illegal if the difference is job relevant, data is needed to establish such relevance.</p><p> Requiring degrees, favoring graduates of elite schools, and using minimum GPA cutoffs can adversely impact underrepresented minorities when such requirements are not directly related to job performance. In the past several years, there&#39;s been more discussion of eliminating these types of requirements, not only to enhance racial justice but also to simply tap a larger pool of high-potential candidates in a tight job market. Although some may interpret this as a form of “lowering standards” to enhance diversity, it should be noted that standards unrelated to performance are unnecessary and potentially illegal and may result in employee overqualification, which can have negative implications for hires&#39; attitudes, well-being, and performance. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Use your data (and that of relevant others) to determine job relevance and get rid of barriers that aren&#39;t boosting your bottom line.</p><h3> Select for Potential, and Train for Performance</h3><p> Though colleges invest considerable resources in preparing students for careers, there are inevitable shortfalls in the competency levels that graduates possess and employers desire. For instance, the National Association of Colleges and Employers indicates that employers are nearly unanimous in naming communication as the most important competency, and almost all students know this. Nevertheless, though 80% of students rate themselves extremely proficient at communication, only 47% of employers see students in this same light. The point is that more than half of employers see graduates as lacking the most important competency. Clearly, the 53% of employers that consider college graduates less than extremely proficient communicators are not leaving their vacancies unfilled. If they were, the unemployment rate for 2022 college graduates would not be 4%. Rather, many, if not most, employers recognize that they will need to invest in training to get new hires up to speed.</p><p></p><p> Identifying potential in a race-neutral yet valid way is certainly easier said than done. Generally speaking, the more closely the indicators used to select employees relate to what employees actually do, the better. This suggests that tools like high-fidelity simulations, work samples, and behaviorally anchored structured interviews may be particularly useful. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> Selection approaches should also focus on identifying trainability to ensure that organizations are able to maximize returns on their training investments. This could entail giving top candidates an opportunity to demonstrate their trainability by actively learning a new job-relevant competency and subsequently demonstrating their proficiency.</p><p></p><p> Over the past half century, affirmative action and its progeny have helped transform the racioethnic landscape of American colleges, universities, and organizations. These programs have done so by providing opportunities to those who history suggests would otherwise have been unlikely (or at least considerably less likely) to receive them. The choice of word — <em>opportunity</em> — is both intentional and important, as many people often lose sight of the fact that these programs grant beneficiaries only the chance to show that they belong. Although the Supreme Court decision eliminated one means of helping to level the playing field, as Alexander Graham Bell once said, “When one door closes, another opens.” Though the path may seem somewhat less clear, innovative companies will create and maintain competitive advantages by finding, attracting, and selecting the most talented people from <em>all</em> racial and ethnic backgrounds.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-outlawing-collegiate-affirmative-action-will-impact-corporate-america/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Make Your Case for Communication Upskilling</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy Duarte. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancyduarte/">Nancy Duarte</a> is CEO of <a href="https://www.duarte.com/">Duarte Inc.</a> , a communication company in the Silicon Valley. She&#39;s the author of six books, including <cite>DataStory: Explain Data and Inspire Action Through Story</cite> (Ideapress Publishing, 2019).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Internal Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[ROI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It’s hard to find a job posting that doesn’t mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Duarte-Upskilling-ROI-pie-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Companies say they desperately want employees who can communicate effectively — leaders tell me that all the time in workshops — but how many of them really mean it? It&#39;s hard to find a job posting that <em>doesn&#39;t</em> mention the communication skill set as a key requirement. And yet, when faced with the skills that candidates actually have and those that they&#39;re weak in, hiring managers find themselves making trade-offs, particularly to meet pressing technical needs: <em>This guy can code like there&#39;s no tomorrow, but his communication is a challenge. Let&#39;s get him in here fast. We&#39;ll coach him up. It can wait.</em></p><p> The thing is, communication skills <em>can&#39;t</em> wait. Executives in “people functions” like human resources and learning and development (L&amp;D) understand that communication and persuasion skills are critical in all areas of business — even software development and accounting. Those who design, manage, implement, and track employee development programs already know the business benefits of being adept at influencing colleagues and others in an organization.</p><p></p><p> So how do you also show the deep skeptics in your organization — for instance, data scientists who view the word <em>persuasion</em> with disdain, as a euphemism for <em>manipulation</em> — that a serious investment in communication skills is worth making?</p><p> You do it by making a solid case for the return on that investment. And you can take your cues from those folks in L&amp;D. They&#39;ve thought long and hard about ways to measure the ROI of their training programs and the best ways to communicate the benefits of those talents.</p><h3> A Measurement-Based Case for Better Soft Skills</h3><p> At a recent event for my company&#39;s customers, our executive vice president of customers led a panel discussion on the ways that large technical brands are building soft skills and what the ROI has been for them. Two L&amp;D executives shared what they&#39;ve discovered about conveying that value in their organizations: Catherine (Cat) Lang, who heads up product training and certification for customers and partners at ServiceNow, a digital workflow company based in Santa Clara, Calif.; and Noelle Anderson, the director of enablement at Snap, the parent company for visual messaging app Snapchat. Here are five key insights from their conversation.</p><h4> Collect examples of the ROI you&#39;ve seen from previous training.</h4><p> One way to start is to think back to previous learning efforts in your organization and see what dots you can connect for stakeholders. For instance, did an in-house workshop on presenting data precede a big win for your organization — like landing a lucrative project or winning a major client? Make that correlation explicit and point to others like it. You might already have more of an ROI track record for some of your soft skills training than you realize.</p><p></p><h4> Help identify the value of future training.</h4><p> When you&#39;re considering or developing future training, look for more direct ways to measure upskilling outcomes. At Snap, for instance, the enablement team has developed a pitch-coaching program in which salespeople, account managers, and creative strategists work together to develop pitches for existing clients. Participants receive lots of coaching and developmental feedback from seasoned communicators while formulating, framing, and practicing their pitches — a big incentive to sign up for the program. They also create real, measurable value by workshopping real pitch content.</p><p> The payoff — whether it&#39;s a renewed contract or the sale of a new product or service — is quantifiable. “What we&#39;ve done on the back end,” Anderson said, “is work with our CRM teams to create a check box in Salesforce to denote whether or not each presentation was part of our pitch program.” From there, the team can filter to see which pitches brought in revenue.</p><p> Although Anderson&#39;s group at Snap reports to the sales team rather than to corporate L&amp;D, they collaborate with L&amp;D as a “sister team” to identify and build soft skills needed on the sales side. That&#39;s an approach that can pay dividends in both directions: Teams throughout organizations can report back to L&amp;D with evidence of ROI in their areas, which supports further investment in companywide learning programs. For its part, the learning organization can share broader insights on what types of development drive employee satisfaction and retention. And L&amp;D can hone its skill-building programs in light of where teams are seeing the greatest impact on day-to-day performance and sales.</p><h4> Recognize qualitative impact — including better employee retention.</h4><p> Even with something like a pitch program in place, it&#39;s tough to tally up the costs of soft skills training in cold, hard dollars — especially when the training is conducted internally by HR staff members or informally by managers and colleagues. The benefits can be tricky to gauge, too, since much of the value in upskilling is indirect.</p><p> For instance, consider one of the pitch program&#39;s key benefits for employees: greater visibility with senior leadership. That pays off for both individuals and the organization, but not in a way that shows up immediately on the balance sheet. Anderson said that batches of pitches are developed and presented in rounds, and by the third round, the two groups with the best pitches get to present their ideas to the executive team for more feedback before sharing anything with clients.</p><p> Sure, these interactions with executives make the pitches themselves better. But think about the other benefits: They kick-start mentoring relationships, and they open up more development and growth opportunities and more doors to advancement — all of which can enhance the employee experience, motivation, and loyalty.</p><p> Can you quantify these results? Sometimes you can&#39;t, so you gauge value qualitatively. That can mean soliciting input from managers and team leaders on a training program&#39;s impact on employees&#39; behavior, effectiveness on the job, and approach to teamwork. Considering the qualitative impact from the employee&#39;s perspective is essential, too, because talent retention has major implications for ROI. For proof of why these intangibles matter, consider a <a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/03/09/majority-of-workers-who-quit-a-job-in-2021-cite-low-pay-no-opportunities-for-advancement-feeling-disrespected/">Pew Research Center 2022 survey</a> that found a tie between “no opportunities for advancement” and “pay was too low” as the top reasons US workers cited for leaving their jobs. Or consider the findings of LinkedIn&#39;s March 2022 “ <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220506202443/https://business.linkedin.com/glint/resources/employee-well-being-report-march-2022">Employee Well-Being Report</a> ,” which found the No. 1 driver of work culture to be “opportunities to learn and grow.”</p><p> Lang said that at ServiceNow, her team is “looking at employee retention and satisfaction with development” and tying those “very, very closely to our employee voice surveys as well” to get a holistic view of the effects of upskilling on retention. She said she saw “quick uptake as we started piloting new soft skills programs.” People have demonstrated keen interest in this type of upskilling at Snap, too: Anderson said employees view it as evidence that the company values them because it&#39;s “demonstrating [its] belief in an individual by investing in them and their development.” She also noted, “These are the types of skills that can help people internally get their own momentum, their own movement, and get their own thoughts put forth in a way in which folks will actually respond.”</p><h4> Strategize about which kinds of jobs to focus on first.</h4><p> Like any organizational change effort, upskilling a workforce requires strategic planning. To help such an initiative gain traction, it&#39;s useful to identify where you&#39;ll see the greatest immediate payoff and plan to concentrate there before you roll things out more broadly.</p><p></p><p> Lang&#39;s group at ServiceNow focuses first on people at the director and senior director levels because they have such a big say in how work gets done day to day and are responsible for keeping employees&#39; efforts aligned with organizational goals. The sooner they&#39;re communicating those goals clearly and framing performance objectives compellingly, the sooner the company will reap the rewards of hitting those targets. Attending to people at the director and senior director levels first also creates a cascade effect, equipping them to share what they&#39;re learning with their teams through one-on-one coaching, mentoring conversations, and even recommendations for courses or other learning content.</p><p> Snap, on the other hand, prefers to upskill front-line managers first, Anderson said. Because she oversees learning in a sales organization, where employees&#39; communication skills have an immediate impact on client relationships, the front line is where she sees the quickest return on investment.</p><h4> Address the time crunch head-on.</h4><p></p><p> Even if an organization&#39;s stakeholders agree that, in an ideal world, they should prioritize helping employees with soft skills, time constraints can make it tough. In the perennial battle between the important and the urgent, the urgent tends to win leaders&#39; attention and resources. Anderson described how what she calls “the here and now” sometimes gets in the way of broader learning goals at Snap: “There have been many classes where folks are like, &#39;I&#39;m so excited. I can&#39;t wait to go.&#39; And they show up, but then they have to drop out.” Work commitments and deadlines often tear people away.</p><p></p><p> One way to address that challenge culturally is by openly acknowledging it and showing how you can accommodate it in your learning schedule and course design. Create the expectation that it&#39;s more than OK for people to engage only as they&#39;re able. Think about dicing up the content into shorter modules or mini-workshops that busy employees can more easily digest. Set aside time in the workday for skill development. Learners need this type of support in the workplace, and the organization benefits too. If executives balk, remind them that making learning doable increases the ROI <em>and</em> shores up employee commitment to the organization in a tight labor market.</p><p> You might need to adjust project deadlines a bit or give people fewer tasks while they&#39;re doing development work so they don&#39;t feel pressure to do their “real” work after hours. Development <em>is</em> real work. Treat it that way as a manager — and discuss it that way with your stakeholders. It&#39;ll be an easier sell if you&#39;ve taken steps to help them see all of the benefits of the investment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/make-your-case-for-communication-upskilling/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>