<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 6 月 27 日星期二 11:51:49 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>沟通是积极员工关系的核心</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Laker. <p>Ben Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) 是雷丁大学亨利商学院的领导学教授，也是<cite>《Too Proud to Lead: How Hubris Can Destroy effective Leadership and What to Do About It》</cite> （Bloomsbury，2021 年）一书的合著者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[In today’s competitive job market, companies must focus not only on finding the best candidates but also on fostering positive relationships with them, starting with the first step of the recruitment process through every stage of employment. Communication is key to successfully creating those connections. How leaders communicate with prospective and current staff members can [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Laker_Communication-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>在当今竞争激烈的就业市场中，公司不仅要注重寻找最佳候选人，还要注重与他们建立积极的关系，从招聘流程的第一步开始，一直到就业的每个阶段。</p><p>沟通是成功建立这些联系的关键。领导者如何与未来和现任员工沟通可以极大地影响其组织作为人们愿意工作的地方的声誉。毕竟，拥有一种包含透明和开放沟通的文化对于建立信任和忠诚度至关重要。</p><p></p><h3>沟通技巧在招聘中的重要性</h3><p>研究表明，口头和书面<a href="https://newmanu.edu/top-5-skills-employers-look-for">沟通技巧</a>是潜在新员工最抢手的五项品质之一：雇主希望员工能够有效地表达自己的想法、观点和知识。</p><p>沟通能力强的员工能够清晰地表达自己的想法和情感，使他们在工作中更有效率。此外，他们能够通过认真倾听、提供准确反馈和解决冲突的能力，更好地管理与客户或同事之间具有挑战性的对话或谈判。</p><p>良好的沟通技巧还可以培养更好的公司文化：当员工能够有效地相互沟通时，他们会建立更牢固的联系。这不仅创造了一个有凝聚力和富有成效的工作环境，而且还提高了他们对组织的忠诚度。</p><p></p><p>招聘经理应筛选简历的清晰简洁的写作能力，并注意候选人在面试中的说话方式，以评估他们的沟通技巧。如果合适，他们应该在面试前索取书面作品样本，以评估候选人的写作能力。能够有效地以书面形式表达自己的资历和技能的候选人可能能够在面试过程中更好地以口头方式表达出来。</p><p></p><h3>招聘流程：明确的期望和公开的对话</h3><p>招聘过程中涉及的所有各方在传达信息时都需要清晰、简洁。招聘经理在与潜在候选人交谈时必须明确界定期望、角色和责任：一项研究发现，48% 提前离职的员工是因为雇主的<a href="https://www.hrdive.com/news/study-48-of-workers-have-left-a-job-because-it-didnt-meet-expectations/551179/">期望不明确</a>。</p><p>在招聘过程中与候选人建立公开对话对于建立信任和深入了解他们的沟通方式至关重要。通过结合使用开放式问题、角色扮演场景和注重沟通的练习，雇主可以更好地了解每位候选人的工作方法，并为牢固的工作关系奠定基础。</p><p>一旦新员工入职，提供有关其沟通技巧的反馈可以帮助他们了解自己在哪些方面已经做得很好以及哪些方面可以改进。</p><h3>应对裁员：透明度、同理心和合规性</h3><p>在经济衰退和裁员的时代，公司如何处理裁员可能对其声誉和员工士气产生深远影响。为了在裁员期间与员工保持积极的关系，雇主应优先考虑清晰、诚实和及时的沟通。这意味着尽可能提前向所有员工发出通知，解释决定背后的理由，并向受影响的员工提供支持，例如职业咨询、简历准备和求职帮助。通过尊重和同情员工，公司可以最大限度地减少负面影响并保持良好的声誉。</p><p>此外，组织必须遵守有关裁员的法律，以确保员工得到公平待遇并避免法律后果。雇主应了解其州和地方法律，以确保满足最低通知要求和其他法规。以 Bed Bath &amp; Beyond 为例，该公司最初决定绕过<a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bed-bath-beyond-to-pay-out-severance-to-1300-workers-after-initially-bypassing-law/ar-AA1aKgBG">遣散费法律</a>导致了诉讼，从而为一家最近宣布破产的公司带来了更多负面宣传，随后又撤销了该决定。</p><h3>创造开放沟通的文化</h3><p></p><p>与候选人和员工建立积极关系的关键在于营造开放沟通的文化。这意味着无论处于哪个就业阶段，都重视透明度、诚实和同理心。公司还应该鼓励组织各个级别之间的公开对话，为员工提供表达担忧和想法的机会。这有助于建立信任感，促进协作的工作环境，并最终为公司的整体成功做出贡献。</p><p>除了促进开放式沟通之外，雇主还应该投资培训和发展计划，帮助员工提高沟通技巧。这对个人有利，有助于营造更有效、更有凝聚力的工作环境，并最终为组织带来更大的成功，并在整体上创造更高效的工作环境。通过在员工生命周期的每个阶段优先考虑沟通，管理者可以培养积极的工作文化，让员工感到受到重视、支持并被赋予成功的权力。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/communication-is-at-the-heart-of-positive-employee-relationships/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>是时候面对学习的三大挑战了</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Lynda Gratton. <p>Lynda Gratton ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lyndagratton">@lyndagratton</a> ) 是伦敦商学院管理实践教授，也是咨询实践 HSM 的创始人。她的最新著作是<cite>《重新设计工作：如何转型您的组织并为每个人提供混合工作》</cite> （麻省理工学院出版社，2022 年）。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Virtual Teams]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Michael Austin/theispot.com Most executives acknowledge that learning is crucial to the performance of their business. But at a recent research workshop that my team and I ran with executives from over 40 companies, it became clear that organizations’ traditional learning models are facing pressure from the emergence of new work models. The participants identified these [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023-0626_Gratton_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">迈克尔·奥斯汀/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>大多数高管承认学习对其业务绩效至关重要。但在我和我的团队与来自 40 多家公司的高管最近举办的一次研究研讨会上，我们发现组织的传统学习模式正面临着新工作模式出现的压力。参与者认为这三个学习挑战是最严峻的：</p><p> <strong>1.工作量增加，学习时间减少。</strong>我们研讨会上 88% 的高管选择工作压力作为他们面临的最大挑战之一。他们表示，许多员工，尤其是那些管理他人的员工，感觉近年来他们的工作量显着增加。一些人分享的敏感内部数据表明，在此期间，倦怠有所增加。工作量增加的最终结果是，员工不仅缺乏学习的空间，而且还感到有压力将工作任务置于学习活动之上。应对这一挑战需要领导者最大限度地利用任何可用学习时间的价值。</p><p></p><p> <strong>2.混合工作增加了学习的复杂性。</strong>三分之二 (66%) 的高管表示，员工工作地点和时间的灵活性是一个重要的挑战。高管们担心，员工在正式和非正式学习的重要时刻可能无法保持联系。经理们表示，他们发现为远程员工寻找发展机会变得更加困难，并且他们担心远程工作会对人们共享隐性知识的方式产生负面影响。事实上，研究表明 47% 的员工担心在家工作时<a href="https://newsroom.poly.com/English/press-releases/news-details/2021/Poly-Evolution-of-the-Workplace-Report-Highlights-Need-for-Work-Equity-and-Total-Meeting-Equality-for-Hybrid-Workers/">错过非正式学习机会</a>。应对这一挑战需要领导者在混合业务环境中制定稳健的学习策略。</p><p> <strong>3.劳动力市场趋紧带来技能短缺。</strong> 65% 的高管认为寻找具有专业技能的员工是一项重大挑战。我们采访的许多高管表示，他们的公司历来都在外部劳动力市场寻找这些专业人才。然而，随着市场收紧，特别是对于难以找到的数字技能，重点已转移到提高内部员工的技能。重新培训一直被认为很重要，但现在变得至关重要。应对这一挑战需要领导者将业务战略与熟练执行的技能提升和再培训计划结合起来。</p><p>尽管这些都是严峻的挑战，但高管们也承认解决这些挑战是多么重要。技能短缺是原因之一，但成功的企业学习也具有重大的激励作用。</p><p>在当今动荡的劳动力市场中，员工会迅速从一份工作转向更有利的工作机会，学习未来有价值的新知识的机会是他们留下来的主要原因。事实上，研究表明，76% 的员工表示，如果能够从学习和发展支持中受益，他们会<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work-is-just-work">在工作岗位上呆更长时间</a>。</p><p>此外，面对对工作场所不平等现象日益增长的担忧，人们认为<a href="https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/files/5552_en.pdf">基于技能的学习</a>有助于显着减少不平等现象。对于那些不胸怀大志、没有大学学位或教育证书、或者历史上被排除在外的员工来说尤其如此。</p><p></p><h3>公司如何重新学习如何学习</h3><p>因此，这是一个悖论：当学习被视为许多公​​司业务战略的重要组成部分时，那些负责实施学习议程的人却描述了重大的艰苦战斗。</p><p>尽管如此，我还是看到管理者们所做的实验，他们通过尝试新的学习方式和新的学习方式来应对这种情况，这些方式可以为处于类似情况的其他人树立榜样。以下是他们解决三个基本问题的方法。</p><h4> 1.他们利用个性化来最大化学习时间的价值。</h4><p>确保学习的每一个小时都有意义的一种方法是使学习与学习者的具体需求紧密结合。这种个性化通常很难大规模提供。但虚拟和在线教学的实验开辟了个性化学习的途径。</p><p>一种方法是制定学习计划或途径。总部位于都柏林的 Matheson 律师事务所的学习团队提供 12 种学习途径（每年变化）供员工选择，例如客户体验或环境、社会和公司治理问题。每个途径都融合了参与核心项目和由主题专家员工提供的教程。一项重要的创新是律师和商业服务员工都可以使用这些途径。学习团队的一名成员告诉我，该方法旨在打破这些社区之间的传统孤岛，并将学习嵌入到工作的自然流程中。</p><p></p><p>其他组织已经通过使用人工智能驱动的职业诊断来完成个性化学习的任务。埃森哲开发了一款名为 Job Buddy 的人工智能工具，帮助员工根据自身、团队和外部劳动力市场的数据制定个人学习计划。该工具旨在使用机器学习算法根据个人当前的工作、技能和经验来建议职业道路和技能提升机会。在进行个人诊断后，学习平台提供了在线课程、研讨会和指导计划等资源。</p><h4> 2.他们倾向于混合体验。</h4><p>这场大流行增加了混合工作的流行，并为学习和工作一样灵活创造了条件。</p><p></p><p>在全球在线市场 Etsy，同伴学习始终是重中之重。 Etsy 战略和运营副总裁 Zofia Ciechowska 告诉我，学习被视为员工甚至供应商与社区分享知识、技能或工艺的机会。员工开设的课程涉及广泛的主题，包括如何乘坐东京地铁系统以及如何制作蜡烛等。种类繁多的课程反映了 Etsy 的文化和使命，即通过让人们展示自己的才能并相互教育来保持商业“人性化”。</p><p>至关重要的是，本着混合工作的精神，Etsy 的研讨会以面对面和在线形式进行。员工无论工作安排如何，都能够充分参与。这个丰富的基于社区的学习计划成功地推动了非正式联系，激发了好奇心，并提高了员工敬业度。</p><p>学习团队表示，看到双向学习流的好处（对于受教者和授课者来说）是令人着迷的。员工有机会展示自己的热情，并通过分享他们引以为豪的知识与同事互动。</p><h4> 3. 他们通过关注可转移技能来减少技能短缺。</h4><p>面对劳动力市场趋紧和技能短缺，最明显的学习策略是专注于对现有员工进行再培训，而不是招聘新员工。正如许多高管所分享的那样，挑战在于这是极其困难的，尤其是在规模上。</p><p>作为一家国际银行，汇丰银行正在不断变化，而重新培训对于实现其战略计划至关重要。该银行正在努力确保所有员工都具备职业发展所需的技能和知识，以便他们现在和未来都能取得成功。</p><p>该银行最近为想要从事财富服务职业的内部候选人推出了一项基于技能的发展计划。通过在三到九个月的时间里花费 20% 的工作时间，参与者能够识别、评估和发展他们在银行财富和私人银行服务业务中担任关系经理角色所需的可转移技能。</p><p></p><p> “这一开创性计划正在帮助我们为我们业务的一个非常重要的部分建立战略人才管道，”汇丰银行财富和个人银行及全球职能全球人力资源主管劳拉·鲍威尔(Laura Powell)表示。汇丰银行计划在今年晚些时候将该计划扩展到外部候选人。</p><p></p><p>在参加我们的学习研究研讨会的高管中，只有 2% 的人表示他们相信讲师主导的学习将是他们组织未来发展的优先事项。相反，39% 的人表示“在工作流程中”学习更为重要。</p><p>显而易见的是，虽然一些更传统的学习形式正在减少，但实验和新项目正在证明如何克服重大挑战。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/its-time-to-face-the- Three-challenges-of-learning/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>如何帮助患有多动症的员工应对远程工作的挑战</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Maria Hamdani, Najma Hamdani, and Maitraye Das. <p>Maria Hamdani 博士是阿克伦大学商学院管理学教授。 Najma Hamdani 博士是一位在俄克拉荷马州和德克萨斯州执业的精神科医生。 Maitraye Das 博士是东北大学 Khoury 计算机科学学院和艺术、媒体与设计学院的助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Neurodiversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Editor’s note: In consultation with the authors, this article was updated June 26, 2023, to better reflect the views of the neurodiversity movement. Flexible work arrangements, such as hybrid and remote models, have become important for talent acquisition and retention in the post-pandemic world. As organizations refine their virtual work practices, it is important to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Hamdani-ADHD-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p><em>编者注：经与作者协商，本文于 2023 年 6 月 26 日更新，以更好地反映神经多样性运动的观点。</em></p><p>灵活的工作安排，例如混合和远程模式，对于大流行后世界的人才获取和保留变得重要。随着组织完善其虚拟工作实践，重要的是要确保它们包容神经分歧的员工。注意力缺陷/多动障碍 (ADHD) 是最常见的神经发散病症之一。虽然一些患有多动症的人可能会发现远程工作非常适合他们的需求，并使他们能够更好地控制自己的工作环境，但其他人可能会发现远程工作带来了独特的挑战。远程工作通常缺乏具体的时间线索，并且可能会引入与面对面办公室环境不同的干扰和共享信息的方法，这对于一些患有多动症的人来说可能是一个挑战。如果这些挑战得不到有效管理，可能会导致一系列问题，例如倦怠、焦虑、生产力下降、缺乏动力，并最终导致辞职。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p>经理可以与患有多动症的员工合作实施简单的策略，以更好地根据他们的需求定制远程工作。由于员工可能未被诊断或选择不透露他们的神经分歧状况，因此我们在下面建议的五种基于证据的干预措施可以帮助促进更好的远程工作实践，从而造福所有员工。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>但在我们更详细地讨论这些之前，让我们先简单讨论一下多动症。</p><p></p><h3>了解多动症</h3><p>ADHD 源于大脑区域的结构差异以及细胞和神经机制的变化，这些变化对目标导向行为的日常自我调节提出了挑战。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a>因此，多动症患者的注意力、时间管理、工作记忆、反应抑制和奖励心理处理等执行功能的运作方式存在不同程度的差异。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a>这些执行流程共同作用，帮助我们将更大的目标、愿景、知识和技能转化为生活各个方面（包括工作）的日常目标导向行动。一些患有多动症的人可能会发现他们的差异会扰乱这些以目标为导向的行动，即使他们拥有清晰的愿景、知识、技能和动机。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>虽然药物可以帮助调节注意力、抑制力和工作记忆，但涵盖五个日常行为维度的包容性工作实践和调整可以帮助释放潜力并为成功创造条件。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a></p><p>成人多动症常常未被充分诊断，因为人们错误地认为这只是一种儿童时期的诊断，或者是所有儿童最终都会长大后摆脱的诊断。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a>诊断不足的性别和种族差异会带来额外的并发症。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>未经诊断和治疗的多动症可能会导致继发性焦虑和抑郁，以及在个人和集体层面造成重大甚至有时是毁灭性的损失，包括生产力损失、医疗保健费用、失业、司法系统影响以及家庭成员的溢出成本。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>正确的多动症诊断和包容性工作实践可以降低这些成本，并使多动症患者能够过上更充实的工作和个人生活。</p><p></p><p> ADHD 的性别差异经常被忽视，这扩大了女性的诊断和治疗差距。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>男性被诊断为多动症的可能性是女性的三倍，而且他们通常在更年轻的时候被诊断出来。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>许多早期教育工作者错误地认为多动症主要是针对男孩的诊断，因此对女孩的诊断不足。男性通常表现出多动症和问题的外在表现（例如课堂混乱或与同龄人打架），而女性通常将注意力不集中的症状内化，表现出低自尊、焦虑和抑郁。这使得女性的检测和转诊更具挑战性，她们可能被误诊为焦虑或抑郁，而不是多动症。在工作场所，患有注意力缺陷多动症的女性可能会感到不知所措和得不到支持，随之而来的自卑和对截止日期或项目细节的焦虑，或担心犯错误，可能会导致生产力下降、绩效下降和错失职业机会。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>多动症资源用于更好地理解</h4><ul><li>美国国家心理健康研究所：“<a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/adhd-what-you-need-to-know">成人注意力缺陷/多动症：您需要了解的内容</a>”</li><li>患有注意力缺陷/多动症的儿童和成人：“<a href="https://chadd.org/for-adults/diagnosis-of-adhd-in-adults/">成人多动症的诊断</a>”</li><li>疾病控制和预防中心：“<a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/adhd/diagnosis.html">多动症的症状和诊断</a>”</li><li> Russell A. Barkley 和 Christine M. Benton： <cite><a href="https://www.guilford.com/books/Taking-Charge-of-Adult-ADHD/Russell-Barkley/9781462546855">掌控成人多动症：在工作、家庭和人际关系中取得成功的行之有效的策略</a></cite></li></ul></article></aside></div><h3>实施包容性虚拟工作实践</h3><p>以下包容性虚拟工作实践使用简单的工具和可行的管理策略来创建一个工作环境，让员工能够坚持做他们已经知道如何做的事情。围绕这些建议调整虚拟工作实践可以提高所有员工的生产力。也就是说，神经分歧的员工通常知道什么条件最有利于他们的工作效率，并且应该就影响他们的工作实践的改变进行咨询。 </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>提高生产力的包容性虚拟工作实践</h4><p class="caption">在远程工作环境中，领导者可以采用这些方法来提高所有员工的工作效率，无论他们是否被诊断出患有多动症。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023-06-22_Hamdani_Figure.png" alt="提高生产力的包容性虚拟工作实践"><br /></article></aside></div><p></p><h4> 1. 时间管理和计划</h4><p>虽然患有注意力缺陷多动症的人可以有效地制定一个大目标或愿景，但他们中的一些人可能会在日常细节中挣扎，这在很大程度上是由于<em>时间盲目性</em>，这是一种对时间的扭曲认知。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a>这可能会导致难以及时组织活动来完成日常任务和满足需求，以及拖延、错过最后期限、忘记和未完成的任务以及多任务处理困难。在远程工作模式中，时间管理尤其具有挑战性，因为缺乏外部时间线索（例如开车上班或午休时间），并且这些环境中的日常监督和问责制较弱。</p><p>为了支持计划和时间管理，管理者应该使用易于访问的日常计划工具，结合他们的报告，将大目标转化为日常的、可操作的部分。他们还可以创建每日问责系统，例如同行签到或每日进度图表。使用有形的时间标记来标记时间的流逝，例如在家庭办公桌上放一个时钟，安排每日提醒来开始一项任务，以及设置计时器来完成任务，然后休息，也有帮助。只要有可能，管理者就应该考虑延长最后期限，以解决时间感知方面的困难。</p><p>与虚拟团队合作时，经理应平衡会议安排和生产力期望。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>仔细考虑每周需要举行多少次团队会议，并在可能的情况下使用异步通信来帮助员工在他们喜欢的时间执行分配的任务。实施一种混合模式，让人们有时去办公室参加会议，其他时间留在家里（或在无干扰的办公空间）专注工作，这可能是平衡生产力与会议安排的可行选择。</p><h4> 2. 心理组织和工作记忆</h4><p>由于工作记忆的差异，一些患有注意力缺陷多动症的成年人可能会受益于使用外部工具进行简单的计算，在解决问题时牢记多条信息，在沟通时整理思绪，并记得回电话或赴约。为了支持心理组织，鼓励使用外部工具将重要信息带入视野，例如每日清单、便利贴、书面说明、颜色编码的视觉提示和清晰可见的截止日期。</p><p>由于信息共享的速度和数量，远程工作可能会造成精神负担，并让人感到不知所措。必须在一天内参加多个虚拟会议（其中可以包含视频、音频、文本聊天和文件共享的组合）可能特别困难，特别是对于神经分歧的员工而言。</p><p>与其营造一种每个人都争夺发言机会的竞争氛围，不如考虑如何使虚拟会议更加包容和包容。例如，会议组织者可以正式制定轮流例程，让人们在发言前有时间整理思绪；安排提问和回答的暂停时间；并关闭大型群体的聊天功能，以尽量减少分散注意力的串扰。提前分享材料并在事后分发笔记、录音和文字记录对于那些发现很难在记笔记的同时注意对话的人特别有帮助。</p><h4> 3.长期任务的自我激励</h4><p>某些患有注意力缺陷多动症的人可能会发现，在没有立即奖励的情况下，在漫长的任务中很难保持积极性和专注力。管理者可以鼓励这些员工将较大的任务分解为较小的步骤，并设定最小的期限和奖励。例如，设定 30 分钟或一小时的目标，并用小奖励来庆祝每一项成就，例如一杯咖啡或到外面散步。为这些休息时间设置计时器以返回工作非常重要； <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-managers-can-help-workers-tackle-digital-distractions/">番茄工作法</a>可以作为一个有用的模型。</p><p>为了对抗“Zoom 疲劳”，在连续会议之间留出过渡时间，并在较长的会议期间提供休息时间以调节注意力。这种方法将有助于防止员工走神，并帮助他们补充精神能量。</p><h4> 4.抑制冲动</h4><p>患有多动症的人可能难以控制冲动，导致他们做出不恰当的反应、做出冲动的评论、打断别人、说话过多、情绪反应、等待困难或不能迅速识别和纠正错误。在社交线索有限的偏远环境中，这些挑战可能更加突出。</p><p>采用辅导和反馈模式可以提高员工对冲动行为的自我意识。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a>建立融洽关系的做法，例如使用工作方式偏好调查，可以帮助管理者找到提高生产力并最大限度地减少神经分歧员工的挫败感的方法。 <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a>记住要富有同情心，给予员工恩典；走神或说话不按顺序等行为并不是由于懒惰或恶意，而是源于信息处理方式的差异。</p><p></p><p>考虑在显眼的位置张贴最佳实践指南，以提供清晰的行动框架。同样，纳入数字<a href=" https://chadd.org/adhd-news/adhd-news-adults/could-a-body-double-help-you-increase-your-productivity/">身体加倍</a>等生产力策略，员工可以通过虚拟协同办公应用程序（例如 Flown 或 Focusmate）与其他人一起工作来完成他们觉得令人沮丧的任务，以帮助保持对手头任务的专注。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>此外，在日常生活中鼓励定期体育锻炼和平静练习对于帮助人们补充自我控制和抑制冲动所需的精神资源至关重要。</p><h4> 5.注意力、集中力和焦点</h4><p>远程工作充满<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-managers-can-help-workers-tackle-digital-distractions/">干扰</a>，需要特殊考虑才能提高注意力。为了增强注意力并减少无聊，可以考虑提供可调节的桌子、膝椅、摇椅和活动座椅。安排休息时间可以帮助人们避免走神，并且当他们在办公室时，提供安静的空间以尽量减少干扰。考虑提供辅助技术来帮助完成任务，例如听写工具、录音软件和降噪耳机，这可以帮助所有员工在远程和混合环境中提高工作效率。</p><p></p><p>我们的研究发现了其他策略，可以帮助减少虚拟工作空间中的干扰。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a>让与会者使用统一或模糊的背景有助于最大限度地减少背景噪音并减少视觉触发。为员工提供关闭摄像头的选项（至少在会议的某些部分）可能会对那些可能过度担心自己的面部表情或因自己的面部表情而分心的人有所帮助。经理们还应该注意在线会议期间提供的大量信息，并且应该允许员工要求澄清，以便在分散注意力后重新集中注意力。</p><p></p><p>多动症会影响人们在生活的许多方面的表现能力，包括在线工作环境。患有诊断的个人有不同的需求，从不需要任何便利到需要合理的个性化便利。诊断中的性别和种族差异、获得护理的障碍以及耻辱加剧了多动症对个人和职业领域整体福祉的成本。通过采用包容性工作实践，组织可以更好地支持和利用多元化劳动力的人才，否则这些人才可能会被边缘化和未得到充分利用。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-help-employees-with-adhd-address-the-challenges-of-remote-work/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>专注于培养员工队伍的技能</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aneesh Raman and Elyse Rosenblum. <p>Aneesh Raman 是 LinkedIn 副总裁兼机会项目负责人。 <a href="https://gradsoflife.org/team-members/elyse-rosenblum/">Elyse Rosenblum</a>是 Grads of Life 的创始人兼董事总经理。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[As the threat of an economic downturn looms, we are entering the fourth consecutive year of uncertainty and rapid change. Three years ago, a global pandemic upended supply chains, and quarantines transformed how we work. Months later, a racial justice reckoning compelled businesses to make unprecedented commitments to building inclusive organizations. Sustained remote work again [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Raman-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>随着经济衰退的威胁迫在眉睫，我们正在进入不确定性和快速变化的连续第四年。三年前，一场全球大流行颠覆了供应链，隔离改变了我们的工作方式。几个月后，种族正义的清算迫使企业做出前所未有的承诺，<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/inclusive-hiring-to-build-better-teams-period/">建立包容性组织</a>。持续的远程工作再次挑战了工作场所的现状，并在某些情况下成为了无障碍的工具。持续紧张的劳动力市场迫使企业重新考虑并调整其吸引顶尖人才的努力。现在，人工智能的进步将重塑每个行业几乎所有工作所需的技能组合。</p><p>所有这些变化使人力资源成为高管对话的中心，雇主对如何发现、培养和发展人才有了不同的思考。很快，技能就开始主导对话。从 2021 年 10 月到 2022 年 10 月，LinkedIn 网络平台上提及技能优先相关主题的帖子平均数量大约增加了一倍。雇主正在努力将技能置于其人才战略的中心——从招聘到晋升——这一点可以证明<a href="http://www.oneten.org/">OneTen</a>和<a href="https://www.businessroundtable.org/workforceskills">商业圆桌会议</a>等团体。由于许多商界普遍谈论可能出现的经济衰退，一个关键问题悬而未决：雇主如何保持对技能优先方法不断增长的投资，以最大限度地提高工人和企业的投资回报？</p><p></p><p> LinkedIn 的新数据为加倍努力以技能为先提供了令人信服的案例。 《 <a href="https://learning.linkedin.com/resources/workplace-learning-report">2023 年工作场所学习报告》</a>显示，Z 世代和千禧一代员工最有可能重视职业发展和技能建设的机会，甚至超过了工作与生活的平衡。调查结果还显示，内部流动性已成为最高管理层领导者的第二大劳动力优先事项，学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 领导者表示与高管的合作比以往任何时候都更加密切。</p><p>随着最年轻的员工要求技能驱动的职业道路和高管的关注，未能维持对技能优先人才战略投资的企业将被抛在后面。然而，在经济放缓期间，人们有一种倾向，即退缩并恢复到旧的、可预测的模式和策略。从本质上讲，企业的生存本能迫使许多人选择停滞而不是创新。在 2008 年经济大衰退期间，以前要求教育程度较低的工作坚持要求大学学位的做法（即所谓的<a href="https://www.hbs.edu/managing-the-future-of-work/Documents/dismissed-by-degrees.pdf">学位膨胀</a>）加速了。这种倒退通过增加招聘成本和流动率直接损害了企业的利润，同时加剧了少数人受益而多数人失去机会的经济格局。</p><p></p><h3>扩大多元化人才的机会</h3><p>如今，即使经济前景仍然不确定，企业领导者有机会以不同的方式做事，而且他们在扩大技能优先战略方面处于更有利的地位。无论您仍在努力吸引人才，还是您的招聘已显着降温，都有一些方法可以将技能优先的方法嵌入到您业务的各个方面，即使在经济放缓期间，也可以推动更强劲的长期成果。</p><p>寻找人员来填补空缺职位过去是一个繁琐的手动过程。如果没有复杂的方法来根据实际技能寻找和培养人才，大学学位就成为雇主用来验证候选人是否具备某些技能和能力的少数生硬工具之一，但它却将<a href="https://www.bls.gov/cps/cpsaat07.htm">大多数美国人排除在外。劳动力</a>，尤其是有色人种工人。</p><p>如今，我们可以使用比以往更多的数据来准确确定我们所需的技能，然后找到拥有这些技能的人员（无论是内部人员还是外部人员）。 <a href="https://economicgraph.linkedin.com/research/skills-first-report">LinkedIn 的数据</a>显示，接受这种转变并注重技能的组织可以看到巨大的影响：LinkedIn 上采取技能优先方法的组织可以将其人才管道扩大近 10 倍。雇主已经开始意识到这一点：LinkedIn 上超过 45% 的企业现在<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/skills-new-currency-ryan-roslansky/">明确使用技能数据</a>来填补空缺职位。</p><p></p><p>为了建立未来所需的多元化、高职能团队，雇主必须关注技能——这种方法对人才管道多元化也产生巨大影响。当雇主要求某职位拥有大学学位时，他们会自动排除 60% 的美国人，其中包括 76% 的非裔美国人和 83% 的拉美裔美国人。</p><p>从职位描述中删除不必要的学位要求是基于技能的人才获取的基础，但这还不够。人才招聘领导者还必须投资扩大采购渠道并修改招聘材料中的语言，以确保其包容性和吸引力。此外，面试问题和招聘流程应以第一天的职位所需的基本技能为基础，而不仅仅是证书或经验，并且应有意且公平地制定这些技能，以揭示这些技能。</p><h3>投资于学习和内部流动</h3><p>虽然聘用具备合适技能的新员工是技能投资的一种方式，但我们有机会重新关注支持现有员工的成长和发展，尤其是在招聘降温的行业。 LinkedIn 工作场所学习报告的最新调查结果表明，鉴于有效地将人才重新部署到优先业务领域的紧迫性再次凸显，2023 年可能成为扩大技能提升和内部流动计划的重要一年。事实上，调查结果显示，预算预测依然强劲，41% 的 L&amp;D 领导者预计今年的消费能力更强，只有 8% 的人预计预算会减少。</p><p>现在为员工投资技能和基于技能的职业道路可以带来回报。 LinkedIn 的调查结果显示，公司在三年内<a href="https://business.linkedin.com/talent-solutions/global-talent-trends">学习了工作技能的</a>员工保留率提高了近 7%。根据工作场所学习报告，在两年内进行过内部调动的员工有 75% 的可能性留在公司，而角色没有改变的员工有 56% 的可能性继续留在公司。</p><p>与技能优先的招聘类似，技能优先的人才管理要求公司对现有流程进行一系列补充性改变并投资新流程。推动技能优先的内部流动性的关键一步是定义特定角色所需和首选的技能以及跨角色的技能如何重叠。从那里，领导者可以帮助他们的团队建立稳健的职业道路，使员工能够通过培养和应用与其目标相符的技能来实现职业发展。最后，整个企业——更重要的是直接与员工——就可用的职业道路和获得这些职业道路所需的技能进行沟通和透明度，对于提高保留率和晋升率至关重要。</p><p>虽然技能提升和再技能计划的势头正在增强，但显然需要加快进展。 LinkedIn的调查结果显示，40%的公司仍处于早期阶段，向利益相关者出售他们的项目并组建他们的团队； 54% 处于中期阶段，正在开发和启动项目；只有 2% 的人表示他们已经完成了一个项目。百分之四的人根本没有开始。</p><p></p><p>除了运营变革之外，培育包容性、以学习为导向的文化也是公司正在做出的核心转变。通过与领先雇主客户的合作，Grads of Life 了解到，要确保代表性不足群体的员工留在公司并在公司内成长，需要的不仅仅是对 L&amp;D 的财务投资。该组织的研究揭示了黑人人才与白人人才<a href="https://gradsoflife.org/equity-career-advancement-insights-from-underrepresented-employees/">在薪酬和晋升方面存在差异</a>。至关重要的是，除了运营变革之外，组织还应投资变革管理并消除薪酬和晋升系统中的偏见，以加强组织文化。对于大多数雇主来说，采用基于技能的方法来招聘和保留人才与现状有很大不同，而面临将其付诸实践的实施团队需要指导、培训和支持才能取得成功。</p><p></p><p></p><p>在阴云密布的经济预测中，首席执行官们正在谨慎地平衡哪些方面要撤退，哪些方面要加倍努力。投资于技能优先的方法来培养优秀人才并培养他们已有的优秀人才不仅可以帮助他们度过当前的风暴。将技能作为公司战略的核心将使您的员工队伍在所有工作不断变化的世界中保持长期的适应力。</p><p> LinkedIn 的数据显示，自 2015 年以来，<a href="https://linkedin.github.io/future-of-skills/#explore">工作技能组合已经发生了约 25% 的变化</a>，到 2027 年，这一比例将翻倍——这意味着今天的工作所需的核心技能与仅仅几年前的同一份工作看起来非常不同前。今天，我们即将进入的人工智能新时代可能会进一步加速这一变化，82% 的领导者承认他们的员工将需要新技能来<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/will-ai-fix-work">采用人工智能的新工作</a>方式。</p><p>现在，当大海波涛汹涌时，那些准备在这个新的工作世界中取得成功的企业领导人将展示如何做到这一点。现在不是等待更好的条件来做出改变的时候。对于企业来说，现在是更新思维、通过关注技能型劳动力来应对挑战的最佳时机。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/focus-on-skills-to-grow-your-workforce/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>人工智能的社会科学：英特尔的 Elizabeth Anne Watkins</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI Augmentation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Relationships]]></category><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Human-Machine Collaboration]]></category><category><![CDATA[Manufacturing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data & Data Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Implementation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[When Elizabeth Anne Watkins started her doctoral program, she landed a research role studying journalists’ use of security and privacy technologies — but she found the security tools confusing and difficult to use. Today, as a research scientist in the social science of AI at Intel Labs, she advocates for other end users faced with [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>当伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins) 开始她的博士课程时，她获得了一份研究记者使用安全和隐私技术的研究职位，但她发现这些安全工具令人困惑且难以使用。如今，作为英特尔实验室人工智能社会科学的研究科学家，她倡导其他最终用户理解和使用新技术。</p><p>伊丽莎白利用社会科学来了解执行复杂芯片制造流程的技术人员所关心的问题，以便开发新的人工智能系统，更好地为这些人类专家服务。在此过程中，她还帮助技术人员认识到人工智能作为支持技术（甚至是同事）的角色，而不是人类的替代品。</p><p>她加入了<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客的这一集，讨论了她作为一名从事技术工作的社会科学家的角色，以及英特尔应用计算机视觉和自然语言处理等人工智能技术来改进半导体制造工艺的一些方式。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-s7-e2-Watkins-intel-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯"></p><h4>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯，英特尔</h4><p>Elizabeth Anne Watkins 是英特尔实验室的研究科学家，也是负责任的人工智能咨询委员会的成员。她推动社会科学方法的战略和执行，以放大人类在人类与人工智能协作中的潜力，并在计算机视觉、自然语言处理等人工智能工具的设计、部署和治理中进行可信度、可解释性、透明度和代理性的研究。机器人技术。</p><p>沃特金斯是数据与社会研究所 AI on the Ground 的附属机构，曾与学术界和工业界的研究中心合作、咨询和合作。她在哥伦比亚大学获得了博士学位，在麻省理工学院获得了硕士学位，并且是普林斯顿大学信息技术政策中心及其人机交互小组的博士后研究员。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><div id="toolkit-watkins"></div><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我们知道人工智能工具正在增强人类的表现，但人们对此有何真实感受？在今天的节目中，了解一家公司如何在开发人工智能工具时考虑到最终用户。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>我是来自英特尔的伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯，您正在聆听<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> 。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>欢迎。今天我们有一位伟大的客人：伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯 (Elizabeth Anne Watkins)，英特尔的研究科学家。伊丽莎白，感谢您今天加入我们。让我们开始吧。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>非常感谢您今天邀请我。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>作为全球最大的半导体制造商，英特尔可能是大多数人都知道的公司，但您能否向我们介绍一下英特尔实验室的概况，以及您的具体角色？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>就像你说的，在目前围绕人工智能、人工智能行业和人工智能领域的大型讨论中，我们并不总是最受关注的，但英特尔内部正在开展许多令人着迷的工作，而且我们有这样的工作对这个领域的独特视角以及进入该领域的独特方式，我很高兴今天在我们的谈话中透露其中的一些内容。</p><p>我于去年八月刚刚加入英特尔，与如此多不同的团队会面真是一次令人难以置信的经历。我加入英特尔，担任人工智能社会科学领域的研究科学家，并在英特尔实验室的 Lama Nachman 手下工作。该小组称为智能系统研究。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>伊丽莎白，您提到英特尔实验室正在利用人工智能做一些独特的事情。您介意与我们分享您正在做的一些事情吗？</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins：</strong>我特别兴奋的一个项目叫做 MARIE，是工业环境中多模式活动识别的缩写。基本上，我将从一个比喻开始：想象一下，你的计算机可以看着你组装，比如说，你在互联网上订购的一件家具。当你读到手册的困难部分时，或者你拿着螺丝刀，你拿着一块胶合板，而你无法回到手册，想象一下你的计算机可以看到你在做什么，知道手册将告诉您做什么，然后帮助您将这两者联系起来。想象一下，你的计算机实际上可以告诉你，“嘿，我想你要把架子 A 拧到支架 B 上”，或者类似的东西。我知道，每次我收到他们说里面有一把扶手椅的扁平包装时，从 A 地到 B 地对我来说都是一段非常艰难的时期。</p><p>我们的员工正在我们的工厂内进行类似的流程，他们实际上是在工厂中构建和制造半导体芯片。因此，在我们工厂内部工作的人们，我们的技术人员，正在做非常复杂和非常精细的工作，处理工厂车间发生的各种手动操作的零件和工具。因此，他们所做的所有工作都与将扁平包装放入扶手椅一样复杂，有时甚至更复杂。涉及到很多工具。有各种不同的工艺、不同的设备、不同尺寸的设备。因此，我们正在构建有点像我所描述的计算机系统，“嘿，你的意思是把螺丝 A 放入支架 B 中吗？”我们正在构建系统来帮助工厂内部的人员完成这种非常仔细且非常复杂的工作。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>实际上，这是一个有趣的类比。我的意思是，我认为我们都觉得扁平包装具有挑战性，尽管我不得不承认我有点喜欢它们。但我确信英特尔内部的情况要复杂得多。我喜欢这个例子的是，我觉得我们经常谈论自动化：我们能让机器学习如何做人类做的事情吗？这就是机器学习 [ML] 的核心。然后我们讨论增强，以及机器如何帮助人类做出决定？这让我觉得有点不同。这是下一步。</p><p>因此，在这种情况下，我们并不试图让机器组装扁平包装。我们并不是想让机器来组装半导体。仍然是人类在做这件事。因此，人类需要在这里学习。这似乎比我们之前讨论的更进一步了。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>我很高兴你明白这一点，山姆。这正是我们在英特尔实验室内谈论的内容：人就是专家。人类知道如何与这些系统交互，并且知道如何将各个部分组合在一起。他们知道将这些微小且非常精密的组件组装在一起所需的所有物理和动态复杂性。</p><p>我们不想训练计算机来做这件事。计算机<em>无法</em>做到这一点。组装和清洁过程的方式——当然，因为所有这些过程都在这些超级洁净的房间内进行，每个人都必须穿着防护服和手套……我们希望支持正在做这件事的人。没有计算机可以做到这一点。这需要人类的判断；需要人类的专业知识才能以全面、真正动态的方式完成这些过程，并能够应对新的压力。</p><p>如果机器的较大部件以特定方式弯曲，或者螺钉以特定方式掉入孔中，那么计算机还需要很多很多年才能评估、诊断和解决这些持续的动态问题。但你知道真正擅长做到这一点的是人类。因此，我们正在努力以人类为中心，以人类的专业知识为中心。这表明了我对玛丽感到非常兴奋的双重原因，那就是它既有技术的一面，也有人性的一面。在技​​术方面，我认为 MARIE 真的很令人兴奋，因为它是多式联运的。它通过环境传感结合了许多不同类型的人工智能系统。它将使用活动识别的计算机视觉与音频传感以及自然语言处理 [NLP] 相结合，有助于在技术人员周围构建周围环境，最终帮助他们完成工作。</p><p>但在系统能够帮助他们所做的事情之前，系统必须实际学习，而人类专家正在教系统如何学习并教系统需要知道的知识。据我所知，这是一种将人工智能系统部署到新领域并将其应用于新问题的全新方式。 ……我们正在面临并解决人工智能发展的一大挑战，那就是数据收集。</p><p>您需要大量数据才能进入新领域。您需要大量以适当方式标记的数据，并根据您要解决的问题类型进行标记。因此，我们有点翻转了脚本：我们不是在部署系统<em>之前</em>尝试获取所有数据，而是继续部署一个系统，然后与现场专家合作，他们教授系统 - 通过大声说话和动态数据标签 - 他们教系统它需要知道什么。因此，希望用于帮助人们完成这些任务的数据将由第一批使用该工具的人产生。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这似乎是一个很好的类比，因为正如你所说，它让我想起如果有新的人类合作伙伴加入该项目，你会做什么。您将执行相同的步骤。</p><p> Shervin 和我进行了一些研究，我们发现<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/achieving-individual-and-organizational-value-with-ai/">60% 的人将 AI 视为同事</a>，而这正是您所描述的那种关系。但这让我想到这里有一点危险。假设当你把这​​个系统放在那里时，它知道的东西并不多，而且你已经有人对它们进行了培训。好的;我是一个人。我感觉我有点生气了。我想，“为什么我要这么努力来培训这个同事？”你如何保持这种活力？您提到该项目有技术方面，但也有社会方面。在我看来，这在社会方面可能比在技术方面更困难。</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>这正是我接下来要谈论的内容，因为这正是我要做的事情。我可以和人们谈论他们对这些系统的实际想法——你是对的。有时他们确实觉得这很烦人，他们会问，“等等 - 所以我正在组装这个非常复杂的仪器，系统问我在做什么，这是<em>错误的</em>吗？那么我应该如何花时间不仅完成我的工作，还教这台机器如何完成我的工作呢？”</p><p>因此，我真的很高兴能够成为现场的社会科学家。我们仍处于开发阶段，公司通常会在部署某些内容之前进行尽可能多的测试，然后，当部署的实际原则出现时（例如用户体验和用户界面设计）这些通常接近开发过程的结束。但在这里，社会科学以及对人们需要什么、人们可能会觉得烦人什么以及他们需要什么来信任与他们合作的机器的理解是正确的发展的DNA。因此，我不断地与我们为其构建系统的技术人员交谈，并向他们提出问题，就像您所描述的那样，问他们：“您认为这很烦人吗？这会如何更有帮助？我们可以在系统中构建哪些其他功能，以使其对您更有帮助？”</p><p>还提出了更深层次的问题，不仅涉及他们与系统的二元关系，还涉及他们更大的社会技术工作背景。询问“你的日程安排是怎样的？”以及“你们的老板对这个系统有何评价？”并且，“有没有一种方法可以让我们通过这个系统，不仅与你的老板，而且与你的其他同事建立更富有成效的关系？”因此，我们的目标是建立非常深入的理解，不仅仅是对一项任务，而是对整个工作空间，并询问我们的系统如何通过成为该空间内人类的同事，以最佳方式帮助放大人类潜力，而且[问]，“如何在了解他们的工作环境的基础上建立这种关系，以促进长期关系？”</p><p>因为我们依靠人们提供数据并依靠人们帮助我们实际进行数据标记这一事实所要求的事情之一是我们需要他们参与，并且我们需要他们喜欢与系统，我们需要他们发现它值得信赖、可靠且有用。要了解如何实现所有这些目标，需要深入了解社会背景、社会习惯、工作习惯和任务流程。这正是我们现在正在努力的方向。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我认为你似乎在思考这个项目之外的事情，这真的很有趣。其中有一个要素是“好吧，我如何让这个特定的项目到位”，但你所谈论的很多事情的背后都是这样的事情，“我们如何找出引入一个新系统的最佳方法” ？我们如何找到转型并实现整体愿景的最佳方式？”这超越了单个项目的范围。你打算如何吸取这些教训？</p><p><strong>伊丽莎白·安妮·沃特金斯：</strong>这是一个非常好的问题。我对我们的实验室以及我们在人类与人工智能协作方面做出的一些重大赌注感到非常自豪，以及从社会科学中获得的投入、贡献和见解正在得到利用，并且在英特尔历史上得到了利用，贯穿他们的研究项目。当我们在教育、制造和无障碍等垂直领域开展研究项目和构建产品时，各个团队都进行了大量投资，以促进和鼓励与像我这样的人（社会科学家）进行对话。</p><p>我们经常把这些非常出色的团队聚集在一个房间里，里面有工程师、数据科学家、政策制定者和社会科学家，其中不仅包括我，还有一个由 Dawn Nafus 领导的优秀人类学家团队，以及另一个社会科学家团队那有心理学家。我们所有人都非常密切地合作，以确保我们构建的产品不仅仅是为了解决一个问题而设计，而是围绕最佳解决方案进行适当的设计，确保我们充分利用我们的所有不同类型的多模式可供性。工具可以提供，并且我们深入了解我们所有产品将部署到的社会和组织环境。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>我认为，在我们第一次讨论这些模型和工具和使用数据之间似乎经常发生一种转变：事情非常以数据和工具为导向，并且非常以科学为导向。 And that made a lot of sense because we didn&#39;t know how to do some of these things. And now, as a society, we&#39;re learning how to do many of these tools and model buildings. But a lot of the team you mentioned there — anthropology, psychology — these are not traditional things that we might have thought of [as] being integral to producing an AI application, but those are the ones you happened to mention. Why did you pick those? I guess that&#39;s some of your background in social science, right?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Yeah, throughout my graduate studies and postdoc work, I was always really invested in the users and in people. And I was always really fascinated by just how weird people can be and how creative and how innovative, and how folks often use technologies in ways that their developers did not anticipate and did not foresee.</p><p> And while there are some dangerous elements to that, as we&#39;ve seen in various misuse and dual-use applications, there are also a lot of really fantastic and wonderful ways that people have figured out for technology to be more suited to them in their context or to work a little bit more smoothly for them. And so seeing how Intel was different because of their history of being a semiconductor manufacturer and being deeply invested in hardware and having an ecosystem approach to the way that AI tools are deployed really showed me that they were a company that cared, just like I did, about the people who were going to be using these tools and the social structures in which these people were embedded, and building tools that could match not just the people who bought or used the tools but also the lives and the communities into which these technologies were going to be interjected.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Elizabeth, clearly a lot of your background has been coming through as we&#39;ve been talking, but could we step back for a second and ask you about how you ended up in this role at Intel Labs?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> I guess my road to this role started way back, probably at the beginning of my graduate career. After I graduated MIT and started my Ph.D. at Columbia, there was an opening for someone to contribute to a project on security and privacy behaviors among journalists. And my adviser said, “Hey, I got you an interview for this project.” And I said, “I don&#39;t know anything about security and privacy.” And she said, “Just go to the interview. I got you the interview. Just go.” And so the night before the interview, I thought, “Oh, I&#39;d better have something to talk about. PGP — Pretty Good Privacy — everyone&#39;s talking about PGP. I better download PGP so I can act like I know what PGP is.” And I tried to figure it out, and it was hard. I couldn&#39;t figure out … I went to the website and I was like, “The website doesn&#39;t really explain what&#39;s happening here. Where&#39;s the key? I download the key, but the key&#39;s also kept in a database, but I write the key on my emails? Oh, I&#39;m so … I can&#39;t do this. I&#39;m so bad at this. This is not for me.”</p><p> And I went into the interview the next day with the wonderful project lead, Susan McGregor, and I said, “You know what? This job&#39;s not for me. I tried to do PGP; it&#39;s weirdly hard. There&#39;s something about it that I just … I can&#39;t quite grok the language.” And she said, “I think that makes you perfect for this job because we are trying to figure out why security and privacy are so hard for people at work, especially journalists who are high-value targets for attack from a lot of different actors, and we are trying to figure out how we can make security and privacy protocols better for them, so it sounds like you&#39;re frustrated with how security is designed.” And I said, “Yeah, that was frustrating.” And she said, “OK, let&#39;s do some work.”</p><p> So we ended up working together for several years studying journalists. We had one particularly harrowing project studying the journalists who published the Panama Papers. And for that, they had terabytes of data. There were journalists working all over the world; none of them were colocated, and they didn&#39;t have a single breach. Never once did they have a breach and in all of that data. And so we saw that as a success story. And we said, “OK. We&#39;re always hearing the bad stories about breaches and attacks; we never hear the success stories.” And so we got to interview the journalists who contributed to the Panama Papers and talked to them about their organizational culture and how making protocols uniform across all journalists helped to instill a sense of teamwork and a sense that they were protecting each other. And seeing the power of culture and shared mission on behaviors around something as difficult as PGP and security protocols … it was really inspirational.</p><p> And around that time, I started paying attention to facial recognition, and from there it was a short bridge over to looking at AI and asking similar questions around “Why is this hard to understand? How can we communicate it to people in a more strategic way that is more understanding of the work that they&#39;re doing and the work that they need to do? And how can we bring some transparency to these systems in a way that is meaningful and understandable for real people?”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One of the things interesting about that is, security&#39;s always like that. If it&#39;s a little bit hard to do, then we all tend to not do it, because it&#39;s tomorrow&#39;s problem versus today&#39;s problem. … That&#39;s something we as humans are terrible about. And you know, I think what we&#39;ve failed [at] in many ways here is not building that into the infrastructure so it&#39;s a default. And there&#39;s a lot of analogies for artificial intelligence: We&#39;re building things, and if we don&#39;t make the defaults easy to use or easy to do the right thing, then people will do the wrong thing — or people will do the easy thing or the short-term thing. And you mentioned facial recognition: What are the kinds of things that we should be building into our infrastructure so we don&#39;t propagate AI-based mistakes?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. Something that drives my research, both throughout my graduate career and here at Intel, is a recognition that people are the experts in their own lives and that we really need to engage with the people and with the users throughout the development pipeline in order to build not just systems but solutions, and solutions for the real problems that are happening on the ground. And as close as a company can get to including the expertise of social science and what social scientists can bring about rigorous and robust tools to study how people live and the kinds of languages they use and the kinds of values they have and what&#39;s truly important to them and what they want to protect and what they want to keep safe, as well as building in different kinds of options and different kinds of pathways into the same technology that might be used differently by people of different levels of accessibility, are all things that I would love to see the entire field take up.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That <em>sounds</em> good. I mean … much like buying low and selling high sounds great. How do companies actually do this? What steps do they need to take to make progress on these?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. The way that we&#39;re doing it at Intel is that we are facilitating conversations between our technical teams — people who are building really amazing systems around robotics and accessibility tools and educational tools — and embedding social scientists across all these teams so that we can ask some questions around “Hey, what are the presumptions of this system? Have you talked to teachers? Have you talked to the folks who are going to be using this robot on the ground? What are your conversations like with the people who are going to be served by these solutions?”</p><p> And I&#39;m really lucky that I get to be in a place where we&#39;re embedding this expertise way back into the problem-formulation stage and into the project-formulation stage, all throughout the development pipeline. I&#39;ve also been really gratified that Intel established the ethical impact assessment process along with the Responsible AI [Advisory] Council. And so this is a process for robustly and rigorously building into the development pipeline that teams all across Intel and across all business units [use]. This is a way to inject the expertise, not just of social scientists but everyone who sits on the Responsible AI [Advisory] Council, including engineers and policy makers and folks from legal and folks from standards, and facilitate conversations with this multidisciplinary Responsible AI [Advisory] Council with development teams through their submission of the ethical impact assessment.</p><p> And the ethical impact assessment is a way for us to put values into practice and ensure that values around human oversights and human rights and privacy and safety and security and diversity and inclusion — these are ways for us to make sure that those values are built into the tools that Intel BUs [business units] are putting together across the organization.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> OK, we have a segment where we ask our guests a series of five rapid-fire questions. Just answer the first thing that comes to your mind. First: What is your proudest AI moment?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh, goodness.这是一个很好的问题。 I am really proud of being able to represent the voices of the technicians who we have on the floor to these teams of engineers and data scientists who are building these systems. And because of the process that Intel has built, where I get to sit with the engineering teams who are building the computer vision and the action recognition and the NLP and choosing the phrases in the semantic frames around tasks and about how tasks are built and how they can be recognized, being able to do the interviews that I do with technicians to ask them about their concerns when this technology is introduced, what we can do to make sure that their concerns are addressed, asking what they need to know around transparency, what they need in order to trust the system, all in the service of enhancing the work that people are doing.</p><p> The fact that I get to grab that information and deliver it consistently to the engineers and to see how quickly they respond. Like, “Oh, well, we can build this and we can build that. And what if we built this into the UI? And what if we built this into the dialog?” It&#39;s such an incredibly compelling process, especially after coming from academia, where I would write a paper and then it would take a year to get published. And then …</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Oh, a year sounds fast.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Right. If I were lucky, it would take a year. I think my longest record was maybe 3½ years it took to get published.我不知道。 What&#39;s your record?</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Uh, 10. So …</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Ten!</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Yeah. Let&#39;s don&#39;t talk about it though, because I&#39;ll get all sad.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh, no.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> So you mentioned concerns that people have. What worries you about artificial intelligence?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Well, one of their biggest concerns, when I started talking to the technicians, was that they were going to get replaced.</p><p> I said, “OK, let&#39;s have a conversation. What do you think this is for?” And they said, “I&#39;ve seen the news. I know you&#39;re trying to build a robot just to do exactly what I do, so I figure I&#39;m training my replacement.” And I thought, “Oh, no! That&#39;s terrible.” And I got to have a lot of conversations with our technicians where I got to say, “That&#39;s <em>not</em> what we&#39;re doing. We are not trying to replace you. You are the expert.我们需要你。 In fact, we need you to teach the system so that the system can go and help other people like you. So by you training the system, you&#39;re actually helping a lot of other folks in Intel fabs [semiconductor manufacturing plants] across the planet, and you are ensuring that they get help in the way that you would like to get help.”</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Some research that Shervin and I were involved in a couple years ago focused entirely on this <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning">organizational learning</a> aspect that you were alluding to — that this is a way for everyone to learn more quickly and to spread knowledge.</p><p> What&#39;s your favorite activity that does not involve technology? What&#39;s <em>not</em> AI going on in your world?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Well, there&#39;s so much happening recently, it seems tough sometimes to figure out what&#39;s AI and what&#39;s not.</p><p> [In] my personal life, I do a lot of baking. It&#39;s been a while since I made a loaf of bread. I do a lot of cooking. I am very lucky to live with my husband in the city of New York, and so we do a lot of exploring — in fact, just getting outside. That&#39;s probably the biggest non-AI activity, is walking outside on our own two feet and looking around with our own eyes. And that always feels very refreshing.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s the first career you wanted when you were young? What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> I wanted to be an artist, and it has been a topsy-turvy winding road. I did my undergrad at UC Irvine, and I studied video art.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> There&#39;s so much that AI can do that humans cannot, but there&#39;s also so much that humans can do that AI cannot. And I think a big challenge, at least for me, and I hope the people with whom I work going forward for the next few years, is going to be figuring out exactly what that balance is and how can we systematize “What do people really need help with that AI systems can do?” but with a really thorough understanding of what it is that people do and how they do it.</p><p> Now that the AI systems are becoming so advanced, but oftentimes in a lab or in a vacuum, as they mature into the real world, I think it&#39;s really exciting what they can do, but we&#39;re facing a lot of work in getting them there. And I think it&#39;s going to be other social scientists and multidisciplinary teams like the ones that we have at Intel all working together to make sure that these systems can really be deployed as solutions.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> That&#39;s a good cap for the episode. Thanks for talking to us. I think one of the things that has come through [is], you&#39;re talking about projects and things you&#39;re working on, but you&#39;re also giving us a hint about what&#39;s going to happen in the future as we move off of the, let&#39;s say, tool-focused “Can we get the ML right? Can we get the model right? Can we get the data right?” You&#39;re talking a lot about what happens next, what happens once we check off some of those check marks — what are those checks? And I think a lot of people can learn from that. Thanks for taking the time to talk with us today.</p><p> <strong>Elizabeth Anne Watkins:</strong> Oh my gosh, it&#39;s been such a pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, Shervin and I speak with David Hardoon from Aboitiz Data Innovation. We&#39;re once again talking about chemical engineering, so you won&#39;t want to miss this one.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/the-social-science-of-ai-intels-elizabeth-anne-watkins/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Impact of Generative AI on Hollywood and Entertainment</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas H. Davenport and Randy Bean. <p>Thomas H. Davenport ( <a href="https://twitter.com/tdav">@tdav</a> ) is the President&#39;s Distinguished Professor of Information Technology and Management at Babson College, a visiting professor at Oxford&#39;s Saïd Business School, and a fellow of the MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy. He is coauthor of <cite>Working With AI: Real Stories of Human-Machine Collaboration</cite> (MIT Press, 2022). Randy Bean ( <a href="https://twitter.com/randybeannvp">@randybeannvp</a> ) is an industry thought leader, author, founder, and CEO and currently serves as innovation fellow, data strategy for global consultancy Wavestone. He is the author of <cite>Fail Fast, Learn Faster: Lessons in Data-Driven Leadership in an Age of Disruption, Big Data, and AI</cite> (Wiley, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Knowledge Workers]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[IT Governance & Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><description><![CDATA[One of the many topics involving generative AI that is receiving a lot of attention is its potential effects on Hollywood and the entertainment industry. It’s an obvious concern because generative AI can create the types of outputs that the industry uses — text (in the form of stories, scripts, ad copy, and reviews), marketing [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Davenport-Bean-Hollywood-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> One of the many topics involving generative AI that is receiving a lot of attention is its potential effects on Hollywood and the entertainment industry. It&#39;s an obvious concern because generative AI can create the types of outputs that the industry uses — text (in the form of stories, scripts, ad copy, and reviews), marketing campaigns, and moving and static images. Segments of the industry are facing economic pressures, which increases the demand for productivity and less-expensive “product.” And a high percentage of current entertainment is derivative of past content, which makes it well suited for generative technologies that are trained on … past content.</p><p> It&#39;s still early days for generative AI-created entertainment, but it&#39;s clear that something big is happening. A recent <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-hollywood-intellectual-property-spongebob-81fd5d15"><cite>Wall Street Journal</cite> article</a> noted that widely available AI tools can suggest storylines, character arcs, and dialogue; it even includes an interactive module that lets readers see for themselves how easily ChatGPT can write a basic script when given a few prompts. The article also raises questions about image intellectual property: “If a user prompts an AI tool to build a new character influenced by say, SpongeBob, should the original creators have to grant permission? Who owns it? Can the new work itself be copyrighted?”</p><p></p><p> Generative AI was used in <a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/05/05/runway-generative-ai-chatgpt-video">making the 2022 film <cite>Everything Everywhere All at Once</cite></a> , and <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/oscars-2023-everything-everywhere-all-at-once-most-awards/">we know how that turned out</a> . Tom recently wrote about the use of generative AI to create <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tomdavenport/2023/03/13/cuebric-generative-ai-comes-to-hollywood/">movie and TV backdrop images</a> . There are already generative AI systems that can create videos, although they are short and relatively primitive. AI is being used to provide data-driven predictions about <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/democratizing-data-in-hollywood-jumpcuts-kartik-hosanagar/">how unusual storylines will land with viewers</a> .</p><p> So, what does this mean for the industry? There are many different components to this question, as a new <a href="https://variety.com/vip-special-reports/generative-ai-entertainment-a-special-report-1235564989/">report from Variety Intelligence Platform</a> suggests. In May, the Writers Guild of America (WGA) went on strike, primarily over film and TV writers&#39; <a href="https://time.com/6277158/writers-strike-ai-wga-screenwriting/">income from streaming services programming</a> , but it also demanded that production companies “<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/29/business/media/writers-guild-hollywood-ai-chatgpt.html">regulate use of material produced using artificial intelligence</a> or similar technologies.” Because there are so many uncertainties about what will happen when and how with the technology, we spoke with two experts on the topic. Both are based in — not surprisingly — Los Angeles, and both are involved with centers at the University of Southern California (USC). However, they don&#39;t work together, and they have very different approaches to the technology.</p><p></p><h3> Resolutely Against Generative AI</h3><p> Jonathan Taplin is director emeritus at the <a href="https://www.annenberglab.com/">Annenberg Innovation Lab</a> at USC. He&#39;s had a long career in the entertainment industry and was previously a tour manager for musicians, including Bob Dylan and The Band. In addition, he&#39;s been a film producer, a banker, and a writer. His latest book, <a href="https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/jonathan-taplin/the-end-of-reality/9781541703155/?lens=publicaffairs"><cite>The End of Reality: How Four Billionaires Are Selling a Fantasy Future of the Metaverse, Mars, and Crypto</cite></a> , will be released in September. As you might infer from the title, he&#39;s not a fan of how big tech firms&#39; generative AI tools are being developed or promulgated.</p><p> “The way they train their models is by ingesting everything on the internet, with no concern for copyright,” Taplin told us. “Google has a music-generation AI trained on every audio file on YouTube. You can issue a prompt like &#39;Write me a song that sounds like Taylor Swift, sad ending, up-tempo,&#39; and the resulting song sounds somewhat like her. Someone could include it in a video game or a bar scene in a movie for free.” Generative AI could do the same kind of repurposing with video content owned by the studios, he added.</p><p> Taplin&#39;s primary concern is that generative AI will replace some of the work done by human writers, artists, photographers, and other creative professionals in the arts and entertainment industry. He also believes that it will exacerbate problems that are already bringing the film and TV industry down. “The biggest problem in the movies is too many formulas. There is a lack of originality, and that&#39;s why the industry isn&#39;t performing,” he said. Generative AI, he added, is only capable of producing even more formulaic content and will make the predictability worse. “Entertainment relies on new ideas, and this technology can&#39;t produce them,” Taplin added.</p><p> He said he&#39;s concerned that generative AI will continue to reduce the number of performers who can make a living in their fields. The majority of entertainment revenue already goes to a very small percentage of artists. This is the <a href="https://www.digitalmusicnews.com/2014/03/05/toponepercent/">reality for musicians</a> , especially on <a href="https://themusicnetwork.com/few-artists-generate-most-streams/">streaming services</a> , and is echoed in Hollywood in the huge <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/655480/all-time-top-grossing-actors-box-office/">box office revenues</a> generated by a handful of leading actors in blockbuster films. When you get an “algorithmic economy,” Taplin said, “the algorithms narrow the funnel, with outsize paychecks for a few.” He&#39;s hopeful that a collective licensing regime — similar to what&#39;s in place for music sampling — will emerge to protect artists when their content is used to train generative AI.</p><h3> Embracing Generative AI, With Some Concerns</h3><p> Yves Bergquist is director of the AI &amp; Neuroscience in Media Project at USC&#39;s <a href="https://www.etcenter.org/">Entertainment Technology Center</a> , which is funded by Hollywood studios. You can guess that his opinion of generative AI is probably much more favorable than Taplin&#39;s. It is, although he said he does have some concerns about AI&#39;s potential effects on the media and entertainment industry: “It&#39;s a completely revolutionary technology” characterized by misinformation and “some insanity.”</p><p> We asked Bergquist whether movie studios would embrace generative AI. Parts of them are already doing so, he said. “Some groups within the studios are highly technologically savvy, such as the chief technology officers and all of the visual effects artists and technicians. They are very sophisticated and are already working with generative AI companies. The studios do a lot of the postproduction work in films — particularly in animation — and there is a lot of pressure to bring costs down. The postproduction companies have a software development culture, so they will embrace generative AI.”</p><p> He also believes that many production companies will embrace the technology because they are already shooting on large LED-based screens and will need generative images for them. Bergquist said he expects that tools offering virtual actors and voice synthesis will be most aggressively adopted by short-form creators who distribute their work on TikTok or YouTube and by video game producers. “Streaming channels, digital ads, games — that&#39;s what kids watch these days,” he noted. “The media industry no longer has a monopoly on entertainment.” Makers of hardware (such as cameras) are experimenting with generative in-camera visual effects as well.</p><p></p><p> The business side of traditional movie studios is sometimes more reluctant to embrace AI, Bergquist observed, simply because they don&#39;t have the same kind of culture of data or software. “It&#39;s being bolted onto organizations and people who aren&#39;t ready,” he said. Even the new streaming studios, like Netflix and Prime Video, have experienced a lot of growing pains in their AI journeys.</p><p> Bergquist said that before the WGA strike started in May, many screenwriters told him that they view the likes of ChatGPT as a “great creative assistant tool” but not something that will replace human writers. “It&#39;s good at brainstorming ideas, but it will output only average content,” Bergquist asserted. “It&#39;s nowhere near capable of the symbolic abstraction necessary for script development, and it can&#39;t output a script with narrative structure and character arcs.” At least not now. Future language models with higher levels of intelligence and new paradigms for AI might be able to do so.</p><p></p><p> Bergquist thinks generative AI will have enormous effects not only on entertainment but also on education. He believes that schools, including the School of Cinematic Arts at USC, need to quickly ramp up their teaching to keep pace with the frenzy of new generative AI tools that are released nearly every week. Bergquist is preparing courses himself on the technology for the Society of Motion Pictures and Television Engineers, an organization that represents technologists in media.</p><h3> Are Both Experts Right?</h3><p> Although Taplin and Bergquist seem to have very different views on generative AI, they might both be right about its impacts. Economic pressures may entice the industry — at least some sectors of it — to embrace these new tools. Generative AI will lead to dramatic changes in production and postproduction, distribution, and intellectual property ownership. The technology may not be good for traditional artists and the companies that employ them, but it is likely to lead to significant changes in the industry over the next few years — hopefully some for the better along with some for the worse. Perhaps the only purely good news is that neither expert expects that humans will be entirely replaced anytime soon.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-impact-of-generative-ai-on-hollywood-and-entertainment/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Recapping Work/23: The Big Shift</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:09:56 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT SMR Editors. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Career Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Remote Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Download the Event Summary Download (PDF) The pandemic irrevocably changed the how, why, and where of work. At Work/23: The Big Shift, a half-day summit held May 4, 2023, MIT Sloan Management Review brought together company executives and academic experts in talent management, hybrid work, employee well-being, and workplace culture. Together, they explained how organizations [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> <strong>Download the Event Summary</strong></h5><p class="is-button"> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cb2792f94c.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Download (PDF)</a></p></aside><p> The pandemic irrevocably changed the how, why, and where of work. At Work/23: The Big Shift, a half-day summit held May 4, 2023, <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> brought together company executives and academic experts in talent management, hybrid work, employee well-being, and workplace culture. Together, they explained how organizations are pivoting to innovate, improve productivity, and achieve balance in this changed world.</p><p> <cite>MIT SMR</cite> editor in chief Abbie Lundberg and editorial director Elizabeth Heichler co-moderated the event.</p><p> The full video of the half-day event is here. Work/23 included these topics and speakers:</p><h4 class="work23-title" id="nalbantian"> Dismantle Career Roadblocks for More Equitable Outcomes</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Haig R. Nalbantian, Workforce Sciences Institute</h5><p> Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Nalbantian outlined ways companies are tackling the obstacles women and people of color continue to face — obstacles that are often due to situational factors, such as the roles people are in or whom they report to.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:02</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="berwick"> The Why, What, and How of Skills-Based Talent Practices</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Beth Berwick, Grads of Life</h5><p> More jobs than ever now require a four-year college degree, including many that never did in the past. But that criterion excludes 64% of the population — including 76% of Black Americans and 80% of Latinos. Berwick is among those calling for a retreat on the degree requirement. She explained how organizations can instead hire effectively based on the skills they need.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 33:24</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="smith"> The New World of Accessing Talent</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Mike Smith, Randstad Enterprise; David Kiron, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> Companies are changing how they approach and apply technology to find the people they need. <cite>MIT SMR</cite> &#39;s Kiron and our presenting partner&#39;s chief executive discussed the ways that innovative organizations are designing their own talent pools, building their talent brands, and expanding DEI initiatives beyond their own boundaries.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 54:44</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="dervin"> Flexible <em>and</em> Effective: Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workplace</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Julie Dervin, Atlassian; Brian Elliott, Future Forum; N. Sharon Hill, George Washington University School of Business; Abbie Lundberg, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> It&#39;s possible to have a healthy workplace culture and high performance in a hybrid workplace; it just requires a deliberate management approach. The speakers in this session expanded on their research and their real-world experience configuring hybrid work arrangements and discussed how to get to the right mix of worker autonomy and organizational alignment.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:07:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="kellerman"> Thriving in the New World of Work</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Gabriella Rosen Kellerman, BetterUp; Martin Seligman, University of Pennsylvania; Elizabeth Heichler, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> Workforce well-being is an urgent issue for leaders who recognize that stress is driving out talented workers. The speakers, who coauthored the book <cite>Tomorrowmind</cite> , detailed the skills that help individuals flourish in pressure-filled work environments, including <em>prospection</em> — the ability to imagine our options, plan for the future, and restore our agency.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 1:42:29</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="gigliotti"> How to Deliver Career Development for All</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Tony Gigliotti, UPMC; Lani Montoya, Pernod Ricard North America; George Westerman, MIT Sloan</h5><p> The speakers in this session outlined how forward-leaning companies are helping all employees — not just a select few — chart rewarding career paths. They explained that companies are doing it by providing ways to learn and practice new skills and by delivering rich feedback. Companies are also making pathways visible, showing opportunities at and above an employee&#39;s current level.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 2:13:11</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="altman"> An Integrated Approach to Workforce Ecosystems</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Elizabeth J. Altman, UMass Lowell; David Kiron, <cite>MIT SMR</cite></h5><p> The speakers&#39; research, featured in the book <cite>Workforce Ecosystems</cite> , found that most leaders consider their workforces to be broader than full-time employees, encompassing gig workers, professional services firms, and even technologies like customer service chatbots. Altman and Kiron explained what it takes to coordinate and successfully manage that expanded workforce.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 2:49:49</h6><hr /><h4 class="work23-title" id="barnes"> The Four-Day Workweek: How to Make It Work in Your Organization</h4><h5 class="work23-speaker"> Andrew Barnes, 4 Day Week Global</h5><p> Barnes has had a front-row seat at the world&#39;s largest trial of what happens when you scale back the workweek from five days to four. It started with an experiment at his own company, where, he said, “we pay 100% income, for 80% time, as long as we get 100% output.” He started a nonprofit to help other companies try it themselves and now has data from 91 participating organizations.</p><h6 class="work23-timestamp"> Section time stamp: 3:14:02 </h6><p></p><style>.work23-title {margin-bottom:0!important;}.work23-speaker {margin-top:0!important;}.work23-timestamp {margin-bottom:25px!important;color: #005b9c!important;text-transform: uppercase;letter-spacing: 1px!important;font-size: 1.4rem!important;margin-bottom:25px!important;}</style> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/recapping-work-23-the-big-shift/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What, Me Worry?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elizabeth Heichler. <p>Elizabeth Heichler ( <a href="https://twitter.com/eheichler">@eheichler</a> ) is the executive editor, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Generative AI]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades Call me shortsighted, but I am not losing sleep over the prospect of a supercharged AI gaining consciousness and waging war on humans. What does keep me up at night is that humans are already wielding the power of artificial intelligence to control, exploit, discriminate against, misinform, and manipulate other humans. Tools that [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-Edit-Letter-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Simon Prades</p></figcaption></figure><p> Call me shortsighted, but I am not losing sleep over the prospect of a supercharged AI gaining consciousness and waging war on humans.</p><p> What does keep me up at night is that humans are already wielding the power of artificial intelligence to control, exploit, discriminate against, misinform, and manipulate other humans. Tools that can help us solve complex and vexing problems can also be put to work by cybercriminals or give authoritarian governments unprecedented power to spy on and direct the lives of their citizens. We can build models that lead to the development of new, more sustainable materials or important new drugs — and we can build models that embed biased decision-making into systems and processes and then grind individuals up in their gears.</p><p></p><p> In other words, AI already gives us plenty to worry about. We shouldn&#39;t be distracted by dystopian fever dreams that misdirect our attention from present-day risk.</p><p> The recent emergence of ChatGPT and similar large language models into broader public awareness has heightened general interest in both the potential benefits and the dangers of AI. A few days before I wrote this, Geoffrey Hinton, a giant of the AI field whose work underlies much of the current technology, resigned from his position at Google, telling <cite>The New York Times</cite> that he wanted to speak freely about the risks of generative AI. “It is hard to see how you can prevent the bad actors from using it for bad things,” he told the newspaper.</p><p> And there, indeed, is where we should put our attention. Throughout human history, new technologies have been put to work to advance civilization, but they have also been weaponized by bad actors. The difference this time is that not only is the technology extremely complex and difficult for most people to understand — so too are the potential outcomes.</p><p> There&#39;s a steep learning curve that all of us must be prepared to climb if we want AI to do more good than harm. The excitement about possible uses for these tools must be tempered by good questions about how automated decisions are made, how AI systems are trained, and what assumptions and biases are thus baked in. Business leaders, especially, need to be as aware of reputational and material risks, and the potential for value destruction, as they are of opportunities to leverage AI.</p><p></p><p> And while AI development is likely to continue to proceed at a breakneck pace that no open letter can arrest, the rest of us ought to proceed deliberately and with caution. In “<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dont-get-distracted-by-the-hype-around-generative-ai/">Don&#39;t Get Distracted by the Hype Around Generative AI</a> ,” Lee Vinsel reminds us that tech bubbles are accompanied by a lot of noise. We need to let go of the fear of missing out (FOMO) and take a measured, rational approach to evaluating emerging technologies.</p><p> Here at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , we will continue to support business leaders with the research and intelligence required for clear-headed decision-making and judicious experimentation. Our ongoing <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/responsible-ai/">focus on responsible AI practices</a> , led by guest editor Elizabeth Renieris of the University of Oxford, is a critical part of that commitment.</p><p> We&#39;re all stakeholders in the AI revolution. Let&#39;s embrace that responsibility and strive to ensure that the good actors outweigh the bad.</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/what-me-worry/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Our Guide to the Summer 2023 Issue</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[MIT Sloan Management Review. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Algorithms]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ecosystems]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Growth Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here’s How to Keep Them on Track. Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi Key Insight: When algorithms aren’t updated to account for changes in the environment, they deliver poor-quality predictions. Top Takeaways: AI models designed to dynamically account for new circumstances don’t always do so effectively. This [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2023SUM-EXECSUM-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="no-underline">Predictive Models Can Lose the Plot. Here&#39;s How to Keep Them on Track.</a></h4><h6> Vern L. Glaser, Omid Omidvar, and Mehdi Safavi</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> When algorithms aren&#39;t updated to account for changes in the environment, they deliver poor-quality predictions.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> AI models designed to dynamically account for new circumstances don&#39;t always do so effectively. This scenario, called <em>algorithmic inertia</em> , can result in poor guidance and flawed decisions. The authors explored the causes and consequences of algorithmic inertia by investigating credit-ratings agency Moody&#39;s and its use of algorithmic models to rate mortgage-backed securities in the years leading up to the 2008 financial crisis. They found that the most significant contributing factors to algorithmic inertia are buried assumptions, superficial remodeling, simulation of the unknown future, and specialized compartmentalization. Exposing data and assumptions, and periodically redesigning algorithmic routines, are two key practices for heading off such inertia.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/predictive-models-can-lose-the-plot-heres-how-to-keep-them-on-track/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="no-underline">Risk Intelligence and the Resilient Company</a></h4><h6> Ananya Sheth and Joseph V. Sinfield</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Taking a more logical approach to risk management can help leaders sustain value generation amid disruption and uncertainty.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Building the resilience of large, complex enterprises is critical in today&#39;s interconnected world. Risk intelligence — the honed ability to rigorously interpret risks and the consequences or opportunities they pose for a company — supports organizational resilience by helping leaders identify and manage a broad array of potential threats to their company&#39;s value exchange system, both over time and across changing business contexts. To strengthen their organization&#39;s risk intelligence, leaders should systematically categorize and interpret risk events, compartmentalize uncertainty and reduce its impact, and construct and contextualize an enterprise risk network.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="no-underline">How Professional Services Firms Dodged Disruption</a></h4><h6> Julian Birkinshaw and David Lancefield</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Professional services firms with longevity hold lessons for other businesses trying to survive disruptions in turbulent markets.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Big professional services firms appeared to be in the crosshairs of new, technology-fueled competitors a decade ago, but many have maintained or even bolstered their positions. These consulting giants, top-tier law firms, and others have found resilience in their capacity to diagnose the different causes of potential disruption and respond accordingly. They have doubled down on their traditional strengths of tackling clients&#39; most challenging problems and providing advice and compliance in high-impact, large-scale, high-risk situations — and charging a premium to do so. And they have learned to live with a pragmatic acknowledgment that their fundamentals are sound, tempered with a touch of paranoid suspicion of emerging technologies and competitors.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="no-underline">The Missing Discipline Behind Failure to Scale</a></h4><h6> Andy Binns and Christine Griffin</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Developing a scaling path for new ventures is both an art and a science, but it&#39;s one that leaders can use to learn and iterate as they go.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Companies make significant investments in developing new business initiatives, but too few follow a rigorous path to broadly implementing them. While 80% of companies claim to ideate and incubate new ventures, only 16% of companies successfully scale them. Scaling paths require a clarity of ambition equal to the scale of opportunity; a set of plausible strategic options for what assets will be needed to achieve that ambition; smart brainstorming about how to acquire those assets; an openness to bringing in new leaders to support the expanding scope of activities; and preparation for the inevitable high-stakes moments when decisions entail commitments that will be difficult, if not impossible, to reverse.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-missing-discipline-behind-failure-to-scale/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="no-underline">Helping Neurodivergent Employees Succeed</a></h4><h6> Emily R. Russo, Dana L. Ott, and Miriam Moeller</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Companies can expand their talent pools by developing a neuroinclusive hiring strategy and work environment.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> When it comes to hiring, management, and retention in the workplace, individuals with neurological differences, especially those on the autism spectrum, are often discounted by employers, to everyone&#39;s detriment. Bringing neurodiversity into the larger conversation about workplace diversity, equity, and inclusion is important not only because it&#39;s the fair thing to do but because neurodivergent individuals can make valuable contributions. Creating a neuroinclusive organization calls for specific training and development efforts that benefit neurodivergent employees and the wider workforce. Managers are key to the success of these programs and need to be educated about how to support their neurodivergent employees.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/helping-neurodivergent-employees-succeed/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="no-underline">How Digitally Mature Is Your Finance Office?</a></h4><h6> Kristof Stouthuysen</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Many finance offices are stuck in traditional operational roles and aren&#39;t benefiting from advanced analytics.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Finance leaders in a wide range of industries are trying to integrate data and analytics to improve operations, but not all CFOs have cracked the code. In particular, many are not capitalizing on the promise of new machine learning applications. CFOs who are able to challenge an often conservative, cautious culture and manage to successfully deploy advanced analytics can deliver more real-time insights, reduce human error and bias, and speed up processes and decision-making. What&#39;s more, while more traditional finance leaders often guard the data they possess, those who embrace advanced analytics — what the author calls <em>digital finance leaders</em> — become strong advocates for democratizing data across a company&#39;s silos.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-digitally-mature-is-your-finance-office" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="no-underline">Cashing Out Excellence</a></h4><h6> Robert D. Austin, Robert H. Hayes, and Richard L. Nolan</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Too many leaders engage in <em>performance hacking</em> — delivering on particular metrics to give the appearance of effective leadership without producing real performance.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Recent disruptive events like the pandemic and war in Europe have exposed businesses weakened by short-sighted leadership decisions. An analysis of Southwest Airlines, Boeing, and GE looks at why successful companies sacrifice the business excellence they spent years building — including values and relationships that have served as their foundation — for near-term financial gains such as cost reductions and stock price improvements that ultimately harm stakeholders. The authors share the typical warning signs that indicate leaders are engaging in the practice.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/cashing-out-excellence/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="no-underline">Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</a></h4><h6> Haig R. Nalbantian</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Understanding what factors drive employee promotion can help managers more equitably position women and people of color for advancement.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> New research shows that factors unrelated to employees&#39; knowledge, capabilities, or behavior have an outsize effect on career advancement. Circumstances such as reporting to a high performer, holding a career-accelerator role such as being a supervisor, and not taking advantage of flexible work options all play a leading role in promotions and pay increases. Disparities in performance ratings also have a cascading effect that adversely affects people of color: In the author&#39;s study, people of color in the majority of companies were up to 50% less likely to receive high performance ratings. Because ratings tend to persist, with a high rating one year predicting the likelihood of a high rating the next, getting shut out from the start can significantly impede career progression.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="no-underline">The Unequal Rewards of Peer Support at Work</a></h4><h6> Nancy Baym and Constance Noonan Hadley</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> Job satisfaction comes in part from how well people feel their organization recognizes and values the social support they provide to colleagues.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Employees&#39; supportive behaviors with one another boost engagement and productivity, but research shows that men gain more benefits from such efforts than women do. Social support includes emotional assistance, esteem reinforcement, social companionship, information or advice, and instrumental help. In the authors&#39; study, more women than men focused their efforts on listening, showing personal interest, and complimenting a coworker, while men reported offering career advice more frequently. Although men said they provided less-frequent social support than women overall, they received higher levels of organizational encouragement, rewards, and job satisfaction. Managers can encourage a more equitable peer culture by making the invisible visible and valuable — providing clarity about which behaviors count while also revising performance management systems.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-unequal-rewards-of-peer-support-at-work/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="no-underline">Moving Beyond Islands of Experimentation to AI Everywhere</a></h4><h6> Amit Joshi, Ivy Buche, and Miguel Paredes Sadler</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> It may make sense to start AI efforts with isolated experiments, but new, companywide structures are needed to scale them and reap broader benefits.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> Artificial intelligence often takes root in isolated experiments within an organization, and many companies stall out on their AI journeys because of difficulty moving beyond these pilots. Scaling technology requires different types of formal structures: The authors found that AI projects generally begin as islands of experimentation before coming together around a corporate <em>center of excellence</em> . A small number then move to a sophisticated <em>federation of expertise</em> model built on a centralized base of knowledge, systems, processes, and tools, and on decentralized embedded capabilities. Enterprises with AI ambitions need to be prepared to make two structural leaps away from the startup stage if they are intent on delivering on the technology&#39;s potential.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/moving-beyond-islands-of-experimentation-to-ai-everywhere/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><hr /><h4> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="no-underline">Manage Your Workforce Ecosystem, Not Just Your Employees</a></h4><h6> Elizabeth J. Altman, David Kiron, Jeff Schwartz, and Robin Jones</h6><p> <strong>Key Insight:</strong> New organizational structures are needed to coordinate workforce ecosystems that include a wide array of external workers and partners.</p><p> <strong>Top Takeaways:</strong> A majority of executives agree that the idea of “the workforce” is being redefined. They say it&#39;s broader than an organization&#39;s full-time employees, instead encompassing ecosystems of contractors, gig workers, service providers, and even technologies. These networks require innovative management practices, given that hierarchical, command-and-control leadership is ill suited for workforces that span internal and external boundaries. In developing new practices, leaders must address three types of issues: structural design (pertaining to the division of labor, goals, and incentives), politics (relating to resources, power, and status), and culture (affecting individuals&#39; search for identity and meaning). Intentionally orchestrating a perspective that considers all players leads to a more nuanced view of how organizations and their partners cooperate to meet their strategic goals.</p><p> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/manage-your-workforce-ecosystem-not-just-your-employees/" class="pan-series__series-read-more">Read the article</a></p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/our-guide-to-the-summer-2023-issue/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Professional Services Firms Dodged Disruption</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:23:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Julian Birkinshaw and David Lancefield. <p>Julian Birkinshaw is a professor of strategy at London Business School, where he also serves as vice dean. David Lancefield is a CEO catalyst, strategist, and coach and a former senior partner at PwC.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Thinking]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors conducted in-depth interviews with more than 25 senior professionals in consultancies and law firms. They also reviewed case studies of a dozen would-be disrupters and carried out an extensive review of the literature. Professional services firms have been threatened with disruption for a long time. In 2015, Richard and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Birkinshaw_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Simon Prades</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors conducted in-depth interviews with more than 25 senior professionals in consultancies and law firms.</li><li> They also reviewed case studies of a dozen would-be disrupters and carried out an extensive review of the literature.</li></ul></aside><p> Professional services firms have been threatened with disruption for a long time. In 2015, Richard and Daniel Susskind foresaw that technology would cause a “steady decline in the need for traditional flesh-and-blood professionals,” while more recently, CB Insights said that “a tectonic disruption is hitting management consulting.” <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Even earlier, Clayton Christensen and colleagues warned, “Although we cannot forecast the exact progress of disruption in the consulting industry, we can say with utter confidence that whatever its pace, some incumbents will be caught by surprise.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a></p><p> But things have not played out as predicted. In consulting and law, the established firms are as influential and profitable as ever. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Many potential disrupters have come along. Some have failed, some have gained strong niche positions, but none has challenged — let alone toppled — the existing order. Most established leaders have used a wide range of strategies and tactics to adapt quickly to the threats.</p><p></p><p> As is the case in many well-established industries, professional services markets are dominated by a small, clearly identifiable group at the top and large numbers of lower-tier firms operating in their shadow. Consulting&#39;s giants include McKinsey, Boston Consulting Group, and Bain; technology-based firms Accenture and Capgemini; and the Big Four accounting firms Ernst &amp; Young, Deloitte, KPMG, and PwC. In law, the top tier includes the five London-based firms informally known as the Magic Circle — Linklaters, Clifford Chance, Freshfields, Allen &amp; Overy, and Slaughter and May — along with Kirkland &amp; Ellis, Latham &amp; Watkins, and DLA Piper.</p><p> How have these firms been so resilient? Our research, which included interviews with 25 executives and a review of case studies on a dozen would-be disrupters, revealed many factors at work. The one that distinguishes the most effective firms is their capacity to diagnose potential causes of disruption and respond accordingly.</p><p> We define <em>industry disruption</em> as an upending of the established order, with incumbents losing out to new competitors. As Joshua Gans has argued, disruption can occur when incumbent firms have blind spots about what customers want (a demand-side effect) or when a new technology makes the incumbents&#39; existing capabilities obsolete (a supply-side effect) — or a combination of the two. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> (See “Four Types of Potential Threat in Consulting and Law.”)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Four Types of Potential Threat in Consulting and Law</h4><p class="caption"> Professional services firms face threats on both the demand and supply sides.</p><p class="caption"> Supply-side disruption increases as the capabilities delivered by the incumbent decrease in value to the customer. Demand-side disruption grows along with increased changes in customer behavior. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_Birkinshaw-Figure.png" alt="Four Types of Potential Threat in Consulting and Law" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Because each scenario requires its own response, understanding the dynamics of supply- and demand-side effects can enable executives in any sector to more readily identify potential disrupters and keep them at bay. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><h3> Demand- and Supply-Side Threats</h3><p> Based on our research, we identified artificial intelligence technology as the biggest supply-side risk, threatening to take over work that professionals have traditionally seen as their own. On the demand side, the threat comes from clients seeking greater control over how they buy and use professional services. Still other would-be disrupters challenge incumbents from both the supply and demand sides at the same time. Meanwhile, new boutique and specialist firms have cropped up to serve particular client needs in lucrative business segments, though they have rarely been truly disruptive. Below, we look at each potential threat in detail.</p><p> <strong>AI undermines the business model.</strong> The launch of generative AI in November 2022 has accelerated the ongoing transformation of many aspects of professional services work, enabling greater accuracy and significant cost savings.</p><p> At law firms, AI tools scan legal documents and review contracts. AI-based services companies such as Kira Systems, Clio, Reveal-Brainspace, iManage, and Thomson Reuters provide assistance in discovery, due diligence, and contract management and review. Thomson Reuters&#39;s services are used by 97% of the largest law firms.</p><p> These companies don&#39;t position themselves as competitors to law firms, but as they scale and the technology gains capabilities, they can begin to undermine those firms&#39; business models. Clio&#39;s legal software, for example, can conduct e-discovery for a claim and even engage in litigation analysis by scanning precedent-setting cases, potentially reducing the number of billable hours that a firm can charge to clients.</p><p> In consulting, AI can help professional services firms provide additional value by uncovering new relationships, identifying patterns of customer behavior, and highlighting cost-saving opportunities. “It&#39;s no longer good enough to show up with a team that knows more about this industry than anybody else,” one Big Four consulting partner said. “You also need a data set or an algorithm that provides additional sources of value.”</p><p> But AI can also be a powerful disrupter. Palantir Technologies started out using AI to detect fraud and has since expanded to applying state-of-the-art machine learning to solve problems for a variety of government and private clients. Its work in support of government surveillance has drawn controversy, but its predictive analytics helped a large automotive supplier make large efficiency gains in its engineering and manufacturing functions. Such results represent a significant advance in the rigor and quality of insights consulting firms can offer.</p><p> Established firms have taken on the threat by building up their own AI capabilities through acquisitions and in-house development. McKinsey has acquired 12 mostly small AI firms since 2013, including UK-based QuantumBlack, which uses advanced data analytics to improve organizational performance. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> In law, San Francisco-based DLA Piper has developed Aiscension, an AI product that monitors compliance risks. The insurance law firm Kennedys created its Kennedys IQ spinoff, which uses AI to assess medical evidence and recommend amounts for damages.</p><p> These acquisitions and partnerships deliver more than new capabilities; they can expand the range of issues their firms can handle for clients.</p><p> Incumbents are also enhancing their role as high-touch trusted advisers, which AI cannot replicate. Several large consulting firms have increased their range of offerings by investing in experience centers — physical and virtual environments where clients and consultants use design thinking and other creative techniques to envision possible futures. Over the past five years, IBM, Deloitte, Accenture, and other firms have bought more than 200 creative agencies to help develop these centers.</p><p> <strong>Clients take control: unbundling the service.</strong> The most profound demand-side threat is unbundling, as increasingly savvy clients look for ways to cut costs and exert greater influence over their relationships with services firms. This can mean reclaiming activities previously handled by outside firms or turning to specialists instead of the broad offering of a large professional firm. Both options can help clients build up their internal capabilities and gain greater accountability for business outcomes. But unbundling threatens the incumbent firms&#39; leverage model by taking away work that would typically be assigned to a lot of their junior — and lower-paid — generalists.</p><p> In law, the emergence of alternative legal service providers (ALSPs) is a testament to this demand-side threat. ALSPs aren&#39;t law firms as such, but they provide a vast array of legal services, such as document review or contract management, at a lower cost. In 2017, DXC Technology, a Virginia-based IT services firm, outsourced almost its entire legal function to UnitedLex, an ALSP based in Overland Park, Kansas. DXC transferred 150 in-house lawyers to UnitedLex, retaining only a small number of senior professionals. While outsourcing in-house legal departments is not uncommon, law firms saw this as a huge threat because it was the biggest transaction of its kind at the time and because it involved an ALSP, which can offer a much lower cost structure.</p><p> Consulting faces a similar challenge from the rise of consulting networks, such as London-based Eden McCallum, and from online platforms, such as New York-based Gerson Lehrman Group. These companies match clients with consultants on a project-by-project basis, bypassing the large firms. London-based Kubrick Group contracts with companies to provide teams of data scientists and technologists, who can later be hired by the client.</p><p> Such arrangements put the onus on the client to define its problems and integrate work teams — something traditionally handled by a large consulting firm. But they eliminate the need to hire a large firm except on the biggest and most complex projects. And without the incumbents&#39; higher overhead, fees are much lower.</p><p> Clients are also changing commercial arrangements, increasingly demanding outcome-based deals that require consultants to demonstrate that they were directly responsible for the desired results, such as a 5% reduction in costs. Because this can be harder to do with projects that involve factors outside the consultants&#39; influence, like growing revenue, most firms agree to outcome-based deals only when they can be confident of contributing to the desired result.</p><p> Incumbent firms are responding to these demand-side challenges in a couple of ways. Law firms have formed their own ALSPs; London-based Allen &amp; Overy created Peerpoint in 2013, a separate operation with 350 largely freelance lawyers and 53 million pounds ($64 million) in revenue. In consulting, Deloitte created a unit called Pixel that breaks down client problems into their constituent parts and then uses a crowdsourcing platform to find the right experts to work on each part.</p><p> The large firms are also doubling down on their traditional strengths: tackling clients&#39; biggest and most challenging problems. Their value comes from their ability to provide advice and compliance in high-impact, large-scale, high-risk situations, and they can charge a premium for the service. “We do open heart surgery rather than provide [general practitioner] services,” said one senior lawyer.</p><p> <strong>Boutiques and specialists find strength in market focus.</strong> New competitors emerge all the time in professional services, as former top partners set up their own boutiques or venture firms back new startups. The successful ones take market share in specific niches but rarely cause much concern to top-tier firms. They cause limited disruption on either the demand or supply side, and they simply reflect the heterogeneity and complexity of the market.</p><p> In consulting, London-based Baringa has grown quickly by focusing on the energy industry, identifying such hot topics as renewable energy and hiring specialists who use scenario modeling to project future energy prices. New York-based AlixPartners focuses on turnarounds, litigation support, and transformation. Both firms have more than 1,000 employees. The legal industry has seen the rapid growth of specialists such as Caldwell Intellectual Property Law in the US and Mishcon de Reya, a specialist in disputes, in the UK and Singapore. The success of such firms shows how deep expertise can create a defensible niche against broad-based competitors.</p><p> Large firms don&#39;t view these smaller businesses as a direct threat and often ignore them altogether. “They&#39;re not on our radar for the work we do with the C-suite,” said a partner in a large London law firm. Still, they can help incumbents stay vigilant.</p><p> For one, they provide a window on a changing marketplace, often prodding established firms to move into business areas they might have otherwise neglected. Deloitte, for example, launched its digital business in response to the emergence of specialized boutique firms. Bain created and spun off The Bridgespan Group in order to focus on nonprofits.</p><p> The specialty firms can also expose weaknesses in top-tier firms&#39; ways of working that need attention. For example, Altman Solon, the largest global strategy consulting firm specializing in telecommunications, media, and technology, commands C-suite attention in large part because the entire firm comprises specialists with deep expertise in those sectors, unlike many large firms that fill junior ranks with a lot of smart generalists. As a result, it is already up to speed with the industries in which it operates and thus is better able to develop client-specific strategies quickly.</p><p> <strong>Would-be disrupters that pose supply- and demand-side risk.</strong> The nightmare scenario for incumbents is disruption that affects the supply and demand sides at the same time. This is ultimately what killed Kodak and Polaroid: Digital technology changed how images were created and how they were consumed, leaving the incumbents nothing valuable to fall back on. The survivors from the photography industry, such as Fuji and Canon, did so by moving into adjacent markets, not by staying and fighting.</p><p> Such challengers have appeared in professional services, but so far they have fallen short as disrupters. For example, HourlyNerd, founded in 2013, had big ambitions to become a marketplace for connecting technology clients with freelance consultants, giving the client a wider choice of consultants at a faster rate than the typical procurement process. “We like to think of ourselves as a replacement to potentially hiring a consulting firm,” one of the cofounders said. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Axiom Law, founded in 2000, sought to provide on-demand legal talent using a network of employees and associates to provide legal services more efficiently. “Axiom has an opportunity to disrupt an industry that hasn&#39;t materially changed in a century,” one investor said. <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a></p><p> Both firms have done moderately well. HourlyNerd, which rebranded as Catalant in 2016, shifted to a software-as-a-service model and today has several hundred employees. Axiom is a midsize law firm with about 1,600 employees, $842.5 million in revenue, and a more flexible business model than most of its competitors. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a> But neither has achieved the disruptive effects it aspired to.</p><p></p><h3> Disruptive Threats on the Horizon</h3><p> So, what looming disruptions keep the executives running consulting and law firms awake at night?</p><p> One factor the senior professionals we interviewed pointed to is a dramatic acceleration in AI and analytics capabilities. In law, codification — the process of capturing the legal reasoning of an experienced partner and turning that into an algorithm that can then be applied to future cases — threatens to eliminate much of the cognitive work now done by professionals. “That would be disruptive,” said a partner in a large London firm.</p><p> Several others indicated that the biggest threat in the near future will most likely come from the giant technology companies: Google, Amazon, Microsoft, and Salesforce, in particular. Each has built client-facing capabilities, some from the large consulting firms, to enhance their strength in selling solutions to clients&#39; technology challenges.</p><p> With their AI capabilities and global reach, they could affect both the supply and demand sides of professional firms&#39; businesses. For example, using the vast amount of data at its disposal, Amazon Web Services could exploit its unique insights into customer behavior to provide retail clients with forecasts of online shopping trends.</p><p> “The greatest impact of Amazon Web Services won&#39;t lie in its position as a supplier of cloud services, but in the extraordinary scale and depth of its information on consumer buying behavior, which no conventional consulting firm could begin to compete with,” said a partner in a large consulting firm.</p><p> Others downplayed the threat. “The likes of Google are not actually that good at client service,” one interviewee said. While it is possible that a tech company could buy a large consulting firm, that would represent a significant strategic pivot from the typical approach of developing partnerships with consulting firms and would reduce the number of firms it could partner with in the future.</p><h3> Staying Nimble</h3><p> The big professional services firms haven&#39;t avoided disruption simply because of the actions they&#39;ve taken. More important is their vigilance and responsiveness to changes in their business environment. While consulting and law firm executives often disparage their seemingly old-fashioned ways of working, their professional partnership models have proved to be remarkably resilient.</p><p> From our interviews, we identified three elements of success that are worth highlighting as potentially applicable to other sectors as well.</p><p> <strong>Innovation efforts are devoted to solving client problems.</strong> This contrasts with many other businesses, where innovation activities are pursued separately from the customer-facing parts of the organization. The best professional services firms pursue product and service innovations based on common limitations, frictions, and opportunities they&#39;ve identified in their clients&#39; businesses. They then develop, test, and refine those innovations with selected clients and partner organizations — such as technology providers — before launching them across their client portfolios.</p><p> <strong>Partners and their juniors work closely together with clients.</strong> The firms&#39; apprenticeship model means that the sense-response gap — the difference between sensing client needs and then taking appropriate action to address them — is narrower than in firms where the leaders are a long way removed from those doing the work.</p><p> <strong>Firms take a cautious approach to investing in new activities.</strong> While this might seem to be a weakness in a fast-changing world, the truth is that most emerging technologies take a long time to realize their potential, and plenty of firms have failed by moving too quickly. Because of the project-based nature of their work, professional firms are able to test new technologies, see what works, and then move forward based on project success and client demand.</p><h3> Staying Ahead of Disruption</h3><p> The experience of professional services firms in holding off potential disruption suggests four actions that firms in other sectors can take to prepare for and respond to change.</p><p> <strong>Diagnose the threat.</strong> While every new competitor or technology can be seen as a potential threat, it&#39;s necessary to assess the magnitude of the risk and the part of the business that it might affect. The consulting and law firms we studied were mostly very thoughtful about separating out the demand- and supply-side effects. (See “Diagnosing the Nature of the Disruptive Threat” for how to apply this logic.)</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Diagnosing the Nature of the Disruptive Threat</h4><p class="caption"> Consider an emerging technology or new competitor in your industry and answer the following questions to determine the nature of the disruptive threat.</p><p class="print no-mobile no-desktop caption"> Take the assessment at https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/</p><p> <a id="interactive-modal" href="#modal-container" class="is-button aqua no-print" style="max-width:275px">Take the assessment now</a> </p><p class="caption"><svg height="20.25" viewBox="0 0 18.183 20.25" width="18.183" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><clipPath id="a"><path d="m0 0h18.183v20.25h-18.183z"></path></clipPath><g clip-path="url(#a)"><path d="m17.081 12.4a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v5.648a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1 1.1h-15.981a1.087 1.087 0 0 1 -1.1-1.1v-5.648a1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1-1.1 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v4.546h13.642v-4.546a1.324 1.324 0 0 1 1.24-1.1m-11.71-4.135 2.618 2.617v-9.642a1.214 1.214 0 0 1 1.102-1.24 1.185 1.185 0 0 1 1.1 1.1v9.643l2.617-2.48a1.012 1.012 0 0 1 .827-.276 1.958 1.958 0 0 1 .827.276 1.254 1.254 0 0 1 0 1.653l-4.545 4.548c-.138.138-.276.138-.413.276a.878.878 0 0 1 -.827 0c-.138 0-.276-.138-.413-.276l-4.546-4.684a1.081 1.081 0 0 1 0-1.515 1.257 1.257 0 0 1 1.653 0" fill="#000000"></path></g></svg> <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a3e29f5546.pdf" target="_blank" class="marketing_click" id="Download_Assessment[Birkinshaw_article]" rel="noopener">Download the scorecard (PDF)</a></p><div id="modal-container"><div  id="btn-close-modal" class="close-modal-container"> ← RETURN TO ARTICLE </div><div class="modal-content"><iframe src="https://survey.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_eWAtUnHf3GCdswu" width="100%" frameborder="0"></iframe></div></p></div><p><script>$("#interactive-modal").animatedModal({modalTarget:'modal-container',animatedIn:'fadeInRightBig',animatedOut:'fadeOutRightBig',animationDuration:'.6s',color:'#292929',overflow:'hidden'});</script></p></article></aside></div><p> <strong>Match the response to the challenge.</strong> Once the supply and demand effects have been mapped, it&#39;s possible to target the appropriate response. Demand-side challenges require experimentation in how clients&#39; needs can be anticipated, understood, met, and adjusted to. Professional services firms are inherently good at this. Project teams are empowered to come up with creative solutions and to experiment with alternative models for forming partnerships and delivering services. This should serve as a cautionary note to firms that have become too “corporate,” with decisions flowing from the top down to partners and teams.</p><p> Supply-side changes, in contrast, require investment in new capabilities and an openness to restructuring and even outsourcing internal activities. This often requires a higher level of centralization, frequently with a dedicated team that hires from the outside or makes small acquisitions. The challenge is to integrate them with client project teams so they are deployed in the market.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Stay focused on the organization&#39;s true mission.</strong> While there are plenty of genuine threats out there, there&#39;s also a lot of noise. Paying too much attention to all of the changes swirling around can cause leaders to lose sight of the bigger picture. For professional services firms, the client relationship transcends all else, and the appropriate response to both demand- and supply-driven threats is to double down on that relationship. “We want to retain the overall relationship, focusing on the areas of premium work,” the partner in a large London law firm said. “The debate is how much we leave ... to other law firms and how much we retain and do via third parties or alternative delivery models.”</p><p> <strong>Balance pragmatism with a healthy paranoia.</strong> The law and consulting partners we spoke with in our interviews were genuinely torn. On the one hand, they saw little or no evidence that their strong positions were under threat, and they agreed that the dire predictions of disruption from a decade ago had been unfounded. On the other hand, they did not want to appear complacent, and they certainly didn&#39;t want to send a message to their junior colleagues that there were no future risks of disruption. Executives must learn to live with a dual mindset: a pragmatic acknowledgment that the fundamentals are sound, coupled with a paranoid suspicion of emerging technologies or new competitors. After all, it was those incumbents that might be caught by surprise that Christensen and his colleagues considered most at risk of disruption.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-professional-services-firms-dodged-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Risk Intelligence and the Resilient Company</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/#comments</comments><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:05:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ananya Sheth and Joseph V. Sinfield. <p>Ananya Sheth ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ananyasheth">@ananyasheth</a> ) is a postdoctoral research fellow at the School of Business, Stevens Institute of Technology. Joseph V. Sinfield is a professor of civil engineering and the director of the Institute for Innovation Science at Purdue University.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Mitigation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Business Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Developing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Simon Prades The Research The authors undertook a holistic study of enterprise resilience that began with the extraction of corporate risk factors from two decades of 10-Ks filed by S&#038;P 500 companies, investment analyst reports, and academic databases. They organized the risks into a value-centric framework composed of eight functions and 99 major risk categories; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Sheth_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Simon Prades</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>The authors undertook a holistic study of enterprise resilience that began with the extraction of corporate risk factors from two decades of 10-Ks filed by S&amp;P 500 companies, investment analyst reports, and academic databases.</li><li> They organized the risks into a value-centric framework composed of eight functions and 99 major risk categories; they then cross-linked the categories and functions with input from risk experts and leaders in 10 economic sectors and 26 industries to create a quantitative risk network.</li><li> They also analyzed cybersecurity risk acknowledgment in S&amp;P 500 10-Ks for five sectors.</li><li> This material is based upon work supported by the National Science Foundation under grant no. 2049782.</li></ul></aside><p> Building the resilience of large, complex enterprises is critical in today&#39;s uncertain and interconnected world. At a time when a container ship grounded in the Suez Canal can bottle up 12% of the world&#39;s trade, or a virus can disrupt the global flow of commodities, components, and talent, a corporation&#39;s ability to quickly adapt in the face of unfolding events is essential to its survival and prosperity.</p><p> Business resilience is a dynamic property that is retrospectively measured by the stability and longevity of corporate value across changing contexts. In real time, it manifests in an enterprise&#39;s timely adaptation to both immediate and gradual changes in the business environment.</p><p> Our work, which employs a complex adaptive systems view of businesses, shows that resilience derives from three fundamental adaptive capacities: sensing and monitoring, to recognize emerging changes in the business environment; business model portfolio development, to build and test capabilities across operating contexts; and fundamental capability development, to drive growth with longevity and avoid corporate stall. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> Moreover, each of these capacities hinges on the development of a capability for <em>risk intelligence</em> .</p><p></p><p> We define risk intelligence as the honed ability to rigorously interpret risks and the consequences or opportunities they pose for a company. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> It allows leaders to see through environmental complexity and systematically identify, categorize, and interpret risks. This enables them to look beyond known risk factors and intentionally explore yet-to-be-known risks, thereby embracing rather than avoiding uncertainty. Importantly, risk intelligence brings recognition that individual risks or the forms in which they manifest matter far less than the often-shared consequences they have on a company&#39;s value exchange system — that is, the manner in which it manages, identifies, creates, conveys, delivers, captures, protects, and sustains value. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> And finally, it provides leaders with a network view of risks that enables more effective allocation of risk mitigation resources by illuminating not just the direct consequences of risks but the manner in which they could cascade across the company&#39;s value exchange system. In this article, we break down risk intelligence into actionable elements that leaders can pursue to help toughen their organizations for the long term.</p><h3> Identify, Categorize, and Interpret Risk Events</h3><p> Leaders cannot accurately predict specific risk events, nor can they prepare their companies for all risks. They can, however, identify, categorize, and interpret risk events in a systematic manner that reveals how seemingly different events could have similar consequences.</p><p> The first step is to work through each business value function and identify plausible risk events that may have implications for its effectiveness. To aid in this process, we constructed an industry-agnostic inventory organizing three tiers of 99 major risk categories identified in our study in relation to individual value exchange system components. (See “A Value Function Risk Inventory.”) While inevitably not exhaustive, this resource serves as a robust starting point to identify potential risks faced by any enterprise. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig1"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> A Value Function Risk Inventory</h4><p class="caption"> This risk inventory derived from 20 years of S&amp;P 500 data shows how the functions of a company&#39;s value exchange system (green nodes) link to business functions and their respective risk categories. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig1.png" alt="A Value Function Risk Inventory"/></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Next, leaders should characterize and group risk events by their <em>scope</em> of impact, the <em>permanence</em> of the changes they induce, and the <em>frequency</em> of event occurrence. (See “Characterizing Risks.”) Leaders can then interpret the linkages between each group of risk events and the components of the company&#39;s value exchange system.</p><div class="callout-highlight" id="fig2"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Characterizing Risks</h4><p class="caption"> Every risk can be characterized according to how widely its impact may be felt, how long the changes it causes may last, and how often it occurs. For example, a major snow event has intra-industry scope, induces temporary changes, and occurs infrequently. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig2.png" alt="Characterizing Risks" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Risk categorization begins with understanding a risk event&#39;s scope, which conveys a sense of how widely a risk&#39;s effects will be felt across the range of affected stakeholders. The wide scope of the COVID-19 pandemic created supply- and demand-side effects across entire value networks, whereas narrow-scope events, such as a labor strike at an individual manufacturing facility, tend to have more bounded effects. When multiple stakeholders experience simultaneous or sequential disruptions, the increased complexity of the impact prevents the system from self-organizing to normalcy. Such circumstances also may invite interventions from sovereign states or international organizations, which can aid recovery or act as new disruptive forces.</p><p> To fully categorize risk events, leaders must also consider the permanence of their consequences. Both the pandemic and the 2021 Suez Canal blockage caused supply-side disruptions, but the permanence of the changes each event induced varied significantly. While supply chain shocks such as the canal blockage often follow a self-organizing correction mechanism in which price increases lower demand and normalize the lagging supply, the same formula cannot be applied to counter a protracted situation like the pandemic. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> It is important to understand permanence before planning and implementing a response strategy. For example, the business interruption created by the pandemic had a scope that was broader and consequences that were of greater permanence, affecting a significantly larger set of value system functions in comparison to the more limited impact of the canal blockage.</p><p></p><p> How often a risk event occurs is important too, because the enterprise mechanisms needed to handle frequent events can be different from those employed for singular events. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> Although companies learn from all events, their responses to those that occur repeatedly are typically converted into standard operating procedures. <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a> For example, the adoption of barcodes and scanners to track and manage inventory in real time has largely eliminated stock-keeping record errors and delays resulting from mismatching data.</p><p> Our scope, permanence, and frequency (SPF) framework provides a structured view that shows how a risk event itself is less important than its consequences. The framework is especially useful when multiple risk events occur at the same time, because it gives managers a common, logical approach for considering them and quickly gaining information and understanding. By then connecting those events to the company&#39;s value exchange system, managers can more easily see when diverse risks are nonetheless leading to similar consequences for its value functions. <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> Consider a manufacturer dealing with both an overseas supplier whose products are suddenly subject to much higher tariffs due to a trade war, and the bankruptcy of a value chain partner. These risk events share SPF characteristics (the scope of both is interfirm, their permanence is reversible, and their frequency is low), and, as important, both events also affect the same value functions. The bankruptcy and the trade war are both likely to slow inputs and raise costs on the supply side and make it more difficult to meet customer demand. Both also would require the manufacturer to secure new supply sources and stabilize operational cash flow. By characterizing these potential risk events according to the SPF framework and linking them to value functions, managers can then view them more simply as groups of risks that have shared consequences for a company&#39;s specific value functions and deserve similar preparedness and response.</p><h3> Compartmentalize and Reduce Uncertainty</h3><p> Uncertainty about the consequences of a risk event is unavoidable, but it can be managed based on where the level of uncertainty falls on a spectrum between complete knowledge and complete ignorance (both of which are extreme and unlikely). <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a> Leaders should then seek to convert risks with higher levels of impact uncertainty to lower levels. (See “Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty.”) </p><div class="callout-highlight callout--expand-column" id="fig3"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty</h4><p class="caption"> Once managers have mapped risks to the appropriate level, they should take the critical action recommended to convert higher-order risks to lower-order risks. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig3.png" alt="Managing Levels of Impact Uncertainty" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p></p><p> Risk events causing level 1 uncertainty usually entail a very limited number of future scenarios with clear intrafirm effects, where causal linkages between risk events and the enterprise&#39;s value exchange system can be accurately known. Examples of such events include routine variation in production, expected sales losses, and human errors in performing manual tasks. When specific types of level 1 events occur frequently, they are indicative of errors in process or oversight that can be rectified permanently if diagnosed correctly. For instance, cargo thefts — a recurrent problem at logjammed transport hubs — can be prevented using optical character recognition scanners that track container freight and maintain real-time records. Importantly, at level 1, the overall uncertainty of the impact on firm value is within an expected, acceptable range.</p><p> Risk events causing level 2 uncertainty involve a larger number of alternate future scenarios and have interfirm consequences; however, even though they are more challenging, the probability that they will occur and their effects can be estimated. Businesses&#39; formal scenario planning exercises often involve level 2 events in which previously acquired knowledge regarding the impact of risk factors leads to improved accuracy and an effective exercise overall. The six-day Suez Canal blockage was predictable because a multiship pileup had closed the canal for two days in 2018. As a result, the Pentagon had already worked a longer blockage into its normal operational preparedness. <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p> Risk events causing level 3 uncertainty involve a bounded set of scenarios where certain known risk events may affect the company in unknown ways. There is limited knowledge about how a chain reaction of consequences from a risk event might manifest at this level. Typically, these risks include less frequently occurring events with intra-industry scope and multistakeholder implications, which should be considered worst-case scenarios.</p><p> <a href="https://www.portrevel.com/">Port Revel</a> , a training facility situated on a lake in the French Alps, reduces level 3 uncertainty by helping ocean shipping companies simulate worst cases and identify the previously unknown consequences of operating increasingly large container ships through shipping infrastructure largely designed for smaller vessels. It closely replicates conditions at the trickiest spots in maritime transport, allowing trainee pilots to navigate scaled giant container ships through strong gusts of wind across a mini-Suez, steer and dock cruise ships in a crowded mini-San Francisco Bay, and maneuver oil tankers through an imitation Port Arthur. These exercises draw out unanticipated ship performance and pilot behaviors, helping to identify and address previously unknown event consequences.</p><p> Level 4 uncertainty encompasses events with unknown risk factors that could have a variety of negative consequences, the repercussions of which can&#39;t be estimated. These unknown unknowns are usually expressed in 10-Ks through statements such as “Other unknown risks may impact our business operations and projected performance.” It is challenging to develop scenario models in the presence of unknown unknowns. The models are incomplete representations of the world that could entail risks unimagined while developing them.</p><p> Once leaders order the uncertainty of impact into levels, they can focus on converting higher-level impact uncertainty into lower levels by discovering unknowns through data, simulation modeling, and logical analyses. For instance, the three-year gap between the UK&#39;s Brexit referendum in 2016 and its departure from the European Union in 2019 offered leaders an opportunity to convert the imagined event into likely scenarios and capture its vast trade implications. By focusing on the most vulnerable aspects of their value chains, such as those with the highest number of cross-border transactions, leaders could have recognized the imminent redistribution of goods passing through congested ports and modeled rerouting scenarios. For example, Felixstowe was known to be handling 48% of the UK&#39;s container trade, which could have been sent instead to multiple smaller and less busy ports. Evidence of impending port congestion also could have implied the high likelihood of delays and the need to hold more inventory in the UK to guarantee on-time deliveries.</p><p> Systemwide changes that are likely to have permanent effects are typically caused by noticeable megatrends, such as technological breakthroughs, changes in consumer demand patterns, global events, or regulatory body interventions. Once these trends are on a company&#39;s radar, they can be tracked and rapidly interpreted (if the necessary observation and modeling capabilities are in place). For instance, the European Union&#39;s carbon border tax, which was enacted in December 2022 after years of debate, won&#39;t be fully implemented until 2026, offering companies several years to reduce the uncertainty arising from it.</p><p></p><p> Further, for potential events that may be infrequent yet high impact, businesses can examine other industries where the consequences of similar events might be better recognized; then they can interpret the implications for their own value exchange system. For example, Brexit strategists could have studied cross-border trade between the US and Canada and the US and Mexico in the automobile and white goods sectors to help them navigate looming free-trade agreements and border regulations.</p><p> The active identification of plausible risk events and their potential consequences are the kinds of actions that contribute to building true risk intelligence. However, our research indicates that companies place little emphasis on discovering unknown and plausible risk events and their outcomes and instead focus attention on managing known risks. We also find that companies do not have a similarly complete knowledge of risks, even when those risks are publicly disclosed by direct competitors. Our study of 10-Ks revealed significant variation in the acknowledgment of risk factors, even among companies in the same industry. For instance, there was a lag of as much as eight years in acknowledging cyber risks after the first public data breach within a group of 18 comparable companies in the financial sector. This pattern was consistent in four additional sectors — including retail, telecom, technology, and health care.</p><p> Moreover, our analyses revealed only marginal levels of acknowledgment of causal relationships between risk factors, which are how risks impact companies in the real world. It is only logical that a known or unknown risk factor, when manifested, would likely influence other linked known and unknown risk factors, thereby creating a cascade of consequences. This ultimately would affect a company in potentially known but unexpected (or, worse, misunderstood) ways.</p><p></p><p> While most companies think they are preparing for risk events, they tend to focus only on level 1 and 2 uncertainty and therefore develop highly specific but narrow mitigation plans. Take Maersk, for example, which in 2017 fell victim to a ransomware cyberattack that brought down its entire network for days and halted its operations at 76 port terminals globally at a cost of roughly $300 million. <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a> Yet the shipping company did not publicly acknowledge the risk of a cyberattack until its 2013 annual report, despite the risk of hacking and other cyberthreats having been well known since the late 1990s (although perhaps not seriously regarded as a primary risk for shippers). Thus, few risks are entirely unknown, and industry-specific unknowns may not be unknowns in other sectors.</p><h3> Construct and Contextualize an Enterprise Risk Network</h3><p> To gain clearer insight into level 3 and 4 uncertainty, it is important to understand the linkages among enterprise risks. Developing quantified risk networks (QRNs) can help. A QRN is a weighted map that links all identified potential risks to a company&#39;s value exchange system functions and helps decision makers interpret related impacts. Moreover, QRNs can reveal counterintuitive insights, such as a function&#39;s indirect exposure to risks typically associated with a different but connected function. For example, the risk of inaccurately forecasting shipping demand in a freight company directly affects its operating expense management function and indirectly affects facility capacity, operational capability, and customer concessions, as well as the company&#39;s reputation.</p><p> Companies should build their own risk networks for three reasons. First, each company has its own unique value exchange system that is best understood by its leaders. Second, resilient companies need to build in redundancies, which is challenging to do in resource-constrained environments. Custom QRNs highlight the most connected — and most vulnerable — value functions, creating an order of priority for allocating resources to bolster the enterprise. Third, custom QRNs provide a shared picture of risk for company leaders, who may or may not agree on critical vulnerabilities. The QRN-building activity focuses managerial attention on the often disregarded but potentially crucial functions and related risk categories to ultimately help leaders anticipate and prepare for the future.</p><p> To begin constructing your company&#39;s risk network, identify the risk events that are particularly relevant to your business by working from critical value functions upon which it relies and from the risk categories captured in the inventory. Identify plausible risk events in each category from data sources such as company memos, public risk disclosures, investment analyst reports, and historical knowledge. For example, leaders managing the operations function can use inventory risk categories, such as facilities and process management, sourcing, and distribution, to build a list of plausible risk factors or events (such as an unexpected storm, an equipment malfunction, input shortages, drained emergency supplies, worker health emergencies, communications interruptions, or labor strikes) that could affect business continuity. Note that these lists will likely contain several risk factors under each risk category.</p><p> Next, characterize relevant risks using the SPF framework, identify plausible scenarios related to the company&#39;s value functions, and identify potential responses. This exercise gives managers the opportunity to pay extra attention to less appreciated risks and helps them reduce the overall level of uncertainty of the impact of risks on the company&#39;s value exchange system.</p><p> Since the archetypal company is organized by function, the consequences of potential risks on individual functions (such as a labor strike&#39;s effect on sourcing) and the interconnectivity between different value functions themselves should be estimated for each functional node in the QRN. For instance, once managers define the level of interconnectivity between the sourcing and operations functions in their company, they can deduce the direct consequences of a labor strike for sourcing and its indirect consequences for operations. Weighting impacts, even using relative terms such as high, medium, and low, provides a common language for managers to discuss significant risks and plausible scenarios and can help resolve debate on what is likely or what is important. Functions identified as particularly important or vulnerable should be analyzed by experts to develop a deeper understanding of the risks affecting them and their interconnectivity.</p><p> We created a generalized QRN, beginning by asking leaders with sector and functional expertise to indicate interconnectivity between their function and other business functions on a 10-point scale. (See “A Quantitative Risk Network.”) Then we asked the leaders to indicate the potential impact of specific risks to their functional area arising from these connections. For example, a sales and marketing expert who indicated significant interconnectivity with the business strategy function was asked whether sales forecasting risks, sales execution risks, and reputation risks would have a high, medium, or low impact on business strategy. Companies can follow this process to build a codified understanding by leveraging their internal leaders as well as external experts. Once coded, the data forms the basis for a network representation of risks and a company-specific QRN. </p><div class="callout-highlight callout-highlight--transparent callout--expand-column" id="fig4"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> A Quantitative Risk Network</h4><p class="caption"> This visual representation of a generalized QRN reveals the linkages between risk categories and enterprise functions. It illustrates how companies can isolate and identify key value functions that link several connected risks and are therefore particularly significant in building enterprise resilience. The more central the function, the larger its font size; the thick links in the QRN imply high-impact relationships between functions and risk categories. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MAG_FE_Sheth_fig4.png" alt="A Quantitative Risk Network" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><p> Such a QRN helps leaders better understand a company&#39;s vulnerability to risk events by illuminating those functions that are central to the value exchange system. A risk event affecting a central function would imply a strong cascade of negative effects across the company&#39;s value exchange system. For example, financial capital management connects directly to 15 financial risk categories and indirectly to 30 risk categories from other functions. Any event occurring in any one of the risk categories affecting financial capital management will have implications for all other connected functions; for instance, significant currency exposure will likely affect the company&#39;s sourcing decisions. Thus, protecting the financial capital management function is critical to resilience. In contrast, a negative effect on the marketing and sales function is unlikely to cause a cascading impact in this company. <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p> Expert knowledge, industry insights, experience, and the simulations are all useful in building a network view of enterprise risks. QRNs are baseline resources that help a company isolate and objectively model for worst-case scenarios, estimate cause-effect patterns, and effectively reduce level 3 and 4 uncertainty.</p><p> A company with a well-honed QRN will be able to differentiate between the scope and consequences of a business interruption due to, say, a pandemic and a transport route blockage. It will also be able to pinpoint the parts of the business that will likely experience significant consequences from these events, such as value delivery, value creation, and value protection, and identify the precise business functions that should be guarded for each of these events. In the case of the pandemic, these functions would include financial capital management, market risk assessment, and technology management; for the lower-scope blockage, these would include operations management and operating expense control. Furthermore, the company could use the value function risk inventory and build scenario models for risk events identified within each of these functions.</p><p> Ultimately, pairing the knowledge of plausible risk events and their likely interactions with the company&#39;s value functions enables strategists to develop tailored mitigation plans and response strategies. Leaders who recognize the need to better understand a specific set of scenarios can invest in developing precise models to reduce the uncertainty of their impact on the company.</p><p></p><p></p><p> The value exchange system that drives any large, complex enterprise is continuously challenged as contexts vary in the dynamic business environment. This raises the stakes for anticipating change, exploring new variations of business models, and continuously pursuing the next wave of growth-enabling capabilities. Risk intelligence helps leaders in this work, enabling them to better focus on maintaining continuous value exchange and fostering the adaptability needed to achieve resilience.</p><p> To create and nurture risk intelligence, a company needs a central risk management function that is staffed with broad functional expertise and given the resources required to identify and categorize risks. It needs to embrace a mindset of risk uncertainty versus risk avoidance and reduce the levels of uncertainty. It needs a company-specific quantified risk network that is updated in a dynamic manner. And finally, it needs a culture of risk intelligence in which leaders across the organization share a common framework and language for interpreting risks and guiding resource allocation for risk mitigation efforts. Ultimately, honing a risk intelligence capability represents the key to building a resilient enterprise.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/risk-intelligence-and-the-resilient-company/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>