<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 7 月 31 日星期一 12:13:35 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator><item><title>遏制假货泛滥</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Robert Handfield, Anand Nair,  and Thomas Y. Choi. <p>Robert Handfield ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robhandfield">@robhandfield</a> ) 是北卡罗来纳州立大学普尔管理学院供应链管理美国银行大学杰出教授。阿南德·奈尔 (Anand Nair) 是东北大学达莫尔-麦金商学院供应链和信息管理教授。 Thomas Y. Choi 是 AT&amp;T 教授，也是亚利桑那州立大学 WP Carey 商学院供应链管理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Global Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Neil Webb/theispot.com The Research The authors conducted research into the state of counterfeiting from 2017 through early 2020. Funding was provided by CAPS Research, a joint venture of Arizona State University and the Institute for Supply Management. During the discovery phase, they ran an in-person workshop and attended the October 2017 annual strategic summit of [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Handfield_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">尼尔·韦伯/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><ul><li>作者对 2017 年至 2020 年初的假冒状况进行了研究。资金由亚利桑那州立大学和供应管理研究所的合资企业 CAPS Research 提供。</li><li>在发现阶段，他们举办了现场研讨会，并参加了密歇根州立大学防伪和产品保护中心 2017 年 10 月的年度战略峰会。</li><li>作者于 2017 年和 2018 年对 20 多名主题专家进行了单独采访。</li><li>作者还于 2018 年 6 月和 8 月对 21 名供应链高管进行了深入调查。</li></ul></aside><p>无论领导者是否意识到，许多公司正在因造假者和不道德的供应链合作伙伴而损失大量收入。任何在街头市场仔细观察手袋的人都知道，找到看起来与真品一模一样但功能可能不同的假货是多么常见。在某些情况下，这可能会让消费者面临风险：例如，一家制药公司在黑市上发现了不含活性药物成分的假冒产品。此外，一家公司的合法产品可能会被转用于未经授权的销售，例如一家全球电子公司发现其网络中的分销商在灰色市场上销售这些部件，这些分销商原本订购了据称用于客户维修的组件。</p><p>每个行业的高需求产品都是欺诈犯罪活动的有利可图的目标。不幸的是，许多公司不愿意承认或向董事会或股东提出假冒产品的问题。高级管理人员经常试图用借口来解释这个问题，认为造假者总会找到复制产品的方法，或者盗版只占销售额的一小部分，不值得追究。这正中了造假者希望企业做的事情：忽视他们。</p><p></p><p>当公司开始量化造假者对其利润的影响程度时，他们可能会采取零敲碎打的方法来解决问题，试图防止问题进一步扩大。但这还不够。</p><p>我们的研究表明，成功打击假货需要广泛的组织职能部门的关注。它最适合包含多种方法并让整个组织及其合作伙伴参与的多层战略。</p><p></p><p>我们建议各组织制定一个一致的计划来识别、遏制和预防假冒行为。这一全面的流程意味着定期密切关注合同制造商并绘制产品如何在供应链中移动的图表。它包括确定消费者市场上销售的产品范围、部署隐蔽标记、审查保修索赔、教育客户以及与主要机构和竞争对手合作。</p><h3>传统策略不起作用</h3><p>关注假货的公司传统上依赖品牌安全功能来追踪犯罪活动。这些团队经常使用一些策略来检测假冒行为，例如在合法产品上应用隐蔽和公开的标记、附加跟踪产品位置的 RFID 标签，以及使用序列化与区块链相结合来创建防篡改的交易记录。例如，符合 GS1 全球追溯标准的条形码用于追踪 COVID-19 疫苗。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>但对于许多组织来说，这些策略还不够。</p><p>产品假冒和非法转移仍然普遍存在：我们 2018 年对 21 名供应链高管进行的调查显示，近一半的高管存在持续存在的问题或在前一年经历过事件。超过 70% 的人表示他们在过去五年中发生过事故。 （参见“研究”。）一位高管告诉我们，他的公司发现相当于整个工厂每月生产的产品被送往黑市，这主要是由于从其自己的供应商之一转移。</p><p>经济合作与发展组织表示，假冒伪劣问题已发展为 2019 年价值 4,640 亿美元的问题，占世界贸易额的 2.5%。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>人们曾经认为造假者只追求高价值或奢侈品，例如药品、名牌手袋或香水。但现在市场上充斥着假鞋、农药、化妆品、玩具、汽车零部件和医疗设备。造假者瞄准任何容易获利的行业和产品线。</p><p>虽然公司可能永远无法完全消除不良行为者复制产品或从授权渠道转移商品的行为，但它们可以显着减少造假者的市场渗透并挽回收入损失。成功的方法可能包括切断造假者进入市场的机会，消除他们对未经授权的商品的供应，或者使产品更难以复制。在这里，我们将详细介绍强有力的行动计划所包含的三项活动：识别、遏制和预防。</p><h3>识别：深入了解问题的范围和性质</h3><p>获得关于假冒问题严重性的基线是关键的第一步。随着问题的严重程度逐渐明朗，关闭该问题的潜在投资回报也开始显现。这可以帮助为防伪团队建立与业务目标和成果相一致的绩效指标。指标示例包括每年因非法产品贸易而损失的收入金额或百分比、收回的总收入（之前因假冒销售而不知不觉损失的美元）以及已确认的非法贸易、假冒、转移事件的数量和篡改。</p><p><strong>创建跨职能的品牌安全团队。</strong>针对当前问题制定切合实际的措施通常需要进行深入调查，其中涉及应用市场渠道分析，探索来自组织内部和外部的销售数据和其他信息的多个来源。为了发挥作用，品牌安全团队应包括销售、营销、运营、采购、物流、财务和会计以及核心品牌安全职能部门的参与者。此类团队通常由全球品牌保护官领导，该官在许多情况下具有执法背景，通常向首席运营官报告。</p><p><strong>检查内部和市场数据以清除可疑活动。</strong>鉴于线索通常隐藏在有关销售、保修、退货和其他产品指标的数据中，公司可能很难发现假冒活动，更不用说衡量假冒活动了。除非有人在寻找，否则异常活动很容易被忽视。</p><p>良好的第一步是首先查看网上销售的商品。电子商务已成为助长假货行业的完美渠道。消费者可能会无意中从在线零售商那里购买产品，而这些零售商不会验证其平台上产品的来源以及是否合法。尽管亚马逊（以及中国的阿里巴巴）定期关闭假货网站，但从事假货交易的运营商通常会在第二天以不同的名称重新开放。亚马逊报告称，仅 2020 年，该公司就屏蔽了 100 亿条假冒商品，销毁了 200 万件假冒产品。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>由于电子商务网站通常是造假者的主要销售来源，因此公司可以首先调查其产品（无论是正品还是假货）在网上销售的地点。寻找假冒网站的共同特征可以缩小可疑活动的范围。例如，一家公司可能会在亚马逊上发现四个不同的卖家提供其手提包的精确副本，列出相同的细节甚至照片。潜在造假者的迹象可能包括拼写或语法错误、模糊的照片或其他看起来不太正确的细节。</p><p>另一个重要的数据来源是保修退货。当消费者因为产品有缺陷而退回产品时（假冒产品经常如此），侦探工作可以追踪到产品的购买地点和购买方式。这可能导致假冒商品进入市场的起源，并成为寻找其下游来源的起点。我们研究的一家全球医疗产品公司聘请了一名全球品牌保护官，负责检查保修和退货数据、现场服务请求和销售数据。在上任的前 100 天里，他发现了 1,000 起已确认的非法贸易、假冒、转移和篡改事件。非法产品贸易每年造成的损失达 14 亿美元（占收入的 2%）。</p><p>估计假货销量是一项困难但重要的任务：公司必须建立一个基线来衡量反假货措施的效果。准确了解问题的范围是决定防伪措施投入多少以及预期投资回报率的先决条件。在许多情况下，业务决策者并没有意识到他们的收入和声誉受到多大程度的威胁。</p><p><strong>绘制供应和分销链地图。</strong>许多公司惊讶地发现不良行为者在自己的供应链中很活跃。生产过剩、黑市销售和未经授权的分销是常见的泄露源，可能会导致产品或其复制品通过公司一无所知的渠道出售。这就是为什么重要的早期步骤是确定公司产品流通的制造和分销渠道。</p><p></p><p>一家大型全球服装公司的品牌所有者告诉我们，他通过经销商网络听说该品牌正在墨西哥销售，尽管该公司在墨西哥没有授权零售店。为了追踪这些产品的来源，该主管查找了运往墨西哥的海运货物的提单和运输记录。书面记录显示，这些货物是从以色列的一个港口发货的——由在美国生产该公司品牌产品的同一家授权制造商负责。该服装公司最终追查到这些衣服，这些衣服都是正品，采用相同规格、相同材料制成，但在双方合同协议之外非法分销。当这家服装公司建立全球品牌安全职能并绘制其整个供应网络时，发现世界各地都在发生类似的产品转移案例。</p><p>分析上游供应链中原材料的花费是开始绘制供应基地图的好地方。采购部门可以联系会计团队来跟踪代表公司进行的所有第三方采购（通常称为<em>支出分析的</em>文件）。如果供应商购买的原材料更多，并且生产水平高于公司订购的水平，则这是一个明显的迹象，表明额外的产品可能正在进入黑市。这需要对供应链的全面可见性，而不仅仅是一级供应商（由于其他原因，这一点变得越来越重要，特别是管理与劳工或环境违规相关的风险）。出于竞争原因，一些供应商可能不愿意披露其上游供应商，但可以放心的是，查询是出于安全目的，而不是试图将他们从供应链中剔除。</p><p></p><h3>遏制：限制问题的蔓延</h3><p>有了专门的团队、对问题范围的初步了解以及对其最容易遭受的特定假冒和转移风险的了解，公司就可以开始系统地管理问题以控制问题。</p><p><strong>分析产品细分。</strong>调查团队的关键任务之一是按渠道、利润、数量和假冒活动风险对产品进行细分。这确保了团队的注意力首先转向最脆弱的市场渠道。</p><p>在许多情况下，对公司供应和分销流程的现状分析有助于揭示造假者所追求的一组常见产品领域。特别是，我们的研究发现，基于成品的品种、成品定制水平、供应商的地理范围、供应链的层级数量、需求的可预测性和制造量的变化，产品线具有高度复杂性。此类别的商品示例包括飞机和汽车替换零件、玩具、高端服装、品牌药品和消费电子产品。造假者更有可能伺机瞄准具有较高复杂性的产品领域，并利用这种复杂性来获取优势。</p><p>我们采访了一家生物技术制造商的高管，他们知道市场上出现假冒产品，但不知道来源。品牌保护团队首先将产品细分为造假者的主要目标（在本例中为高利润产品），并分析数据以估计每个品牌的事件数量。该团队是通过特许经营商、品牌所有者和区域销售经理之间的密切合作组建的，然后向特许经营合作伙伴和国家业务部门推出了一项计划。这按产品线确定了品牌保护优先级，并提供了一个系统来按品牌跟踪客户报告的事件，并每六个月进行一次数据审查。</p><p>与此同时，分析师开始收集有关供应链漏洞的市场情报，包括潜在的物流中断和监管干预的威胁，这对各地区的业务计划和增长目标构成了重大风险。总的来说，这些努力帮助制造商优先考虑品牌保护最能保障市场收入免受突然中断的业务和地区。在此过程中，该团队发现了一种影响重磅输液药物的重大假冒和转移活动，该药物使许多患者面临风险。该公司表示，最终能够将事故数量从每年 100 起减少到零。这就需要坚持不懈地努力，通过详细分析来推断每起事件的根源，并提出对策——包括向造假者发送信息，警告他们将被追捕，希望说服他们去寻找更容易的目标。</p><p>这种分析从识别初始线索并跟踪活动线索开始。最初的问题可能表现为一个小问题，例如客户保修问题、经销商似乎订购了过多的替换零件，或者特定品牌产品的大量客户退货。这些问题中的任何一个都可能是导致造假活动的渠道的暗示。</p><p><strong>从电子商务网站开始，然后联系海关和其他当局。</strong>分析师团队应该持续追查电子商务网站上公开的假冒行为，并向平台运营商（例如亚马逊）和执法部门报告。至少，这会给一些不良行为者的业务带来更多摩擦，从而减慢他们的速度。</p><p>假冒产品几乎总是必须跨境并通过执法机构监督的转运点和海关检查。这些是供应链中的关键参与者，组织必须将他们视为打击收入损失和知识产权盗窃的合作伙伴。这些关系在高度监管的环境中尤其重要，例如制药、食品、航空航天和汽车制造，在这些环境中，假冒产品可能会危及用户的安全。</p><p>美国海关与边境保护局 (CBP) 的一位官员告诉我们，让品牌所有者了解 CBP 的流程并在帮助该机构解决问题方面发挥自己的作用可能具有挑战性。 “我们在现场检查集装箱，”他说。 “如果美国海关边防总署官员打开集装箱并看到可疑的东西，他们将首先查看我们的内部注册品牌数据库。如果警察看不到任何东西，他们就无能为力。”向 CBP 和美国专利商标局注册品牌是遏制假冒的关键一步。</p><p><strong>教育（并警告）客户。</strong>必须让消费者了解购买假货的可能性和风险。公司应该通过品牌营销让客户意识到，如果他们从未经验证的在线第三方卖家处购买产品，他们将面临产品无法保修的风险，或者更糟糕的是，产品出现故障并带来可怕的后果。我们知道的一家公司开始在其亚马逊网站上添加一份声明，警告退回给其的未经许可的产品将不享受保修。公司还应该向客户强调出于保修目的注册产品序列号的重要性，如果他们购买的合法产品被发现有缺陷或有缺陷，这可以保护他们。如果客户尝试注册假冒产品的序列号，则会显示错误并提醒品牌安全团队注意问题。</p><h3>预防：在未来的假冒行动开始之前阻止它们</h3><p>一旦组织发现假冒产品在其市场渠道中的传播方式并采取初步措施来遏制该问题，它就必须继续监控犯罪活动并建立强有力的预防措施。在此阶段，公司的许多职能部门都发挥着重要作用。</p><p><strong>产品包装专家应该探索数字追踪技术。</strong>当前追踪技术的功能提供了积极的产品认证，可以指示篡改，可以增加复制的难度，并允许产品跟踪和追踪。安全标记——使用各种包装、区块链和序列标记技术——是跟踪产品的一种方法。许多行业正在与 ASTM International 或 GS​​1 等标准组织合作，开发验证产品的通用方法。这有助于避免造假者不仅试图复制产品，还试图复制数字标记的问题。</p><p>在前面提到的生物技术示例中，品牌保护团队与企业合作识别隐蔽和公开的身份验证功能，当假冒产品通过市场渠道销售时，该功能会自动发出警报。该团队还利用网络广告、有针对性的电子邮件和 Twitter 活动以及零售商关于从未经授权的来源购买商品的危险的警报，制定了全面的客户沟通计划。该活动提高了公司销售合作伙伴网络的认识，并为识别新的假冒销售发生地奠定了基础。</p><p><strong>质量保证应审查数据以追踪产品问题和退货的情况。</strong> QA 可以在其数据收集过程中创建触发器来标记潜在的非法活动。我们知道有一家公司注意到其产品退货量有所增加，发现这些产品不合法，并追踪到销售点，从而揭露了假冒产品的来源。</p><p><strong>供应管理部门应加大对供应商的审核力度。</strong>跟踪供应商的过度生产以及他们如何处置不符合质量标准的产品（这些产品最终可能通过黑市渠道流通，从而规避贸易合规政策）可能特别有效。一家大型服装公司开始监控其供应商设施内的库存水平，并注意到供应商的入库原材料库存远远大于其运送到该公司的成品数量。这表明产品正在通过其他渠道在其他地方生产和销售。</p><p><strong>物流应绘制供应路线以记录运输提供商的合规情况。</strong>这有助于确保全球供应链的监管链，特别是在港口、仓库和配送中心等交接点。拥有多层分销渠道的公司应记录每次物流交接，并进行随机审核，以确定所有分销中心是否有适当的保安人员和上锁的大门。</p><p><strong>人力资源部门可能需要考虑监控直接处理目标产品的员工。</strong>这可能包括进行背景调查以及加强培训以提高员工意识。如果库存缺失严重或产品销量突然增加或下降，可能需要进行调查。</p><p><strong>售后销售应跟踪保修索赔和零件销售，以识别产品质量问题。</strong>与质量保证团队一样，售后销售第一线的人员能够了解到产品的性能未达到预期，这可能再次表明假冒产品正在进入市场渠道。例如，一家大型零售商认识到这些特定销售渠道（尤其是电子商务）中存在假冒产品的巨大潜力，因此决定限制其分销渠道和授权经销商。</p><p></p><p></p><p>假冒和产品转移不是单一组织可以打击的犯罪行为。它们需要品牌、零售商、包装公司和物流企业的努力。这是一个罕见的例子，与竞争对手合作可以产生重要的见解。公司应考虑加入联盟并与行业同行合作。特定行业团体包括汽车制造商的汽车防伪委员会和制药公司的 Rx-360。 React 是一个大型防伪网络，其成员包括 Marvel Entertainment、Mattel、Pfizer、Philips、Prada 和 Timberland。</p><p>假冒产品也不仅仅是私营部门供应链的问题。劳工和人权倡导者、消费者教育机构、海关人员、联邦和州执法机构、当地警察和假冒产品消费者都对查出未经授权的活动感兴趣并发挥作用。虽然假冒伪劣和产品转移问题无法杜绝，但专门的努力可以显着减少这两种现象。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/taming-the-counterfeiting-epidemic/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>消除职业障碍以获得更公平的结果</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Haig R. Nalbantian. <p>Haig R. Nalbantian 是劳动力科学研究所的联合创始人和共同领导者。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition and Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Even organizations that specifically focus on advancing diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) struggle with improving representation in a sustainable way. Women and people of color continue to face obstacles advancing to more senior roles and are frequently not positioned to succeed in the same ways as their White male counterparts. That was the message from [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/W23-QA03_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p>即使是专门致力于推进多样性、公平性和包容性 (DEI) 的组织，也难以以可持续的方式提高代表性。女性和有色人种继续面临晋升更高职位的障碍，并且往往无法像白人男性同行那样取得成功。</p><p>这是劳动力科学研究所联合创始人兼共同领导人 Haig R. Nalbantian 在 2023 年 5 月举办的<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>研讨会<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a>期间传达的信息。Nalbantian 帮助组织应用基于证据的实证方法来加强其 DEI 工作和保留策略，并断言“在人力资源领域大量使用分析来为工作和劳动力管理提供信息”是未来工作的重要组成部分。</p><p></p><p>虽然天赋和干劲对于塑造职业生涯很重要，但情境因素会深刻影响员工在工作中的表现。其中包括员工获得“加速器”角色，例如面向客户的工作；员工如何适应灵活的工作安排，例如兼职状态；以及员工的汇报关系，例如他们是否向上级或高绩效主管汇报。纳尔班蒂安指出，这些易于识别的情况（他称之为<em>“解释差异”</em> ）很普遍。</p><p></p><p>许多组织在选择晋升人员方面也普遍存在巨大且<em>无法解释的差异</em>。纳尔班蒂安表示，在他自己和其他人的研究中，在所有条件相同的情况下，精英大雇主的经理“实际上更有可能对女性给予高度评价”，“但在大多数公司中，她们不太可能”得到晋升。”</p><p>他表示，公司必须解决已解释的差异并探索无法解释的差异。</p><p>纳尔班蒂安无法回答活动期间与会者提出的所有问题，因此他在下面回答了其中一些问题。 （为了清晰起见，问题和答案已进行了轻微编辑。）</p><h6>您的研究在分析中是否涉及交叉性？您谈到了女性和有色人种，但是有色人种女性和其他具有多重交叉少数群体身份的人呢？</h6><p>在我的研究中涉及的许多客户案例中，我们确实直接检查了交叉性。我们在美国较大的组织中已经做了很多这样的事情，这些组织拥有足够的这些人口群体的人口用于建模目的。</p><p>客户组织特别感兴趣的领域之一是报告关系的交叉性。也就是说，主管的具体人口统计数据是否会影响员工是否得到晋升、获得高评价或获得更高的加薪？例如，白人男性主管对待黑人女性报告的态度是否比白人男性或白人女性报告更差？白人女性主管是否会帮助她们的女性报告的前景，无论肤色如何？</p><p>我可以说，这些结果几乎没有什么规律性——当然远远少于我在绩效评级、角色、主管绩效和水平以及灵活工作方面报告的结果。</p><p></p><h6>这项研究是否将社会经济地位映射为交叉影响？</h6><p>不幸的是，我们关于社会经济因素的数据要有限得多，部分原因是我们的大多数客户将这些研究重点放在他们的受薪人群上，而忽略了他们的小时工。这让我感到担忧，因为它揭示了一种低估一线工人的倾向。我试图提醒组织，一线人员发生的事情可能会对业务成果产生重大影响。我在客户作业中看到并记录了这一点。尽管如此，组织的趋势仍然是优先考虑受薪员工——专业人士、经理和高管。</p><h6>您提到，比同龄人年轻是成功的一个有利因素。您能否详细说明一下您的研究发现的有关年龄不平等的情况？</h6><p>在我们对客户组织的分析结果中，年龄的负面影响几乎是普遍存在的。一个简单的事实是，一旦员工超过了其群体的中位年龄，所有事情都会变得消极：他们升职的可能性较小，获得高绩效评级的可能性较小，而且他们的薪资增长会趋于平稳或拒绝。</p><p>积极的一面是，老员工的流动率较低，而且通常要少得多。事实上，可能正是因为年长的员工倾向于留下来，雇主才觉得有必要像对待年轻员工那样对他们进行晋升、支付工资或认可。后者有更多的外部机会，因此可能需要不断地吸引他们。</p><p></p><p>这些关于老年工人的负面信号可能非常具有误导性。我们经常发现，年长员工较多的群体实际上比年轻员工较多的群体表现更好。与团体或组织层面相比，个人层面的发现存在不一致。</p><p>这表明，老年工人的生产力并不体现在他们自己对个人绩效的衡量上，而是体现在与他们一起工作的人的绩效上。我们称之为<em>溢出效应</em>。因此，举例来说，如果年长的员工不太可能跳槽，他们可以促使年轻的同事效仿，从而为他们的工作团队带来更多的稳定性并提高他们的工作效率。有关老年工人生产力的更多证据，请参阅我最近与 Richard A. Guzzo 和 Nicholas L. Anderson 进行的研究，我们在文章“<a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">年龄、经验和业务绩效：工作单位的元分析”</a>中讨论了该研究<a href="https://academic.oup.com/workar/article/8/2/208/6574297">水平效应</a>”，发表在<cite>《工作、老龄化和退休》</cite>杂志上。</p><h6>组织如何确保将年龄多样性和包容性纳入其公平和多元化计划？</h6><p>同样，企业领导人普遍认为年长员工的生产力较低。由于它们的成本往往更高，因此它们更多地被视为负债而不是资产，尽管有大量证据表明事实并非如此。出于某种我难以解释的原因，打击年龄歧视在 DEI 议程上并不重要，尤其是与解决性别和种族不平等问题相比。我责怪 DEI 社区在这方面没有更加积极主动。</p><p>劳动力老龄化几乎在所有地方都是一个不争的事实。如果组织不能有效应对这一长期趋势的影响并确保有效管理年长员工，则可能会面临组织绩效下降的风险。实际上，他们可能会将毫无根据的刻板印象变成自我实现的结果。</p><p></p><p>我总是敦促我的客户进行严格的诊断工作，以评估他们自己员工队伍的现实，以确定溢出效应是否确实在他们的组织中发挥作用，并做出相应的反应。通过这个过程，他们中的许多人会发现他们拥有需要保护的资产，而不是需要丢弃的负债。</p><h6>是否对公司业绩或股价与调查显示的情况之间的相关性进行了分析？</h6><p> I&#39;ve undertaken client studies in which we link workforce characteristics and management practices to various business outcomes, including profitability, financial and operational productivity, revenue growth, and customer retention, among others. Our results have been mixed. In some, we&#39;ve seen that greater diversity in work group or unit composition improves business performance; in others, we&#39;ve found no effect or statistically negligible results. The most robust review and synthesis of the results of these studies is the meta-analysis of the effects of age and tenure noted above. That study did not focus on the effects of race and gender.</p><h6> What concrete steps can organizations take to battle these biases?</h6><p></p><p> My article in the summer 2023 issue of <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , “ <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/opening-access-to-the-fast-track-for-career-equity/">Opening Access to the Fast Track for Career Equity</a> ,” speaks directly to this question. I explain how organizations can use the results of this kind of modeling to help eliminate or reduce the influence of demographics on how well employees are positioned to succeed at work. The reality is that all too often, situational factors inordinately affect the ability of employees to succeed and that women and people of color are situationally disadvantaged.</p><p> Employers who recognize that they are not positioning this talent to succeed can deploy an approach I call <em>proactive career management</em> to change this reality on the ground. This may involve getting more women and people of color into supervisory or other accelerator roles, changing reporting relationships, and neutralizing the negative effects of flexible working, among other things. I share a case study in my article to illustrate this approach in action.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/dismantle-career-roadblocks-for-more-equitable-outcomes/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Do Consumers See Your Business as a Force for Good?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cynthia E. Clark. <p>Cynthia E. Clark, Ph.D., is a professor of management at Bentley University. She is also a coauthor of <cite>Business and Society: Ethical, Legal, and Digital Environments</cite> (Sage Publications, 2020) and the author of <cite>Giving Voice to Values in the Boardroom</cite> (Routledge, 2021).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Environmental Sustainability]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[The public’s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s efforts to impose fines on businesses for greenwashing, point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald’s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Clark-Eco-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> The public&#39;s growing concerns about environmental issues, along with the US Federal Trade Commission&#39;s efforts to impose <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/04/13/ftc-is-expected-crack-down-greenwashing/">fines on businesses for greenwashing</a> , point to the potential fallout when companies engage in environmentally damaging actions. Companies such as Burger King, KFC, and McDonald&#39;s have all been recent targets of government and investor pressure to cut plastic waste. Last year, <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/blog/2022/04/55-million-total-ftc-settlements-kohls-and-walmart-challenge-bamboo-and-eco-claims-shed-light">both Kohl&#39;s and Walmart</a> reached settlements of $2.5 million and $3 million, respectively, for falsely claiming that dozens of rayon textile products were actually made from environmentally friendly bamboo.</p><p> When such large, visible companies issue false claims or fail to act, it results in missed opportunities, a growing performance-expectation gap, and, eventually, reputational damage among consumers. So, what makes a business a force for good when it comes to the future of our environment? To find out, Bentley University and Gallup recently conducted a survey of 5,757 Americans to assess how they feel about business and its potential to have a positive impact on society and the environment. The <a href="https://www.bentley.edu/news-Announcing-the-Bentley-Gallup-Force-for-Good-survey-results">results of the Force for Good survey</a> highlight areas in which businesses, small and large, are failing to meet people&#39;s expectations — and how they can do better.</p><p></p><p> The public&#39;s expectations of large companies like Kohl&#39;s, McDonald&#39;s, or Walmart were made clear in our research. A slight majority of our respondents (53%) said that businesses overall have a negative environmental impact. Almost two-thirds (65%) said they feel this way about <em>large</em> businesses, whereas 16% said that <em>small</em> businesses have a negative impact on the planet/environment. Younger respondents in our study had higher expectations of businesses overall, with a whopping 81% of those age 18 to 29 saying that large businesses have a negative impact on the planet, compared with 54% of respondents age 70 or older.</p><p> Drilling down into the data, we found that more than 9 in 10 respondents rated four social and environmental concerns that businesses could act on as extremely or somewhat important: practicing sustainable manufacturing (92%); promoting increased access to education and training (92%); investing time and money into local communities (92%); and operating in a way that is sustainable for the environment (91%). Just 1 in 3 people surveyed said that businesses are currently doing an excellent or good job in any of these areas, and about 1 in 4 (26%) said that businesses are doing an excellent or good job of operating in an environmentally sustainable way.</p><h3> The T-Shirt Experiment</h3><p> One perspective on sustainability is that companies should practice environmental responsibility for the greater good — the “doing good to do good” perspective. Another approach focuses on the importance of “doing good to do well” so that both business and society benefit from leaders&#39; actions. But are these approaches in tension? Need they be?</p><p> One section of the Force for Good survey — what we called our T-shirt experiment — was aimed at getting a better read on how people think about this tension. Amid rising prices for almost everything, we asked whether respondents would be willing to pay extra for a T-shirt depending on a variety of company characteristics. Sixty-three percent of respondents said they would be willing to pay extra — 82% more — for a T-shirt if the company that made it was known for having a positive impact on the environment. The numbers are even higher for respondents age 18 to 29 and for women: Young people were most likely to say they would pay more — about 8 in 10 — and almost 7 in 10 women. (See “Results of the T-Shirt Experiment.”) Both of these consumer groups are key markets for many companies.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Results of the T-Shirt Experiment</h4><p class="caption"> To differing degrees, depending on age and gender, respondents indicated their willingness to pay more for the same product based on a business&#39;s sustainability practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig1-1.png" alt="Results of the T-Shirt Experiment" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> When people were asked how much they would pay for the T-shirt without being given any additional information, the median response was $10. This held true for those with personal incomes between $24,000 and $179,000. In other words, personal income had little effect on the value they assigned to the product.</p><p></p><p> Respondents were then asked how much more they would pay if the company were known for various attributes: having a positive environmental impact, making a positive impact on the local community, treating employees well, and contributing to charities. Among the four attributes, the premium was highest for companies known to have a positive environmental impact, with a median response of $7.</p><p> Our data indicates that Americans are, in fact, willing to reward companies for doing good. A company known for positive environmental performance can charge more for its products — evidence that “doing good to do well” works.</p><p></p><h3> A False Dichotomy?</h3><p> Most of the respondents didn&#39;t see a trade-off between good environmental performance and good financial performance. In other words, they believe that both can happen concurrently, despite business leaders&#39; arguments that sustainable practices harm financial performance. About 7 in 10 respondents (69%) said businesses that prioritize making a positive impact on society are just as profitable (47%) or more profitable (22%) than their competitors. People who said they have expertise in owning, leading, or managing a business were no less likely than those without such expertise to say that businesses that prioritize making a positive impact are at least as profitable as their competitors.</p><p> Members of different political parties had notable differences of opinion regarding the importance of sustainability. For example, 84% of Democrats said it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner, compared with 31% of Republicans and 59% of independents. However, a large majority of Republicans (80%) said that sustainability is at least <em>somewhat</em> important. These perspectives might affect a host of company actions, such as choosing content and spending amounts for advertising in red versus blue states and the very design of their products.</p><p></p><p> Likewise, we found significant differences across ethnic identities. Seventy percent of Black respondents, 82% of Asian respondents, 65% of Hispanic respondents, and 59% of White respondents said they believe it is extremely important for businesses to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner. When asked how they feel about focusing on long-term benefits like those for the environment versus short-term benefits like profits, 77% of Asian respondents said they are likely to support that focus — compared with 56% of respondents overall. The figures for both Black and Hispanic respondents hovered around 60%.</p><p> Even when we asked the question in a slightly different way, respondents did not see it as a trade-off but as more of a “both and” situation. For example, when asked about meeting the financial goals of investors, 79% said they believe it is somewhat or extremely important. Eighty-eight percent of respondents also said that making the world a better place is somewhat or extremely important.</p><h3> How Can Your Company Become a Force for Good?</h3><p> Results from this deep dive into what a broad and varied set of Americans believe suggest several actions companies can take or plan for.</p><p> <strong>Pay attention to your local footprint.</strong> Small companies are perceived as better at most stakeholder-related activities. Respondents were twice as likely to say small businesses positively impact people&#39;s lives than large businesses (82% and 41%, respectively). What&#39;s more, respondents are more likely to think large businesses have a negative impact on Americans&#39; lives in general (38%) than they are to say the same about small businesses (4%). This data, combined with the results across age and gender in the figure below (see “Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?”) on positive community impact, suggests that companies — particularly large ones — should improve their relationships with their surrounding communities.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Recognize that younger Americans expect more.</strong> Millennials (born between 1981 and 1996) and Gen Zers (born between 1997 and 2012) expect more from businesses in terms of both social and environmental responsibility than older respondents do. In our T-shirt experiment, 82% of respondents age 18 to 29 were willing to pay more for a T-shirt from a company known for having a positive impact on their local community. Again, young respondents (73%) agreed more than any other age group that businesses&#39; efforts to reduce their carbon footprints and/or emissions are important. Companies will need to account for their environmental stewardship among their customers and future employees.</p><p> <strong>Mind the performance-expectation gap.</strong> Environmental stakeholders and regulators are on the lookout for any discrepancy between expectations of a company&#39;s responsible environmental management and what it is actually doing — the performance-expectation gap. The vast majority of respondents (89%) said businesses have “a great deal” or “some” power to make a positive impact on people&#39;s lives, but just 57% said that businesses are very or somewhat effective at doing so. In terms of the environment, the findings revealed performance-expectation gaps of at least 30 percentage points between “the importance of” and “the performance of” several environmental goals. On questions about reducing businesses&#39; carbon footprints, engaging in sustainable manufacturing, and making the world a better place, we found considerable gaps: On those three points, 52% to 57% of respondents indicated that it is extremely important for businesses to do so, but only 24% to 28% thought they are excellent or good at it.</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4> Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?</h4><p class="caption"> There is a considerable gap between respondents&#39; opinions on the importance of sustainability practices and their perceptions of businesses&#39; actual practices. </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023-07-26_Clark_fig2.png" alt="Sustainability Is Important to Consumers — but Are Businesses Practicing It?" /><br /></article></aside></div><p> While having a dedicated sustainability leader, support from senior management, and education for employees and executives is necessary, it&#39;s important to stay vigilant in addressing the widening performance-expectation gap. In what has become a hypercritical business environment, leaders must pay greater attention to how perceptions of what their company is doing compare with what they are actually doing.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Set sustainability goals.</strong> Think carefully about how to measure what you&#39;re doing. This is a logical next step after gaining the support of senior management, and it can help your company determine the progress it has made and where it has soft or blind spots. In fact, regulators have proposed requiring companies to disclose how they set climate-related targets and measure their progress toward meeting them. Consider signing on to broadly recognized and accepted goals like the United Nations Global Compact&#39;s (UNGC&#39;s) <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals</a> , which can help your company publicly commit to a plan of action, step by step. The UNGC also requires annual statements on progress to help ward off greenwashing.</p><p></p><p> With increasing attention on environmental sustainability, gaining an understanding of how various stakeholders perceive your statements and actions is vital. By identifying and understanding current perceptions and their implications, as the Bentley-Gallup study does, companies can amend their environmental commitments and processes to ensure that they invigorate their efforts to be a force for good, which will benefit the company, its stakeholders, and, most importantly, the environment.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/do-consumers-see-your-business-as-a-force-for-good/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Myth of the Mainstream</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/#comments</comments><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marcus Collins. <p>Marcus Collins is a clinical marketing professor at the University of Michigan&#39;s Ross School of Business and former head of strategy at Wieden+Kennedy New York. He is the author of <cite>For the Culture: The Power Behind What We Buy, What We Do, and Who We Want to Be</cite> (PublicAffairs, 2023).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Approach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Product Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marketing Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com For years, McDonald’s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension. The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/2023FALL-Collins_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Benedetto Cristofani/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> For years, McDonald&#39;s seemed to embody everything that was wrong with the American diet. The brand had become a symbol of food choices that were driving escalating rates of obesity and hypertension.</p><p> The company spent more than a decade trying to fight this perception among American consumers by targeting them with messaging about its updated menu, which offered healthier alternatives more in line with contemporary diet trends — but to no avail. Year over year, McDonald&#39;s sales declined, and its brand perception continued to spiral downward.</p><p></p><p> Finally, the company decided to go on the offensive. Instead of combating the opposition&#39;s hate and attempting to win over those in the middle, McDonald&#39;s decided to focus on its fans — the people who self-identify as McDonald&#39;s devotees despite the vitriol directed at the brand. The company&#39;s tactics included launching its Famous Orders campaign, which celebrated the favored menu items of superstar fans (like hip-hop mogul Travis Scott and K-pop megastars BTS); creating adult-targeted Happy Meals; and promoting fans&#39; own menu hacks. In doing so, it tapped into what these devotees love about McDonald&#39;s and not only activated their collective consumption but also inspired them to spread the word on behalf of the brand. The result of this strategy was a 10.4% increase in global revenue for McDonald&#39;s from 2018 to 2021 and the return of dormant customers: more than a quarter of those who came in to buy the Travis Scott meal, for example, hadn&#39;t visited the chain in over a year. Seemingly overnight, McDonald&#39;s went from being a cautionary tale to the darling of brand marketing and a case study for advertising effectiveness.</p><p></p><p> What&#39;s going on here? Conventional wisdom would tell us that in a world of increasingly polarized opinions, our best bet is to appease the middle, if only because that&#39;s where the majority of the market is. That also seems like a safe bet to many companies, as a middle-of-the-road position is less likely to alienate potential customers. But McDonald&#39;s demonstrated what can happen when you dismiss this conventional approach. Instead of trying to speak to the mass market, it chose a side. It chose to embrace the love instead, fighting the hate, and it abandoned the notion of enticing the large but indifferent middle of the market. By doing so, McDonald&#39;s marketing efforts activated a legion of fans who not only consumed but also won over others as well. What McDonald&#39;s realized is an important lesson for contemporary marketers: If you want to get people to move, you must choose a side. The notion that you can win by playing to the middle is a misleading myth.</p><p></p><h3> Choose a Side</h3><p> The core function of marketing is to influence people to adopt a desired behavior. That is to say, we go to market to get people to move — to buy, to vote, to recycle, to subscribe, to download, to watch, to evangelize, to wear a mask — and to drive a host of other desirable behavioral outcomes that will benefit our organization or interests. And what influences people the most? Well, according to everything we know about human behavior, we are most influenced by other people — not ads, not value propositions, but other people. More specifically, we are most influenced by <em>our</em> people: the individuals who abide by the same culturally established conventions and expectations that dictate what is considered acceptable behavior for people like us. These individuals typically share a similar worldview and, therefore, adhere to a shared way of life in an effort to promote social solidarity among themselves — their subculture. They consume the way the subculture consumes, vote the way it votes, and behave the way it behaves, because that is what is expected of people like them.</p><p> If these people are against you because of the shared conventions and expectations of people like them (their culture), then the likelihood of getting them to take action on your behalf will be slim. That&#39;s why right-wing Republicans won&#39;t bother trying to convert left-leaning Democrats. Instead, Republicans speak to their base — the collective of people who see the world similarly, express a similar set of cultural characteristics as the brand, and are more inclined to move in step with the brand as an act of social solidarity. They identify as members of this group and follow its behavioral norms.</p><p> Those in the unaffiliated middle of the population, on the other hand, are by nature indifferent and risk averse. While they may have opinions, they lack strong convictions in either direction and are therefore less likely to take action. In politics, they don&#39;t vote in primaries or campaign for candidates; instead, they sit on the sidelines and wait to see how things shake out. Their behavior is the same when it comes to brands.</p><p> The middle doesn&#39;t adopt new products with any urgency. They are not the first to respond to marketing communications, nor are they likely to weigh in on a debate between advocates and detractors. They mitigate their own risk of moving out of step with what might be considered generally acceptable by stepping back and observing other people&#39;s responses first.</p><p> The red herring is that we perceive this indifference as an opportunity to persuade them to one side or the other. But the truth is, they are not typically convinced by any marketing communications. Instead, they, too, take cues from other people — sometimes those who are for you, and at other times those who are against you.</p><p></p><p> With this in mind, it becomes abundantly clear that in a polarized scenario, the chances of marketers getting people to move are far greater when we activate the collective of the willing as opposed to trying to convince detractors or even persuade the indifferent. And yet, historically, marketers have focused their efforts on the middle because it represents the biggest market opportunity. However, our chances of successfully influencing behavior increases when we choose to address the people who are most likely to take action. When we do so effectively, we catalyze a propagation effect that causes the product, behavior, or idea to cascade throughout the population, thanks to the process of social contagion — the spread of affects, behaviors, cognitions, and desires due to direct or indirect peer influence of people “like us.”</p><h3> The Power of Propagation</h3><p> The idea of propagation demands that marketers leave behind the conventional approach of targeting the middle, where the majority of the population resides. Besides being of questionable effectiveness, as discussed above, reaching the middle requires costly media spending (think prime-time TV and Super Bowl ads) and places marketing messages in an arena that is noisy and saturated with competing messages. Marketers pay little attention to the fringe, a population that conventional wisdom tells us is too small and too niche. But everything that is now mainstream once started on the fringe: It started within a subculture and propagated out to become popular culture.</p><p> For instance, if you were into comic books 20 years ago, you would have been considered a nerd. Today, however, many of the most-viewed movies across the globe, such as Marvel&#39;s <cite>Avengers</cite> series, originated from comics. Twenty years ago, if you were into video games, you would have been perceived as an immature adult. Today, gaming is not only considered cool but is also a multibillion-dollar industry. Indeed, what is now normal was once fringe. Thanks to social contagion, the cultural characteristics of a community propagate from the fringe to the middle — from the subculture to popular culture. It happens from the outside in, not the inside out.</p><p></p><p> Unlike traditional marketing communications, the reach and subsequent adoption that is achieved through this kind of propagation does not rely on people hearing a message from a company or brand. (It helps, but it&#39;s not necessary.) Instead, people hear about it from someone they trust — someone like them — which increases their likelihood of adoption. As the network scientists Nicholas Christakis and James Fowler contended, “When a small group of people begin acting in concert — displaying similar visible symptoms — the epidemic can spread along social network ties via emotion contagion and large groups can become quickly emotionally synchronized.” This is the network effect that is catalyzed when you activate the collective of the willing. Don&#39;t focus on the middle: Focus on the people who see the world the way you do. Choose a side, and they will convince the bystanders, the passive, the indifferent.</p><p></p><p> Although broadcast messaging might get our attention, it&#39;s the influence of people like us, people with whom we identify, that changes our outlook and, subsequently, our behaviors. This provides a new perspective, and corresponding strategies, for marketers who aim to communicate with consumers in a culture where ideological binaries seem to divide the market. Like McDonald&#39;s did, marketers benefit from choosing a side that is most likely to move and then activating its members so that they might convert people on the brand&#39;s behalf. Status quo practices position the middle as a safe bet. However, the dynamics of cultural diffusion subvert these long-standing best practices for connecting with consumers and influencing behavioral adoption, and demand that today&#39;s practitioners develop new strategies and accompanying tactics.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-myth-of-the-mainstream/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> Sustainability Progress Is Stalled at Most Companies</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[CB Bhattacharya and Rob Jekielek. <p>CB Bhattacharya is director of the Center for Sustainable Business and the HJ Zoffer Chair in Sustainability and Ethics at the Katz Graduate School of Business at the University of Pittsburgh. Rob Jekielek is managing director of The Harris Poll.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Sustainability & Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability-Driven Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Social Responsibility]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category><description><![CDATA[While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else’s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual.1 On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bhattacharya-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> While many companies talk the talk of sustainability, claiming to be integrating environmental and societal concerns into their business models, far fewer walk the walk: Managers typically treat sustainability as someone else&#39;s problem and relegate it to a department or even a single individual. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> On the other hand, companies that have been successful in transforming their business models to be more sustainable have embedded sustainability into their corporate DNA. This means that they have endowed their employees with a sense of sustainable ownership, spurring them to engage in more sustainability-supporting behaviors. When every employee integrates environmental and social concerns into every business decision, sustainability progress is accelerated — an aspirational goal for all companies.</p><p> To shed light on the state of play in embedding sustainability and identify key bottlenecks, the Center for Sustainable Business at the University of Pittsburgh collaborated with The Harris Poll to conduct a survey of US employees. We wanted to find out whether their employers were taking measures that our earlier research had identified as important to prompting employees to conduct business through a sustainability lens. Our survey drew responses from 1,056 employees, representative of the US employee base. We defined sustainability for the respondents as “integrating environmental and societal concerns into business decisions and actions.”</p><p></p><p> We asked respondents to rate their level of agreement with a series of 19 statements about the status quo, such as “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance,” on a 4-point Likert scale (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”). We also presented respondents with a series of 12 issues that could pose challenges to sustainability progress, such as “Sustainability is not built into our business strategy,” and asked them to rate the extent to which that is an actual challenge at their company (from “major challenge” to “not at all a challenge”).</p><p> Roughly one-third of the respondents asserted that their employers have made significant strides in their sustainability journeys. Although that number might sound low given the enormity of the task facing us, the good news is that there is momentum, which we can help accelerate by pointing out the roadblocks as perceived by employees. Below, we provide six key recommendations that emerged from our data for managers seeking to embed sustainability in the organizational culture and business models.</p><p> <strong>Establish a purpose based on values.</strong> Purpose is a business&#39;s raison d&#39;être — the answer to the all-important question, “Why do we do what we do?” Paul Polman, former CEO of Unilever and a leader in the corporate sustainability movement, has said, “Sustainability is totally driven by purpose.” <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> Organizations that are successful at embedding sustainability articulate the societal benefit they aim to deliver to their stakeholders, and this overarching purpose guides everything the organization does.</p><p> In our study, 36% of the respondents strongly agreed with the statement “My company wants to make a difference in people&#39;s lives, not just make profits,” while 33% strongly agreed with “My company has a higher purpose beyond profit maximization.” If purpose is the starting point for sustainability, we aren&#39;t doing very well; it is apparent that the profit-maximization narrative is alive and well. Consistently, 43% of employees cited short-term focus, a lack of investor interest, and, importantly, “Our leaders don&#39;t believe in sustainability,” as challenges. Unless CEOs and top management teams realize that profit is the <em>consequence</em> of value creation for all stakeholders and not the starting point for strategy development and execution, progress will be stifled. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p></p><p> <strong>Bake sustainability into corporate strategy.</strong> Academic researchers and others have noted that efforts to make meaningful progress toward sustainability must be driven by corporate strategy. <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Doing so increases the likelihood that, over time, “doing the green thing” will be seen as a normal part of employees&#39; jobs, and more and more decisions will be made through the lens of sustainability. With only 29% of respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company has a clear business case for improving our sustainability performance” and 27% with “Sustainability is core to how my company executes our business strategy,” it appears that we have a long way to go. Consistent with the status quo, 43% agreed that their company&#39;s failure to build sustainability into its business strategy represents a challenge.</p><p> <strong>Train employees, and incentivize actions that advance sustainability.</strong> Companies that are successful in engaging their workforce have invested in training that gives employees guidance on how to improve sustainability. With only 30% of employees surveyed strongly agreeing with the statement “I understand how I can improve my company&#39;s sustainability performance through my role,” there seems to be a dearth of role-specific knowledge at the individual employee level. Lack of training was cited as a major/moderate challenge by 44%, while a similar number (45%) indicated that they don&#39;t know what actions to take to improve sustainability performance. Companies need to invest more in training and sustainability knowledge creation so that employees know <em>what</em> they can do in their roles and <em>how</em> to do what needs to be done.</p><p> Managers must also do more to provide employees with incentives to advance the sustainability agenda: Forty-nine percent of those surveyed found the lack of such incentives to be a major or moderate hurdle to improving sustainability performance. Leaders should also consider whether the management culture encourages engagement and intrinsic motivation by giving employees the autonomy to solve sustainability challenges, which often require creative thinking. However, when we asked survey respondents to rate their level of agreement with the statements “My company allows me to make a lot of sustainability-related decisions on my own” and “My company gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out sustainability initiatives,” we found that, at most, 29% of respondents strongly agreed.</p><p> <strong>Create a sustainability culture in your organization.</strong> Managers can keep sustainability salient in the organizational culture by communicating progress, celebrating milestones, recognizing achievements, and collaborating on solutions both internally and with industry partners. Our research has identified the lack of a sustainability culture as one of the biggest impediments to progress, with 48% of respondents indicating that that is a major or moderate impediment at their organization. Communicating sustainability progress to employees is a key component of a sustainability culture, because it keeps issues top of mind. Celebrating successes will pique employee interest and legitimize the importance of sustainability to the organization — but only 31% of respondents strongly agreed that their company celebrates sustainability successes.</p><p></p><p> Collaborating with traditional competitors — which is increasingly necessary to address those complex “ <a href="https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/tragedy-of-the-commons-impact-on-sustainability-issues">tragedy of the commons</a> ” problems — signals to employees that the company is serious about transformational change and reinforces the culture to employees. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> With only 25% of survey respondents strongly agreeing with the statement “My company collaborates with other organizations to address complex sustainability issues,” it is evident that much work is required to open corporate leaders&#39; eyes to the potential of progress via collaboration.</p><p> <strong>Conduct business through a sustainability lens.</strong> Imagine the progress we would make if every employee in every company — from the mailroom to the boardroom — integrated environmental and social issues into every business decision they made. This, in our view, is conducting business through the lens of sustainability — an aspirational but necessary goal to reach if we are to surmount our existential crises. As previous research has shown, employees taking individual ownership of sustainability is a key driver for engaging in sustainability behaviors. In our survey, 28% of respondents strongly agreed with the statement “Employees at my company take ownership of improving sustainability performance,” while 45% identified a belief among employees that “sustainability is someone else&#39;s responsibility” as a challenge. This lack of personal ownership of sustainability performance is reflected in our survey results: Only 27% of respondents strongly agreed that they “invested ideas and creativity” to help their company be more sustainable, and just 24% strongly agreed that every business decision they make is viewed through the lens of sustainability.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Bridge the last mile.</strong> We noted a significant difference between how corporate and front-line employees responded to our questions. Compared with front-line nonmanagers working in roles such as customer support, managers working in corporate roles were, on average, about 15% more likely to see sustainability as embedded.</p><p> To ensure that their commitment to sustainability is real and provides tangible benefits to their organizations, leaders must address this last-mile gap between corporate and front-line employees. Broadly communicated messaging about the corporate purpose and environmental, social, and governance targets might not suffice in this instance; there is a real need to drive sustainability through practical initiatives and actions that can be integrated into daily tasks and routines that employees perform across the entire organization.</p><p></p><p> Interestingly, perceiving sustainability as more embedded in the organization also opens employees&#39; eyes to the roadblocks and challenges that impede progress. Our data shows that employees who are more engaged and perceive sustainability to be more embedded also perceive more roadblocks, on average, than those who are less engaged.</p><p> The implication here is that as companies bridge the last-mile gap in embedding sustainability, they should be prepared to field more questions and listen to more opinions as employee engagement on the issue increases. Companies should use one-on-one coaching, action playbooks, and tailored communication to make sustainability everyone&#39;s job. Companies need to be prepared to invest more resources into embedding sustainability — and get the entire organization to conduct business through the sustainability lens.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/sustainability-progress-is-stalled-at-most-companies/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item><item><title> How Robots Can Enhance Performance Management for Humans</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bryan Hong and Lynn Wu. <p>Bryan Hong is associate professor of entrepreneurship and management at the Bloch School of Management at the University of Missouri-Kansas City. Lynn Wu is associate professor of operations, information, and decisions at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Performance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Process Efficiency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Automation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to invest in robotics for their business. Our research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Wu-Robots-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> We are in the middle of a robot revolution. The past decade has seen dramatic growth in robot adoption across an increasing number of industries, and it shows no signs of slowing. In a recent McKinsey survey of companies worldwide, 88% of respondents said they plan to <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/advanced%20electronics/our%20insights/growth%20dynamics%20in%20industrial%20robotics/industrial-robotics-insights-into-the-sectors-future-growth-dynamics.ashx">invest in robotics</a> for their business. Our research has found an equally and perhaps more important transformation taking place: The adoption of robots is improving companies&#39; ability to recognize and reward good employee performance.</p><p> Within every organization, leaders face a fundamental question: How do we get the best from our people? One of the most common methods is offering monetary rewards — usually, periodic bonuses — that are linked to performance. This practice is grounded in the idea that better performance should be more highly rewarded. But that approach is rarely simple to implement in practice because it requires that performance be measured well enough to be evaluated effectively. This is challenging to accomplish for most roles and even more so for individual employees. Because so much work is done in teams and managers can&#39;t monitor the specific activity of each employee or accurately measure individual performance, many organizations choose to pay bonuses based on team or company performance rather than on individual performance. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a></p><p></p><p></p><h3> Measuring Human Performance When Colleagues Are Robots</h3><p> What does all this have to do with robots? In our research, we have found that companies that adopt robots improve their ability to measure human performance. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> To illustrate, let&#39;s say you&#39;re working in a team of two. Your manager can see and evaluate your combined productivity as a team but not what each of you is doing individually at all times. In theory, both of you are supposed to be contributing equally; in practice, you&#39;re doing far more of the work, which isn&#39;t visible to your busy manager.</p><p> Then, let&#39;s say your teammate is replaced with a robot. As a machine, the robot is much more precise and consistent in doing its work tasks and might even provide data about its performance while operating. Because it&#39;s so consistent and transparent, any disruptions or spikes in productivity can much more clearly be identified as coming from either the robot or from you. If there are others in your organization who work with the same type of robot in a similar way, then it&#39;s much easier to see how their individual productivity varies from yours.</p><p> In other words, because robots are, by their very nature, much more consistent and transparent than humans, human activity becomes easier to observe if robots join the team. The more robots there are relative to humans, the easier it is to distinguish and measure individual human performance.</p><p></p><p> In one real-world example, a repair facility at a major US-based electronics company experienced a dramatic improvement in its ability to observe employee productivity after robots were implemented to assist workers in the repair process. Because robots, unlike humans, do not get physically tired while performing repetitive tasks, they were able to perform more consistently. This reduced variance in the production process and allowed managers to more clearly observe individual employee behaviors. Many employees followed a regular pattern of being more productive in the morning than in the afternoon, with substantial variance in their afternoon productivity. As a result, many workers ended up with more repairs to finish later in the day as they rushed to meet their daily quotas. This “cramming” of work was especially problematic because it typically resulted in more errors due to the workers having rushed.</p><p> Integrating robots into the repair process eased the tracking of individual employee productivity in two ways. First, robots made different types of errors than humans. The robots&#39; errors were consistent, which made human errors easier to distinguish. Second, the robots themselves provided precise data about their own performance, which made it easier to isolate performance outcomes, both positive and negative, caused by human behavior. This data generation capability allowed managers to better monitor productivity overall and to more easily detect weaknesses in the production process. Managers at the repair facility, for example, hadn&#39;t been aware of the extent of the afternoon cramming behavior until robots were incorporated into the production process. Once the problem was clearly identified, they were able to reorganize the work process to reduce errors; overall error rates at the facility have since improved.</p><p></p><p> These types of improvements in performance measurement can have especially dramatic effects on productivity in combination with performance-based incentives. If it&#39;s easier to observe and measure the performance of individual employees within organizations, good performers — who may have received little reward or recognition because of measurement challenges — become easier to identify and reward, and leaders really can do better in getting the best from their teams. And this is exactly what we find in our research: Companies that adopt robots are also more likely to adopt bonus incentives tied directly to individual performance as opposed to team or organizational performance. With better measurement comes increased rewards for an organization&#39;s good performers, and a more productive workplace. Using robots is fairer for the people who work at an organization.</p><p></p><p> Robots are changing the nature of work. Beyond eliminating some jobs and creating new ones, robots are also changing organizations&#39; ability to get the best from their people, as well as the way we experience work itself. Robots offer an exciting opportunity for businesses to redesign the roles and responsibilities of the humans that work with them, giving those companies a competitive edge over rivals not because of superior technology but because of better processes. The robot revolution isn&#39;t going to eliminate the need for humans. Rather, it&#39;s bringing both new challenges and opportunities for identifying, rewarding, and managing human talent.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-robots-can-enhance-performance-management-for-humans/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Detecting the Good and the Bad With AI: Airbnb&#39;s Naba Banerjee</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) is a professor in the information systems department at the Carroll School of Management at Boston College, as well as guest editor for <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> &#39;s Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy Big Ideas initiative. Shervin Khodabandeh is a senior partner and managing director at BCG and the coleader of BCG GAMMA (BCG&#39;s AI practice) in North America. He can be contacted at <a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a> .</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> is a collaborative podcast from <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> and Boston Consulting Group and is hosted by Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. Our engineer is David Lishansky, and the coordinating producers are Allison Ryder and Sophie Rüdinger.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Ethics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Information Sharing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operational Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Predictive Analytics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Psychological Safety]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Security & Privacy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Naba Banerjee’s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> Naba Banerjee&#39;s identity as a “forever learner” led to her become the first female engineer in her family. That curiosity has informed her career choices as well, leading her to companies as varied as Tata, Cognizant, AAA, and Walmart. Now, as director of trust product and operations at vacation rental platform Airbnb, she continues to let curiosity be her guide as she applies her previous data science experience to the travel industry.</p><p> On this episode of the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, Naba joins hosts Shervin Khodabandeh and Sam Ransbotham to talk about how she and her team use AI and machine learning to increase the safety of the guests and hosts who use Airbnb&#39;s platform. She also discusses collaboration between humans and machines and the importance of recognizing that neither is an infallible decision maker. </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MMAI-S7-E1-Banerjee-Airbnb-headshot-3000-scaled.jpg" alt="Naba Banerjee"></p><h4> Naba Banerjee, Airbnb</h4><p> Naba Banerjee is the director of trust product and operations at Airbnb, overseeing the company&#39;s efforts to combat fraud, build trust between hosts and guests, and stop bad actors from using the platform. Her most recent work includes the development of Airbnb&#39;s reservation screening technology, which helps to identify users making potentially high-risk reservations and prevent them from taking advantage of the platform.</p><p> Banerjee has over two decades of experience building products that deliver innovative, customer-centric solutions. She joined Airbnb after spending 13 years at Walmart.com, where she played an instrumental role in the evolution of product management, including shipping packages to customers more quickly and building mobile apps to enable customers to check out faster.</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> AI for Leaders on LinkedIn<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;"> If you&#39;re enjoying the <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> podcast, continue the conversation with us on LinkedIn. Join the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">AI for Leaders</a> group today.</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">Join now »</a></p></aside><p> Subscribe to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple Podcasts</a> , <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a> , or <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google Podcasts</a> .</p><div id="toolkit-banerjee"></div><h4> Transcript</h4><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Machine learning can detect fraudulent activity, but it may also miss good behavior. Find out how one platform company manages these risks and trade-offs on today&#39;s episode.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m Naba Banerjee from Airbnb, and you are listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Welcome to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> , a podcast on artificial intelligence in business. Each episode, we introduce you to someone innovating with AI. I&#39;m Sam Ransbotham, professor of analytics at Boston College. I&#39;m also the AI and business strategy guest editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I&#39;m Shervin Khodabandeh, senior partner with BCG and one of the leaders of our AI business. Together, <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG have been researching and publishing on AI since 2017, interviewing hundreds of practitioners and surveying thousands of companies on what it takes to build and to deploy and scale AI capabilities and really transform the way organizations operate.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Today, Shervin and I are speaking with Naba Banerjee, director of trust product and operations at Airbnb. Naba, thanks for joining us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you; a pleasure to be here.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think most people know Airbnb, but maybe tell us a brief overview of the company and what you do.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Airbnb stands for a place which fosters connection and belonging. Millions and millions of hosts open up their homes to complete strangers, and you and I and our families get to travel to an exotic destination, and instead of staying at a hotel, you actually get to truly immerse yourself in the local culture. And at times, if you&#39;re really lucky, you get to stay at the house of a host and actually experience hosting as it&#39;s meant to be, thereby creating and fostering connection and belonging.</p><p> And in this world that is increasingly becoming insular and connection is becoming a rare thing, I am so glad to be part of a company that is trying to create more connection. And what my team does, the trust and safety team at Airbnb, is along the entire customer journey, right from the time that you create an account on Airbnb throughout the journey. At times, it is possible that something could go wrong: A fake account could get created, or your account could get taken over. The listing you&#39;re trying to stay at could be a fake listing; the reviews you&#39;re looking at may not be exactly genuine. But our job is to make sure that you can focus on your magical stay, the host can focus on being the perfect host, and we try to anticipate some of these risks, and we minimize the risk of those kinds of issues from happening. And using technology and data to enable that magical user journey is what my team does.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think we all hear headlines where something goes wrong. How much goes wrong in the course of the gazillions of transactions that you do?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That&#39;s a great question. In 2021, we had around 70 million trips that happened on Airbnb, and less than 0.1% of those trips resulted in a host or a guest reporting potentially an issue that happened in that stay. And when our team went in and investigated and actually looked at where the real harm happened or somebody had to be removed from the platform, that number is even smaller.</p><p> I know that even one bad incident is probably too bad and should not be happening, but in the bigger scale of things, what you come back to realize is the majority of people are actually good. Ninety-nine point nine percent of people are meaning to just go about their daily business, enjoy a great stay, or be a great host. But sometimes, [on] that very rare occasion when that bad thing happens, we want to make sure that we reduce the risk of that.</p><p> If you really look at where a person is causing harm to another person, those incidents are like a fraction of a fraction of a fraction. But when we talk about safety, we&#39;re looking at [things like] a carbon monoxide gas leak. It could be slip and fall; it could be property damage, where glass broke and you probably had a stain on your carpet. We are also looking at those kinds of issues.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What I&#39;m hearing from what you&#39;re saying is, your role is, No. 1, a good role. You&#39;re the protector of the good and the “warder-offer” of evil, right?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I love that. You should be part of our branding team.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> It&#39;s a good thing, right? It&#39;s a very purposeful role. And the second part of it is, you&#39;re talking about microscopically small incidents.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, needles in a haystack.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Right? And those are fun problems. Tell us more about under the hood — what happens?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I would say it&#39;s three parts. One is, we start with the “why,” which is — you framed it really well — that we are the protector of the good and trying to ward off the bad. We can never say that we stop everything bad. Like, to Sam&#39;s point, you cannot do that. But how are we learning and getting better? And that&#39;s where AI and ML [machine learning] comes in, where [we ask], “How can we use [the] power of data and technology to learn and get better?” And every year, the risks don&#39;t stay the same; the data keeps growing.</p><p> And then the second thing is, “How do we use technology responsibly?” Which is, you could go too blunt and try to block as much as possible to specifically look at fraud and safety incidents and keep them down, but then, if the data that you are using to make these decisions has bias in it, is potentially creating unfairness, then you could close off your doors to a lot of good people who genuinely are just trying to have a good stay. So [it&#39;s about] using technology responsibly. … It is having self-governing mechanisms, which is, we have our privacy team, our data privacy team, our infosec team, our anti-discrimination teams, which are … almost like mirrors to the trust team. [There are also] other teams in Airbnb, where every time we are really laser-focused on this particular fraud vector, this bot detection, this account-takeover detection or party detection, they are constantly making sure that are we using the data in a safe way and a transparent way, giving users control and then not introducing bias.</p><p> And then, lastly, having ways for us to give people a path back, which is, we are going to — based on the data available to us, and the technology available to us, and the maturity of that technology — make our best possible decision. But if we get it wrong, can we create transparency and a process for users to appeal and get back on the platform when we do block them or remove them so that, again, we can learn and get better? So that, at the highest level, is how my team is working under the hood.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And what are some of the use cases?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> One of the use cases that we have talked about quite a bit is, you know … I&#39;ll take you on a little story, which is, when I joined the trust team in 2020, the world had just shut down; the pandemic was raging. And very similar to how the world was waiting for a vaccine, while waiting for a vaccine, we went into lockdown mode.</p><p> That was a blunt instrument … to prevent people from exposing themselves to situations which would make them unsafe. Similarly, Airbnb became an unfortunate product-market fit for unauthorized house parties. When the hotels and bars shut down, unfortunately that less than 1% or 0.1% of users who were looking for places where they could throw these parties, they started renting out Airbnbs. And as a result, we realized that it was causing a lot of pain to our communities of hosts and guests who use this platform, which was based on a foundation of trust. So initially, we had to use some very blunt instruments.</p><p> We first instituted our global party ban, saying that Airbnb does not allow for any kind of party whatsoever. Second, we started looking at some patterns and found that someone under 25 booking an entire home for just one night or two nights less than 50 or so miles away from their home — those seem to be all signals that lead to parties. When parties happen, we usually find … that account was created yesterday. Then we implemented a blunt rule called “under 25,” and we put that in place. Now, we had to be careful, because those rules don&#39;t exactly work globally. But that worked in North America, and we saw right away that there was a reduction in the number of unauthorized parties.</p><p> But over time, just as it happens with rules, we saw that people started to game those rules. They would get an older friend to book the reservation for them. And instead of one night, they would book it for three nights, and so on and so forth. [And] the impact on good users was so high that we said, “We kind of need to move to machine learning. We need to get smarter.” And so we did our first pilot in Australia, where we segmented the place and looked at the place that had this new party model that we&#39;d built versus the other. Do we see a reduction? And again, this is like looking for a needle in the haystack, but we still saw 35% fewer parties in the area that had the party model versus not. And when we started experimenting in North America, we did see that it was as effective as the heuristic, with lesser impact to good users.</p><p> And that kind of gave us the confidence to keep moving forward, because not doing anything was not an option. We had to do something and had to be smart about it. That was one of the use cases where we could go out and talk about it — not claiming that we are stopping all parties, but at least Airbnb is taking a strong stance about it.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> One common thread that I&#39;m hearing in how you&#39;re describing the problem and the solution is a need for constant adaptability and ongoing learning, and using the right instrument for the right job. At times it&#39;s a rule, then maybe its unsupervised learning, then there&#39;s a human intervention. It does sound quite multidisciplinary, including the part where the rules change, or the fraudster&#39;s mode of operation changes, and you also have the issue of “Is it too blunt? Does it limit some unintended but good or benign behaviors?” How does the human and machine collaboration or interaction work in these situations?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You summarized it really well, Shervin, which is, it&#39;s not a one-and-done thing. You build it, and then you have to constantly learn and optimize from even the kind of decisions you are making, as well as how the world around you is evolving. And that is an area [that] humans are really good at, which is, you do have to have the discipline of training your models with the latest data, with the right data, making trade-off decisions on what is the optimal threshold at which you are going to say, “OK, this is risky, and we are ready to use that risk.”</p><p> At Airbnb, we have been constantly on this journey of how to leverage humans in the loop. I have a trust operations team in addition to the product and planning teams. This operations team constitutes full-time employees as well as agents globally. And whenever we build a new model, in the beginning we often have the model make a risk threshold-based decision: “This is the top 1%. This is the next tranche. This is the next tranche.” And at times, we will route that to human beings to then create labels on top of that to say, “I agree with the model&#39;s decision,” or, “I don&#39;t agree with the model&#39;s decision,” which then serves as training data back to the model.</p><p> And then, when we have more confidence in the decision-making capability of the model, we would go toward auto-decisioning. This party model, to your point, right now it&#39;s completely auto-decisioned. But what ends up happening is, when we get an appeal back from a user saying, “I was incorrectly blocked,” that then serves as data that&#39;s coming by the customer telling us. And then an agent looks at that appeal and says, “Actually yes, this decision was incorrect.” And if the agent made a correct decision, that customer appealed correctly, and no incident happened, we know that that was a false positive.</p><p> But let&#39;s say the agent approved, and then that customer went on to throw a party; that was a false negative. We are learning from that continuously, but we do it iteratively. First, we try to have the model direct to a human. And again, there is no guarantee that the human is better at decision-making than the model, but we constantly measure the performance. Then we go toward higher-order decisioning [with less] human decisioning. And sometimes we will also have … let&#39;s say the party model makes decisions. People go about their merry way, have the reservation. Sometimes after the reservation has been booked, we will also still have humans look at the top 1% risky reservations to try and correct anything that they can.</p><p> So it is either trying to balance that out as to, when are humans the right people to make the decision? When should the machine make the decision? It&#39;s been a not-easy, nonlinear journey that we have been on.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> You mentioned at first you&#39;re maybe reviewing more cases and then learning from those cases. But at the same time, you have people … these 70 million transactions are happening constantly. And, for example, when you gave the illustration of the hotel … shutdown at the beginning of the pandemic, that&#39;s a time where it&#39;s happening to individual hosts and customers. How do you balance that trade-off of needing to get something in place quickly [while] at the same time needing to go through a process?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> That probably is the hardest thing, and the hardest thing in my entire career I would say that I have dealt with. Before this, I was managing all of product for Samsclub.com, which is part of Walmart, and I thought my job was hard then. And while we were serving customers, helping them check out, it still felt like we were on a growth path, and we could choose how fast we grew or how slowly we grew. And I always had teams that were looking at people who were trying to check out [but] couldn&#39;t and serving them while we were building longer-term architecture, but people&#39;s lives were not at stake; [it was] people&#39;s money — fraudsters using stolen credit cards and swindling the company of millions of dollars.</p><p> There is a team at Airbnb that is trying to protect the good and ward off the bad. What we do is that you have to get really good at prioritization, which is also very hard to do in the world of trust and safety.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And in many ways, I mean, the choices are what, Sam, you said in the beginning: These kinds of economies are not risk-free. They cannot be risk-free. And the good collectively outweighs the evil, so then it becomes all about prioritization. But I have to say, we&#39;ve talked to many people in analogous roles that you have, in other organizations — you mentioned Sam&#39;s Club, others — where they&#39;re using technology, digital AI/ML to drive a variety of use cases. I think yours stands out in the sense that it is a continuous balancing act, and the stakes are high. And then you have this sort of thread of purpose and the humility of saying, “Well, we believe that we&#39;ll make mistakes, and the system cannot be mistake-free.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> But over time, things are getting better. Which brings me to my next question: How do you measure this, your effectiveness? Is it in terms of number of incidents, and some severity and frequency of bad things happening?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I&#39;m glad you asked this question, because I was naturally going to go toward this, which is, at the highest level, the metrics that we measure ourselves on are number of fraud incidents per million trips, number of safety incidents per million trips, as well as good user impact. That&#39;s the balancing metric to see “How many good listings did we block? How many good hosts and good guests did we prevent from moving forward to truly understand our false positives and false negatives?” But at the end of the day, it&#39;s good trips that we are looking at across the board.</p><p> We are also looking at dollars in terms of fraud loss that is potentially happening. We are looking at customer support tickets that are coming in, user NPS [Net Promoter Scores] resulting from anyone who encounters a friction that is thrown by our teams. So at a basic level, we are looking at these metrics. But one of the challenges that, for the first time, again, in my career I&#39;ve run into — not so much in the fraud world, where we can A/B test — we are constantly iterating our models.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You are probably also, when you do that, preventing quite benign behaviors and intentions as well. But as you said, there is a point where the human judgment needs to trump and say that this is something where even the risk to one person might be too high. And yes, I mean, we always talk about exploration and exploitation when it comes to machine learning, and sort of ongoing feedback loops, but there&#39;s a cost to learning, always, right? But when I send you a marketing message you may not like, the cost of learning is very minimal, so I will send you many of them, and I&#39;ll do all kinds of A/B/X testing. But when I do that kind of A/B testing to groups or populations where the stakes are higher, then you might as well make that human judgment call of not doing it and relying on retrospective data.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And I think you elucidated that point quite well for us.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And one question that we ask ourselves is, what makes a human being trust another human being? What makes a human being trust Airbnb? And we are realizing that we can [train] all kinds of models in the background, and you wouldn&#39;t even know whether you were in the risk threshold 1% or 2%, or marked as a good user.</p><p> But there is also a dialogue that needs to happen between Airbnb and you as a guest or you as a host, or between the host and the guest, that truly instills trust. Like when we ask someone, “Would you be comfortable sending your 17-year-old girl to a stranger&#39;s house in Greece, when she wants to backpack before joining college?” You can probably tell this is a personal experience. I have a 17-year-old who&#39;s about to go to college. And I realized that the first thought is, “No — not happening,” and I run trust and safety at Airbnb. But then when I think, “Well, if I could talk to the host; if she&#39;s going to stay with someone else in a house; if that person is a mom like me …”</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And we as Airbnb could say, “We are running all these models in the background; don&#39;t worry, your daughter is safe” — I don&#39;t think that&#39;s going to fly. I think as a parent, you will want to have the information you need to see, even though your judgment may not be better than the machine&#39;s. So we are also working on, what is it that we need to say, that we need to do? And sometimes when we say things like, “Airbnb is not going to allow one-night stays that are booked at the last minute within the same neighborhood,” I think it makes a lot of parents feel better too, that OK, at least this option is gone. They will probably figure something else out. And that message cannot be convoluted. That message has to be simple. That message has to be clearly understood. And in addition to asking people what not to do, we also need to encourage people on what good behaviors they should do, like, talk to the host, talk to the guest, ask questions.</p><p> We have launched a program for solo female travelers because we were starting to see a slightly higher rate of maybe personal safety incidents in private rooms with solo female travelers. We started encouraging [women to] find out, is there going to be a lock in your room? Is that lock going to be working? Will you have access to the bathroom just by yourself? Which spaces are shared? Which are not? So this was not a model that was stopping anything. This was simply an educational module that we had published in multiple languages, which was really helpful for our solo travelers. Part of my team&#39;s work is not just to build invisible defenses but also to create trust and the perception of trust upfront through education and messaging.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. I have to say, you mentioned you&#39;re a mother of five. And I have to say, I think you stand on very solid ground when it comes to telling your kids what they can and cannot do, because you have so much data and so much experience, versus me when I say something and they&#39;re like, “Well, how would you know?” And you could say, “Well, trust me; I do 70 million transactions a year, and I know what&#39;s going on.”</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> And growing.是的。 I&#39;m happy to talk to your kids, by the way. Anytime.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yes, that would be great. I&#39;ll take you up on that.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> One thing about your measurements that I thought was interesting, maybe come back a little bit to that. You mentioned some positive metrics, too. So I think it&#39;s a little tempting, and I think even in this conversation we&#39;ve done that, is we titrate toward the negative. And that&#39;s the news problem in general — is that bad news sells papers. Well, I think in the course of this conversation, we&#39;ve shifted toward that. But some of the metrics you mentioned I thought had a more positive ring to them, didn&#39;t they?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah, absolutely. And this was an epiphany that we have been having over the past few years, because any kind of machine learning model typically does well when there is a lot of data to learn from. And with these kinds of cases, where out of 70 million-plus trips, when 0.1% of those result in even a report, and a fraction of a fraction of those results in an actual incident where someone gets removed, there is very little to learn from, and as a result, these models take time to mature. Of course, with technology evolving, that is going to get better, but we realized that we have a lot more data about good user behavior.</p><p> We have a lot more users who are actually coming in, booking their stay months in advance; they are probably checking in on time, leaving the property even better than they found it, communicating with the host and the guests, leaving honest reviews. So if we can actually flip the switch, and while we need to continue to look for the anomalies and the trends and the bad actors, if we can get really good at learning what good behavior looks like while making sure that we are also measuring for potential bias or discrimination and privacy compliance in how we collect and use this data, then that can be really powerful in informing when something does look risky. For example, if an account typically is accessed from the US, [and] suddenly we see that that IP is now accessing from the Philippines, and it feels like “Oh, this is an account takeover.” But if this is a good user who has typically been traveling around the world quite a bit, maybe this is not an account takeover, and there is history there from the good user behavior for us to be smarter about “What does normal look like and what does an anomaly look like?” Not broadly, but very specifically, based on the user segment.</p><p> So this is not new stuff, but I think we sometimes tend to obsess about just really learning what bad behavior looks like and getting good at detecting that, as opposed to complementing what an anomaly looks like [compared] to what normal behavior looks like.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Yeah. And you have such a wealth of insights and information in a field that is really an evolving field. I mean, it&#39;s not like a typical collaborative filtering situation where “users like you also bought this.” I mean, so much more goes on in terms of matching. This must be a very interesting and worthwhile problem to get your arms around.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Yeah. And it requires us to get out of our trust and safety silo and work really closely with our search, relevance, and personalization teams because our job — unlike my job when I used to work in e-commerce — is not just to do the collaborative filtering and say, “People like you bought this, so you should buy this,” or, “You traveled to Paris, so maybe next you want to go to Rome.”</p><p> It&#39;s about … you&#39;re traveling with the family this time. You have little kids; you probably want day care, and we know that this host offers day care, and this location might be great for you. Or with the same customer maybe traveling alone, maybe we need to offer up different recommendations. And having these trust and safety signals embedded into our search-relevance algorithms can get really powerful in matching the right person with the right listing.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Naba, you didn&#39;t start at Airbnb. Tell us a bit about how you got there. You referenced Walmart and some background there, but how did you end up in your current role?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I was the first female engineer in my family. My father took a chance on me and said, “You&#39;re curious. You&#39;re a forever learner. Do you want to do engineering?” And I had no idea what engineering was at that time, but I signed up anyway and went on to become the first female engineer in my family.</p><p> I worked with Tata Consultancy Services, then went on to join Cognizant, came through Cognizant to the US, and worked for some time at AAA. I would just keep going to different projects and different jobs that would help me learn something completely new.</p><p> Walmart happened around 2006. I was asked to work on supply chain at Walmart, which is probably, if you want to learn supply chain at a company, that&#39;s the company to go to. And while I was doing supply chain, every year I kept getting bigger and bigger responsibilities and projects until I found myself, from Walmart, leading almost all of the supply chain teams to going to Sam&#39;s Club, which is a part of Walmart — leading all of product and front end and cart and checkout and marketing and pricing, which I had never done before. But it gave me a chance to get a well-rounded experience learning how the back end of a large retailer works, as well as [how] front-end customer experience works.</p><p> And right after Sam&#39;s Club, I was asked to lead search. Right around that time, I was starting to get really interested in a world that runs on machine learning and AI, and search was a great landing ground for me. I did a course from MIT, interestingly, to learn about the application of AI and ML, and that gave me the courage to take on the search job.</p><p> And from there, Airbnb happened, after 13 years, almost, at Walmart. I was so curious about the travel industry and this marketplace that was so different from anything I had done in Walmart. So the theme here is that I have always gravitated toward something that helps me leverage the skills that I have but then use my curiosity and learning to do something completely new and build myself up as I go along. That&#39;s kind of my background.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Naba, we have a section now where we ask you a series of rapid-fire questions, and just tell us the first thing that comes to your mind. What is your proudest AI/ML moment?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> You&#39;re asking me to choose between my different teams, which is career-limiting for me. But I will say that the work that we did on party detection and party risk reduction was groundbreaking, and there&#39;s no one else in the industry who did it the way we did, so that is [a] really proud [moment for me]. But I am proud of all my teams, just for the record.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> That&#39;s a great answer. What worries you about AI?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> What worries me is how powerful it is. We had a chance to get to see [OpenAI CEO] Sam Altman up close and in person as he came to Airbnb. And just how fast this technology is improving and how much capability it has … I worry about it falling into the wrong hands. I worry that while my team has this technology, the fraudsters have this technology too, and so I worry about, if today we are worried about fake IDs and fake spam messages being sent to our hosts and guests, how much more advanced this technology is going to get and how much more difficult it is going to get for us to detect the good from the bad. And I think it&#39;ll be AI to the rescue as well in detecting fake AI.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Your favorite activity that involves no technology?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Painting with watercolors. I love painting nature. And so paper, watercolors, and just peace and tranquility, no technology, is my favorite thing to do. And of course hugging my kids and spending time with them just listening to their day, trying to make them not be on their cellphones while they talk to me. Those two.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> Very well said. The first career you wanted: What did you want to be when you grew up?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I wanted to be a teacher. I come from a family of teachers, and I feel so much joy when I&#39;m seeing someone&#39;s eyes light up with the gift of knowledge. I am a forever learner. Every job that I take has been completely different from my previous job; it&#39;s because I love to learn. And so, yeah, that&#39;s what I wanted to be.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> And you probably do a fair amount of teaching in your current role anyway.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> I do a lot of mentoring.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> You&#39;ve taught us quite a lot.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, thank you. I do do a lot of mentoring, because I feel like if someone else can see me do what I do, that will make them feel that they can do it too. So if I can just do that, that&#39;s my life&#39;s mission accomplished.</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh:</strong> What&#39;s your greatest wish for AI in the future?</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> My greatest wish for the world, actually, is to not be so afraid; to give it a chance. Because I think sometimes our fear of the bad holds us from embracing the good. There is so much wasted effort that goes into activities that should be automated through AI — so many patients who are not getting treatment; so many companies that probably need help and need so much funding to stand up basic things that can be done by AI; so many countries, probably, who are underdeveloped [but could] get so much advantage. I know that when it falls into the wrong hands, it can be used for bad, but the world has more good people than bad people, and I believe in the power of us using AI for good — using our collective goodness.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> I think everyone will probably resonate with your idea that the world is better than it is bad. We do tend to hear most of the negative stories, but it&#39;s refreshing to hear how, one, how much attention you&#39;re paying to try and to prevent those, but also to hear something about the good stories too that your platform enables. Thank you for taking the time to talk with us today. We&#39;ve enjoyed it.</p><p> <strong>Naba Banerjee:</strong> Thank you, Sam. Thank you, Shervin. My pleasure.</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham:</strong> Thanks for listening. Next time, we&#39;re joined by Zan Gilani, principal product Please join us.</p><p> <strong>Allison Ryder:</strong> Thanks for listening to <cite>Me, Myself, and AI</cite> . We believe, like you, that the conversation about AI implementation doesn&#39;t start and stop with this podcast. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve created a group on LinkedIn specifically for listeners like you. It&#39;s called AI for Leaders, and if you join us, you can chat with show creators and hosts, ask your own questions, share your insights, and gain access to valuable resources about AI implementation from <cite>MIT SMR</cite> and BCG. You can access it by visiting <a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a> . We&#39;ll put that link in the show notes, and we hope to see you there.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/detecting-the-good-and-the-bad-with-ai-airbnbs-naba-banerjee/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Case Against Restricting Stock Buybacks</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Guest, S.P. Kothari, and Parth Venkat. <p>Nicholas Guest is an assistant professor of accounting at the Johnson Graduate School of Management at Cornell University. SP Kothari is the Gordon Y. Billard Professor of Accounting and Finance at MIT&#39;s Sloan School of Management, where he was previously deputy dean. Parth Venkat is an assistant professor of finance at the Culverhouse College of Business at the University of Alabama.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Boards and Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Shareholders]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Boards & Corporate Governance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Frontiers]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com Are stock buybacks as bad as they’re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/2023SUM-Kothari-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carlo Giambarresi/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p> Are stock buybacks as bad as they&#39;re made out to be? The ubiquitous corporate practice of repurchasing shares has been the focus of much political and media scrutiny. The federal Inflation Reduction Act of 2022 included a 1% excise tax on repurchases (which President Biden has proposed increasing to 4% in his 2024 budget). In addition, senior Democrats have shown interest in barring executives from selling shares for three years after a repurchase, the federal government has suggested that companies that give up buybacks will receive preferential treatment, and the Securities and Exchange Commission has proposed a significant increase in the extent and frequency of repurchase reporting.</p><p> The debate on the economic consequences of stock buybacks has so far tended to focus on small samples or cherry-picked examples. Given that thousands of companies repurchase their shares each year, and aggregate repurchases have exceeded $500 billion annually for the past five years, we decided that a large-sample study of repurchasing behavior was warranted. Our study, published in the journal <cite>Financial Management</cite> , outlines the benefits of the practice, as stated by its proponents, and provides evidence that casts doubt on the alleged costs cited by its critics.</p><p></p><p> Critics of buybacks typically make three arguments against the practice. First, they claim that share repurchases enable companies to manipulate the market either by increasing the demand for — and therefore the price of — shares or by tricking naive investors by inflating earnings per share (EPS). Second, they allege that share repurchases enable insiders to benefit through compensation contracts or the sale of shares at inflated prices. And lastly, critics charge that share repurchases crowd out investment and thus sacrifice innovation and long-term economic growth.</p><p> Meanwhile, those who support or engage in stock buybacks offer several justifications for the practice. First, payouts to shareholders align manager and shareholder incentives by reducing the potential misuse of free cash flow. Second, using repurchases instead of or in addition to dividends gives corporations flexibility in the amount of cash returned to shareholders, the ability to award repurchased shares to employees as equity compensation, a modest tax advantage to shareholders (less pronounced since the 2003 dividend tax cut), and the ability to signal the company&#39;s good prospects to the market. Finally, share repurchases represent well-disclosed and regulated arm&#39;s length transactions at current market prices between willing participants.</p><p> Given the drive to regulate share repurchases, we would expect evidence of their drawbacks to be observable in public data. To test this, we documented trends in repurchases and compared trading volume, share price performance, CEO pay, and corporate financial activities (evidenced by investment and profitability) of companies that do and do not repurchase shares. We segmented the businesses that repurchased shares in two ways: (1) small positive versus large positive repurchase amounts (defined as below versus above median values), and (2) frequent versus infrequent repurchasers (defined as companies that repurchase in one or two quarters as opposed to three or four quarters of the year).</p><p> Our large-sample evidence on thousands of US exchange-listed companies over the past three decades shows that repurchases in the US are a mainstream corporate financial activity that returns several hundred billion dollars of capital to shareholders annually. At an aggregate level, we found that this activity neither creates nor destroys much wealth (that is, it does not produce significant changes in share price). In addition, while repurchases are associated with higher past profitability, they are not associated with excessive CEO pay or underinvestment.</p><p> Trends in aggregate repurchasing activity over time indicate that while repurchases have quickly grown in value, much of the growth can be attributed to inflation and increases in market capitalization. In addition, repurchases are now similar in size to dividends and have not grown faster than dividends for quite some time. However, unlike dividends, repurchases drop precipitously (and temporarily) in times of corporate stress, indicating that they do in fact provide companies with the aforementioned benefit of payout flexibility.</p><p></p><h3> A Closer Look at the Data</h3><p> Through our analysis, we were able to systematically address each of the stated criticisms of stock buybacks.</p><p> First, do companies use share repurchases to manipulate the market by creating excess demand to drive up stock prices? If they do, companies that repurchase shares should have higher trading volumes than those that do not. But average trading volumes have largely remained quite similar for all listed companies, regardless of whether or how often they repurchase shares. In fact, in recent years, the trading volumes for companies that do not repurchase shares have greatly exceeded those of repurchasing companies, suggesting that any excess volume arising from repurchases is dwarfed by other forces.</p><p> If naive investors are tricked into buying shares of companies that engage in repurchasing behavior because of the resulting EPS inflation, we should observe short-term price bumps followed by poor long-term performance. However, regardless of whether or how intensely and frequently companies repurchased shares, we found no evidence that companies significantly outperformed in the quarters with repurchases. While we did find some marginal evidence that companies that intensely repurchase do outperform slightly in the quarter after repurchases, we found no evidence of future reversals in the short or long terms. This pattern of outperformance is more consistent with companies using repurchases to signal undervaluation — a benefit to investors — rather than to manipulate the market.</p><p></p><p> The second critique is that repurchases allow insiders to unfairly profit. If share repurchases as rent-seeking behavior by insiders were a common, systematic abuse, CEOs whose companies buy back shares would receive abnormally high pay, including salary, bonuses, and the value of equity awards. Using a model-generated measure of excess pay that has been vetted in earlier academic literature, we estimate that CEOs of companies that make large positive repurchases earn only $51,000 more than CEOs of companies that do not repurchase shares — a statistically and economically insignificant amount of excess pay. The difference is even smaller — $4,000 — when we compare CEOs of companies that repurchase frequently with those that do not repurchase. These differences are economically tiny in relation to the average CEO&#39;s pay of several million dollars. Surprisingly, CEOs of companies that repurchase infrequently or repurchase small positive amounts earn the least excess pay, less than even the CEOs of non-repurchasing companies. None of this evidence suggests that companies use repurchases to boost CEO pay.</p><p> The third and final critique is that repurchases reduce companies&#39; ability to take advantage of investment opportunities, thereby sacrificing innovation and economic growth. We found that companies that do not repurchase shares invest more but are significantly less profitable than those that do repurchase shares. The companies that repurchase frequently and in large amounts are highly profitable and have steadily made investments in the past, and they continue to make large investments and, at the same time, return capital to shareholders. This suggests that profitable companies repurchase shares while maintaining a steady level of investment, whereas less profitable or loss-making companies do not (or maybe cannot) repurchase shares but are more investment-intensive in the hope of becoming profitable. While there might be isolated examples of poorly governed companies that choose to avoid profitable investments and instead return capital to willing shareholders, it is hard to see how directives encouraging or incentivizing such poorly run companies to retain cash would lead them to make good investments.</p><p> Potential stakeholders who may be affected by repurchase regulations include managers, other employees, shareholders, governments, and society at large. If a company is profitable, a CEO can pay excess cash out to shareholders in the form of buybacks or dividends, keep the money on their balance sheets, or invest in new projects. A small tax on share repurchases may not change corporate behavior significantly and might raise a small amount of revenue for the government. But if the tax rate grows high enough, companies will choose to not buy back shares and instead pay out exclusively via dividends or retain cash. In that case, the government raises no revenue but implements a de facto ban on share repurchases.</p><h3> How a Buyback Ban Could Backfire</h3><p> If a company were to switch to only paying out dividends, shareholders would lose the ability to choose whether to receive a cash payout and could face negative tax ramifications, given that dividends are taxed as income while capital gains are often taxed at a lower rate, and only when gains are realized. In addition, the company would lose important flexibility in difficult times, because cutting dividends is punished more by the market than cutting repurchases.</p><p></p><p> However, the move to restrict stock buybacks seems intended not to motivate companies to shift to paying back shareholders through dividends but to invest more in the business. There is evidence that retained cash is correlated with CEOs making value-destroying decisions, such as pursuing empire-building mergers, accruing personal expenses, or funding pet projects. It seems implausible that restrictions on share repurchases would induce CEOs of poorly governed companies to invest in value-enhancing projects that they otherwise would not have been funding.</p><p></p><p> From an employee standpoint, there is some evidence that labor unions are able to negotiate more successfully if their employers have excess cash, but there is plenty of evidence that constraints on a company&#39;s flexibility to raise and distribute capital is bad for employees, especially during downturns. Empire-building mergers can also be bad for employees, given that M&amp;As often result in the employees of the acquisition target being laid off and employees of the acquiring company being misallocated. In addition, some repurchased shares are reissued to employees, making any actions that are bad for shareholders also bad for stockholding employees.</p><p> Overall, our results show an absence of correlation between share repurchases and price manipulation, return reversals, excess CEO compensation, and underinvestment, which makes it highly implausible that economically significant causal effects of share repurchases still underlie the data. Corporations lose flexibility if they have to rely only on dividends, and evidence shows that poorly governed CEOs who retain cash often spend it on value-destroying mergers, expenses, or pet projects. It is implausible that policies designed to reduce repurchases will also reduce alleged but unobserved malpractices without imposing costs on US public companies and other stakeholders.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-case-against-restricting-stock-buybacks/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Are You Ready for the Next Supply Disruption?</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:46:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Johnny Rungtusanatham, David A. Johnston, and Elizabeth Heichler . <p>M. Johnny Rungtusanatham is a professor of operations management and information systems and the Canada Research Chair in Supply Chain Management (Tier 1) at the Schulich School of Business at York University. David A. Johnston is a professor of operations management and information systems and the research chair and director of the George Weston Ltd. Centre for Sustainable Supply Chains at the Schulich School of Business. Elizabeth Heichler is editorial director, magazine, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain & Logistics]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Capabilities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chain Resilience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Crisis Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Supply Chains & Logistics]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &#8220;Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, Nov. 7, 2022. Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &#8220;black swan&#8221; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently. M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> J. Rungtusanatham and D. Johnston, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/get-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Get Ready for the Next Supply Disruption</a> ,&quot; <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , Nov. 7, 2022.</p></aside><p> Supply disruptions triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic caught many companies off guard. To prepare for future &quot;black swan&quot; threats to supply chains, managers must think differently.</p><p> M. Johnny Rungtusanatham and David A. Johnston have researched the triggers and performance consequences of supply disruption. Their ADDAPT framework can help leaders better manage disruptions and maintain product flow.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why traditional risk management may not be adequate to prepare for the next catastrophic supply disruption.</li><li> Why you need to develop six capabilities — anticipate, detect, diagnose, activate, protect, and track — to prepare for and manage for supply disruptions.</li><li> What changes you need to make to your business strategy, practices, processes, and systems to improve supply chain resilience.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/are-you-ready-for-the-next-supply-disruption/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Flexible and Effective: Leadership Strategies for the Hybrid Workplace</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:00:34 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Elliott. <p>Brian Elliott is the executive leader and a cofounder of Future Forum, a research-driven consortium that helps senior executives around the globe reimagine how people, processes, and tools come together to make work better through data and dialogue. Future Forum was formed through a partnership between Slack, BCG, Management Leadership for Tomorrow, and MillerKnoll. He&#39;s coauthor of <cite>How the Future Works: Leading Flexible Teams to Do the Best Work of Their Lives</cite> (Wiley, 2022).</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Corporate Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hybrid Work]]></category><category><![CDATA[Productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace Environment]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Performance Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Work-Life Balance]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Many leaders don’t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it’s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/W23-QA02_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> Many leaders don&#39;t know how to manage work based on outcomes versus the proverbial “bums in seats” — tracking who is at the office and for how long. But it&#39;s possible to have a high-performing, healthy workplace culture in a hybrid workplace, with flexibility in when and where people work. It just needs to be managed differently.</p><p> That was the message of Future Forum&#39;s Brian Elliott, who presented on a panel with N. Sharon Hill of the George Washington University School of Business and Julie Dervin of Atlassian during <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/series/work-23-the-big-shift/">Work/23</a> , an <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> symposium held in May 2023.</p><p> Elliott said that 93% of the 10,243 knowledge workers his company polled said they want flexibility in when they work. Those who were given some choice, he said, had <a href="https://futureforum.com/research/future-forum-pulse-winter-2022-2023-snapshot/">productivity scores 39% higher</a> than those who were not. Those with some flexibility about <em>where</em> they work also scored higher (8%).</p><p></p><p></p><p> Finding an equilibrium between employees&#39; desire for flexibility and an organization&#39;s strategic goals requires a reexamination of the kinds of work that need to be done in person. It also may require different work configurations for different groups within the same organization, and it certainly requires different ways of benchmarking the work employees accomplish.</p><p> Attendees had more questions for the presenters than there was time for, and Elliott agreed to answer some after the event. (Questions and answers have been lightly edited for clarity.)</p><h6> How do you measure productivity? Most workers say they are more productive working from home and on their own schedule, but are they really?</h6><p> Here&#39;s a heretical take: We need to stop trying to measure productivity in knowledge work and focus all that time and energy on measuring outcomes.</p><p> Productivity metrics take outputs (emails sent, cases closed) and divide them by inputs (hours active), and the better ones adjust for quality (cases reopened). That can work, somewhat, for rote, routine tasks, which are what get automated over time. But also, those metrics can be gamed, and people will game them — up to and including buying <a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07VHBQQVG">mouse jigglers</a> . As Dominic Price of Atlassian has <a href="https://www.atlassian.com/blog/productivity/the-problem-with-productivity-metrics">written</a> , “Productivity has always been a good way to measure the impact of machines and capital. It&#39;s just never been a good way to measure the impact of <em>humans</em> .”</p><p> At Future Forum, we&#39;ve ventured into this; we compared populations with and without flexibility to see that those with location flexibility report higher productivity scores, and those with schedule flexibility have an even bigger advantage. There are also academic studies by Stanford&#39;s <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">Nick Bloom</a> , HBS&#39;s <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w30292">Raj Choudhury</a> , and others that show the same thing.</p><p> But it&#39;s an odd question in that we didn&#39;t ask it when people were in the office. We simply assumed that because people were present, they were doing something productive. We all know that&#39;s not accurate.</p><p> Instead, let&#39;s skip the whole mess and take the time to get clear on our organization&#39;s objectives and key results (OKRs), and do it in a way that those can cascade down by business unit and function, and to the team level. From the team level, much can be taken to the individual level to find the individual&#39;s impact both in terms of what they did and how they were as a teammate.</p><p> Assessing people on the impact they have on a team&#39;s goals is harder but will take us a lot further than installing more productivity metrics that measure their inputs and outputs.</p><h6> Random collisions seem to be key in driving innovation. How do you promote serendipity in terms of making connections across teams?</h6><p> Connections are an essential part of employee engagement and retention, but the connection to innovation is at best spurious. <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=991">Study</a> after <a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/4093796">study</a> has shown that what really enables innovation is psychological safety.</p><p> In research we conducted in 2021, Future Forum found that location (whether fully onsite, hybrid, or fully remote) had little to no correlation to team innovation. Instead, what <em>did</em> matter were factors like whether people felt they could ask questions and whether teams were willing to take risks — that is, whether they felt psychological safety.</p><p> Building connections is important, but we should do it intentionally in organizations instead of relying on random chance. Here are three ways you can do this:</p><p> <strong>1. Intentional cross-team connections.</strong> Programs like open brown-bag lunches where a rotating cast of internal experts present or host an “ask me anything session,” bringing leaders from other functions into your quarterly planning cycles, and creating public channels in Slack or Teams for sharing insights based on topics (like AI) can go a long way.</p><p> <strong>2. Leverage tools to build connections.</strong> Products like Donut, an app for Slack or Teams that pairs up individuals across teams programmatically, help ensure that everyone gets connected, not just those who work on the same floor or in the same building.</p><p> <strong>3. Help new employees build a network.</strong> One of the big challenges of the past few years is that too many companies hired people without rethinking how they build connections and get to understand the culture. One of my favorite tips comes from Genpact in Europe, where new employees are given six people to meet outside their team, either in person or at a virtual coffee, and each of those is supposed to provide two to three more contacts.</p><p> Investing in new tools and processes can also be a big boost. Think about processes like <a href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/12/using-brainwriting-for-rapid-idea-generation/">brainwriting</a> before a brainstorming session: Allowing people the heads-down space to think about some research results or a problem, write out their thoughts ahead of time, and then share with the group at the same time brings out more new ideas. It also lowers the odds of groupthink.</p><p></p><h6> How can you communicate an expectation that people should come into the office one or two days a week in a way that is inspiring and inclusive, and not forceful and dictatory?</h6><p> The last two years are littered with companies that declared that three days a week in person is the answer and saw 1.5 days a week as an average. This hides the fact that there&#39;s typically a more junior group of employees coming in two or three days a week, while more senior employees are coming in less often.</p><p> Repeating the policy doesn&#39;t work, and threatening to fire people who don&#39;t come in more often is unrealistic and breeds resentment. Leadership knows that it&#39;s some of the more experienced, critical talent that&#39;s coming in less often. The junior staff knows this too.</p><p> Instead, what we&#39;ve seen work is focusing on helping teams figure out their own rhythms through team-level agreements. The needs of a sales team and an engineering team, for instance, are different. The sales team might end up mandating two days a week that are default days in the office, and stacking those days with specific activities that are more “heads-up” than heads-down, such as training sessions, mentoring hours, and one-on-ones. The engineering team, on the other hand, might end up with one week of the month in person for planning, lunches together, and demo days.</p><p> Encouraging senior staff to come in at least one day a week for mentoring sessions, to be available for training, and for coffee with junior staff goes a lot further than simply telling them to show up.</p><p> The other critical element is that coming to the office can&#39;t be consistently worse than working at home. People don&#39;t want free lunch all the time, they want a place for team meetings, the ability to find a quiet spot for customer calls, and Wi-Fi that works. For a large number of companies, that requires redesigning the workspace.</p><h6> What should managers do to avoid having flexible work perpetuate or even exaggerate existing biases in the workplace? Being “out of sight, out of mind” is a real concern.</h6><p> Proximity bias and the chances of presenteeism leading to better opportunities as well as rewards is a real risk. We need to create a level playing field, and that starts with training managers and leaders to assess team and individual performance on the outcomes they generate, not the inputs (hours in the office, speed of response, being always-on). Leaders and their people partners need to look not only at the promotion and rewards cycle but also at their talent development pipeline and who&#39;s getting the new, shiny projects.</p><p> Working with the Slack executive team, we set a rule that all of the senior executives&#39; regular reviews — such as the CMO&#39;s weekly review of new project proposals — be done entirely virtually. That helped not only the usual challenges of people not hearing those at the other end of the room but also the pressure to be “in the room where it happens” for those meetings, which more junior staff might attend only once or twice a year.</p><h6> Many companies and industries outside of tech have a split between knowledge workers and those who need to be present in person to do their job (such as retail and manufacturing). How would you recommend positioning flexibility so as not to create an unfair dual standard?</h6><p> The differences between desk (office) workers and deskless (or front-line) workers extend far beyond the ability to work remotely: They include pay, benefits, facilities, training, and more.</p><p> The talent shortage in deskless workers is a massive challenge for many companies. But I don&#39;t think the answer is to force desk workers back into offices full-time. That doesn&#39;t really solve any issues for deskless workers.</p><p> The answer here is investing in the specific needs of deskless workers. According to <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2022/why-deskless-workers-are-leaving-and-how-to-win-them-back">research by Boston Consulting Group</a> , schedule flexibility and choice are top factors in talent retention. Leaders are investing in programs like the ability to swap shifts and having multiple types of schedules for call center workers. Neiman Marcus Group reduced turnover by 20% by offering sales associates flexibility in choice of stores and departments, as well as hours.</p><h6> I&#39;m at a startup. In a budding company, management focuses a lot on work culture as they grow. How does a startup, or any enterprise for that matter, build culture while allowing a remote or hybrid model?</h6><p> I&#39;m a strong believer that culture is built regardless of where you are located, the slogans on the wall, or the quality of the happy hours. Culture gets built based on the everyday experiences your employees have and the decisions you make: what you prioritize as a company, how you treat your customers and employees, what projects you resource, and whom you reward.</p><p></p><p> That said, there are a set of practices that I&#39;ve seen used that really help build a solid foundation. Here are three of them:</p><p></p><p> First, digital-first doesn&#39;t mean “never in person.” Getting people together, even if widely distributed, is an important part of building culture. For teams, I&#39;d recommend — at least quarterly — a few days focused primarily on team building, socialization, and connection. As a startup grows, this often goes from everyone quarterly to teams quarterly and everyone once a year.</p><p> Second, get clarity on how you work together, and share more about yourself. Your <a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/06/23/team-level-agreements/">team-level agreement</a> shouldn&#39;t just focus on how often people are together, it should also get into how you communicate, how you make decisions, and more. Sharing tools like <a href="https://futureforum.com/2022/07/15/personal-user-manual/">personal user manuals</a> can also go a long way toward establishing a culture of trust.</p><p> And third, create transparency at work. One of the key factors that drive culture is leadership communication, and as a company scales, it&#39;s important to remain transparent while putting in place guardrails. What topics matter to your company and mission most? How do we interact with one another? Scaling internal communications from CEO “ask me anything” sessions to public forums for knowledge sharing takes time and effort; <a href="https://slack.com/blog/transformation/a-modern-leaders-guide-to-organizational-transparency">guidelines from others</a> can help.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/flexible-and-effective-leadership-strategies-for-the-hybrid-workplace/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> How to Support Your Team When Uncertainty Is High</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Liz Fosslien. <p>Liz Fosslien ( <a href="https://twitter.com/fosslien">@fosslien</a> ) is an expert on emotions at work and the coauthor and illustrator of <cite>The Wall Street Journal</cite> bestseller <cite>No Hard Feelings: The Secret Power of Embracing Emotion at Work</cite> (Portfolio, 2019) and <cite>Big Feelings: How to Be Okay When Things Are Not Okay</cite> (Portfolio, 2022). She is also on the leadership team of Atlassian&#39;s Team Anywhere and previously served as the head of content and communications at Humu.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Employee Motivation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Psychology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Uncertainty]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[“My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don’t really know what’s going to happen in six months either. What can I do?” If you’ve found [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Fosslien-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><br /></figure><p> “My team seems really anxious,” a manager recently told me. “We just went through a reorg, and there are a lot of concerns about the future. I want to give everyone some kind of assurance, but I don&#39;t really know what&#39;s going to happen in six months either. What can I do?”</p><p> If you&#39;ve found yourself in a similar situation recently, you&#39;re not alone. Almost every people leader I&#39;ve met with over the past year has asked me some version of this question. And in a recent study, 89% of HR leaders shared that their teams have voiced concerns about <a href="https://www.humu.com/blog/the-toll-of-workplace-anxiety-and-what-to-do-about-it">job security, leadership changes, or reorgs</a> .</p><p> When uncertainty is high, managers should aim to make work a place of stability rather than another source of stress. “The most effective managers clearly communicate that they care about the people on their team,” explained Molly Sands, head of practices for Atlassian&#39;s Team Anywhere. “Research shows that what managers of top-performing teams consistently do differently is to make their reports <a href="https://assets-global.website-files.com/601872ae12d42e2264ff9ac4/62d6d89b1037a1bb82393638_Infographic _ Actions that drive great management.pdf">feel valued and comfortable</a> .”</p><p></p><p> How can you offer assurance when a lot of big decisions — and broader economic conditions — are outside of your control? It may seem almost impossible, but it&#39;s not. Here are seven ways managers can support their teams during turbulent times without making promises they can&#39;t keep.</p><p> <strong>Help each employee work toward their dream job.</strong> You can&#39;t always guarantee someone a promotion (or, unfortunately, even job stability), but you can commit to giving your employees the kinds of valuable learning opportunities that will help them no matter what comes next.</p><p> To surface the experiences or projects your team members would be excited to take on, ask them to show you a job posting for a role they&#39;d be thrilled to have in three to five years. Walk through the listed responsibilities together, and pinpoint any for which they think they lack the skills or compelling experience. Then commit to helping them grow in these areas by offering them relevant tasks or projects.</p><p> It can also be useful to make career chats a habit. Every six weeks, schedule 30 minutes with each of your reports to ask questions like these:</p><ul><li> What kinds of projects or tasks do you enjoy most?</li><li> What parts of your current responsibilities do you find energizing?</li><li> Do you feel like you&#39;re learning and growing in your role?</li><li> Are there skills you&#39;re looking to grow in the future?</li></ul><p> Make it a point to create or offer them relevant opportunities based on these conversations.</p><p> <strong>Cocreate a medium-term mission with your team.</strong> When faced with uncertainty or frequently shifting priorities, we often feel stuck or like we have little to show for all the effort we&#39;re putting in. This sense of helplessness can lead to apathy and disengagement. In fact, research my team at Humu conducted in February on the impact of continued uncertainty showed that roughly 40% of <a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/web-assets-humu/eBooks/FY24 Q1 eBook - Uncertainty/eBook_Uncertainty_01.pdf">employees felt less ambitious</a> than they did a year earlier.</p><p> To reenergize your team members, bring them together to define and work toward a shared three-month goal. Looking three months out can create a longer-term sense of stability for your people, but it&#39;s a short enough time period that, even if things shift around you, you likely won&#39;t have to change your mission. For example, a marketing team might aim to increase website traffic by 25% over the next quarter, or run experiments on how to more quickly share information and make decisions. As Jamie Woolf and Heidi Rosenfelder, founders of Creativity Partners, advise, “To better enlist your team in the cocreation of the future, try asking questions like &#39;What new sources of profit can replace dwindling ones?&#39; or &#39;What can we do to break down silos within our team?&#39;”</p><p></p><p> <strong>Help your team achieve wins within two weeks.</strong> Quickly boost your team members&#39; sense of progress by focusing them on what they <em>can</em> control and giving each of them a specific task they can cross off within a week or two. Start by dividing your medium-term mission or longer-term goals into mini-milestones, and track and celebrate each one as it&#39;s achieved.</p><p> Sarah, an engineering manager, recently split an ambitious product launch into a series of specific features and updates and then assigned her reports individual tasks from the list. She also set up a 15-minute team check-in at the end of each week to celebrate what they had achieved and track the group&#39;s collective progress toward their shared goal.</p><p> <strong>Create clarity when you can.</strong> Thoughtful explanations in tough situations are critical to earning trust and reducing anxiety. The next time you have an update to share, prepare to walk through the story of how the decision was made, and think through any concerns or questions that might come up. Plan how you&#39;ll address each one. If you&#39;re unsure of what to say, ask other leaders or HR for recommendations. When you do share the decision with your team members, encourage them to ask clarifying questions.</p><p> It&#39;s also important for managers to speak to their own emotions — while avoiding emotionally processing news in front of their team. “You should say, &#39;I am disappointed about the results this quarter,&#39; but not, &#39;I am so disappointed by the results. I am so terrified we are all going to lose our jobs. I don&#39;t know what to do,&#39;” Sands suggested. “Transparency doesn&#39;t mean you have to share everything you feel or are concerned about.”</p><p></p><p> You can also run a clarity audit by talking with your team about a recent decision that affected them (such as a new product road map or a change in the expense policy). In your next series of one-on-one meetings, ask the following questions:</p><ul><li> How and when did you learn about this decision?</li><li> Is anything unclear?</li><li> What can I do differently the next time I&#39;m communicating a change with the team?</li></ul><p> These conversations can help you identify how to improve transparency — and make it clear to employees that you&#39;re doing your best to keep them up to date.</p><p> <strong>Provide context when you can&#39;t create clarity.</strong> Managers tend to stay quiet until they can share a concrete decision. But a lack of communication is still a form of communication — and it usually breeds mistrust and gossip.</p><p></p><p> To avoid misunderstandings, explain why you can&#39;t offer more details, and aim to provide a timeline for when you expect to have more information. For example, you might say something along the lines of “I haven&#39;t heard back on what changes will be made to the sales pitch. I&#39;m hoping to have more to share with you in a week or so, but I wanted to be as transparent as possible with where we are right now.”</p><p> <strong>Encourage your team to benefit from benefits.</strong> Studies show that up to 80% of employees are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbeshumanresourcescouncil/2019/07/02/only-half-of-employees-understand-their-benefits-heres-what-hr-leaders-can-do-about-it/?sh=a4a1a578133c">confused about the benefits</a> their company provides. When budgets shrink, it can be an uphill battle to design and fund new ways to support your team. You might be surprised at how much you can boost morale simply by making employees aware of what already exists. For example, though my former employer offered women returning from maternity leave the option to work part time for their first month back, many expectant mothers were unaware of this policy. After Sands, then a product leader at Humu, flagged this option on a companywide Slack channel, several women (including me) took advantage of it and expressed gratitude for the policy.</p><p> Review your company handbook, or schedule a quick meeting with HR for a refresher. In an upcoming team meeting, give a brief overview of your organization&#39;s benefits, and encourage your team members to take full advantage of them. You might want to specifically highlight mental health benefits, vacation policies, or flexible work options. Start by saying something like “I know it&#39;s been a stressful time and uncertainty is high, so I want to highlight a few programs and benefits our company offers that might help you feel better.”</p><p> <strong>Help your team say no.</strong> Preserve your team&#39;s mental health by stepping in to protect their time. Set clear and reasonable expectations, and back your reports when they turn down nonurgent requests.</p><p></p><p> You can also look for ways to get more visibility into everything they&#39;re being asked to do — and aim to set up friendly barriers. For example, when I learned that my team was being overwhelmed with requests from sales, I created a short form and advised my reports to direct all of the requesters to complete it in order to start the process. This served three functions: (1) It allowed me to better understand what my team was being pulled into, (2) I could help my reports prioritize or say no as necessary, and (3) it reduced the number of requests, because few people actually filled out the form.</p><p></p><p> Uncertainty breeds anxiety, and although managers can&#39;t snap their fingers and magically make everything fall perfectly into place, they can take steps to help their teams feel more empowered, supported, and able to succeed. Offering team members personally meaningful growth opportunities and helping them achieve quick wins can restore their sense of control and motivation. Creating transparency around changes and updates — or explaining why a decision has not yet been announced — can restore employee trust. And helping people invest in their well-being and set healthy boundaries can make it easier for them to weather workplace storms.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-support-your-team-when-uncertainty-is-high/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>