<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"><channel><title>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</title><atom:link href="http://sloanreview.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu<description>可持续创新</description><lastbuilddate>2023 年 10 月 25 日，星期三 11:00:43 +0000</lastbuilddate><language> en-US</language><sy:updateperiod>每小时</sy:updateperiod><sy:updatefrequency>1</sy:updatefrequency><generator> https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator><item><title>团队里其实有一个“我”</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elad N. Sherf, Subra Tangirala, and Alex Ning Li. <p>埃拉德·N·谢尔夫 (Elad N. Sherf) 是北卡罗来纳大学教堂山分校凯南-弗拉格勒商学院组织行为学副教授，也是莎拉·格雷厄姆·凯南学者。 Subra Tangirala 是马里兰大学罗伯特·H·史密斯商学院管理学院长教授。 Alex Ning Li 是德克萨斯大学达拉斯分校纳文金达尔管理学院的助理教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Teamwork]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jing Jing Tsong/theispot.com Imagine running a factory that assembles electronic devices. Your operators work in highly interdependent teams on the assembly lines, and they’re dealing with a fundamental technological change that you recently implemented. Robotic arms and automated machines were put in place to streamline the assembly process, replacing several tasks previously performed by hand. [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Sherf_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">宗晶晶/theispot.com</p></figcaption></figure><p>想象一下经营一家组装电子设备的工厂。您的操作员在装配线上高度相互依赖的团队中工作，他们正在处理您最近实施的根本性技术变革。机械臂和自动化机器的安装到位，以简化装配过程，取代了以前由手工执行的多项任务。</p><p>现在，机械臂可以处理重复且精确的运动，例如将组件拧在一起和涂粘合剂。这一变化使操作员摆脱了繁琐的工作，让他们专注于装配过程中更复杂的方面，例如质量控制、故障排除和过程优化。然而，他们必须适应新的工作环境：他们需要单独学习如何操作和维护自动化系统，同时还要学习如何作为一个团队进行不同的协调。</p><p></p><p>这种对团队成员与个人角色以及彼此之间关系的根本性改变在各种工作场所中都会发生。无论是由采用新技术、新法规还是结构转型的组织决策引发的，都需要个人和团队层面的适应。</p><p>例如，会计团队的成员在努力应对披露法的变化时，可能需要单独掌握新的报告规则，并重新考虑团队内部的协作以建立新的内部控制系统。从职能结构过渡到部门结构的组织的员工除了学习如何在新的跨职能环境中与同事有效协调之外，可能还需要单独获取有关每个部门提供的产品和服务的知识。</p><p>克服这些双重学习和适应挑战是成功变革管理的关键，但正如我们在<a href="https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2022.1621"><cite>《组织科学》</cite>最近的论文</a>中指出的那样，领导者往往没有充分关注团队中的个人是否、何时或如何进行再培训，以及何时进行再培训。这样做时，他们的关注点往往是整个团队。我们的研究表明，优先考虑个人再培训可能会带来好处。我们对制造公司的团队和个人如何适应变革的研究表明，当个人学习首先发生时，团队更容易适应根本性变革。</p><p></p><h3>在团队之前重新培训个人</h3><p>成功的团队合作需要两个不同层面的技能：团队成员需要精通自己的任务，并且需要很好地合作。我们认为，在团队成员掌握个人技能之前，团队很难掌握并最大化集体协调。这是因为集体掌握通常只能建立在个人技能的基础上。为了最好地应对根本性的变化，个人技能的发展应该首先发生。</p><p>这些想法得到了我们对中国东部一家拥有 10,000 多名员工的大型电子制造公司的一个部门所发生的根本性变化的研究的支持。我们在几个月内跟踪了 116 个制作团队。这些团队刚刚开始适应一系列激进的技术进步，需要使用新颖的工具和生产流程。为了衡量变革前后的团队绩效，我们使用了公司自己的指标“产量”，即按照技术规格正确制造的产品的百分比。</p><p></p><p>正如我们预期的那样，适应变化的需要确实对产量产生了负面影响。变动前两周左右，平均收益率为99.15%；变化后约4周，平均收益率已降至93.82%。但下降的情况并没有在所有球队中平均分配。我们将团队之间的一些差异归因于团队面临的变革强度的差异：一些团队在个人和集体层面上都有更多需要重新学习的东西。</p><p>然而，考虑到变革的强度后，我们发现最初专注于个人技能再培训的团队比立即专注于改善集体协调的团队表现要好 12%。奖励系统发挥了关键作用：在初始阶段获得更多以个人为中心的奖励（与以团队为中心的奖励相比）的团队成员在从变革中恢复的早期表现出色。</p><p>两个月后，当我们在变革的后期再次探索收益率时，所有团队的平均收益率已回升至 96.95%。然而，与变革前的团队绩效相比，团队绩效存在很大差异。</p><p>此时，以个人再培训为基础、现在专注于集体协调的团队的表现比没有进行这种转变的团队高出 11%。这种焦点的改变是通过更加集体导向的奖励制度实现的。在变革的后期阶段强调团队奖励的团队更容易将注意力从个人重新技能转移到集体协调。</p><h3>分两个阶段管理变革</h3><p>我们的研究表明，管理根本性的组织变革需要两阶段、顺序的响应。</p><p>在发生根本性变革后的早期，领导者应鼓励个人任务重新技能化。这种再培训不仅意味着提供相关培训，还意味着在尝试改进整个团队之前，让成员有时间单独试验和掌握他们的任务。在我们的研究中，早期成功的团队给了成员更多的时间来尝试新的方法来完成自己的任务，并使标准化设备适应自己的需求。</p><p>奖励制度应该支持这一阶段的个人再培训。当奖励反映个人贡献时，团队成员就会专注于提高个人技能。这种奖励可以促进自我关注和对个人目标的追求。</p><p></p><p>在发生根本性变化之后的后期，一旦团队成员掌握了各自的任务，他们就可以开始尝试协调和任务流程，并确定集体流程中的冗余。在我们的研究中，一旦成员单独掌握了新任务，很明显他们中的一些人可以比以前更快地完成任务。这一结果意味着团队必须改变任务分配方式以最大限度地提高工作流程效率。在这个阶段，应该更加重视团队奖励。当奖励以团队为中心并且成员之间的薪酬差异最小化时，团队成员就会专注于学习集体技能。这些奖励促进对他人的关注、协作和对团队目标的追求。</p><p>奖励的顺序对于确保团队成员以正确的顺序专注于正确的优先事项至关重要，从最初关注个人重新技能转变为后来才练习集体协调。从一开始就只提供以团队为导向的奖励无法激励构成团队行动基础的个人再培训。</p><h3>时机很重要</h3><p>虽然我们的研究提供了一些经验证据来支持在团队技能之前培养个人技能的想法，以提高对商业环境变化的适应能力，但我们可以观察到这一原则如何同样适用于其他领域。</p><p> 20世纪90年代初，足球界引入了一项新规则，禁止守门员用手接住后卫踢回给他们的球。这代表了这项运动的方式发生了<a href="https://99percentinvisible.org/episode/unsure-footing/">根本性的变化</a>，因为它需要新的技能和新的协调方式。</p><p>起初，球队在新规则下表现不佳。防守队员习惯性地将球踢回给守门员。由于守门员无法用手触球，步法不熟练，导致球队出现失误。</p><p>许多足球教练最初关注守门员和后卫之间的交接，以改善这组球员之间的协调方式。这些方法并不是很成功。他们要求球员在守门员和后卫都发展出新的个人技能之前就注重协作，从而本末倒置。</p><p></p><p>相比之下，其他教练则专注于帮助守门员和后卫首先熟练掌握自己的带球和传球技巧，而不是让他们互相配合。直到后来，一旦球员们单独获得了这些技能，这些球队才将他们聚集在一起，以新的、创造性的方式协调他们的防守和进攻。这一策略更加成功，并导致了对整个游戏玩法的重新构想。</p><p></p><p>集体能力只有在强大的个人技能的基础上才能增长。领导者经常忘记这一点，并且在变革时期，在成员掌握各自的任务之前尝试团结团队更好地合作。管理变革的领导者应该记住，在加入团队制定如何最好地进行集体协作之前，为个人提供足够的空间和激励，让他们自己尝试和学习新技术和知识。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/there-actually-is-an-i-in-team/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>企业中的创业型人工智能：LG Nova 的 Shilpa Prasad</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Ransbotham and Shervin Khodabandeh. <p>Sam Ransbotham ( <a href="https://twitter.com/ransbotham">@ransbotham</a> ) 是波士顿学院卡罗尔管理学院信息系统系教授，也是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>》人工智能和商业战略大创意计划的客座编辑。 Shervin Khodabandeh 是 BCG 的高级合伙人兼董事总经理，也是北美 BCG GAMMA（BCG 人工智能业务）的联合领导者。您可以通过<a href="mailto:shervin@bcg.com">shervin@bcg.com</a>联系他。</p><p class="mt20"> <cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite>是<cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团合作推出的播客，由 Sam Ransbotham 和 Shervin Khodabandeh 主持。我们的工程师是 David Lishansky，协调制作人是 Allison Ryder 和 Sophie Rüdinger。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs]]></category><category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Innovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[New Product Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Business Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[A former startup employee herself, Shilpa Prasad knows the level of commitment and effort required to begin a new venture. That’s what led her to join LG Nova, electronics manufacturer LG’s innovation incubator, as an entrepreneur in residence. In her role, Shilpa identifies promising startups — particularly those working with AI — and coaches and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p>希尔帕·普拉萨德 (Shilpa Prasad) 本人曾是一家初创公司的员工，她知道创办一家新企业所需的承诺和努力程度。这促使她作为入驻企业家加入电子产品制造商 LG 的创新孵化器 LG Nova。 Shilpa 在她的角色中发现了有前途的初创公司——尤其是那些与人工智能相关的初创公司——并指导和培养企业家，同时密切关注有一天可能会进入 LG 生态系统的产品。</p><p>在本期<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能</cite>”播客中，Shilpa 解释了如何把握初创企业的脉搏帮助 LG 电子对创新和新商机保持开放态度。她还讨论了为什么人工智能是她与初创公司合作的最前沿，以及她认为使用增强现实和人工智能技术来改变技能培训提供方式的光明前景。 </p><aside class="callout-info"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MMAI-S8-E2-Shilpa-Prasad-LG-Nova-headshot-3000-1x-scaled.jpg" alt="希尔帕·普拉萨德"></p><h4>希尔帕·普拉萨德，LG Nova</h4><p> Shilpa Prasad 是创业生态系统中经验丰富的领导者，对创业和企业创业参与/创新充满热情。她将超过 15 年的企业创业战略和风险投资全球经验带入 LG Nova 担任常驻企业家，帮助公司识别市场趋势并建立合作伙伴关系。</p><p>普拉萨德在推动企业、政府和加速器之间的各种开放式创新项目的创新以及在全球创业生态系统中建立新的合作伙伴关系方面发挥了重要作用。作为一位经验丰富的创始人，她还投入时间为初创企业提供指导和建议。</p></aside><aside class="callout-info fl mobile-fn mt40"><h5> LinkedIn 上的人工智能领导者<br /></h5><p style="font-size:1.4rem;">如果您喜欢<cite>“我、我自己和人工智能”</cite>播客，请在 LinkedIn 上继续与我们对话。立即加入<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">领导者人工智能</a>小组。</p><p class="is-button mt20"> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/13977401/" class="marketing-click" id="AI_for_leaders_link[MMAI]">立即加入 »</a></p></aside><p>在<a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/me-myself-and-ai/id1533115958">Apple 播客</a>、 <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/7ysPBcYtOPVgI6W5an6lup">Spotify</a>或<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9tZW15c2VsZmFuZGFpLmxpYnN5bi5jb20vcnNz">Google 播客</a>上订阅<cite>“我、我自己和 AI”</cite> 。</p><h4>成绩单</h4><p><strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>常驻企业家如何在大型现有组织中启动基于人工智能的新业务？看看今天的节目就知道了。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我是 LG Nova 的 Shilpa Prasad，你们正在听<cite>我、我自己和 AI 的</cite>声音。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>欢迎来到<cite>《我、我自己和人工智能》</cite> ，这是一个关于商业人工智能的播客。每集我们都会向您介绍人工智能创新人士。我是 Sam Ransbotham，波士顿学院分析学教授。我还是<cite>《麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论》</cite>的人工智能和商业战略客座编辑。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>我是 Shervin Khodabandeh，BCG 的高级合伙人，也是我们人工智能业务的领导者之一。自 2017 年以来， <cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 一直在人工智能方面进行研究和出版，采访了数百名从业者，并对数千家公司进行了调查，了解如何构建、部署和扩展人工智能能力，并真正改变组织的运营方式。</p><p>大家好。今天，Sam 和我很高兴能与 LG Nova 驻场企业家 Shilpa Prasad 一起加入。嗨，希尔帕。欢迎来到节目。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>谢谢你，谢尔文。很高兴来到这里。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>请介绍一下 LG Nova 以及您在那里的角色。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我经常被问到这个问题。 LG Nova 是 LG 电子的创新中心，总部位于硅谷。我们的任务非常简单：我们的任务是为 LG 电子寻找新的商机，而这些商机并非其主要业务的核心。 LG电子是一家传统的消费电子制造商，希望进军解决方案驱动的业务。因此，[它]不断地识别他们可能感兴趣的新技术和领域，并希望以此为基础开展价值数十亿美元的业务。</p><p> LG Nova 就是这样。我在 LG Nova 的角色是常驻企业家，这意味着我身兼数职，其中之一是公司的普通顾问。我所说的顾问并不是传统的咨询，而是更多的背景，比如需要关注哪些趋势、哪些新技术领域可能会很有趣、[以及]我们如何能够结合多种技术，也许，为了一个商业机会？这是其中的一部分。</p><p>它的第二部分非常关注由外而内的创新。我们的根基是这样一个事实：我们不想做别人已经做过的事情，而初创公司就是他们创新速度的一个很好的例子。我们希望将这种创新带入我们所在的企业，并利用其中的一些能力来共同规划一条道路。</p><p>因此，与初创公司的合作是关键，这就是我作为企业家的一面发挥作用的地方——你必须能够理解企业家的心态、他们运作的速度、他们的动力、是什么让他们做事他们所做的事情——并以有效的方式将其传达给公司。当然，还有相反的角色，企业家在公司之外不一定了解大公司的运作方式，我认为如何弥合这一差距对于这个角色非常关键。这听起来很简单，但从这个意义上讲，有很多问题悬而未决，您必须能够同时兼顾所有这些问题，同时密切关注建立新业务的目标。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>您谈论的是一家大型、全球性、价值数十亿美元的公司，该公司以给定的速度运营，并且您还希望该集团以更快的速度（我认为是创业速度）运营。所以我可以想象为什么它要玩很多球。</p><p>我想问你，是对这些技术或创新机会/颠覆者的识别，还是对这些技术或创新机会/颠覆者的补充——孵化和建设？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。因此，既有构思部分，也有风险建设部分，而风险建设的一部分就是孵化。因此，您可能有六个月的时间来识别机会，朝着某些目标迈进，然后在必要时向高级利益相关者和投资者展示产品方面和业务方面的能力，然后将其推动到新业务。所以这绝对是我在那里所做的一个重要部分。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>也许这就是 Shervin 和我经常听到的说法，但是初创公司中有很多人工智能，而你还没有提到人工智能。那么人工智能如何与你的角色交叉呢？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>人工智能并不交叉。这是我正在做的事情的最前沿。如果你还记得一年半前，萨姆，关于虚拟宇宙的大肆宣传，技术来来去去。我的重点是确定可以使用其中一些技术来解决的现实世界问题。所以AI绝对是走在最前沿的。企业内部有很多与人工智能相关的工作，重点是为现有业务部门提供服务，但这不是我要做的事情。我的职责是将人工智能视为一种技术，并确定在这个巨大的世界中可能有兴趣解决的问题，并围绕它建立业务。</p><p>我无法详细说明我正在构建的内容，但我可以谈论这样一个事实：我个人在内部绘制了增强现实和人工智能的交叉点，这可能会改变技能培训的方式转移、技能提升、再技能以及围绕这些的内容将会发挥作用。</p><p>我相信你已经知道这一点——现在有了人工智能的混合，很多事情都可以变得如此直观，可以为受训者和审阅者生成一个反馈循环，并且基本上允许劳动力发展或技能培训特别是要以更快的速度前进。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>看来人工智能将更多地成为其中的关键成分，而不仅仅是添加剂，因此让人类参与其中将更加关键。我听到你所谈论的主题集中于此。请告诉我们一些有关正在发生的人工智能的信息。你说你不能说太多，但我还是想从你嘴里套出一些信息。因此，谈谈这个创新中心内发生的人工智能，或者将其与企业中发生的人工智能进行对比。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我相信你们俩都非常熟悉一家大型企业以及将任何产品推向市场所必须通过的渠道。我所说的“将任何东西推向市场”的意思也是指发布对企业内部影响更大的东西，对吗？因此，当你观察企业内部围绕人工智能进行的传统研究时，尤其是 LG 电子，到目前为止，我的理解是，冒险的兴趣是有限的，因为它扰乱了他们现有的许多工作，[而] 我正在规划的类似的东西是利用现有的一些技术，当我们向市场推出类似的东西时，现有的部分都不会受到影响 - 事实上，它们会受益。</p><p>以 LG 为例，全球有 85,000 多名工人在工厂环境中工作。今天每个人都明白，从一线工人的角度来看，工厂中的劳动力存在缺口。企业内部不断提出与生产力相关的要求，以确保满足整个……产能。这些都是企业内部人工智能研究尚未解决的现实问题。</p><p>您询问了上市时间。我的任务是在六个月内确定一家企业是否可以上市。我认为在企业方面，即使不是更长，也需要几年，对吗？两到五年之间的任何时间。</p><p>这一直是人们谈论的话题：“企业发展缓慢；启动速度很快。”所以我本质上是在公司内部建立一家初创公司。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>所以，我所听到的是，摆脱了许多传统规模的束缚——随之而来的是惯性——并且像新企业一样，速度要快得多。当然，其中一些创新可以帮助一些现有的企业人工智能，对吗？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。绝对地。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>太棒了。您谈到了技能提升、再培训，以及可能重新想象人类在与人工智能的整个组合中的角色——在您谈到的组合中。请告诉我们有关生成式人工智能的信息以及您认为它在其中发挥的作用。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为可能性是巨大的，就像人工智能领域的任何其他机会一样。例如，增强现实技术与人工智能交叉的一个方面意味着我们不仅关注人工智能方面的语音和文本，而且还关注正在捕获和处理的计算机视觉相关数据流，以便进行技能转移尽可能有效地发生。</p><p>因此，考虑一下护士培训环境。我们不是在真正的病人身上练习，而是在假人身上练习。如果您必须教见习护士如何将患者放在床上以执行特定的程序，那么从首席培训护士那里捕获数据流以了解如何做到这一点具有很大的价值，并且，当你真正练习的时候，得到实时反馈，对吗？</p><p>所以我们在这里研究多个数据流。因此，不仅仅是 NLP [自然语言处理]，我们还会研究基于计算机视觉的技术，并引入人工智能来几乎增强该过程以及双方的受训者和培训经验，对吗？这就是我们如何以不同方式做事的一个例子。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>通常情况下，我对我们谈论的人工智能的应用感到非常兴奋，但我在这里受到了一点威胁。我的意思是我是这里的一名教育家，我听到你谈论各种不同的重新技能和再培训方式。我要去哪？您之前提到过护士的一个模型，经验丰富的护士会教经验不足的护士。也许其中很多都被替换了。在这种新模式中，经验丰富的护士现在扮演什么角色？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。好吧，实际上，山姆，我认为你的恐惧可能在这里是错误的，让我解释一下。我们并不是想更换教练。我们正在做的实际上是让培训师有更多机会去做他们应该做的事情。因此，在护士培训的例子中，护士长必须实际上站在实习护士旁边，可能在一天中多次，并教他们如何完成特定的任务。现在想象一个场景，在首席培训师真正参与进来并了解发生了什么之前，我们已经消除了至少两个级别的反馈、审查和评估。</p><p>所以我认为认证还是非常非常重要的，对吧？无论是制造业，还是医疗保健——我们正在谈论的两个例子——认证仍然很重要，而该认证来自培训师，他是专家。所以我们不会删除专家。它实际上使专家能够有效地进行培训，而不必监视正在工作的实习护士的 100 个屏幕。所以你希望看到差异。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·霍达班德：</strong>是的。萨姆是一位终身教授，所以我认为他不会去任何地方。但是，山姆，这有点像正教授，即你自己，不会陷入研究生可以处理的事情中，而你只做困难的事情和那些真正考验你大脑的事情。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这对我来说听起来很光荣。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为这是一名助理，对吧？你会有一个人工智能助手，它实际上可以完成很多繁重的工作，否则你必须坐下来做。所以我认为它是有价值的。至少我们看到了我们能够在早期的对话中产生的一些有价值的推论。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>太棒了。 Shilpa，请告诉我们一些您的背景，以及您如何最终担任这个角色。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我的职业生涯是一条曲折线，Shervin；这与我今天所做的事情并不是一条直线。多年来，我认为从头开始创造一些东西总是能找到很多价值和乐趣。从无到有、创造出新东西所需的能量、动力和严谨性一直是我所做的一切的核心。</p><p>因此，在我职业生涯的早期，我有机会与某人合作创办一家平面设计工作室。在那里，我了解了实际创建企业所需的机制。它教会了我很多其中的内容。</p><p>从那时起，我一直让自己担任实际上具有创业性质或为创业生态系统服务的角色。我想提一下我第一次来硅谷时曾在这里工作过的一家名为 YouNoodle Inc. 的公司。在那里，我了解到选择合适的初创公司或创新公司进行合作以推动创新向前发展的力量，无论是在企业、政府、大学甚至大型加速器项目的背景下。</p><p>这让我在新冠疫情期间再次踏上自己的创业之旅。真的很难。我创办了一家名为 LongPlay 的初创公司，并组建了一个大约 10 人的团队。它的重点是改变企业创新的方式。我认为有一件事是，当你在公司之外时，你根本没有办法理解正在发生的所有不同的活动部分。因此，我们无法证明产品与市场的契合度，而这正是 Nova 发挥作用的地方。我再次有机会尝试在一个与我习惯的有点不同的行业和环境中进行产品市场适应，但我认为具体细节是相同的。这只是我的简单背景介绍。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这非常令人兴奋——非常跨学科。这让我想到了下一个问题：人工智能没有一刀切，当然它是一个由工程师、软件工程师、提示工程师、人工智能工程师和数据科学家等组成的完整生态系统。但是我注意到过去的技能逐渐演变，我想说，10年、12年、15年左右，从仅限于核心技术到更加多学科，并且“多学科”可以是多种形式的区域。它可以是社会科学，也可以是人机交互，也可以是哲学或其他领域。但您是否也有同样的看法？您对人工智能领域未来人才有何看法？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>这是一个有趣的问题。我不得不说我没有看到同样的事情。</p><p><strong>谢尔文·科达班德：</strong>好的。</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我看到的不是宽度，而是深度。我认为，在跨学科能力方面，劳动力仍然存在巨大差距。就您而言，有很多深入的技术工作正在发生，特别是围绕人工智能。</p><p>我认为，在接下来的几年里，许多像我这样负责这项技术如何发展的人将不得不随身携带。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>这也涉及到测量。我的意思是——谢尔文，我知道这<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/big-ideas/artificial-intelligence-business-strategy/">对你来说是一个热门话题</a>——但是当你谈论影响力时，你必须弄清楚如何衡量它。必须采取某种措施来衡量“这有效吗？这不行吗？”这些看起来像是一些难题，特别是考虑到技术的新颖性和你所谈论的时间表的新鲜度。似乎很难弄清楚这对你的角色是否有效。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的。我的意思是，我可以给出一点个人看法。我的构建项目风格总是提到尽可能多地与有问题的客户一起进行测试。</p><p>这就是产品焦点对我来说非常重要和中心的地方，这就是为什么风险投资令人兴奋。当我们谈论衡量时，肯定有不同的方法可以衡量我们正在创造的东西或我们试图创造的东西的影响。这里有一个市场验证方面，对吗？肯定有一个投资者验证方面，这意味着我们的投资者......这不仅仅是关于我的项目，对吧？这不仅仅是关于我正在创建或构建的项目。实际上更多的是钱的去向。当然，其中有一点是炒作，但也有一点是抓住了下一件可能改变人工智能在日常环境或环境中使用方式的机会。 。</p><p>我认为这里的第三部分也是关于最终为用户提供我们正在创建的任何解决方案和我们正在构建的任何解决方案的授权，以便获得商业机会......最终[它]必须为人类增加价值 - 也就是说，你和我，实际上将使用这项技术来改善我们的生活。今天，我们正在以与我们被教导的或我们习惯的或我们已经学会的方式完全相同的方式做工作，我们将不得不改变它或适应它并转向一种新的方式做事。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>人工智能是否能让您获得更好的数据和信息？人工智能是否能让你了解 20 年前可能需要更长时间才能了解的事情？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>当然，但我认为“人工智能能够帮助我吗？我认为，只有<em>它</em>才能做到这一点，这可能对人工智能有很大的影响，而与过去 10、15 年在特定行业所做的事情不太相关。我认为人工智能也有它的另一面，那就是，有时它把太多的东西摆在你面前，然后你必须真正浏览顶层才能真正弄清楚这些数据可以在哪里使用以及如何使用这些数据被应用。所以人工智能也有优点和缺点。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你提到了缺点。您从与您合作的这些初创公司中看到了哪些缺点？这里的人们在挣扎什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>我认为尤其是初创公司仍在寻找可以应用他们所开发的内容的方法。人工智能的有效应用方式仍有待确定。因此，初创公司正在创建所有这些与项目相关的 LLM（大型语言模型），但他们不知道它将<em>如何</em>实际翻译。</p><p>所以我想说，初创公司要想理解它，还有一段路要走。例如，就我今天所担任的角色而言，我还使初创公司能够了解他们如何使用他们创建的技术并将其转化为有意义的问题，但是……这就是为什么我说之前咨询。它还为初创公司提供咨询：为他们提供一些真实的场景，您可以应用我们共同构建的东西，然后看看它如何转化为价值。所以我认为初创公司肯定仍在学习，萨姆。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>所以这些事情实际上可能与谢尔文关于知识广度和多学科的评论有关，因为你没有具体提到他们正在与技术作斗争。我在那里听到了很多并不是特别以技术为导向的事情。</p><p>让我们在这里过渡一下。我们在本集结束时做的一件事是问您五个问题。我们要尽快询问他们。我们只想了解您对他们的第一反应。您认为目前人工智能最大的机会是什么？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>医疗保健。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>好的。人们对人工智能最大的误解是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>它将取代它们。它将取代我们作为人类。我想这不会发生。我们离这个还有很长的路要走。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>很远。好的。你想要的第一个职业是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>成为一名企业家。我认为它一直存在于我的 DNA 中。</p><p><strong>萨姆·兰斯博瑟姆：</strong>很好。你小时候有过柠檬水摊吗？</p><p>什么时候人工智能太多了？我们要在哪里将方钉插入圆孔？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong> Sam，我想我没有给你一个具体的答案。所以，如果你要换一个问题……</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>这样问：会不会太多？</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>你能在产品中投入太多人工智能吗？</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>是的，绝对如此。我认为我想到的一个领域是协作机器人——协作机器人。它可能有效，也可能无效，而且它很大程度上是由人工智能驱动的。因此，自动化是关键，但我认为其中有多少相关性对我个人来说是值得怀疑的。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>如果你在幻想的话，你希望人工智能现在能做但目前还不能做的一件事是什么？</p><p> <strong>Shilpa Prasad：</strong>让我听起来尽可能好。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong> Shilpa，非常感谢你。这很有启发性，也很精彩。感谢您参加节目。</p><p> <strong>Sam Ransbotham：</strong>感谢您加入我们。</p><p><strong>希尔帕·普拉萨德：</strong>谢谢。</p><p> <strong>Shervin Khodabandeh：</strong>感谢您今天的收听。在我们的下一集中，我们将听到哈佛商学院教授 Ayelet Israel 如何建议通过生成人工智能来增强企业市场研究。请加入我们。</p><p><strong>艾莉森·莱德：</strong>感谢您聆听<cite>我、我自己和人工智能的演讲</cite>。和您一样，我们相信关于人工智能实施的对话不会从这个播客开始和结束。这就是为什么我们在 LinkedIn 上专门为像您这样的听众创建了一个群组。它被称为 AI for Leaders，如果您加入我们，您可以与节目创作者和主持人聊天，提出您自己的问题，分享您的见解，并获得来自<cite>MIT SMR</cite>和 BCG 的有关 AI 实施的宝贵资源。您可以通过访问<a href="https://mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders">mitsmr.com/AIforLeaders</a>来访问它。我们会将该链接放在演出笔记中，希望在那里见到您。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/audio/entrepreneurial-ai-in-the-enterprise-lg-novas-shilpa-prasad/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>摩擦可以改善客户体验吗？</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco Bertini, Diego Aparicio, and Aylin Aydinli. <p>Marco Bertini 是巴塞罗那 Esade 和 Ramon Llull 大学的营销学教授，也是 Globalpraxis 的高级顾问。迭戈·阿帕里西奥 (Diego Aparicio) 是巴塞罗那 IESE 商学院营销学助理教授。艾林·艾丁利 (Aylin Aydinli) 是阿姆斯特丹自由大学市场营销学副教授。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Customer Engagement]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Experience]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customer Journey]]></category><category><![CDATA[E-commerce]]></category><category><![CDATA[Pricing]]></category><category><![CDATA[Customers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><description><![CDATA[Otto Dettmer/Ikon Images Companies are on a mission to design purchase journeys that are as free of frustration and inconvenience as possible. “Friction kills the customer experience!” has become the conventional wisdom. This is thought to be particularly true when serving online shoppers, who are known to be less patient and have shorter attention spans; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2024WINTER-Bertini_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">奥托·德特默/Ikon Images</p></figcaption></figure><p>公司的使命是设计尽可能没有挫折和不便的购买旅程。 “摩擦会破坏客户体验！”已成为常识。人们认为，在为在线购物者提供服务时尤其如此，众所周知，在线购物者缺乏耐心且注意力集中时间较短。毕竟，只需点击几下鼠标即可到达竞争对手的网站。</p><p>我们认识的大多数企业领导者在显示价格和收款时都会优先考虑消除“关键时刻”的摩擦，因为除了想让热切的客户生活更轻松之外，他们还担心让客户有理由停下来重新考虑他们的决定。但正如我们将要证明的那样，正是在资金紧张的情况下，让客户有时间考虑他们的购买决定，才能为公司带来长期利益和成本节约。</p><p></p><h3>摩擦与善变的在线购物者</h3><p>很容易理解为什么让购物尽可能无缝对电子商务公司来说如此紧迫，因为过去 12 个月的全球平均购物车放弃率总体高达 71.7%（使用台式机或笔记本电脑的人为 60.7%）。使用平板电脑的比例为 65.1%，使用手机的比例为 77.4%。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a>最后一个数字可能是最令人不安的，因为美国的移动购物在三年内增长了 2,000 亿美元以上，到 2022 年将达到 4,310 亿美元。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>根据 Baymard Institute 的数据，大型电子商务网站平均可以提高转化率通过简化结账流程，成本降低了 35%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p>毫不奇怪，亚马逊和阿里巴巴等电子商务巨头正在大力投资，通过使价格和支付几乎不可见来快速引导消费者度过关键时刻。亚马逊早在 1999 年就率先推出了一键式购物。如今，人们的注意力集中在其 Just Walk Out 技术上，该技术融合了计算机视觉、重量传感器和深度学习，为实体店带来了在线购物的一些便利：顾客可以利用信用进入零售店时使用卡打开虚拟购物车，从货架上选择商品，然后离开，无需在收银台停留。在阿里巴巴，数字支付和自助结账台已成为其 300 家盒马超市的常态。人们甚至可以利用其支付宝子公司的面部识别技术来“刷脸支付”。</p><p>资源较少的公司正在对其采购流程进行改变，这些改变更加渐进但同样重要。例如，考虑一下最近流行的“立即购买，稍后付款”分期付款融资或基于订阅的服务的自动续订条款，这些条款允许公司避免客户重新考虑是否仍然需要该服务的年度清算。在线企业已经抓住了这些和其他机会，通过让客户不去思考花钱的问题，从而减轻花钱的痛苦。</p><p>然而，将摩擦视为具有严格的负面影响（例如惹恼客户或抑制销售）的想法过于简单化。诚然，购买过程中阻力太大很容易抑制购买欲望，但阻力太小会降低决策效率，导致错失与客户更好联系的机会。那么，我们建议企业领导者问问自己，他们是否真的希望客户自动购买。</p><p>在本文中，我们解释了购买过程中的一些摩擦如何帮助公司吸引客户，并就如何利用这些影响建立更牢固的客户关系提供指导。</p><h3>一分耕耘一分收获</h3><p>购买过程中的一些摩擦可以保护消费者免受欺诈、隐私侵犯或他们自己的意外行为。例如，要求两步验证和要求客户确认他们想要完成购买是两个常识性的不便，但最终确保客户免受威胁和错误。</p><p>但围绕购买决策的摩擦过多或过少都会产生负面影响。购买过程中的步骤过多可能会分散购物者的注意力，使他们没有足够的认知能力来仔细考虑自己的决定。这会提高购物车放弃率，并消除客户通过评论、推荐、推荐或其他互动与公司互动的机会。摩擦太少，人们就不会充分考虑自己的决定，从而屈服于人类节省脑力劳动的倾向。这种没有摩擦的情况令人麻木，购物者与购买的联系越少，他们就会变得越矛盾。从长远来看，缺乏承诺反过来会导致产品退货、削弱品牌并降低满意度。</p><p>然而，具有足够挑战性的购买过程却很有吸引力。由于交易既不紧张也不简单，因此人们有动力在任务中投入脑力。换句话说，适量的摩擦可以促使客户完善和巩固他们的偏好，并可以为公司带来三个好处。</p><p></p><p> <strong>1.摩擦力帮助卖家选择合适的客户。</strong>那些将客户群的长期盈利能力置于销售的直接收益之上的公司必须以全面且同样长远的视角来发展与目标受众的关系。这涉及对收购、保留和增长的投资。考虑到这一点，问题是，增加考虑费用的心理痛苦的障碍是否会不成比例地阻止那些获取成本更高、未来再次购买的可能性较小或不太可能增加支出的潜在客户随着时间的推移对品牌的关注或推荐品牌。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>在奢侈品市场以及公司希望潜在客户表现出承诺的任何情况下，通过摩擦来淘汰错误的客户或选择正确的客户是一种常见的技术。例如，法拉利以难以购买特别版汽车而闻名。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a>同样，奢侈时尚品牌并不介意排队（无论是虚拟的还是真实的），也不介意通过暂时扣压价格、延长结账流程或使用其他方法来使购买流程复杂化。这些策略背后的简单逻辑是，只有对公司产品最感​​兴趣或对品牌投入最多的客户才会发现在购物过程中可以接受这些不便和复杂的情况。</p><p></p><p> <strong>2. 当摩擦能够带来更好的决策时，客户满意度就会提高。</strong>利用摩擦让消费者有时间停下来考虑购买的影响，可以防止买家后悔，并鼓励购物者在可用的替代方案中选择最合适的选项。</p><p>充分明确潜在买家将支付的费用和他们将收到的东西之间的权衡，有助于防止一时冲动做出盲目的购买决定。例如，社交媒体可能会宣传“现在购买，稍后付款”融资作为一种精明的预算购买方式，但此类服务的简便性和便利性（现在许多电子商务网站的结账流程中都提供）可以鼓励家庭超支，导致财务紧张和债务积累。一项调查发现，申请此类贷款的美国人中有 42% 至少有过一次逾期付款。 <a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">6</a>此外，研究表明，在自然消费时刻之前或之后很久进行支付可以降低人们对成本的关注。 “先买后付”的支持者声称，这“将购买的乐趣体验与繁琐的支付过程分开”，而事实上，这种“交易脱钩”已被证明可以降低消费者使用所购买商品的可能性。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p>从公共政策的角度来看，避免错误决策的好处相对明显：大多数人都会同意，购买商品的过度支出和长期利用不足并不是社会所期望的品质。但通过购买过程中的摩擦鼓励客户进行更周到的参与也可以为企业带来回报。</p><p>一个直接的好处是退货率下降。在许多行业，在线退货对财务业绩造成了相当大的拖累——每美元退货商品的价格加起来高达 15 至 30 美分。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>根据 Appriss Retail 和美国零售联合会的一项研究，2021 年，美国数字零售商退回了价值近 2,200 亿美元的商品，约占在线销售额的 21%。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a>当然，这种拖累不仅是财务方面的，也是环境方面的。退回的产品可能由于磨损或其他问题而无法转售，最终被送往垃圾填埋场或销毁。据一份报告称，仅在美国，在线退货每年就会产生 50 亿磅垃圾填埋废物和 1500 万吨碳排放。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>增加摩擦还可以让客户有时间考虑购买并加大投入。香奈儿 (Chanel)、路易威登 (Louis Vuitton) 和巴黎世家 (Balenciaga) 等品牌以各种方式延迟价格沟通——例如，通过向销售人员引入个性化体验——不仅是为了选择更好的客户，如上所述，而且是将产品置于中心舞台，帮助客户内化其品质和意义。市场营销和神经科学交叉点的研究报告显示，在产品信息之后揭示价格的重点是对吸引力和需求的评估（人们问自己，“我喜欢这个吗？”），而相反的做法则侧重于对货币价值的评估（人们问自己，“这值得么？”）。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a>在 Gartner 的一项研究中，B2B 和 B2C 客户一致认为，如果他们“意识到自己的需求或自己的目标有新的变化”，他们购买更多产品的可能性就会增加 1.73 倍。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a></p><p>利用摩擦来激发思考，从而做出购买决定，可以培养对产品的所有权感。这可以增强公司与客户之间的联系，并增加客户在这种关系中投入额外资源的意愿。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>当顾客在购买决定时投入更多的考虑时，他们往往会对最终选择的产品产生更强烈的情感依恋。有证据表明，在情感层面与客户建立联系是实现客户价值最大化的有效途径。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p>最后，研究还表明，当人们通过努力获得产品时，他们往往会更加看重产品——这恰如其分地命名为“宜家效应”，指的是零售商将家具组装外包给顾客的政策。 <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a>努力的体验会影响人们对产品或服务的价值和质量的看法，而在线购买过程中付出的努力可能会引发这种效应。</p><p></p><p>总体而言，我们发现摩擦能够成功地触发参与度，而且我们知道参与度较高的客户通常对他们与品牌和零售商的互动和体验更加满意。积极参与的客户成为倡导者，提高公司的知名度和可信度。他们可能会产生积极的口碑，从而赢得新客户并提高品牌声誉。他们还可能拥有更好的客户服务体验，感受到公司的重视，并提供有意义的反馈和建议。此类反馈对于了解不断变化的客户需求以及随着时间的推移对产品或服务进行正确的改进非常有价值。</p><p> <strong>3.摩擦为企业与客户的沟通创造了空间。</strong>当人们面临价格和支付时，保留一些摩擦，尤其是当这种摩擦是意外的时候，会引起人们的关注。对于公司来说，这是一个宣传他们的立场和产品优点的机会。</p><p>利用摩擦力进行晋升的方法有多种。首先，公司可以让客户参与支付过程，以唤起积极的情绪。例如，一种常见的做法是让客户可以选择将交易金额四舍五入到下一个最高的美元，并将差额捐赠给慈善机构。另一种可能性是推出按需付费活动，让客户选择他们愿意为产品支付的价格。虽然这些举措并不能加快付款速度（考虑一个人愿意为某样东西支付多少钱是令人惊讶的努力），但它们可以带来更大的情感联系。</p><p>公司还可以故意以非常规的方式表达价格，以迫使客户更深入地思考潜在的信息。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>例如，宜家的一则广告使用罐装苏打水来有趣地量化其产品的价格。当然，零售商不会接受苏打水作为家具付款。尽管需要花点时间来理解“汇率”，但还是向顾客传达了这样的信息：家具与苏打水等小额商品一样便宜。</p><p>另一个例子是时代啤酒 (Stella Artois) 屡获殊荣的“令人放心的昂贵”营销活动。该品牌试图通过将价格与质量之间的依赖关系引入其价格沟通中来表明其啤酒的高品质。 Stella 开玩笑地提供一张提高产品价格的优惠券，颠覆了消费者的期望（“带上这张优惠券，购买下一款 Stella Artois 时需额外支付 1.25 美元”）。通过提出看似令人困惑且不合逻辑的“交易”，它促使客户得出结论：该产品远远优于竞争对手的产品（并且物有所值）。</p><p>支付过程中的摩擦也可以用来传达品牌的价值观。例如，2014年，救援组织Misereor通过在机场等地点部署交互式屏幕，要求路人通过在屏幕上刷信用卡来捐赠2欧元，从而提高了捐款率。刷卡激活了一个引人入胜的互动序列，例如描绘信用卡切一片面包来喂饥饿的人或释放被监禁的孩子。</p><p>最后，举一个极端摩擦的大胆例子，户外零售商 REI 在美国一年中最大的购物日“黑色星期五”关闭了实体店并停止处理在线支付。其目标是反对消费主义并鼓励潜在消费者。购物者应该花时间在户外——这一信息强调了该公司致力于无障碍探索的决心。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17 号</a></p><h3>摩擦最佳点</h3><p>更好的客户选择、消费者决策和促销是放弃零摩擦这一简单化目标的三个充分理由。鉴于鼓励客户自动购买的缺点，企业领导者应设法确定公司购买流程的适当摩擦程度。根据我们的经验，至少有五个因素需要考虑。我们将审查它们并引入一个记分卡，将它们聚集在一起并帮助指导决策。 （请参阅“对于在线客户体验而言，适当的摩擦力是多少？”）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>对于您的在线客户体验来说，适当的摩擦力是多少？</h4><p class="caption">使用此记分卡可帮助您确定最佳摩擦力，以帮助您<br />培养持久的客户关系。</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p>对于每家公司来说，第一步都是对摩擦采用更准确的定义。目前，所有摩擦都被负面看待，这降低了组织需要明确其实际含义的意识。大多数人认为，摩擦是通过节省时间来实现的。但并非所有的时间都是平等的。事实上，公司应该将负面摩擦视为阻碍或分散客户购买决策的任何事物，而将正面摩擦视为优化深思熟虑的任何事物。</p><p>第二步是了解哪些环境可以从积极的摩擦中受益——因为这种需求并不普遍。特定购买决策的利害关系是什么？通常需要高还是低的客户参与？两者经常同时出现，因此高风险的决策也需要高度的参与，但情况并非一定如此。例如，经济上有保障的消费者可能不会仅仅因为商品价格昂贵而更多地参与购买决策。正是当这种关系破裂时，你需要介入并主动管理摩擦。高风险决策可能是由于相关产品或服务的重要性、财务支出的规模或购买的个人或社会后果而做出的。本着这种精神，在体育场馆中使用亚马逊的“Just Walk Out”等技术可能对那些不再因小贩摊前排太长的队伍而劝阻购买不健康零食的人来说可能并不好。</p><p>第三，考虑您的商业目标。如果您关心强调相对于竞争对手的价格节省的成本，那么，是的 - 通过预先发布几乎好得令人难以置信的价格来减少摩擦是值得的。然而，如果你在创新、质量或客户服务的基础上进行竞争，那么最好通过延迟报价来保留一点摩擦，因为这会让客户思考并具体化他们的偏好。一些摩擦可以让企业将话题从“值得吗？”转移过来。到“我喜欢吗？”如果目标是强化品牌，那么增加摩擦是正确的方法。</p><p>第四，考虑客户群的构成以及客户关系的相对紧密程度。不同的客户群体可能需要或多或少的摩擦，具体取决于他们对产品或服务的理解或支付能力的期望。同样，关系阶段也很重要。与回头客相比，您可能希望在与新客户的交易中增加更多的摩擦，特别是那些可能不太熟悉您的产品或产品类别的客户。您可能希望让潜在客户更难购买，为回头客增加一些摩擦，并为完全了解产品或服务的忠实客户提供无摩擦的体验。公司应该最大限度地提高与客户的持久关系——因为这是增加客户价值的唯一途径。</p><p>第五，考虑您选择的市场途径。所有零售环境都可能从一些摩擦中受益，但它们的应用会有所不同。在实体店中，添加痛点来激励销售人员与客户之间的互动可能是正确的摩擦类型。然而，在在线商店中，增加促进深思熟虑的步骤可以减少退货并提高随后对公司的满意度。在社交媒体上，公司可以寻求平衡吸引客户互动的内容，而不仅仅是点击率，从而帮助阻止用户盲目或冲动地购物。</p><p></p><p>事实上，对于在实体店和网上销售相同产品的企业来说，在线或移动渠道可能需要更多（积极的）摩擦，因为这些渠道的产品回报往往是最大的。一些时尚品牌最近推出的一项有趣的技术是对在线退货收取费用。 Anthropologie、H&amp;M 和 Zara 等公司对网上退货收取费用（但店内退货不收取费用）。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a>是的，收取退货费用可能会激怒一些顾客。但同样，这一点可能是留住最相关的客户并加强与那些坚持购买的客户的关系的关键。</p><p></p><p> “我们怎样才能让我们的价格不那么引人注目并且更容易支付呢？”这是用户体验团队和专家最常问的问题之一。但企业领导者应该拥抱客户的关键时刻，而不是努力消除它。他们不应该相信“摩擦是最终转化杀手”这一流行观点。</p><p>毫无疑问，如果使用不当，摩擦会破坏客户体验。但无摩擦的世界也同样危险。这是我们大多数人多年前从高中物理老师那里学到的一课：太多的摩擦会阻碍实现目标的进展，但太少的摩擦会使一切陷入混乱。</p><p>事实上，许多企业领导者已经告诉我们，他们希望客户在购买决策上花费更多富有成效的时间。这听起来像是摩擦力的完美工作。如果思考引导购物者做出更安全、更好的选择，反过来，这些选择通过降低产品退货、更可持续的消费者行为、更高的客户满意度和更高的忠诚度来影响公司，那么让我们都接受并拥抱一些麻烦和障碍——尽管令人惊讶——以客户为中心的工具。</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/can-friction-improve-your-customers-experiences/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>您的组织在负责任的人工智能方面投资足够吗？我们的数据表明“可能不会”</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/#respond</comments><pubDate> Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[David Kiron and Steven Mills. ]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category><category><![CDATA[Business Priorities]]></category><category><![CDATA[Risk Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Technology Investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[AI & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Data, AI, & Machine Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Managing Technology]]></category><category><![CDATA[Responsible AI]]></category><description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group have assembled an international panel of AI experts to help us understand how responsible artificial intelligence (RAI) is being implemented across organizations worldwide. For our final question in this year’s research cycle, we asked our academic and practitioner panelists to [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><cite>麻省理工学院斯隆管理评论</cite>和波士顿咨询集团连续第二年组建了一个国际人工智能专家小组，帮助我们了解全球组织如何实施负责任的人工智能 (RAI)。对于今年研究周期的最后一个问题，我们要求学术界和从业者小组成员对这一挑衅做出回应：<em>随着商业界越来越意识到人工智能的风险，企业正在对 RAI 进行足够的投资。</em></p><p>尽管他们的理由各不相同，但大多数小组成员都承认 RAI 投资未能满足需要：13 人中有 11 人不愿意同意组织对负责任的人工智能的投资是“足够的”。小组成员在很大程度上肯定了我们<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/building-robust-rai-programs-as-third-party-ai-tools-proliferate/">2023 年 RAI 全球调查</a>的结果，其中不到一半的受访者表示他们相信他们的公司准备对 RAI 进行足够的投资。对于优先考虑人工智能并必须管理人工智能相关风险的公司来说，这是一个紧迫的领导挑战。</p><p> H&amp;M 集团负责任的人工智能和数据主管 Linda Leopold 表示，扩大 RAI 投资的需要标志着一个重大转变，因为“人工智能相关的风险不容忽视”。虽然对 RAI 进行足够的投资曾经是一个重要但不是特别紧迫的问题，但 Leopold 表示，生成式人工智能的最新进展和第三方工具的激增已经表明此类投资的紧迫性。</p><p>由于衡量方面的挑战，对 RAI 进行充分投资变得复杂。没有提供指导的行业标准，因此您如何知道您的投资何时或是否足够？更重要的是，理性的高管对于什么是充分投资可能有不同的看法。显而易见的是，认知问题不应成为行动的障碍，尤其是当人工智能风险构成真正的业务威胁时。</p><div class="callout-chart"><div class="callout-chart__bg"><div class="callout-chart__container"><div class="callout-chart__info"><h3>小组成员回应</p></h3><h2>目前尚不清楚组织是否对 RAI 进行了适当的投资。</p></h2><p>大多数小组成员不愿意同意组织正在对 RAI 进行“足够”的投资。</p><p><a href="#sf-inter-app" class="callout-chart__info__anchor link-offset">跳转至下面小组成员的详细回复。</a> </div><div class="callout-chart__bars"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-Chart.jpg" alt="图：0 强烈同意； 15% 同意，46% 既不同意也不不同意； 39% 不同意； 0% 强烈不同意"></div></p></div><p class="callout-chart__source">资料来源：由 13 名人工智能战略专家组成的 Responsible AI 小组。 </p></p></div><p><path id="Path" d="M0,0,14.067,15.065,28.941,0" transform="translate(1.096 1.054)" fill="none" stroke="#fff" stroke-miterlimit="10" stroke-width="3" /> <a href="" class="callout-chart-add__button"><span class="callout-chart-add__button-text"><strong>显示</strong>全球调查结果</span></a></p><div class="callout-chart-add"><div class="callout-chart-add__container"><div class="callout-chart-add__info"><h4></h4><h3> 2023 年全球高管调查的回复<br /></h3><p>“您认为您的组织在多大程度上准备好投资（减少收入、增加成本）以遵守负责任的人工智能计划？” </p></p></div><div class="callout-chart-add__chart"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/RAI2023_Article4-survey.jpg" alt="条形图：中等或较大程度：48%；在某种程度上：29%；较小程度：8%；完全没有：3%；不知道：12%" class="mt0"></p><p class="callout-chart-add__source">资料来源：对代表年收入至少 1 亿美元的组织的 1,240 名受访者进行的调查数据。这些受访者代表了 87 个国家/地区 59 个行业的公司。在中国进行的调查是本地化的。</p></p></div></p></div></p></div></div><h3>公司正在投资 RAI，但还不够</h3><p>小组成员提出了公司没有对负责任的人工智能进行足够投资的几个原因。几位小组成员表示，利润动机是一个因素。联合国大学校长兼联合国副秘书长 Tshilidzi Marwala 认为，“只有 20% 意识到人工智能风险的公司正在投资 RAI 项目。其余的人更关心如何利用人工智能来实现利润最大化。”新加坡国立大学大卫·马歇尔教授兼副教务长西蒙·切斯特曼 (Simon Chesterman) 补充道：“围绕生成式人工智能的淘金热导致科技公司的安全团队规模缩小，新产品的上市路径也缩短了。 ......在许多组织中，即使不是全部，对错过的恐惧正在战胜风险管理。”</p><p>投资不足的另一个原因是，在整个企业中更多地使用人工智能会扩大 RAI 的范围并增加所需的投资。正如 Armilla AI 的人工智能政策主管 Philip Dawson 所观察到的那样，“对人工智能功能的投资继续大大超过对人工智能安全和实施人工智能风险管理的工具的投资。企业正在一场艰苦的战斗中追赶，而且只会变得更加艰难。”利奥波德补充说，生成式人工智能和越来越多的可能应用“显着增加了负责任的人工智能项目必须覆盖的受众规模”。</p><p></p><p>第三个原因是，对人工智能风险的认识不断增强并不总是转化为对这些风险的准确评估。非洲负责任人工智能观察站的政策专家 Oarabile Mudongo 表示，一些公司可能没有对其 RAI 项目进行足够的投资，因为它们“低估了人工智能风险的程度”。</p><h3>您如何知道自己的投资是否足够？</h3><p>其他小组成员指出，尽管对RAI进行足够的投资很重要，但很难衡量投资是否足够大或有效。企业应如何计算 RAI 投资回报？什么才算是“足够”的回报？什么才算投资？ Aboitiz Data Innovation 首席执行官兼菲律宾联合银行首席数据和人工智能官 David R. Hardoon 问道：“如果 (1) 所有公司都不受相同水平的标准，（2）我们尚未就什么是“足够”或“可接受”达成一致，或者（3）我们没有验证第三方的机制？”</p><p> Dataiku 的 AI 负责人 Triveni Gandhi 对此表示同意：“在那些花时间投资 RAI 项目的公司中，这些项目的实际设计和实施方式存在很大差异。对于如何实施或实施 RAI 价值观缺乏一致或明确的期望，使得组织很难开始有效的投资。”</p><p> Stemly 联合创始人、首席运营官兼首席科学家朱塞佩·马奈 (Giuseppe Manai) 表示：“很难确定公司在负责任的人工智能项目上进行了多大程度的投资，因为人们的认知度和相关性非常广泛。”华为技术（英国）研究总监艾莎·纳西尔（Aisha Naseer）补充道：“目前尚不清楚这些投资是否足够，因为这些投资的规模从微不足道到巨额资金都被分配用于控制人工智能和相关风险缓解。”</p><p></p><h3>建议</h3><p>对于寻求充分投资 RAI 的组织，我们建议如下：</p><p> <strong>1. 培养领导层对人工智能风险的认识。</strong>领导者需要意识到，使用人工智能是一把双刃剑，既会带来风险，也会带来好处。专注于增加人工智能收益的投资，而不相应地关注管理其风险，会从两个方面损害价值创造。一是，如果没有适当的护栏，人工智能的好处可能不会令人印象深刻：我们的研究发现，当 RAI 实践到位时，人工智能的创新就会增加。其次，人工智能带来的风险与其所嵌入的工具一样迅速扩散。对人工智能风险和收益的强烈认识支持领导层努力管理风险和发展公司。建立管理意识可以采取多种形式，包括高管教育、讨论论坛和 RAI 计划，这些计划拥有不同类型的人工智能风险暴露（和经验）的利益相关者。</p><p> <strong>2. 接受 RAI 投资将是一个持续的过程。</strong>随着人工智能开发和使用的增加（没有可预见的结束），RAI 实践和实施也需要适应。这需要持续的 RAI 投资来不断发展 RAI 计划。随着欧盟、美国和亚洲的监管格局即将发生变化，领导者将面临越来越大的压力，要求其发展以人工智能为中心的风险管理系统。等待在技术、文化和财务方面对这些系统进行投资（或停止投资）可能会损害业务增长。当新的法规和行业标准生效时，为满足合规性要求而快速调整流程可能会干扰人工智能相关的创新。最好将 RAI 程序与 AI 开发共同发展，这样它们就能相互补充，而不是造成这种不必要的干扰。随着公司扩大人工智能投资，他们的 RAI 投资也需要增长。但那些已经落后的公司需要迅速采取行动，积极投资 RAI，以避免始终落后。</p><p> <strong>3. 制定 RAI 投资指标。</strong>投资 RAI 很复杂——这种投资的回报是什么样的？就像网络安全投资一样，最好的 RAI 回报可能是在人工智能相关问题在品牌声誉受损、监管问题和成本增加之前被发现时保持沉默。也就是说，沉默不应被误认为是充分的投资。正如我们的调查结果所示，投资最少的公司可能不会仅仅因为不寻找问题而发现问题。领导者应就 RAI 投资的构成、评估这些投资的适当指标以及由谁来决定投资水平达成一致。随着时间的推移，衡量 RAI 计划成功与否的指标对于支持 RAI 计划是必要的，但它们可能是一个滞后指标。指标还应该评估前瞻性维度，例如领导承诺、计划采用、培训和劳动力需求以及文化变革。领导者还必须确定 RAI 资金与 AI 项目资金的关系。每个大型人工智能项目都应该为 RAI 留出预算吗？或者 RAI 资金是否应该独立于具体项目或基于项目（分散）和机构（集中）投资的某种组合？</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-your-organization-investing-enough-in-responsible-ai-probously-not-says-our-data/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title>推动护理危机的真正问题</title><link/>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Jack Daly The Research We analyzed the free text of 150,000 reviews written by U.S. nurses from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. For each review, we analyzed whether it mentioned one of 200 topics and assessed whether the nurse spoke about that topic positively or negatively. The topics were derived from research [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Sull_Nursing_Main_1290x860.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution">杰克戴利</p></figcaption></figure><aside class="callout-info"><h4>这个调查</h4><p>我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论的自由文本。对于每条评论，我们分析了它是否提到了 200 个主题之一，并评估了护士对该主题的评价是积极还是消极。这些主题源自对员工体验的各个要素的研究，包括文化、薪酬和福利、工作时间表以及感知的组织支持。我们将相关主题聚集成两打更广泛的主题。</p><p>我们将这些主题用作 XGBoost 模型中的特征，该模型以 5 分制预测每位护士对其现任或前任雇主的总体评分。然后，我们计算 SHAP 值（为模型中的每个特征分配一个重要性值），以直接比较不同主题在预测工作满意度方面的相对重要性（通过每个护士给雇主的总体评分来衡量）。我们还使用文本分析来比较旅行护士与医疗保健系统工作人员的护士谈论话题的积极程度。</p><p>使用护士提到的主题以及他们对每个主题的情绪作为预测变量，我们的模型解释了护士之间 29% 到 39% 的评分差异——几乎比我们使用所有权、组织类型和位置所能解释的要高一个数量级作为预测因子。<a id="reflinki" class="reflink" href="#refi">我</a></p></aside><p>医疗保健领导者面临着一系列艰巨的挑战——成本上升、向数字医疗的过渡以及支付模式的转变等等。但根据美国医疗保健高管学院最近的一项调查，医院首席执行官面临的第一大问题是员工短缺和倦怠。 <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> 90% 的受访首席执行官将护士短缺视为一个特别严重的痛点。</p><p> 2021年，在美国工作的注册护士总数出现40年来最大降幅，其中年轻护士的流失率最高。 <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a>到 2025 年，美国医疗保健系统可能会短缺多达 45 万名护士，比患者护理所需的护理人员数量少 20%。 <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p></p><p>高度的工作不满和倦怠正在驱使护士离开这个行业。 COVID-19大流行给所有医护人员带来了巨大压力，但自大流行结束以来，护士的不满和倦怠并没有改善。从某些角度来看，情况可能会变得更糟：2021年，近三分之二的注册护士会鼓励其他人成为一名护士，但只有一半的人表示他们会在两年后推荐护理作为职业。 <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a></p><p>了解护士不满情绪的最丰富来源之一是他们在 Indeed 和 Glassdoor 等招聘网站上如何用自己的话描述自己的工作。这些信息数量庞大，但难以综合，因为其中大部分采用非结构化自由文本的形式。为了了解护士面临的挑战，我们分析了自疫情爆发以来，其中 15 万名护士在 Glassdoor 评论中如何描述其雇主。 （参见“研究”。）在本文中，我们分享了该分析的重要见解，并就如何解决护士最紧迫的问题向医疗保健领导者提供建议。</p><h3>医疗保健领导者脱节</h3><p>护士认为他们的经理与患者护理的日常现实脱节。我们将他们对管理者的评价分为近 50 种领导特质。第二个最常被提及的特征是，管理者没有意识到护士在工作场所面临的挑战。当护士们讨论管理者如何理解床边生活时，十分之九的评论都是负面的。</p><p></p><p>护士们尤其批评高级管理团队成员的脱节。高层团队因脱节而受到批评的可能性是一线主管和中层管理人员的 10 倍。我们的结果证实了另一项调查，其中近一半的医院护士表示，他们认为管理层没有倾听他们的担忧。 <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a></p><p>为了解决不满和倦怠问题，医疗保健领导者必须首先了解床边发生的情况。这可能具有挑战性，特别是在拥有数千名护士跨多个地点和专业工作的大型医疗保健系统中。</p><p>从历史上看，领导者一直在努力系统地分析护士挫败感的金矿，这些见解可以从员工调查或外部审查中的评论中收集到。阅读、理解和分析大量非结构化文本数据根本不切实际。然而，人工智能的最新进展使得识别大量文本中的深层模式并大规模理解反馈成为可能。领导者现在可以挖掘自由文本，以深入了解导致护士不满和倦怠的问题，并利用这种洞察力改善护理人员的工作生活。 （请参阅“文本分析入门”。）</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>文本分析入门</h4><p>我们的研究分析了来自数百个组织和数十万名护士的数据，但您也可以更深入地研究自己员工的反馈。无论您是在内部、通过劳动力分析功能还是与外部合作伙伴一起开发人工智能文本分析功能，您都应该牢记这些原则，以最大限度地提高文化衡量的有效性。</p><p><strong>精确度很重要，但记忆力也很重要。</strong>精确度（被正确分类为讨论某个主题的文本实例的百分比）是自由文本分析的关键要素。召回率也是如此——文本分析平台捕获的文本正文中主题提及总数的百分比。如果您仅通过精度来衡量成功，那么您最终会得到一个高度准确的分析平台，但会忽略员工实际所说的大部分内容。复杂的人工智能工具将识别俚语、习语、首字母缩略词、文化参考和组织特定的语言，以捕获很少提及但信息丰富的术语的长尾。</p><div class="callout-toggle"><p><strong>让主题专家了解情况。</strong>文本分析的核心是将自然语言分类为有意义的主题。理想情况下，衡量文化的人在开发分析主题时应聘请主题专家。主题专家可以确保所选择的文化和工作场所主题得到明确定义、与现有研究相关联并得到适当衡量。</p><p><strong>李克特问题有严重的缺点，但适度使用会非常有帮助。</strong>太多的李克特量表问题可能会导致调查者进入自动驾驶模式。但李克特的问题不应该被完全抛弃。有效的文化衡量将广泛主题（例如参与度、流失意图和其他重要衡量标准）的李克特规模结果与自由文本数据相结合，以确定在数百个自由文本主题中哪些对结果具有最强大的影响。</p><p><strong>透明度很重要，而且未来可能会更加重要。</strong>虽然人工智能将如何受到监管还有待观察，但立法者或法院可能不会善待黑盒模型做出的重要决策，而不解释这些模型如何得出结论。领导者经常依靠文化衡量来做出重要决策，例如薪酬政策、人事变动以及如何优先考虑资源。他们应该警惕完全依赖做出人类无法理解的决策的模型。</p><p><strong>员工们讨厌你监视他们——而且你不会学到太多关于文化的知识。</strong>领导者应该抵制诱惑，将文本分析工作扩展到电子邮件、Slack 渠道、电话消息和其他并非旨在提供员工反馈的沟通形式的内容。许多员工认为监听他们的工作谈话是窃听或更糟的行为。此外，工作电子邮件和 Slack 消息所包含的文化信息往往比明确邀请员工讨论组织中有效和无效的问题提示少得多。让员工倾听双方同意的意见，并让老大哥远离工作场所。</p></div></article></aside></div><h3>通过基准测试确定相对优势和机会</h3><p>不同雇主的护理满意度差异很大。我们确定了美国 200 家最大的医疗保健雇主，包括医院和医疗保健系统、家庭医疗保健提供者、老年生活设施运营商以及人才中介机构。对于每位雇主，我们计算了从 COVID-19 大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月，护士在 Glassdoor 上对组织和高级领导层的评价<a id="reflink6" class="reflink" href="#ref6">。6</a></p><p>在大型雇主中，护士的 Glassdoor 评分范围从很差（2.6）到近乎完美（4.9）（满分 5 分）。护士对大流行期间和之后高级领导表现的评估更加多样化，在相同的 5 分制中，从 2.1 到 4.9 不等。 Glassdoor 评级的巨大差异与另一项调查一致，该调查显示美国 60 家医院中护士不满意的比例从 2% 到 48% 不等。 <a id="reflink7" class="reflink" href="#ref7">7</a></p><p> 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工可以使用我们的<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/">交互式工具</a>来查看他们的组织相对于其他组织的排名。该指数根据护士的总体评分、对最高领导层的评估以及护士满意度的四个最有力的预测因素进行排序：薪酬、工作量、组织支持和有毒文化。 </p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Interactive_512.jpg" class="launchscreen no-mobile"></p><h4>护士如何评价他们的雇主？</h4><p class="caption">使用护理满意度指数来比较护士如何评估 200 家大型医疗保健组织的员工体验。</p><p></p></article></aside></div><p>平均而言，在人事代理机构工作的护士（有时被称为旅行护士）比其他护士更满意。我们样本中排名最高的五家雇主（前十名中的六家）是人才中介机构。</p><p>当然，较高的薪酬是造成这种差异的部分原因，但不是全部。我们比较了在人才中介机构工作的护士与医院和医疗保健系统雇用的护士谈论 200 个话题的积极程度。 （参见“人事机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高”。）虽然机构护士对薪酬的看法更有利，但围绕解决护士问题和开放、诚实的沟通问题，两组之间的情绪差距更大。通过将护士视为客户，人才中介机构擅长提高满意度，而不仅仅是支付更高的工资。其他医疗保健领导者可以从他们的例子中学习，我们将在下面提出一些具体建议。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高</h4><p class="caption">我们分析了从大流行开始到 2023 年 6 月期间美国 Glassdoor 护士评论的自由文本，以了解他们对各种话题的积极评价。然后，我们将在人才中介机构工作的护士的积极情绪与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士的积极情绪进行了比较。虽然人事代理机构在许多关键主题上的评分较高，包括诚实沟通、有效解决问题和建立信任，但医院和医疗保健系统在学习和发展、福利、同事和晋升机会方面表现更强。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig1.png" alt="人才中介机构在许多关键因素上的评分更高" /><br /></article></aside></div><h3>优先考虑工作满意度的驱动因素</h3><p>为了了解护士工作满意度的驱动因素，我们分析了样本中护士自 COVID-19 大流行开始以来撰写的所有评论的自由文本，并将文本分为近 200 个主题。 <a id="reflink8" class="reflink" href="#ref8">8</a>然后，我们将主题分为两打更广泛的主题，并使用这些主题来预测护士对其雇主的总体评分。然后我们比较了每个主题在预测收视率方面的相对重要性。 （参见“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素。”）</p><p></p><p>薪酬是护士对当前雇主满意度的首要预测因素，这并不奇怪，因为在我们分析的期间，通货膨胀侵蚀了实得工资的购买力。工作量的重要性是第二重要的驱动因素，这与另一项大规模调查的结果相吻合，该调查发现人员配备不足是护士工作不满、倦怠和辞职意愿的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink9" class="reflink" href="#ref9">9</a></p><p>工作量和薪酬是护理危机必须解决的根本原因，但它们并不是影响护士工作满意度的唯一因素。我们的分析揭示了工作环境的其他方面，包括有毒文化、组织支持、工作时间表、沟通、学习和发展机会，领导者可以关注这些方面来改善护士的工作生活。</p><p>该分析还强调了不太可能改善护士工作场所体验的领域。福利固然不错，但无法弥补繁重的工作量或跟不上通货膨胀的工资。强调促进患者健康的企业使命也无济于事。护士们已经知道他们的工作有更高的目标；这就是为什么他们中的大多数人首先成为护士。</p><h3>挖掘自由文本以获得可行的见解</h3><p>许多医疗保健组织依赖年度员工调查，其中有数十个项目按 5 分制评分，并事后添加了一些开放式问题。面对一长串的多项选择题，员工很容易转向自动驾驶仪，并为非常不同的项目分配相似的分数。问题的选择限制了员工可以讨论的内容，而且很少有空间来扩展他们为什么选择特定的数字答案。</p><p>开放式的自由文本反馈提供了丰富的细致入微且可操作的见解来源。当护士可以决定要写哪些主题时，他们会利用自己的自由来讨论对他们来说最重要的事情。开放式问题为护士提供了用自己的语言阐述他们的担忧、提供关键背景并针对他们面临的问题提出具体和可行的解决方案的空间。个人自由文本回复可以汇总为更广泛的主题，以确定领导者可以集中注意力和有限资源的优先顺序，以最大程度地提高护士满意度。</p><p>虽然组织平均值很有用，但重要的是要记住，不同的亚文化可以在同一组织内共存。对于通过并购发展起来的大型医疗保健系统来说尤其如此。例如，一家全国性连锁医院在近 50 个地点的评级范围为 1.9 到 3.9。医疗保健领导者不能仅仅依赖组织平均水平，而必须衡量和分析地点、部门、职能、团队和个人领导者之间的差异。</p><p>女性、代表性不足的少数族裔和年长员工也会体验到与其他员工截然不同的组织文化。 <a id="reflink10" class="reflink" href="#ref10">10</a>了解不同员工群体工作满意度和倦怠的驱动因素至关重要。</p><p></p><p>领导者可以挖掘免费文本，详细了解特定群体最关键的痛点，并相应地调整干预措施。例如，日程安排对护士的工作满意度有重大影响，但日程安排的哪些方面最重要将取决于具体职位。轮班安排的灵活性和不间断工作休息的能力对于医院和初级保健机构的护士来说非常重要，而家庭保健护士则非常看重可预测的时间表。 <a id="reflink11" class="reflink" href="#ref11">11</a></p><p>护士的意见为改善工作场所和患者护理提供了宝贵的实用建议。例如，我们研究的 Glassdoor 评论包括数十条关于雇主如何改进日程安排的可行建议。有些是易于实施的行动，例如使用应用程序更容易接班或调换班次，或者向最后一刻接班的护士支付 20 至 50 美元的奖金。其他则是更系统性的改变，例如将护士纳入一个旨在制定时间表的委员会，或确保接受学费援助的员工能够安排他们的课程工作。</p><h3>倾听离开您组织的护士的心声</h3><p>大多数组织将调查范围限制在现任员工。离职面谈如果有的话，也是随意进行的，而前员工的反馈往往被视为不满者的咆哮。但忽视前员工的反馈是一个很大的错误。 </p><div class="post_video_player fit-video"><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KJE4DW0Lbuk?rel=0&showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><p>对前员工进行访谈或调查可以揭示他们离职的原因，并找出留住人才的最有效行动。由于没有报复的威胁，即将离开（或已经离开）组织的护士更有可能提供坦诚的反馈，甚至是当前员工不愿讨论的禁忌问题。通过收集离职者的反馈，组织可以发现潜在的盲点。</p><p>在我们的样本中，超过三分之一的 Glassdoor 评论是由前员工撰写的，这些评论提供了对用脚投票的护士最重要的见解。 <a id="reflink12" class="reflink" href="#ref12">12</a>图左侧的条形图“护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素”对预测离职护士如何评价其前雇主的因素进行了排名，它揭示了护士可能离职的一个关键原因。</p><p>在 <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/">之前的一篇文章</a>中，我们认为五种行为属性——不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和辱骂——将组织文化标记为有毒。 <a id="reflink13" class="reflink" href="#ref13">13</a>在辞职的护士中，有毒文化对他们总体满意度的预测作用是薪酬或工作量的两倍多。有毒工作场所对辞职护士的重要性与早期的研究一致，该研究发现毒性是大辞职的前六个月内行业调整后人员流失的最强预测因素。 <a id="reflink14" class="reflink" href="#ref14">14</a></p><p>在大流行后时代，有毒文化对于护士来说变得更加重要。当我们比较哪些因素最能预测护士在大流行前后对雇主的评价时，发现在 COVID-19 之后，有毒文化的相对重要性获得了最大的提升（其次是工作量、幸福感和薪酬）。如果您的组织遭受文化毒性，我们的另一篇文章“<a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">如何修复有毒文化</a>”提出了几种基于证据的干预措施，医疗保健领导者可以用来为自己的组织排毒。</p><div class="callout-highlight"><aside class="l-content-wrap"><article><h4>护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素</h4><p class="caption">我们将超过 150,000 条护士的 Glassdoor 评论文本分为两打影响员工体验的主题，然后分析哪些主题最能预测护士如何评价其雇主。该图表通过显示每个主题对整体预测的贡献程度，对每个主题在预测这些评级中的重要性进行排名。 </p><p><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sull_Nursing_Fig2.png" alt="护士工作满意度的最高和最低预测因素" /></p><p class="attribution"></article></aside></div><h3>学习人才中介机构的做法</h3><p>正如“人事机构在许多关键因素上评分较高”这一数字所示，护士对人事机构为快速有效地解决问题而制定的流程非常积极。在提及人事代理机构流程效率的护士中，75% 的护士持积极态度，而只有 23% 的护士对医疗保健系统表示积极看法。对于旅行护士来说，常见的流程问题包括入职、获得所需的证书和执照、合同谈判和报销。最好的人才中介机构会听取反馈，深入了解旅行护士面临的典型问题，并优化工作流程来解决这些问题。</p><p>专职护士遇到的许多痛点与机构护士所遇到的痛点有所不同。然而，医疗保健系统、家庭保健机构和长期护理提供者可以采用类似的方法来捕获和分析护士的反馈，优先考虑他们面临的最常见和令人沮丧的挑战，并与工作人员合作解决这些问题。</p><p>持续倾听反馈并采取行动也可以与护理人员建立信任。与在医院和医疗保健系统工作的护士相比，人事机构的护士更积极地认为拥有心理安全感，可以说出困难的问题并让别人听到。</p><p>然而，如果管理层对护士提出的问题反应缓慢，心理安全的好处就会减弱。护士们高度评价人才中介机构对她们的问题和疑虑的快速反应。相比之下，护士经常抱怨其他类型的雇主即使得到回复，也对提出问题的电子邮件回复缓慢。护士还非常重视与主管的多种沟通渠道，包括短信、电子邮件、Facebook、Jabber 和 24/7 热线。</p><p>我们研究的另一个见解是护士重视诚实和透明度。他们和任何人一样了解医疗保健面临的挑战，并且希望就组织中正在发生的事情、它如何影响他们以及做出决定的原因进行诚实的沟通。 Triage 是一家人才中介机构，也是我们研究的第四大评价最高的大型雇主，它将诚实的沟通置于其价值主张的核心：“我们按事实说话，这样你就不会对其进展感到惊讶。” <a id="reflink15" class="reflink" href="#ref15">15</a></p><p>医疗保健系统可以向人才中介机构学习，但也可以利用自己的独特优势来吸引和留住护士。全职护士在组织生活的三个重要方面对医院和医疗保健系统的评价高于人才中介机构：学习和发展（包括晋升机会和培训报销）、福利和同事。这三个因素是护士评价雇主的十大预测因素之一。医疗保健系统应投资于其比较优势，并在向潜在和现有员工传达其价值主张时强调这些优势。</p><p></p><h3>将反馈转化为行动以建立信任</h3><p>收集员工反馈是一回事，但持续根据这些见解采取行动则是另一回事。如果员工认为管理者不会采取行动，他们就不太可能提出问题或提出潜在的解决方案。 <a id="reflink16" class="reflink" href="#ref16">16</a>更糟糕的是，如果员工认为管理层缺乏权力、资源或兴趣根据他们的建议进行变革，他们更有可能辞职。 <a id="reflink17" class="reflink" href="#ref17">17</a>近一半的护士认为管理层不会解决临床工作人员提请他们注意的问题。 <a id="reflink18" class="reflink" href="#ref18">18</a></p><p>组织需要建立适当的结构，以一致地根据员工的反馈采取行动。一个著名的例子是 Kaiser Permanente 的单位团队 (UBT)，该团队由经常在特定单位或部门一起工作的临床工作人员和管理人员组成。 <a id="reflink19" class="reflink" href="#ref19">19</a>这些团队每月至少召开一次会议，对其部门的绩效负责，并由一名经理、一名劳工代表以及通常还有一名临床工作人员共同领导。</p><p> UBT 确定了四个方面的改进机会：质量（包括患者治疗结果）、患者服务、负担能力和员工体验。团队利用员工反馈来识别改进机会并确定其优先顺序。接下来，团队使用最佳实践和基于证据的方法开发和测试解决方案。一旦解决方案被认为有效，就会在整个单位、部门，或者在某些情况下整个组织中实施。然后，UBT 监控这些变化对患者治疗结果、员工满意度和成本降低的影响。</p><p></p><p>自 COVID-19 爆发以来，我们对美国护士撰写的 150,000 条评论进行了研究，结果显示，护士对雇主的整体评价存在很大差异，特别是在薪酬、工作量、有毒文化和组织支持方面——这四个因素对雇主的影响最大。塑造护士的工作满意度。我们认为，这种变化传递了希望的信息。尽管所有医疗保健组织都面临结构性挑战，但<em>仍有</em>可能提供一个让护士每天都期待上班的环境。</p><p>许多组织，包括一些最大的护士雇主，都有很大的改进空间。这些排名的目的不是为了“点名羞辱”，而是为了让医疗保健领导者意识到他们的组织绩效与为护士提供健康工作场所的可能性之间的差距有多大。我们还希望有关医疗保健组织如何在对护士最重要的因素上排名的客观数据可以为其领导者提供改进的动力，并提供证据来说服所有利益相关者迫切需要进行变革。</p><p></p><p>领导者不应该做的是要求护士更加努力地工作，承受更多的挫折和压力，却不能理解和解决使许多人的生活变得悲惨的组织因素。当工作人员辞职、工人成立工会以及州和联邦立法者制定保护护士利益的法规时，继续照常营业的领导者不应感到惊讶。</p><p> To improve the work lives of nurses, and indeed all health care workers, leaders must collect and act on their feedback, recognizing that different parts of the organization and different populations will face distinctive challenges and issues. Listening to nurses demonstrates that there are meaningful steps health care leaders can take to fix the nursing crisis. The single most important step is to listen to them in the first place.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-solve-nursing-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Explore How Nurses Rate Their Employers</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Donald Sull and Charles Sull. <p>Donald Sull ( <a href="https://twitter.com/culturexinsight">@culturexinsight</a> ) 是麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院的高级讲师，也是 CultureX 的联合创始人。查尔斯·索尔 (Charles Sull) 是 CultureX 的联合创始人。</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Interactive]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses’ own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by U.S. nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses’ overall ratings [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><p> To understand the job challenges nurses face, health care leaders need to listen to nurses&#39; own words about burnout. We analyzed the free text of 150,000 Glassdoor reviews written by US nurses since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic and classified the text into two dozen themes that we used to predict nurses&#39; overall ratings of their employers.</p><p> We calculated the relative importance of each theme in predicting nurses&#39; overall satisfaction. Four factors — toxic culture, organizational support, compensation, and workload — emerged as the strongest predictors of how satisfied nurses were with their employer.</p><p></p><p> One significant finding for health care leaders: Among nurses who had quit, toxic culture was more than twice as predictive of their overall satisfaction compared with compensation or workload.</p><p> Nurses&#39; job satisfaction varies widely among employers. Our interactive Nursing Satisfaction Index shows how nurses evaluate the employee experience at 200 of the largest health care employers in the United States, including hospitals and health care systems, home health care providers, operators of senior living facilities, and staffing agencies.</p><p> For each employer, we calculated how highly nurses rated the organization and senior leadership on Glassdoor from the beginning of the pandemic through June 2023. We also report on how positively or negatively nurses spoke about compensation, workload, toxic culture, and organizational support. Each employer&#39;s score on all dimensions is expressed as standard deviations above/(below) the average for all 200 employers.</p><p> <a href="#interactive-launcher">Explore the index above</a> .</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/nursing-satisfaction-index/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> What Health Care Leaders Need to Know to Fight the Nursing Shortage: Nurses Speak</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/#respond</comments><pubDate> Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[M. Shawn Read. <p>M. Shawn Read is multimedia editor at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> .</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Analytics & Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Recruitment and Retention]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Turnover]]></category><category><![CDATA[Health Care]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[The Truth Behind the Nursing Crisis]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Behavior]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What’s driving that burnout? What’s most important to a nurse’s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Nurses are burning out and leaving the profession, generating fears that a looming nursing shortage will impact many aspects of patient care. What&#39;s driving that burnout? What&#39;s most important to a nurse&#39;s job satisfaction? How common are toxic cultures in health care settings? What can health care leaders do to improve the problems? In this video, we talk to five current and former nurses to learn about the reality of working in health care, including the toxic cultures and stressors they&#39;ve experienced, and get advice from them and health care experts on what needs to change.</p><p> Article author and researcher Donald Sull also discusses the truths about job satisfaction revealed by the analysis of 150,000 employer reviews by nurses on job site Glassdoor, and what health care leaders can learn from them.</p><p></p><p> “The key, actionable finding from our research is, nurses are telling you what&#39;s not working for them, often in very granular detail, and they&#39;re offering concrete recommendations to address these issues. They want to help. They want their voices heard, and they want to make a positive impact,” Sull says.</p><p> “One of the most difficult or frustrating things about being a nurse is really not having enough time to spend with the patient,” says Jennie Evans, who served as a pediatric oncology and ICU RN for 18 years. “Those moments where you can sit, talk with the patient, hold their hand, talk with the family, and really get to know them and understand not just the disease but other underlying anxieties or fears that the patient might have.”</p><p> Watch the video to hear more from nurses on what they want health care leaders to know about toxic cultures, mental health, growth opportunities, and other issues that are critical to caregivers.</p><p class="attribution"> Image credit: Jack Daly</p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/how-solve-nursing-shortage/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Upgrading Culture for Growth and Transformation</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:34:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Per Hugander and Laurianne McLaughlin . <p>Per Hugander is a strategic adviser and professor of practice at Hult International Business School. His work on decision-making, problem-solving, and culture has been published in <em>Harvard Business Review</em> , <em>MIT Sloan Management Review</em> , and <em>Knowledge at Wharton</em> . Per shares his thoughts and ideas on his blog <a href="https://leadershipbackbone.com/">leadershipbackbone.com</a> . Laurianne McLaughlin is senior editor, digital, at <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> . She moderated the session.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Change Management]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Video]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinar]]></category><category><![CDATA[Webinars & Videos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Related Reading P. Hugander, &#8220;Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change,&#8221; MIT Sloan Management Review, May 22, 2023. Many leaders know that their organization’s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don’t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><aside class="callout-info"><h5 style="margin-top:0"> Related Reading</h5><p> P. Hugander, &quot; <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/take-a-skills-based-approach-to-culture-change/" class="marketing-click" id="Sidebar_callout[WebinarArchive]">Take a Skills-Based Approach to Culture Change</a> ,&quot; <cite>MIT Sloan Management Review</cite> , May 22, 2023.</p></aside><p> Many leaders know that their organization&#39;s culture is blocking opportunities from disruptive technologies — but they don&#39;t know what to do about it. Soft skills and psychological safety can enable the collaboration needed to drive transformation and growth. But despite ambitious efforts to infuse such skills into their culture, many organizations fail. The secret to success: Shorten the time to reward when people experience the new skills helping teams beat longtime challenges.</p><p> Per Hugander has helped leaders at organizations including Swedish financial services group SEB make progress on complex strategic challenges. His practical approach helps people to link psychological safety to tangible business results.</p><p> In this webinar, you will learn:</p><ul><li> Why many organizations fail at culture change: Just testing the waters can be dangerous.</li><li> How to go deep — not wide — on culture change and win over skeptics.</li><li> How to put the new skills to use quickly on the organization&#39;s toughest problems and create lasting culture benefits.</li></ul><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/video/upgrading-culture-for-growth-and-transformation/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Five Steps to Build and Sustain Diversity in Your Organization</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/#respond</comments><pubDate> Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:41 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Keith D. Dorsey. <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dr-keith-d-dorsey-798a2681/">Keith D. Dorsey</a> , Ed.D., is a managing partner and the US practice leader of CEO and Board Services at Boyden, a global executive search firm. He built his career as a turnaround (glass cliff) specialist in corporate America and writes on issues related to diversity, governance, and strategic growth for private and public corporations and boards.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Diversity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Organizational Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategic Planning]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Development]]></category><category><![CDATA[Diversity & Inclusion]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leading Change]]></category><category><![CDATA[Workplace, Teams, & Culture]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR &#124; Getty Images No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Dorsey-1290x860-2.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR | Getty Images</p></figcaption></figure><p> No matter how diverse the pipeline of job candidates is, if we have not properly prepared our organizational landscape, the odds are stacked against the talented professionals we work so hard to find, recruit, and welcome aboard. Many organizations have instituted measures to monitor and increase their diversity hires; however, less attention is paid to what happens after the hire. Only when we effectively create a more equitable landscape and support women and people of color in navigating it can we benefit from the full engagement and contributions of all of our people and avoid losing them to turnover or disengagement.</p><p> Occupational minorities — those individuals who are <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/unleash-the-superpowers-of-your-one-and-only-employees/">relative rarities</a> in their profession due to their gender or sexual identity, ethnicity, age, or other factors — have accomplished what countless more have only dreamed of: They have broken through the glass ceiling, navigated the often inhospitable <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90920778/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-i">corporate jungle</a> , and often successfully negotiated the <a href=" https://www.businessinsider.com/women-and-people-of-color-face-glass-cliff-us-2020-7?op=1">glass cliff</a> . Although the executives who represent diverse populations in your organization have successfully overcome these challenges, an important task remains: building a path for others to follow. This is hard, painstaking work that requires many different tools and competencies, yet it is necessary if others are to safely navigate the landscape.</p><p></p><h3> Steps to Sustaining Diversity</h3><p> Although various resources offer suggestions for how professionals from underrepresented populations can navigate and overcome organizational challenges, it is equally essential that organizations identify where <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/02/stop-telling-women-they-have-imposter-syndrome">persistent systemic bias and racism</a> lurk and take concrete action to address them. Organizations can take the following five steps to begin the process of creating more inclusive environments where all employees have equal opportunities to thrive and advance in their careers.</p><h4> Step 1: Establish leadership commitment to diversity with sponsorship.</h4><p> Leadership throughout the organization must demonstrate a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion. When leaders model these behaviors, employees throughout the organization naturally follow their example. However, this commitment cannot be limited to one-off efforts or statements on corporate values.</p><p> Leaders must consciously exhibit their commitment to hiring people from underrepresented populations by helping to develop and equip these candidates for advancement. Specifically, every leader, regardless of organizational level, should identify at least one such candidate to intentionally sponsor. After getting to know the candidate&#39;s background, career goals, and support needs, the leader should (1) counsel them in navigating the organization, (2) support them in developing the competencies needed to advance in their career, and, critically, (3) help them secure progressive leadership positions.</p><p></p><p> Although formal mentoring, sponsorship, and buddy programs can be helpful in this effort, relationships that develop informally often are equally, if not more, rewarding and beneficial and tend to continue long after one or both individuals have advanced in or moved out of the organization.</p><h4> Step 2: Remove glass ceilings by addressing systemic factors.</h4><p> The metaphor of the glass ceiling depicts the systems of discrimination that prevent certain groups of people (typically women and people of color) from accessing high-level opportunities for career growth and advancement. Clues that glass ceilings exist within your organization include a lack of diversity within the upper-management and executive ranks compared with your overall workforce; pay disparities between individuals with similar roles and qualifications; limited mentorship, sponsorship, development, or advancement for certain groups of people; explicit or implicit biases regarding which groups are a better fit for leadership roles than others; and attrition levels within underrepresented groups that exceed those of other groups.</p><p> To identify and eradicate glass ceilings in your organization, closely scrutinize every aspect of the employee experience. For example, address biased hiring and promotion practices using blind recruitment techniques; review salary ranges and promotion criteria to ensure that equal pay is awarded for equal work; and make clear career paths and development opportunities available to all employees. Diversity goals, inclusion initiatives, and employee education on recognizing and avoiding unconscious biases also can support a diversity-conducive climate. Supporting flexible work arrangements and work-life balance can encourage the full participation of employees who might otherwise be overlooked due to their needs to balance personal and professional responsibilities.</p><p></p><h4> Step 3: Reduce glass cliffs through due diligence.</h4><p> The term <em>glass cliff</em> describes a phenomenon in which women and other minorities are preferentially selected for leadership positions in times of crisis, placing them at increased risk for failure. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> This phenomenon occurs across industries and geographies, and for women and ethnic minorities alike. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> The problem with giving people from underrepresented populations leadership opportunities only in times of crisis is that those who lead during turbulent times tend to be seen as part of the problem, which perpetuates stereotypes and reduces future opportunities for such candidates. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a></p><p> To avoid this outcome, care must be taken to recognize and fully examine the situation before assigning a leader to address it. While the temptation to dive in and do something to “stop the bleeding” is overwhelming, taking the appropriate time to first fully understand the problem is a small price to pay for a much-improved chance of success. The diagnosis process should include identifying project parameters (such as performance targets, deadlines, and budget), project stakeholders, past actions taken, the current situation, and desired outcomes — from the perspectives of all stakeholders. My article on the <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/from-glass-ceilings-to-glass-cliffs-a-guide-to-jumping-not-falling/">glass cliff phenomenon</a> provides more details on the process of due diligence and the questions that can be used to diagnose these situations. Only after diagnosing the problem will it be possible to select the most appropriate candidate to lead the effort.</p><h4> Step 4: Broaden the pathway by changing the conversation.</h4><p> Corporate environments can be fraught with challenges for women and people of color. Many challenges are systemic, such as organizational cultures that <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace">disadvantage certain groups</a> versus others, or workloads and behavioral expectations that require long hours in the office and around-the-clock responsiveness. These systemic challenges can make the corporate landscape seem foreign and antagonistic. In turn, occupational minorities might compensate by nursing cognitive biases that result in too much or too little confidence; limiting their social networks to similar peers rather than nurturing<a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90932520/navigating-the-jungle-beyond-the-glass-cliff-part-ii">vital connections</a> to sponsors, mentors, and career guides; and failing to strike an appropriate work-life balance.</p><p> Although leaders must deliberately sponsor occupational minorities (Step 1), mentors, sponsors, and allies throughout the organization also play important roles in guiding candidates toward success because they, too, have already successfully navigated the organization. Supporting emerging leaders means changing the typical mentoring conversation. Typical conversations involve identifying a mentee&#39;s short- and long-term goals and seeking the mentor&#39;s situational advice, guidance on skill development, and feedback on performance. Mentoring that supports diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging should be adapted to include a clear framework for professional development, an explanation of how various opportunities and positions contribute to the candidate&#39;s career goals, and a discussion of how to navigate the organizational culture — all in light of the glass ceilings, glass cliffs, and systemic challenges they face as occupational minorities.</p><p> Cognitive biases also should be part of the conversation so that candidates can avoid the traps of both being overconfident and overcompensating for perceived shortcomings. Evaluation and adjustment of cognitive biases might be best accomplished by gathering 360-degree feedback regarding the mentee&#39;s performance on key tasks and engaging the mentee to describe their feelings, thoughts, and general experiences related to performing those tasks. Overconfidence might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is at or below average while their own experience of that task reflects strong enthusiasm, satisfaction, and a sense of achievement. In contrast, overcompensation might be occurring when the mentee&#39;s task performance is evaluated as or above average yet their described experiences suggest that they are spending too much time on tasks or that they harbor concerns about their performance.</p><h4> Step 5: Measure and track progress.</h4><p> A popular business adage is that we must inspect what we expect. This truism applies equally to any diversity effort. The process begins with defining what success looks like according to key diversity metrics such as hiring, retention, and advancement for various employee populations. It might be tempting to stop there; however, defining the goal is only the beginning. Additionally, it is necessary to measure the organization&#39;s current performance on these KPIs and then examine why that is the current state. Understanding the organization&#39;s current performance requires the following assessments:</p><p> <strong>1. Gauge buy-in.</strong> To what extent do organizational leaders and members understand and agree that the KPIs defined are the right indicators and performance targets?</p><p> <strong>2. Gauge feasibility.</strong> What organizational structures, processes, and other features facilitate the achievement of the KPI? What features threaten or obstruct achievement?</p><p> <strong>3. Gauge support needs.</strong> Leaders are taught to adapt to the needs of individual subordinates based on each person&#39;s skill level. In the same way, leaders throughout the organization need to adjust the amount of oversight, encouragement, and direction they provide as departments and employees across skill levels work to achieve diversity goals. For example, a recruiting department that is relatively inexperienced at hiring professionals from underrepresented groups will need strong, step-by-step guidance and frequent feedback until their competency grows, while a manager who is highly skilled at developing and including such professionals generally should be allowed the autonomy to exercise their talents to their fullest.</p><p></p><p> As initiatives are implemented, continue to regularly assess these metrics to gauge your progress and fine-tune your efforts. As the saying goes, “What gets measured gets done.” Achievement of your diversity goals will happen only if they are deliberately defined and regularly assessed.</p><p></p><p></p><p> I often have been one of few Black leaders in the organizations where I&#39;ve worked. At one point in my career, I was a town hall presenter at two meetings separated by level — one attended by rank-and-file employees, and the other attended by management. Although the Black customer service representatives were pleasantly surprised to see someone who looked like them in an executive role, I was shocked and dismayed to realize that nearly our entire customer service representative force was Black while all of our supervisors and managers were White. This was puzzling because the leadership team seemed to care about diversity from a recruiting standpoint, but it was glaringly obvious that systemic barriers were obstructing the retention and advancement of professionals from underrepresented groups.</p><p> Often, it is only when executives, board members, or the HR team notices a lack of diversity in their organization&#39;s upper levels that problems in the talent management system are noticed — but typically poorly understood and only rarely solved. Such disparities in advancement might be at least partially explained by inhospitable organizational settings and the need to broaden the pathway for these professionals from underrepresented populations to succeed.</p><p> Organizational leaders, coaches, mentors, sponsors, and other potential career enablers all have a part to play in eliminating sources of inequity and equipping occupational minorities to survive and thrive in corporate environments. As more and more diverse groups of professionals travel the pathway to career success, the pathway will become smoother and broader, resulting in an ongoing and cumulative organizational transformation.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/five-steps-to-build-and-sustain-diversity-in-your-organization/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> Why Pay Transparency Regulations Are a Strategic Management Opportunity</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/#respond</comments><pubDate> Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tamara Montag-Smit, Karoline Evans, Brandon Smit, and Cassondra Batz-Barbarich. <p>Tamara Montag-Smit is an assistant professor of management at the University of Massachusetts (UMass) Lowell. Karoline Evans is an associate professor of management at UMass Lowell. Brandon Smit is an assistant professor of management at Bentley University. Cassondra Batz-Barbarich is an assistant professor of business at Lake Forest College.</p> ]]>; </dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Compensation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Employee Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Equity]]></category><category><![CDATA[Gender]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hiring]]></category><category><![CDATA[Negotiations]]></category><category><![CDATA[Transparency]]></category><category><![CDATA[Financial Management & Risk]]></category><category><![CDATA[Strategy]]></category><category><![CDATA[Talent Management]]></category><description><![CDATA[Annalisa Grassano Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, pay transparency laws are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women’s Law Center reports that altogether, [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Montag-Smit-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Annalisa Grassano</p></figcaption></figure><p> Touted as one remedy to the gender wage gap, <a href="https://www.adp.com/spark/articles/2023/03/pay-transparency-what-it-is-and-laws-by-state.aspx">pay transparency laws</a> are increasingly being rolled out across the United States at the state and local levels. Nine states — including New York, as of September — are currently regulating some aspect of pay disclosure. The National Women&#39;s Law Center reports that altogether, more than one-quarter of US employees live in a location where <a href="https://nwlc.org/resource/pay-range-transparency-laws-benefit/">pay information is regulated</a> .</p><p> By and large, pay transparency regulations have emphasized disclosing a salary range for advertised positions and internal opportunities for advancement. These laws are designed to ensure equal pay for equal work and effectively close the gender wage gap. The logic is simple: If underpaid employees, including women and minorities, aren&#39;t aware of what their coworkers are paid, they are at a significant disadvantage in leveling the playing field through litigation and negotiation. How can inequities be addressed when they remain in the dark? Without pay transparency, enforcement of existing laws, such as the <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/equal-pay-act-1963">Equal Pay Act of 1963</a> , becomes difficult. Based on <a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/fact-sheet-notable-eeoc-litigation-involving-pay-discrimination">recent cases</a> and notable discrepancies that have been exposed (some spanning years of underpayment), it seems that greater transparency has an important role to play.</p><p></p><h3> Organizational Responses to the Changing Regulatory Landscape</h3><p> Despite the increasingly widespread adoption of pay transparency regulations, many organizations have responded with pushback, resistance, and minimal compliance. After Colorado became the first state to require organizations to disclose pay ranges in advertised positions in 2021, organizations soliciting applicants from across the country began <a href="https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/state-and-local-updates/pages/some-employers-are-excluding-colorado-applicants-for-remote-work.aspx">explicitly excluding Colorado residents</a> from consideration to skirt the new laws, prompting the state&#39;s department of labor to issue <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/coloradans-excluded-job-listings-department-labor/">warnings and fines</a> . Another organizational tactic is to comply with pay information requirements with pay ranges that are so wide that applicants cannot meaningfully predict what salary they might be offered. In one notable example, Netflix posted a job with a salary range that <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/90000-to-900000-pay-transparency-laws-usher-in-baffling-pay-ranges-in-job-postings-200857290.html">spanned $90,000 to $900,000</a> .</p><p> While approaches to compliance with transparency laws at the organizational level have taken many forms, leaders have expressed several common concerns regarding the potential negative consequences of pay transparency to their business operations and culture:</p><ul><li> <strong>Will everyone just ask for more money?</strong> More pay information might prompt more conversations about pay (and why someone is receiving what they are). Managers worry that they&#39;ll be caught in the middle trying to juggle competing goals around budgeting and employee satisfaction.</li><li> <strong>What happens if some employees find out that they&#39;re paid less than others?</strong> Explaining to long-standing employees why they are paid the same as a new hire is likely to be uncomfortable and prompt substantial criticism of the employer.</li><li> <strong>Will pay transparency affect our ability to work together?</strong> Pay transparency can elicit jealousy and counterproductive competition when individuals perceive themselves as inequitably rewarded. Managers worry that employees might fight and undermine one another when discrepancies are exposed.</li></ul><p></p><h3> New Insights Into Managing Pay Transparency</h3><p> Our work provides new insights into addressing some of the main questions organizations have about transparency. Most new laws focus exclusively on creating pay transparency by requiring organizations to disclose pay ranges for open positions. In academic research, this form of transparency is referred to as <em>distributive transparency</em> , because it reveals information only regarding the <em>amount</em> of money employees are paid.</p><p> In our research, however, we have delineated several ways in which pay information can be transparent. <a id="reflink1" class="reflink" href="#ref1">1</a> With <em>procedural transparency</em> , the emphasis is on sharing information about how pay <em>decisions</em> are made; at the most transparent level, this would include a formula for calculating compensation (such as base pay or a merit-based raise).</p><p> Distinguishing between distributive versus procedural transparency is crucial because, as our research shows, procedural transparency can mitigate many of the risks and drawbacks associated with distributive transparency.</p><p> Implicit in pay transparency regulations is the idea that underpaid employees will take it upon themselves to <a href="https://qz.com/how-women-can-use-pay-transparency-to-negotiate-1850228867">negotiate for a fairer wage</a> . In fact, a large-scale study of over 100,000 academics over the past two decades found that changes in pay transparency were related to significantly more wage parity between men and women. <a id="reflink2" class="reflink" href="#ref2">2</a> However, the research also showed that transparency doesn&#39;t equate to <em>everyone</em> asking for more.</p><p> To explore this further, we conducted a series of four experiments to better understand <em>how</em> and <em>when</em> pay transparency can encourage employees (especially women) to more effectively negotiate for fair wages. In our first study, lab participants were paid for their performance after four rounds of a popular word search game and were given the opportunity to negotiate for better compensation. In studies 2, 3, and 4, online participants prepared themselves to go into a performance review, armed with varying degrees of information regarding performance and pay, to possibly negotiate for a better annual raise. They were told that they were slated for a 3% raise but that raises could range from 3% to 10%. Across these studies, we varied the amount of information participants could access regarding both the amount other people were paid and participants&#39; performance relative to their peers&#39;.</p><p> These studies yielded four important findings regarding distributive and procedural pay transparency:</p><p> <strong>1. People made clearer comparisons.</strong> We found that the best predictor of whether someone tried to negotiate for higher pay was their performance relative to that of peers. Compared with average performers, high performers were approximately 50% more likely to request higher pay when they knew their ranking relative to others. It&#39;s important to note that in our study, participants saw the previous year&#39;s performance and pay data for their team members, and it was clear that increased performance was directly related to increased pay. Although not an explicit formula indicating performance-based pay, this information provided a clear signal to participants that pay raises were largely determined by performance.</p><p> <strong>2. People negotiated fairly.</strong> Average performers were more likely to accept the minimum raise offered to them, often citing the raise as fair based on their performance. As one person stated, “Considering I only met expectations throughout the year rather than exceeded them, asking for a higher raise seems fruitless and unearned.” Generally, average performers rarely asked for the maximum raise, in part because they considered the fact that they were performing at a lower level than some peers. This was true, though, only when they had all of the information. When they were told nothing about their performance, 85% of people requested the maximum pay amount. Lacking performance information, average performers asked for the highest raises available within the pay range.</p><p> <strong>3. Women <em>do</em> ask for higher pay.</strong> Counter to a pervasive assumption, women didn&#39;t seem to need much encouragement to negotiate. In fact, when the percentage of participants who negotiated is considered, women were often more likely than men to negotiate (though this was not a statistically significant difference). These findings cast some doubt on the idea that one reason for the gender wage gap is that women negotiate less often than their male counterparts. Recent research combining information from dozens of negotiation studies has come to the same conclusion: Many of the negotiation gaps between men and women have largely disappeared in recent years. <a id="reflink3" class="reflink" href="#ref3">3</a> Although this is good news, it does little to close the gender pay gap as it currently stands.</p><p> <strong>4. People were motivated to perform better.</strong> Average performers expressed motivation to work harder and perform better to earn a higher raise during the next review cycle. When asked why they did not negotiate for more money, one participant stated, “My numbers did not show that I deserved a higher raise. With better numbers the following year, a case would be made for a higher raise.” Another stated, “I knew I&#39;d done an average job, so I hope to do better in the future and hope to get a better raise next year.”</p><p> Our findings replicate and extend an old but powerful notion in management research: the <em>fair process effect</em> . <a id="reflink4" class="reflink" href="#ref4">4</a> Employees will accept unfavorable outcomes if they believe those outcomes were produced by a fair system. Put differently, if people know <em>why</em> they are being paid less (in other words, there is procedural transparency), they will not respond negatively and might even work harder.</p><h3> Make Pay Transparency a Win-Win for Your Organization</h3><p> Pay transparency can be a win-win opportunity rather than a compliance hurdle. But simply listing pay data in job postings without any context in response to regulations might be a big mistake. These practices not only disregard the spirit of the laws but also come at a heavy price and forfeit significant opportunities. Leaders should think beyond compliance and consider ways to strategically leverage pay transparency for their organization to improve applicant attraction and employee retention. Our research offers some insights into how this can be done.</p><p> <strong>Make pay only <em>part</em> of the transparency equation.</strong> Counter to some pervasive fears that transparency will increase labor costs, cause jealousy, and create conflict, the reality is that secrecy around pay creates problems of its own. As researchers at Payscale found, most employees are <a href="https://www.payscale.com/content/whitepaper/Fair-pay-perception-and-pay-transparency-combat-turnover.pdf">unsure whether they are paid fairly</a> , with many believing they are underpaid when they are not, which leads to greater turnover and dissatisfaction. Our research suggests that without a reference point for performance, employees have little to no basis for judging what compensation would be fair and are therefore more likely to make unreasonable requests. Transparency in both performance <em>and</em> pay can enable employees to better assess the fairness of their pay and make more reasonable requests.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Focus on the pay decision-making process.</strong> Procedural transparency helps managers more clearly communicate with employees about pay because salaries/bonuses are based on performance rather than on seemingly intangible or, worse yet, bias-laden factors. Providing information on how pay is determined helps incumbent employees understand why their pay is higher or lower than their peers&#39; and, more importantly, how to move up. Managers can&#39;t be accused of favoritism and bias when pay is directly determined by performance, which puts them in a collaborative role during pay conversations. With a focus on performance, these conversations can focus on development and examine how employees can perform better and earn higher raises.</p><p> <strong>Recognize that (distributive) pay transparency will not fix inequity on its own.</strong> There&#39;s an assumption that distributive pay transparency will close pay gaps; however, evidence suggests that this alone is not enough to create an equitable workplace. Research has shown that women and men are <em>asking</em> for salary increases in <a href="https://hbr.org/2018/06/research-women-ask-for-raises-as-often-as-men-but-are-less-likely-to-get-them">relatively equal proportions</a> , but women are still less successful at getting what they ask for. Distributive pay transparency can help reduce some ambiguity, but both performance and pay transparency (procedural transparency) together equip employees with the tools they need to ask for what they deserve. When people know what to expect from negotiations (that is, what the bargaining zone is and what&#39;s reasonable to ask for), gender differences are minimized. <a id="reflink5" class="reflink" href="#ref5">5</a> For example, <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/negotiating-as-a-woman-of-color">women of color</a> don&#39;t often take advantage of opportunities to negotiate roles, responsibilities, or flexible work arrangements, creating long-term inequities that explain pay gaps beyond starting salary. Broader transparency helps reduce the ambiguity that often leaves women and members of other minority populations hesitant to negotiate, even when they know they could.</p><p> <strong>Consider the benefits for current employees <em>and</em> applicants.</strong> Simply posting pay ranges is only one piece of the puzzle. Applicants have negative reactions to excessively wide pay ranges because they don&#39;t offer useful information. In this case, pay is still essentially secret. As we found in our study, without meaningful information, individuals are inclined to ask for the maximum amount to see what is possible. This creates yet another headache for hiring managers. A better approach would be to leverage procedural transparency to clearly outline the factors used when determining a salary offer, and perhaps even how heavily those factors are weighted. For example, Buffer, a marketing company, has done a great job of creating a <a href="https://buffer.com/salaries?ref=buffer.com">pay system</a> that balances simplicity (for better understanding) and complexity (for capturing nuance) by using a standard formula for making pay decisions: salary = job type x seniority x experience + location + $10,000 or equity.</p><p></p><p></p><p> Despite organizational concerns and hesitancy to implement government regulations around pay transparency, such policies continue to gain traction and are just one force behind growing expectations around salary disclosures. In a 2022 report from HR technology firm Visier, 79% of surveyed employees said they want <a href="https://www.visier.com/company/news/visier-report-pay-transparency/">pay transparency</a> ; Gen Z employees were the strongest proponents of it.</p><p> Our research highlights the potential for procedural transparency to strategically mitigate the perceived organizational risks while also meeting legal requirements and social expectations. While changes are clearly happening, we hope business leaders think more deeply and creatively about <em>how</em> to make pay transparent in ways that both support organizational goals and meet employee needs.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-pay-transparency-regulations-are-a-strategic-management-opportunity/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 0</slash:comments></item><item><title> The Delicate Dynamics of Challenging a Superior</title><link/> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/<comments> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/#comments</comments><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Laker. <p>Benjamin Laker ( <a href="https://twitter.com/drbenlaker">@drbenlaker</a> ) is a professor of leadership at the University of Reading&#39;s Henley Business School.</p> ]]>;</dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Communication]]></category><category><![CDATA[Conflict Resolution]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Leadership Skills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Skills & Learning]]></category><description><![CDATA[Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one’s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person [&#8230;]]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p><figure class="article-inline"><img src="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Laker-color-yellowpink-1290x860-1.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><p class="attribution"> Carolyn Geason-Beissel/MIT SMR</p></figcaption></figure><p> The act of challenging a superior necessitates more than just raising one&#39;s voice; it involves understanding, navigating, and engaging in the subtle yet complex dance of power dynamics, diplomacy, and mutual respect. Approaching someone above you in the professional hierarchy requires a delicate balance and a deep understanding of both the person and the situation.</p><p> For those keen on maintaining professional decorum and growing in their roles, this guide can help ensure that your challenging conversations are both constructive and respectful.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Choose your battles wisely.</strong> Workplaces are vibrant ecosystems of opinions, processes, and methodologies. It can be enticing to address every single discrepancy or divergence in opinion that one encounters, but wisdom lies in discerning which battles are worth fighting. Every time a potential disagreement arises, consider: Is this issue so significant that it warrants a confrontation? Minor differences in opinion might be addressed more effectively through passive channels or should even be overlooked. But larger concerns, especially those affecting team dynamics, company culture, or broader business objectives, require a more direct approach.</p><p> <strong>Understand the importance of timing.</strong> In the world of professional communication, timing can be everything. Choosing the right moment can make the difference between a concern being genuinely considered or hastily dismissed. Before even considering challenging a superior, it&#39;s crucial to pause and assess the situation from a holistic viewpoint. Is your concern so immediate that it demands to be addressed immediately? Alternatively, would it be better to earmark it for a detailed, private discussion later? It&#39;s wise to avoid confronting superiors during high-pressure situations or public forums because it can be misconstrued as an attempt at disruption or showmanship. By choosing the optimal time, you create a smoother path for constructive dialogue.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Prioritize private discussions.</strong> The environment in which you choose to voice your concerns plays a pivotal role in how those concerns are received. Engaging in public disagreements or conflicts can lead to multiple unforeseen complications, including being perceived as aggressive or confrontational. By choosing a private setting for these discussions, you provide both yourself and your superior with an atmosphere conducive to open and genuine dialogue. This approach not only minimizes distractions and potential biases but also reinforces the idea that the intent is constructive feedback, not public criticism.</p><p> <strong>Master the art of “I” statements.</strong> Effective communication is as much about content as it is about delivery. The words we choose and the manner in which we frame our concerns can significantly influence the reception of our message. Instead of adopting a potentially confrontational tone, use “I” statements to express observations, feelings, and suggestions. For instance, instead of bluntly stating, “You&#39;ve overlooked this crucial aspect,” a more collaborative approach would be, “I feel that this particular aspect could benefit from further attention.” This approach ensures that the focus remains on the issue at hand and not on personal biases or confrontations.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Embrace the feedback process.</strong> The journey of challenging a superior or expressing concerns is inherently bilateral. It&#39;s not just an avenue for you to voice your thoughts but also an opportunity to understand the other person&#39;s perspective. Demonstrating a genuine openness to feedback, even if it&#39;s contradictory to your viewpoint, is vital. This approach not only paves the way for mutual respect but also fosters a culture of continuous learning and collaboration within the organization.</p><p> <strong>Align with like-minded peers, but tactfully.</strong> While individual concerns have their merit, there&#39;s undeniable strength in numbers. Finding allies or colleagues who share your perspective can provide additional weight to your concerns. However, it&#39;s imperative that this alignment is not perceived as cliquey or divisive. The primary focus should always remain on the collective benefit of the organization rather than on forming factions within the team.</p><p> <strong>Keep the organization&#39;s goals at the forefront.</strong> Any concerns or challenges you raise should inherently resonate with the broader objectives and goals of the organization. By consistently aligning your feedback and suggestions with the company&#39;s mission and values, you reassure your superiors of your commitment to the collective success of the organization over your individual aspirations.</p><p> <strong>Brace for a spectrum of outcomes.</strong> While we all hope for positive and constructive outcomes from our disagreements, it&#39;s essential to be prepared for a variety of reactions. Your superior might be receptive, indifferent, or even defensive. By anticipating these potential responses and planning your strategies accordingly, you ensure that you remain balanced, constructive, and professional, irrespective of the immediate feedback.</p><h3> The Aftermath: Reflect, Adapt, and Evolve</h3><p></p><p> Every professional interaction, especially those involving challenges or confrontations, provides a rich opportunity for personal and professional growth. After the discussion, take the time to evaluate the effectiveness of the conversation, the strategies employed, and the outcomes achieved. These reflections will bring invaluable lessons to light and help you to continuously refine and enhance your communication skills for future challenges.</p><p> Ultimately, while the task of challenging a superior might seem steeped in potential pitfalls, with the right strategies and a focus on mutual growth and respect, it can be navigated with tact and professionalism. Encouraging open dialogue and a culture of feedback is the bedrock of innovative and forward-thinking organizations.</p><p></p> ]]>;</content:encoded><wfw:commentrss> https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/the-delicate-dynamics-of-challenging-a-superior/feed/</wfw:commentrss><slash:comments> 1</slash:comments></item></channel></rss>