<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Marketing When Budgets Are Down]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_27_523536254.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;大卫·扎伊茨/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;企业财务的一般规则是，营销预算一有麻烦就会像石头一样下降，而一旦环境恶化，营销预算就会像羽毛一样上升解决了。到 2023 年中期，我们距离稳定状态还很远——西方市场预计的 GDP 增长令人沮丧地持平，事实证明通货膨胀相当顽固，而且这些干扰仍在不断发生。短期内很难看到营销预算大幅增加。 Gartner 对数百名 CMO 进行的年度调查绘制了近期营销支出的演变情况，为企业领导者如何在更短的时间内交付成果并建立推动增长的能力提供了指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span >; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;营销的数字化转型带来了前所未有的增长，无论是功能范围还是消费能力。新渠道、新技术、新能力需要新水平的投资。但美好时光不可能永远持续下去，随着预算的减少，大流行迎来了一个新的、更加严峻的时代。这使得&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing&quot;>;首席营销官 (CMO)&lt;/a>; 面临着减少其投资组合中以前神圣不可侵犯的部分（例如营销技术）的支出的压力。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/495785/1158365?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBCMOSPENDSURVEY&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;Gartner 年度调查&lt;/数百名 CMO 绘制了近期营销支出的演变图，为企业领导者如何在更短的时间内交付成果并建立推动增长的能力提供指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;无人知晓因在更多数字化和技术上花费而被解雇&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您什么时候第一次成为数字化的？ 20 年前，我得到的第一份工作的标题中就包含“数字”一词，我想这让我成为了一名数字营销老手。当时，我构建业务案例的时间几乎与激活活动的时间一样长。这很容易被忘记，但在 2000 年代中期从线下转向数字化绝非易事。数字营销领导者总是渴望更多 - 更多的预算、更多的技术、更多的数据、更多的人员、领导团队的更多关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实上，这就是这个时期的开始更多。数字化对营销造成了沉重打击，而与消费者和客户互动、联系和交易的可能性创造了巨大的机会。它还创建了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/leadership-vision-chief-marketing-officer?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_CMOVISION2022&amp;amp ;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;首席营销官面临的挑战&lt;/a>;，他们努力平衡勇敢的数字营销领导者与非数字领导者的预算需求。前者提出了一个令人信服的论点：我们不断赞扬数字化的优点，认为它是具有成本效益、可衡量和可优化的选择。相比之下，任何线下的东西都显得古板、过时，而且是模拟的。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;没有人因为在数字和技术上花费（甚至更多）而被解雇&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;更多的时期持续了相当长的一段时间。毕竟，数字化是一头饥饿的野兽，拥有看似无穷无尽的诱人工具、技术、人才和渠道。早在 2016 年初，我就成为了一名营销分析师，当时营销技术和数字渠道占据了营销总预算的很大一部分。届时，我们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/495785/1158365?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBCMOSPENDSURVEY&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;年度 CMO 支出和策略调查&lt;据报道，企业平均营销预算高达公司收入的 12.1%。 2016 年，超过四分之一的营销总预算分配给了技术，而且支出排名前三位的渠道都是数字渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然 2016 年的营销总预算可能达到了一个高水位线。 ，这当然不是异常值 - 事实上，技术支出占营销预算总额的比例在 2018 年达到峰值，几乎占营销预算的三分之一 (29.2%)。2016 年至 2020 年间，营销预算平均占公司收入的 11.2%，令人印象深刻.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;更少，但更多&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当我们在 2020 年初、大流行封锁之前对 CMO 进行调查时，CMO 无法预料到疫情的全面规模Covid-19 的影响：营销预算被削减，客户旅程被打乱。但这场大流行也为数字和技术带来了另一个推动力。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/digital-iq-index-genius-brands?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_GENIUSBRANDSEBOOK&amp;amp;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;品牌&lt;/a >; 以前落后于同行的企业现在别无选择，只能转向数字渠道来与锁定的受众进行互动和交易。已经在数字化方面投入巨资的品牌别无选择，只能进一步加快投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，即使投入较少，也会有更多。更多电子商务、&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/multichannel-marketing-survey?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_MULTICHANNELMKTG&amp;amp;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;更多数字渠道&lt;/a>;，以及更多技术。当我们在 2020 年对 CMO 进行调查时，他们表示，与付费媒体或代理机构等资源组合中的其他要素相比，他们更有可能保护对技术的投资，因为他们相信技术将是帮助他们在未来发展的重要工具。大流行——当我们进入“新常态”时。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;疫情后的漫长回升&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;就像一根棍子上挂着的胡萝卜令人沮丧的是，过去几年“新常态”一直遥不可及。世界卫生组织可能已经宣布 Covid-19 全球卫生紧急状态结束，但我们距离正常状态还很远。从最近大型银行的倒闭到各种社交媒体平台的波动，这些问题都困扰着整个最高管理层，无论他们受到影响的程度如何。这一系列看似永无止境的破坏导致了企业增长的许多锚点：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;更高的利率&lt;/strong>;影响新投资的投资回报率潜力。在当前&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/recession-playbook-marketing-leaders?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_GMLRECESSIONPLAYBOOK&amp;amp;utm_term= ebook&quot;>;宏观经济环境&lt;/a>;，投资者优先考虑当前的利润和现金流，而不是等待未来的增长。较高的利率也削弱了经济需求，抑制了增长。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人才市场依然困难&lt;/strong>;，员工流动率较高，对战略性重要职位的竞争加剧，员工信任度降低管理方面的问题，以及混合和远程工作方面的紧张局势。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;数字化转型滞后&lt;/strong>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/ press-releases/2022-10-19-gartner-says-89-percent-of-board-directors-say-digital-is-embedded-in-all-business-growth-strategies&quot;>;2023 年 Gartner 董事会调查&lt; /a>; 报告称，81% 的董事会尚未在实现数字业务转型目标方面取得进展或实现。此外，2022 年 Gartner 的一项调查发现，67% 的 CFO 认为过去三年的数字化支出没有达到企业预期。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;虽然可以方便地在前后构建近期企业历史记录——疫情方面，另一个拐点也可能已经出现。企业已经从集中投资支持数字化增长的工具和能力的时期转向这些投资需要开始回报的时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当技术投资和数字营销不再酷炫和与众不同时，它们是&lt;em>;主流&lt;/em>;。用 Gartner 的话来说，此类投资已经从&lt;em>;创新系统&lt;/em>;（变革性、颠覆性且很大程度上未经证实）转变为&lt;em>;记录系统&lt;/em>;（其中占主导地位的战略力量） &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/455982/1074604?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGOPERATIONS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;运营效率&lt;/a>; ，并且企业期望可预测性、可靠性和稳定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;我们（不需要）需要更大的船&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这让我们到了 2023 年Gartner 5 月底发布的年度 CMO 支出和战略调查数据表明，“更多”时代已经结束。首先（也是最明显的），它表明我们调查的 400 多家北美和欧洲 CMO 的营销预算尚未恢复到新冠疫情前的峰值。事实上，2022 年调查报告的收益有所下滑，平均预算从 2022 年公司收入的 9.5% 降至 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2023-05 -22-gartner-survey-reveals-71%的cmos相信他们缺乏足够的预算来在2023年全面执行他们的战略&quot;>;2023年将达到9.1%&lt;/a>; .&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许比高层预算趋势更令人担忧的是营销支出能力明显受到挤压。 （人才和数字媒体）成本的增加和（营销技术利用率）收益的下降造成了一场营销生活成本危机，类似于过去 18 个月许多市场的消费者所经历的危机。简而言之，每营销一美元购买的东西就会减少。因此，实际上，我们已经从“多”时代转向了“少”时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“少”时代对财务和心理的影响可以从对此的反应中清晰地听到。年的调查。超过 70% 的受访者表示，他们的企业缺乏足够的预算或资源来成功实施 2023 年的营销策略。75% 的受访者表示，他们的企业要求他们用更少的资源做更多的事情，86% 的受访者表示，他们“他们面临着对营销方式进行重大改变以实现可持续成果的压力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今年调查中最令人惊讶的发现可能与企业对技术投资越来越不耐烦有关。四分之三的受访者表示，他们面临着企业削减 Martech 投资的压力——这在几年前是不可想象的。更重要的是：数字媒体看似势不可挡的崛起已经陷入停滞。当我们看看分配给数字渠道和线下渠道的媒体支出比例时，会发现到 2023 年，这一比例下降了 1 个百分点，达到 55%。到 2023 年，完全有可能因为在数字和技术上投入更多而被解雇。错误引用 1975 年经典电影《大白鲨》：我们不需要更大的船；我们需要的是更大的船。我们需要一个更高效的电影。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;适应更少的时代&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;关于 70 年代经典电影的主题，弗朗西斯·福特·科波拉 (Francis Ford Copolla)在谈到他 1979 年的代表作《现代启示录》时，他曾说过一句名言：“我们人太多了，我们拥有太多的钱、太多的设备，但渐渐地我们都发疯了。”这并不是说首席营销官经历了科波拉所说的那种过剩，但他确实提到了更多的主要挑战之一：有时更多实际上带来的效果更少。或者，反过来说，有时你可以用更少的钱获得更多的东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，用更少的钱提供更多的东西是那些可怕的陈词滥调之一 - 说起来容易，但实现起来却非常困难。这具有挑战性，因为“更多”是大多数企业领导者的首选状态。多年来，在我与首席营销官和营销领导者进行的数千次对话中，相当一部分内容涉及“如何构建业务案例来增加营销预算？”这一主题的变化。另一个合理的块？ “我如何定义我可以削减的东西和我不能失去的东西？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些基本问题的答案无法在闪亮的新技术中找到；相反，这是吃蔬菜的战略版本。作为领导者，您需要有一个坚定的计划来定义营销范围，并清楚地了解该职能的范围如何逐步实现企业目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，您的计划必须立足于近期和未来的目标。长期行动将提供使今天保持活力的销售线索和销售，以及有助于明天实现差异化和增长的投资。这需要一个细致入微的故事来阐述&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/ Three-techniques-to-prove-the-value-of-marketing?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp; utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_PROVEMKTGVALUE2023&quot;>;营销的价值&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/ Three-techniques-to-prove-the-value-of-marketing?utm_source= press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_PROVEMKTGVALUE2023&quot;>;向企业提出的建议&lt;/a>; — 营销如何实现&lt;em>;目标回报&lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;投资回报&lt;/em>;。它需要接受这样一个事实：构建这个价值故事的工作不是计量经济学模型或归因分析；而是关于构建价值故事的工作。这些是达到目的的手段，而不是目的本身。这是关于与利益相关者就营销如何创造价值达成相互理解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这也是关于拥抱和探索大量的不确定性，并使用情景规划和敏感性分析的核心战略工具来了解当前存在的问题。是成功的关键，使您的团队能够制定适当响应的战略选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过回归健全战略管理的首要原则，营销人员将制定一个计划，摆脱无关的东西，从而实现&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487268/1142263?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGSYMTAKEAWAYS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;关注右侧&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot; https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487268/1142263?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGSYMTAKEAWAYS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;&lt;em>;更少&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;最有可能支持目标的实现。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了以稍微不同的方式来阐述这一点，在 Gartner，我们讨论 CMO 如何将自己从 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/ newsroom/press-releases/2023-05-22-gartner-says-catalytic-marketing-allows-cmos-to-drive-profit-growth-amid-macroeconomic-stress&quot;>;暴政更多&lt;/a>;通过关注三个主要领导特质：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;清晰。&lt;/strong>; 精挑细选很重要。 CMO 必须就战略生命周期内将支持和不支持哪些内容做出清晰的决定。应该对那些未通过的举措给予同等的思考和考虑，并明确原因。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;勇气。领导者必须有勇气向团队提出难题。它识别虚假假设、战略感伤和有害的文化规范。例如，首席营销官必须消除“仅仅因为我们在一个项目上花费了 10 万美元，并不意味着我们应该多花 10 万美元”的沉没成本偏见。同样，首席营销官必须与历史性的价值假设作斗争：仅仅因为一项投资在三年前有意义，并不意味着业务案例会逐年滚动。所有重大投资都应该能够根据对未来目标（而不是过去目标）的可衡量贡献来证明自己的合理性。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;联系。&lt;/strong>;成功几乎总是如此一种协作努力。成功合作的开始是沟通和理解。 CMO 必须与 CFO、CSO、CIO 等合作，对营销计划如何实现业务目标有明确的定义和共同的理解。同样，他们必须了解营销与价值创造过程中其他职能的交叉点。抛弃市场营销所喜爱的晦涩指标和三个字母的缩写。将品牌话语转化为商业话语，以揭开营销的神秘面纱并增加联系。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;等等，但是人工智能呢？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您可能会问“人工智能肯定会改变一切吗？”也许&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/how-should-cmos-respond-to-chatgpt-today?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_YOY_GML_NPP_PR1_RECHATGPT&quot;>;变革力量人工智能&lt;/a>;将迎来数字投资的新时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但由于几个原因，现实很复杂。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，人工智能对于营销 - 它已经存在，隐藏在您的技术堆栈（以及您的合作伙伴和代理机构的技术堆栈）中多年。其次，虽然&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487667/1143179?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGGENERATIVEAI&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;生成式人工智能&lt;/a>;的承诺激发兴趣和热情，这一切都发生在技术利用率大幅下降的时期。 Gartner 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/marketing-technology-survey-2022?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_MARTECHSURVEY22&amp;amp;utm_term=gi&quot; >;2022年营销技术调查&lt;/a>;报告称，martech的使用率仅为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2022-10-03-gartner-survey -发现营销人员只利用了他们的营销技术堆栈功能的 42%&quot;>;42%&lt;/a>;。因此，您在营销技术上花费的每一美元，您所利用的还不到投资的一半。鉴于营销技术一直占总营销预算的四分之一以上，这种收益水平不仅仅是技术风险，而是财务风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种水平的财务风险并不能阻止 CMO通过寻找新技术解决方案。但这应该让他们在一头扎进新的承诺之前认真思考。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;还会有更多&lt;em>;更多&lt;/em>;吗？ &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;企业财务的一般规则是，一旦出现麻烦，营销预算就会像石头一样下降，而一旦环境稳定下来，营销预算就会像羽毛一样上升。到 2023 年中期，我们还远未达到稳定的状态——西方市场的 GDP 增长预计将持平，令人沮丧，通货膨胀被证明相当顽固，而这些干扰只会不断出现。短期内很难看到营销预算大幅增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，情况有些复杂。平均值掩盖了差异，而且不同行业和地区的预算差异很大。如果您是营销消费品的 CMO，那么您 2023 年的预算很可能比金融服务领域的同行健康得多。如果您在德国，您的预算很可能不如您在英国的同事。然而，在我们 2023 年调查的所有行业和市场中，预算都落后于大流行前的水平。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2024 年会怎样？预测未来一直是一件愚蠢的事。也许我们将再次看到另一个更多的时代，新技术、体验和渠道为营销开辟了新的机会。也许我们会从更少的时代学到宝贵的经验教训，即使资金增加，营销也会变得精益和高效。也许吧。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx. net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; 目标=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managing Anxiety When There&rsquo;s No Room for Error]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_27_57363406.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;fStop 图片 - Brian Cassie/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当您的工作岗位必须不惜一切代价避免错误时 &amp;#8212;想想医疗、安全、金融和运输行业——人们很容易害怕制作一个。但有一些方法可以建设性地降低潜在错误的风险并减少您的焦虑。首先，区分严重和不太严重的潜在错误，并重点关注前者。然后采用系统和习惯来减轻这些威胁。获得他人的支持来解决您的弱点，同时找到发挥您优势的解决方案。与关注相同问题的其他人合作。解决任何自我破坏行为，例如不寻求帮助。通过消除大部分小错误的小行动，减少因小错误担忧而造成的干扰。最后，考虑一种你可以犯一些无后果错误的爱好。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres -no-room-for-error?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在某些领域，错误是正常的，而且代价也不是很高。如果设计师在制作精美的封面图片之前多次重新开始，发明家在找到可行的原型之前尝试了一百个原型，或者企业家从一个想法转向另一个想法，那么这并不重要。关于客户的反馈。在这些角色中，失败是成功之路的一部分。在其他情况下，风险可能会受到一个人较低级别的责任的限制。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是那些期望完美的角色呢？没有人希望他们的神经外科医生犯错误，或者他们的刑事辩护律师休息一天。会计师不能向美国国税局、美国证券交易委员会或任何其他监管机构提交有缺陷的财务报表。一些安全角色专注于监视潜在威胁，成功意味着永远不会错过任何威胁。你的工作可能属于这一类。或者，也许工作中出错的后果并不那么严重，但你觉得这是因为老板刻薄、裁员迫在眉睫或根深蒂固的焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你如何应对这种感觉你根本就不能搞砸吗？我的建议是使用策略来减少犯严重错误的机会，同时减少对此的担忧。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;焦虑的基础知识&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;让我们从焦虑如何产生的一些基本背景开始。首先，过度思考并不能解决问题。它让我们陷入瘫痪，而不是让我们动员起来。其次，人们常常沉迷于一种特定类型的错误或威胁，而忽视其他类型的错误或威胁，因为恐惧会缩小我们的注意力。最后， &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/gretchenrubin_one-of-my-aphorisms-is-action-is-an-antidote-activity-6651614263683137537-w-8Y?trk=posts_directory&quot;>;行动是焦虑的解药&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;错误代价高昂或危险的工作（例如医学、会计、工程或安全）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse. com/books/316156/the-anxiety-toolkit-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;有时会吸引天生认真负责、勤奋且善于把事​​情做好的人。但对于已经具有这种性格类型的人来说，时刻保持谨慎可能会很困难。这有点像父母“小心”的告诫会让本来就谨慎或焦虑的孩子变得更加紧张。如果您的培训或机构专注于消除错误，这可能会加剧您的完美主义和焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是您可以采取的措施来减轻紧张感。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;区分大和小小错误&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果你考虑一下你可能犯的每一个错误，它会让你分心，忽略那些你最应该害怕的错误。如果你经常采取行动来减少犯最严重错误的风险，你的精神负担就会减轻。要确定要优先考虑哪些风险，请考虑那些容易想到的风险以及经常被忽视的风险，例如机会成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他一些人们看不到的、有些相关的主要风险类别。一是前国务卿唐纳德·拉姆斯菲尔德所说的“未知的未知”：来自意想不到的情况的风险，以至于不会被考虑。另一个是“你不知道你不知道什么”，指的是你没有意识到的盲点，或者&lt;a href=&quot;/2012/05/discover-what-you-need-to-know ”当您认为自己完全理解某件事，但实际上没有理解时&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建立适当的机制来减轻这些风险。例如，每月安排一次与同事的会议，讨论您如何处理困难案例，以此发现您遗漏的任何潜在风险。在你的日历上安排一个定期会议，并期望你将讨论复杂的决策，将确保这一切得以完成。考虑一些例子，并询问您在自己的角色中可能会遇到哪些类似情况：也许您不知道学生可能会以与您预期不同的方式解释指令，从而导致您的实验室出现危险情况。您不知道手术室中的巡回护士会使用他们熟悉的程序，而不是您经常使用的程序，从而导致混乱或错过重要步骤。您不知道软件提供商会在重要截止日期的前一天推出有缺陷的更新并破坏您所依赖的系统。您现在可以做什么来确保不犯这些错误？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;谨慎的人可以重新训练自己寻找并规避最严重的风险。但这需要一种超越他人通常做法的心理能力，并能够容忍不确定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;采用降低风险的系统和习惯&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;而不是思考通过意志力减少错误，永远不会有糟糕的一天，创建不依赖于那种不切实际的机器人完美的系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有证据表明，诸如 &lt;a href=&quot;/podcast/2010 /01/using-checklists-to-prevent-fa.html&quot;>;例如，清单可以减少错误&lt;/a>;，但&lt;a href=&quot;/2010/02/draftwhat-sort-of-checklist-sh&quot; >;在特定领域未得到充分利用&lt;/a>;。如果您正在寻找灵感，请考虑如何调整在其他行业或角色中采取的行动。例如，心脏监护仪和呼吸机等医疗设备通常包含冗余传感器和警报器，以检测故障并提供及时警报。您的角色如何才能更早地收到或自动重复警告信号？航空等行业对未遂事件有严格的报告要求。如果一篇文章因重大事实错误而即将付印，或者一个项目在工作人员通宵达旦后才勉强按时完成，您是否应该这样做？什么是最有用的并且真正专注于学习而不是指责？ &lt;a href=&quot;https://toddkashdan.com/the-art-of-insubordination/&quot;>;自学科学&lt;/a>;如何建立多元化的团队，分享相反的观点，勇敢地表达担忧，并进行健康的辩论。创建一种奖励人们征求和积极强化不寻常观点的文化。当有人指出您不知道的事情时，请特别注意鼓励他们将来继续这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;获得支持来解决您的弱点&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当我还是一名治疗师时，我的弱点始终是记录保存。我讨厌记录。我的大脑运转得很快，感觉录音一直在拖慢我的速度。我更喜欢将所有精力投入到与客户面对面的互动中。如果我再次担任这个角色，我将不再尝试自己在该领域进行改进，并接受我需要一个支持人员来让我保持记录的正轨。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，如果您&#39;如果你是唯一知道如何扮演关键角色的人，而你又不擅长将你的流程系统化，那么你可能会得到帮助来做到这一点。如果你不是最好的沟通者，但正在向客户或老板做一个必须获胜的推销，你可以请导师、朋友，甚至是具有更多这些技能的人工智能聊天机器人来帮助你更有说服力吗？同样，如果冲突管理不是强项，但团队内斗可能会导致关键项目脱轨，也许您可​​以聘请一位顾问，您可以根据需要提供建议，甚至可能实施建议。或者，如果您凌乱的办公室确实存在丢失文件的风险，那么请专业的组织者进来，每隔几个月就给您一个新的开始。请记住，帮助您避免错误的不仅仅是您自己的意志力和勤奋。您可以招募一群同事 - 甚至朋友、家人和技术 - 来帮助您。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;发挥您的优势&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I &lt;a href =&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/645534/stress-free-productivity-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;经常争论&lt;/a>;利用你的优势来减轻你的劣势，这可以延伸到如何避免错误。例如，如果你在视觉上有创造力，你可以创建视觉提醒，或者如果幽默是一种优势，那么幽默的。只需谷歌“有趣的航空公司安全视频”即可找到如何让人们注意严肃的安全建议的示例。如果你善于交际并且善于与人相处，你会如何利用这种天赋来获取其他人通常保守秘密的信息，比如告诉你为什么你可能不想与某个特定的个人或团体合作？相比之下，如果你比较内向，你如何利用你的自然倾向去倾听和观察而不是说话，以注意到迫在眉睫的问题，或者让人们更有可能足够信任你，揭露你的担忧或错误，而不用担心你会告诉你其他的？考虑一下您的最大优势如何帮助您解决特定问题。 One question you can ask yourself to identify your uncommon strengths is: What are you willing to do that 95% of other people aren&#39;t?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Address self-sabotaging behaviors&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When we&#39;re very anxious about something, we often self-sabotage in ways that increase the chances of the feared thing happening. For example, you know you&#39;ve got a weakness, but you don&#39;t seek mentors or supervisors who could help you address it because you don&#39;t want to draw attention to it. Or you don&#39;t ask for an accommodation for your depression due to embarrassment and stigma or a belief you should tough it out, but that increases the chances of making a mistake on a bad day. Or you hate wasting money, so you don&#39;t try an option that might solve the problem but isn&#39;t guaranteed. Or you&#39;re a perfectionist so you don&#39;t seek to solve a problem where improvements are possible but perfect seems impossible. Get creative about overcoming your self-sabotage, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/be-kinder-to-yourself&quot;>;talk to yourself compassionately about it&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Collaborate with others focused on the same issues&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When you think about mistakes, you may mostly do so on a personal or team level. “How can I prevent myself or a colleague from getting this important thing wrong?” But to seek out better solutions — and the camaraderie of a group that shares your fears — consider getting involved in larger efforts to reduce mistakes in your field, like sitting on a committee for complaints and disciplinary actions or one establishing new guidelines for people in your role. Teaching also usually improves our own practice, so consider finding opportunities to teach others about how your work is done in a way that minimizes or eliminates mistakes. Write a talk on this for an industry conference or host a panel.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reduce small-threat distraction by taking simple actions to mitigate those risks&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Though most of your focus should be on the biggest threats, some simple strategies can lessen the risk of small mistakes so they won&#39;t distract you from that focus. You&#39;ll want to take simple actions that help reduce the frequency of minor problems, and then accept that you can&#39;t eliminate all of them. Pick the low-hanging fruit. For example, if a doctor is worried about forgetting names of patients and family members, they might write the names down on the top of each page as they&#39;re taking notes during interactions. Address minor potential mistakes to the extent that they free up your mental capacity to think about and prevent larger ones.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Consider a hobby that allows you to make mistakes&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To add some balance to your life, you might want to take up an activity in which mistakes and false starts aren&#39;t at all costly. For example, I&#39;ve recently taken up vegetable gardening, and it&#39;s refreshing to partake in an interest in which a low rate of success is perfectly acceptable. After all, a packet of a hundred seeds costs only a few dollars. A friend of a friend is an avid surfer, content to miss or bail out on dozens of waves to eventually get few good rides, which is a great antidote to his day job as a startup CFO trying to make sure the company doesn&#39;t run out of money.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When perfection is expected and mistakes are costly, it&#39;s easy to become terrified of making one. You might lose sleep over it or avoid leadership and increased responsibility. But there are ways to constructively reduce the risk of potential mistakes and reduce your anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Manage Your Team&rsquo;s Workload After Layoffs]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_98413121-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Susanne Walstrom/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;All too often in the case of layoffs, the people who survive it are expected to pick up the work that their terminated colleagues left behind. Meanwhile, these layoff survivors are often struggling with survivor guilt, anxiety, and low morale. In short, after a layoff, more is being asked of people who have less to give. This is a recipe for disaster when it comes to burnout and retention of key talent. In this piece, the authors outline four strategies for right sizing the workload on your &lt;span data-markjs=&quot;true&quot;>;team.&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Facing economic uncertainty and slowing revenue growth, companies continue to announce layoffs affecting thousands of workers. These downsizings, which have shifted beyond the tech industry to multiple&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-companies-conducting-layoffs-in-2023-heres-the-list-11673288386&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;other sectors&lt;/a>;, are undeniably tragic for layoff victims. But they&#39;re also terrible for the workers left behind. Layoff survivors often struggle with psychological impacts from the downsizing, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizreport.com/layoff-aftermath-survey-2022/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;guilt, anxiety, and depression&lt;/a>;. In a state of diminished&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/what-companies-still-get-wrong-about-layoffs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;trust and morale&lt;/a>;, they also remain on edge as they fearfully await another round of cuts. And all too often, layoff survivors are expected to pick up the work their terminated colleagues left behind.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In short, companies often ask even more of their people at a time when they have less to give. This dynamic is a recipe for disaster when it comes to burnout, retention of key talent, and the long-term success of your team. For the health and performance of your team, it&#39;s essential to evaluate your team&#39;s capacity after a layoff and to take significant steps to right-size your team&#39;s workload. Here&#39;s how:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Identify projects and initiatives to postpone&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a state of overload, it&#39;s a natural stress response to put your nose to the grindstone to make a dent in the volume of work. However, it is critical to step back and identify where your team should invest its precious time and energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Start by creating a comprehensive list with your team of all ongoing initiatives and projects and discussing what each one solves, creates, or improves.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Next, rank these initiatives based on their expected impact and each project&#39;s potential benefits to the organization.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Finally, identify which initiatives can be postponed but easily resumed later versus those where temporarily pausing might be consequential and difficult to reverse.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Due to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/07/how-susceptible-are-you-to-the-sunk-cost-fallacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;sunk cost fallacy&lt;/a>;, we are reluctant to abandon a strategy or course of action that we have already invested in. However, many projects can be put on hold and resumed easily at a moment&#39;s notice. Acknowledging this distinction will allow you and your team to override this fallacy and make decisions more swiftly so you can focus on the most critical work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you choose projects to postpone, however, ensure you retain one or more future-focused projects. These projects often serve as a source of inspiration and motivation for the team, infusing energy into their work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Align with your boss to manage your “shelf space”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Supermarkets and retail stores are naturally constrained by their shelf space, unable to add a new product unless they remove an existing one. Leaders should apply a similar principle in managing their team&#39;s workload, but rarely do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next time your boss requests something from your team, ask whether the new request requires immediate attention. If it does, ask your manager to help you prioritize the request among your team&#39;s other assignments. For example, you might say, “The team is also working on these three other initiatives. Are there any that can be dropped or postponed to make room for this one?” Giving your boss a choice gives them a &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33400628/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;sense of control&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;and is more effective than flatly pushing back.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Also, get in the habit of proactively sharing the estimated resource requirements for any requests. Most leaders are unaware of the effort and expense teams expend to fulfill their demands. When you proactively communicate resource requirements with your boss, they become more discerning in their inquiries, significantly reducing your team&#39;s workload.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Uncover your team&#39;s full set of talents&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Teams are often unaware of the complete set of skills, knowledge, and abilities within their ranks. This talent goes untapped to the detriment of team productivity and performance precisely when you need it most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address this issue and unlock your team&#39;s potential, schedule a meeting to uncover all the talent resident on your team. Give team members 10 minutes to reflect and write down their talents and skills. Next, ask each team member to share their list with the team. As they do so, encourage the team to add additional talents or skills they recognize in their colleague that they didn&#39;t mention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This simple exercise is a profound eye-opener, revealing hidden talents and helping teams identify their go-to colleagues when they need help. It also serves as an energizing experience for all participants, as colleagues rarely discuss and acknowledge each other&#39;s talents and skills in a direct and focused manner. In our experience facilitating this exercise with over 30 teams and hundreds of participants, every participant has had the uplifting experience of having talents that they were unaware of or took for granted added by their colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This simple exercise can deliver a significant boost in both engagement and productivity on teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Simplify, simplify, simplify&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the face of overwhelming workloads, teams often overlook opportunities for simplification.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://webinar.gartner.com/463005/agenda/session/1092611&quot;>;Gartner data&lt;/a>;, 27% of employees and 38% of managers feel overwhelmed by the ever-mounting burden of information. Discuss with your team how to simplify communication and information overload. For instance, it can be helpful to agree to limit any write-ups, such as proposals or meeting pre-reads, to a one-page summary that clearly highlights its relevance in the present context. Additionally, in meetings or chats — where opinions often overflow and unnecessary complexity arises — encourage participants to distill their ideas to their essence. Prompt team members to get to the crux by asking, “Can you summarize the essence of your suggestion in two sentences?” And as you discuss any workstream or product with your team, consistently challenge yourselves to simplify by asking, “How can we shorten or simplify this?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A second frequently neglected area is to seek input from your internal customers on what can be simplified in the solutions or services you offer them. Surprisingly, their perspectives can illuminate unnecessary complexity that your team may have overlooked. For example, the Dutch company AFAS Software regularly holds meetings with its clients solely dedicated to discussing what features or elements they should remove from their software solution. This proactive approach ensures that their software remains up-to-date and free from needless complexity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Layoffs are difficult and stressful for everyone involved. But by implementing the strategies above, you can help shield your team from the damaging effects of work overload. Your efforts will help eliminate depleting low-value work, ensure your team can focus on the most critical work, and boost their morale and engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out for These 3 Gender Biases in Performance Reviews]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Anja Sušanj&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Three kinds of bias often creep into the performance-review process, in ways that disproportionately affect women, especially when they choose to take advantage of the flexibility offered by hybrid and remote work. These biases are &lt;em>;experience bias&lt;/em>;, which leads reviewers to overvalue tasks that are easy to define; &lt;em>;proximity bias&lt;/em>;, which leads them to think that people in their immediate orbit do the most important work; and i&lt;em>;n-group/out-group bias, &lt;/em>;which leads them to give preferential treatment to people they feel belong to a group they identify with. This article, based on the author&amp;#8217;s study of a large multinational consulting group, explains the nature of these biases and offers suggestions for how to combat them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Because women continue to bear most of the burdens of caregiving, many have benefitted from the flexibility of hybrid and remote work, which has allowed them to remain part of the full-time workforce while spending more time at home. In theory, this is good news, because full-time employees tend to be promoted more often and let go less often — but &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace&quot;>;in practice&lt;/a>; that&#39;s not what&#39;s happening.为什么？ Because when women take advantage of hybrid and remote work options today, they become subject to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/6-ways-to-make-performance-reviews-more-fair&quot;>;biases&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;that creep into the performance-review process and cause them to be &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-gender-bias-corrupts-performance-reviews-and-what-to-do-about-it&quot;>;judged unfairly&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I witnessed this problem firsthand during a consulting project I did recently for a global company with hundreds of thousands of employees worldwide. During the project, which took place as the company (which I&#39;ll call HAPI&amp;nbsp; Consulting, to preserve its anonymity) was in the midst of a large reorganization, I was reporting to the CEO, his executive, and the board. With their support, I gathered and analyzed data on performance reviews given in a hybrid work environment (pre- and post-pandemic), and in that context I identified three specific kinds of bias that were hurting women and their career prospects. I&#39;ll explore them in turn below.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Experience bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first bias I observed was what we call &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/05/fooled-by-experience&quot;>;&lt;em>;experience bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; one aspect of which is overvaluing tasks that are easy to define.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This form of bias, I found, was prevalent in performance reviews at HAPI Consulting — where, because of the reorganization, many employees had been forced to put their routine work on hold. During that period, reviewers had judged employees instead on how they had chosen to refocus their energies. Men, on the whole, had chosen work that was much easier to recognize. They spent more time on highly visible external tasks, such as speaking at industry conferences and giving interviews to journalists, bloggers, and podcasters. These tasks were straightforward to review when it came to short-term measures of success. Meanwhile, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/research-women-took-on-even-more-invisible-work-during-the-pandemic&quot;>;women&lt;/a>; spent more time on much less visible internal tasks, such as boosting team cohesion to help get projects back on track and providing psychologically safe spaces for team members to ask questions and process elements of the reorganization that were taking place at the company. These tasks had longer timelines and were harder to evaluate in the short term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These choices lent themselves to experience bias. It&#39;s easy to understand, for example, how somebody who has presented at a major conference (probably a man) might have immediately provided a measurable benefit to the company. In fact, men were three times more likely than women to speak at outside events. But how easy is it to measure and evaluate the work that somebody (probably a woman) has begun to do in a long-term effort to repair team dynamics or prevent deep-rooted problems that might ultimately affect hundreds or thousands of employees? Needless to say, given the nature of experience bias, reviewers at HAPI Consulting praised the men more regularly in their performance reviews for having succeeded in their work. More specifically, men who reviewed other men assessed them 12% higher than women, on average, as compared to when women reviewed both men and other women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With the support of leadership, I tested several interventions designed to help reviewers at the company correct this bias. While some interventions failed, two had a statistically significant chance (with a 95% confidence interval or above) of reducing biases at this company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first was for managers to help employees set individualized goals with tailored metrics and then ask them to track what they had done every week — and to do it on a virtual whiteboard that the rest of the team and the directors up the chain could see. In this way, people who had contributed to less-easily-defined outcomes, such as team cohesion, could still point to a record of their efforts over time for all to see. This whiteboard could record important work even if it wasn&#39;t easily described in terms of traditional goals and metrics. This was helpful come performance review time. Even if employees had failed to reach the goals laid out for them in their last performance review, there was still a record of all their efforts and achievements, which, according to the post-survey results, helped reviewers better grasp the value of the more ambiguous, internal work that (mostly) women were performing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The second was designed to help employees become better at describing their own efforts. At the beginning of the week, for each project they were working on, employees were asked to provide two different estimates on their virtual whiteboard: how long each task would take to accomplish and its level of difficulty (high, medium, or low). For example, an employee might identify the three projects they&#39;re working on for the week and allocate the amount of time they plan to spend on each, based on the type of task and estimated difficulty. At the end of each week, employees were asked to revisit their estimates, note how their time was actually allocated and how difficult the task ended up being, and reflect on the reasons for the differences between their forecasts and “actuals.” This practice allowed employees to look back on their recorded predictions, reflect on what the record showed in comparison to their perceptions, and fine-tune their ability to paint an accurate picture of their efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Initially, the data showed that women were more accurate in their estimations of the time a task would take, although they often overestimated the difficulty of tasks. Meanwhile, men underestimated both the time a task would take and its difficulty. Following the intervention, the likelihood of women accurately identifying the difficulty of the task increased by a factor of 28, while men were 12.5 times more likely to do so. Additionally, men became 7 times more likely to accurately estimate the time required for a task, whereas there was no significant difference in this aspect for women.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Proximity bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;An other form of bias I observed was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/employee-relations/pages/preventing-proximity-bias-in-a-hybrid-workplace.aspx&quot;>;&lt;em>;proximity bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; or the tendency to think that people who are in your physical orbit do the most important work. A hybrid work environment exacerbates this bias and was penalizing women at HAPI Consulting, where men were more likely than women to come into the office. Reviewers tended to express skepticism, or at least confusion, about what women did when they worked remotely, whereas they tended to give men the benefit of the doubt and assume that they were more focused and productive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even when women came into the office as often as men, reviewers assigned them achievement levels that were a statistically significant 3% lower than those they assigned to the men. And when women came into the office more than men, reviewers seemed to believe that they were doing so only because they were looking out for themselves and wanted to “have a seat at the table” to defend their position in the reorganization of the company. Conversely, when men came into the office an above-average amount, they were seen as strong leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address this problem of proximity bias, I administered a survey to employees to gauge their preferences among several choices: more online gatherings, an “anchor day” when everybody was expected to be in the office, or more offsite team-building opportunities. The employees&#39; preference was that the company create an anchor day, which it did. This intervention led to a statistically significant drop in proximity bias that was observable in the next performance-review cycle. In addition to having employees post their current projects on a virtual whiteboard each week, teams were also asked to hold weekly meetings during which they would discuss three achievements from the previous week, their goals for the current week, and three challenges they were facing in trying to achieve them. By drawing more equal attention to the work that everybody was doing, no matter where they did it, these meetings helped the company resist proximity bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;In-group/out-group bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The third form of bias that was creeping into remote-work performance evaluations was &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2000-08465-006&quot;>;&lt;em>;in-group/out-group bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; or giving preferential treatment to people you feel belong to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11752497/&quot;>;group you identify with&lt;/a>;. Not surprisingly, employees who were working remotely, and particularly those who had moved away from the office and across state lines, were increasingly seen as members of the out-group — and they had annual performance review scores that were lower by an average of 20%. Benefits would accrue to those in the in-group, including vertical promotions, horizontal promotions (providing employees with new opportunities to learn new skills and take on more prized tasks that would position them well for vertical promotions), and bonuses, such as equity shares in the company. Both men and women were subject to this form of bias, but because men tend to be seen more readily as leaders, they were more easily able to join the in-group than women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To increase a sense of belonging, the company launched a campaign called “I am HAPI Consulting, We are HAPI Consulting.” One element of the campaign asked employees to answer simple, sometimes silly questions so that teams could come to know the commonalities among them. For example, when providing updates at meetings, employees might also have to tack on the answer to the question, “Dog or cat?” or “What is on your bucket list this year?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Questions like these provided some memorable moments that everyone could share, no matter whether they worked in the office or remotely, and they allowed more people to experience in-group moments. Strikingly, this practice led to a 14% increase in feelings of belonging to the in-group, and a 17% increase in employees&#39; perceptions of which &lt;em>;other&lt;/em>; employees belong to the in-group. At performance-review time, reviewers were also asked to recall one thing they had in common with the person they were about to review. We found that this simple intervention, which meant that reviews began from a point of commonality, decreased the gender discrimination in the company&#39;s performance reviews by several percentage points.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Men and women often experience the workplace differently, whether in-person or virtually. To include and support the best talent for your company in a dynamic environment, it&#39;s important to take a careful look at the data, be alert to the three kinds of biases discussed in this article, and identify practices that are leading you to overvalue the efforts of certain groups. The insights you gain from doing so will not only help you treat women more fairly but also will lead to fewer predictable surprises, more productive work hours, and increased efficiency in smoothly leading teams — and your company — to success.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[28 Questions to Ask Your Boss in Your One-on-Ones]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1398880959.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;NicoElNino/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Good one-on-one meetings between managers and their direct reports address the practical and personal needs of the employee, benefitting their performance, growth, and well-being, as well as the success of their team and the broader organization. However, since managers are typically the ones who run these meetings, the employee&amp;#8217;s needs are often forgotten. Then it&amp;#8217;s up to the employee to ask questions to get the attention they need. The authors&amp;#8217; research points to twenty-eight questions that can drive the best conversations.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When she started a new role, Brianna was told she would be having regular one-on-one meetings (1:1s) with her manager, Jayden. She welcomed this news; she saw it as a great opportunity to get aligned with and supported and mentored by her new boss. But her hopes were quickly dashed. In their initial meeting, Jayden focused only on project updates and then assigned her a few additional tasks. This pattern continued over the weeks and Brianna routinely left their meetings feeling both micro-managed and unsupported in her development.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This story is, sadly, a composite of many we have heard from employees in our research on 1:1s between managers and their direct reports. As one of us (Steve) described in a new book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Glad-Met-Art-Science-Meetings/dp/0197641873&quot;>;&lt;em>;Glad We Met: The Art and Science of 1:1 Meetings&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;,&lt;/em>; a good one-on-one meeting addresses both the practical and personal needs of the employee (practical: information, instruction, alignment; personal: the need to be treated with consideration, respect, trust, and support). As such, these meetings are a critical source of growth and support for the employee and promote the thriving and success of teams and the broader organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But these benefits are only realized when the meeting includes frequent conversations that &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/make-the-most-of-your-one-on-one-meetings&quot;>;address those employee needs&lt;/a>;. And as 1:1s are typically facilitated by managers, they often devolve into addressing what is front of mind for them, rather than the employee. That&#39;s especially true because it is very rare for managers to receive training on how to run these meetings well, so they often simply recycle dysfunctional practices they themselves have experienced.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are in Brianna&#39;s position — if your boss&#39;s approach to your 1:1s has left you feeling unsupported and unheard — you should feel empowered to direct the conversation toward your needs yourself. You can do this by asking smart questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Questions to Ask&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Based on published research as well as data we collected from nearly 200 employees on important topics to broach in a 1:1, we have identified 28 key questions in seven broad categories to help you get the most value from your check-ins with your boss. You can use, adapt, and put these into your own voice as you see fit.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Ask for Guidance and Input&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Use these questions to get help from your manager on any tasks or projects you are having difficulty with, or to express your need for additional resources, input, or support.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;I am having some challenges and struggles with X. Can you help me think about how to navigate and address X successfully?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Could you suggest any ideas and thoughts around how I could get more support (people, time, funding) to help with Y?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What do you think of my idea Z? Do you have any suggestions for how to improve it? Or, might you have an alternative idea I should consider?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Clarify Priorities and Expectations&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To be sure you are on track and working efficiently, make sure you and your manager are on the same page. Ask for clarification on what tasks need your most focused attention from their point of view.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;4&quot;>; &lt;li>;Given what is on my plate, what should I be prioritizing right now, and can you help me understand why?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you review my workload, am I taking on on the right projects and tasks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Am I on track for meeting my goals and your expectations from your perspective? Is any any refocusing necessary?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there any context I might be missing about the projects I am working on? For example, what is the reasoning for doing project X?&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Align with the Organization and Its Strategy&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Ask questions to understand how your role relates to the broader strategic goals of the organization and the way its leaders are thinking about the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;8&quot;>; &lt;li>;What is going on further up the tree (or in other parts of the organization) that would be helpful for me to know as I work on my key tasks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To better help me understand the big picture, how does the work I&#39;m doing or the assignment you just gave me fit into the broader goals and strategy?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything that the management team is working on or considering that you think I should know about at present given its potential impact on my role?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is new in our strategic priorities as a company that you feel I should know about, if anything?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Seek Growth Opportunities and Career Advancement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Come to the meeting with your thinking (however inchoate) around your professional short-term and long-term goals and ask your manager what steps you should take to get there.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;12&quot;>; &lt;li>;I would value your counsel. What can I do to prepare myself for greater opportunities or to pursue X interest of mine?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you reflect on where the organization is going, do you have any thoughts on how I should improve and develop to best align?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What strengths do you think I have and how might they be helpful in the future?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;From your perspective, what should I be targeting as my next career move and why do you recommend that position?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How can we make sure that my skillset is put to the best use to support the team and the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How can we make sure that my full potential is achieved?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Get Feedback on Your Performance&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Check in with your manager to see how you are doing, performance-wise. You shouldn&#39;t make every meeting into an official performance evaluation, but it is important to periodically check in and calibrate if your manager isn&#39;t doing that themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;18&quot;>; &lt;li>;Am I meeting your expectations? I would relish learning your perspective on my work performance.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What feedback might you be able to share with me about how I&#39;m doing at X or Y task?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Do you feel I have any spots I&#39;m overlooking when it comes to A or B?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you reflect on what I do at work, what should I start, stop, or continue doing?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Build a Relationship&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Your 1:1 is a critical place for you to build and nurture your relationship with your manager. Allocate time at the beginning or end of the meeting to connect with your manager personally.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;22&quot;>; &lt;li>;How is your day going?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How are things going for you overall? Are you doing ok?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is something you are excited about outside of work?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything you would like to know about me? (If needed, be prepared to say “I don&#39;t feel comfortable sharing that, but here&#39;s something else you should know about me.”)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Offer Support&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Consider ways in which you can help your manager achieve their goals and fulfill their role. Managers need assistance, reassurance, and support to optimize their efficiency and performance. Just like you&#39;d expect your manager to support you, see how you can lend them a hand. This will also increase the chances of you getting what you need in the 1:1.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;26&quot;>; &lt;li>;What are your priorities over the next X days? What can I do to help you with this?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Where can I offer you support?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything keeping you up at night that I can help with?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to Use the Questions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;For each 1:1 meeting, pick a category or two to focus on. You can&#39;t address them all in every meeting, so you will need to rotate or pick the most relevant at a given time. Likewise, choose sparingly from among the questions — no need to ask them all at one time. You&#39;ll simply want to sample from all categories over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Don&#39;t hesitate to follow up on your manager&#39;s responses to your questions. A great follow-up is often simply “why?” You&#39;ll glean strategic insights into the rationale, motives, assumptions, and big picture behind your day-to-day work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Good 1:1 meetings with your manager are critical for your success and the success of your team and organization. Asking the right questions to make sure those meetings give you what you need can have a huge impact on your work experience — helping you stay engaged, developing your understanding of your role and place in the organization, and improving your relationship with your manager — not to mention enhancing your well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies That Replace People with AI Will Get Left Behind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1300035600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;piranka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies are integrating AI into their operations so quickly that job losses are likely to mount before the gains arrive. White-collar workers might be especially vulnerable in the short-term.The speed of this adoption presents an opportunity for companies to step up their pace of innovation, however &amp;#8212; and if enough companies to go on offensive, then we won&amp;#8217;t have to worry about AI unemployment. Adopting a bias for boldness and a startup mentality will help companies find the agility to make the most of this moment, and protect jobs as a result.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;After much discussion, the debate over job displacement from artificial intelligence is settling into a consensus. Historically, we&#39;ve never experienced macro-level unemployment from new technologies, so AI is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/long-run-ai-job-creator-destroyer-babak-pahlavan%3FtrackingId=6uoHh%252F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%253D%253D/?trackingId=6uoHh%2F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%3D%3D&quot;>;unlikely to make&lt;/a>; many people jobless in the long term — &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/05/24/artificial-intelligence-ai-eric-schmidt-demographic-crisis-babies-labor-shortage/&quot;>;especially since&lt;/a>; most advanced countries are now seeing their working-age populations decline. However, because companies are adopting ChatGPT and other generative AI remarkably fast, we may see &lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/podcast/ripple-effect/rise-of-ai-are-robots-taking-our-jobs-lynn-wu/&quot;>;substantial job displacement in the short term&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Compare AI with the rise of electricity around the turn of the twentieth&amp;nbsp;century. It took factories decades to switch from steam-powered central driveshafts to electric motors for each machine. They had to reorganize their layout in order to take advantage of the new electric technology. The process happened slowly enough that the economy had time to adjust, only new factories adopting the motors at first. As electricity created new jobs, laid-off workers in steam-powered factories could move over. Greater wealth created entirely new industries to engage workers, along with higher expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Something similar happened with the spread of computing in the middle of the twentieth century. It went at a faster pace than electrification, but was still slow enough to prevent mass unemployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI is different because companies are integrating it into their operations so quickly that job losses are likely to mount before the gains arrive. White-collar workers might be especially vulnerable in the short-term. Indeed, commentators are describing an “AI gold rush” rather than a bubble, powered by advanced chipmakers such as Nvidia. Goldman Sachs &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65102150&quot;>;recently predicted&lt;/a>; that companies would use it to eliminate a quarter of all current work tasks in the United States and Europe. That probably means tens of millions of people out of work — especially people who thought their specialized knowledge &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-negative-impact-middle-class-white-collar-workers-2023-5?utm_medium=newsletter&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Insider%20Today%2C%20June%202%2C%202023&amp;amp;utm_term=INSIDER%20TODAY%20SEND%20LIST%20-%20ALL%20ENGAGED&quot;>;gave them job security&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That leaves two possibilities to mitigate this risk. The first is that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/23/business/jobs-protections-artificial-intelligence.html&quot;>;governments step in&lt;/a>;, either to slow down the commercial adoption of AI (highly unlikely), or to offer special welfare programs to support and retrain the newly unemployed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there&#39;s another, often neglected possibility that comes without the unintended consequences of governmental intervention. Some companies are rapidly integrating generative AI into their systems, not just to automate tasks, but to empower employees to do more than they could before — ie, making them more productive. A &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-ai-is-helping-companies-redesign-processes&quot;>;radical redesign&lt;/a>; of corporate processes could spark all sorts of new value creation. If many companies do this, then as a society we&#39;ll generate enough new jobs to escape the short-term displacement trap.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But will they? Even the least aggressive company tends to be pretty good about cutting costs. Innovation, however, is another matter. We didn&#39;t worry about this in the past, because we had enough time for a few aggressive companies to gradually change industries. They innovated over time to make up for the slow loss of displaced jobs. That innovation created new jobs and kept unemployment low. But macroeconomically speaking, we don&#39;t have the luxury of time with the AI transition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So the alternative to relying on the government is to have many companies innovating fast enough to create new jobs at the same pace that the economy as a whole eliminates existing ones. Generative AI is spreading fast in business and society, but that speed also means an opportunity for companies to step up their pace of innovation. If we get enough companies to go on offense in this way, then we won&#39;t have to worry about AI unemployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, companies won&#39;t — and shouldn&#39;t — lean into AI in order to solve macroeconomic problems. But fortunately they have good business reasons to do so. The companies that create opportunities from AI will also position themselves to thrive in the long run.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Going on the Offensive with AI&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Already we can point to aggressive companies looking to innovate in AI. Having become a trailblazer in reusable rockets and electric cars, Elon Musk is now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/twitter-elon-musk-linda-yaccarino-spacex-244f0125?mod=series_elonmuskcompanies&quot;>;promising to make&lt;/a>; Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-wants-to-see-an-ai-rival-to-google-microsoft-a299e27f?mod=hp_lista_pos1&quot;>;as much of a leader&lt;/a>; in AI as Microsoft and Google. Musk, however, is &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/does-elon-musk-have-a-strategy&quot;>;a famous outlier&lt;/a>; and the jury is still out on Twitter. So what does it mean for a company to go on offense with AI?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To answer this question, let&#39;s look at what makes companies adept at navigating the kinds of changes we&#39;re seeing now. One of us (Tabrizi) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Going-Offense-Playbook-Perpetual-Innovation/dp/1646871375/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679313&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;>;assembled a team&lt;/a>; of researchers to study 26 sizable companies with good data from 2006–2022. The team divided the companies into groups of high, medium, and low agility and innovation over time, with comparable data and case studies of each.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What set the agile, innovative companies apart from those who remained neutral or defensive? The team narrowed the differentiators down to eight drivers of agile innovation: existential purpose, obsession with what customers want, a Pygmalion-style influence over colleagues, a startup mindset even after scaling up, a bias for boldness, radical collaboration, the readiness to control tempo, and operating bimodally. Most leaders praise those attributes, but it turns out it&#39;s remarkably hard for big organizations to sustain any of them over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tabrizi has written &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/how-microsoft-became-innovative-again&quot;>;elsewhere&lt;/a>; about how Microsoft went on offense to become a corporate leader by overhauling its hierarchy and pursuing partnerships such as with Open AI. But other companies have done something similar with AI as a result of those drivers. Let&#39;s focus on two of the most important drivers here — the bias for boldness and the startup mentality. Getting those drivers in place can take a company far into agile innovation, because these force changes throughout the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Bias for Boldness&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Any company that invests in AI in the near future is likely to make money from it. Yet mere investment is likely to offer only incremental gains. The numbers might look good, especially in cutting costs. But the company will miss the opportunity for big gains by creating substantial value — or a defensible future niche. Cautious investment won&#39;t protect you in the long run from competition, and certainly won&#39;t help us with the macroeconomic challenge we&#39;re facing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s the problem with any new technology: You can proceed cautiously and probably do just fine. Big companies hate risk, &lt;a href=&quot;/2000/03/meeting-the-challenge-of-disruptive-change&quot;>;which is why&lt;/a>; they operate as well-oiled machines churning out reliable products at an affordable cost. That&#39;s also why many of them outsource their innovation by acquiring startups — and even that approach often leads to timid improvements. All successful organizations, especially at size, prefer to minimize risk and daring. But as Brené Brown &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Rising-Strong-Reckoning-Rumble-Revolution/dp/0812995821/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679119&amp;amp;sr=1-7&quot;>;points out&lt;/a>;, “You can choose courage, or you can choose comfort, but you cannot choose both.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boldness has become a corporate cliché, with leaders protesting too much, but with AI we need companies to really mean it — to embrace rather than minimize risk. Take Adobe, whose Photoshop program has long held the largest share of the photographic design market. Adobe could have played it safe as generative AI emerged, adopting it in small areas while waiting to see how the technology worked out. That&#39;s what Kodak did with digital photography, and what Motorola did with digital telephony. But instead, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/search/results/content/?fromMember=%5B%22ACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ%22%5D&amp;amp;heroEntityKey=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_profile%3AACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ&amp;amp;keywords=jj%20delgado%F0%9F%A4%99&amp;amp;position=0&amp;amp;searchId=a8067e47-50fe-43fd-a269-0d80da62e1f5&amp;amp;sid=8k2&amp;amp;update=urn%3Ali%3Afs_updateV2%3A(urn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A7066792598446743552%2CBLENDED_SEARCH_FEED%2CEMPTY%2CDEFAULT%2Cfalse)&quot;>;Adobe has pushed&lt;/a>; generative AI deeply into Photoshop, to the point that ordinary users can create all sorts of videos they couldn&#39;t before. Adobe could have seen AI as a threat or distraction, and it has continued to improve Photoshop without AI. But its leaders had the courage to invest aggressively in AI to elevate what users can do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deeper in the technology, Nvidia, the chipmaker, has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-06-03/chips-inside-nvidia-s-30-year-ride-to-overnight-ai-success?sref=bsFVYL6k&quot;>;getting headlines&lt;/a>; for offering the best semiconductor chips for AI. To outsiders, the company might just seem lucky, with the right technology at the right time. But Nvidia&#39;s current success is no accident: In the past decade, it aggressively acquired and developed expertise in AI, including creating customized chips and software. We can expect that aggressiveness to continue, enabling not only higher-value offerings for Nvidia, but better uses for AI than simple cost-cutting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boldness won&#39;t work every time. But a bias for boldness is essential to overcome the deep-seated risk aversion in corporate hierarchies.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Startup Mentality&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Similar to boldness, and equally important for successful AI, is adopting the mentality of a startup company, no matter your company&#39;s age or size. Startups excel in looking widely at markets and pivoting quickly to what customers are wanting now. Big companies have the resources to apply to those opportunities, but they usually move so slowly, with so many barriers (and lack of boldness), that startups get to markets faster. Open AI, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johanmoreno/2022/12/29/openai-positioned-itself-as-the-ai--leader-in-2022-but-could-google-supersede-it-in-23/?sh=b69aaa953216&quot;>;beat out&lt;/a>; Google with ChatGPT, had the best of both worlds: a startup mentality free of the hesitations that hampered Google, but with ample resources supplied by Microsoft and other investors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The startup mindset is not just about courage and flexibility; it also involves a ferocious commitment to big achievement, a kind of hero&#39;s journey to address a great challenge. Instead of predictability churning out good products at scale — though that&#39;s a perfectly worthwhile goal — startups want to create something extraordinary. So they put a premium on looking around, flexibly partnering with others. They dispense with existing structures and biases, no matter how old and respected, in order to get done what needs to be done.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Amazon, the e-commerce giant, demonstrated a startup mentality in its embrace of AI. As the technology developed over a decade ago, the company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/how-amazon-made-alexa-smarter/&quot;>;saw an opportunity&lt;/a>; in creating a “smart speaker” as a new interface to the web. Amazon had no expertise in AI, but it picked up what it needed through hiring, acquisition, and internal development. The result was the Echo speaker and Alexa digital assistant, which did far more than simply help people order more items for purchase. It opened a new channel for adding value (and jobs) in many areas. Amazon has gone on to invest aggressively in AI beyond Alexa, with CEO Andy Jassy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/amazons-alexa-head-defends-companys-work-on-ai-amid-chatgpt-boom.html&quot;>;saying&lt;/a>; the technology promises to “transform and improve virtually every customer experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies can&#39;t adopt these drivers overnight, but they can start moving toward a point of serious commitment to new possibilities. Most of those drivers also work at the level of individuals looking for purpose and achievement in their own careers. They can embrace boldness, adopt a startup mentality, and other imperatives. Like companies, employees can invest aggressively in AI by acquiring the requisite skills and experience — thereby not just protecting their careers, but adding value &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-boom-share-profits-workers-productivity-wages-2023-5?inline-endstory-related-recommendations=&quot;>;at a higher level&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of corporate life has quite properly been about churning out reliable products at low cost. What we need now, to prevent mass unemployment, is for many firms to break out of this discipline and speed up the AI future. The great danger is that most companies will play it safe, make the easy investments, and do fine in the short term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Humanity never thrives when it fears innovation. Imagine if the first humans feared fire; yes, they got burned sometimes, but without harnessing the power of it, we might have gone extinct. We think the same applies to AI. Rather than fear it, we need to harness its power. We must put it in the hands of every human being, so we collectively can achieve and live at this higher level.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Your New Leadership Role with the End in Mind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_22_Carlo_Cadenas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Carlo Cadenas&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To successfully step into a new role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance &amp;#8220;now-forward&amp;#8221; planning with &amp;#8220;future-back&amp;#8221; visioning. That is, you must start with the end in mind, envisioning what you want to accomplish during this era of your leadership and what needs to happen before for can take the next step. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When taking on a new leadership role, it&#39;s&amp;nbsp;natural to focus on the immediate challenges of making a successful transition, including accelerating your learning, building relationship with stakeholders, and securing early wins. However, it is essential to complement this “now-forward” planning with “future-back” thinking about your desired destination and what it will take to get there. As Stephen Covey expressed in his best-selling book, &lt;em>;The Seven Habits of Highly Effective People&lt;/em>;, you want to “start with the end in mind.” This means envisioning what you want to accomplish in the new role so you will be ready to move beyond it and then working backward to map out how you will get there. In so doing, you can shape your early actions to lay the foundation for long-term success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The starting point is to engage in what Dan Ciampa, the noted executive coach, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.danciampa.com/more-designated-successors.php&quot;>;defined as “era planning&lt;/a>;.” Your era is the anticipated duration of time you think you will be in the new position. Of course, you may end up staying longer or leaving earlier, but try to make a rough guess about when you will have accomplished enough to be “done.” You&#39;ll want to ask yourself two key questions: “As I wrap up this job, what will be true?” and “What will be possible?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Envisioning &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Your Leadership Legacy &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first question — “What will be true?”&amp;nbsp;— asks you to outline the legacy you aspire to create and the story you will tell about your achievements. Focus on what you want to be remembered for in your new position and what you want your team and peers to say about your leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider key areas such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Performance outcomes:&lt;/strong>; What are the tangible results — for example, in terms of increased productivity or profitability — you will achieve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Organizational transformation:&lt;/strong>; How will you reshape the team and its culture?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Innovation:&lt;/strong>; What will you do to foster creativity and develop new areas for growth?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Talent development:&lt;/strong>; How will you hire and train people to take the organization into the future?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Distill these into a concise, written personal narrative. Then, think about what you need to do, starting now, to realize this legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Creating&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>; Future Possibilities &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second question — “What will be possible?” — encourages you to envision futures beyond your current role and strategize the steps you&#39;ll take to turn them into viable options. This process involves identifying multiple potential paths forward and pinpointing the skills you&#39;ll need to acquire and the connections you&#39;ll need to establish over the course of this era to make those viable options. By exploring different scenarios and actively planning your development, you&#39;ll be better equipped to adapt and seize emerging opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take these steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Create a list of potential futures, considering logical next steps in your organization and your industry, as well as less conventional but still attractive options that would take you in different directions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Assess whether there are skill gaps you need to close to achieve some or all of those futures by reflecting on your existing strengths and areas for improvement.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Identify the bridges — the steps and connections — that would allow you to transition from your current role to your desired future options. These might include expanding your professional network, deepening your industry knowledge, or engaging in what Ken Banta and Orlan Boston &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/the-strategic-side-gig&quot;>;described as “strategic side gigs&lt;/a>;,” such as teaching or working on boards of directors.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Develop a plan for how you&#39;ll acquire the skills and build the bridges to make the potential futures you have identified realistic options, setting specific goals and holding yourself accountable for achieving them.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As Peter Drucker said, “The best way to predict the future is to create it.” By imagining multiple potential futures and working toward them, you&#39;ll create real options for yourself when you&#39;re ready to move on from your current role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To successfully step into a new leadership role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance “now-forward” planning with “future-back” visioning. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Roles Could Generative AI Play on Your Team?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_22_1273134318.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Normform/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The recent advances in ChatGPT are merely the first application of new AI technologies. As such, companies and leaders need to think about the various applications outlined here and use the framework described in the article to develop applications for your own company or organization. In the process, they will discover new types of GPTs. By classifying these different GPTs in terms of potential value to businesses and the cost of developing them, applications that begin with a single human initiating or participating in the interaction (GroupGPT, CoachGPT) will probably be the easiest to build and should generate substantial business value, making them the perfect initial candidates. In contrast, applications with interactions involving multiple entities or those initiated by machines (AutoGPT, BossGPT, and ImperialGPT) may be harder to implement, with trickier ethical and legal implications.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The frenzy surrounding the launch of Large Language Models (LLMs) and other types of Generative AI (GenAI) isn&#39;t going to fade anytime soon. Users of GenAI are discovering and recommending new and interesting use cases for their business and personal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/04/14/upshot/up-ai-uses.html&quot;>;lives&lt;/a>;. Many recommendations start with the assumption that GenAI requires a human prompt. Indeed, &lt;em>;Time&lt;/em>; magazine recently proclaimed “prompt engineering” to be the next hot job, &lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/6272103/ai-prompt-engineer-job/&quot;>;with salaries reaching $335,000&lt;/a>;. Tech forums and educational websites are focusing on prompt engineering, with Udemy already offering a course &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.udemy.com/course/master-prompt-engineering-with-chatgpt&quot;>;on the topic&lt;/a>;, and several organizations we work with are now beginning to invest considerable resources in training employees on how best to use ChatGPT.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, it may be worth pausing to consider other ways of interacting with GPT technologies, which are likely to emerge soon. We present an intuitive way to think about this issue, which is based on our own survey of GenAI developments, combined with conversations with companies that are seeking to develop some versions of these.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Framework of GPT Interactions&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A good starting point is to distinguish between who is &lt;em>;involved in the interaction&lt;/em>; — individuals, groups of people, or another machine — and &lt;em>;who starts the interaction,&lt;/em>; human or machine. This leads to six different types of GenAI uses, shown below. ChatGPT, where one human initiates interaction with the machine is already well-known. We now describe each of the other GPTs and outline their potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;CoachGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;is a personal assistant that provides you with a set of suggestions on managing your daily life. It would base these suggestions not on explicit prompts from you, but on the basis of observing what you do and your environment. For example, it could observe you as an executive and note that you find it hard to build trust in your team; it could then recommend precise actions to overcome this blind spot. It could also come up with personalized advice on development options or even salary negotiations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CoachGPT would subsequently see which recommendations you adopted or didn&#39;t adopt, and which benefited you and which ones didn&#39;t to improve its advice over time. With time, you would get a highly personalized AI advisor, coach, or consultant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations could adopt CoachGPT to advise customers on how to use a product, whether a construction company offering CoachGPT to advise end users on how best to use its equipment, or an accounting firm proffering real-time advice on how best to account for a set of transactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To make CoachGPT effective, individuals and organizations would have to allow it to work in the background, monitoring online and offline activities. Clearly, serious privacy considerations need to be addressed before we entrust our innermost thoughts to the system. However, the potential for positive outcomes in both private and professional lives is immense.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;GroupGPT &lt;/strong>;would be a bona fide group member that can observe interactions between group members and contribute to the discussion. For example, it could conduct fact checking, supply a summary of the conversation, suggest what to discuss next, play the role of devil&#39;s advocate, provide a competitor perspective, stress-test the ideas, or even propose a creative solution to the problem at hand.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The requests could come from individual group members or from the team&#39;s boss, who need not participate in team interactions, but merely seeks to manage, motivate, and evaluate group members. The contribution could be delivered to the whole group or to specific individuals, with adjustments for that person&#39;s role, skill, or personality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The privacy concerns mentioned above also apply to GroupGPT, but, if addressed, organizations could take advantage of GroupGPT by using it for project management, especially on long and complicated projects involving relatively large teams across different departments or regions. Since GroupGPT would overcome human limitations on information storage and processing capacity, it would be ideal for supporting complex and dispersed teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;BossGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;takes an active role in advising a group of people on what they could or should do, without being prompted. It could provide individual recommendations to group members, but its real value emerges when it begins to coordinate the work of group members, telling them as a group who should do what to maximize team output. BossGPT could also step in to offer individual coaching and further recommendations as the project and team dynamics evolve.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The algorithms necessary for BossGPT to work would be much more complicated as they would have to consider somewhat unpredictable individual and group reactions to instructions from a machine, but it could have a wide range of uses. For example: an executive changing job could request a copy of her reactions to her first organization&#39;s BossGPT instructions, which could then be used to assess how she would fit into the new organization — and the new organization-specific BossGPT.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the organizational level companies could deploy BossGPT to manage people, thereby augmenting — or potentially even replacing — existing managers. Similarly, BossGPT has tremendous applications in coordinating work across organizations and managing complex supply chains or multiple suppliers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies could turn BossGPT into a product, offering their customers AI solutions to help them manage their business. These solutions could be natural extensions of the CoachGPT examples described earlier. For example, a company selling construction equipment could offer BossGPT to coordinate many end users on a construction site, and an accounting firm could provide it to coordinate the work of many employees of its customers to run the accounting function in the most efficient way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AutoGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;entails a human giving a request or prompt to one machine, which in turn engages other machines to complete the task. In its simplest form, a human might instruct a machine to complete a task, but the machine realizes that it lacks a specific software to execute it, so it would search for the missing software on Google before downloading and installing it, and then using it &lt;a href=&quot;https://autogpt.net/auto-gpt-vs-chatgpt-how-do-they-differ-and-everything-you-need-to-know/&quot;>;to finish the request&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a more complicated version, humans could give AutoGPT a goal (such as creating the best viral YouTube video) and instruct it to interact with another GenAI to iteratively come up with the best ChatGPT prompt to achieve the goal. The machine would then launch the process by proposing a prompt to another machine, then evaluate the outcome, and adjust the prompt to get closer and closer to the final goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the most complicated version, AutoGPT could draw on functionalities of the other GPTs described above. For example, a team leader could task a machine with maximizing both the effectiveness and job satisfaction of her team members. AutoGPT could then switch between coaching individuals through CoachGPT, providing them with suggestions for smoother team interactions through GroupGPT, while at the same time issuing specific instructions on what needs to be done through BossGPT. AutoGPT could subsequently collect feedback from each activity and adjust all the other activities to reach the given goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike the above versions, which are still to be created, a version of AutoGPT has been developed and was rolled out in April 2023, and it&#39;s quickly gaining broad acceptance. The technology is still not perfect and requires improvements, but it is already evident that AutoGPT is able to complete a set of jobs that requires the completion of several tasks one after the other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We see its biggest applications in complex tasks, such as supply chain coordination, but also in fields such as cybersecurity. For example, organizations could prompt AutoGPT to continually address any cybersecurity vulnerabilities, which would entail looking for them — which already happens — but then instead of simply flagging them, AutoGPT would search for solutions to the threats or write its own patches to counter them. A human might still be in the loop, but since the system is self-generative within these limits, we believe that AutoGPT&#39;s response is likely to be faster and more efficient.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ImperialGPT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;is the most abstract GenAI — and perhaps the most transformational — in which two or more machines would interact with each other, direct each other, and ultimately direct humans to engage in a course of action. This type of GPT worries most AI analysts, who fear losing control of AI and AI “going rogue.” We concur with these concerns, particularly if — as now — there are no strict guardrails on what AI is allowed to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the same time, if ImperialGPT is allowed to come up with ideas and share them with humans, but its ability to act on the ideas is restricted, we believe that this could generate extremely interesting creative solutions especially for “unknown unknowns,” where human knowledge and creativity fall short. They could then easily envision and game out multiple black swan events and worst-case scenarios, complete with potential costs and outcomes, to provide possible solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the potential dangers of ImperialGPT, and the need for tight regulation, we believe that ImperialGPT will be slow to take off, at least commercially. We do anticipate, however, that governments, intelligence services, and the military will be interested in deploying ImperialGPT under strictly controlled conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Implications for your Business&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;So, what does our framework mean for companies and organizations around the world? First and foremost, we encourage you to step back and see the recent advances in ChatGPT as merely the first application of new AI technologies. Second, we urge you to think about the various applications outlined here and use our framework to develop applications for your own company or organization. In the process, we are sure you will discover new types of GPTs that we have not mentioned. Third, we suggest you classify these different GPTs in terms of potential value to your business, and the cost of developing them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We believe that applications that begin with a single human initiating or participating in the interaction (GroupGPT, CoachGPT) will probably be the easiest to build and should generate substantial business value, making them the perfect initial candidates. In contrast, applications with interactions involving multiple entities or those initiated by machines (AutoGPT, BossGPT, and ImperialGPT) may be harder to implement, with trickier ethical and legal implications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You might also want to start thinking about the complex ethical, legal, and regulatory concerns that will arise with each GPT type. Failure to do so exposes you and your company to both legal liabilities and — perhaps more importantly — an unintended negative effect on humanity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our next set of recommendations depends on your company type. A tech company or startup, or one that has ample resources to invest in these technologies, should start working on developing one or more of the GPTs discussed above. This is clearly a high-risk, high-reward strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In contrast, if your competitive strength is not in GenAI or if you lack resources, you might be better off adopting a “wait and see” approach. This means you will be slow to adopt the current technology, but you will not waste valuable resources on what may turn out to be only an interim version of a product. Instead, you can begin preparing your internal systems to better capture and store data as well as readying your organization to embrace these new GPTs, in terms of both work processes and culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The launch and rapid adoption of GenAIs is rightly being considered as the next level in the evolution of AI and a potentially epochal moment for humanity in general. Although GenAIs represent breakthroughs in solving fundamental engineering and computer science problems, they do not automatically guarantee value creation for all organizations. Rather, smart companies will need to invest in modifying and adapting the core technology before figuring out the best way to monetize the innovations. Firms that do this right may indeed strike it rich in the GenAI goldrush.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Leadership Teams Navigate Uncertain Times]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_21_816813440.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While we don&amp;#8217;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&amp;#8217;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&amp;#8217;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand &amp;#8212; and reward &amp;#8212; high-performing leadership teams. Based on his conversations with more than 100 clients across industries, PWC US Chair and Senior Partner Tim Ryan has identified seven factors that set these teams apart: 1) They create a &amp;#8220;company-first&amp;#8221; culture; 2) They think and act across the enterprise; 3) They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business; 4) They free up the right people for the hard stuff; 5) They&amp;#8217;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills; 6) They encourage healthy debate, but avoid undermining fellow leaders; and 7) They strive to be humble and objective.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Whether it&#39;s inflation, rising interest rates, supply-chain disruptions, geopolitical tensions — there is a lot happening in the global economy. And on top of those forces, consumer expectations are increasing, competition is intense and investors are raising the bar. There&#39;s never been a more challenging time to be a CEO or member of senior management.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the complexities, it is no surprise that some companies are performing exceptionally well, a lot are doing just ok and there are others struggling to keep up. Based on my latest discussions with more than 100 clients across industries, what I&#39;ve seen is that the outperforming companies have leadership teams with the following seven factors in common:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They create a “company-first” culture.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Senior leadership teams are typically made up of individuals who are highly skilled in their domain — but what&#39;s different at high-performing companies is these leaders embrace a company-first culture. This means doing what&#39;s right for the business and your people, instead of driving individual agendas or objectives. One CEO of a high-performing industrial company shared that being part of his leadership team is like being on a sports team: “The team comes first, not the star individual.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They think and act across the enterprise&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-performing teams recognize that their role extends beyond the individual unit they manage, and they operate across silos. One CEO of a leading digital bank shared with me that his team&#39;s enterprise-focused mindset drove a reimagined customer experience resulting in industry-leading efficiency ratios. They achieved this by sharing data across the enterprise and committing to one set of data governance rules.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Too often CEOs and senior leadership focus the majority of their time on running the business, while the portfolio and business-model reinvention takes a back seat. Strong companies are putting the bold reimagining of their business at the top of the agenda.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bold actions include running the business with unparalleled discipline, managing costs, simplifying wherever you can, and pulling on every lever to win. Taking bold action also involves reshaping portfolios while reinventing the back, middle and front offices—with a sense of urgency.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One CEO of a pharmaceutical company, who was looking to innovate and disrupt their industry, implemented a bold new business model powered by a cutting-edge commerce and marketplace platform in a matter of months. This resulted in a direct, better way to reach customers, increased margins, and greater trust and transparency across their entire value chain.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They free up the right people for the hard stuff. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Reinventing your business is a full-time job and needs dedicated minds who aren&#39;t also focused on managing other day jobs. High-performing leadership teams find the time to focus on the hard stuff and delegate the day-to-day operations to others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A CEO of a major energy company put one of his top business leaders in charge of their enterprise-wide business model transformation to both enable its success and send a clear message to all stakeholders of the importance of the transformation. While it&#39;s difficult to have a leader step away from the work they are doing to take on a transformation effort, the dedicated focus makes all the difference. The energy company&#39;s transformation leader has since positioned the company for significant value accretion and cost optimization through standardization and simplification, all while driving leadership commitment, organizational readiness and business outcome sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They&#39;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-quality teams are inclusive in all ways. This means inclusive of genders and ethnicities, but also of diverse views, backgrounds, and skill sets. It&#39;s critical to have a breadth of leaders in your C-suite that bring forth differentiated expertise and perspectives to enable an organization to innovate more robustly and accelerate transformations. It&#39;s why top leadership teams have a chief technology officer, chief people officer and chief communications officer at the table.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one instance, a CEO of a major technology company shared with me that too many companies lack a diversity of skills in the C-suite, particularly when it comes to technology. As a result, senior management might not be able to identify what the “art of the possible” is when transforming their business and how different tools, like emerging technologies, could help. In these cases, leadership teams focus on building a “faster horse and buggy”&#39; rather than reimagining what&#39;s next.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They encourage healthy debate but avoid undermining fellow leaders. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Good teams have healthy debates, transparently talk about pros and cons and explore alternatives together. Before transformation efforts begin, they spend a lot of time agreeing on the desired outcomes and business requirements of the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Getting leadership teams to engage in open, honest discussions is critical. One CEO of a major industrial company shared with me that she never imagined the amount of time she needed to spend helping her team “get along.” What I took from her comment is that leadership is about coaching the team to share their various points of view, challenge each other with healthy debate, and come together once a decision is made to row in the same direction.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They strive to be humble and objective. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Humility is critical at the CEO and senior levels of any company because it filters down to every level of the organization. It helps fight complacency. Most companies have a lot to be proud of, but if the focus is always on the success of the past instead of the opportunity for the future, other companies will quickly pass you by.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, some leaders struggle with objectively assessing their current performance and where their company and results truly stand. Leading companies are constantly challenging themselves and use objectivity to both drive performance, keep the competition in the rearview mirror and shareholder activists at bay.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I recently spoke with a CEO from a consumer technology company about the importance of having the right people on your company&#39;s board and the critical role the board plays in bringing an outside-in perspective. Board members are in the advantageous position to help the C-suite look around corners, prepare for potential challenges, and discover blind spots.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While we don&#39;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&#39;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&#39;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand — and reward — high-performing leadership teams. They&#39;ll drive outsized growth, increase shareholder value, and likely have a little more fun along the way — working together and sharing the successes of a team that is creating more value for their customers, employees, and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Brand-Influencer Partnerships Reach Gen Z]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1479691532.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Authenticity is among Gen Z&amp;#8217;s most important values. They feel empowered to ask and answer their own questions in a variety of social forums on any topic &amp;#8212; from beauty to health to home improvement to technology to science. And their view of authority has expanded from traditional sources, like academic institutions or reputable editorial voices, to perceived influence. The author offers five lessons for brands who want to tap into this era of influencers and make authentic connections with Gen Z.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;If you haven&#39;t heard about Alix Earle, it may simply be a matter of time. This young influencer — who just graduated from the University of Miami — has more than 5 million followers on TikTok and was recently signed by United Talent Agency (UTA), one of the top three firms that represent talent globally across the media and entertainment ecosystem. She has leveraged her personal brand to partner with beauty companies like Tarte and Rare Beauty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Watching the myriad of Alix Earle videos online makes her formula quite clear. She has model-like beauty, checking the box for sheer aesthetics. She&#39;s perfected the “get ready with me” (GRWM) format (among others), a short-form video in which she goes from natural beauty to flawless perfection, displaying professional yet replicable makeup techniques and product use. As she applies her look during “selfie” videos, she offers a mix of storytelling, humor, vulnerability, aspiration, relatability, and product mentions in a fast-talking, effortless monologue. She feels just approachable enough to be just another college student.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That approachability is why Earle resonates so much with Gen Z. Authenticity is among this generation&#39;s most important values. As &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-knowhttps:/www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-know&quot;>;recent EY research highlights&lt;/a>;: “After an era of fake news and filtered photos projecting the &#39;perfect life,&#39; Gen Z is over it.” They feel empowered to ask and answer their own questions in a variety of social forums on any topic — from beauty to health to home improvement to technology to science. And their view of authority has expanded from traditional sources, like academic institutions or reputable editorial voices, to perceived influence — as demonstrated by Earle&#39;s meteoric rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Studying Alix Earle&#39;s success offers brand marketers five powerful lessons for how to tap into this era of influencers — and make authentic connections with Gen Z.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Find the right influencers for your brand&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Simply force-ranking top influencer lists is not the answer. Brands want to find the person or people who reach their target audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once brands define the category in which they compete, marketers can look for the influencers who have the most engagement and who have a voice and style that resonates with the brand. AI and other tools to analyze data can help you figure this out — for example, data analytics can reveal followers, creative approaches, and communities in common between influencers and brands. There are also companies, from Gallery Media, for example, to leading talent agencies, who curate influencers and manage more complex relationships and execution for brands.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Create brand stories for mobile consumption&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gen Z fills their spare moments by scrolling through their algorithmically driven, personalized “for you” feeds on their phones, filled with photos, videos, and memes. Ideally, brands should empower the influencers they work with to create content that is short, compelling, and made for mobile.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Embracing vulnerability and openness, like Earle does in short one- to three-minute stories, enables brands to connect with younger generations in a way that&#39;s personally relevant and authentic. However, brands must understand that this is not a 30-second scripted television spot, and the influencers will take the story in a direction of their own choosing. This is a complement to other brand storytelling — not a replacement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Motivate consumers to make brand content their own&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unlike previous generations, Gen Z does not “broadcast” their posts to social networks writ large. They share more often with far fewer people via “private stories.” Engagement is much higher because of the frequency and the intimacy of these posts, and with this shift, we also see Gen Z moving away from prior generational behaviors of broadcasting their happy moments widely on their social media accounts to sharing more raw moments like personal crisis and tears in more private circles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A young person who sees a beauty product in a GRWM video from Earle on TikTok who subsequently endorses that product with their friend group in their private story on Snap is an example of how the brand journey goes from high-profile social media influence to deeply personal influence. A brand must earn the right to access this sacred space — and it must understand the opacity and new risks of these more personally intimate venues.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Cross boundaries to stand out&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s going to take new sources of inspiration and creativity to stand out as generative and conversational AI are applied in creative contexts at scale. As all influencers now have access to the same technology to drive research, enhance ideas, and accelerate production, forward-thinking brands will look to differentiate through human originality or true celebrity. The bar for real creativity will only get higher, requiring unorthodox juxtapositions of brands or new invitations to consumers to co-create. Our current definition of influence may shift rapidly as AI manipulates both the targeting and creative driving the algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Avoid clone culture&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As marketers, we may prize the opportunity to drive consumption at all costs by engineering trends to have velocity through influencers. But if we succeed too much on the science of it all, are we creating trend echo chambers that contradict our commitments to diversity and inclusion, or cloning repeat behaviors within certain social archetypes? And if influence relies on at least the veneer of originality, will it be harder as everyone uses similar AI-driven insights? Brands drive their commercial ambition with precision using a combination of creativity and data (or art and science), but increasingly, they may seek to broaden strategies to find new audiences, voices, and inspiration to diversify their base of consumers and ideas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The creator economy is thriving, creative, and valuable, particularly as technology-enabled economic models motivate strong talent to make it a true professional endeavor. Brands that harness its new dynamics to create value will differentiate themselves and drive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/cmo?WT.mc_id=14001454&amp;amp;AA.tsrc=pr&quot;>;exponential growth&lt;/a>;. The key to success is to lean into the newest sources of influence along with all the latest dynamics of risk and reward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;The views reflected in this article are the views of the author and do not necessarily reflect the views of Ernst &amp;amp; Young LLP or other members of the global EY organization.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Can Help Stressed-Out Managers Be Better Coaches]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_21_1433543804.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;SvetaZi/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The expectations placed on managers to assess and guide their employees&amp;#8217; performance have increased, a trend amplified by generational shifts and remote work. Employees want frequent, personalized, one-on-one coaching, but managers are constrained by their already heavy burdens. New AI tools show promise to improve the efficiency and effectiveness of managerial coaching &amp;#8212; but first, common sources of fear and mistrust must be overcome. Based on research and case studies, the authors present five steps to ensure the use of AI-assisted coaching enhances the lives of both managers and employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Middle managers are receiving pressure from their leaders to &lt;a href=&quot;https://workforceinstitute.org/our-2023-workplace-predictions/&quot;>;spend more time developing and coaching&lt;/a>; their direct reports. The pressure is also coming from below, as employee &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/all-things-work/pages/performance-management-evolves.aspx&quot;>;expectations have risen&lt;/a>; for real-time, personalized feedback, particularly among those early in their careers or who were onboarded remotely. The challenge is satisfying these demands without incurring even higher levels of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/357404/manager-burnout-getting-worse.aspx&quot;>;middle manager burnout and stress&lt;/a>;. Based on our research and advisory work, we foresee new AI tools making it easier for managers to provide high-quality coaching more efficiently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Employees want more coaching, but managers are out of capacity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;OC Tanner&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octanner.com/global-culture-report/2023/leadership-at-risk.html&quot;>;2023 Global Culture Survey&lt;/a>; found that leaders whose supervisory responsibilities — including training employees — had increased over the past year showed a 21% higher rate of anxiety, which increased the odds of burnout by a staggering 520%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the potential for overload, managers generally want to coach their employees because they know it&#39;s beneficial. In fact, managerial coaching has been shown to increase &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/01492063211003951&quot;>;job satisfaction&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://bpspsychub.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/joop.12402&quot;>;knowledge sharing&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/hrdq.21175&quot;>;performance&lt;/a>; — all outcomes that organizations (and managers!) want.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The AI opportunity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our review of the field indicates that AI-based managerial coaching is not yet commonplace, so we offer two case examples to demonstrate how it might work in your organization:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Eleos Health&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Eleos Health is a behavioral health technology company that Katherine studied in depth as part of her ethnographic &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyt.2022.990370/full&quot;>;research&lt;/a>;. The Eleos platform uses HIPAA-compliant software to record and analyze conversations between therapists and clients. In addition to saving time for therapists in note-taking, the platform&#39;s AI automatically identifies relevant evidence-based techniques and summarizes key moments in conversations between therapists and clients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One therapist explained: “After each session, the Eleos platform analyzes the counseling techniques I used and provides a helpful summary. This gives me a great sense of where I left off with that patient and what interventions I should use next time to best help them.” In this way, the AI platform enables therapists to make self-directed improvements in their work without having to rely so heavily on supervisors for guidance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, the AI platform can facilitate more useful checkpoints between therapists and their supervisors when they do need to meet. For example, it can be used to quickly synthesize or extract relevant client session data when discussing a complex case, reducing reliance on memory or notes. As one supervisor told Katherine, “New therapists often have questions … Eleos&#39; analyses allow me to zero in on key moments in their session visits, or on techniques the therapists have used, as well as patient progress over time, so that our coaching time together can be spent most productively.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Gong&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A second example comes from Gong, which has developed an AI platform for sales teams. Gong&#39;s platform unobtrusively captures live interactions between agents and prospective clients. While the conversation is unfolding, AI is crunching data in the background, examining how variables like pace, topic, tone, and turn-taking compare to best practices at that company. This data is used to provide insights and advice to sales agents in real time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moreover, Gong&#39;s AI can automatically create a library of high-quality examples of recorded sales conversations to serve as a resource for independent learning. This has been found to be especially helpful for new employees, who can listen to exemplary sales calls at their own pace, rather than relying on direct training from others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Identifying essential onboarding content and providing sales reps with real-time advice during sales calls saves managers hours of time that used to be spent listening to new employees&#39; calls to help them understand what works and what doesn&#39;t in the sales process. The result is efficient knowledge transfer. As one Gong user told us, “The platform empowers me to improve my skills and share best practices with fellow sales reps. I find that AI-based knowledge-sharing through feedback and metrics leads to continuous improvement for the entire team.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Understanding potential challenges&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re not endorsing any particular tool or company, but we do encourage HR and people managers to be on the lookout for AI options that could enhance managerial coaching in their organizations. Other companies in this space include &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/aclk?sa=l&amp;amp;ai=DChcSEwiTpMbD1r3-AhUv5uMHHSv6CJkYABABGgJ5bQ&amp;amp;sig=AOD64_22a36n60RhrD3gwoHexVSlB_b0HA&amp;amp;q&amp;amp;adurl&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiy477D1r3-AhXXkYkEHSXLCgYQ0Qx6BAgIEAE&quot;>;Beamery&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humu.com/&quot;>;Humu&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultureamp.com/?_gl=1*td4rop*_up*MQ..&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwi46iBhDyARIsAE3nVrY95mViC1V0iVh7byxvuAVNebyAoaKUOfSTaQAgP1hJzXQFE0X73XUaAhsGEALw_wcB&quot;>;Culture Amp&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterup.com/platform&quot;>;BetterUp&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.skillsoft.com/meet-skillsoft-percipio&quot;>;Skillsoft&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/ibm-transforms-human-resources-ai.aspx&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;. We expect new offerings will continue to emerge, including those embedding generative AI capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you shop around, assess your workforce&#39;s readiness for adopting an AI-assisted coaching system. Keep in mind that evaluating someone&#39;s work and trying to improve it are already &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90753495/how-to-manage-the-anxiety-of-giving-negative-feedback&quot;>;emotion-laden processes&lt;/a>;; adding technology to the mix can amplify anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One well-documented phenomenon is “&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2155&quot;>;algorithm aversion&lt;/a>;”: people&#39;s reluctance or unwillingness to trust algorithms more than human judgment. This can be even more potent when the algorithm is judging an employee&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;efficacy&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, introducing a new source of evaluation can potentially create a social distance between managers and their employees, especially if there are concerns about bias, transparency, and privacy. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1002/smj.3322&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; showed that employees resented AI-based feedback, even if it was objectively helpful, if they were not apprised ahead of time that their manager was using it. This study speaks to the importance of not only considering factors such as cost, accuracy, and timing when evaluating an AI-assisted coaching tool, but also the human factors that can influence its success or failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Five steps for successful AI-assisted coaching&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To ensure that AI-assisted coaching initiatives achieve the best possible outcomes for both employees and managers, we recommend the following steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Establish psychological safety and trust&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Decades of research show that a trust-based relationship between parties is essential for effective feedback and coaching. This is &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0008125619867910?casa_token=AcqTP9eZ4YQAAAAA:EDc0DKjUi5MDT8xnmyBu_pLBv4WWtMd7sUp9EyoG4MRqu3zvEk5LKvc58CvLSBchVrOz9BtWnrw&quot;>;even more essential&lt;/a>; when dealing with the “black box” of AI-generated assessments. In a new study, for example, employees who felt their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90762918/ai-can-hurt-worker-morale-when-managers-dont-have-these-specific-skills&quot;>;managers had their best interests at heart&lt;/a>; were more willing to accept AI-generated recommendations — even ones they didn&#39;t initially agree with. Managers can &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/make-it-safe-for-employees-to-speak-up-especially-in-risky-times&quot;>;create psychological safety&lt;/a>; and trust in the tool by clarifying the rationale for the AI integration, giving assurances as to how employee data will be used, and encouraging people to speak up about problems or questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Engage employees in design and implementation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For the best quality as well as the most buy-in, it&#39;s critical to &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-on-the-front-lines/&quot;>;be inclusive of employees throughout the exploration and adoption process&lt;/a>;. Microsoft found in a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/four-ways-leaders-can-empower-people-for-how-work-gets-done&quot;>;survey of 4,500 global executives&lt;/a>; that giving people a say in technological initiatives goes a long way toward keeping them satisfied and engaged with the tools. Ideally, employees will be involved down to the level of &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;determining the performance metrics&lt;/a>; and type of coaching that will be generated by AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Give employees some control over their data and participation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Giving employees agency over how they engage with AI-assisted coaching systems helps alleviate scrutiny and privacy concerns. For example, Eleos Health&#39;s platform allows clinicians to opt out of using the platform for specific patient sessions. Another recommended approach is to form an employee-inclusive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/hr-gets-help-vetting-ai-tools.aspx&quot;>;AI governance board&lt;/a>; to ensure transparency in what data is being collected, how it&#39;s being used, and what safeguards are in place to protect employees&#39; privacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Streamline and customize the output&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Typically, AI tools allow managers to customize the data displays and analyses generated; we recommend organizations take full advantage of these features. At the start of a rollout, for example, it might be helpful to focus the output on only a few performance metrics until people feel more comfortable with the tool.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers can also customize the quality of the feedback to reflect specific employee needs — for example, by having the output provide &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/how-ai-driven-nudges-can-transform-an-operations-performance&quot;>;more encouraging feedback during employee onboarding&lt;/a>;. In one &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0022242920956676&quot;>;study&lt;/a>;, the AI coaching tool was found most effective for moderately skilled employees, as less-skilled employees sometimes found the feedback overwhelming (too many suggestions), while more-skilled employees sometimes found it lacking in nuance. What employees want is personalized coaching, so it&#39;s important to pick an AI tool that&#39;s flexible enough to accommodate the array of people and situations in your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Train managers intensively&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many managers could benefit from &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/most-managers-dont-know-how-to-coach-people-but-they-can-learn&quot;>;basic training in effective coaching&lt;/a>;, including how to embed genuine empathy and compassion in the process. Integrating AI tools will require additional &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/technology-skills-employees-should-have-fdc6c0ba&quot;>;upskilling of managers&lt;/a>;. They should be trained not only in technical know-how but in how to translate AI-generated data sensitively and competently to employees. AI tools may also prove useful for training new managers by providing practice cases and other forms of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.yu.edu/facultynews/wp-content/uploads/sites/13/2022/05/Flaherty_2022_J-of-SW-Education.pdf&quot;>;experiential learning&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI tools hold special promise for increasing the frequency, personalization, and accuracy of coaching, without increasing the burden on managers. These gains are not guaranteed, however. To be successful, it&#39;s critical to integrate AI technology in a way that leads to a better &lt;em>;human&lt;/em>; experience for both managers and employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>