<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Nail Your Presentation &mdash; Even When Your Time Is Cut Short]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jun23_12_1285616.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;胡安·莫亚诺/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;作为公共演讲者，您可能遇到的最常见的令人不快的意外之一就是时间被缩短。您在参加会议时，根据分配给您的时间制定了要讨论的内容的计划。然后，该技术直到会议开始 15 分钟后才起作用。或者决策者迟到了，而你一直等到他们到达才开始。或者小组中的某个人（也许是每个人）跑了几分钟，当轮到你时，这几分钟已经变得复杂起来，你只能急着完成。成为一名优秀的公共演讲者需要计划以及灵活性和韧性。仅仅因为您没有计划的时间，并不意味着您无法产生预期的影响力。本文涵盖了每个演讲者在时间紧迫时都需要的三个 B 计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href= &quot;/2023/07/nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07 /nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;作为三十年来的专业演讲者，我&#39;我不得不应对一些意外的情况，这些意外可能会完全破坏我的演示。就像什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;就像在两次单独的停电期间说话，没有灯光、AV 或功能性厕所。就像举办为期两天的培训课程一样，在第一天的中间，所有参与者都会收到一封电子邮件，让他们知道裁员迫在眉睫。就像在布朗克斯动物园的刚果展览馆内的玻璃封闭会议室中进行演示一样，每次我推进幻灯片时，一只大猩猩都会敲打窗户。 （我很快就关掉了投影仪并继续进行。）&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为公共演讲者，您可能遇到的最常见的令人不愉快的意外之一就是时间被缩短。您在参加会议时，根据分配的时间制定了要讨论的内容的计划。然后，该技术直到会议开始 15 分钟后才起作用。或者决策者迟到了，而你一直等到他们到达才开始。或者小组中的某人（也许每个人）跑了几分钟，轮到你的时候，这几分钟已经复合了，你只能急于完成。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这可能是一种失败- 参与者和演示者都会输。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，如果一组中的第一个发言者可以慢慢来，但后面的发言者有自己的信息，那么参与者可能会遇到内容分布不均匀的情况被截断。其次，如果演示被缩短或加速，参与者可能会错过提出问题、澄清理解和参与讨论的机会。如果参与者在时间结束之前快速发言，他们也不太可能理解演讲者在说什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;演讲者的情况也好不到哪儿去。他们可能会感到时间压力，并对情况（或他们的团队成员）感到沮丧，这不适合有吸引力的演示风格。他们可能会错过提供&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/the-best-public-speakers-put-the-audience-first&quot;>;对观众重要的信息&lt;/a>;，而转而分享他们真正想要的内容更愿意谈谈。如果他们没有练习他们计划说的话的简短版本，他们可能听起来毫无准备、紧张和脱节。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;提前管理这种动态的一种方法是要求每个人都练习他们的演示部分带有计时器，并减少自己的演示以满足分配的时间。这有助于防止团体环境中不可避免的“时间蠕动”。管理此问题的第二步是确保主持人或主席不会过度安排会议。他们应该确保活动有足够的余裕，允许提出问题、评论、离题，甚至出现一两个小故障。第三，无论谁主持会议，都应该善于根据会议分配的时间管理问题、评论和离题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;处理所有这些问题的另一种方法是确保每个参加会议的人都有他们愿意并且能够尽快适应的 B 计划。以下是每个演讲者都需要的三个备用计划，以防时间缩短：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1。准备好两个版本的演示文稿。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;准备好您计划的演示文稿的完整版本和仅占您计划内容 50% 的版本。确保您已经练习过这两点（仅仅拥有较短的演示文稿并不能让您准备好进行有效的、较短的演示）。一旦您开始意识到您将无法完成分配的全部时间，请恢复到较短的版本。您可能需要快速决定是否仍需要删除某些内容。并计划让你的听众知道你将在会议结束后以书面形式提供额外的背景或内容。采纳英国作家阿瑟·奎勒-库奇爵士的建议，他&lt;a href=&quot;https://tinhouse.com/murder-your-darlings/&quot;>;创造了短语&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;“谋杀你的亲爱的”，意味着愿意客观地、不带感情色彩地削减你关心的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2.只需点击标题即可。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这意味着您必须构建演示文稿标题而不是页眉。标题和标题有什么区别？标题是您将在幻灯片中讨论的内容的中性包罗万象，而标题则提供幻灯片顶部的故事。它让演讲者和听众首先了解底线。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;比较这些：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幻灯片标题：“2023 年经济展望”&lt;br>; 幻灯片标题：“2023 年经济展望看起来乐观”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幻灯片标题：“第二季度销售额”&lt;br>; 幻灯片标题：“第一季度令人失望后，第二季度销售额反弹”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幻灯片标题：“下一步”&lt;br>; 幻灯片标题：“后续步骤：招聘、入职和培训”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你展示你的发现的时间有限时，你可以通过覆盖你的幻灯片的标题来提供有效的（尽管简短）叙述即使您无法解释每张幻灯片的详细信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3.不要道歉，不要让你的同事陷入困境，也不要生闷气。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;表现得好像这正是你一直计划呈现的版本。 （除非你告诉他们，否则你的听众很可能不会知道。）尽管你可能会想说“如果我们的技术团队今天早上做好准备就好了……”或“自从我的同事加班以来” ……”不要这样做。保持专业并保持协作。所有这些对话都可以在会议之后进行，而不是在会议期间进行。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，做一些&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/managing-your-teams-emotional-dynamic “情绪管理”&lt;/a>;，这样观众就不会觉得你生气、沮丧、怨恨或听天由命。情绪是会传染的，尤其是负面情绪。除非你想让你的听众感受到你所感受到的紧张，否则请深呼吸一两次，并了解你当前的现实，而不是你希望的那样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;成为一名优秀的公共演讲者需要规划以及灵活性和弹性。仅仅因为您没有计划的时间，并不意味着您无法产生预期的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div >;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Simple Power of Communicating with Kindness]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-simple-power-of-communicating-with-kindness]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_12_1494065747.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当今世界，许多问题正在侵蚀我们彼此之间的联系：缺乏专注、高速互动、政治两极分化渗透到专业互动中，缺乏信任。人们很容易把日常的礼貌抛在一边——或者以愤怒和凶猛的态度来处理困难的谈话——但是，作者告诉我们，她作为企业传播主管的经历表明，领导者加倍友善是有好处的。她概述了三种有效的策略：以仁慈打破防御、给予信任和创造空间。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/the-simple-power-of-communicating-with-kindness?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-simple-power- of-communicating-with-kindness?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我相信，在每一次人际交往中，领导者都应该尽量选择友善。这句话看似简单，但却需要勇气去生活——尤其是现在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们生活在一个许多问题正在侵蚀我们彼此之间联系的世界。注意力不集中：你最后一次在没有人检查手机或同时处理多项任务的情况下进行谈话是什么时候？或者速度：我们从一件事跑到另一件事，而没有反思我们刚刚所做的事情对人类的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，当你考虑到人们可能不想要&lt;/em>;时，挑战就会变得更加困难友善。在那些对特定社会或政治问题有强烈看法的人中，只有 30% 的人表示他们会帮助那些对最新的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.edelman.com/trust/”持不同观点的人2023/trust-barometer&quot;>;爱德曼信任晴雨表调查&lt;/a>;。由于政治两极分化，一切都变成了政治声明（想想大流行带来的掩盖）。也许由于这些因素，工作场所中常见的不文明行为&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/frontline-work-when-everyone-is-angry&quot;>;猖獗&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从我在政府、商界和政界工作的四十年中——在公司最高层的沟通工作中，目前担任辉瑞公司的执行副总裁兼首席公司事务官——我发现，伟大的领导力就是通过以下方式与人们建立联系：他们感觉自己被看见、被听见。这意味着要抵制所有这些趋势和冲动，而是实践我所说的“亲切的沟通”。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;p>;本文是“创意韧性：时代领先”系列文章中的一篇第 15 届年度&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.druckerforum.org/&quot;>;全球彼得德鲁克论坛&lt;/a>;的主题。查看会议日程&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .druckerforum.org/2023/program/&quot;>;此处&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;这涉及到允许建立联系的小手势和整体举止。对于高级领导者以及任何有抱负的领导者来说，这种沟通在日常互动以及大型、困难的对话中都很重要。您会发现自己拥有更牢固的关系和受人尊敬的领导力，以及更多的创造力、韧性，并最终获得更强大的领导力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是实现这一目标的三种方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 >;&lt;strong>;以仁慈打破防御。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;走进激烈的局面时是我最善良的时候。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我身处艰难的环境，例如参议院听证会，或者正在接受审讯时对于一位好斗的律师，我总是首先说：“非常感谢您今天邀请我来到这里。”当我说这句话时，我面带微笑，我是认真的。这表明我来这里是为了倾听和贡献，而不是阻碍任何人。这很让人解除戒心：它可以减轻情绪并打开耳朵。同时，这需要勇气，也显示出你的成熟。这样可以更有创意、更高效地解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;需要明确的是，我并不是说没有地方可以向某人表达愤怒。例如，如果他们伤害了你或你的家人，愤怒是适当的反应。但这并不是打开思想、感动心灵的最有效工具。愤怒会让对方变得封闭；善良会打开他们的大门。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;而且，作为一个领导者，其他人总是在关注你的沟通，如果你被认为是一个吹毛求疵的人，你就会与重要的负面消息隔绝。愤怒或不稳定的组织文化会降低人们&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/make-it-safe-for-employees-to-speak-up-special-in-risky-times&quot;>;发声的可能性&lt;/a>;关于重要的风险或问题。这会降低您的组织对危机的快速响应能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;在应得的信任处给予信任。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;人们喜欢被看到和赞赏。认可那些值得的人会产生热情、努力工作、信任和忠诚。我记得几年后我从老板那里收到的感谢卡，从那时起，我就养成了为我的团队写这些感谢卡的习惯，并给予他们认可的时刻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;表达感激之情也能激发我的创造力：事后反思我与某人的互动常常会激发我与他们的另一个机会的想法，或者以另一种方式继续对话。它帮助我放慢脚步，让这些想法浮现出来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;给予认可对于你的同事和你所领导的人来说都一样强大。我是执行委员会的成员，每当我看到小组中有人受到认可（一位获得著名奖项的科学家，或者一位制造人员达到了新的安全标准），我就会将其分发给小组的其他成员。我这样做是因为我钦佩与我一起工作的人，并且真诚地相信我所说的话。但我也相信，这也让我这个信用给予者看起来不错：它表明我有成熟和自信来欣赏别人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个令人惊讶的举动，因为声称信用是如今企业界的一件大事。想一想谦虚的吹牛：有人抱怨自己为了完成一个重要项目而熬夜了多少个可怕的夜晚（对观众来说，重点是该项目有多么重要以及他们在其中扮演的角色有多大）。或者在社交媒体上发帖，表达他们对于获得巨大晋升是多么幸运或谦卑。这是无休止且令人作呕的，因为将所有事情归功于自己的需要最终会具有破坏性并适得其反。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果有人刚刚将您的想法或工作归功于您，那么想要获得认可的冲动就会特别强烈。但在你介入纠正记录之前，请三思而后行。人们善于观察；他们经常可以看到谁在做这项工作。那一刻保持沉默，而不是急着说“不，&lt;em>;我&lt;/em>;做到了！”充分显示出您对自己的信心程度，以及是否能够与他人保持联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，在大流行期间，我和我的老板与另一家大型制药公司提出了一个想法公司承诺我们都将遵守某些高安全标准，并且不会在疫苗竞赛中走捷径。你可以想象，当我在 2022 年的一次会议上听到其他公司之一的某人声称获得荣誉时，我感到多么惊讶。我脖子后面的汗毛都竖起来了，双手紧握，一时之间我想到了打断谈话并愤怒地纠正。但没有这么做。我意识到，如果我声称自己享有应得的荣誉，我就会故意在公共场合让别人难堪，而且我会对我们所有人都是如此优秀的合作者的整个想法产生怀疑。我看起来会更糟，而且保持沉默也不会让我付出什么代价。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，在某些情况下你应该举手鞠躬，比如当你领导的团队取得了成就时一个延伸目标（在这种情况下，说“我们”）或当您的公司声誉受到威胁时。最后，给予他人荣誉对你来说比接受他人更有力量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;给对方空间和清晰的思路。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;无论如何当你想与某人交谈时，不要让他们措手不及或失去兴趣。无论是一个无害的快速问题还是一个严重的坏消息，总是询问现在是否合适，并尝试让他们了解您想讨论的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这让您的对方有机会做好准备告诉他们您需要分享的任何惊喜或坏消息，并明确表示您有兴趣听取他们的回应。它还可以让他们平静下来——他们从不知道会发生什么变成了解情况。它为您的漫步提供了路线图。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这可以很简单，只需联系同事并说“现在是讨论我们秋季活动的好时机吗？” （而不是像我以前那样，在非固定时间通过 FaceTime 与他们进行视频通话）。它可能为可以以不同方式感知的新闻提供一些情感背景。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于重大问题，这可能需要更多准备：前一周我有一些重要的事情要与老板讨论。我告诉他，“如果我们能在场外抽出几分钟时间来讨论我与我的团队相关的这个问题，我将非常感激”，并向他发送了几张幻灯片，以便他知道它是关于什么的并且知道当他有 15 分钟而不是两分钟的时候来找我。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你并不总是有时间准备，但仍然有办法给对方空间。如果在谈话中需要反驳某件事或传递坏消息，你可以说“我们就此打住吧”并保持坦诚。但如果是集体情况，如果可以的话，等到会议结束后再给他们回电话。假设他们说了一些冒犯的话。给他们打电话并说：“你可能不知道这是如何发生的”，然后从那里进行讨论。公开羞辱他人不是一个好主意，但私下里尝试教育他人则是一个好主意。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论您选择什么策略，其目的都是不要在谈话中给对方带来负担，而是要让对方感到轻松。向外关注——关注他人，而不是你自己。无论这有多困难，特别是在当今两极分化和快节奏的世界中，它都会为你的人际关系、你的领导力和你自己的福祉带来巨大的红利。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What SCOTUS&rsquo;s Affirmative Action Decision Means for Corporate DEI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_12_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anja Sušanj 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然最高法院最近关于平权行动的裁决主要针对政府行为者和大学，但不可避免的是，一些企业领导人将以此为理由放弃他们已经反对的多样性、公平性和包容性计划。然而，作者认为，法院为继续在工作场所推进 DEI 留下了足够的空间。即使法律继续向保守方向发展，三种常见做法也将持续存在：1）抵消偏见的做法，例如从职位描述中删除陈规定型语言或使用标准化问题列表进行结构化面试； 2) 有助于促进整体多元化的环境政策，例如员工资源小组、导师计划或家庭友好政策； 3）普遍政策，例如增强心理安全感。这些策略在法律上是安全的，因为它们使所有人受益，但受益最多的是处于边缘的人，正是因为如果没有这些举措，他们感觉最被排除在工作场所之外。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div >; &lt;p>;在最高法院最近对平权行动做出重磅决定之前，一些人预测禁止这种做法的裁决将“&lt;a href=&quot;https://nypost.com/2023/05/31/affirmative-action- scotus-case-could-take-down-diversity-industry-too/&quot;>;取缔&lt;/a>;”多元化行业或提供“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features /2023-06-22/supreme-court-affirmative-action-ruling-jeopardizes-corporate-diversity-too&quot;>;震荡&lt;/a>;”对工作场所多样性和包容性努力造成打击。在法院实际上废除了注重种族的大学招生后，一些声音变得更加强烈。由前特朗普顾问斯蒂芬·米勒创立的“美国第一法律”组织 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://aflegal.org/america-first-legal-puts-woke-corporations-law-firms-and-hospitals-on-notice -all-dei-programs-and-workplace-balancing-based-on-race-national-origin-and-sex-violate-the-law/&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>;“所有 DEI 计划”现在都是“非法的” .”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没那么快。我们相信法院留下了足够的空间来继续推进工作场所的多样性和包容性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的意思并不是最明显的意义上的，即法院的意见集中于政府行为者和大学而不是私人雇主。当正确的案件到达法院时，刚刚支持高等教育“色盲”方法的法官也可能认为私人雇主在工作场所决策中不能考虑种族、性别或其他受保护的特征。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这样的一项裁决确实会危及最激进的支持多样性政策。为代表性不足的群体保留招聘或晋升名额，指示经理在选择候选人时使用种族或性别作为“决胜局”，或者设定与经理薪酬相关的严格人口目标，这些都容易受到司法谴责。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，多样性和包容性举措远远超出了平权行动名义下的政策范围。即使假设法律继续朝着保守的方向发展，我们相信至少三种多样性和包容性工作将会持续下去。我们将这些称为消除偏见工作、环境工作和普遍工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多常见的多样性和包容性实践都涉及消除工作场所偏见。举一个典型的例子，几十年前，在美国排名前五的交响乐团中，女性音乐家仅占 5%。截至 2016 年，这一比例&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/What-Works-Gender-Equality-Design/dp/0674089030&quot;>;超过 35%&lt;/a>;。研究人员&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hup.harvard.edu/catalog.php?isbn=9780674986565&quot;>;将这种急剧增加部分归因于一个简单的设计修复：管弦乐队掩盖了音乐家的性别要求他们在屏幕后进行试镜。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然在大多数工作场所使用物理屏幕来改进招聘流程是不切实际的，但许多雇主&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/7-practical-ways- to-reduce-bias-in-your-hiring-process&quot;>;采取类似的举措&lt;/a>;来消除环境中的偏见，例如消除招聘广告中的刻板语言、使用一致的问题进行结构化面试以及改进晋升流程以使其成为可能更加透明和基于绩效。大多数无意识的偏见培训——无论你怎么想——旨在消除机会均等的障碍，因此它与&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-66058664&quot;>;六位保守派法官在法院最近的裁决中提出了“色盲”哲学。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，虽然反歧视法规范离散的就业决策，例如招聘和晋升、多样性和包容性计划经常是周围环境。根据我们的经验，很少有雇主明确告诉经理在选择求职者时要考虑种族或性别。相反，他们通常采取各种举措来整体促进劳动力多元化，例如向不同的大学进行推广、建立员工资源小组、创建导师计划以及实施护理室和灵活的工作选择等家庭友好政策。即使最高法院未来的裁决宣布雇主不能再利用种族或性别来平衡员工队伍，这些更广泛的多元化举措也不涉及此类内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;重要的是，心怀不满的员工不能挑战雇主的多元化政策监管就业的主要联邦法规——1964 年《民权法案》第七章——仅仅是因为他们感到沮丧或怨恨。相反，在典型的索赔中，员工需要证明他们遭受了“不利的就业行为”，例如被拒绝工作机会、拒绝晋升或被解雇。然后他们需要证明该行动是由于他们的种族或性别而采取的。简单地指出黑人员工网络或妇女历史月庆祝活动的存在作为歧视的证据并不能解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，与我们合作的许多组织都倾向于采取干预措施，而不是针对特定人口群体融入普遍多样性和包容性框架，让所有人齐心协力。例如，“盟友关系”的概念近年来席卷了美国企业界，部分原因是这个概念适用于每个人：我们都有优点和缺点，因此我们都可以彼此成为盟友并获得盟友关系作为回报.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他通用框架侧重于创建工作文化，以实现更大的真实性和自我表达，或提高员工的“&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety” >;心理安全&lt;/a>;”敢于发声而不用担心受到惩罚。这些策略在法律上是安全的，因为它们使所有人受益，包括历史上占主导地位的群体的成员。但受益最多的是处于边缘的人们，正是因为如果没有此类举措，他们是最感觉被排除在工作场所之外的人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，法院的色盲转变是更广泛的文化反弹的一个症状这使得多样性和包容性的倡导者越来越处于防御地位。三年前，随着“黑人生命也是命”运动的复兴，各组织纷纷呼吁展示其对社会正义的承诺。现在，在右翼活动人士和政客的压力下，许多组织正在淡化其多元化举措，并利用经济条件&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-labor-report/corporate-diversity-承诺-fizzle-amid-layoffs-gop-backlash&quot;>;解雇&lt;/a>;从事这些工作的专业人员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些企业领导人可能不可避免地会猛烈抨击最高法院的这项裁决有理由放弃他们已经反对的计划。然而，这三种类型的作品——去偏见的、环境的和普遍的——表明多样性和包容性的时代还远未结束。只要雇主在做出具体的就业决策时不使用种族和性别等受保护的特征，他们就可以自由地促进更具包容性的文化，并打破阻碍女性、有色人种和其他边缘群体在工作场所蓬勃发展的障碍。鉴于多元化和包容性的员工队伍对于创新、生产力和员工敬业度的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/research/why-diversity-and-inclusion-matter/&quot;>;好处&lt;/a>; ，这样的举措不仅仅是一种理想，而且是 21 世纪企业的必需品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在人口和社会快速变化的时代，塑造制度使每个人都能够参与其中比以往任何时候都更加紧迫- 无论他们的身份和背景如何 - 都可以归属。即使在这位激进的最高法院的领导下，这项工作仍然至关重要，而且最重要的是，它是合法的。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Ecodesign Can Help the Environment and Your Bottom Line - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM SIEMENS]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/how-ecodesign-can-help-the-environment-and-your-bottom-line]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359826&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Header-visual_HBR.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;虽然已经签署了许多建设循环经济的承诺在世界范围内，工业消耗的资源仍然多于可再生的资源。如今，需要 1.75 个地球才能满足全球需求。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，只有 7% 多一点的材料被保留下来供进一步使用，其余的则被送往废物处理（这一顺序称为“资源的线性使用”）。因此，未来将会出现更多的供应风险和价格高峰，从而使经济增长面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;资源的线性使用危及我们的环境。根据&lt;a href=&quot;https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/biodiversity-report&quot;>;艾伦·麦克阿瑟基金会最近的一项研究&lt;/a>;，自然资源的开采导致了气候变化和 90% 以上的生物多样性丧失。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，人类有充分的理由迅速行动起来，在全球企业中实施循环经济原则。通过这样做，我们可以将资源消耗与绝对增长脱钩。我们可以事半功倍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;循环经济和生态设计&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从线性经济成功过渡到循环经济的关键是什么？是产品设计。产品生命周期中高达 80% 的环境影响是由其设计决定的。这就是生态设计的用武之地。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生态设计是如何工作的？&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync ()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;而传统产品开发主要侧重于在可用性、安全性、成本、质量等因素上，生态设计强调生态因素。这意味着找到重复利用材料的方法，同时最大限度地提高产品的安全使用和价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与传统的产品设计方法不同，生态设计考虑了整个产品生命周期，包括资源提取、采购、原型设计、系列生产、多种产品使用、生命周期结束阶段以及所有物流和运输过程。生态设计产品开发远远超出了公司的范围，从“摇篮到坟墓”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;实施生态设计对于任何组织来说都是一项重大变革。 Making the strategy work requires the commitment of top executives, and it means teams must embrace new ways of thinking and working.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Robust Eco Design: Three Phases &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In 2020, Siemens introduced a dedicated, holistic ecodesign approach to its development processes called Robust Eco Design (RED). With RED, Siemens aims to systematically identify ways to achieve the same or greater customer value, while consuming less energy and fewer resources, minimizing the dissemination of nonnatural substances into the environment, and managing the required technical and biological resources in a circular loop.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On their way to environmentally compatible products, Siemens&#39; design departments follow a three-step-approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, teams specify environment-related customer requirements, such as energy efficiency or product longevity, and regulatory targets, such as the EU&#39;s Circular Economy Action Plan.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Then they collect comprehensive data on all inbound and outbound material and energy flows from the entire life cycle, including emissions to air, water, and soil as well as resources taken from nature. Subsequently, they quantify different designs&#39; environmental impacts and effects on human health and make those findings transparent to their stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Finally, they give recommendations for environmentally optimized design specifications that don&#39;t require trade-offs in areas such as safety or quality. Recommendations might include an increased use of recyclates or changes that allow for easy reuse, repair, refurbishment, remanufacturing, or recycling.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;How Digitalization Boosts Ecodesign &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some may argue that adding new environmental parameters to product design doesn&#39;t make decision making any easier. And to some extent, that&#39;s true. Organizations might face more conflicting requirements, such as stronger materials that enable more product longevity but also require more energy-intensive processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, digitalization and simulation can solve such challenges. “Digital twins” of real-life products can simulate the repairability or robustness of a product without wasting real-life resources. They can also support factories in cutting energy and resource consumption, CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; emissions, and waste production by simulating production processes. Future-forward organizations need to bring in the technology and expertise that help them integrate these&amp;nbsp;powerful tools&amp;nbsp;with their operations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Digitalization also allows organizations to share emission data without disclosing strategic secrets. In open, cross-industry networks like Estainium, manufacturers, suppliers, and customers can exchange trustworthy product carbon footprint data.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;A Strategy That Makes Sense &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ecodesign is not just a matter of protecting climate and biodiversity. It&#39;s also a smart business strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By adopting ecodesign principles, companies can simultaneously reduce costs, minimize waste, and gain a competitive edge. The potential benefits are significant, including billions of dollars in cost savings for materials and new revenue streams through innovative business models like anything-as-a-service (XaaS). Collaboration across industries in open ecosystems can further amplify environmental and economic advantages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taking the leap into circular economy practices is a major transformation. So make your sustainability efforts worthwhile and focus on product design, because that&#39;s how you maximize your impact—on both your bottom line and our environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Learn more about ecodesign and how to build your “circular advantage” in Siemens&#39; white paper &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siemens.com/global/en/company/sustainability/environment.html?stc=decg211247&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Ecodesign: Multiplying impact, shaping the world&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;. &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[To Get Better Customer Data, Build Feedback Loops into Your Products]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Daniel Creel&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Thanks to the increasing availability of AI, including machine learning algorithms, deliberately creating &lt;em>;customer data feedback loop&lt;/em>;s is now possible for most products and services. This means that as a firm gathers more customer data, it can feed that data into machine learning algorithms to improve its product or service, thereby attracting more customers, generating even more customer data. For some products, it is easy; for others, one needs to find more creative ways to engineer the data feedback loops. This article explains how to do so.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The combination of user data and AI often creates data feedback loops. This means that as a firm gathers more customer data, it can feed that data into machine learning algorithms to improve its product or service, thereby attracting more customers, generating even more customer data. Think, for example, of search engines: the more people search on Google and click on the links provided, the more data Google gathers, which allows its algorithms to provide more accurate and relevant search results, attracting even more users and searches, and so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such data feedback loops can help create a &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/01/when-data-creates-competitive-advantage&quot;>;sustainable competitive advantage&lt;/a>;, provided that &lt;a href=&quot;https://platformchronicles.substack.com/p/six-questions-to-evaluate-data-enabled&quot;>;certain conditions exist&lt;/a>;. But the strength of these data feedback loops can vary greatly, and companies can make deliberate choices in their products or services to strengthen them. How to do so is the focus of this piece.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Not All Data Feedback Loops Are Created Equal&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Some products have naturally very strong data feedback loops. Think of smart thermostats, where every temperature adjustment by a user provides a valuable data signal that the device can use to achieve better personalization. Or Google Maps, where every user&#39;s choice of route and the time taken to reach the destination help the algorithm improve its route recommendations and traffic predictions. Or Spotify, whose recommender system learns directly from users&#39; choices of which recommended songs to include in their playlists and how often they listen to those songs. The reason these feedback loops are so strong is that users reveal clear and unambiguous signals of their preferences in the natural process of consuming the product, which are leveraged to further improve the product or the service for those users.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the other end of the spectrum are products with naturally weak data feedback loops. Their usage is hard to track or does not reveal useful information about user preferences, or it is difficult and slow to gather informative feedback from users.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is obviously true of traditional “dumb” products like cars, furniture, and clothes: They are not digitally connected, so the only way to create any data feedback loops from customers is to manually collect feedback via focus groups and surveys, which can only help for future product releases. And it is also true of products where the feedback loops involve very long cycles of learning and improvement such as financial institutions&#39; credit scoring systems (feedback mainly comes from defaults, which take years to materialize), or venture investing (it takes years to figure out which startups succeed and which fail).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Less obvious is that even some digital products that collect lots of user data may have weak data feedback loops. This means most of their value comes from pre-programming and in-house data training and does not increase much, if at all, via learning from users.&amp;nbsp;For instance, popular wearables such as Fitbit, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whoop.com/&quot;>;Whoop&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://to.nutrisense.io/&quot;>;Nutrisense&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ouraring.com/&quot;>;Oura&lt;/a>; have fairly weak data feedback loops, even though they provide lots of data insights.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the latest Fitbit tracker, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;Charge 5&lt;/a>;, which has an impressive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;list of features&lt;/a>;. The tracker measures a wide array of data from the user (heart rate, speed and distance of movement, sleep, skin temperature) and provides valuable insights such as heart rate variability, time spent in different heart rate zones, a cardio fitness score, a readiness score for working out, a quality of sleep score. However, these insights do not appear to get better with more usage or more users. They are straightforward summary statistics of what is being measured by the tracker, or the result of comparisons between user data measured by the Fitbit tracker and relevant reference points based on pre-existing research, which are pre-programmed in the Fitbit system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Fitbit &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.fitbit.com/articles/en_US/Help_article/2096.htm&quot;>;explains&lt;/a>; that “the cardio fitness score is determined by your resting heart rate, age, sex, weight, and other personal information.” Similarly, the readiness score &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/technology/daily-readiness-score#:~:text=Your%20Daily%20Readiness%20Score%20uses,to%20gauge%20your%20energy%20levels.&amp;amp;text=Heart%20rate%20variability%20(HRV)%20is,contribute%20to%20a%20high%20score.&quot;>;is based on&lt;/a>; the user&#39;s recent sleep patterns as measured by the tracker — which are presumably compared to some stable reference points. In other words, these are estimates of the “true” state of a user, but they do not improve with more usage data, simply because Fitbit has no way of figuring out how close its estimates came to the “true” state and adjusting them accordingly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there may be some limited ways in which wearables could improve the value provided to each user based on usage data from that user or other users. At the most basic level, any connected product can learn which user interface is more engaging (eg, via A/B testing), which is technically a form of data feedback loop, albeit a limited one — table stakes for most products.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And there are correlations that wearables could analyze to recommend behavior. For instance, a correlation between the time users go to bed and the quality of their sleep, which can be used to recommend an optimal time to go to bed; or between the time users exercise and the quality of their sleep, which can be used to recommend an optimal time to exercise. In these cases, as users adjust their behavior based on the recommendations, the wearable gets some feedback on whether this is helping or not, and so can further improve by learning from users. Still, this type of process requires lots of data from lots of users, and the wearable provider may never really know the extent to which correlation means causation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, consider the data feedback loops of large language models (LLMs) such as Open AI&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://chat.openai.com/&quot;>;Chat GPT&lt;/a>; or Google&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://bard.google.com/&quot;>;Bard&lt;/a>;. These models ingest enormous amounts of data from the web and use machine learning models to generate answers to user questions. In the early versions of these models, their capabilities are largely determined by pre-launch “in-house” training and testing — the quality of their answers improves only to a moderate extent with more users or more usage. Indeed, as of this writing, there are two main mechanisms that create data feedback loops around LLMs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Users click on the thumbs-up or thumbs-down buttons at the end of the answers. (Most users probably ignore this most of the time.)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Users ask follow-up questions, which could signal whether an answer was satisfactory or not. (This inference is likely difficult in most cases.)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Note the difference with regular search (on Bing or Google), where the user&#39;s choice of which displayed links to click on provides a much clearer signal of the relevance of the search results. Of course, things may change drastically as the LLMs are updated and start incorporating more reliable ways to generate data feedback loops — a topic we discuss in the next section.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to Enhance Data Feedback Loops&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The key question is then, for those products where the data-enabled learning feedback loops are not naturally strong, what can be done to enhance them?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;(Re)design the product to create natural data feedback loops.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Ideally, one would want to (re)design the product or service in such a way that customers, in the natural course of using the product, are creating data that signals how useful/effective the product is for users. This data can then be used by the provider to improve the quality of the product or service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, LLMs could add new features that allow users to save and organize the responses they found most helpful into folders of favorites (akin to bookmarks) and delete those they don&#39;t want to keep. They could add a document-creation feature (akin to Microsoft Word) where they would copy and edit LLM responses. They could also create challenge games (AI vs. users) and leader boards where the AI and users seek to answer questions, and users vote on the answers.等等。 The idea is to create opportunities for users to provide reliable signals of the perceived quality of the LLMs&#39; answers, which can then be used to improve their algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fitbit and other wearables could add standardized fitness tests or challenges (eg, run one mile or do three sets of 20 sit-ups) and measure users&#39; total time, heart rate, and other biometrics before and after. This would allow the wearables&#39; AI to more accurately predict users&#39; readiness for working out as they observe more data from more users. Which in turn should induce users to rely on the wearables more and more for deciding when to work out. Of course, this still relies on assumptions about unobserved user behavior, but the key point is that the devices need to perform some sort of quasi-experiments on users in order to obtain data that can help them learn and improve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Integrate with other products to create data feedback loops.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In many cases, redesigning the actual product or service to engineer feedback loops may be challenging (as illustrated by the wearables example above). An alternative way of achieving the same goal is to integrate your offering with other existing products that customers already use or could use.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Fitbit (or Whoop or Oura) could create an integration with smart thermostats to enable the wearable to automatically control the ambient temperature during a user&#39;s sleep. This would allow the wearable&#39;s AI to adjust the temperature and determine its effect on the quality of a user&#39;s sleep as measured by the wearable. The more a customer uses the wearable (ie, wears it to sleep), the closer the wearable can come to figuring out the ideal temperature pattern for any given user. This can be achieved by automatically experimenting with many different temperature patterns as the user sleeps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Or the wearables could integrate with Peloton or Tonal, which provide standardized workouts, so that Fitbit&#39;s AI could correlate a user&#39;s biometrics with the type and intensity of workouts. The advantage relative to the option described above (where the wearables are simply asking users to perform specific workouts) is that here the actual workout behavior can be observed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, LLMs could integrate with whatever software or tools their answers are being used in. For example, they could integrate with content creation/editing software (eg, Google Docs, Substack, Salesforce), which would allow them to observe which parts of their answers end up being used in the content created by users and use that data to improve their answers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask users for feedback in a minimally intrusive way that makes the benefits clear to them.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Still, for many products, finding such ways of making user feedback inherent to product usage — directly or via integration — may be hard or impossible. Short of that, the next-best option is to explicitly ask users for feedback. Most online products and services do this to a certain extent. As mentioned above, LLMs ask users for thumbs-up or down after every answer generated; Netflix asks users for a thumbs-up or down after each piece of content they watch in order to improve its recommendation system; Amazon asks buyers to rate the products they purchased; Airbnb asks both travelers and hosts to rate each other, and so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, the difficulty with asking for explicit feedback is obtaining useful information while not inconveniencing users too much. Nobody likes being badgered with surveys that “only take three minutes of your time,” or seeing feedback polls (“how likely are you to recommend us to your friends?”) pop up every other screen.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to making requests for user feedback as easy and painless as possible, it helps to clearly communicate to users how that feedback might benefit them personally whenever possible (eg, “by rating this movie, Netflix will be able to give you better recommendations of which other movies you are likely to enjoy”). This ensures that they have an incentive to provide honest feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Include humans in the loop.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;An important way to manufacture a data feedback loop while minimizing the feedback burden on users is to include humans in the loop to complement (or even replace) user feedback. A good example of this is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexi.com/&quot;>;Alexi&lt;/a>;, an AI-powered legal research service offered to law firms. Customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexsei.com/howitworks&quot;>;submit legal questions&lt;/a>; along with any relevant case facts, and Alexi sends back a legal research memo containing an answer, complete with summaries of the relevant case law and litigation. The memos are generated by Alexi&#39;s AI but then reviewed and amended (when necessary) by Alexi&#39;s in-house legal team — the humans in the loop. Thus, Alexi&#39;s AI gets the benefit of learning from customer queries and the implicit feedback provided by the in-house team&#39;s corrections, without burdening customers. This works well here because customers do not expect instant answers. (Alexi promises an answer within 24 hours, a very reasonable turnaround in this context.) Nor do they ask hundreds of questions a day like Chat GPT or Bard users might.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another example of good use of humans in the loop is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.grammarly.com/&quot;>;Grammarly&lt;/a>;, an AI-powered writing assistant that helps users improve grammar, spelling, punctuation, and style. Grammarly provides suggestions in real time, while users are writing in any application or site (eg, word processing, email, social media, communication apps). Users have the option to accept or reject the suggested edits, which obviously helps improve the algorithm and creates a data feedback loop. However, Grammarly also uses human reviewers to check the suggestions made by the AI model and review ambiguous cases (a user rejects a suggested edit, but it is unclear why he did so), instead of asking users for feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other examples of AI-based products or services that use humans in the loop to complement or replace user feedback include content moderation on social media platforms (human moderators get involved in the most complex cases that the AI has trouble with), AI-powered radiology services such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gleamer.ai/&quot;>;Gleamer&lt;/a>; (human specialists complement AI diagnostics and would correct any issues in the diagnosis the system automatically writes up), and AI-powered security services such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deepsentinel.com/&quot;>;Deep Sentinel&lt;/a>; (the AI detects threats and decides when to escalate to human guards, who can then decide whether the AI made the correct call).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, the main weakness of the humans-in-the-loop approach is that it does not scale well to hundreds of thousands or millions of customers or to services with very high frequency of usage and expectation of quick turnaround times. Not many companies can afford to hire armies of over 15,000 content moderators as Meta does for Facebook. This is why most companies employing humans in the loop try to minimize the time required from humans in the process. Nevertheless, the humans-in-the-loop approach can be very effective in the early stages of a product/service, when the learning curve is steepest. The hope is that the need to involve humans decreases rapidly over time as the AI system learns.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The increasing availability of artificial intelligence, including machine learning algorithms, means that deliberately creating data feedback loops is now possible for most products and services. For some products, it is easy; for others, one needs to find more creative ways to engineer the data feedback loops — via integrations or minimally intrusive requests for user feedback that provide benefits for the users. When they are strong, these feedback loops can create a form of network effect (more users bring more data, which makes the product better, in turn attracting more users, and so on) and compounding competitive advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Factors That Make for a Great Employee Experience]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_200021503-002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;戴利和牛顿/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;数十年的业务战略促使领导者将大部分业务精力集中在客户体验上。虽然优先考虑客户而不是员工可以推动短期收入增长，但这将使公司在长期员工保留和敬业度方面付出代价。作者和同事对来自世界各地、跨多个行业的数千名员工和高管进行了一项新研究。通过回归分析，他们确定了创造更好的员工体验的五个最重要的因素：相互信任、最高管理层问责制、员工价值观与公司愿景的一致性、认可成功以及无缝技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=es&quot;>;阅读en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt; /div>; &lt;p>;我们听说过这样的格言：快乐的员工会带来快乐的客户，但新数据揭示了员工体验的影响有多么重要，以及如何利用它来促进组织发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;数十年的业务战略促使领导者将大部分业务精力集中在客户体验上。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4215010&quot;>;哥伦比亚大学最近的一项研究&lt;/a>;发现“高管们[在财报电话会议上]谈论客户的频率是原来的 10 倍比员工。当他们这样做时，高管们会将客户视为机会，将员工视为风险。”即使公司谈论良好的员工体验游戏，他们实际上仍然会根据客户体验采取行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然优先考虑客户而不是员工可以推动短期收入增长，但这将使公司在长期员工保留方面付出代价和参与度。根据我和我的 Salesforce 同事进行的研究，公司可以通过改善员工体验&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想确定员工体验的关键驱动因素，以帮助高管改善员工体验。对于我即将出版的书，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Experience-Mindset-Changing-Think-Growth/dp/059354269X&quot;>;&lt;em>;体验心态&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，我和我的同事对来自世界各地、跨多个行业的数千名员工和高管进行了一项新研究。通过回归分析，我们确定了创造更好员工体验的五个最重要因素：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1。相互信任&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;信任有两种：员工对组织的信任和组织对其员工的信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相互&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/begin -with-trust&quot;>;信任&lt;/a>;会赋予员工权力。它表明了管理层对其员工的信心，从而增强了员工对领导层和彼此之间的信任。它还可以激励员工、促进创造力和协作、提高保留率并减少风险规避，所有这些都有助于实现盈利。这种授权和信任在苹果公司和丽思卡尔顿公司等公司都很明显，在苹果公司，商店员工无需申请特殊批准即可解决许多客户问题；在丽思卡尔顿酒店，员工可以花费高达 2,000 美元来解决客人问题，无需管理层批准。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;相互信任也有助于员工感到被倾听。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/hybrid-work-making-it-fit-with-your-diversity-equity-and-inclusion -strategy&quot;>;根据麦肯锡&lt;/a>;的说法，这种包容性会让员工留在公司的可能性增加 47%，并且他们会竭尽全力互相帮助的可能性增加 90%。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;当总部位于多伦多的金融贷款公司 Clear Co 开始经历高速增长时，首席执行官 Michele Romanow 希望&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/whats-next-podcast/enter- the-dragons-den-with-serial-entrepreneur-michele-romanow&quot;>;在保持其创业文化的同时实现流程现代化&lt;/a>;。因此，她设置了一个电子邮件收件箱，其标题为“我们所做的愚蠢的事！”并向员工询问有关简化业务和消除可预防的挫折的想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据 Romanow 的说法，这个简单的练习实现了两个目标。首先，它让员工有一种主人翁意识，并参与改善他们的日常生活并帮助公司。其次，它创建了一个反馈循环，允许领导层建立员工信任，同时在问题转移之前发现并解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2.高管问责制&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;高管问责制与信任密切相关，意味着确保公司领导层对企业及其员工做出承诺并做出回应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在一个层面上，问责制是关于愿意提出问题并积极倾听答案。领导者无法满足他们不了解的员工需求。更广泛地说，它涉及文化：具有强大高管责任感的企业了解员工体验的重要性并优先考虑它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司的言论和行动之间往往存在差异。我们在研究中发现，虽然 49% 的高管认为他们的公司擅长根据员工反馈采取行动（老实说，这个数字很低），但只有 31% 的员工同意这一观点。这种差距会吞噬增长、动力和人才。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;创造一种文化，让每个人都明白员工体验是一项集体责任。例如，希尔顿建立了跨职能团队，确保最高管理层以正式、结构化的方式密切关注员工体验。正如希尔顿执行副总裁兼首席商务官 Chris Silcock 所说，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/salesforce/2020/11/05/how-hilton-uses-the-golden-rule-to- drive-commercial-success/?sh=4661f676733c&quot;>;观察到&lt;/a>;，“你如何对待你的团队成员，他们就会如何对待你的客户。”希尔顿多次被《财富》杂志评为“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greatplacetowork.com/best-companies-to-work-for&quot;>;最佳雇主&lt;/a>;”之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在您的公司，这可能看起来像一个经验咨询委员会，帮助打破传统障碍并促进集思广益和构思；卓越中心，在存在知识或技能差距的情况下提供最佳实践；员工资源小组提供同行咨询并促进职业发展；或“员工之声”调查，以征求和收集员工的需求、愿望和期望。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3．员工价值观与公司愿景保持一致&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;员工希望与公司价值观保持一致，但这使得高管层有责任明确阐明这些价值观，然后确保公司行动与这些价值观保持一致。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;明确的目标以及明确的里程碑和成功指标将员工与公司的使命联系起来，并帮助他们了解自己在推进公司使命中的角色。我们在研究中发现，确保员工感到受到重视并成为公司愿景的核心是报告收入增长的重要驱动力。然而，只有 36% 的员工表示有这种感觉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;支持体验思维的公司文化了解其内部为员工所做的事情与如何转化为客户体验之间的内在联系。例如，Airbnb 于 2013 年在一家美国大公司聘请了第一位员工体验主管。“文化只是一种充满激情地做某事的共享方式，”当时首席执行官布莱恩·切斯基 (Brian Chesky) 在一篇题为“&lt;a href= “https://medium.com/@bchesky/dont-fuck-up-the-culture-597cde9ee9d4&quot;>;别搞砸文化&lt;/a>;。” “文化越强，公司需要的企业流程就越少。当文化强大时，你可以相信每个人都会做正确的事。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一致性是这种文化的重要组成部分，甚至在员工加入 Airbnb 之前就开始了。该公司进行了两次独立的“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegrowthfaculty.com/blog/Employeeexperiencestaffretention?recacheSoql=true&quot;>;核心价值观面试&lt;/a>;”，由招聘职能之外的团队成员进行，以便他们能够独立于职位空缺的具体需求来评估文化契合度。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4.认识到成功。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;正如活动家和慈善家 &lt;a href=&quot;https://chopra.com/articles/what-you-appreciate-appreciates&quot;>;Lynne Twist 观察到的&lt;/a>;，“什么你欣赏欣赏。”认可可以是&lt;a href=&quot;https://focus.kornferry.com/employee-recognition-the-secret-ingredient-to-high-employee-engagement-asean/&quot;>;提高员工敬业度的一种经济高效的方式&lt; /a>;，这对忠诚度、保留率和生产力具有积极的溢出效应。相信自己的成功会得到认可的员工&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quantumworkplace.com/future-of-work/importance-of-employee-recognition&quot;>;高度敬业度的可能性高出 2.7 倍&lt;/a >; 根据员工敬业度公司 Quantum Workplace 的数据，高于没有这样做的同事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，表扬并不是认可的总和。它还涉及识别和培养潜力，为员工提供成长所需的技能。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/use- Purpose-to-transform-your-workplace&quot;>;联合利华&lt;/a>;制定了一项涵盖整个组织的领导力发展计划。在领导力发展研讨会上，员工会制定个性化的“未来适应计划”，每个计划都侧重于对个人既重要又符合公司目标的目标。结果？ 92% 参加过研讨会的人表示，他们的工作激励他们加倍努力，而没有参加过的人中只有 33% 有同样的感觉。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;5.减少员工日常摩擦的无缝技术&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;高管们常常将技术作为解决公司绩效、生产力和成本的一种方式，但却很少考虑它如何适应公司的需求。组织的其余基础设施、现有流程和人员工作流程。正如工程师和管理顾问 W. Edwards Deming 在大约 40 年前所说的那样，“百分之八十五的失败原因是系统和流程的缺陷，而不是员工的缺陷。管理层的作用是改变流程，而不是纠缠个人做得更好。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/survey-employees-want-business-technologies-to-be- more-collaborative&quot;>;员工常见的抱怨&lt;/a>;是他们需要在大量的应用程序之间导航才能完成工作。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.mulesoft.com/ty-report-connectivity-benchmark.html#loaded&quot;>;企业平均使用&lt;/a>;超过 1,000 个不同的应用程序，其中只有 29% 是集成的（即相互沟通）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;技术本身并不是目的，而是提高生产力和减少工作量的工具。然而我们的研究表明，技术是员工体验评价最差的维度之一：不到三分之一的员工表示他们公司的技术有效，不到四分之一的员工表示他们配备了无缝技术。即使是最高管理层也明白这一点：只有 52% 的高管表示，他们的公司为员工提供了有效的技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您能想象要求客户在多个选项卡之间切换只是为了向您下订单吗？ ？可能不会——大多数公司都在努力减少客户的这种摩擦。然而，当员工使用的系统未集成时，这就是我们每天对他们提出的要求。结果是满意度降低和糟糕的员工体验。我们必须确保客户体验和员工体验都获得平等的资源。如果您将精力转移给员工，那么节省客户时间只会获得很少或没有收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;重振员工体验&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 和大辞职激励员工重新评估他们的工作优先事项并赋予他们采取行动的权力。这促使公司重新认识到曾经的既定事实：他们最宝贵的资源是他们的员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一开始是对领导者如何拯救公司免遭人才外流的警钟，但也可能是一个机会增长和竞争力 - 但前提是他们学会通过关注信任、最高管理层责任、一致性、认可和技术来平衡客户体验和员工体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这五个要素是相互交织的。每个都建立在其他的基础上，以建立更强大的员工体验并释放新的价值。快乐的员工会带来快乐的客户，管理好两者之间的关系也会让领导者和投资者感到快乐。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The State of Globalization in 2023]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_1383390211.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;丹尼尔·格里泽尔吉/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Covid-19 大流行之初，贸易、资本和人员流动急剧下降，引发了一波关于全球化终结的猜测浪潮，俄罗斯入侵乌克兰引发了更多关于国家自给自足倒退的预测。但是，根据最新的 DHL 全球连通性指数研究，国际流动没有显示出持续下滑的迹象。数据显示美国和中国之间存在广泛的脱钩模式，但与美国和中国地缘政治结盟的国家的流动并没有“减少”。至少现在还没有？表明敌对集团之间存在更广泛的分歧。也没有证据表明全球化正在让位于区域化。尽管企业确实需要针对地缘政治紧张局势加剧进行调整，但它们不应放弃全球战略。事实上，企业去全球化可能比通过集中调整来缓解地缘政治风险更具风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization- in-2023?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;有关全球危机和不断升级的地缘政治紧张局势是否已开始逆转全球化的争论的核心是三个关键问题：跨境贸易、资金、信息、人员流动出现逆转？地缘政治紧张局势是否正在将世界经济分裂成相互竞争的集团？全球化正在让位于区域化吗？尽管有证据表明中美脱钩，这三个问题的答案仍然是“否”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这一结果——脱钩但不去全球化——意味着大多数跨国公司应该通过有针对性的调整来应对日益加剧的地缘政治紧张局势。他们的全球战略和风险管理。虽然公共政策环境变得不利于全球化，但全球流动的弹性提醒人们不要基于市场全球化程度大幅降低的观念而进行更剧烈的战略变化。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;全球流动出现逆转？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;贸易、资本和人员流动急剧下降&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/will-covid-19-have-a- permanent-impact- on-globalization&quot;>;在 Covid-19 大流行之初&lt;/a>;引发了一波关于&lt;a href=&quot;https://foreignpolicy.com/2020/04/03/coronavirus-end-globalization/ ”全球化的终结&lt;/a>;以及俄罗斯对乌克兰的入侵带来了更多关于倒退到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakviews/ukraine-speeds-global-rush-self- sufficiency-2022-03-09/&quot;>;国家自给自足&lt;/a>;。但国际流动没有显示出持续低迷的迹象。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;DHL 全球连通性指数&lt;/a>;，由我们的团队开发&lt;a href=&quot;https://stern.nyu.edu/globalization&quot;>;纽约大学斯特恩管理未来中心&lt;/a>;通过比较国际流量的增长与国内流量的增长来衡量全球化的“深度”经济活动。我们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/global-en/delivered/globalization/global-connectedness-index.html#parsysPath_download_box_copy_co&quot;>;最新报告&lt;/a>;表明，贸易、资本、到 2021 年，信息流已高于大流行前的水平，国际人员流动将在 2022 年加速恢复。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!--开始——全球人员流动已基本恢复到大流行前的水平以上。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360176&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_INDEX_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;来源： DHL 全球连通性指数 2022&quot; title=&quot;全球流量已基本恢复到大流行前的水平以上。&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;626&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和视觉中的更多 HBR 图表 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p >; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- 结束——全球流量已基本恢复至疫情前水平以上。-->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/后国际贸易迅速反弹05/will-covid-19-have-a- permanent-impact-on-globalization&quot;>;在大流行开始时直线下降&lt;/a>;。世界货物贸易量&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-november-2022&quot;>;在 2022 年中期达到了大流行前水平的 10%&lt;/a>;，服务贸易也回到了高于&lt;a href=&quot;https: //documents.worldbank.org/en/publication/documents-reports/documentdetail/099444311022220882/idu026d6c21108fa504c770ae550637a6bc89aa7&quot;>;大流行前水平&lt;/a>;。初步数据&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;表明&lt;/a>;的价值2022 年，世界出口占 GDP 的比重有所上升，达到 2008 年创下的&lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/NE.EXP.GNFS.ZS&quot;>;历史新高&lt;/a>;。 2022 年底，全球经济增长放缓导致贸易&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-march-2023&quot;>;疲软&lt;/a>;，但国际货币基金组织 (国际货币基金组织）的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;最新预测&lt;/a>;仍然呼吁贸易在 2023 年以 2.4% 的温和速度增长，然后在 2024 年加速到更典型的增长率 (3.5%)。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;国际商业投资也从新冠疫情初期的下降中迅速复苏。 19 流行病。外国直接投资 (FDI) 流量（反映公司在海外购买、建设或再投资业务）在 2020 年大幅下降，但&lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot; >;到 2021 年恢复到大流行前&lt;/a>;水平。外国直接投资流量，如贸易，&lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/system/files/official-document/diaeiainf2022d5_en.pdf&quot;>;减弱&lt;/a >; 乌克兰战争爆发后，但没有&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oecd.org/daf/inv/investment-policy/FDI-in-Figures-April-2023.pdf&quot;>; &lt;/a>; 与 Covid-19 大流行开始时类似的崩溃迹象。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;企业全球化的其他衡量标准证实，即使 FDI 流量仍然存在，企业并没有广泛撤出外国市场低于历史峰值水平。使用外国知识产权的付费&lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BM.GSR.ROYL.CD&quot;>;持续增长&lt;/a>;，而跨国并购份额；交易&lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;保持稳定&lt;/a>;，跨国公司海外业务在全球产出中所占的份额刚刚&lt;a href=&quot;https: //unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;从 2000 年代中期创下的历史高位小幅回落&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然 Covid-19 疫情暂时减弱贸易和资本流动，导致国际数据流激增。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techblog.comsoc.org/2022/09/19/telegeography-global-internet-bandwidth-rose-by-28-in-2022/#:~:text=According%20to% 20Telegeography%2C%20Global%20internet,%2Dyear%20CAGR%20of%2029%25.&quot;>;随着面对面互动被在线活动取代，国际互联网流量增长率在 2020 年翻了一番，并且继续增长2021 年和 2022 年每年增长 20% 至 30%。与 2019 年相比，2022 年跨境数据量增加了一倍多。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;国际人员流动受到 Covid-19 大流行的最严重打击，但正在完全康复的路上。联合国最新预测&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.e-unwto.org/doi/abs/10.18111/wtobarometereng.2023.21.1.2&quot;>;预测&lt;/a>;前往国外旅行的人数将仅为到 2023 年，这一数字将比大流行前的水平低 5% 到 20%。事实证明，移民也具有弹性，居住在出生国以外的人口比例&lt;a href=&quot;https://worldmigrationreport.iom.int/wmr-2022-互动/&quot;>;即使在 2020 年，仍继续上升&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;总而言之，有关全球流动增长的数据强烈反驳了大规模从国际活动转向国内活动的观点。大多数类型的国际流动都处于或接近历史最高水平，而 2022 年末和 2023 年初贸易等一些流动的疲软主要反映了为了抑制通胀而大幅加息后全球经济增长放缓。&lt;/ p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;地缘政治紧张局势是否正在使世界经济分裂成敌对集团？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;随着美国和中国之间的紧张局势持续升级，&lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/06/shifting-geopolitical-tectonic-plates-straight-talk&quot;>;人们越来越担心&lt;/a>;新的冷战可能会导致代价高昂的世界经济的分歧。关于国际流动的最新数据确实显示了美国和中国之间广泛的脱钩模式，但与美国和中国地缘政治结盟的国家的流动至少目前并不表明敌对集团之间存在更广泛的分歧，这是一个结果&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/News/Articles/2023/03/25/032623md-china-development-forum-remarks&quot;>;国际货币基金组织警告&lt;/a>;将“离开为了衡量中美脱钩，DHL 全球连通性指数报告考察了 11 类贸易、资本、信息和人员流动，发现美国和中国都自 2016 年以来，两国大幅减少了对彼此流量的关注。流入或流出中国的美国流量份额在 11 个类别中的 8 个类别中下降，平均从 9.3% 降至 7.3%（使用我们指数流量权重的加权平均值）。中国对美国的流量份额在 10 个类别中的 7 个类别中下降，平均从 17.8% 下降到 14.3%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- 开始 -- 衡量中美脱钩。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360174&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt; p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和数据中的更多 HBR 图表。视觉效果&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!--结束--衡量中美脱钩。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，美中脱钩的程度不应被夸大。美国和中国之间的贸易、资本、信息和人员流动总量仍然比任何其他没有共同边界的国家都要大。以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.piie.com/blogs/realtime-economics/ Five-years-trade-war-china-continues-its-slow-decoupling-us-exports&quot;>;美元价值&lt;/ 2022 年，美国和中国之间的贸易额增长至&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/foreign-trade/balance/c5700.html&quot;>;历史新高&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;更重要的是，在全球层面上，地缘政治上与美国和中国结盟的国家的流动表明，世界经济并没有出现有意义的分裂，形成相互竞争的集团。美国和中国的亲密盟友（按&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.capitaleconomics.com/clients/publications/china-economics/china-economics-focus/mapping-decoupling&quot;>;资本经济学分类&lt;/a） >;）没有大幅减少与竞争对手集团的流量份额。在某些领域，例如进口和科研合作，美国的盟友甚至增加了与中国及其盟友的往来份额，而美国则退出了这些交流。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start ——全球资金流并没有分裂成美国和中国的竞争对手。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360175&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_ALLIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;来源：国际货币基金组织贸易统计方向、联合国商品贸易统计数据库、外国直接投资市场、汤森路透、国际货币基金组织 CPIS、Clarivate Web of Science、联合国经济和社会事务部国际移民存量、联合国世界贸易组织旅游统计、凯投宏观&quot; title=&quot;全球流动并未分裂至中美竞争对手集团.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1157&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot; noopener&quot;>;查看更多 HBR 数据与视觉图表 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- 结束 -- 全球流动并未破裂进入敌对的中美集团。-->;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;全球化让位于区域化吗？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;地缘政治紧张局势加剧——以及新冠疫情期间的供应中断-19 大流行 — 也促使许多观察家&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;预测全球化向区域化的转变&lt;/a>;。换句话说，许多人预计国际流动的比例将不断上升，将发生在区域内部，而不是区域之间。然而，实际流动模式的数据并未表明这种转变已经发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们更愿意通过衡量国际流动的平均距离来分析区域化程度上升的可能性，因为更常见的衡量标准——区域内发生的流量份额——&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;产生截然不同的结果&lt;/a>;，具体取决于选择的绘制地点区域边界。如果国际流动变得更加区域化，那么平均而言，它们将在更短的距离内进行。事实上，贸易和许多其他类型的流动往往发生在更远的距离。这种模式的主要例外是人员流动，因为在 Covid-19 大流行期间，邻近国家之间的旅行比例较高。 2020 年和 2021 年，资本流动也发生在较短的距离内，但目前尚不清楚这是否反映了向更加区域化的投资模式的有意义的转变，因为这些流动的波动性往往会导致类似幅度的短期波动。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- 开始——没有证据表明全球化正在让位于区域化。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360177&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_NO_REGIONALIZATION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt; p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和数据中的更多 HBR 图表。视觉效果 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- 结束 -- 没有证据表明全球化正在让位于区域化。 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2020 年和 2021 年贸易流动甚至延伸到更远的距离，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eiu.com/n/campaigns/the-great-unwinding-covid- 19-supply-chains-and-regional-blocs/&quot;>;与预测相反&lt;/a>;，即与流行病相关的中断将促使人们更加依赖附近的供应商。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;这种模式的关键驱动力&lt;/a>;是亚洲制造业的弹性，导致亚洲与遥远地区之间的贸易增加。初步数据还显示，2022 年各国贸易的平均距离有所增加，部分原因是乌克兰战争对贸易模式和大宗商品价格的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;世界贸易是否会持续增长仍然是一个悬而未决的问题。未来将变得更加区域化。许多公司&lt;a href=&quot;https://supplychaindigital.com/supply-chain-risk-management/nearshoring-happening-faster-than-expected-says-gartner&quot;>;专注于近岸生产&lt;/a>;，以便在更近的距离生产商品其客户，主要的供应链重新配置可能需要几年的时间才能执行。许多国家的政府都支持这些区域化努力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一方面，国际流动已经高度区域化，这一事实限制了区域化大幅增长的范围。如上所示，一半以上的贸易已经发生在大致相当于大陆大小的区域内。此外，许多公司没有采用近岸外包，而是采取了其他策略来增强弹性，例如-重塑供应链&quot;>;数字化和双重采购&lt;/a>;。与此同时，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/d739cd47-e434-43c3-9b4e-472bcef4abaf&quot;>;集装箱运输成本&lt;/a>;已经回落，而&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/01/31/world-economic-outlook-update-january-2023&quot;>;通货膨胀依然居高不下&lt;/a>;，增强了低成本来源的吸引力&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;地缘政治动荡与全球战略&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;虽然全球流动仍然保持弹性，但公共政策环境对企业来说变得更具挑战性全球业务。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heritage.org/index/trade-freedom&quot;>;贸易保护主义&lt;/a>;有所抬头，&lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment- report-2022&quot;>;国际投资&lt;/a>;因国家安全原因面临更严格的审查，&lt;a href=&quot;https://itif.org/publications/2021/07/19/how-barriers-cross-border-data- flow-are-spreading-globally-what-they-cost/&quot;>;数据流限制&lt;/a>;正在激增，并且&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hinrichfoundation.com/research/article/wto/international -交易系统受到信任侵蚀的威胁/&quot;>;国际机构&lt;/a>;在成员国之间关系紧张的情况下难以发挥作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;全球战略的核心原则可以&lt;a href =&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-new-global-road-map-enduring-strategies-for-turbulent-times/10172&quot;>;帮助企业领导者驾驭&lt;/a>;这个动荡的环境。全球化的关键&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbsp.harvard.edu/product/2620BC-PDF-ENG&quot;>;业务驱动力&lt;/a>;——更多的增长和创新，加上更低的成本和更好的多元化风险——仍然存在强大，并且&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/strategy-and-corporate-finance/our-insights/global-flows-the-ties-that-bind-in-an-interconnected- world&quot;>;新技术&lt;/a>;继续扩大国际机遇。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但跨越地缘政治鸿沟运营的挑战和风险&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/how-companies-can-navigate-今天的地缘政治风险&quot;>;已经增加&lt;/a>;。全球战略家经常发现，将这种转变视为改变之间的&lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;隐喻距离&lt;/a>;是有用的。国家。日益紧张的局势拉大了地缘政治竞争对手之间的距离，并拉近了友好国家之间的距离，至少相对而言是这样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;全球战略的基本概念之一是，国内企业拥有一个&lt;a href=&quot;https ://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1075425312000543?casa_token=y_2Xo8t1_UwAAAAA:29n5LgCrPdVFnV9rfY1GksXnPbZQZ6OscJKksAyd7DAw_sK87s3-jNyiDEMdoYmWEnRmQRY&quot;>;主场优势&lt;/ a>; 超过外国公司，以及必须&lt;a href=&quot;/2001 /09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;弥合距离更短&lt;/a>;——不仅在地理上，而且在政治上——通常比必须弥合更远距离的公司更有优势。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/41411007&quot;>;公司的独特资产&lt;/a>; - 技术、品牌价值等 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org /10.1017/9781316678503.007&quot;>;对其能够成功桥接的距离产生很大影响&lt;/a>;。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;其业务对地缘政治和其他跨国距离来源的敏感性&lt;/a>;也是如此.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;领导者应该检查他们在距离越来越远和越来越远的国家中的竞争地位有多强，看看他们是否需要重新平衡他们的地理投资组合。请记住，不断变化的地缘政治关系既能创造机遇，也能带来挑战。一家公司也许能够从地缘政治对手的竞争对手那里赢得业务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果一家公司拥有足够强大的优势来跨越地缘政治分歧进行竞争，&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/the-strategic-脱钩的挑战&quot;>;可能需要改变其在政治上遥远的市场中的运作方式&lt;/a>;。一种常见的方法是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-based-managers-gain-more-autonomy-from-global-companies-ac8f66d3&quot;>;提供更多自主权&lt;/a>;帮助当地管理者更好地调整运营以适应日益多样化的条件。这可能很有用，但重要的是不要高估外国公司可以走多远才能被视为本土企业。当紧要关头，公司的&lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/the-cosmopolitan-corporation&quot;>;大本营仍然是其感知（而且通常是真实）忠诚的核心&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;正如许多在俄罗斯经营的西方公司在全面入侵乌克兰后所看到的那样，紧张局势可能会升级到除了退出市场之外别无选择的地步。跨地缘政治分歧拥有大量业务的公司应该做好准备，应对逐渐脱钩转变为突然分离的意外情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不过，好消息是，大多数公司不需要从根本上重组其全球战略审慎应对地缘政治紧张局势。正如我们所看到的，中美脱钩至少还没有开始将世界经济分裂为相互竞争的集团，全球化尚未让位于区域化，大多数类型的国际流动仍在增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;脱钩而不去全球化通常需要对全球战略进行重点调整，这不仅是因为全球流动的弹性，还因为大多数国际业务已经发生在邻近的友好国家之间。以美国为例，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bea.gov/news/2023/us-international-trade-goods-and-services-december-and-annual-2022&quot;>;进口&lt;/a到 2022 年，来自加拿大和墨西哥的产量将比中国多出 66%，来自欧洲的产量将多出 35%。在全球范围内，DHL 全球互联指数衡量的流量有一半发生在世界主要地区，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/content/dam/dhl/global/dhl-spotlight/documents/pdf /10-years-lessons-gci-2021-report.pdf&quot;>;在国家之间的距离和差异没有影响的世界中，比人们预期的要多三倍&lt;/a>;。近岸外包和友岸外包实际上是全球化的长期特征，并且针对特定漏洞的增加将与&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wto.org/english/news_e/spno_e/spno32_e. htm&quot;>;世贸组织总干事恩戈齐·奥孔乔-伊维拉 (Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala) 设想&lt;/a>;为“贸易的未来”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对企业国际运营方式的重点调整也与政策圈日益普遍的观点相一致： “去风险”是对地缘政治紧张局势的更好回应，而不是完全脱钩。欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉·冯德莱恩&lt;a href=&quot;https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/speech_23_2063&quot;>;在 2023 年 3 月的一次演讲中&lt;/a提出强调“去风险”该报告将大多数欧盟与中国的贸易描述为“互惠互利且‘无风险’”，但也强调了欧盟98%的稀土供应、97%的锂和93%的镁供应依赖中国的问题。不到两个月后，美国和其他大型发达经济体&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/05/20/g7-hiroshima-leaders-communique/ &quot;>;在 2023 年 5 月的 G7 峰会上正式接受&lt;/a>;“去风险，而不是脱钩”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最重要的是，企业确实需要针对地缘政治紧张局势加剧进行调整，但他们应该不要因为中美脱钩必然导致去全球化而放弃全球战略。事实上，企业去全球化&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/abandoning-globalization-will-only-hurt-us-businesses&quot;>;可能是一条比进行集中调整以减轻地缘政治风险更具风险的道路&lt;/a>;。全球战略的另一个原则是企业应将其战略与市场的全球化相结合。只要市场不去全球化，退出全球化的公司就可能使其竞争地位面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[In Uncertain Times, Embrace Imperfectionism]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_10_1192111806.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;变革正在加速，每个行业领域都存在不确定性和颠覆威胁。全球赢家通吃竞争的变化步伐和兴起意味着传统的产品市场结构战略方法以及核心能力思维难以在实践中实施，并可能产生误导性的答案。在当今的条件下，作者认为实时问题解决应该成为战略制定的核心，而不是理论框架，并且他们提出了这种方法的框架。这种方法要求公司通过多个视角或有利位置来审视战略，通常将这些视角或优势锚定在公司外部的生态系统或之外。通过供应商、客户、当前竞争对手和潜在外部进入者的视角来审视您的业务，将使您对威胁和机遇有更多的了解，而不是停留在公司的主流思维方式和惯例中。它还应该寻求通过实验生成关于这些观点的新数据，通过众包外部想法和技术来增强这些新数据，以发挥集体智慧。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07 /in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;如果您是亚马逊客户，您很可能遇到过 Amazon Prime 和 Zappos 等家喻户晓的品牌。您不太可能注意到亚马逊为将其核心业务扩展到消费者金融服务之外所采取的小步骤。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;收购 TextPayMe、投资 Bill Me Later、从 GoPago 聘请团队以及远程卡支付设备 Amazon Local Register 的推出都是温和的举动，涉及的财务支出很少，并且在当时引起的关注相对较少。他们也以明显的失败告终，TextPayMe 于 2014 年关闭，Local Register 在 Square 的竞争下退出市场，Bill Me Later 被竞争对手 PayPal 收购。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，如今亚马逊已是一家强大的公司。在消费金融领域，其泛经济亚马逊在美国拥有 24% 的用户份额支付服务&lt;/a>;，并定位于进一步发展成为全球金融参与者。该公司是如何通过一系列看似不起眼的小举措取得大规模成功的？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;答案是，亚马逊是一个不完美主义者，这是我们在帮助公司和非营利组织的过程中发展了几十年的概念。 ，我们认为这一点对于组织在当今独特不确定的经济环境中努力繁荣至关重要。正如我们将解释的，不完美主义是一种公司成长的方法，不是通过遵循战略框架或计划，而是通过实时的多次、频繁的实验，逐步积累有价值的知识、资产和能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;为什么需要新方法&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们都经历过：变革正在加速，每个行业领域都存在不确定性和颠覆威胁。人工智能、可编程生物学、机器人技术和其他技术正在改变现有行业并催生新行业。外部冲击跨越国界，影响所有企业，甚至那些看似享有结构性优势的企业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个动荡多变的环境中，既定的战略制定方法不再有效。没有稳定的产业结构或新的市场均衡可以回归。全球赢家通吃竞争的变化速度和兴起意味着传统的产品市场结构方法以及核心能力思维在实践中难以实施，并且可能会产生误导性的答案。在特定领域推翻主导公司的玩家更有可能以&lt;em>;从头&lt;/em>;的方式从外部进入，而不是成为现有的竞争对手。看看 Instagram、Quibi 和 TikTok 在短视频社交媒体领域的战斗就知道了——现在的获胜者在五年前还默默无闻。 &amp;nbsp;我们需要响应式战略方法来应对外部波动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种变化的环境的一个影响是，大多数公司战略规划流程不适合不确定且快速变化的世界，使许多管理团队陷入紧张之中观望态度。&amp;nbsp;其他公司领导者通过恐慌性押注来避免停滞，包括“未雨绸缪”收购，试图“拥有”新空间，但通常收效甚微。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你应该做什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;拥抱不完美&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;正如我们在书中所描述的，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Imperfectionists% 3A+战略+心态+for+不确定+时代-p-9781119835677&quot;>;&lt;em>;不完美主义者&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，亚马逊没有等待战略清晰的时刻，也没有利用其庞大的余额收购一家难以消化的银行的单据。它通过采取一些小步骤，逐渐陷入了不确定性：投资拥有有趣技术的年轻公司，从失败的金融科技公司聘请团队，以及推出内部开发的服务和工具。它运行了多个并行的计划，并了解哪些有效，哪些无效。它通过大多后果低且可逆的举措建立了宝贵的能力和资产。其建立主要金融服务业务的方法中没有战略框架的概念。最终结果就是我们所说的举措阶梯、务实的揭示策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359260&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/ Article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_STAIRCASE_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; >;查看数据和数据中的更多 HBR 图表视觉 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;这种循序渐进的做法并非偶然——亚马逊在进入商业金融领域时也遵循了同样的做法以及它对云计算的创建和主导地位。现在它似乎正在医疗保健领域做类似的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在当今的条件下，我们认为，战略制定的核心应该是实时解决问题，而不是理论框架。这从一个假设开始，通常被视为一个大胆的问题，当得到回答时，将为解决方案阶梯的第一步提供战略洞察力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，战略制定通常会通过多个镜头或有利位置来看待事物将这些内容锚定在公司外部的生态系统中或之外。通过供应商、客户、当前竞争对手和潜在外部进入者的视角来审视您的业务，将使您对威胁和机遇有更多的了解，而不是停留在公司的主流思维方式和惯例中。在组织的各个层面举办观点采择研讨会可以帮助提出新的观察结果，这些观察结果可以成为新战略路径的核心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;接下来，它通过实验寻求有关这些观点的新数据，并通过众包来扩充这些新数据发挥集体智慧的外部想法和技术。可以肯定的是，很少有组织善于让其他人在自己的花园里辛勤劳作，但获得新能力的一种途径是众包新技术和方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这导致了一项务实的计划，以应对不确定性，收集更多信息从小的举动中获取信息，同时增加能力和资产，尽可能地消除他人的风险，并从错误和成功中吸取教训。它涉及到认识到战略决策是概率性的赌注，并且采取的行动与赔率的评估相称。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大型企业尤其在这一点上挣扎。他们通常不愿意从概率角度进行思考，这反过来又会产生一种强大的风险规避形式，如 &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/your-company-is-too-risk-averse 中所述&quot;>;2020 年 HBR 文章&lt;/a>;，作者：Dan Lovallo、Tim Koller、Robert Uhlaner 和诺贝尔奖获得者 Daniel Kahneman。他们发现，即使有利的可能性很明显，管理者仍坚持做出规避风险的选择。克服这种根深蒂固的偏见的一个起点是坚持所有策略讨论都包括概率估计和潜在结果的范围。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359259&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_IMPERFECTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target= &quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;在数据和图表中查看更多 HBR 图表视觉效果&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我们的研究表明，这种不确定性下的战略方法不仅被亚马逊等公司有效地采用，其他精明的公司和非营利组织也一样。这里有四个例子，每个例子都说明了该过程的四个主要组成部分之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Invisalign 隐适美：透过新镜片看事物&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;直到 20 世纪 90 年代初期，正畸几十年来牙套几乎没有改变。渐进式的改进来自牙科实践内部，但缺乏重大创新。凯尔西·沃斯 (Kelsey Wirth) 和齐亚·奇什蒂 (Zia Chishti) 是斯坦福商学院的 MBA 学生，没有牙科资格，他们致力于将一种全新的、不同的视角应用于牙齿矫正。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;齐亚成年后只有经济能力来矫正牙齿，就在商学院之前不久。当他终于摘下牙套时，他注意到了一些有趣的事情：他的保持器几乎看不见，但它仍然移动了他的牙齿，如果他忘记戴几天，他就能感觉到。这个小小的见解激发了一个革命性的假设：如果一个简单的塑料保持器可以稍微移动牙齿，也许可以改进技术以移动牙齿很多，但不会像传统牙套那样影响人的外观。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; Chishti 和 Wirth 提出了一系列透明的、定制的可拆卸塑料对齐保持器，通过软件设计的治疗计划开发。他们将他们的解决方案称为 Invisalign 隐适美，强调矫正器对其他人来说并不显眼。通过每隔几周更换一套新牙套，患者的牙齿将逐渐移动到所需的位置，而无需使用金属牙套。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过这些以客户和技术为中心的新颖产品来解决牙齿矫正问题Zia 和 Kelsey 使正畸治疗变得不那么痛苦、不那么尴尬，而且更便宜。如今，该公司已经改变了牙齿矫正行业，市值超过 150 亿美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;SpaceX：不懈的实验&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;每个人都知道使用 A/ 的软件公司B测试以完善产品。但这种方法能否在最终的重工业领域取得战略成功呢？在短短二十年的时间里，SpaceX 通过不懈的实验极大地改变了近地太空旅行。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;SpaceX 工程师们已经学会了通过反复测试新假设，做出小动作，累积成大改进。这种快速测试和改进的方法使他们能够以合理的成本获取新信息，并更快地沿着经验曲线前进。他们将自己的决策系统称为“飞行、测试、失败、修复”，并承认失败（“计划外拆卸”）是测试可能性边界的必要部分。他们率先采用低成本 3D 打印火箭部件，使更多部件可重复使用，并放弃昂贵的外部承包，80% 的部件在内部生产。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;向下移动成本曲线要求大幅增加发射频率。在其航天飞机计划的 30 年期间，NASA 平均每年飞行 4.5 次。 2021 年，Space X 在轨道上发射了 31 枚火箭，高于前一年的 26 枚。 2022 年初，它每月发射三到五个任务。更频繁的发射和其他创新极大地降低了将一公斤质量送入太空的成本。从 1970 年代到 2000 年代初，这一成本基本没有变化，平均每公斤成本为 54,550 美元。 SpaceX 已将每公斤成本削减至 2,720 美元，降低了 95%。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;TNC FishFace：利用集体智慧&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;大自然保护协会跨国公司 (TNC) 是一家致力于保护濒危鱼类种群的全球保护组织，正在寻找有效的策略来在海上渔船上实施保护措施。 TNC 想知道渔船是否可以部署数字技术来识别濒临灭绝的物种，以便它们可以在还活着的情况下返回大海。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但 TNC 本身不具备开发解决方案所需的人工智能技能，因此它决定通过 Kaggle（一个举办机器学习竞赛的在线平台）众包解决方案。 TNC 竞赛在五个月内吸引了 2,293 名参赛者，奖金为 150,000 美元。选择获胜作品后，TNC 现在拥有一个准确率达到 90% 到 95% 的原型。它被称为 FishFace。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了解决复杂的渔业监管合规问题，TNC 立足于自身组织的能力之外，邀请世界上最优秀的人工智能开发人员提供新颖的战略解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;人工智能群体平台是这种方法的一种变体，对于预测不确定事件特别有用。斯坦福大学医学院的一项研究&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;发现，使用 Swarm AI 算法的医生群体&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/swarm-ai-与仅使用历史数据的最先进的深度学习算法相比，系统的诊断准确率提高了 22%&lt;/a>;。不同之处在于群体中的参与者实时“一起思考”，并通过算法控制的交互汇聚解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Quib​​i 与 TikTok：锚定内部与外部&lt;/strong>;&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;在每个例子中，导致突破性战略思想的战略洞察力的很大一部分是锚定在行业传统边界之外的想法。要做到这一点并不容易——想想 Quibi 的经历。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Quib​​i 是一个简短的流媒体平台，于 2020 年 4 月大张旗鼓地推出；到 12 月 1 日，该公司解散，损失超过 10 亿美元。 A级投资者包括阿里巴巴、迪士尼、谷歌和高盛。全明星管理层由 eBay 和惠普前首席执行官梅格·惠特曼 (Meg Whitman) 以及梦工厂的杰弗里·卡森伯格 (Jeffrey Katzenberg) 领衔。投资者确信这是一个了解市场需求的内部人士团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Quib​​i 应用程序在 2020 年第二季度的下载量为 450 万次，但到 2020 年第三季度 Quibi 的下载量仅为 71 万次付费订阅者，并且在免费试用期满后失去了 90% 的早期用户。 Quibi 扎根于旧的好莱坞模式，但在短视频竞争对手 TikTok 爆发式增长（2020 年第一季度下载量达到 3.15 亿次）时却失败了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;区别？ TikTok 通过对用户提供的内容进行高度复杂的人工智能管理，拥抱了用户的集体智慧。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;当你回顾亚马逊进军消费金融服务或上面的其他例子时，它们看起来像是一位战略大师的杰作。但这掩盖了现实：为了建立支持这些职位的能力和资产，我们采取了许多小举措，包括一路上的失误和失​​败。战略上灵活的组织明确地规划了进入新领域的潜在途径，并根据自己的经验更新其模型。他们了解以适度成本建立地位的可逆战略举措与孤注一掷决策之间的区别。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div >;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt; a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Ways to Become a More Collaborative Leader]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_08_1484644095.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In today&amp;#8217;s fast-paced corporate landscape, most highly experienced leaders entering an organization are driven by a desire to make a significant impact and drive meaningful change. However, the approach they adopt in championing new ideas becomes the differentiating factor between success and failure. Unfortunately, when faced with resistance, some leaders become frustrated and disengaged or even choose to leave the organization. Affecting lasting change is not a solitary quest, but an inherently shared effort. It requires embracing a collaborative mindset that respects and includes diverse perspectives, maintains a strategic focus, and patiently navigates the complexities of organizational dynamics. It&amp;#8217;s not about surrendering your passion or advocacy but leveraging them in a more inclusive, strategic, and ultimately effective way. The author recommends shifting your mental model from that of a crusader to that of a collaborative leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When “Kathy,” a former client of Luis&#39;s, got hired as a VP at a fintech company, she wanted to have an impact. She saw things that could be better, had ideas about how to change them, and was hungry to get down to the business of making those changes. She approached change-making like a crusader, driven by her passion for what she believed in. She expressed her ideas fervently,&amp;nbsp;making impassioned speeches during team meetings. She fearlessly pointed out what was going wrong and what could be better. And as someone who was seen as not being afraid to “speak truth to power,” she adopted the role of advocate for less-vocal or more junior team members. While on occasion these pitches landed and led to short-term change, she was much more frequently frustrated at the lack of action that resulted. Worse, this approach made her increasingly isolated in the organization, feeding a vicious cycle that made it increasingly difficult for her to affect change.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In today&#39;s fast-paced corporate landscape, most highly experienced leaders entering an organization are driven by a desire to make a significant impact and drive meaningful change. However, the approach they adopt in championing new ideas becomes the differentiating factor between success and failure. Unfortunately, when faced with resistance, some leaders become frustrated and disengaged or even choose to leave the organization. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14697010500082902&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; that this is particularly true for leaders who are hired specifically to be “change agents.” Moreover, the leadership training and research firm Leadership IQ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leadershipiq.com/blogs/leadershipiq/35354241-why-new-hires-fail-emotional-intelligence-vs-skills&quot;>;found&lt;/a>; that 46% of newly hired executives fail within the first 18 months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recognizing the need for a transformative approach that would allow her to advocate for her ideas without alienating others, Kathy needed to shift her mental model from that of a crusader to that of a collaborative leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The crusader approach: Passionate but isolating&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A crusader is a leadership style described in the book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Built-Growth-Builder-Personality-Business/dp/1633692760&quot;>;&lt;em>;Built for Growth&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;. The crusader embodies a passionate advocacy for their vision, values, and goals. Their decisions are guided by a set of core beliefs and values. They tackle change directly and forcefully, driven by a profound sense of purpose that fuels their willingness to voice their opinions, even in the face of opposition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While this approach can initially instill confidence and self-efficacy as leaders witness the short-term positive impact of their ideas, it often proves counterproductive in the long run. The crusader leader is often perceived as closed minded, inflexible, and overly passionate. While passion can be a positive trait, it becomes detrimental when accompanied by predictable negative behaviors. Crusader leaders tend to:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Speak up frequently and vehemently, sometimes to the point of dominating conversations.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Interrupt others or answer questions with their viewpoint. In other words, they don&#39;t always listen to understand.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Be outspoken about their opinions, often pushing their own agenda without considering other perspectives.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Exhibit visible and frequent frustration when faced with resistance, doubling down on justifying or defending their approach, often assuming that pushback stems from ignorance rather than a genuine divergence of viewpoints.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Are you a crusader leader?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As you reflect on your leadership style, you might recognize some traits of a crusader. Even though there&#39;s no single reason why someone might adopt this approach, it can be driven by various factors, each with its own set of consequences. It&#39;s important to be introspective and understand the root cause and impact of your leadership style so you can adopt a more balanced one. Here are some key indicators of crusader approach:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You&#39;re passionate.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Leaders who are passionate about an issue may display behavior that can be misinterpreted as inflexible and defensive. They often have considerable expertise in an area. They believe passionately that their way is the best way forward, which makes them less likely to accept or consider alternative perspectives. This leads to exhaustion, as &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/dont-let-passion-lead-to-burnout-on-your-team&quot;>;research has shown&lt;/a>; that prioritizing passion above all else can be ineffective and harmful.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You get frustrated by the slow pace of a particular change.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Crusader leaders see themselves as needing to single-handedly push hard to make progress, adopting a tightly focused approach and losing the opportunity to recruit supporters and collaborators to help make lasting change. Their sense of urgency is not shared by the group they&#39;re trying to influence.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You&#39;ve seen the crusader approach work in the past. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some leaders default to the crusader style because they&#39;ve seen its immediate results in past situations. They&#39;ve witnessed how this approach can achieve impressive results, overwhelming dissent and driving to decisions — in the short term. But in the longer term, these tactics can backfire and undermine the crusader&#39;s ability to achieve lasting change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to make the shift from a crusader to collaborative leader&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A more effective approach to driving change in the workplace involves adopting the mindset of a collaborator. Instead of doggedly pursuing a myopic perspective, collaborators focus on building relationships, understanding organizational dynamics and reasons for resistance, and using this knowledge to advocate for change in a shared, strategic manner. Here are six ways to become a more collaborative leader:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Understand the organizational culture.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Whether we like it or not, how influential we are is ultimately in the hands of those we want to influence. And influence is highly context dependent. Instead of sticking to your guns and putting yourself out there without understanding the context you&#39;re operating in, a better approach is to identify how things work in your organization. Look for clues about what works and what doesn&#39;t. In meetings, pay attention to which behaviors are rewarded and which aren&#39;t as effective. Watch the most effective leaders in the organization and consider asking them how they might approach a particular situation. Is their approach different from yours? When you understand the “rules” of the game, you&#39;ll be in a much better position to play it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Choose your battles.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Crusaders tend to advocate for changing big things — things that, to their frustration, are complex and require a winning coalition. And in some instances, the crusader isn&#39;t the right person to make those changes. For instance, suppose you&#39;re a manager at a software company and notice inefficiencies in both the software development process and the company&#39;s recruitment strategy. While your passion and drive may urge you to tackle both issues, overhauling the recruitment strategy might be more complex, requiring collaborative efforts and a broad coalition to address effectively. Fighting the recruitment battle can lead to frustration, burnout, and an erosion of credibility if changes don&#39;t materialize quickly. And most likely, the recruitment team will respond defensively to your initiative. Instead, focus your energy and resources on streamlining the software development process, an area where you can make a significant and meaningful impact given your expertise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Seek feedback.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Others often see us more objectively than we see ourselves. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Self-Insight-Roadblocks-Detours-Knowing-Psychology/dp/0415654173/&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; has shown that people don&#39;t realize how they behave in certain situations, or they misremember their actions, leading to an inaccurate perception of themselves. Crusaders, often consumed by their vision, may overlook crucial details or perspectives, leading to an incomplete view of the situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be relentless about asking for feedback and suggestions to better understand how your approach is being perceived and what you can do next time to become more effective. This is a transformative (and often sobering) step for a crusader transitioning to a collaborative leadership style. It not only cultivates self-awareness, but also gives you a comprehensive understanding of your actions&#39; consequences, including potential negative effects on team dynamics, morale, and productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Develop and leverage relationships.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s crucial to build and foster a winning coalition of individuals who can support your ideas. Imagine the organization as a heavy wagon that&#39;s difficult to stop or steer in a different direction from the outside. Instead of trying to push or pull the wagon alone, leaders should get on the wagon and work with the drivers to steer it from the inside. This approach requires building relationships and coalitions within the organization to gain support for ideas and create a sense of shared ownership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An easy way to “get on the wagon” is to align your ideas with other people&#39;s as a way to gain supporters and allies. For example, let&#39;s say you&#39;re a scientist who is concerned about high staff turnover rates. During a meeting, a colleague from HR discusses their goal of increasing employee engagement. Instead of pushing your staff retention concern independently, you could propose a joint project that addresses both concerns — for example, a pilot program in your department that integrates strategies to enhance employee engagement that might reduce turnover rates. By doing so, you&#39;re integrating your initiatives with the needs and concerns of your HR colleague, making it easier for others to support yours and their proposal.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Be open to other perspectives.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To gain influence, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/09/3-ways-to-grow-your-influence-in-a-new-job&quot;>;you must also be open to being influenced&lt;/a>;. Nobody wants to “negotiate” with someone who isn&#39;t open to other perspectives and can only see the world through their own limited view. Instead, try to cultivate genuine curiosity about other ways of seeing challenges and solutions. Instead of digging in or restating your preferred approach, ask open questions of colleagues who don&#39;t share your view and try to identify shared perspectives. While you might see a straight line between the problem and solution based on your perspective and expertise, others may not see the trajectory as clearly and will struggle to enact the desired strategy as a result. Even the right decision can lead to the wrong outcome if you&#39;re unsuccessful in creating a shared understanding of how to successfully implement the change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Focus on long-term goals.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Building lasting change requires maintaining focus on the long-term objective. Sometimes, being a crusader is warranted and appropriate, particularly when urgent action is needed and you have the authority to make a change. However, these situations tend to be few and far between. If you want to achieve ambitious lasting change, it&#39;s unlikely to happen all at once, and you most likely can&#39;t do it by yourself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Confront your crusader self with these three questions: Is this problem mine to solve? Do I need to solve it alone? Do I need to solve it now? With this focus, you can apply the right level of long-term vision to the things that really matter, including letting go of fighting every battle along the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;. 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The need for change is inevitable in any organization, but the approach to driving change is a determinant of its success or failure, as Kathy, our passionate crusader, realized. Affecting lasting change is not a solitary quest, but an inherently shared effort. It requires embracing a collaborative mindset that respects and includes diverse perspectives, maintains a strategic focus, and patiently navigates the complexities of organizational dynamics. It&#39;s not about surrendering your passion or advocacy but leveraging them in a more inclusive, strategic, and ultimately effective way.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the Construction Industry Be Disrupted?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_08_1299614411.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Dan Reynolds Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Construction is often maligned as the industry that technology left behind. Industry observers routinely deride the lack of technological sophistication in the construction industry, and have pigeon-holed it as old-fashioned and lagging behind more forward-looking and purposeful industries such as manufacturing. But that view ignores where the industry has advanced &amp;#8212; specifically, in information management systems that have created significant gains. Moreover, it fails to take into account why automation and robotics don&amp;#8217;t work on jobsites, which is that they&amp;#8217;re often a poor fit for the dynamic environments that bear little resemblance to factory floors. Understanding why some tech takes root and why some doesn&amp;#8217;t, however, is essential to making smart investments in new tools and systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 1910, the French artist Villemard created a series of illustrations imagining life in the year 2000. In one of his drawings, an architect &lt;a href=&quot;https://wearereplicants.wordpress.com/2011/03/10/french-artist-villemards-vision-of-the-future/&quot;>;sits in a booth pushing buttons on a console&lt;/a>; to manipulate a series of machines operating in the usual debris of a construction site. The various machines cut, shape, lift, and place stone blocks to build a house. There are no human laborers in his projection — mechanization has made them obsolete.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Villemard&#39;s vision has not panned out, however. On the contrary, industry observers routinely deride the lack of technological sophistication in the construction industry, and have pigeon-holed it as old-fashioned and lagging behind more forward-looking and purposeful industries such as manufacturing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This story has been told and told again. In the wake of the post-WWII housing boom, the editors of &lt;em>;Fortune&lt;/em>; published a 1947 article titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biblio.com/book/fortune-magazine-volume-xxxvi-number-2/d/1489550271&quot;>;The Industry Capitalism Forgot&lt;/a>;,” in which they mocked homebuilding&#39;s “feudal character” and “picayune scale.” In 2006, MIT Professor John Fernandez summed up the conventional wisdom when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/books/edition/Material_Architecture/AtMrBgAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;dq=the+slowest+of+all+industries+of+such+scale+in+implementing+proven,+scientifically+sound+technological+innovation&amp;amp;pg=PA11&amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;>;he wrote&lt;/a>;: “It is widely believed that construction is the slowest of all industries of such scale in implementing proven, scientifically sound technological innovation.” A decade later, McKinsey consultants &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/reinventing-construction-through-a-productivity-revolution&quot;>;continued the drumbeat&lt;/a>;, blaming limited productivity improvements on “poor project management and execution … underinvestment in skills development, R&amp;amp;D, and innovation.” In early 2023, University of Chicago economists Austan Goolsbee and Chad Syverson published an article titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w30845&quot;>;The Strange and Awful Path of Productivity in the US Construction Sector&lt;/a>;” in which they concluded that aggregate data “demonstrate a large and decades-long decline in construction sector productivity.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Anecdotes about the opposition to change paint a similar picture. Regardless of the era, workers who worried that labor saving devices might deepen the inherent insecurity of life in the trades sometimes frowned on the introduction of new machinery on the construction jobsite. Carpenter Joseph Emanuello &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/j.ctv941wxz.19?seq=2&quot;>;recalled&lt;/a>; the first time he encountered electric circular saws: “One guy took the Skilsaw on the roof of the building and threw it off. He said, &#39;The saw&#39;s too fast, I&#39;m going to cut by hand.&#39;” The hesitancy to adopt innovation extended to the contractor&#39;s office. When John Tocci, fresh out of engineering school, bought an expensive mainframe computer for his multi-generational family general contracting firm in 1983, his father — the owner — looked at the bulky item and grumbled, “When that freaking thing can lay brick, I&#39;ll learn how to use it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But it is easy to exaggerate the level of resistance. In 1993, a researcher conducted interviews with tradesmen about their attitudes toward technological innovation. With few exceptions, they welcomed new tools that made the work safer and less physically demanding and, for the most part, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/23746019&quot;>;their pride in increased production outweighed their fears of displacement&lt;/a>;. In general, construction has adopted an evolutionary, not revolutionary, pace of change.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not everyone wants it to stay that way, however: Villemard has contemporary followers who continue to envision a fully mechanized future for construction, just over the horizon. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.roboticsbusinessreview.com/construction/more-than-7000-robots-will-work-in-construction-by-2025-report-says/&quot;>;2019 report by Tractica&lt;/a>;, a technology market intelligence firm, declared that construction is “ripe for disruption” due to its history of technological underdevelopment and predicts that the purchase of construction robots will increase tenfold by 2025. Gaurav Kikani, vice president of Built Robotics, suggests that there will be “an explosion of robotics” that will replace the eight-hour workday with automated activity around the clock. A recent global survey indicated that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forconstructionpros.com/construction-technology/article/21451998/abb-group-robotic-automations-potential-to-enhance-productivity-efficiency-and-safety-on-construction-sites&quot;>;81% of construction businesses&lt;/a>; will introduce or increase their use of robotics and automation in the coming decade. In a 2020 report, McKinsey &amp;amp; Co. futurists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/McKinsey/Industries/Capital%20Projects%20and%20Infrastructure/Our%20Insights/The%20next%20normal%20in%20construction/The-next-normal-in-construction.pdf&quot;>;predict that 45% of the industry&#39;s value chain&lt;/a>; will shift from traditional processes in the next 15 years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What both the optimists and pessimists struggle with, however, is why some technologies take root in the industry — often creating significant gains in productivity — and why others, such as worksite robots, don&#39;t. Understanding this point will help construction companies and the firms that supply them predict which investments will pay off and which will end up as curiosities that sit gathering dust.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why Certain Tech Doesn&#39;t Take Hold&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many of the inventions breathlessly touted by the industry press remain on the fringes of the industry. State-of the-art six-axis articulated robots may have transformed the auto industry, but their stationery character does not work on a construction site. A robot that is immobile and cannot adjust to the rough terrain and multi-story nature of a building project is functionally useless. Autonomous earth-moving machinery can dig out and prepare foundations. Robots can do simple layout. Drones can navigate job sites and record daily progress. Exoskeletons can relieve the burden of lifting heavy items and YouTube videos portray the wonders of 3D printing. Yet many of these advances remain novelty items, available only to a minority of firms that have the resources and inclination to experiment with equipment and systems that have not consistently been proven to be quality- or cost-effective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People think robots are intelligent. They&#39;re getting better, but they&#39;re still pretty dumb,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/db2b5d64-10e7-11e8-a765-993b2440bd73&quot;>;says Jeremy Hadall&lt;/a>;, chief technologist for robotics and automation at the United Kingdom&#39;s Manufacturing Technology Centre. “Robots have a place in building productivity in the construction industry, but you have to be realistic about what they can do. Are we going to see completely automated robotic building sites in 10 years? No.” Similarly, Erin Bradner, Director of Robotics at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autodeskresearch.com/groups/robotics-lab&quot;>;Autodesk Robotics Lab&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/charlestowersclark/2020/01/10/construction-co-bots-need-to-be-smarter-more-adaptive-part-two/?sh=126d2c296a79&quot;>;suggests the current level of sophistication of co-bots may be exaggerated&lt;/a>;: “They&#39;ll stop when they encounter an obstacle, but you don&#39;t want your project stopping every time a person sneezes.” Reza Akhavian, a professor of engineering at San Diego State University, received a $691,000 National Science Foundation grant to study robotics in construction. “Currently and for the foreseeable future, the field of robotics in general, and construction robotics in particular, are not even close to a state in which robots can replace human workers,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive.com/news/contech-conversations-sdsu-professor-says-robots-not-close-to-replacing/600771/&quot;>;Akhavian argues&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reluctance to embrace new technology is based on more than the irascible and retrograde attitudes of industry players. Robots and other forms of automation are costly and require an extended time frame before offering a satisfactory return on capital. Given the decentralized nature of the industry and the predominance of small and medium-sized firms, few owners have the financial capacity to purchase expensive paraphernalia that may only provide a profit in the very long term. And while large general contractors may have more cash on hand, subcontractors employ the bulk of the workforce. There is little motivation for one well capitalized company to invest in a technology that will ultimately benefit another smaller firm.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, companies in other industries have traditionally been motivated to spend capital on automation and expensive new procedures to reduce escalating labor costs. Unfortunately, construction executives found simpler ways to cut labor costs through the misclassification of employees as independent contractors, cash compensation, and reduced wages and safety standards — all components of &lt;a href=&quot;https://lwp.law.harvard.edu/files/lwp/files/erlich_ilrr_final_article_11.28.20.pdf&quot;>;a successful crusade to undermine the union sector&lt;/a>; in many parts of the country. There is less incentive to buy robots to replace high-priced labor when the labor itself is not as pricey.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Construction&#39;s Digital Transformation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Still, the digital revolution in the twenty-first century has propelled construction, particularly the architectural functions and project management systems. Building Information Modeling (BIM), a software process that transforms traditional blueprints into digital images, has introduced the critical factor of coordination into the previously siloed products from the various design disciplines — architectural, structural, mechanical, electrical, civil — and allowed the management team to essentially build a project twice: once virtually on the office desktops and tablets and a second time with the actual trades workers and materials in the field. Jeff Gouveia, Executive Vice-President of Suffolk Construction, described the pre-BIM work style to me in an interview: “Prior to modeling, coordination was done with a light table with a clear piece of plastic over it. You overlaid 2D drawing on top of 2D drawing on top of 2D drawing. You got them just right, taped them in the corner, made sure that they were in the right scale, and then you basically started circling conflicts, where a piece of ductwork or pipe went into a column or a beam.” Modeling allows for the advance visualization of an entire development from site-work to finish hardware.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Modeling may reduce total construction costs, but it requires upfront investments on a scale that is only available to larger general contractors and a narrow slice of elite subcontractors that can afford the software and, above all, the hiring and training of highly computer-literate staff. Institutional owners like universities and hospitals that expect their projects to last decades are more likely to accept the initial costs of modeling than developers who tend to focus on the bottom line, just surviving through the warranties and short-term flipping goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While BIM initially just involved the professionals, modeling has since filtered down to workers in the field to offer suggestions and critiques of the unfolding designs. Gouveia describes the transition on a standard task like laying out the sleeves for plumbing and electrical pipes through a concrete deck. “Before, you&#39;re unrolling the drawings, the wind is blowing, you&#39;ve got a piece of rebar on one side, and you&#39;ve got a brick on the other side, and you&#39;re trying to hold it down. Then you&#39;re scaling it and going over and using your tape. Now, someone&#39;s got a laptop or a tablet or an iPad, with the model on there, with that floor laid out. You&#39;re laid out in a matter of 90 minutes, whereas before that would have taken maybe five hours.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though currently limited to larger projects, digitization and modeling will continue to penetrate further into the industry. The 2021 $1.2 trillion Infrastructure Investment and Jobs Act (ILJA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive.com/news/construction-tech-praise-110-million-infrastructure-bill-push-for-more/610126/&quot;>;included $100 million&lt;/a>; for advanced digital construction management systems and related technologies. While the language in the bill is non-specific, the funds are expected to support advanced digital management tools, 3D modeling, drone visualization, and data analysis. In 2016, the use of BIM was mandated on public projects in the United Kingdom and the National Institute of Building Sciences (NIBS) hosted a meeting in early 2021 to consider adopting a BIM standard for the US Modeling is expanding beyond three dimensions to incorporate 4D (scheduling), 5D (cost) and even 6D (facility management).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the job site, foremen have company-issued tablets as part of their tool kit so plans and modifications can be transmitted instantaneously. The old reliable gang boxes that housed workers&#39; tools for overnight storage now can also have Wi-Fi, printers and flat screens on the underside of the lid to display the latest shop drawings electronically. Most union training programs have incorporated CAD and BIM into their curricula. New young entrants into the industry from diverse demographic and socio-economic backgrounds may be able to translate their home computer expertise into modeling proficiency in the field. “We are always going to need mechanics to assemble stuff,” John Tocci told me in an interview. “but the mechanic of the future will also be the video game guy.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While Villemard&#39;s vision may now seem like the stuff of science fiction, there have been steady if undramatic steps to transform the industry. It takes far fewer trades workers to erect a skyscraper than it did even a decade or two ago. Tools and materials are constantly upgraded and BIM represents a novel and exceptional method to design and build a project. Turbulent change is unlikely, however, in an industry that remains fundamentally decentralized. The ability to invest in game-changing technologies is limited to the upper tier of the contracting community. For the foreseeable future, the vast majority of small and medium-sized subcontractors and trades workers will adjust and adapt, not disrupt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;This article is adapted from the author&#39;s book, &lt;/em>;The Way We Build: Restoring Dignity to Construction Work.&lt;em>; It is the first part of a two part series.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Responsible Computing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_4689448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;For businesses, technology has a variety of interconnected impacts including unintended consequences, data risks, and appropriateness of technological uses, as well as broader environmental concerns. The authors offer a systemic Responsible Computing Framework that integrates environmental challenges including energy consumption and emissions with many other social and governance aspects. It is a practical blueprint that firms can use to make their IT more green, ethical, trustworthy, and sustainable, based on six pillars that leaders need to address for their business to become a responsible computing provider: data centers, infrastructure, code, data, systems, and impact. For each they provide several KPIs that leaders should focus on.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Over the past few years, IBM has spoken to hundreds of chief technology officers (CTOs) reflecting a cross-section of industries for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/thought-leadership/institute-business-value/en-us/c-suite-study/cto&quot;>;a series of Architecture Decision Points reports&lt;/a>;. Clearly, business leaders recognize that technology will be a central part of delivering the future enterprise. However, they are also well aware that society is looking to businesses to prove they can live by the values they espouse — and computing has a key role to play. And these same CTOs mentioned that the societal impact of technology is keeping them up at night.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For businesses, technology has a variety of interconnected impacts including unintended consequences, data risks, and appropriateness of technological uses, as well as broader environmental concerns. Leaders are worried about introducing vulnerabilities to their companies, about deploying systems with harmful biases, about how AI will be perceived internally and by the public, and about the environmental impact of using certain technologies. These issues are all connected, though they&#39;re often discussed separately. If companies want to ensure they are responsible users of technology, they need a holistic approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Developed at IBM in conjunction with our CTO outreach, we have created a systemic &lt;a href=&quot;https://responsiblecomputing.net/&quot;>;Responsible Computing Framework&lt;/a>; that integrates environmental challenges including energy consumption and emissions with many other social and governance aspects. It is a practical blueprint that firms can use to make their IT more green, ethical, trustworthy, and sustainable. Our Responsible Computing Framework highlights six pillars that business leaders need to address for their business to become a responsible computing provider: data centers, infrastructure, code, data, systems, and impact. For each we provide several KPIs that can be used to provide comparisons.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Data Centers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first pillar of responsible computing is the physical infrastructure you need to develop and deliver IT services — whether or not you run data centers yourself. The global power capacity of data centers has grown by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/02/23/2390642/0/en/The-Global-Data-Center-Market-Size-to-Reach-288-30-Billion-by-2027-Arizton.html&quot;>;43% in the last three years&lt;/a>;, and inefficiency is a significant problem: the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nrdc.org/sites/default/files/data-center-efficiency-assessment-IP.pdf&quot;>;average server&lt;/a>; runs at 12% to 18% of its capacity but draws 30% to 60% of maximum power. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;International Energy Agency (IEA)&lt;/a>; predicts that the energy use of global data centers will jump from 1% of worldwide electricity demand to more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-06610-y&quot;>;more than 20%&lt;/a>; in just over a decade.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To measure the impact of your data centers, you need to consider the energy sources, energy use related to cooling&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; and water usage, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techtarget.com/searchdatacenter/feature/Words-to-go-6-key-data-center-sustainability-metrics&quot;>;track KPIs for each&lt;/a>;. If you don&#39;t run your own data centers, most mature cloud services providers, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sustainability/&quot;>;AWS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://newsroom.ibm.com/IBM-Cloud-Carbon-Calculator-Aims-to-Help-Organizations-Address-Greenhouse-Gas-Emissions-to-Advance-their-Sustainability-Objectives&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/how-microsoft-measures-datacenter-water-and-energy-use-to-improve-azure-cloud-sustainability/&quot;>;Microsoft&lt;/a>; measure this as part of their service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider the carbon footprint, or the amount of CO2 that was emitted in generating the energy used by data centers. Consider how much carbon dioxide a data center produces every day (carbon usage effectiveness); how clean the energy consumed by the data center is (technology carbon efficiency); and how much renewable energy is generated onsite (green energy coefficient).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, there&#39;s the efficiency footprint, or how optimized the data center is for its computing infrastructure. To measure this, you can look at the how much energy is used specifically by a data center&#39;s infrastructure, how much energy in the data center is reused elsewhere in the facility, and the HVAC system&#39;s effectiveness, or the overall efficiency of the cooling system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, there is the amount of water used by data centers as part of their operation, or water footprint. This requires breaking down how water is used, considering infrastructure, power generation, and how much gets recycled for other purposes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By having a clear picture of your power sources, cooling, and water usage of your data centers, business leaders can start to critically think about addressing the issue. How can you move to sustainable energy sources? How can you use carbon offsets? Would moving your infrastructure to a cooler climate save energy? Could you use the heat generated by your infrastructure for another purpose? How can you save water?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Infrastructure&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second pillar is reducing the environmental impact of computation. This requires that you assess the whole computing ecosystem you work in, not just your own infrastructure, including the hardware, software, and networks required to develop, test, deliver, monitor, control, and support IT services. While most manufacturers share this information when asked, there are also multiple industry initiatives, such as from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.itu.int/en/ITU-D/Environment/Documents/Toolbox/GEM_2020_def.pdf&quot;>;International Telecommunication Union&lt;/a>;, to standardize data and develop best practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider the computing hardware in use now. This can be measured by power usage KPIs, such as the average electricity consumption per hardware unit, how often computing hardware is used, and the proportion of hardware in use over a month compared to what is installed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, you need to understand the greenhouse gas emissions per unit of hardware, or unit carbon footprint. This KPI measures the total greenhouse gas emissions generated by a single hardware unit over the different stages of its life cycle — from the original extraction of resources through manufacturing of precursors and the making of the unit, its operation, and then the emissions of disposal once it is superseded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, measure the amount of waste that computing generates. This can include how much hardware is sent to landfill versus refurbishment, reuse, resale, or salvage (e-waste rate). It can also feature an assessment of your plastic footprint, calculated either by the total weight of plastic used or by the types of plastic polymers used, and their potential end destinations or likelihood of being recycled.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you have considered your infrastructure, you can start to consider actions to address your computing impact. What technologies could you use that reduce power per unit? How can you get more bang for your buck — for example, through consolidation, rationalization, or removing systems you don&#39;t use? How about using your spare capacity for other purposes? How can you recycle or reuse more effectively?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Code&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The third pillar is the efficiency of your code, and the potential environmental, societal, and economic impact of the code in use. This involves bringing responsibility to the level of individual developers and ensuring the development of responsible design principles or architectures that will help them make the right choices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Key to understanding how responsible code works are “function points,” which are a way of expressing the amount of business functionality that code provides. There are a wide range of software tools (both &lt;a href=&quot;https://owasp.org/www-community/Vulnerability_Scanning_Tools&quot;>;open source&lt;/a>; and commercial) that can assist organizations in their analysis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Start by measuring how efficient the function points are, such as page size or HTTP requests per process. You should also measure the carbon impact of each function point — the electricity consumption for an entire system, individual function points, or even for individual processes within a function point. Measuring the security of function points, such as the number of identified vulnerabilities, is also vital.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, take a close look at your code architecture. How scalable is it? How easy is it for the code to be moved to another platform? The time taken or cost to integrate function points in one system with ones in other systems is also a valuable KPI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, measure the quality of your code — for instance, the number of defects per function point — and its maintenance and rework attributes. You should also measure the reliability of your code, such as the average uptime per quarter for an entire system, function point, or even individual process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you understand the efficiency of function points, as well as the overall architecture and quality then you can start to consider how to improve. Should you use open or proprietary code? How secure is your code? How open is your code? Does making code reusable do more harm than good? Could you reduce the resolution of calculations through approximate computing?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Data&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The fourth pillar of responsible computing is the privacy, transparency, sharing, and acquisition of data. This pillar directly addresses your duty to understand the ethical, legal, and social responsibility of processing data across its lifecycle and allows the leader to take or delegate ownership and accountability on the protection and privacy of the data and its usage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thankfully there is significant work going on in this area, and we suggest one KPI: the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ictworks.org/responsible-data-maturity-model/&quot;>;Responsible Data Maturity Model&lt;/a>; which provides insight into how data is being managed in your business across 15 domains (awareness &amp;amp; capacity, policy &amp;amp; governance, accountability, partnership, inventory, privacy, legal, risk, minimization, transfer, security, sharing, combining, retention, and incident response).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With this analysis you can understand how each domain can be improved, and also how to track improvement. Do you have sufficient data governance in place? Are you aware of all the data that your business is responsible for? Who is responsible for what data? What are your current data and legal risks? How quickly do you respond to data incidents?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Systems&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Responsible systems are those that are fair, accountable, and transparent. This fifth pillar asks business leaders to understand their “systems” — the integrated sets of hardware, data, code, models, and services used in work— and the ethical implications of using them. At the core of this pillar is the fairness — or bias — that the systems within your organization have, and how accountable your firm is for what those systems do in your name.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider how one of your systems may discriminate against or harm people based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or disability. Measure this through comparing the outcomes between groups. More sophisticated comparisons can recognize that groups differ in more than one dimension. Another approach can measure how many complaints are received about the system fairness and how they are addressed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, determine which systems have specific individuals assigned as responsible for outcomes, and measure compliance with regulations, what means of legal redress are available, and how liable the business is for any harms that may have happened. These perspectives will help you make these systems more transparent. By having a clear picture of how fair, accountable, and transparent your systems are, you can start to critically think about addressing the issue. How can we reduce bias in our systems? How can we minimize our exposure to liability? Who is responsible for what system?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An important KPI is the analysis of the number of outcomes from the systems that are auditable, and another is how explainable system outcomes are. Furthermore, measure the number of knowledge artifacts that explain the goals, methods, and limitations of your systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Impact&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pillar considers how technology can be used for good — for example, to address social mobility or exclusion. But just because your organization can do something, doesn&#39;t mean it should. We suggest the best way to have responsible impact is to consider your computing in the context of the UN&#39;s 17 Sustainability Development Goals (SDGs). Some impacts are more general, such as enabling gender equality in hiring (SDG 5), providing decent work (SDG 8), or reducing inequality in income (SDG 10). KPIs here can consider how IT investment has led to such impacts by looking at before and after statistics. Similarly, actions to meet climate change goals (SDG 13) can be measured through KPIs such as the carbon impact per employee, per customer, and per SKU (stock taking unit).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, other impact measures will be specific to industries. For instance, the type of impact your IT use can have in agriculture is different to retail. Agricultural firms can measure how their IT investments have reduced the amount of water required to irrigate the crops (SDG 6). Similarly, retail firms can measure how their IT investments have enabled more sustainable consumption and production (SDG 12).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you have insight into how your computing impacts your performance on the SDGs, then you can start to critically evaluate how to improve in the future. How can your IT help to save lives, or improve life, in a similar way? How can you create new jobs, or help people develop new skills? How could you help speed up the response to disasters or emergencies?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Way Forward&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;World events since the pandemic and geopolitics have shown business leaders very clearly that their workers need protection, and that their supply chains are shakier than they thought. That has focused attention on corporate responsibility and how we use scarce resources. In IT specifically, the new normal is all about being fast, efficient, effective, and responsible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The task facing business leaders is to position their firms for both scale and success while taking an ethical and responsible approach to how, where, and why they use IT. The CTOs we spoke to agreed that achieving real and lasting change requires a holistic approach that encompasses every aspect of the computing ecosystem, from emissions and materials right through to ethical sourcing, data stewardship, and social responsibility work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, business leaders can&#39;t do it all on their own. They need to ensure that the entire IT function is aligned behind their responsible computing vision. Every member of the IT function will need to appreciate the ethics that underpin the responsible computing vision, as well as being accountable for their actions. This will require a professionalized IT function that has both the competence to be able to deliver on the vision, as well as the inclusivity to ensure diversity of opinion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond the IT function, the entire C-suite, employees, suppliers, partners, and customers will need to be more mindful about how they consume and conserve valuable resources—which means offering them the right incentives to do so. Everyone will have a part to play: infrastructure experts and application developers, but also professionals in sales, marketing, operations, finance, procurement, and facilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, it&#39;s a big task, but the reward will be greater trust in the organization — and, ultimately, a better world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>