<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Research: A Little Nature in the Office Boosts Morale and Productivity]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-a-little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_MaryHaasdykVooys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Mary Haasdyk Vooys 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more -caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;综述。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;“微观自然”研究&amp;#8212;将小型、经济实惠的自然元素融入工作场所——展示了其对员工绩效和福祉的积极影响。研究表明，在工作中接触大自然可以提高生产力、乐于助人和创造力，而且没有证据表明存在负面影响。建议包括真实的和人造的自然，延伸到办公环境之外，利用未充分利用的空间，并鼓励工作时间之外接触自然。工作场所融入自然可以提高整体业务绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a-little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=es&quot;>;学习西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a-little-nature- in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在金丝雀码头这个繁华的地区，许多全球企业的伦敦基地，开发商正在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.architectsjournal.co.uk/news/glenn-howells-and-eden-project-to-give-canary-wharf-a-green-revamp&quot;>;建设一个“绿色脊柱”&lt;/a>;很快就会蜿蜒穿过摩天大楼，让工人们在工作日可以随时进入绿色空间。在城镇另一边，正在建设中的 Google 英国总部，一座&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/6/1/15723642/google-london-office-pictures-headquarters-kings-cross&quot;>;300 米长的屋顶公园&lt;/a>;拥有 250 多棵树，为员工提供了远离办公室和城市环境的自然场所。在大西洋的另一边，零售商 LL Bean 砍掉了其中一个仓库的中间部分，将空间变成了庭院，这样&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90908239/ll-bean-new-headquarters&quot;>;新家庭办公室&lt;/a>;的每个人都可以在工作时欣赏到大自然的景色。这些将自然融入商业空间的现实例子是设计场所日益增长的趋势的一部分，让员工在工作期间可以沉浸在大自然中。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在工作环境中增加自然环境无疑与许多公司的可持续发展举措相一致。然而，其动机也源于自然对人类的影响——众所周知，自然让我们感觉更好。我们的情感、我们的思维、我们与他人的联系以及我们的身体健康&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2017.0177&quot;>;都因置身于自然之中和周围而得到增强&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管接触自然与我们的福祉之间存在联系，但将自然带入工作场所的大量投资引发了一些棘手的问题。首先，在经济逆风和成本削减的时代，是否存在将自然融入员工环境的商业案例？其次，那些不可行或不明智的工作场所如何纳入绿色脊柱或屋顶花园？回答这些问题需要首先了解自然是否对关系到组织底线的指标（例如员工满意度和绩效）产生影响，如果有，不太极端的自然剂量是否足以产生这些收益。因此，我们着手测试我们所谓的“微观自然”——一种小型、经济实惠、看似无害的将自然融入工作场所的方式——对员工的工作感受和表现的影响（如果有的话）。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;研究&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们通过多项研究，对美国、加拿大、中国、新西兰和印度尼西亚的员工以不同的方式测量或操纵了工作中与自然的接触。在实验中，工作成年人只是简单地看到充满自然元素的工作场所图像或没有自然元素的匹配图像。然后，我们要求他们想象自己在这些空间中工作，并报告他们的感受和表现如何。我们还在现实工作环境中进行了更复杂的研究。例如，我们评估员工在一周的工作中与自然的实际接触情况（例如，在植物、自然景观或流水声附近工作），然后衡量他们的感受和客观工作绩效。最后，在一家会计师事务所的现场实验中，我们晚上走进办公室，在一些员工的办公桌上放置盆栽植物，在其他办公桌上放置类似的盆，只装满办公用品。然后，我们测量了两组人的态度和工作表现，并进行了比较。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些研究的结果基本一致：即使在工作中体验少量的自然环境，也能改善员工的感受，从而促进&lt;a href=&quot;https://discovery.ucl.ac.uk/id/eprint/10166977/1/Tang%20et%20al%20final%20prepublished.pdf&quot;>;更高的任务绩效，增加帮助&lt;/a>;，以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063231172182&quot;>;增强创造力&lt;/a>;。这些发现表明，将微观自然融入工作环境可以以有意义的方式促进员工的福祉和绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们还研究了员工之间是否存在影响自然如何影响他们工作的因素，例如个人对自然的欣赏程度，以及他们被新奇体验所吸引的程度。我们的研究结果表明，有些人特别容易体验到大自然的好处。然而，我们没有发现任何证据表明任何员工因工作中接触自然而受到负面影响；因此，微观自然似乎为员工带来了巨大的希望，而且几乎没有什么缺点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑到这些发现，我们认为，自然应该让尽可能多的员工接触到自然，而不仅仅是那些幸运地在绿色屋顶下或公园旁边工作的人。公司应该为员工提供微观体验。下面，我们提供了将微观自然融入工作场所的建议，同时也鼓励管理者在其特定组织中自由发挥并发挥创造力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;利用微观自然&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;真实是最好的，但人工也可以。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在自然方面，让员工有机会接触“真实的事物”是理想的选择：室内水景、可欣赏自然景观的窗户或打开后可听到鸟鸣等自然声​​音的窗户。但仅仅因为它不是真实的东西并不意味着员工不会从大自然中受益。研究表明，即使是壁画和人造花等对自然的描绘，也能给员工带来自然的激励。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;超越办公室的思考……&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;不言而喻，受益于自然的不仅仅是办公室职员。在工作环境特别远离自然的环境中（例如仓储或制造业），员工特别有可能注意到室内的一些户外活动，并受到户外活动的积极影响，因为这与他们的现状有很大不同。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;……而且超出了工作场所。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;自然的好处超出了员工的工作生活。我们的一些研究着眼于工作日结束后晚上在户外度过的与工作相关的好处。我们发现，前一天晚上在户外活动时，员工&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063221106430&quot;>;第二天的工作效率更高&lt;/a>;。特别是对于混合型和远程工作者来说，其影响是显而易见的：在家亲近自然的好处可以延续到工作中。因此，即使激励员工晚上散步也可以帮助他们在第二天提高工作效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;利用未使用或未充分利用的空间。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;根据定义，微观自然很小，可以很简单，例如用自然色调粉刷墙壁、在休息室添加鲜花或美化员工窗外的区域。我们鼓励管理者留意工作场所周围未使用或未充分利用的空间，这些空间可以轻松且廉价地转变为自然特征。例如，为过度工业化的停车场添加更多景观可能会提高员工的士气。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;总体而言，我们的研究结果表明，在工作中将员工与自然联系起来的好处不仅限于可持续性，还包括对员工的福祉及其工作方式产生积极影响。因此，我们认为与大自然的接触是对精心设计的工作的宝贵补充，这些工作已经包括有意义的工作、公平的报酬和尊重的待遇。对于提供这些东西并正在寻找更多方法来改善员工工作环境的公司来说，微观自然提供了巨大的希望。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies Need to Prove They Can Be Trusted with Technology]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1282056839.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Hiroshi Watanabe/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption =&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;相信技术 &amp;#8212;以及使用它的公司——过去几年受到了打击。针对个人的违法行为——隐私、企业或个人偏见钙化为改变生活的算法、新技术侵蚀他们谋生能力的持续威胁，以及在毫无戒心的民众身上对不安全或有缺陷的连接设备或车辆进行 Beta 测试，这些都鼓励了健康的怀疑态度。为了重建数字信任，企业需要追求三个广泛的目标：安全性和可靠性、问责制和监督以及包容性、负责任和合乎道德的使用。实际上，这需要三个步骤：1) 定义数字信任的愿景，2) 计划以更值得信赖的方式行事，3) 招募有助于赢得信任的人员。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a >; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;技术解决主义——即可以信任技术开发人员通过创新或编码来摆脱问题并走向繁荣的想法——正在消失。个人对技术和开发技术的公司的信任已被无数的失败所侵蚀。对于企业来说，在不采取措施确保技术可信的情况下使用技术是不再可接受的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最近侵犯个人隐私的行为、企业或个人偏见钙化为改变生活的算法、新技术侵蚀他们谋生能力的持续威胁，以及在毫无戒心的民众上对不安全或有缺陷的连接设备或车辆进行 Beta 测试，普通民众——以及越来越多的立法者和监管者——合理地产生了怀疑。展望不久的将来，随着生成式人工智能和虚拟世界的实施速度超出我们的追踪速度，信任问题只会变得更糟。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;更多的技术并不能解决这个问题。客户正在关注公司领导者做出的选择，并评估这些选择是否符合个人消费者和公民的价值观，以及他们是否以人为本。由于每家公司在运营以及与客户和合作伙伴的关系中都使用某种形式的数字技术，因此每家公司都需要担心数字信任。 “数字信任计划是必要的，如果做得好，它既可以成为企业的差异化因素，也可以成为企业的推动者。 Salesforce 首席信任官兼世界经济论坛数字信任指导委员会成员 Vikram Rao 表示，“随着公司证明自己值得信赖的要求不断提高，组织应该努力建立满足或超出客户期望的数字信任策略，而不仅仅是法律要求的策略。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些公司可能会看到这个问题，并希望能够通过购买或雇佣方式摆脱困境。在某些情况下，首席信任官或首席数字信任官等新角色可能会有所帮助。但在首席执行官和董事会急于创建高管职位作为万能药之前，他们需要认真审视 21 世纪值得信赖的技术到底是什么样子，公司如何赢得数字信任，以及为此需要做出哪些改变和投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;是什么让技术值得信赖？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;没有一种技术本质上是值得信赖或不值得信赖的。毕竟，技术本身并没有任何作用。相反，正如非洲未来主义电影&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://greatergood.berkeley.edu/article/item/twelve_new_films_that_highlight_the_best_in_ humanity&quot;>;Neptune Frost&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;中的一个角色所说，“技术只是我们的反映。”对技术的信任反映了人们在开发、使用和实施技术时做出的决定。尽管思考信任的方式有很多种，但当世界经济论坛召集可信技术领域的企业、政府和民间社会领导人时，聚集的小组&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;达成了这一共识&lt;/a>;：“数字信任是个人对数字技术和服务以及提供这些技术和服务的组织将保护所有利益相关者的利益并维护社会期望的期望和价值观。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这项工作中，论坛的&lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/community&quot;>;数字信任社区&lt;/a>;意识到，关于技术要问的最重要的问题不是“如何让人们信任技术？”相反，它是“作为技术开发人员、所有者和用户，我们需要做什么来尊重人们的价值观和期望？”有了正确的心态和正确的目标，就可以制定有效且值得信赖的数字技术使用策略。从本质上讲，这种值得信赖的技术战略来自于对受到新技术影响的个人的考虑（无论所讨论的技术是什么）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑到尊重个人权利和期望，值得信赖的数字技术战略应该确定正确的目标。世界经济论坛的数字信任社区提出了三大目标：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;安全性和可靠性&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;问责制和监督，以及&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;包容、道德和负责任的使用&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;正如微软首席隐私官兼论坛数字信任指导委员会成员 Julie Brill 当时所说，“任何人工智能或其他技术开发人员的目标都应该反映使用或遇到的组织和个人的目标。那个技术。包容性和负责任的使用、强有力的隐私和安全保护以及有效监督的共同目标是在开发人员、其客户和使用该技术的个人之间建立值得信赖的关系的基本要素。”用户和消费者可以更好地依赖保护他们的技术，这些技术包含他们的需求并符合他们的价值观，并且具有良好的治理实践，以纠正任何无意的伤害。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;如何投资数字信任？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;赢得数字信任并不简单，而且无法自动化。相反，它需要一系列的判断、投资和组织变革，以反映技术对个人可能产生的总体影响。这些涉及整个业务的转变只能由公司领导者精心策划。正如 Google 首席隐私官兼数字信任指导委员会成员基思·恩赖特 (Keith Enright) 所说，“公司现在就准备情况做出的决策决定了他们在信任方面的发展方向。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;准备好开始赢回信任需要首席执行官和董事会至少做三件事：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;定义数字信任的愿景&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;计划以更值得信赖的方式行事&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;招募有助于赢得信任的人员&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;领导者需要进行的首要投资是花时间和精力真正了解他们创建或部署的技术的影响。对于组织如何使用技术来实现其目标以及依赖技术的人员的目标制定现实而全面的愿景，决定了组织如何投资数字信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;领导者在做出涉及技术的决策时，应清楚地了解&lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_World_Economic_Forum_Digital_Trust_Initiative_2023.pdf&quot;>;这些技术如何反映和影响核心组织价值观&lt;/a>;以及组织的价值观企业经营所在的社会。他们创造或采用新技术的愿景必须考虑对企业和社会的好处，同时对新技术可能对潜在客户或其他利益相关者造成的潜在危害进行清晰和负责任的评估。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，采用生成式人工智能的企业必须评估该技术如何提高效率（对企业有利），解锁新的解决方案来应对紧迫的挑战（对社会有利），同时制定计划以防止&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-the-risks-of-generative -ai&quot;>;例如，人工智能“幻觉”或错误信息对民主进程以及因这些先进技术而失业的工人的预期危害。只有负责任地考虑新技术的好处和风险的愿景才能真正被认为是值得信赖的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在决定包含值得信赖的目标的愿景后，组织需要制定一个计划来采取行动以实现数字信任。该计划要求领导者投资于最能支持数字信任的内部结构和团队。对于数字技术的所有应用，论坛的&lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/framework&quot;>;工作&lt;/a>;确定了积极行动可以帮助实现组织目标的八个维度——包括信任目标和总体财务或战略目标。这些维度包括网络安全、安全性、透明度、互操作性、可审计性、可纠正性、公平性和隐私性。 （与数字信任目标一样，这些维度在论坛的洞察报告中进行了定义和探讨，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;&lt;em>;赢得数字信任：值得信赖的技术的决策&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;。）&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在大多数组织中，这些领域可能属于不同的部门和领导者，这意味着优化它们需要采用跨学科的方法 - 可能还需要一些跨学科的方法结构性变革——以支持赢得用户和其他利益相关者信任所需的谨慎决策。然而，特定行业或公司的现实可能意味着不可能最大化所描述的每一个维度。例如，对于从事高度敏感行业（例如国家安全）的公司来说，可能无法提高透明度，因此必须补充其责任和安全。同样，可信度的某些方面（也许最明显的是隐私）在不同司法管辖区和地区之间也有所不同。人们的期望和价值观是检验技术是否值得信赖的试金石。信任本身可能具有高度的地区和行业特定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三大初始投资是对能够帮助企业赢得数字信任的人员的投资。使技术值得信赖是在组织（或社会）规模上进行的多方面努力——这意味着可信度的最终责任落在首席执行官身上。然而，这种值得信赖的技术决策的一般责任并不意味着企业不应该投资招聘专家（甚至可能是最高管理层），他们可以帮助建立正确的战略和正确的结构，以支持数字信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这位领导者，可能是首席信任官，但也可能是首席隐私官、总法律顾问、CISO 或其他高管，必须既是利益相关者管理方面的专家，又是首席执行官和董事会值得信赖的顾问。当公司已经具备网络安全、隐私、合规甚至道德职能时，利益相关者管理就会发挥作用。每个角色的领导者都与公司数字化战略的整体可信度息息相关——无论是构建数字化战略还是从中受益。为了成为数字信任顾问，这个人还必须能够系统地思考——在这些学科之间架起桥梁，以帮助领导者就如何、在哪里以及应用新技术做出最佳判断。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了发挥最大作用，负责数字信任的官员不能成为每项技术和信任各个方面的专家，而是必须能够了解公司的战略以及受影响的个人、员工和客户的价值观。他们通过向首席执行官和董事会传达整个系统范围内的技术前景，并帮助制定支持信任而不是削弱信任的战略，来支持建立值得信赖的愿景。他们还帮助监督无数相互依赖的行动，这些行动共同赢得了用户、合作伙伴和其他利益相关者的信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首席执行官必须明白，对几乎所有业务的基础和支持的技术的信任是买不来的，但通过投入时间做出正确的决策、建立值得信赖的愿景并招募有效的支持者，这是可以赢得的。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens After the U.S. Economy&rsquo;s Soft Landing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-u-s-economys-soft-landing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1427804800.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;baona/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; 关闭-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;一年前，经济衰退被视为已成定局 &amp;#8212;然而，美联储似乎已经成功降低了通胀，而没有引发经济衰退。许多负面预测都遵循低估美国经济弹性的模式，通常是因为它们是基于历史模型和先例，而不是情境和特殊背景。虽然软着陆可能正在有希望地取得进展，但它不会是最终状态。新的不平衡将会出现。领导人不能等待宏观经济的确定性或稳定性。相反，他们必须认识到宏观经济仍将不受模型的控制。重要的是判断。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=pt&quot;>; Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;美国经济再次挑战了末日论者的说法。一年多以来，经济衰退被视为已成定局，“软着陆”几乎不可能实现。但如今，软着陆已经取得了很大进展，尽管尚未完成：美联储在降低通胀方面取得了成功，但没有引发经济衰退。劳动力市场是经济陷入衰退的唯一可靠证据，它已经降温，但没有推高失业率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这是个好消息，但围绕经济的长期不确定性让许多领导人感到困惑，并让那些因预期经济衰退而过早退缩的人付出了代价。这种不确定性将持续存在。软着陆之后会发生什么（如果实际上可以完成的话）？为了回答这个问题，我们来看看为什么衰退的预测是错误的，以及未来会发生什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;经济衰退预言，未实现&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;就像在大流行中一样，末日论者预测“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.project-syndicate.org/commentary/coronavirus-greater-great-depression-by-nouriel-roubini-2020-03&quot;>;更严重的萧条&lt;/a>;”，过去一年半的公共话语中充斥着许多负面情绪。一些领导人预测“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/01/jamie-dimon-says-brace-yourself-for-an-economic-hurricane-caused-by-the-fed-and-ukraine-war.html&quot;>;飓风&lt;/a>;”很快就会袭击经济；其他人&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@alex.domash/can-job-vacancies-fall-without-an-increase-in-unemployment-1031fe19c635&quot;>;甚至否认软着陆的可能性&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但如下图所示，这正是过去 16 个月所发生的情况。由于公司感到压力减轻，职位空缺数量已从高位回落，而随着员工跳槽的诱惑减弱，辞职率也有所下降——而招聘（“工资单”）仍在继续强劲增长。由于失业率仍接近 60 年来的最低水平，没有衰退的迹象。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360940&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230719_SZLEZAK_SOFT_LANDING_360.png&quot; >; &quot; title=&quot;美国劳动力市场软着陆的进展。&quot; width =&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1592&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和视觉中的更多 HBR 图表&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;出了什么问题，或者更恰当地说，什么是正确的？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多负面预测都遵循低估的模式评估美国经济的弹性，通常是因为它们是基于历史模型和先例，而不是情境和特殊背景。考虑以下四种弹性表现：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;劳动力市场弹性。&lt;/strong>;普遍的假设是货币政策将集体压低劳动力需求。相反，我们看到了被总体实力所掩盖的一些弱点。在招聘超过预期的领域（例如科技行业），出现了大规模裁员，但在其他行业（例如服务业），招聘仍在迎头赶上并保持强劲。下岗工人找到了新工作。衰退行业与蓬勃发展行业的不同寻常的经济多元化体现了韧性。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;消费者韧性。&lt;/strong>;裁员人数增加、通货膨胀侵蚀家庭预算以及投资组合下降削弱资产负债表，导致支出崩溃的预测。但背景很重要。资产负债表有缓冲，包括现金。尽管个人预算受到挤压，但随着招聘的持续进行，收入总数继续快速增长，从而提供了消费者的力量。总体下行趋势尚未发生。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;住房弹性。&lt;/strong>;人们普遍担心利率上升会削弱房地产市场——推迟建筑活动，压低价格，甚至像一些末日论者预测的那样，引发另一场以住房为中心的衰退。但这些叙述忽视了这样一个事实：经济活动依然存在正是因为&lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/08/09/real-estate-housing-market-falling-prices-economic-risk/&quot;>;住房库存较低&lt;/a>;。结果，较高的利率抑制了——而不是抑制了——房地产活动。新屋开工和价格下降，交易量下降，但已趋于稳定并再次上升。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;金融体系的弹性。&lt;/strong>;另一个普遍的担忧是美联储将加息，直到出现问题。正如&lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/03/15/svb-collapse-financial-instability-fed-inflation-recession-finance-banks-economy-carlsson-szlezak-swartz/&quot;>;SVB崩溃所证明的那样，认为金融体系将成为高利率的附带损害的想法并非没有道理。但蔓延的风险被高估了，而政策制定者避免蔓延的能力却被低估了。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;好于预期的结果有一个共同的模式。每个问题都有其优点，但被认为过于狭隘。特殊的、背景和情境的驱动因素比历史关系以及基于历史关系的模型对这些行业的影响更为重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个经常吸取的教训似乎是，对宏观经济模型的信任仍然过于强烈。周期的特殊性需要判断，而不是精确的预测。与此同时，当麦克风可靠地传递给最悲观的声音时，末日预言通常会被放大。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;未来之路&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;经济学常常无益地将经济周期描述为“走向均衡”。 （航空业的“软着陆”类比同样有罪。）事实上，我们总是从一种特殊的不平衡转向另一种，这意味着&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/business-forecasts-are-reliously-wrong-yet-still-valuable&quot;>;高管不能依赖预测&lt;/a>;。新的特殊驱动因素总是会带来模型无法轻易捕捉到的新情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，新的不均衡可能是什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管软着陆的第一阶段是成功的，但排除经济衰退的可能性将是一个错误。它仍然是一种可能的、甚至是合理的结果（并且随着时间的推移，这是不可避免的）。货币政策仍然踩着刹车。真正的冲击总是可以结束一个周期，特别是当增长已经缓慢、经济因此更加脆弱，并且银行倒闭等金融压力源可能会意外出现时。考虑到&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/assessing-the-current-risks-to-the-us-economy&quot;>;三种类型的衰退&lt;/a>;风险仍然是不可或缺的，但我们仍然认为短期内的衰退风险远低于共识。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于有弹性的经济成功度过了这段疲弱（但非衰退）增长时期，因此更有可能重新加速。然而，这种重新加速可能会以不同的方式发挥作用，有些是受欢迎的，有些是不受欢迎的。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;情景 1：过度经济的重新运行&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;如果需求强劲增长并超过经济能力（想想可用的劳动力、资本和已知流程），则可能会出现另一轮通胀。 This would necessitate a fresh round of monetary tightening with all the risks we discussed above.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even so, it would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; immediately point to an “inflation regime break” — the mistaken narrative of the last two years that the US economy was seeing a structural return of inflation. It would mean another bout of cyclical inflation that comes (and goes) with a mismatch of demand and supply.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 2: A Just-Right Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If demand grows in line with the economy&#39;s capacity, the expansion can plod along at acceptable growth rates without renewed inflation pressures. Monetary policy could ease from its very tight stance toward a more neutral stance — until a shift toward a new disequilibrium arises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 3: A Better-Than-Good Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We know this has arrived when the economy&#39;s capacity grows considerably faster than demand, facilitating rapid growth without concomitant cyclical inflation. While strong capital formation and strong labor participation can help facilitate this scenario to a degree, it&#39;s crux would be an acceleration of productivity growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Can this happen and is it likely?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many are eager to pencil in much higher growth courtesy of ChatGPT and other applications of AI — but not so fast. The mere availability of labor does not guarantee faster productivity growth; think of tech as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/08/the-secret-of-productivity-growth-is-not-technology/&quot;>;just the fuel&lt;/a>;. The &lt;em>;spark&lt;/em>; typically comes in the form of tight labor markets. When firms are forced to substitute capital for labor, they tend to do more of it. When they can&#39;t hire the next worker, they transform their processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such sustained labor market tightness and its benefits are a realistic prospect. Still, leaders should remain prudent about size and speed of such gains. Big productivity gains at the macroeconomic level come gradually, not abruptly, and their size is often overestimated — as we saw in the pandemic, when analysts rushed to pencil in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/10/how-to-be-realistic-about-covids-impact-on-productivity-growth/&quot;>;an extra 1 percentage point of growth&lt;/a>; that did not materialize.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The benefits of such a scenario would be broader than just somewhat higher growth. Tight labor markets create real wage growth across the income distribution, and the biggest winners tend to be at the bottom of the distribution. This creates opportunities for career advancement and job creation for those who have had fewer opportunities or struggled to get on the job ladder, and it pulls into the labor market those who may have otherwise exited.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While the soft landing may be progressing with promise, it won&#39;t be an end state — a new disequilibrium will emerge. Leaders can&#39;t wait for macroeconomic certainty or stability. Instead, they must recognize that the macroeconomy will remain untamed by models — and that what matters is judgment. Gloomy headlines will persist, and economic models will offer a flat view of the world that misses out on critical context. Leaders must apply the same skills they employ each day to lead their firms through uncertainty to navigating the macroeconomy. They must avoid both overreacting to the latest piece of data and preparing for only one unchanging view the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For firms, the &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/why-firms-are-struggling-with-the-us-economys-soft-landing&quot;>;challenges of a tight economy&lt;/a>;, including margin pressure, as well as higher, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/06/07/inflation-interest-rates-higher-but-healthy-bcg/&quot;>;healthy interest rates&lt;/a>;, are likely here to stay — but they are preferable to the alternative of recession. Meeting these challenges head on means more capital for labor substitution, more reinvention, and more technological absorption. Each of these form the foundation of the better-than-good economic scenario.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Using Sprints to Boost Your Sales Team&rsquo;s Performance]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_20_stk149282rke.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;George Doyle/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Over the last two decades, technology developers have utilized the agile methodology to work more effectively. As sales teams are stretched thin and face change initiatives and strategy shifts, using the sprints made popular by agile can help them focus on priorities that will drive results. At the heart of this is a cadence of structured, weekly meetings between the manager and the salesperson.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Fueled by a rapidly changing digital world, sales organizations are spending significant amounts of resources and energy on strategic initiatives. Whether these involve wholesale changes (eg, reorganizing the sales team or shifting to hybrid field-digital customer engagement) or less disruptive ones (eg, introducing new sales quotas or adopting new sales technologies), the primary roadblock to intended impact is the failure to achieve execution excellence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For sales teams, executing on new strategies can be quite difficult. Sales is a multifaceted job, with many choices of what to do at any moment. Demanding customers, sales managers, marketing managers, and digital nudges can push salespeople in inconsistent directions. They may choose to do tasks that are easier, such as calling on friendly accounts with modest upside, or focusing on small short-term wins rather than advancing larger longer-term opportunities. Further, salespeople can be reluctant to adopt new approaches that disrupt how they have engaged customers in the past. Results, especially with large deals, follow weeks and months after the actions salespeople take to drive those results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A solution that has helped many sales teams close execution gaps is sales sprints – time-boxed periods of one to two weeks bookended by a one-on-one meeting between the sales manager and salesperson (or account team). The idea is to break down strategies and goals into small, more manageable tasks to help sales teams stay focused and be accountable. Sales sprints have some obvious parallels to &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/05/embracing-agile&quot;>;agile sprints for technology development&lt;/a>; – both break down work into small segments and those involved meet frequently to monitor progress and adjust. But unlike agile sprints (which are used for projects with a beginning and an end), sales sprints are part of a regular management cadence for continually improving the processes of growing value for customers and driving sales.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales sprints sound straightforward, and they are. However, successful implementation takes work. To be effective, sales sprints must be embedded into the operating rhythm of an organization; they can&#39;t pile on more administrative duties for sales teams. Sprints work best when the effort is supported by a centralized digital platform that connects the approach to sales management programs including pipeline management, goal setting, coaching, and rewards.&amp;nbsp;Further, sales managers must collaborate with their peers across the organization to bring insights and experiences to each sprint conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Sales Sprints in Action&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The global steel and wire manufacturer Deacero has a vast product portfolio and longstanding customer relationships. To achieve aggressive growth targets, the company wanted to move beyond a transactional “inside-out” sales process in which its sales teams focused on getting orders for what was in inventory. Leaders recognized the need for a new market-focused “outside-in” sales strategy that would rely on anticipating market trends, and proactively prioritizing accounts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deacero launched “Win the Week,” a program of sales sprints to gradually introduce new capabilities (eg, key account management, solution selling) and activities (eg, account prioritization and planning). The goal was to ensure salesperson focus on individual customer opportunities and needs. After a short training session, sales managers started using sprints to guide their salespeople to define and complete a set of customer advances to increase pipeline value.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In each weekly 50-minute 1:1 meeting, usually on a Friday, the manager and salesperson discussed three questions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What happened?&lt;/strong>; For example, how did the planned actions play out last week? How did we do on pipeline progress and key result areas? What did we learn about customers and the market?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What&#39;s next? &lt;/strong>;For example, which prospects and customers should we focus on next week? What actions should we take? What offers and value do we need to communicate? What customer advances or progress should we seek?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How can the manager help?&lt;/strong>; For example, what could the manager do to support next week&#39;s planned efforts? What support is needed from the rest of the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Sales managers used sprint conversations to help their salespeople break down larger, more complex sales strategies (eg, increase product portfolio sales) into smaller, more manageable, opportunity-specific customer activities (eg, in vertical market A, sell solution B, to account C, by meeting with decision maker D, and leveraging value proposition E). Managers ensured that weekly schedules centered around spending a greater portion of time with accounts that demonstrated the highest growth potential. Planning conversations focused on how Deacero&#39;s full suite of products could best meet the needs of key accounts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The success of sprints with the sales team encouraged Deacero to use sprints with more teams and across organizational levels. Sales, marketing, and manufacturing executive teams began working together in bi-monthly sprint meetings to align the business towards specific market opportunities. Sales executives then worked with sales managers to break down quarterly forecasts into salesperson-based key performance indicators.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deacero supported the sprints with a leading CRM platform. The mindset and processes of the organization transformed to produce what the market needed, rather than to sell what was produced.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Results were stellar – with increased focus on customer advances, sales reps sold an average of 8% more product categories to each account. Within the first six months in the new organization, sales reps exceeded sales goals previously thought unachievable, resulting in a 16% revenue increase.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why Sales Sprints Are Effective&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Here is what salespeople and sales managers say about how sales sprints drive results.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Move from strategy to execution:&lt;/strong>; “Our quarterly plans before were like checking the box. I never looked at them after I had developed them … Sprints make the plans dynamic and actionable.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Collaborate across the business:&lt;/strong>; “I&#39;ve never had this type of conversation. Marketing and sales brainstorm together to generate ideas that move the needle.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Link insights to actions:&lt;/strong>; “The past approach was too general and not relevant. Sprints help us stay informed on the market and focused on priority actions that help us achieve our sales goals.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Focus on the customer:&lt;/strong>; “The weekly game planning for specific customer decision makers helps me focus on what is important in each conversation. Things don&#39;t fall through the cracks.”&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As companies across industries such as manufacturing, technology, health care, and professional services seek to drive growth in a fast-changing digital world, they are leveraging sales sprints to connect their ever-changing strategies to execution. Further, these organizations are accelerating the success of their sprints by supporting them with cross-functional collaboration, incentive compensation plans aligned with growth strategies, and CRM dashboards that help identify sales pipeline gaps. Sales sprints are helping organizations keep strategy and execution in synch, and in turn, drive value for customers to “win&#39;” each week, quarter, and year.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make Generative AI Greener]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_AlexWilliam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Alex William&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Generative AI is impressive, but the hidden environmental costs and impact of these models are often overlooked. Companies can take eight steps to make these systems greener: Use existing large generative models, don&amp;#8217;t generate your own; fine-tune train existing models; use energy-conserving computational methods; use a large model only when it offers significant value; be discerning about when you use generative AI; evaluate the energy sources of your cloud provider or data center; re-use models and resources; include AI activity in your carbon monitoring.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While observers have marveled at the abilities of new generative AI tools such as ChatGPT, BERT, LaMDA, GPT-3, DALL-E-2, MidJourney, and Stable Diffusion, the hidden environmental costs and impact of these models are often overlooked. The development and use of these systems have been hugely energy intensive and maintaining their physical infrastructure entails power consumption. Right now, these tools are just beginning to gain mainstream traction, but it&#39;s reasonable to think that these costs are poised to grow — and dramatically so — in the near future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The data center industry, which refers to a physical facility designed to store and manage information and communications technology systems, is responsible for 2–3% of global greenhouse gas (GHG) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;emissions&lt;/a>;. The volume of data across the world doubles in size &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivery.io/blog/big-data-statistics-how-much-data-is-there-in-the-world/&quot;>;every two years&lt;/a>;. The data center servers that store this ever-expanding sea of information require huge amounts of energy and water (directly for cooling, and indirectly for generating non-renewable electricity) to operate computer servers, equipment, and cooling systems. These systems account for around &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;7% of Denmark&#39;s&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www1.villanova.edu/university/engineering/faculty-research/Energy-Smart-Electronic-Systems/Datacenter-efficiency-challenges.html&quot;>;2.8% of the United States&#39;&lt;/a>; electricity use.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Almost all of the best-known generative AI models are generated by “hyperscale” (very large) cloud providers with thousands of servers that produce major carbon footprints; in particular, these models run on graphics processing unit (GPU) chips. These require 10–15 times the energy a traditional CPU needs because a GPU uses more transistors in the arithmetic logic units. Currently, the three main hyperscale cloud providers are Amazon AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If we try to understand the environmental impact of ChatGPT through the lens of carbon footprint, we should understand the carbon footprint lifecycle of machine learning (ML) models first. That&#39;s the key to beginning to make generative AI greener through lower energy consumption.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Determines the Carbon Footprint of Generative AI Models?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;All large generative models are not alike in terms of their energy use and carbon emissions. When determining the carbon footprint of an ML model, there are three distinct values to consider:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint from training the model&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint from running inference (inferring or predicting outcomes using new input data, such as a prompt) with the ML model once it has been deployed, and&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint required to produce all of the needed computing hardware and cloud data center capabilities.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Models with more parameters and training data generally consume more energy and generate more carbon. GPT-3, the “parent” model of ChatGPT, is at or near the top of the generative models in size. It has 175 billion model parameters and was trained on over 500 billion words of text. According to one &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.blog/2023-04-07-what-developers-need-to-know-about-generative-ai/&quot;>;research article&lt;/a>;, the recent class of generative AI models requires a ten to a hundred-fold increase in computing power to train models over the previous generation, depending on which model is involved. Thus overall demand is doubling about every six months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Training models are the most energy-intensive components of generative AI. &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3442188.3445922&quot;>;Researchers&lt;/a>; have argued that training a “single&amp;nbsp;large&amp;nbsp;language deep learning model” such as OpenAI&#39;s GPT-4 or Google&#39;s PaLM is estimated to use&amp;nbsp;around 300&amp;nbsp;tons&amp;nbsp;of CO2 — for comparison, the average person is responsible for creating &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/the-world-s-top-1-of-emitters-produce-over-1000-times-more-co2-than-the-bottom-1&quot;>;around 5 tons&lt;/a>; of CO2 a year, though the average North American generates &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/the-world-s-top-1-of-emitters-produce-over-1000-times-more-co2-than-the-bottom-1&quot;>;several times that amount&lt;/a>;. Other &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1906.02243&quot;>;researchers&lt;/a>; calculated that training a medium-sized generative AI model using a technique called “neural architecture search” used electricity and energy consumption equivalent to 626,000 tons of CO2 emissions — or the same as CO2 emissions as driving five average American cars through their lifetimes. Training a single BERT model (a large language model developed by Google) from scratch would require the same energy and carbon footprint as a commercial trans-Atlantic flight.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Inference, or using the models to get responses to user prompts, uses less energy each session, but eventually involves many more sessions. Sometimes these models are only trained once, and then deployed to the cloud and used by millions of users for inference. In that case, deploying large deep-learning models to the cloud for inference purposes also consumes a lot of energy.&amp;nbsp;Analysts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2019/05/09/google-cloud-doubles-down-on-nvidia-gpus-for-inference/?sh=7aa7fce46792&quot;>;report&lt;/a>; that NVIDIA estimates that 80–90% of the energy cost of neural networks lies in ongoing inference processing after a model has been trained.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to initial training and inference usage of energy by large generative models, users and resellers of these models are increasingly employing &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data&quot;>;fine-tuning or prompt-based training&lt;/a>;. When combined with the original generative model trained on large volumes of data, fine-tuning allows prompts and answers that are tailored to an organization&#39;s specific content. Some &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2205.01541.pdf&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; suggests that fine-tuning training consumes considerably less energy and computing power than initial training. However, if many organizations adopt fine-tune approaches and do it often, the overall energy consumption could be quite high.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although it is difficult to calculate the cost of manufacturing the computers needed to run all this AI software, there is reason to believe that it is very high. One &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.networkworld.com/article/2229029/computer-factories-eat-way-more-energy-than-running-the-devices-they-build.html&quot;>;2011 study&lt;/a>; estimated that 70% of the energy used by a typical laptop computer is incurred during its manufacture, and that desktop computers are even higher. It is likely that the complex and powerful GPU chips and servers used to run AI models are much higher than laptops and desktops.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Make AI Greener&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given all that, there is a movement to make AI modelling, deployment, and usage more environmentally sustainable. Its goal is to replace power-hungry approaches with more suitable and environmentally-conscious replacements. Change is needed from both vendors and users to make AI algorithms green so that their utility can be widely deployed without harm to the environment. Generative models in particular, given their high energy consumption, need to become greener before they become more pervasive. We know of several different ways in which AI and generative AI can move in this direction, which we describe below.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use existing large generative models, don&#39;t generate your own. &lt;/strong>;There are already many providers of large language and image models, and there will be more. Creating and training them requires enormous amounts of energy. There is little need for companies other than large vendors or cloud providers to generate their own large models from scratch. They already have access to the needed training data and massive volumes of computing capability in the cloud, so they don&#39;t need to acquire it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Fine-tune train existing models. &lt;/strong>;If a company wants a generative model trained on its own content, it shouldn&#39;t start from scratch to train a model but rather refine an existing model. Fine-tuning and prompt training on specific content domains consume much less energy than training new large models from scratch. It can also provide more value to many businesses than generically-trained models. This should be the primary focus for companies wishing to adopt generative models for their own content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use energy-conserving computational methods.&lt;/strong>; Another approach to reducing generative AI energy consumption is to use less computationally expensive approaches such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tinyml.org/&quot;>;TinyML&lt;/a>; to process the data. The TinyML framework allows users to run ML models on small, low-powered edge devices like microcontrollers with low bandwidth requirements (no need to send the data to the server for processing). While general CPUs consume an average of 70 watts of power and GPUs consume 400 watts of power, a tiny microcontroller consumes just a few hundred microwatts — a thousand times less power — to process the data locally without sending it to data servers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use a large model only when it offers significant value.&lt;/strong>; It is important for data scientists and developers to know where the model provides value. If the usage of a 3x more power-hungry system increases the accuracy of a model by just 1–3% then it is not worth the extra energy consumption. More broadly, machine learning and artificial intelligence are not always required to solve a problem. Developers need to first do research and analysis of multiple alternative solutions and select an approach according to the findings. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://montrealethics.ai/publications/&quot;>;Montreal AI Ethics Institute&lt;/a>;, for example, is actively working on this problem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Be discerning about when you use generative AI. &lt;/strong>;Machine learning and NLP tools are revolutionary for medical-related health problems and prediction. They are great for predicting natural hazards such as tsunamis, earthquakes, etc. These are useful applications, but tools just for generating blog posts or creating amusing stories may not be the best use for these computation-heavy tools. They may be depleting the earth&#39;s health more than they are helping its people. If a company is employing generative AI for content creation, it should try to ensure that the models are used only when necessary or to reduce other computing costs, which should also reduce their overall computing budgets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate the energy sources of your cloud provider or data center. &lt;/strong>;AI (and software in general) carbon intensity can be minimized by deploying models in regions that are able to use environmentally friendly power resources and are carbon friendly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlco2.github.io/impact/#publish&quot;>;This practice&lt;/a>; has shown a 75% reduction in operational emissions. For example, a model trained and operating in the US may use energy from fossil fuels, but the same model can be run in Quebec where the primary energy source is hydroelectric. &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/sustainability/clean-energy-projects-begin-to-power-google-data-centers&quot;>;Google&lt;/a>; has recently started to build a $735 million clean energy data center in Quebec and plans to shift to 24/7 carbon-free energy by 2030. It also offers a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://services.google.com/fh/files/misc/active_assist_sustainability_spotlight.pdf&quot;>;Carbon Sense Suite&lt;/a>;” to help companies reduce energy consumption in their cloud workloads. Users of cloud providers can monitor the companies&#39; announcements about when and how they have deployed carbon-neutral or zero-carbon energy sources.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Re-use models and resources&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;.&lt;/strong>; Just like other materials, tech can be reused. Open-source models can be used rather than training new ones. Recycling can lower the impact of carbon-producing AI practices. Raw materials can be extracted to make newer generations of the latest laptops, processors, hard drives, and much more.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Include AI activity in your carbon monitoring.&lt;/strong>; Carbon monitoring practices need to be adopted by all research labs, AI vendors, and AI-using firms to know what is their carbon footprint. They also need to publicize their footprint numbers in order for their customers to make intelligent decisions about doing AI-related business with them. The calculation of GHG emissions is dependent on the data sets of the data suppliers and processing firms such as research labs and AI-based service providers such as OpenAI. From the inception of the ideas to the infrastructure that will be utilized to gain research results, all need to be following green AI approaches. There are several packages and online tools available like &lt;a href=&quot;https://codecarbon.io/&quot;>;CodeCarbon&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.green-algorithms.org/&quot;>;Green algorithms&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlco2.github.io/impact/#compute&quot;>;ML CO2 Impact&lt;/a>;, which can be included in your code at runtime to estimate your emissions and we should encourage the developer community to consider these performance metrics to establish benchmarks and to evaluate ML models.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there are many considerations involved with the use of generative AI models by organizations and individuals: ethical, legal, and even philosophical and psychological. Ecological concerns, however, are worthy of being added to the mix. We can debate the long-term future implications of these technologies for humanity, but such considerations will be moot if we don&#39;t have a habitable planet to debate them on.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Protecting Your Workforce from Extreme Heat]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_20_1484622360.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies have more than one reason to be worried about soaring global temperatures and heat waves. The health risks to employees range from exhaustion, cramps, worsening mental health, diabetic complications, and even stroke. In addition, extreme heat is projected to cause the loss of more than $4 trillion annually in productivity by 2030. The author, a physician who advises corporate leaders, recommends six best practices to help employers safeguard their people and their business.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Temperatures are soaring, records are being &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/whats-causing-this-record-breaking-heat/&quot;>;shattered&lt;/a>; and it can feel as if there is no relief in sight. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2023/07/13/heatwave-california-arizona-florida-texas-records/&quot;>;coast-to-coast heat domes&lt;/a>; to eponymous heatwaves like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-66183069&quot;>;Cerberus&lt;/a>;, extreme heat events may be the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/10/climate/climate-change-extreme-weather.html&quot;>;new norm&lt;/a>;. And companies have more than one reason to be worried.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://assets.website-files.com/5df9172583d7eec04960799a/618872a58d35f2643cbcaef2_BX9770_ESG_Critical%20industries%20have%20substantial%20exposure_7Nov2021.pdf&quot;>;2021 Moody&#39;s report&lt;/a>; identified heat stress as a physical risk that impacts almost every sector. Beyond rising &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/heat-waves-can-create-stormy-economic-weather-n894311&quot;>;cooling costs&lt;/a>; and shifting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/13/business/disney-world-universal-orlando-attendance-down/index.html&quot;>;consumer demand&lt;/a>;, heat stress represents a major threat to companies because of its effects on human health. Heat waves can cause exhaustion, cramps, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/news-room/news-releases/extreme-heat-contributes-to-worsening-mental-healt#:~:text=Extreme%20heat%20has%20been%20associated,with%20an%20increase%20in%20suicide.&quot;>;worsening mental health&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/diabetes/library/features/manage-diabetes-heat.html&quot;>;diabetic complications&lt;/a>;, and even stroke. There is considerable risk in any population, and this includes your company&#39;s workforce.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to direct health costs of heat waves, the World Health Organization cites one of the most important economic impacts as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789240057906&quot;>;lost productivity&lt;/a>;. Two percent of total working hours are projected to be lost each year due to heat stress at work, representing more than $&lt;a href=&quot;https://futureearth.org/publications/issue-briefs-2/heatwaves/&quot;>;4 trillion annually&lt;/a>; by 2030. So when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2023/07/13/heatwave-california-arizona-florida-texas-records/&quot;>;100 million Americans&lt;/a>; are under a heat alert, that could mean up to one in three employees – or more, depending on your company&#39;s geography — are at risk at a given time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Keeping your cool when extreme heat hits your workforce isn&#39;t easy, but insights from health care can help. As a physician working for an international organization advising corporate leaders, I&#39;m seeing employers looking to deepen their understanding of heat stress to adopt new best practices that safeguard their people &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; their business. Here are six actions to consider in navigating this challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Take a preventative approach.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Employers should start by educating employees on what heat stress is, how it affects their health and safety, and how it can be prevented.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In any warm environment, the human body relies on its ability to get rid of excess heat to maintain a healthy internal body temperature. This happens naturally through sweating and increased blood flow to the skin. If this doesn&#39;t happen quickly enough, body temperature rises and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ehs.research.uiowa.edu/occupational/heat-stress&quot;>;heat stress&lt;/a>; can occur.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Workers may experience symptoms including thirst, irritability, &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22440-heat-rashprickly-heat#:~:text=A%20heat%20rash%20is%20an,in%20hot%20and%20humid%20climates.&quot;>;heat rash&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21480-heat-exhaustion#:~:text=Heat%20exhaustion%20happens%20when%20your,resting%20in%20a%20cool%20place.&quot;>;heat exhaustion&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21812-heatstroke#:~:text=A%20note%20from%20Cleveland%20Clinic,loss%20of%20consciousness%2C%20among%20others.&quot;>;heat stroke&lt;/a>; which includes brain dysfunction such as slurred speech, confusion, disorientation or even coma. Heat stress can also impair &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facilities.udel.edu/safety/5224/&quot;>;fine motor s&lt;/a>;kills, such as typing, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1518/001872007X230226&quot;>;reduces capacity&lt;/a>; to process task-relevant information.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During heat waves, workers may experience a combination of two kinds of heat-related illness: “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC164365/&quot;>;exertional heat illness&lt;/a>;” due to physical activity and “&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/582911&quot;>;environmental heat illness&lt;/a>;” due to ambient conditions like heat and humidity. The latter is especially common in &lt;a href=&quot;https://climatekids.nasa.gov/heat-islands/#:~:text=An%20urban%20heat%20island%20occurs,environment%20absorb%20and%20hold%20heat.&quot;>;urban heat islands&lt;/a>; where temperatures in a city are much warmer than nearby rural areas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ultimately, heat stress can lead to illness, hospitalization, and even death. Given the potential severity, upstream solutions are critical. An effective heat-related illness prevention program should be incorporated in your organization&#39;s broader health and safety program and align with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/safety-management&quot;>;Occupational Safety and Health Administration&#39;s&lt;/a>; (OSHA) recommended practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During the first few days in a heat wave, employers should encourage workers to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/UserFiles/works/pdfs/2017-126.pdf&quot;>;hydrate&lt;/a>;, take frequent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/UserFiles/works/pdfs/2017-127.pdf&quot;>;breaks&lt;/a>;, and quickly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/osha3154.pdf&quot;>;identify&lt;/a>; any heat-related symptoms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Know how hot is too hot — and for whom.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Workplace heat exposure involves a combination of factors. To determine if heat stress is too high, employers need to assess the:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Environment (including conditions such as humidity, sunlight, and airflow)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Job (for example, whether it involves physical activity or protective gear)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Worker (assessing common individual risk factors, such as age, pre-existing health conditions, and lifestyle)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The most accurate way to measure environmental heat impact on body temperature is with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.popsci.com/environment/wet-bulb-globe-temperature/&quot;>;wet bulb globe temperature&lt;/a>; (WBGT) meter, which incorporates temperature, humidity, sunlight, and air movement into a single measurement. OSHA provides &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/hazards#environmentalheat&quot;>;guidance&lt;/a>; for use and interpretation of results. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weather.gov/ama/heatindex#:~:text=The%20heat%20index%2C%20also%20known,combined%20with%20the%20air%20temperature.&quot;>;heat index&lt;/a>; focused on temperature and humidity alone can provide &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25616731/&quot;>;helpful surrogate data&lt;/a>; in certain circumstances.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Job-related physical activity can be estimated using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/hazards#metabolicheat&quot;>;metabolic heat and workload tables&lt;/a>; with workload classified from light (eg, sitting or standing) to very heavy (eg, intense activity). Employers should also be aware of whether workers&#39; clothing increases risk and recognize jobs in hot environments such as firefighting, farming, construction work, mining, and factory work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Individual worker factors can also indicate unique risks whereby different employees react to heat in different ways. This includes vulnerable populations, such as those who are 65 years of age or older, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/repro/heat.html&quot;>;pregnant&lt;/a>;, have certain types of heart disease, high blood pressure, obesity, diabetes or use certain &lt;a href=&quot;https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-heat-and-how-it-affects-medication/&quot;>;medications&lt;/a>;. Gender differences are important to consider as well. The National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) reports &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccohs.ca/oshanswers/phys_agents/heat/heat_health.html#:~:text=The%20National%20Institute%20for%20Occupational,less%20heat%20tolerant%20than%20men.&quot;>;several studies&lt;/a>; showing women are less heat tolerant than men.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Maximize indoor thermal comfort.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccohs.ca/oshanswers/phys_agents/thermal_comfort.html&quot;>;Thermal comfort&lt;/a>; for office work is important for well-being and productivity. Too warm, and employees feel &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/288297978_Effects_of_thermal_discomfort_on_performance_of_office_work_and_physiological_behaviours&quot;>;fatigue or experience mood disturbance&lt;/a>;. Too cold, and attention can &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23443576/&quot;>;drift&lt;/a>; with employees feeling restless or distracted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Maintain consistent thermal conditions in the office environment. Even minor deviation may cause stress and affect performance and safety. Workers already under stress are less tolerant of uncomfortable conditions, so temperature becomes particularly important for high-demand jobs and during periods of high-stress crisis response.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Optimize temperature to match recommended guidelines. The American Society of Heating, Refrigerating, and Air Conditioning Engineers (ASHRAE) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/indoorenv/hvac.html&quot;>;Standard&lt;/a>; recommends temperature ranges of 68.5°F to 75°F in the winter, and 75°F to 80.5°F in the summer. The difference in seasonal temperature ranges is largely due to clothing selection.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some situations, legislation may have specific requirements and it is important for employers to meet these. Beyond federal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/standards&quot;>;OSHA standards&lt;/a>;, some states have adopted OSHA-approved &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/stateplans/&quot;>;state plans&lt;/a>; that cover hazards not otherwise addressed. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mn.gov/admin/assets/heat_stress_guide_tcm36-207189.pdf&quot;>;Minnesota&lt;/a>; regulates indoor air temperatures in places of employment and varies requirements based on intensity level of work. Similarly, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.opb.org/article/2022/05/11/oregon-heat-wildfire-smoke-farmwork-laborer-rules/&quot;>;Oregon&lt;/a>; recently adopted some of America&#39;s most protective heat rules for workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recommended temperature ranges meet the needs of at least &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ashrae.org/File%20Library/Conferences/Specialty%20Conferences/2018%20Building%20Performance%20Analysis%20Conference%20and%20SimBuild/Papers/C036.pdf&quot;>;80% of individuals&lt;/a>; but some employees may feel uncomfortable even if these values are met. Temperature needs and preferences vary greatly, and there is no one temperature that can satisfy everyone. Additional measures may be required.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Difference in thermal comfort may be due to indoor climate regulations being based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://cris.maastrichtuniversity.nl/en/publications/energy-consumption-in-buildings-and-female-thermal-demand&quot;>;standard values in men&lt;/a>; and can impact women&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2019/05/26/727108363/how-office-temperature-affects-cognitive-performance&quot;>;cognitive performance&lt;/a>;. In general, women prefer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0360132306000242&quot;>;higher ambient temperature&lt;/a>; at home and in the workplace. That being said, when it comes to heat waves, women are generally &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935122013135&quot;>;more vulnerable&lt;/a>; to high temperatures. And this vulnerability increases after menopause when &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26674572/&quot;>;lack of estrogen production&lt;/a>; makes it more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935122013135&quot;>;difficult to adapt&lt;/a>; to sudden temperature increases.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given thermal comfort is determined by a number of factors beyond temperature, such as activity levels, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/engineering/solar-gain#:~:text=Solar%20gain%20(or%20solar%20heat,results%20from%20absorbed%20solar%20radiation.&quot;>;solar gain&lt;/a>;, and air flow, optimizing for those can help. For example, enhance access to desk fans or working areas of greater air flow for menopausal women experiencing hot flashes. Other options to make the workplace more comfortable include changes to workload and schedules. For example, scheduling work during off-peak temperature hours or shorter shifts with frequent rest breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Tailor training and safety for outdoor workers.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Provide a heat stress training program before hot outdoor work begins. Training may include proper use of heat-protective clothing and equipment, effects of drugs and alcohol on heat stress tolerance, immediate reporting of signs or symptoms of heat-related illness (in oneself or coworkers), and procedures for responding to these symptoms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Supervisors should be provided with additional training. This may include monitoring alert reports, responding to hot weather advisories, procedures to follow when a worker has signs or symptoms of heat-related illness (including contacting emergency medical services where appropriate), encouraging hydration, and reinforcing rest breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond training, employers should reduce workplace heat stress using engineering and administrative controls. Engineering controls include changes to work-setting design that reduce exposure to heat, such as the use of reflective or heat-absorbing shielding. Administrative controls are changes to tasks or schedules that reduce heat stress, for example, limiting time in the heat, increasing recovery time in cool shaded areas, increasing the number of workers per task, or providing adequate cool, potable water. It is also important to limit heat burden while wearing personal protective equipment (PPE) and to explore auxiliary cooling systems, like water-cooled garments or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6997718/&quot;>;cooling vests&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Additional strategies include creating a multi-disciplinary working group (eg, cohort of workers, qualified health care provider, safety manager), instituting medical and self-monitoring programs, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7374462/&quot;>;wearable monitors&lt;/a>; to estimate workload (eg, heart rate sensors), and a buddy system where workers observe each other for signs of heat-related illness.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Practice acclimatization.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Individuals can adapt to higher temperatures through repeated exposures, for example, via increased sweating efficiency. This is particularly relevant for outdoor workers during rapid onset heat waves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers should develop acclimatization schedules in hot conditions that gradually increase worker exposure time and physical demands. This is typically done in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/userfiles/works/pdfs/2017-124.pdf&quot;>;step-wise process&lt;/a>; over a seven to 14 day period. New workers will need more time to acclimatize than those with pre-existing exposure, and absence for a week or more may require re-acclimatization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The level of adaptation for each worker is relative to physical fitness and heat stress experienced. It is also important to consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33205218/&quot;>;gender differences&lt;/a>;, as women require greater intensity, frequency, and duration of heat exposure for adaptation. Given related literature primarily focuses on males, current guidelines may not account for physiological differences and may require employers to explore &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10289939/&quot;>;new frameworks&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6. Adopt a long-term heat-health action plan&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As extreme heat continues to worsen, employers must adopt a long-term approach. The World Health Organization&#39;s guidance for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789289071918&quot;>;heat-health action plans&lt;/a>; offers particularly useful principles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similar to how airlines track weather for flight planning, employers should tap into accurate and timely temperature alert systems that trigger weather-related warnings, determine thresholds for action, and communicate risks. &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalnews.ca/news/8738567/summer-air-travel-heat-wave-impact/&quot;>;Establishing links&lt;/a>; with local public health systems and emergency response services also helps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You should also have a communication plan that includes what to communicate, to whom, and when. Recognize that you may be managing multiple environmental health issues simultaneously — for example, extreme heat and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires&quot;>;air quality issues&lt;/a>; related to wildfires — and be sure to streamline messaging. Avoid overwhelming employees with multiple non-synchronized communications. Also tailor your messaging for local areas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your heat-health action plan should also include short and medium-term heat relief approaches, such as reduction in indoor heat exposure, enhanced outdoor worker protections, and a care strategy for vulnerable populations. Your long-term approach should include strategic urban planning to address &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90653389/how-an-ancient-design-technique-could-help-us-survive-extreme-heat-no-ac-needed&quot;>;building design&lt;/a>;, location, and transit access points that can reduce heat exposure for employees in their end-to-end journey from home to work and back.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Track efficacy of your heat-health strategy over time. Implement real-time surveillance and evaluation particularly for outdoor workers, and don&#39;t forget oversight of indoor environment controls. Monitor for quality and consistency to make sure you are meeting ASHRAE recommendations and local legislation requirements. Engaging safety checklists and standard best practices found in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://airlines.iata.org/2014/12/08/severe-weather-warning&quot;>;airline industry&lt;/a>; can be especially helpful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Extreme heat can greatly impair the performance and health of your greatest assets — your people. As these high temperatures become more commonplace, employers must seize the opportunity to protect their employees today and into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: How to Effectively Market Green Products]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1173369992.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Richard Drury/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A study, involving Edelman and nine major brands, finds that despite corporate hesitations, sustainable products are growing twice as fast as conventional ones, appealing across all demographics. Brands should ensure that product quality is not compromised while promoting sustainability. Combining sustainability claims with core brand attributes can broaden consumer appeal. Effective sustainability messages prioritize the personal and community benefits, while technical or scientific claims are less compelling unless tied to consumer benefits. Sustainably-marketed goods are consistently growing across demographics, indicating that compelling sustainability claims can boost customer engagement and business growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In these polarized times, corporate leaders are growing skittish about promoting sustainability in their products. Yet &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/csb-sustainable-market-share-index&quot;>;our research&lt;/a>; on actual consumer purchases demonstrates that sustainable products are growing two times faster than conventional, at a 28% premium in average, across most demographics.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help brand managers and marketing leads capitalize on this growing market, we partnered with Edelman and nine leading brands across different industries (tech, apparel, beverage, food) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/research-initiatives/effective-sustainability-communications-best-practice-guide-brands-marketers&quot;>;to research which sustainability messages work best with consumers.&lt;/a>; In contrast to current hyperbole about polarized consumers, we found that the most resonant sustainability claims are highly compelling for &lt;em>;all&lt;/em>; demographics — old/young, blue state/ red state, high income/low income, men/women, etc.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We conducted a custom online study of a sample of the US general population in end 2022/early 2023 for the nine iconic brands. Respondents for each brand were asked to evaluate 30–35 different claims (including a mix of category and environmental sustainability claims) to gauge their overall appeal. Rather than using a traditional rating scale, we utilized a user-friendly and robust analytical approach called MaxDiff. It forces a top and bottom pick from a short list of claims in each choice set, making the respondent task easier, and providing better discrimination in responses across the claims. Each respondent evaluated multiple choice sets, allowing for claims to be randomized based on an experimental design. The MaxDiff results yielded an appeal score for each claim — in aggregate and among key sub-groups of interest. Most importantly we added a TURF component to identify the optimal combination of claims to maximize overall appeal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Following are the insights and lessons learned.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Core category claims are paramount — the product must work, be tasty, clean properly, etc. This makes sense. Who wants sustainable chocolate that does not taste good or a sustainable cleaning product that does not clean? Yet, occasionally, marketing materials focus solely on sustainability which can limit a brand&#39;s potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Compelling sustainability claims anchored in the core brand attributes significantly expand brand reach by bringing in new consumers. As seen in Figure 1, the core attribute claim may resonate with 44 of every 100 people (average among nine brands tested), but when you add compelling sustainability claims you can increase customer appeal to 74 in every 100 people. An example of a high-performing, laddered claim is: “Formulated with sustainable ingredients that are good for your skin.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;High-resonance sustainability claims focus on what is in it for the consumer, starting with themselves and their families and then moving to their communities. For instance:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Healthy for you and your family: “&lt;em>;Grown without harmful ingredients synthetic pesticides, herbicides, or fungicides” &lt;/em>;for food, and “&lt;em>;Formulated without harmful ingredients parabens, phthalates, dyes and aluminum” &lt;/em>;for skincare&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Saves you money: &lt;em>;“Lower energy for lower monthly energy bills,” &lt;/em>;or&lt;em>; “Helps reduce waste and save money.&lt;/em>;” For non-CPG items, messaging can stress durability and access to repair services.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Protects our children: “&lt;em>;For future generations.&lt;/em>;”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Helps local farmers: “&lt;em>;Working with local farmers to use regenerative farming practices to help conserve nature, encourage biodiversity, and improve soil health.&lt;/em>;” Claims that only talked about regenerative practices without connecting the claims to local farmers did not resonate.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Protects animals: &lt;em>;“Not tested on animals.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Sustainably sourced: “&lt;em>;Sourced from 100% sustainable ingredients/materials.&lt;/em>;”&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Lower performing claims included science-based claims, traceability, packaging-based claims, and certifications. In other words, the consumer is less interested in technical topics than in personal concerns. However, if the reason for the consumer to care was added to science-based claims they performed better (eg, carbon neutral for cleaner air to breath vs. carbon neutral). Certifications, while not highly resonate by themselves, are important to ensure the brand protects against green-washing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In summary, effective sustainability marketing, though to a certain degree category specific, has a top 10 set of components that are compelling for all demographics. Marketing leaders can use the following guidance to develop messaging (and also review the full report). It should be stressed that sustainability marketing needs to be tied to real and effective sustainable sourcing and production practices. To move forward:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Prioritize the communication of your brand benefit first and foremost.&lt;/strong>; Leverage the relevant sustainability messaging to strengthen the brand positioning.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Link the sustainability claim to the category reason-for-being.&lt;/strong>; “100% sustainably farmed for a great tasting product.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Focus the claim on the benefit to the consumer and their families.&lt;/strong>; Consider sustainability claims that ensure the products are safe for human consumption or contact such as “made without chemicals harmful to human health.” Articulate the claim with an emotional component, particularly as it relates to the long term health of the planet or their children, such as “good for your children/future generations,” or “good for the planet.” To the extent possible, provide a personal monetary benefit to the claim, such as “longer life,” “less waste,” “lower energy bills.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;The term sustainable, as it relates to “sustainable sourcing and production” is compelling&lt;/strong>; and does not need further explanation. Eg, “100% sustainably sourced,” “100% sustainably produced.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Consumers are concerned about animal welfare&lt;/strong>;. If appropriate, include communication to ensure that no harm is done to animals in the testing of the product, such as “no animal testing” or “cruelty-free.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;For food and personal care categories, if possible&lt;strong>;, tie the claims to farmers and local sourcing,&lt;/strong>; such as “sourced from local farmers.” Regenerative agriculture claims are compelling, for example, when focused on local farmers and their farms. Eg, “Partnering with local farmers to ensure the long-term health of the farm for the future of our food systems.” or “Partnering with local farmers to ensure the farms stay climate resilient, nutrient dense.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Provide a reason to care when communicating the more scientific aspects of sustainability&lt;/strong>;. “Carbon neutral to reduce the impact of climate change” vs. “carbon neutral” by itself.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Quantify sustainability claims for greater resonance&lt;/strong>;, such as&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; “Using 1 million tons of ocean-recovered plastic bottles.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Use certifications to guard against greenwashing, but don&#39;t rely on them as the sole point of information.&lt;/strong>; For example, “100% sustainably sourced and certified by the Rainforest Alliance” works better than just putting the label on pack.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Deliver the product with fully recyclable packaging&lt;/strong>;. While consumers generally were less responsive to sustainable packaging claims, “made from 100% recycled plastic/cardboard” was the most compelling.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We are convinced that compelling sustainability claims will help businesses grow consumer loyalty and market share. In another research initiative with Circana (which collects consumer purchasing data), we have reviewed purchases of consumer packaged goods in the US on an annual basis since 2019 (when we looked back to 2014). In reviewing 36 categories annually (several hundred thousand products), we have observed consistent conversion of conventional products into sustainable ones. For example, in 2019, nine out of 36 categories were over 20% market share in terms of sustainability-marketed products and 14 categories were under 5%. Today 13 categories are over 20% and 9 categories are under 5%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And, while purchasing skews younger, wealthier, urban, and more educated, in fact we see significant purchasing across all demographics. Sustainability-marketed milk and yogurt, for example, which have more than 60% market share, are purchased by virtually every demographic at that rate, including rural, high school education or less, seniors and lower-income (despite an approximate 30% premium).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sustainable production of goods is beneficial for the planet, for consumers and for business. Corporate leaders can take heart from this research and invest in authentic and compelling messaging to engage customers, grow market share and make a positive contribution to society.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20 Questions to Ask When Your Team&rsquo;s Vibe Is Off]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1347421073.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Has your team lost sight of its purpose and the goals you&amp;#8217;re working toward together? If so, it might be time for a team reset that focuses on realignment. Or, maybe your team just doesn&amp;#8217;t feel like a team anymore? Maybe team members feel disconnected, invalidated, or frustrated, and even minor issues are creating friction? In that case, your reset must focus on revitalizing your team dynamic. This article focuses on some approaches that managers can use to address alignment gaps to jump-start a new, healthier, happier team dynamic.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Is your team feeling stuck, stymied, or just a bit stale? Have you fallen into routines that are no longer serving you? It&#39;s okay; teams need occasional course corrections, even in calm waters. And in today&#39;s stormy seas, you might need to chart a whole new course as we navigate return-to-office and hybrid work arrangements. The good news is that resetting your team can be easier than you think.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your first step is to reflect on what feels off. You can think about it in two broad categories. First, is the problem that your team has lost sight of your purpose and the goals you&#39;re working toward? If so, your reset will need to focus on realignment. The other possibility (and it could be both) is that you don&#39;t feel like a team anymore. Maybe team members feel disconnected, invalidated, or frustrated — so much so that even minor issues are creating friction. In that case, your reset must focus on revitalizing your team dynamic. Here&#39;s how to navigate both of these approaches:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Realignment&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You&#39;ll want to prioritize realignment over revitalization for two reasons. First, many team dysfunctions manifest as trust issues when, in fact, they stem from discrepancies in goals, priorities, or expectations. Clearing up those misunderstandings often resolves what you thought were interpersonal issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another reason to start with realignment is that it allows you to tie your reset to external shifts rather than individual behavior problems, making it less likely to trigger defensiveness. When you realign, you&#39;re not judging anyone; instead, you&#39;re asking how you need to evolve to capitalize on opportunities and mitigate emerging risks. Here are some anchor points for realignment. Choose the ones that best match your situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team&#39;s mandate.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The first possibility is that your team&#39;s purpose needs to evolve. You can explore that possibility with these questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What external trends require us to adapt?&lt;/strong>; What are the most salient changes in the external environment, and how do they change the context for your team? For example, if you&#39;re a content marketing team, how does ChatGPT change your team&#39;s value?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How does a shift in company strategy affect your role?&lt;/strong>; Does your organization have a new vision, strategy, or KPI that alters what your team needs to deliver? For example, if you&#39;re an HR team, does opening European offices require new capabilities or activities?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How is your value within the organization evolving?&lt;/strong>; As organizations grow and change, the role of teams can evolve. How will changes in your organization structure require you to refocus? For example, how will you tailor your offerings if you&#39;re an R&amp;amp;D team now supporting two units instead of one?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team&#39;s goals.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If your mandate has changed, you&#39;ll certainly need to revisit your goals, but even if your purpose is unchanged, your goals might need a refresh. So, consider these as reasons to move the target.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How will you build on prior results?&lt;/strong>; What did you accomplish in the last quarter, and how does that change the trajectory you want for the next few quarters? If you&#39;ve been achieving your goals, are they ambitious enough? On the other hand, if you&#39;ve been missing consistently, do you need to lower your goals or risk demoralizing everyone?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How will external factors affect your goals? &lt;/strong>;Is there anything external that might suggest a goal change? For example, do you need to temper expectations in light of an economic downturn, supply chain backlogs, or labor shortages? On the other hand, if your team benefits from new technological advances, could you accomplish more than planned?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What can you do to improve your measures?&lt;/strong>; Are your goals fuzzy, or are your metrics nebulous? Your fastest way to improve alignment might be to tighten your definitions or tweak your metrics, making it more evident whether you&#39;re getting traction.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your strategies and tactics.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Any changes based on your mandate or goals will necessitate reexamining your strategies. But don&#39;t limit a strategy refresh to situations where the targets have moved; considering new possibilities can be a good reset anytime.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Are your strategies aligned with your mandate?&lt;/strong>; If your mandate or goals have shifted, how must your strategy change in response? For example, if your team has been tasked with adding professional services to your software offering, what will it take to make that business model successful?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Where do you need revised tactics?&lt;/strong>; If you&#39;re still working toward existing goals, what&#39;s been working, and where could you change your tack? Conversely, what do you need to abandon? Where could you double down?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What contingencies might emerge?&lt;/strong>; Even if you&#39;re sticking with your existing mandate, goals, strategies, and tactics, you can reset by considering new scenarios and preparing your contingency plans. What assumptions are embedded in your current plan? What would negate those assumptions? What would be the leading indicators that something is changing?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your roles.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s possible that your team is on the right track but that you&#39;re not optimizing the energy and talents of team members. In that case, consider these questions about individuals&#39; accountabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Do people need a change in role?&lt;/strong>; Are there any changes in roles or responsibilities that would make the people in your team more effective? Do you need to change someone&#39;s portfolio? Could you shake up who&#39;s in what role for multi-skilling, development, or succession advantages? Who might be reinvigorated by a new challenge?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you make accountabilities more straightforward?&lt;/strong>; Are there opportunities to fine-tune people&#39;s responsibilities to make them more compelling? Are there spots where shared accountabilities are diluting people&#39;s sense of obligation? How could you increase alignment, efficiency, and effectiveness by clarifying who owns which decisions?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;One of the most constructive ways to reset your team is to refocus on what your organization, colleagues, and customers are counting on you to do. Rekindling your team&#39;s passion and reminding them what you&#39;re fighting for is the best place to start.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Revitalization&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second type of reset is to revitalize your team dynamic. Does it feel like you&#39;ve devolved from being a true team into a loose collection of people where the whole is no more than the sum of the parts? Or worse, is mistrust or unhealthy conflict making it feel like teamwork is a net negative? In that case, your reset might need to focus less on &lt;em>;what&lt;/em>; your team needs to do and more on &lt;em>;how&lt;/em>; you do it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your communication habits.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Over time, teams can become lazy and fall into communication patterns that dilute connection. Revisiting your communication habits can help you reconnect.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Can you reset your communication channels?&lt;/strong>; Do you default to certain modes of communication that aren&#39;t optimized for the content? For example, if you&#39;re using Zoom to inform and email to debate, you&#39;ve got it backward. Can you use richer communication vehicles for more novel content, contentious discussions, and unfamiliar participants? Can you shunt informational items to email?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What warrants synchronous communication?&lt;/strong>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/hybrid-tanked-work-life-balance-heres-how-microsoft-is-trying-to-fix-it&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that the average person has more than double the hours of meetings than before the pandemic. Which types of information could you share asynchronously instead to allow people more control over their schedules?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you implement blackout periods?&lt;/strong>; In addition to the deluge of meetings, most people are also inundated by a torrent of emails. How could your team enforce blackout periods where people can turn off notifications and work without communication obligations? How can you increase the opportunities for people to work &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/to-control-your-life-control-what-you-pay-attention-to&quot;>;without distractions&lt;/a>;?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your meetings.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you optimize your standing meetings?&lt;/strong>; Meetings tend to be more effective when they have homogeneous content. Could you clean up your &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/04/a-step-by-step-guide-to-structuring-better-meetings&quot;>;meeting structure&lt;/a>; to separate content that requires different mindsets and behaviors?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Does the participant list need to change?&lt;/strong>; One way to reset the conversation is to change who&#39;s party to it. Is it time to step out of some meetings and let your team take the reins? Would new voices and new perspectives bring some &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/01/if-your-team-agrees-on-everything-working-together-is-pointless&quot;>;productive conflict&lt;/a>;?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Do you need to prepare better?&lt;/strong>; Inefficient meetings are infuriating meetings. How could you use &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/how-to-create-the-perfect-meeting-agenda&quot;>;better primer documents&lt;/a>; to prepare team members to contribute in evidence-based and thoughtful ways?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team dynamics.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What would be your new ground rules?&lt;/strong>; Maybe you&#39;ve had &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/write-down-your-teams-unwritten-rules&quot;>;ground rules&lt;/a>; and stopped respecting them, or you never had any. What behaviors have you been tolerating that need to stop? What would be a welcome addition? Revisiting the principles for how team members behave can be an excellent way to reset.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you resolve conflict debts?&lt;/strong>; If your team has been avoiding difficult conversations about priorities and trade-offs or trust and disrespect, you need to get the issues out in the open to move beyond them.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What activities would foster insight into each other?&lt;/strong>; If your team dynamics are suffering, you might want to enlist outside help with formal team development activities. For example, psychometric tools or group coaching could foster trust and promote candor.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;If your team is accomplishing plenty but finding it&#39;s harder than necessary, these different approaches will jump-start a new, healthier, happier team dynamic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And finally, a personal note. While you ponder your team reset, it&#39;s an excellent time to consider whether you need to reset your own approach. For example, has work started consuming more time and energy than is healthy? Are you taking on too much and delegating too little? This is also the perfect opportunity to consider &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;what reset you need as the team&#39;s leader&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Taking a Vacation Improves Your Well-Being]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1393555725.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Javier Zayas Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Making sure your employees regularly take time off is key to creating a more sustainable workplace. Research shows that taking time off benefits employees in three ways: 1) Mentally. Taking a vacation provides greater opportunity for rest and better sleep (both quantity and quality), which can help unclutter your mind to boost creativity. 2) Body. Relaxing on vacation can reduce the levels of your stress hormones and allow your immune system to recover, making you less prone to get sick. 3) Soul. While it sounds hokey, answers to life&amp;#8217;s big questions &amp;#8212; like &amp;#8220;What do I really want?&amp;#8221; or &amp;#8220;What&amp;#8217;s most important to me?&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; are more likely to come to us when there is some space and stillness.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;fJZdvvhLBXBnM0awCRi2N9HHNyNCvzzf/ZLTeqiPe9l6izIl1hjxZtNoQ9yiC+8U&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5iAHwuINYiqwQMPfwPWVfV9MxEM9MBqao9YfMEZCzGrw==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;07&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; >; &lt;p>;We all know that taking vacation is good for you, but it&#39;s less clear that both employers and employees understand exactly just &lt;em>;how good&lt;/em>; it is for you, given that every year more than half of Americans give up paid time off. According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ustravel.org/toolkit/time-and-vacation-usage&quot;>;US Travel Association&lt;/a>;, in 2018, this amounted to 768 million days of unused vacation time, with more than 30% of it forfeited completely. Add to this, the fact that over &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;50% of managers&lt;/a>; feel burned out, taking vacation (and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/set-these-5-boundaries-before-you-go-on-vacation?ab=HP-latest-text-3&quot;>;actually unplugging&lt;/a>;) has never been more important.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: The ESG Issues That Matter Most to People]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-the-esg-issues-that-matter-most-to-people]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_18_1357167258.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Xavier Lorenzo/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Research conducted by nonprofit organization JUST Capital highlights the importance of public opinion in determining corporate behaviors. The study reveals that when evaluating American firms, the public places a significant emphasis on the treatment of workers. This priority remains consistent across demographic and political groups, making it a crucial factor for managers aiming to improve their firms&amp;#8217; ESG (environmental, social, and corporate governance) performance. JUST Capital&amp;#8217;s methodology involves gathering public input through focus groups and surveys to define and assess justness in corporate behavior. Statistical analysis assigns weights to 20 key behaviors, with worker-related issues consistently ranking highest. Approximately 44% of respondents deem worker-related issues as most important, compared to other stakeholder categories. These findings have implications for managers seeking to be perceived as just. Prioritizing fair wages, health and safety, career advancement, and work-life balance for workers is essential. Incorporating public opinion in corporate rankings can provide a more objective and legitimate framework for evaluating justness.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;8oN0NgHb4VzIBbabZ4UnAXI9/jh3tbTxQWHkMpUG6gDJwFkyngdMQ8jHXBTRovc4&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5RStiASCfgwomdu6zjiF5VHaQTd+KY1kvraIJ0DINe/Q==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;07&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;research-the-esg-issues-that-matter-most-to-people&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; >; &lt;p>;For many corporate managers, improving their firms&#39; ESG (environmental, social, and corporate governance) performance is a central goal. To achieve it, they face trade-offs: Should they improve treatment of their workers, or instead reduce carbon emissions? Should they protect shareholders or the human rights of overseas workers?&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Worried About Impending Layoffs?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/worried-about-impending-layoffs]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_18_200564246-003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Thomas Jackson/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Getting laid off can be a traumatic event, but a little bit of preparation can go a long way. In this piece, the author outlines four ways to get started: 1) Just as it&amp;#8217;s important to maintain your health by getting periodic check-ups, you should also update your resume and LinkedIn profile regularly. It&amp;#8217;sa prudent best practice to take care of these updates before you need to. 2) Develop a list of your own top values. This self-knowledge gives you the lens through which to evaluate fit as you look at a company. 3) Get your finances in order. To be financially ready, you don&amp;#8217;t necessarily need to save a substantial amount of money from each paycheck &amp;#8212; start small and increase your savings rate occasionally. 4) Divorce your personal and work data. The simplest way to separate personal from work data is to use only devices you own for personal matters. The more prepared you are, the less impactful the layoff will be on your mental health and finances &amp;#8212; and the easier it will be to find a new job.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;C8VhVMBEJupffpPFlb2oO3fbl1FpiLmgaVeT15nP9AzhoIOs0ARAar83Vv+B+jTE&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5fOSgNbrbT592lu2yewJaW77T/Hq0AjYEZeuS3OvJDGg==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;07&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;worried-about-impending-layoffs&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; >; &lt;p>;Mass layoffs hit dozens of US companies in 2022 and show no sign of slowing, despite the robust economy and continued growth in new jobs. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://layoffs.fyi/&quot;>;Layoffs.fyi&lt;/a>;, tech companies slashed more than 187,000 positions in 2023 alone, compared to 80,000 in March to December 2020 and 15,000 in 2021. And it&#39;s not just tech that&#39;s feeling the pain — significant cuts have come from a wide range of sectors and blue-chip companies including the Gap, Disney, LinkedIn, FedEx, Dow, 3M, and Wayfair, to name a few.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>