<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Does Your Company Have a Culture of Quiet Retaliation?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_05_1423429755.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;无声的报复形式非常常见，并且在工作场所可能会传染。接受这种形式的报复作为标准做法的组织很难雇用和留住优秀人才。报复&amp;#8212;各种形式的不仅会伤害当前的团队成员，而且容忍报复的文化也会损害使命和组织向客户和利益相关者提供服务的能力。为了创造一种心理安全成为常态、创新蓬勃发展、团队效率高的文化，解决暗中发生的报复问题至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我们大多数人都熟悉教科书或人力资源政策中对报复的定义。公开、大声的报复时刻确实会发生，比如有人在大声疾呼或正式表达担忧后被解雇。然而，在我们与团队的合作中，我们经常目睹更微妙的报复形式，这些报复经常发生，但通常被忽视或忽视。微妙的、通常是无声的报复会毁掉职业生涯，侵蚀目标个人的价值感，并损害团队的效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们尚未遇到任何自称具有报复性的领导者，但我们经常看到报复的发生在团队上。当领导者只通过公开和大胆的行动来看待报复时，他们就会忽视其更微妙的表现，而其后果同样严重。如果领导者无法识别自己和他人的这些行为，他们就有可能对个人、团队和他们所服务的组织造成短期和长期伤害。为了创造一种心理安全为常态、创新蓬勃发展、团队效率高的文化，我们必须了解暗中发生的报复行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;报复的现实&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在在美国，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/eeoc-releases-fiscal-year-2020-enforcement-and-litigation-data&quot;>;55.8% 的索赔中提到了员工报复&lt; /a>; 于 20 财年向美国平等就业机会委员会 (EEOC) 提交了申请 - 这正是所报道的内容。举报报复行为可能会给个人的财务稳定性、未来职业发展和声誉带来重大风险。举报所需的时间和精力对许多人来说是一种威慑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些最常见的报复行为涉及经理&lt;em>;不&lt;/em>;采取的行动。这种悄悄的——有时是隐蔽的——报复行为极其有害，因为它可能会持续多年而不被发现、不被提及或不被报道。它不仅会影响目标个人，还会降低目睹这一事件的团队成员的信任水平、创造力和生产力，并使虐待文化永久化。维拉诺瓦教授 Manuela Priesemuth 在她的文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/06/times-up-for-有毒-workplaces&quot;>;有毒工作场所的时代到了&lt;/a>;”中分享了虐待和报复文化如何“蔓延到整个组织，形成了整个虐待氛围。因为员工向经理寻求并向经理学习，他们逐渐明白这种人际虐待在公司是可以接受的行为。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是我们在工作辅导中观察到的五个隐蔽报复的具体例子领导者及其服务的团队：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;拒绝提供指导、反馈或专业发展机会&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;拒绝为项目或部门提供资源&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;故意给予在几乎没有支持的情况下完成具有挑战性的任务，或者给出注定会失败的具有挑战性的任务&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;阻止其他人倾听或重视团队成员的声音、专业知识或贡献&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将团队成员排除在必要的之外马克*以报复性着称，在退休前曾担任一家大型零售公司的首席执行官十多年。当我们与新任首席执行官领导下的剩余领导团队合作时，我们很快发现，仅靠马克的离职不足以平息员工的恐惧。尽管马克已经不在了，但公司里仍然存在着明显的恐惧情绪。我们从几位领导那里听说，与马克的任何分歧都意味着你在公司内成长的终结。 “当他对某个敢于发声的人感到失望时，他会露出一种表情，”我们从几位领导人那里听到了这样的说法。 “他会在你的名字上画一条线，而不是在名字下面。每个人都知道，比赛基本上就结束了。你被困住了。”对于马克来说，报复采取了社会破坏和排斥的隐蔽形式。这对组织的影响是巨大的：创新停滞、文化受损、业务停滞。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Julia 是一家中型科技公司的首席财务官。当她收到部门内部有关敌对工作环境投诉的通知时，她表示自己已经意识到这些问题，因为这些问题已经发生多年，但一直避免解决。朱莉娅一直直言不希望她的团队成员与人力资源部讨论任何问题。 “为什么人们不能低下头完成工作呢？为什么我的工作就是处理他们幼稚的行为？”她问她的同龄人。朱莉娅随后剥夺了投诉团队成员获取执行工作所必需的信息和文件的权限。朱莉娅还不再及时回复她的电子邮件，并希望缺乏通信会导致项目按时完成的延误，进一步让团队成员在同事面前丢脸。当被问及这些行为时，朱莉娅回答说：“这不可能是报复，因为我没有解雇他们。”我们经常看到领导者进行悄悄的报复行为，从而产生巨大的影响，但他们并不认为这是报复，因为他们将报复狭隘地定义为解雇员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;罗恩曾在一家医院担任护士长。医院急诊科连续15年获青睐，年内大幅晋升。虽然医院内的正式领导赞赏罗恩严格、传统的管理风格，但其他急诊室工作人员的经历却截然不同。 “如果你做了一些让他烦恼的事情——也许表达了担忧或指出某些供应不足——你可以预期你将来所说或所做的一切都会受到审查。他无法接受任何反馈，即使是关于口罩或手套库存等简单的事情，”我们从一位值班领导那里听到。在这种特殊情况下，持续的负面审查对文化和僵局造成的负面影响不仅影响了部门，还危及公共安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;领导者应如何自我评估其影响&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;领导者经常将自己视为部门或组织中正确行为的看门人。在我们刚才描述的每种情况下，领导者都相信这就是他们正在做的事情。危险并不在于看不到你的意图和影响之间的脱节。领导人报复的连锁反应是巨大的。当领导者缺乏加深对其行为及其影响的自我认识所需的工具时，对所有利益相关者来说后果可能是可怕的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们倾向于根据我们的良好意图来判断自己，并根据他们的影响来判断他人。我们的领导指导原则之一是：你无法决定你的影响力；你可以决定你的影响力。其他人也这么做。那么，您如何才能更好地评估您的行为的影响并了解您行为的根本原因呢？从这三个实践开始：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;进行勇敢的审核。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;检查自己的行为并深入挖掘行为背后的动机。我们强烈建议基于&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gse.harvard.edu/hgse100/story/changing-better&quot;>;免疫变化&lt;/a>;的工作进行“勇敢的审计”实践罗伯特·基根和丽莎·莱希。变革免疫模型在这种情况下特别有效，因为它挑战我们思考我们的行为（或缺乏行为）如何妨碍创建心理安全的工作环境。想想团队成员中最让你沮丧的情况，并寻找你的行为方式是否没有效率或可能具有报复性。挑战自己，好奇地提问并勇敢地回答：我在做什么或不做什么会妨碍安全文化？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;意识到适得其反的行为是改变它们的第一步。我们经常听到领导者说，以这种方式反思自己在同事面前显得太脆弱，因此与经验丰富的教练合作是增强您在工作场所中的思想和行为的自我意识的有效方法。&lt;/p>; &lt; h3>;识别你的影子意图。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;影子意图是指我们（有意识或无意识）出于自我和自我保护的立场而行动。拒绝你自己声称的“提供帮助”或“保护你的部门”的愿望。您的想法或行为以何种方式意图通过隐蔽或被动的方式伤害团队成员？你什么时候被自我保护驱使而不受控制？您什么时候可能会允许您的第一次压力驱动反应对您对他人产生的影响产生负面影响？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;伊丽莎白是一家不断发展的 IT 公司的一员，而且从各方面来看，她都是领导团队的重要成员。当发生合并时，“必须为即将上任的领导者腾出空间”，她也多次被忽略晋升。虽然她希望继续证明自己的价值并领导好团队，但她需要支持来积极摆脱自己希望新领导者失败的阴影意图，这样她就可以因其卓越和持续的承诺而得到奖励。通过努力放松她的影子意图对她的控制，她能够将更多的注意力带回自己的部门并更好地支持创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;探索你的内群体/外群体。&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;评估您对周围人的想法和假设。谁能对你诚实，甚至不同意你的观点？你看重谁的意见？为什么？你和谁一起奋斗？你的团队内成员与团队外成员之间存在哪些共同点？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;确定自己​​的模式是打造一个每个人都参与并充分贡献的团队的关键第一步。丹是一家中型公司的首席执行官，他希望以不同的方式思考因退休而发生的几次领导层变动。他希望引进新的高管，并与其余成员建立一支有凝聚力的团队。在对自己的内部和外部团队进行审计时，他发现执行团队的两名领导者在他的外部团队中。两者都是在大流行期间开始的，丹没有与他们进行一对一的交流，他通常会投资于团队中的新高管。 Dan 决定开始更有意识地与他们建立联系，每月安排一次单独的午餐，每周与他们每人进行一次 15 分钟的一对一谈话。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有很多策略可以帮助领导者与他们的外群体建立联系，但要记住的最重要的一点是，最有权力的人必须发起联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;无声的报复形式非常常见，并且在工作场所可能会传染。我们所服务的那些接受这种形式的报复作为标准做法的组织很难雇用和留住优秀人才。各种形式的报复不仅会伤害当前的团队成员，而且容忍报复的文化也会损害使命和组织向客户和利益相关者提供服务的能力。组织是由他们庆祝什么和他们容忍什么来定义的。参与或容忍报复行为的领导者可能会给个人和组织造成持久的伤痕。我们服务的人类应该得到更好的待遇。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* 为了保护隐私，名称已全部更改。&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div >;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Removing the Roadblocks That First-Generation Americans Face at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_03_1369183308.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;许多第一代美国人在试图在西方工作场所取得成功时面临文化跷跷板效应。例如，亚裔美国人和太平洋岛民 (AAPI) 社区的成员可能会发现自我推销具有挑战性，因为这违背了他们的价值观。他们从很小的时候就被教导要谦虚，要保持低调，永远不要纠正权威人物，以示尊重。他们希望他们的努力能够不言而喻。但自我推销和表达意见已成为在西方工作场所蓬勃发展所需的关键要素，这显然对某些人有利，对另一些人不利。此外，第一代美国人和其他边缘化社区承受着许多代际、社会和工作场所的创伤，这些创伤造成了心理健康差异，这可能导致他们担心在工作环境中为自己辩护。虽然领导者无法控制员工如何应对社会和代际创伤，但他们有责任营造一种环境，让所有员工都能放心地举手寻求支持。为了成功实现这一目标，组织应密切关注当前员工行为是否确实促进了包容性，或者是否需要修改流程和规范以为所有员工提供公平的环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first- Generation-americans-face-at-at-work?language=es&quot; >;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first- Generation-americans-face-at-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;大约四十年前，当我的家人从印度移民到美国时，他们并没有意识到新世界会带来什么。他们充满希望，这次搬迁将提供以前无法获得的剩余机会。带着这种希望，人们对新社区的接受程度产生了合理的保留，因此他们采用了许多移民家庭采用的策略：同化和繁荣。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;目标不是压制我们的身份。相比之下，则是以一种没有负担的方式与外国人接触新环境。我的父母并没有要求升职，而是耐心地等待，直到他们的辛勤工作最终得到回报——比他们的美国同龄人晚了好几年。他们没有在日常职责中寻求支持，而是默默承担额外的责任来证明自己的价值。我的父母都以他们的利他主义、不朽的承诺和坚定不移的奉献精神作为荣誉徽章——幸福地把这些价值观传递给我，希望我能在我的职业生涯中复制他们的职业道德。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我进入了拥有我父母的高尚道德、无畏精神和正直的员工队伍将带领我完成未来的努力。不幸的是，历史以意想不到的方式重演。我因我的辛勤工作而被剥削。我的界限不断被高层领导侵犯。当我向团队寻求支持时，我感到很震惊，因为我确信这将是软弱的表现，并会损害我的职业形象，最终阻碍成长机会。它造就了我所鄙视的一个版本：缺乏安全感、犹豫不决、极其温顺。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;作为第一代美国人工作&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我的成长岁月是我一直以为我的家庭环境很独特，但事实并非如此。许多第一代美国人在很小的时候就面临着类似的挑战，因为他们要适应两种文化的社会期望，从而导致了一种独特的现象，称为“&lt;a href=&quot;https://srcd.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/” abs/10.1111/cdep.12071&quot;>;移民悖论&lt;/a>;“。由于美国的种族和民族差异，第一代美国人的发展成果、教育成就甚至心理健康挑战不断减少——这对我们的父母提出了挑战甚至新移民也不会面临，因为他们通常在青春期后移民。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了加剧这种体验，第一代美国人还面临&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2022/ 10/26/health/mental-health-children-of-immigrants-wellness/index.html&quot;>;移民内疚&lt;/a>;，因为他们试图拼命地坚持他们继承的传统，同时在他们的家庭无法提供的文化中和谐相处有关的任何指导。适应西方文化，同时感到“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-othering-5084425&quot;>;其他&lt;/a>;”可能会导致无法塑造一个完全落入的身份在两种文化、传统和经验中。虽然我们的家人可能本意是为我们提供他们的智慧和成功的价值观，但它并没有很好地转化为为那些从未与我们分享身份的人建立的工作场所结构。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是许多第一代美国人在试图在工作场所取得成功时面临着文化跷跷板效应。亚裔美国人和太平洋岛民 (AAPI) 社区（以及许多类似文化）发现了它 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-we-need -谈论亚裔美国人心理健康？cid=other-eml-dre-mip-mck&amp;hlkid=a774e1a8976d4a078406df70a8406fd5&amp;hctky=12012649&amp;amp;hdpid=9ae1a3af-4f90-48c7-84bd-0389 613c0228&quot;>;挑战自我推销&lt;/a>;，因为这违背了我们的价值观。我们被教导要谦虚并保持低调。我们从小就被教导永远不要纠正权威人物，以示尊重。与我父母的职业生涯类似，许多 AAPI 社区成员希望他们的辛勤工作能够不言而喻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，为什么工作场所和领导者在寻求创造公平和包容性的工作时需要考虑这一点很重要环境？ &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/savvy-self-promotion&quot;>;自我推销&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/glennllopis/2012/03/19/员工必须直言不讳的六大原因已成为在西方工作场所蓬勃发展所需的关键要素，但这显然对某些人有利，对另一些人不利。此外，第一代美国人和其他边缘化社区承受着许多代际、社会和工作场所的创伤，这些创伤造成了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/culture-competency/education/mental-health-facts# :~:text=Racial%2Fethnic%2C%20gender%2C%20and,of%20awareness%20about%20mental%20health&quot;>;心理健康差异&lt;/a>;，这可能会导致人们担心在工作环境中为自己辩护。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，如果雇主采取致力于优先考虑所有身份和背景的包容性的方法，那么我们就可以在扭曲的成功定义方面取得进展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;领导者如何能够改变叙述并帮助修复有缺陷的系统&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导者无法控制员工如何应对社会和代际创伤。然而，他们有责任营造一种环境，让所有员工都能放心地举手寻求支持。为了成功实现这一目标，组织应密切关注当前员工行为是否确实促进了包容性，或者是否需要修改流程和规范以为所有员工提供公平的环境。根据我与全球组织合作的经验，事实证明，在制定解决方案之前进行关键的暂停是改善包容性的关键因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;评估您的包容性努力&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了了解哪些做法支持包容性，哪些做法不支持包容性，需要进行彻底的评估。在以前的领导角色中，我成功地进行了这项评估，最终通过三个具体维度评估整个组织和管理实践的包容性：作为一个团队共同创造成功，培育有目的的社区，以及评估反馈机制的有效性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这三个维度是进一步了解组织的背景、文化和创建实质性包容性意​​图的综合方法。它还为领导者深入研究现行流程奠定了基础，以确定当前的公司氛围是否整合了第一代员工带来的差异，并允许他们参与决策过程以实现战略目标。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;彻底检查每个维度后，采取行动并优先考虑需要立即关注的特定领域是关键。它将在组织层面培育持续学习和改进的文化，同时创造新的实践，让第一代员工有安全的成长空间。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;作为一个团队共同创造成功&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们从这个维度开始，因为我们传统的工作场所实践通过强调特定的个人行为来定义成功，而不是创造有利于整个员工群体的实践。这种&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/how-to-infuse-liberatory-practices-into-work-practices&quot;>;分而治之&lt;/a>;方法特别阻止第一代员工确定他们的成功是什么样子，进一步说明他们独特的见解不如主导群体重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为领导者，您可以通过首先评估您为自己的团队提供的协作和包容性水平来纠正这些做法。开始修复实践并邀请所有团队成员定义他们的成功是什么样的。通过这样做，您可以让第一代员工放弃以前对完美员工的看法，并创建一种团结的文化，让他们更有可能表达自己的意见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，锻造参与规则、了解与他人的首选沟通方式以及最终确定领导层在项目开始时应提供的支持，从而为每个第一代员工保持界限。最终，如果你不断征求意见，并在商定的时间表上重新讨论有关成功定义的对话，那么与提出担忧相关的耻辱就会慢慢消失。此外，维持这些工作关系并相互承诺满足彼此的需求将有助于实现公平的决策过程并提高所有团队成员的士气。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;培养有目标的社区&lt;/strong>;&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;可以说，这可能是包容性评估中最重要的组成部分，因为它为第一代员工提供了一个避风港，让他们讨论如何应对仅适用于他们的独特工作场所压力源。例如，员工资源小组 (ERG) 对于试图加强包容性努力的组织来说非常受欢迎。然而，他们经常&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/ effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at -work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;达不到要求&lt;/a>;，因为他们缺乏责任感或特定使命。根据我的经验，我看到 ERG 仅仅被用作下班后的社交聚会——这很重要，但并没有在工作场所培养第一代员工应有的纠正做法。为了使这些社区更加有效，我建议寻找一位已经在实践&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/why-inclusive-leaders-are-good-for-organizations-and-how-to-become -one&quot;>;包容性领导力&lt;/a>;以同理心和战略来领导 ERG。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在之前的职位中，我担任业务发起人，并支持推出类似的 ERG，为期六个月行动计划。前两个月只是作为一个社区进行联系——减压并谈论我们的社区如何以特定方式被边缘化。第三个月和第四个月用于过渡到战略。我们研究了以下问题：&lt;em>;我们如何才能赋予自己寻求支持的能力？我们需要领导层采取哪些具体行动，让我们不断感受到自己被赋予了权力，从而为组织带来价值？这些对话通常很困难，有时甚至让人精神疲惫，因为它要求我们中的许多人重新审视我们的移民负罪感在工作场所是如何表现出来的。这就是为什么任何 ERG 的业务发起人都应该具备良好的装备和技能来促进这些对话。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，第五个月和第六个月致力于在具体工作实践中向高级领导层建立一个案例，需要进行修改，以便让我们在工作场所感到受到重视、被包容和受到保护。然后根据我们前几个月的圆桌讨论得出的连贯沟通计划制定了一项具体提案。当我们共同制定该计划时，ERG 的每位成员都被邀请提供反馈，并对我们想要解决的首要问题进行投票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在 ERG 社区的集体支持下，我们能够建立跨客户项目的新规范，以解决能力限制，加强与团队的交叉合作，并确定各级问责措施。对于许多 ERG 成员来说，这种成功伴随着对自己职业生涯的独特主人翁意识，而这在以前似乎是陌生的。社区里的人们习惯于保持沉默，回想起我们许多人在面对职场挑战时所承受的代际创伤。然而，这一成功带来了一线希望，即自我推销实际上可以带来切实的成果，从根本上改变企业的运营方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;评估反馈机制的有效性&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h3>; &lt;p>;虽然多年来通过敬业度调查进行员工反馈作为增强包容性的明确措施已变得流行，但许多第一代员工不愿提供他们的见解。由于我们的身份复杂，感觉被排斥，并且缺乏与我们认同的榜样，我们感到有必要首先评估工作环境，以确定大声疾呼会受到赞扬还是惩罚——无论反馈对于改变工作条件是否是必要的。为了解决这个问题，领导者应该积极分析他们正在提倡的文化类型，以便准确了解工作环境。如果没有心理安全这一核心组成部分，员工敬业度调查将仍然是对组织实际情况的错误幻想。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，如果您的目标是通过敬业度调查寻求建议来减少员工倦怠，请评估该类型在寻求反馈之前您所庆祝的行为。如果您要扩大员工全天候工作的能力，允许其他人接受每一个客户需求，或者创建&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90662451/its-very-time-sensitive-why-a-快节奏的工作环境伤害了所有员工&quot;>;错误的紧迫感&lt;/a>;，你没有营造一个包容的环境，让其他人举手寻求支持。事实上，你是在告诉你的员工，这是每个人都必须遵守的黄金法则。第一代员工在解决这些负面工作场所压力源时提供反馈会感到不安全，因为组织无意中支持了这种类型的倦怠行为。无论您的调查意图多么善意，有害的工作环境都会使任何重大变革的努力付之东流，并消除第一代员工的任何信誉。然而，如果最终目标是创造可持续和包容性的工作环境，请尽可能定期指出不良行为，让员工知道这些行为不是对员工的期望。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦仔细检查了工作场所实践，通过敬业度调查、团队论坛甚至一对一会议寻求个人反馈可以进一步证明可以增强第一代员工的能力。这种持续的行动方针实现了一致性的积极循环，鼓励自我倡导，而不是期望第一代员工在没有适当基础的情况下克服他们的保留意见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，当您寻求反馈时，请仔细分析第一代员工的观点。您可能并不总是同意他们的反馈，甚至并不完全理解他们的观点。然而，如果您的最终目标是包容性，那么您仍然有责任尽最大努力实施变革。一旦这个过程开始，一个重要的考虑因素就是不要让反馈闲置。最终，如果反馈被忽视，可能会在您和第一代员工之间造成不信任的环境。请记住，这个特定的群体在提供反馈时会做很多事情来克服他们自己内在的耻辱，希望工作文化能够得到转变。沟通您将如何处理反馈并保持敏捷。您可能需要花一些时间解读第一代员工的反馈，或者进行另一份后续调查问卷，以澄清有关他们工作条件的要点。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align ：中心；&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As organizations continue to correct a flawed system by building inclusion for all communities, it is imperative to support those who may not be able to advocate for themselves. First-generation employees sit at a unique juncture in applying determination and diligence in a new era of work, continuously shifting between cultures. Organizations need to create an environment where we can shed our layers and authentically thrive in the hopes of creating a more equitable world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Benefits of Being Bored at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_XLRivrl9mNI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&amp;#8217;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life. Based on the body of research exploring this emotion, the authors highlight some of boredom&amp;#8217;s benefits and detriments and offer insights into how you might harness the best of boredom.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Bored at work?我们都去过那里。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/1745691612456044&quot;>;Boredom&lt;/a>; is that experience of wanting to be occupied in a satisfying activity, yet somehow being unable to do so. And being busy is no antidote: You may be both very busy — and very bored — simultaneously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Early in life we learn that boredom is no fun, and as we age we might begin to see it as a waste of time, or a missed opportunity to do something more productive (or at least more interesting). At best, boredom has been considered an unpleasant to &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691612456044?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;aversive &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/152c9TgGipX6UOMCIbfTdrGy_vN6kopCv/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;experience&lt;/a>;, and at worst, a state that evokes a deep sense of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springer.com/journal/13164&quot;>;meaninglessness&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XXpz4j8kTTtUdXJdlak3e3_kuIJLNskz/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;.&lt;/a>; In addition, when feeling the discomfort of boredom, time &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gNy8bUlah9IHjM1CZZjkS6EnRV7AxXzX/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;tends to pass slowly&lt;/a>;, which can make work days seem endless.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Considering this, it&#39;s no surprise that boredom often triggers an intense desire to escape the situation (or job!) that evokes it. In today&#39;s ultra-connected world, this escape is just one tap away. At your fingertips, you find a world of data, breaking news, shows and stories, messages from friends and family, or gifs, memes, and video clips that help you avoid feeling bored — at least at the surface level. Research shows that use of smartphones not only distracts the mind, it offers an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/IJPHM-08-2016-0044/full/html&quot;>;addictive hit&lt;/a>; of dopamine, which &lt;em>;temporarily&lt;/em>; replaces the discomfort of boredom with pleasure. However, this&amp;nbsp;feeling is short lived, as this mindless scrolling results in long-term decreases in overall mental health and quality of life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next time you&#39;re feeling that creeping sense of boredom at work, pause before you pick up your phone. Boredom can have important benefits, and you&#39;ll miss them if you&#39;re not tuned in to what you&#39;re feeling and why.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Pros and Cons of Workplace Boredom&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Boredom has a negative reputation for a reason. At work, it&#39;s often viewed as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;counterproductive state&lt;/a>; that ignites discomfort, desperation for a new role, or perhaps simply a desire for the day to end. Boredom at work has been linked to &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2160&quot;>;risky decision-making&lt;/a>;, costly mistakes, and accidents triggered by inattention or lack of focus — and that&#39;s not to mention the fatigue that being bored can generate. Boredom can also incite other types of problematic behavior, such as “cyberloafing” (that is, non-work-related browsing) and childish emotional responses. Prolonged exposure to monotonous activities can even cause &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-pathology-of-boredom/&quot;>;hallucinations&lt;/a>;. In addition, when it comes to well-being, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000187912200118X&quot;>;one recent study found&lt;/a>; a linkage between boredom at work and burnout, as well as decreases in job satisfaction and increased desire to quit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the flip side, recent research shows that boredom — when handled constructively — has big “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;bright sides&lt;/a>;.” Moments of boredom can offer a pause, or a short respite for your brain and body in a world designed to distract, overwhelm, and overstimulate. A sense of boredom can create the space to daydream, which can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2014.901073&quot;>;hatch creativity&lt;/a>;, new ideas, and innovation. Prolonged boredom can prompt you to reflect and ask yourself, “Am I on the right path? Am I doing the right thing?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Your Boredom for the Better&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re not advocating that you seek out jobs where you&#39;ll spend large parts of the day feeling bored. However, getting better at working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; your boredom — and harnessing it for the good — can help you capture its bright sides. Here&#39;s how:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Notice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you feel that discomfort of boredom setting in, avoid acting on it immediately. The fact that you&#39;ve noticed you&#39;re bored means that you&#39;ve managed to (briefly) resist the urge to instantly engage in mindless scrolling. Noticing and naming your boredom in order to intentionally direct it opens up the opportunity to develop your resilience and the potential to use boredom for positive ends. Most importantly, in a bout of boredom, don&#39;t make snap decisions (like to quit your job) as a way to escape the discomfort.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Decipher.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Not all experiences of boredom are the same — &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11031-013-9385-y&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that various “types” of boredom manifest differently in the body and mind, giving rise to different behaviors. Decoding which types you&#39;re feeling early on can help you make a game plan to deal with boredom, or prevent it from escalating or clouding your decision making.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ask yourself what your boredom is telling you. Could it be that you simply need a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research&quot;>;micro-break&lt;/a>; because you&#39;ve worked too long without pausing and you&#39;re tiring? Or maybe your tasks are becoming monotonous and you&#39;re losing motivation and energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider what you&#39;re bored with specifically: Is it your role, the content or form of the work, or your prospects for the future in your job that bore you? Can you decipher a pattern with a typical type of work that ignites this uncomfortable feeling? This can be an opportunity to consider your goals and values and whether you feel you&#39;re moving forward or feel “stuck.” Here are five research-based types of boredom to consider as you work to decipher yours:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Indifferent boredom.&lt;/strong>; This is one of the more positive types of boredom. It can feel like relaxation or a sense of cheerful fatigue and reflects a general indifference to (and withdrawal from) the external world. This type of boredom can help boost rest and recovery, particularly during busy days.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Calibrating boredom.&lt;/strong>; This one&#39;s slightly more unpleasant and is one of the most common types. It occurs when you&#39;re not fully engaged in a task or activity and your mind starts to drift. It can show up as wandering thoughts or not knowing what to do to change the situation, yet wanting to get out of it somehow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Searching boredom.&lt;/strong>; This type reflects a restlessness and active search for alternative actions and distractions to ease the negative experience (eg, through other activities, leisure pursuits, interests, and hobbies). While unpleasant, this type of boredom ignites activity and the pursuit of change and often has positive outcomes, such as creativity, innovation, and personal growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Reactive boredom.&lt;/strong>; Reactive boredom arises in situations where a person is required to do a repetitive or tedious task (such as being stuck in a long and ineffective meeting with no chance of escape). It&#39;s an action-oriented and deeply unpleasant type of boredom, which causes restlessness and frustration that might be expressed in a more angry or aggressive fashion toward others or toward the boring experience. Those experiencing it may persistently fantasize about other options and feel anxious to make a change or escape quickly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Apathetic boredom.&lt;/strong>; This can relate to feelings of disinterest, lack of motivation, and emotional detachment toward activities or events one would normally find stimulating or enjoyable. Apathetic boredom isn&#39;t necessarily accompanied by feelings of frustration or restlessness but rather a sense of disengagement and indifference. It can occur as a result of chronic stress, depression, or other mental health issues and can lead to feelings of hopelessness and helplessness. People experiencing apathetic boredom may feel like they&#39;re going through the motions of life without any real purpose or enjoyment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Decide what to do.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Based on the type of boredom and what it&#39;s telling you about yourself or your situation, decide what to do about it. Maybe your boredom is simply allowing you to relax and unwind after a period of intensity at work. Or perhaps it&#39;s telling you something about your role itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All roles have certain elements that are monotonous, frustrating, or simply boring, and sometimes these tasks must be done to get to the “good stuff.” If you find yourself persistently bored, try to harness the boredom to catalyze change, perhaps by engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>; to bring out the elements of your role that you really enjoy. This could involve, for example, making changes to the type, variety, complexity, or significance of your tasks. You might intentionally evade boredom by seeking out, envisioning, and championing new ideas at work, which can also boost your leadership abilities and potential. Reflecting and engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23163710/&quot;>;nostalgia&lt;/a>; can also counteract the sense of meaninglessness you might feel when bored.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Cultivate mindful boredom.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Moments of boredom can be opportunities to help you unwind from a fast-paced and hyper-connected world and allow you the opportunity to simply be in the present moment. Use moments of boredom for positive intentions rather than mindless distraction, for example, by taking a moment to breathe, doing another activity you find simulating, or simply mindfully allowing the discomfort to pass. As boredom can spark &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20200522-how-boredom-can-spark-creativity&quot;>;creativity&lt;/a>;, you could even include space for it as unstructured time in your work routine, for example, before you&#39;re required to innovate, come up with new ideas, and be at your best.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&#39;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Ways to Earn the Respect of a More Powerful Colleague]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_03_144694173.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;retales botijero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When you are stuck in an unequal power dynamic, it helps to remember that not only is the placement of power temporary, but you can equalize it. In this article, the author outlines four strategies you can use to creatively pivot in the moment and frame the connection differently, so that you are building the respect you deserve and positively shifting the perception of your power.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Whether we want to acknowledge it or not, in many colleague relationships there is a power differential, often based on each party&#39;s status in the organization and who has more control over what the other needs at a given time. For instance, the engineering leader whose team ultimately determines a product line&#39;s time-to-market may hold more power over the sales leader trying to deliver for impatient customers, and the leader of a mature and “unexciting” business unit may find their needs consistently deprioritized by the IT department, which is rushing to support a fast-growing division, instead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s a deeply frustrating dynamic for those in the “inferior” position — but to develop a mutually respectful relationship with colleagues (and perhaps even claim more relative power), it&#39;s vital to take steps toward rebalancing the equation. With a willingness to assert yourself in creative ways, you develop more agency for yourself, particularly at times when feeling dismissed or dependent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.columbia.edu/~da358/publications/ames_pushing_up_to_a_point.pdf&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; there is a “Goldilocks” effect when it comes to assertiveness in interpersonal relationships, where you&#39;re able to hit a sweet spot between being too assertive and not enough. When done properly, &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/why-we-should-be-disagreeing-more-at-work&quot;>;healthy dissent&lt;/a>; can lead to deeper trust and mutual respect. Based on my work as an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.partnerexec.com/&quot;>;executive coach&lt;/a>; for senior leaders at global companies, here are four strategies you can deploy in your relationships to distribute power more evenly.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Choose to decline certain requests. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It may feel incredibly challenging to decline a more powerful colleague&#39;s request. But in any interaction, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Framing_effect_(psychology)&quot;>;framing effect&lt;/a>; takes place where each party is sizing up who has more power and influence. Since power is comprised of many factors and is situational, even if you find yourself typically powerless relative to a colleague, there do emerge situations where they need something from you just as much as you need them. Even if you&#39;ve always acceded in the past, in occasional moments, it&#39;s important to capitalize on the opportunity to politely refuse the more powerful person&#39;s demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/meet-catch-and-keep/201602/4-truths-about-power-in-relationships-including-yours&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; on relationships defined power as not only having a greater ability to influence the other, but also having the stronger &lt;em>;resistance to the other&#39;s influence&lt;/em>;. So, the next time you sense your colleague is overly exerting their power over you (for instance, making another last-minute request even though they have been inaccessible for yours), it may be a good idea to not immediately drop what you&#39;re doing and jump to the rescue.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I once coached a leader whose peer often dumped work on her but managed to stay above the fray when others needed her help. This colleague would frequently cite her interactions with their shared boss as a way of justifying her power and drop their name while making requests that purely served her.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are in a similar position as my client, respond to your colleague by saying something like, “I wanted to let you know I got your request. I&#39;m happy to help but have other commitments I must address at the moment. In the meantime, feel free to send me more information in case I can suggest another solution.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ideally, you want to send a message that you expect them to invest their limited time as well into the relationship. If you are true to the minimum promises you&#39;ve made, then you can confidently hold your ground as an equal partner. This not only encourages them to respect you but forces them to make sacrifices as needed for the relationship as much as you do.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Connect them to other people in power who value you.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Another way to shift the power in the relationship is by subtly reminding them of your social value by connecting them to other people they respect, with whom you&#39;ve cultivated a relationship. This does three valuable things: first, it shows them (through the principle of social proof) that you must have something to offer if people they admire see value in you; second, it may tip the scales in your relationship dynamic because you possess access they&#39;d like to enjoy; and third, it sends a signal that you already have high-profile access, so are not desperate to chase their approval.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I worked with a leader who struggled to be seen as a “strategic” executive and was continuously downplayed for higher level roles by HR when succession planning discussions took place. But in truth, he was quite innovative and eager to contribute to more forward-looking aspects of the business; it was because he was so good at operational execution that HR and his boss didn&#39;t want to rock the boat through a promotion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To disrupt this power dynamic, which was limiting his advancement, my client started to develop relationships with other senior leaders and socialized ideas that could help their business needs. And then he started making introductions between his new contacts and some of the colleagues in HR and his business who held influence over his career. By showing his access to other powerful leaders and sharing it as well through connecting others, his brand began to rise toward the perception of an enterprise-level leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Help them surface their blind spots as a way of supporting them.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Even the most powerful people can&#39;t see themselves exactly the way other people perceive them. In other words, they have blind spots just like the rest of us. And when you can help them gently recognize an aspect of their thinking or behavior that is getting in the way of their goals, they can begin to view you as a highly trusted partner, rather than someone below their level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of my clients was an SVP at a technology company who was privy to the chatter across the organization about the CEO&#39;s lack of decisiveness and how it was creating confusion for employees and teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While she agreed with the general sentiment, she was happy with how the CEO treated her. While he had more power than her, she generally accepted the idea of working under his leadership and meeting his expectations as best as she could. After all, she thought, why risk her relationship with the CEO and give him tough feedback that could backfire on her for being the messenger?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But she also recognized that to become a trusted partner to him, she would need to truly be in his corner, through good and bad, and that required being honest with him for his benefit. So, she decided in her next one-on-one to share her observations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The SVP said, “I know how important it is to you to do the right thing for the business and our people. And sometimes our strengths can be over-leveraged to the point of becoming a weakness. I think because you care so much about listening to all sides of an issue, it&#39;s starting to delay making decisions. And I wanted to offer this possibility because you may be too close to this style to see how it&#39;s impacting others.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In taking the risk of putting a mirror up to the CEO, the SVP earned a high measure of respect and gratitude from him. Their relationship became one of trusted advisor and not just direct report.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you meet with people in power and simply tell them everything they&#39;ve heard before or the same things as others in your position, you will be forgotten and relegated to the status quo. But by stepping out of your comfort zone to — kindly, but assertively — point out something that the powerful person had not noticed, you not only become memorable but start to gain influence and respect with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Make them work to earn your attention.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gaining the respect of colleagues more powerful than you is an interesting paradox: by putting them in a position to work for your approval, you earn more of their respect. So, a fourth strategy is to create conditions where they must “sell” their value to you. Basically, work less at earning their respect and put the burden on them to explain why they should be worth your attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Over the years, I&#39;ve coached leaders at companies that had undergone a merger or reorganization that required many employees and leaders to “reapply” for a job, either within their division or in a new part of the company. This experience can be unsettling, not just because they are back to being a candidate competing against others for a job, but because unlike applying to a new company from the outside, their reputations precede them and provide more subjective input that will influence interviewers when evaluating them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The natural mistake many people make in these situations is to overprepare for the questions they think they will be asked and try their best to hedge their answers to please the hiring colleague. This seems like the path of least resistance but in fact positions them as forgettable and unremarkable in the eyes of the other party.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, find ways to be generous with your answers but unafraid to also ask questions that put them a bit on their heels. When your colleague asks you that oft-repeated question, “Why should we hire you for this job?” your first instinct may be to prove your value to their satisfaction, even though you and they know that most everyone is applying for jobs because of the reorganization, not because they wanted to try something new.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, take a beat and say something like, “Actually, I&#39;m not sure you should hire me just yet. I&#39;d like to explore if there&#39;s a mutual fit between my experience and your vision of where this team is going. Anything you could share about your management style would be helpful as I&#39;m exploring my next steps.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Expecting people in power to “earn” your interest rather than take it for granted can bring positive results. Not only can it set you apart from the competition, but it can ensure you are working with colleagues who respect you rather than keep you under their power and whims.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you are stuck in an unequal power dynamic, it helps to remember that not only is the placement of power temporary, but you can equalize it. By adopting these strategies, you can creatively pivot in the moment and frame the connection differently, so that you are building the respect you deserve.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Explain a Gap in Your Resume]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_1105032.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Audshule/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Since the pandemic, most employers have been more understanding and less discriminating regarding resume gaps &amp;#8212; but you have to be ready to explain the gaps clearly, confidently, and without stumbling. Owning your career trajectory means connecting all the dots for the recruiter and hiring manager. Shaping the narrative around any gaps yourself will help make them a non-issue. The author discusses five common reasons for work-history gaps &amp;#8212; and how to own the gap during the interview process.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;At least once in every interview process you&#39;ll be asked some version of, “Can you walk me through your resume?” In addition to your skills and experience, you need to be able to explain your transitions between jobs, including gaps. This is critical: When you ignore gaps between jobs when discussing your resume, you lose the opportunity to control the narrative about your job transitions or time away from the commercial workforce.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Based on my research of employment gaps for my book, &lt;em>;Wanted → A New Career: The Definitive Playbook for Transitioning to a New Career or Finding Your Dream Job&lt;/em>;, here are five common reasons for work-history gaps — and how to own the gap during the interview process:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Stay-at-home parenting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you took time off from the commercial workforce &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/helping-stay-at-home-parents-reenter-the-workforce&quot;>;to raise children&lt;/a>;, explain how you used that time to gain skills, knowledge, or experience that&#39;s relevant to the job. For example, did you volunteer at your kids&#39; school? Organize events or fundraising efforts? Were you the parent who arranged travel for sports team activities? All of those things can be translated to the job you&#39;re applying for. For example, say you&#39;re looking to continue your career in global fundraising. You could tell the interviewer, “I took time off to care for our children but I was able to keep my skills fresh while volunteering for the kids&#39; sports league, developing fundraising goals and helping the team successfully achieve fundraising quotas to provide financial assistance for those who needed it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Bereavement or caring for a sick family member&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you took time away to care for a parent or family member, own the choice you made to spend that important time with them. Take a look at that experience through the lens of the job. For example, if you&#39;re trying to move back into a customer service role, you could focus on your role as a liaison with your family member&#39;s health care providers:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I took time off to care for my father. During that time I was able to leverage my effective communication skills with multiple health care providers, as well as my organization skills in coordinating meetings with his financial planner, brokers, and legal representation, which gave him peace of mind. I would like to use those same problem-solving skills plus my ability to remain calm under pressure in this job.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re applying for a finance job, you could focus on your role as executor:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I took time off to spend with my mother before she passed away. I was named executor because I am highly responsible, organized, and have financial acumen. I was able to leverage my finance skills in reconciling her estate as well as soft skills, such as using effective communication with multiple creditors, including utilities, credit card companies, medical facilities, and banking institutions. My skills enabled me to quickly and efficiently close out the estate, and now I&#39;m looking to bring my skills to a new challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h2>;Traveling the world&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When moving back into a corporate work setting after taking time off to explore, focus on how you used that time to gain new perspectives. For example, if you&#39;re interviewing with a multinational company, you could discuss the nuances of interacting with people from different cultures and how experiencing life in other countries gave you a perspective many people don&#39;t have in the workplace. If you&#39;re pursuing an operational role, you could focus on your efficiency in travel planning, budgeting as it relates to a P&amp;amp;L, and how you used critical thinking to determine where to travel to next. If you spent time learning a second, third, or fourth language, explain how your ability to be conversational or fluent will make you a higher-performing candidate than those who aren&#39;t multilingual.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Going back to school&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Perhaps you went back to school to obtain an MBA or doctorate. If you went to school full time, explain how specific projects you worked on are directly relevant to the job and how they, along with any past work experience, will allow you to bring unique value to the position. Perhaps you achieved an MBA and want to work in business operations. Did you work on projects for real companies? Include them on your resume to so you can discuss them during an interview.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you developed your skills &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/5-ways-to-acquire-new-skills-without-going-back-to-school&quot;>;without going back to school&lt;/a>; for a traditional degree — for example, by taking a course or getting a certification — describe how those skills apply to the prospective job and set you apart from other candidates. If you read specific books to gain a new perspective on your field or enhance your leadership capabilities, talk about how you would apply the principles you learned at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Terminated employment&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you were &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/what-to-do-after-being-laid-off&quot;>;impacted by a mass layoff&lt;/a>; that wasn&#39;t performance related, explain to the interviewer that the business strategy changed and your department or team were let go in the latest wave of layoffs. You can even position the unfortunate situation positively: “But it has been a blessing because I was considering looking for a new challenge.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you were terminated for performance, clearly your employer didn&#39;t think you were successful in your job, but perhaps you have a different perspective or didn&#39;t feel the role was what you expected. In this case, you can explain that the job was different than you believed it to be and didn&#39;t leverage your skills and capabilities in the most effective way. Always explain what you learned from the experience and how you&#39;re actively working to make sure your next move is closer to your expectations. For example:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I knew soon after I started that the job wasn&#39;t as described, but since I committed to the company, I wanted to give it my best effort. In the end, my skills of A, B, and C weren&#39;t being utilized effectively to bring value to the business. So we amicably separated, which is allowing me to take the time to find the right job where I can bring the most value based on business need.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;If you were in a toxic environment or decided to quit for any other reason, don&#39;t bring that negativity into job interviews. Find a positive perspective on why you departed — for example, “I needed focused time to find a job that&#39;s more in line with my values, and I couldn&#39;t find the time to do it while working 60 hours a week.” Most importantly, don&#39;t ever badmouth anyone, because that behavior makes you look like someone who blames others without taking accountability — and who could do the same at the new company. This is the time to take the high road.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Since the pandemic, most employers have been more understanding and less discriminating regarding resume gaps — but you have to be ready to explain the gaps clearly, confidently, and without stumbling. Owning your career trajectory means connecting all the dots for the recruiter and hiring manager. Shaping the narrative around any gaps yourself will help make them a non-issue.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[13 Principles for Using AI Responsibly]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_200245321-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Boris SV/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The competitive nature of AI development poses a dilemma for organizations, as prioritizing speed may lead to neglecting ethical guidelines, bias detection, and safety measures. Known and emerging concerns associated with AI in the workplace include the spread of misinformation, copyright and intellectual property concerns, cybersecurity, data privacy, as well as navigating rapid and ambiguous regulations. To mitigate these risks, we propose thirteen principles for responsible AI at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Love it or loath it, the rapid expansion of AI will not slow down anytime soon. But AI blunders &lt;a href=&quot;https://cmr.berkeley.edu/2022/01/the-reputational-risks-of-ai/&quot;>;can quickly damage a brand&#39;s reputation&lt;/a>; — just ask Microsoft&#39;s first chatbot, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;Tay&lt;/a>;. In the tech race, all leaders fear being left behind if they slow down while others don&#39;t. It&#39;s a high-stakes situation where cooperation seems risky, and defection tempting. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://heritage.umich.edu/stories/the-prisoners-dilemma/&quot;>;“prisoner&#39;s dilemma”&lt;/a>; (as it&#39;s called in game theory) poses risks to responsible AI practices. Leaders, prioritizing speed to market, are driving the current AI arms race in which major corporate players are rushing products and potentially &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies-cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;short-changing critical considerations&lt;/a>; like ethical guidelines, bias detection, and safety measures. For instance, major tech corporations are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies-cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;laying off their AI ethics teams&lt;/a>; precisely at a time when responsible actions are needed most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s also important to recognize that the AI arms race extends beyond the developers of large language models (LLMs) such as OpenAI, Google, and Meta. It encompasses many companies utilizing LLMs to support their own custom applications. In the world of professional services, for example, PwC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/pwcs-4000-legal-staffers-get-ai-assistant-law-chatbots-gain-steam-2023-03-15/&quot;>;announced&lt;/a>; it is deploying AI chatbots for 4,000 of their lawyers, distributed across 100 countries. These AI-powered assistants will “help lawyers with contract analysis, regulatory compliance work, due diligence, and other legal advisory and consulting services.” PwC&#39;s management is also considering expanding these AI chatbots into their tax practice. In total, the consulting giant plans to pour $1 billion into “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bcg.com/x/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai&quot;>;generative AI&lt;/a>;” — a powerful new tool capable of delivering game-changing boosts to performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a similar vein, KPMG launched its own AI-powered assistant, dubbed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afr.com/companies/professional-services/custom-chatgpt-tool-to-help-kpmg-s-consultants-win-new-work-20230321-p5cu3m&quot;>;KymChat&lt;/a>;, which will help employees rapidly find internal experts across the entire organization, wrap them around incoming opportunities, and automatically generate proposals based on the match between project requirements and available talent. Their &lt;a href=&quot;https://kpmg.com/au/en/home/media/press-releases/2023/03/kpmg-unveils-cutting-edge-private-chatgpt-software-march-2023.html&quot;>;AI assistant&lt;/a>; “will better enable cross-team collaboration and help those new to the firm with a more seamless and efficient people-navigation experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slack is also incorporating generative AI into the development of &lt;a href=&quot;https://slack.com/blog/news/introducing-slack-gpt&quot;>;Slack GPT&lt;/a>;, an AI assistant designed to help employees work smarter not harder. The platform incorporates a range of AI capabilities, such as conversation summaries and writing assistance, to enhance user productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These examples are just the tip of the iceberg. Soon hundreds of millions of Microsoft 365 users will have access to &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/&quot;>;Business Chat&lt;/a>;, an agent that joins the user in their work, striving to make sense of their Microsoft 365 data. Employees can prompt the assistant to do everything from developing status report summaries based on meeting transcripts and email communication to identifying flaws in strategy and coming up with solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This rapid deployment of AI agents is why &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/04/20/ibm-ceo-work-ai-artificial-intelligence-careers-tech-arvind-krishna/&quot;>;Arvind Krishna&lt;/a>;, CEO of IBM, recently wrote that, “[p]eople working together with trusted AI will have a transformative effect on our economy and society … It&#39;s time we embrace that partnership — and prepare our workforces for everything AI has to offer.” Simply put, organizations are experiencing exponential growth in the installation of AI-powered tools and firms that don&#39;t adapt risk getting left behind.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI Risks at Work&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, remaining competitive also introduces significant risk for both employees and employers. For example, a 2022 &lt;a href=&quot;https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000380861&quot;>;UNESCO publication&lt;/a>; on “the effects of AI on the working lives of women” reports that AI in the recruitment process, for example, is excluding women from upward moves. &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1408.6491&quot;>;One study the report cites&lt;/a>; that included 21 experiments consisting of over 60,000 targeted job advertisements found that “setting the user&#39;s gender to &#39;Female&#39; resulted in fewer instances of ads related to high-paying jobs than for users selecting &#39;Male&#39; as their gender.” And even though this AI bias in recruitment and hiring is well-known, it&#39;s not going away anytime soon. As the UNESCO report goes on to say, “A &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3450077&quot;>;2021 study&lt;/a>; showed evidence of job advertisements skewed by gender on Facebook even when the advertisers wanted a gender-balanced audience.” It&#39;s often a matter of biased data which will continue to infect AI tools and threaten key workforce factors such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raconteur.net/responsible-business/ais-threat-to-diversity-equity-inclusivity/&quot;>;diversity, equity, and inclusion&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Discriminatory employment practices may be only one of a cocktail of legal risks that generative AI exposes organizations to. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bloomberglaw.com/tech-and-telecom-law/openai-hit-with-first-defamation-suit-over-chatgpt-hallucination&quot;>;OpenAI is facing its first defamation lawsuit&lt;/a>; as a result of allegations that ChatGPT produced harmful misinformation. Specifically, the system produced a summary of a real court case which included fabricated accusations of embezzlement against a radio host in Georgia. This highlights the negative impact on organizations for creating and sharing AI generated information. It underscores concerns about LLMs fabricating false and libelous content, resulting in reputational damage, loss of credibility, diminished customer trust, and serious legal repercussions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to concerns related to libel, there are risks associated with &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/generative-ai-has-an-intellectual-property-problem&quot;>;copyright and intellectual property infringements&lt;/a>;. Several &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/27/the-current-legal-cases-against-generative-ai-are-just-the-beginning/&quot;>;high-profile legal cases&lt;/a>; have emerged where the developers of generative AI tools have been sued for the alleged improper use of licensed content. The presence of copyright and intellectual property infringements, coupled with the legal implications of such violations, poses significant risks for organizations utilizing generative AI products. Organizations can improperly use licensed content through generative AI by unknowingly engaging in activities such as plagiarism, unauthorized adaptations, commercial use without licensing, and misusing Creative Commons or open-source content, exposing themselves to potential legal consequences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The large-scale deployment of AI also &lt;a href=&quot;https://siliconangle.com/2023/06/06/new-report-warns-cybersecurity-risks-generative-ai-technology/&quot;>;magnifies the risks of cyberattacks&lt;/a>;. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/opinion/Generative-AI-the-next-biggest-cyber-security-threat&quot;>;fear amongst cybersecurity experts&lt;/a>; is that generative AI could be used to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consent.yahoo.com/v2/collectConsent?sessionId=3_cc-session_e69b334f-36d8-44b0-9f52-93ea6089aa5a&quot;>;identify and exploit vulnerabilities&lt;/a>; within business information systems, given the ability of LLMs to automate coding and bug detection, which could be used by malicious actors to break through security barriers. There&#39;s also the fear of employees accidentally sharing sensitive data with third-party AI providers. A notable instance involves Samsung staff unintentionally &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-generative-ai-tools-like-chatgpt-after-april-internal-data-leak/&quot;>;leaking trade secrets&lt;/a>; through ChatGPT while using the LLM to review source code. Due to their failure to opt out of data sharing, confidential information was inadvertently provided to OpenAI. And even though Samsung and others are taking steps to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2023/05/19/apple-joins-a-growing-list-of-companies-cracking-down-on-use-of-chatgpt-by-staffers-heres-why/&quot;>;restrict the use of third-party AI tools&lt;/a>; on company-owned devices, there&#39;s still the concern that employees can leak information through the use of such systems on personal devices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On top of these risks, businesses will soon have to navigate nascent, varied, and somewhat murky regulations. Anyone hiring in New York City, for instance, will have to ensure their AI-powered recruitment and hiring tech doesn&#39;t violate the City&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/new-york-city-s-automated-employment-6844706/&quot;>;automated employment decision tool&lt;/a>;” law. To comply with the new law, employers will need to take various steps such as conducting third-party bias audits of their hiring tools and publicly disclosing the findings. AI regulation is also scaling up nationally with the Biden-Harris administration&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/ostp/ai-bill-of-rights/&quot;>;Blueprint for an AI Bill of Rights&lt;/a>;” and internationally with the EU&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://artificialintelligenceact.eu/&quot;>;AI Act&lt;/a>;, which will mark a new era of regulation for employers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This growing nebulous of evolving regulations and pitfalls is why thought leaders such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/your-7-biggest-chatgpt-questions-answered&quot;>;Gartner&lt;/a>; are strongly suggesting that businesses “proceed but don&#39;t over pivot” and that they “create a task force reporting to the CIO and CEO” to plan a roadmap for a safe AI transformation that mitigates various legal, reputational, and workforce risks. Leaders dealing with this AI dilemma have important decision to make. On the one hand, there is a pressing competitive pressure to fully embrace AI. However, on the other hand, a growing concern is arising as the implementation of irresponsible AI can result in severe penalties, substantial damage to reputation, and significant operational setbacks. The concern is that in their quest to stay ahead, leaders may unknowingly introduce potential time bombs into their organization, which are poised to cause major problems once AI solutions are deployed and regulations take effect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/06/08/1180838096/an-eating-disorders-chatbot-offered-dieting-advice-raising-fears-about-ai-in-hea&quot;>;National Eating Disorder Association&lt;/a>; (NEDA) recently announced it was letting go of its hotline staff and replacing them with their new chatbot, Tessa. However, just days before making the transition, NEDA discovered that their system was promoting harmful advice such as encouraging people with eating disorders to restrict their calories and to lose one to two pounds per week. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/06/13/1074551/an-algorithm-intended-to-reduce-poverty-in-jordan-disqualifies-people-in-need/&quot;>;World Bank&lt;/a>; spent $1 billion to develop and deploy an algorithmic system, called Takaful, to distribute financial assistance that Human Rights Watch now says ironically creates inequity. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-chatgpt-courts-e15023d7e6fdf4f099aa122437dbb59b&quot;>;two lawyers from New York&lt;/a>; are facing possible disciplinary action after using ChatGPT to draft a court filing that was found to have several references to previous cases that did not exist. These instances highlight the need for well-trained and well-supported employees at the center of this digital transformation. While AI can serve as a valuable assistant, it should not assume the leading position.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Principles for Responsible AI at Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To help decision-makers avoid negative outcomes while also remaining competitive in the age of AI, we&#39;ve devised several principles for a sustainable AI-powered workforce. The principles are a blend of ethical frameworks from institutions like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsf.gov/od/recr.jsp&quot;>;National Science Foundation&lt;/a>; as well as legal requirements related to employee monitoring and data privacy such as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bja.ojp.gov/program/it/privacy-civil-liberties/authorities/statutes/1285&quot;>;Electronic Communications Privacy Act&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecpra.org/&quot;>;California Privacy Rights Act&lt;/a>;. The steps for ensuring responsible AI at work include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Informed Consent. &lt;/strong>;Obtain voluntary and informed agreement from employees to participate in any AI-powered intervention &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; the employees are provided with all the relevant information about the initiative. This includes the program&#39;s purpose, procedures, and potential risks and benefits.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Aligned Interests. &lt;/strong>;The goals, risks, and benefits for both the employer and employee are clearly articulated and aligned.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Opt In &amp;amp; Easy Exits. &lt;/strong>;Employees must opt into AI-powered programs without feeling forced or coerced, and they can easily withdraw from the program at any time without any negative consequences and without explanation.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Conversational Transparency. &lt;/strong>;When AI-based conversational agents are used, the agent should formally reveal any persuasive objectives the system aims to achieve through the dialogue with the employee.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Debiased and Explainable AI. &lt;/strong>;Explicitly outline the steps taken to remove, minimize, and mitigate bias in AI-powered employee interventions—especially for disadvantaged and vulnerable groups—and provide transparent explanations into how AI systems arrive at their decisions and actions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;AI Training and Development. &lt;/strong>;Provide continuous employee training and development to ensure the safe and responsible use of AI-powered tools.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Health and Well-Being. &lt;/strong>;Identify types of AI-induced stress, discomfort, or harm and articulate steps to minimize risks (eg, how will the employer minimize stress caused by constant AI-powered monitoring of employee behavior).&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data Collection. &lt;/strong>;Identify what data will be collected, if data collection involves any invasive or intrusive procedures (eg, the use of webcams in work-from-home situations), and what steps will be taken to minimize risk.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data. &lt;/strong>;Disclose any intention to share personal data, with whom, and why.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Privacy and Security. &lt;/strong>;Articulate protocols for maintaining privacy, storing employee data securely, and what steps will be taken in the event of a privacy breach.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Third Party Disclosure. &lt;/strong>;Disclose all third parties used to provide and maintain AI assets, what the third party&#39;s role is, and how the third party will ensure employee privacy.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Communication.&lt;/strong>; Inform employees about changes in data collection, data management, or data sharing as well as any changes in AI assets or third-party relationships.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Laws and Regulations. &lt;/strong>;Express ongoing commitment to comply with all laws and regulations related to employee data and the use of AI.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We encourage leaders to urgently adopt and develop this checklist in their organizations. By applying such principles, leaders can ensure rapid &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; responsible AI deployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make Leadership Positions More Enticing to Primary Care Physicians]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_1293518427.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/The Good Brigade/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the brink of collapse due to historic highs of physician stress, burnout, and exhaustion; mass departures from the profession; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective advocacy to improve primary care on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Healthcare organizations who understand and work to address the issues PCPs face &amp;#8212; and encourage their professional development &amp;#8212; will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://catalyst.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/CAT.23.0029&quot;>;brink of collapse&lt;/a>; due to historic highs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-help-primary-care-physicians-craft-sustainable-careers&quot;>;physician stress&lt;/a>;, burnout, and exhaustion; mass &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostonglobe.com/2023/03/16/metro/months-long-waits-accessing-care-leave-patients-sicker-anguish/&quot;>;departures from the profession&lt;/a>;; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective &lt;a href=&quot;https://nap.nationalacademies.org/catalog/25983/implementing-high-quality-primary-care-rebuilding-the-foundation-of-health&quot;>;advocacy to improve primary care&lt;/a>; on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/why-is-it-so-challenging-to-find-a-primary-care-physician-202209282822&quot;>;shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care&lt;/a>; under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If primary care is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/16/opinion/pandemic-recovery-primary-care.html&quot;>;touted as the foundation of a well-functioning health care system&lt;/a>; — the front line of clinical care and the initial point of contact for most patients — how can it be allowed to deteriorate without unified and passionate intervention? Our research suggests that the answer may be straightforward. While primary care accounts for roughly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aamc.org/data-reports/workforce/data/active-physicians-largest-specialties-major-professional-activity-2021&quot;>;one in three&lt;/a>; practicing physicians and is seen as the bedrock of the health care system, it is also the most overlooked and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jabfm.org/content/primary-care-physician-leadership-top-ranked-us-hospitals&quot;>;underrepresented in the realms of health care leadership&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transformational changes to primary care will require leadership with holistic training, a clear vision, an insider&#39;s perspective, and skin in the game. PCPs are &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/early/2022/05/19/leader-2022-000591.abstract&quot;>;uniquely positioned to lead&lt;/a>; this change. They are the Swiss Army Knives of medicine, offering an increasingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cfp.ca/content/68/11/801&quot;>;rare generalist perspective, requiring strong communication skills, and a community-focused&lt;/a>; approach to care delivery. Not only are they responsible for managing day-to-day concerns for their patients, they also coordinate care across specialties and organizations for those who may have medically complex diagnoses. These clinicians are accustomed to leading teams every day to care for their patients, and must be adaptable, thoughtful, and flexible, given their vast breadth of clinical responsibilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, it is paradoxical that those best poised to lead are often reluctant to do so. In fact, many physicians are not only &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/healthcare-network/2014/sep/01/nhs-leadership-doctors-reluctant-manage-lead&quot;>;reluctant&lt;/a>; but &lt;em>;averse&lt;/em>; to taking on leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We interviewed PCPs in leadership roles to better understand what they believe prevents so many other physicians from pursuing such positions. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.lww.com/jhmonline/Abstract/2022/08000/Engaging_Physicians_in_Leadership__Motivations,.6.aspx&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; highlights three key deterrents:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;PCPs viewed leadership roles as a path to losing autonomy and limiting their ability to develop long-term therapeutic relationships with patients — a key reason many physicians chose careers in medicine in the first place.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs associated leadership roles with major resource constraints, evaporating both time and earnings potential.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs lamented the loss of camaraderie with other physicians when taking on leadership roles, feeling that the roles interrupted collaboration with peers and generated uncomfortable conflict.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Despite these concerns, PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Health care organizations who understand and work to address these deterrents will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1097/HMR.0000000000000173&quot;>;quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three ways that health organizations can counteract these disincentives and support PCPs embracing leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Provide the On-Ramp&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs crave system change and personal growth, but often feel disempowered. They see their experience as valuable and want to leverage it to make a positive impact on the health care system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can tap into this motivation by framing leadership as a constructive opportunity to be a change agent. While organizations may not have the ability to alter a &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/05/creative-job-titles-can-energize-workers&quot;>;position&#39;s specific title&lt;/a>;, the job description can be used to reflect openness to an entrepreneurial mindset and an opportunity for improving perceived system deficits. Instead of drafting a typical (and often dry) administrative job description, frame it to emphasize how the role will enact change or address major obstacles in health care. Postings should speak to a PCP&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicfootprints.org/7-top-tips-on-recruiting-doctors-to-non-clinical-or-leadership-roles/&quot;>;adaptability based on the breadth of their training and diversity of practice experience&lt;/a>;, and PCPs should be encouraged to apply.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By using the frustration PCPs experience with the status quo and their frontline experience, health care organizations can promote vacant or novel leadership roles as opportunities to expand the impact on patients and to garner a broader scope of knowledge and expertise for PCPs identified as having leadership interest or potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Role Design and Definition&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs want to grow and develop professionally, but our study showed that they also identified clear disadvantages in taking on leadership roles. They identified the least attractive aspect of leading, in a word, as “loss.” They feared the loss of autonomy, time, close patient relationships, and camaraderie with peers. This can be due, in part, to their exposure to disappointing experiences observed in peers who have assumed leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can help mitigate this with the use of strategic &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/why-managers-design-jobs-to-be-more-boring-than-they-need-to-be&quot;>;job design&lt;/a>;, where organizations create an optimal job role, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>;, which allows PCPs to define and customize their role themselves. These two complementary pieces of the puzzle yield large gains in employee satisfaction and fulfillment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When organizations realize that fear of loss is a major barrier, they are better positioned to design purposeful and motivating work for PCPs taking on leadership roles. To address the concern for loss of autonomy, the role should be intentionally constructed to allow PCPs the agency to make decisions per their expertise. For those apprehensive about losing time, the role can be devised to encourage a flexible approach in how goals are achieved, including the freedom to decide how they will balance their clinical responsibilities with their new leadership role. In order to address concerns about losing relationships, organizations must provide opportunities for leaders to meet with their colleagues in informal settings and encourage leaders to continue to be actively engaged as a member of their clinical team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Empowering PCPs to engage in job crafting allows them to adjust aspects of the job to suit individual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-job-crafting-how-to-do-it-work-satisfaction-2022-6&quot;>;interests, values, and passions&lt;/a>;, making them more likely to be&lt;a href=&quot;https://positiveorgs.bus.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/What-is-Job-Crafting-and-Why-Does-it-Matter1.pdf&quot;>; engaged and more likely to thrive&lt;/a>; at work, while being successful in their leadership role. PCPs can independently alter the &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/what-job-crafting-looks-like&quot;>;type and scope of tasks; relationships and with whom they work; and how to think&lt;/a>;, communicate about, or conceive of the job. When PCPs have some degree of ownership and authority over how the job is defined, they will have the opportunity to include more of their passion points, while also thoughtfully reducing those aspects of the job that are seen as pain points.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Tools, Training, and Mentorship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs may want system change and growth, but they also need the tools, training, and mentorship to be successful. In most cases, PCPs &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/most-doctors-have-little-or-no-management-training-and-thats-a-problem&quot;>;aren&#39;t taught finance, accounting, management, or leadership skills&lt;/a>; in medical school, nor is there an emphasis on systems operations, despite the fact that, as physicians enter residency, they immediately begin leading medical teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are stark contrasts, both operationally and culturally, between &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/04/turning-doctors-into-leaders&quot;>;business and medicine&lt;/a>;. Executives and health administrators should provide opportunities for PCPs to cross-train with current administrators and to have access to mentors who can help with the transition. Providing resources to support the transition into leadership can help highly qualified and motivated PCPs avoid the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/robertpearl/2016/02/04/five-reasons-why-even-the-best-of-physicians-may-fail-as-leaders/?sh=1c79323bce22&quot;>;common pitfalls than can derail&lt;/a>; their ability to influence others and be successful in their expanded role. This may include offering or supporting continuing medical education (CME) or credentialing opportunities that feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mgma.com/practice-resources/human-resources/the-importance-of-physician-leadership-education&quot;>;management and leadership skills building&lt;/a>;, partnering with institutions of higher education to create pathways into &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.nejmcareercenter.org/article/eyeing-physician-career-boost-via-formal-business-education/&quot;>;graduate business or policy programs&lt;/a>;, or engaging with organizations that specialize in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.physicianleaders.org/about&quot;>;physician leadership training&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having PCPs in leadership roles has never been more important. Without a highly functioning and sustainable primary care system, all health care in the US will suffer. If we want a system that promotes effective and sustainable primary care, PCPs need to be involved in co-designing that system and leading change. Ultimately, this will benefit the entire health care system, and all of us who will, at any stage of our lives, depend on it for our own care and that of our families and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Nail Your Presentation to the Board]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_29_1296672467-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;sturti/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The boardroom is a distinct forum that requires a different type of presentation and preparation. In this article, the author outlines three practices every business leader should embrace to enhance their board presentations: 1) Start with a governing thesis: a big idea or perspective that captures the main point of the discussion. Presentations that start this way leave the audience with a compelling message. 2) Understand that the CEO is not the target audience. A board presentation has to provide some quick refreshers on the operating environment and &amp;#8212; more importantly &amp;#8212; identify the biggest problems that need fixing. 3) Steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback. Instead of concluding remarks that restate key business results, share two or three important ideas that will drive future success and concerns that could benefit from director input. The goal: Get the board&amp;#8217;s validation or critiques of a proposed course of action. The result, invariably, is a mix of candid feedback and intelligent, probing questions that create thoughtful board engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For most executives, even those at the most senior level, a presentation to the board of directors is the most demanding test of leadership communications. Very few succeed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Conversations with more than 100 public and private boards directors over the last decade reveal that dissatisfaction with presentations is nearly universal. PowerPoint decks are too long, too granular, or simply uninformative, they report.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet the feedback most senior executives receive — “Make it crisper,” “Fewer slides,” “Don&#39;t get caught up in operational details,” or even “More details, fewer headlines” — is often generic and unhelpful. Operators are told they are insufficiently strategic; strategic leaders are criticized for having insufficient operational depth. Both directors and presenter leave frustrated.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, the advice offered by professional speaking coaches is just as likely to lead senior executives astray. “Enhance vocal delivery,” “Use fewer bullet points,” “Tell a story,” or similar well-worn coaching points are rooted in the belief that a board presentation is simply a matter of stagecraft — a variation of a keynote presentation to a customer audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This counsel reveals a misunderstanding about the purpose and value of board meetings. The boardroom is a distinct forum that requires a different type of presentation and preparation. It demands elevated exchanges that leverage both the knowledge of senior leaders and the objectivity of seasoned directors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having coached executives preparing board-level presentations for more than 15 years — including senior leaders auditioning to become the next CEO — I have concluded that the executive&#39;s most important task is to share their thinking about the business they lead. The goal is not just to report the results of the last quarter. (Directors can read that on their own.) Instead, the senior leader should engage the board by discussing the most pressing challenges they face and how they intend to respond.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While each board has unique needs shaped by the company&#39;s operating environment, below I suggest three practices every business leader should embrace to enhance their board presentations — and their own value within the upper levels of the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Bring a compelling message.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The senior executive who arrives in the board room has typically submitted a set of slides well in advance that has been carefully vetted by the CEO and the legal team. In most cases, directors will have already studied the material, or at least flipped through the main points. What, then, is the purpose of the 10 to 30-minute slot that has been allotted to the nervous presenter?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rushing through a slide review might be useful as a quick refresher, but it neither deepens the board&#39;s understanding of the topic nor showcases the leadership skills of the executive. Instead, every presentation should start with a governing thesis: a big idea or perspective that captures the main point of the discussion. Presentations that start this way leave the audience with a compelling message.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Anne Mulcahy, who has served on multiple boards, including J&amp;amp;J, Target, LPL Financial, and Williams-Sonoma, has felt frustrated by the executives who want to convey too much data and information with a series of dense slides. “It almost seems like the objective is to demonstrate how much they know about their business, she says. “It has the opposite outcome. Directors don&#39;t know what the point of the presentation is supposed to be.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By contrast, a “thesis mindset” forces the presenter to confront the future rather than just reciting the facts of the past. The thesis-driven board presentation doesn&#39;t need to be an audacious proposal or a request for more funding. But it ought to frame an issue that requires board attention. At a minimum, the governing thesis tells directors: This is where I see my part of the company going. That idea can&#39;t be slipped into slide 19. It has to be stated unambiguously and boldly at the outset. At the very least, it provides insurance against off-topic interruptions or mid-presentation dozing.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Understand that the CEO is not the target audience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;By the time they are asked to present to the board, a member of a senior leadership team has had plenty of practice leading discussions with the CEO. They may even be very comfortable updating their boss, in an informal way, with little preparation. Unfortunately, bringing the same mindset and habits to the boardroom is a crucial mistake.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I am always struck by how often business unit leaders come to the boardroom and direct their talk to their boss, rather than the directors assembled around the table,” said Scott Miller, who has been serving on public and private company boards for more than two decades. Miller&#39;s point is not merely a criticism of presentation style, but a recognition that senior officers rarely consider the needs of directors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The board of directors is a unique audience with no comparison to the groups most executives regularly engage. They are not customers who need to be sold. And they are not true business colleagues, where strategy alignment and deep familiarity with the operational details of the business can be assumed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A public company board may be compromised of business leaders, academics, former CEOs, current financial officers, and executives who bring expertise from entirely different industries. As a rule, their range of knowledge about the company and any given topic will vary greatly. Some have been serving on the board for well over a decade; others may be attending their third or fourth meeting. There is also an unspoken (and sometimes unknowable) hierarchy on the board, with its own unstated group of alliances and range of authority.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ron Sugar, the lead director of Uber who also serves on the boards of Apple, Chevron, and Amgen, advises that the job of the presenter “is to fly at the right altitude” in the boardroom: “Dumb it down too much, and you risk insulting the directors. On the other hand, no board wants to be a working group. They want to understand what issues need to be on their radar screen.” He suggests planning to use half the allotted time so that the main point is reached quickly and discussion can follow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sugar&#39;s advice is sound. A board presentation has to provide some quick refreshers on the operating environment and — more importantly — identify the biggest problems that need fixing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These problems will be familiar to the CEO (who should never be taken by surprise in the boardroom). The directors, however, need both a reminder of the core issues in an executive&#39;s portfolio (talent, operations, regulation, or a particular geography) along with looming challenges. Too many executives miss the opportunity to frame problems in the right way — and make their presentations far less engaging than they should be.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The purpose of presenting challenges is not to frighten the board but to enlighten them and engage them in the operational and strategic questions that preoccupy the person presenting the material.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/how-to-increase-the-boards-impact-and-value&quot;>;2022 study&lt;/a>;, EY&#39;s Center for Board Matters found that public company directors felt confident they added value to discussions of capital allocation and succession. But very few felt the top value they delivered came in areas such as revenue growth, innovation, or disruption. Ironically, these latter topics are most frequently what executives are asked to address when they invited into the boardroom.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Effective leaders can help rebalance the value that directors ought to derive from a board meeting by setting up genuine discussions that invite reaction and input. Alas, too many board presentations come to an abrupt conclusion followed by a quick call for “any questions?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Following a presentation, many business unit leaders complain they find themselves falling down a rabbit hole of technical details triggered by an unexpected and mostly irrelevant question from a persistent director. In most instances, the blame is entirely on the presenter. They are ones who failed to set up the right conversation and missed the opportunity to steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback from the board.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Randy Foutch, the former CEO of Laredo Petroleum, who has sat on many small and large company boards, believes that many executives “miss the opportunity to solicit feedback from the directors with relevant experience.” He has seen so many executives wary of raising questions with directors that they leave directors silent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet driving a sophisticated conversation that promotes “good questions” is the unspoken mandate of robust board presentations. Instead of concluding remarks that restate key business results, a confident executive should share two or three important ideas that will drive future success and concerns that could benefit from director input. In other words, the presenter must sincerely seek out the board&#39;s point of view by posing questions that remain unresolved or business risks that will persist. The goal: Gt the board&#39;s validation or critiques of a proposed course of action. The result, invariably, is a mix of candid feedback and intelligent, probing questions that create thoughtful board engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During an interview, Frank Blake, the former CEO of The Home Depot, described the typical tone of a meeting between an on-the-ground store team and chief executive who has stopped by for a visit. “What the CEO will always hear is some version of: &#39;You&#39;re doing great.我们做得很好。 Now leave.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The same tone of forced cordiality — and unproductive feedback — has become the all-too-common standard for board presentations delivered by senior executives. They represent missed opportunities to elevate a company&#39;s board discussions and ensure that both the top team and the directors are getting the greatest intellectual value and leadership insight from every conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Managers Can Make Time for Their Own Development]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_sb10065848cx-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Diamond Sky Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Managers today must balance their day-to-day work with multiple &amp;#8220;ands,&amp;#8221; such as delivering on quarterly objectives &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;thinking strategically. Given these numerous demands, managers tend to deprioritize their own career development. It doesn&amp;#8217;t have to be that way. The more managers take control of their development, the better able they&amp;#8217;ll be to avoid the common career mistakes that will get in the way of their growth. And the more their team members see the positive impact of investing in their career development, the more likely they are to do the same.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Being a successful manager today is a tough task that requires grappling with multiple “ands”: Supporting team members &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;influencing senior stakeholders; making progress on the day job &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;troubleshooting unexpected problems; delivering on quarterly objectives &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;thinking strategically. In the midst of the “and overload,” it&#39;s not surprising that managers tend to be the least-likely people in an organization to prioritize their own career development.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Through our global work on “squiggly” and nonlinear careers, we support thousands of managers every year who share a sense of frustration that their career development is stalling but struggle to find the time to invest in their own learning. We&#39;ve observed three common career development mistakes managers make and uncovered a few tried-and-tested solutions to help them balance the demands of the day-to-day with investing in their own development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. The Say-Do Development Gap&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our clients often tell us that they find coaching and supporting their team members&#39; career development to be a motivating and enjoyable part of their managerial role — and yet they undervalue the importance of modeling this behavior themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When teams don&#39;t see their manager investing in their own development, it creates a “say-do” development gap, which has a negative ripple effect for both managers and their teams: Team members lose confidence that committing time to their career development is the right thing to do and may even question whether their manager really values continual learning. At the same time, managers miss out on important moments to develop skills and capabilities to improve their performance and support their ambitions for the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Share learning goals&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;One simple and effective way for managers to avoid the say-do development gap is to share their learning goals openly with their teams. Sharing development priorities has multiple benefits. First, it prompts managers to identify what development they want to focus on, and sharing their goals increases accountability. Second, involving team members means that managers are surrounding themselves with more people to support their development and removes the idea that learning from others is linked to levels and hierarchy. Finally, when team members see their managers setting and sticking to development goals, it prompts them to do the same.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a manager who shares a learning goal to increase their internal profile might benefit from a team member spotting an opportunity for them to speak at an event. A manager looking to develop their ability to use data to drive decisions could be supported with feedback from their team members on what they currently do well and what could be better.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When approached in this way, development doesn&#39;t need to be another thing that gets added to a manager&#39;s to-do list; it becomes part of their daily work and is accelerated by the people who work for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. The Bubble Barrier&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;With so many demands on their workdays, it&#39;s understandable that managers rarely spend time on development outside of their organization. The challenge of finding the time and opportunity to learn in different places and with new people often feels insurmountable and falls into the category of “should do” rather than “will do.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Relying on internal-only development results in managers developing a narrow view of the world and limits their learning. And operating in the bubble of internal knowledge and networks means that managers are reenforcing who and what they already know rather than cultivating their curiosity. Managers need to learn beyond the internal bubble so that it doesn&#39;t become a barrier to their growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Knowledge-swap sessions&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;An efficient way to bring the outside in is to approach peers in a non-competing organization to co-host a team development session, where both teams share their expertise with each other. For example, a team with agile expertise could knowledge-swap with a team that has strong communication capabilities. Or an established team in a large organization might spend time with a team from a smaller startup, exchanging insights on innovation in different operating contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-sidebar data-sidebar-alternate=&quot;sidebar&quot;>; &lt;h4>;Example agenda items for knowledge-swap sessions&lt;/h4>; &lt;div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;“What if?” wall:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares an idea or objective they&#39;re working on, and the other organization creates a “what if?” wall of questions to spark new thoughts. For example: What if you were famous for your customer service? What if your product sold twice as much as it does today?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Day in the life:&lt;/strong>; One person from each team describes the reality of a day in their life. This helps create a sense of connection between people, especially when the speaker includes non-work activities. For example: I started my day by taking my five-year-old to the dentist where he decided to scream the place down.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Mistake moments:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares a mistake moment they&#39;ve had and what they learned. This can help teams preempt potential problems and recover quickly when they happen. For example: We were communicating across too many technology platforms and people were getting overwhelmed and missing important information. The team created a communications policy that helps people feel more in control. &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Pride postcards:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares one thing they&#39;re proud from the past few months and how they came together to achieve it. This inspires the other team with the art of the possible and gives them practical insights on how to make it happen. For example: We introduced a new well-being policy for our organization that got featured in the media as an example of best practice. The three things that helped us most were… &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Surprise stories:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares an example of something about their organization or function that might surprise others who aren&#39;t on “the inside.” This gives teams ideas for what they can do differently. For example: In our organization, everyone gets an extra day of holiday on their birthday.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Superpower swaps:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares one of their superpowers and three top tips on how to develop that skill. For example: One of our superpowers is problem-solving, and our three top tips are to use your strengths to solve problems, hold problem-solving hack sessions, and pair people up on problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/article-sidebar>; &lt;p>;These knowledge-swap sessions allow everyone to spend time in a different working world, create new connections, and learn together (which also supports overcoming the say-do gap). The format of a swap session can range from a virtual hour over lunch to a full day in a room. Holding knowledge-swaps gives managers — and their teams — regular opportunities to learn from people outside the organization in a way that&#39;s part of their existing rhythm of work, rather than something extra to squeeze in.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. The Time Trap&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We often hear managers say: “I don&#39;t have time to invest in my development. I&#39;ll get around to it when everything calms down, or when this project has finished, or when I&#39;ve recruited this person, etc.” This way of thinking means keeps many managers stuck in a time trap, which will hold their career back over the long-term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These time traps aren&#39;t a result of managers making excuses — they reflect the reality of the challenges they&#39;re dealing with. The mistake is the hope that one day we&#39;ll magically have more time and fewer things to do. If managers look for the perfect moment to focus on their development, they&#39;re likely to be left waiting and stagnating in their career.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Manager micro-learning moments&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many people still associate development with formal learning methods like taking a course. But what managers need are small, easy ways to make development part of their day-to-day. Practicing micro-learning moments is a memorable and simple way for managers to kickstart the habit of continual improvement. Effective micro-learning moments usually take less than 10 minutes, and they&#39;re small but significant in their impact, as managers benefit from a compound effect of continual learning over time. Here are a few examples:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Fast feedback:&lt;/strong>; Ask your team members to answer the same fast feedback question: &lt;em>;What three words would you use to describe me at my best? &lt;/em>;This simple question gives managers instant insight into whether their intent is matching their impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;One-minute weekly review:&lt;/strong>; End your week by spending one minute jotting down the answers to these two self-awareness questions: &lt;em>;What has given me the most energy this week? What could have been better this week?&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Strength accelerator: &lt;/strong>;Pick one skill you want to strengthen and identify an action related to either regularity (how could you use that strength more?), range (where else could you use that strength that you don&#39;t today?), or reach (who could you share that strength with?).&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The more managers take control of their development, the better able they&#39;ll be to avoid the career mistakes that will get in the way of their growth. And the more their team members see the positive impact of investing in their career development, the more likely they are to do the same. Helping managers helps everyone succeed in their squiggly careers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Find the Time to Connect with Colleagues When You&rsquo;re Very, Very Busy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_482824941.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HollenderX2/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A consequence of our often never-ending to-do lists at work is the loss of camaraderie among coworkers. While productivity is important, the balance between task completion and taking the time to connect with your team is essential in avoiding burnout and making work more enjoyable. The common misconception is that there simply isn&amp;#8217;t enough hours (or energy) in the day to get your work done and socialize; the reality is that just a quick slack message, coffee run, or group share in the beginning or ending of a meeting are all simple yet impactful acts that require minimal effort and time and thus make the former argument null and void. Studies show that socializing, despite feeling like a daunting task, can be effective in combating mental fatigue by energizing us. Increased energy improves performance and therefore proves socializing to be even more beneficial than the head down work one might prioritize over fostering those connections with colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re feeling behind on tasks and pressed against deadlines, catching up with and connecting with colleagues is about the last thing you feel like doing. You just want to put your head down, check off tasks on your to-do list, and get things done.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are absolutely times when you should put on blinders and focus solely on your tactical objectives. But exclusively interacting in a transactional manner with your coworkers could cause you to lose any sense of personal connection, especially if you work remotely. By taking even a few minutes each day to foster a sense of rapport at work, you could unlock the key to a &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/to-be-happier-at-work-invest-more-in-your-relationships&quot;>;greater sense of purpose and well-being, reduce burnout, and even improve your performance.&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So how do you make time for people without feeling more stressed and overwhelmed? As a time management coach, I&#39;ve seen that with just a little more intention, you can make much more meaningful connections without investing much time.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Chat in One-on-One Meetings&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you already have one-on-one meetings scheduled with your team, take a few minutes at the start of the discussion to find out how they&#39;re doing before jumping to the business agenda. You don&#39;t need to spend the whole time on personal updates, but even reserving five minutes to ask about their recent vacation, find out if their mom is out of the hospital, or to see how they&#39;re recovering from surgery can make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can use the same strategy for one-on-one meetings with colleagues who you regularly work with on projects. Depending on the length of the meeting and how much you need to cover, you may not have time to catch up each time. But if every few meetings you use a few minutes at the beginning or end to talk about more than the projects at hand, you can strengthen those ties. This could include bonding over your excitement about a particular sports team, talking about your families, or discussing anything else that gives you space to connect beyond a one-dimensional, task-oriented level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If remembering details about people&#39;s lives doesn&#39;t come naturally to you, make a private note in your calendar with memory cues, such as asking them about their new puppy, about their kids&#39; latest extracurriculars, or how their side venture is going.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Encourage Group Sharing During Meetings&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a large team meeting, there won&#39;t be much space for personal catchups. But if you have a smaller team, it may be appropriate to take some time on a weekly or monthly basis for updates. This could be as simple as a quick share at the beginning of a meeting about a recent event, such as attending an industry conference. This can also happen organically if you work in person and have a specific forum designated for it: for example, if you bring in coffee and bagels on Monday mornings and have breakfast together, or if there&#39;s a Friday afternoon happy hour. Even 15 to 20 minutes of unstructured talk can lead to a greater sense of team engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re part of a remote or hybrid team, it may be harder to connect organically. Consider hosting a virtual happy hour or have a few people share during a team meeting. Just keep these updates short so that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/irl/highs-lows-weekend-tiktok/&quot;>;the highs and lows don&#39;t turn into a viral meme&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Turn Breaks into Informal Social Time &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Grab a bite to eat with colleagues over your lunch break. Your meeting schedule may not allow a proper lunch break every day, but blocking out at least a couple of days a week where you&#39;re not multi-tasking at your computer can make your lunch more enjoyable and more social. This could be planned out in advance, where you meet up with someone in another department who you don&#39;t get to see often, or it could be more informal with a team member who works right by you. If you&#39;d like to have a relaxed approach, simply ask someone if they want to join you when you&#39;re heading out the door or reheating your leftovers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://creativecloud.adobe.com/discover/article/a-science-backed-guide-to-taking-truly-restful-breaks&quot;>;Social breaks can also effectively combat mental fatigue&lt;/a>; in the mid-afternoon slump and help you feel refreshed for the final work stretch before you&#39;re done for the day. When you notice your eye lids drooping and your head bobbing, stand up and get moving. If you&#39;re in the office, this is an excellent time to walk the halls and connect with a few people or invite someone to grab a cup of coffee. Similar to lunch, you can stop by to chat with members of your own team or drop in on a different department. The movement and conversation will wake you up and serve as a time of connection and potentially internal networking. If you&#39;re working remotely, send a friendly Slack message to a colleague, rather than turning to scroll social media. Even if they&#39;re too busy to respond, they may offer to catch up with you later.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Make Calls During Your Commute &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you commute into the office or travel for business, some of your travel times could offer an ideal opportunity to catch up in an informal manner with colleagues. One of my clients who was an executive with a packed meeting schedule used his drive home to reach out and have informal conversations with his leaders. This helped him get a more personal view on their thoughts and concerns, as the company was going through a major transition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re on the road, you can call from airports, Ubers, or hotels or send messages when you&#39;re waiting in lines or on trains. Even a five- to 10-minute conversation can increase your rapport and, most importantly, show that you care.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Take Advantage of Virtual Messaging &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re working exclusively remotely, the options for informal social connection will be limited. In these cases, you can simply send a quick chat message or text asking how someone is doing or share a quick update with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These conversations can end up taking a lot of time if you&#39;re not conscious of how long they go, so you&#39;ll want to limit how frequently you engage in purely social messaging. But reaching out a few times a week can be fun and help you feel connected. Consider pinging people at natural times when you would have said “Hello!” to coworkers in the past, such as when you first get to your desk, around lunch, or when you&#39;re waiting for a meeting to start.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It can be a challenge to find time to talk with people when you barely feel like you have time for completing tasks and projects. But there are benefits to connecting with your coworkers. Rather than keeping your head down and focusing only on work, find those pockets of time in your schedule where you can thoughtfully connect with colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Prepare Your Culture for AI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_1468369205.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;gremlin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The platform shift to AI is well underway. And while it holds the promise of transforming work and giving organizations a competitive advantage, realizing those benefits isn&amp;#8217;t possible without a culture that embraces curiosity, failure, and learning. Leaders are uniquely positioned to foster this culture within their organizations today in order to set their teams up for success in the future. When paired with the capabilities of AI, this kind of culture will unlock a better future of work for everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As business leaders, today we find ourselves in a place that&#39;s all too familiar: the unfamiliar. Just as we steered our teams through the shift to remote and flexible work, we&#39;re now on the verge of another seismic shift: AI. And like the shift to flexible work, priming an organization to embrace AI will hinge first and foremost on culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The pace and volume of work has increased exponentially, and we&#39;re all struggling under the weight of it. Leaders and employees are eager for AI to lift the burden. That&#39;s the key takeaway from our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/will-ai-fix-work&quot;>;2023 Work Trend Index&lt;/a>;, which surveyed 31,000 people across 31 countries and analyzed trillions of aggregated productivity signals in Microsoft 365, along with labor market trends on LinkedIn.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nearly two-thirds of employees surveyed told us they don&#39;t have enough time or energy to do their job. The cause of this drain is something we identified in the report as digital debt: the influx of data, emails, and chats has outpaced our ability to keep up. Employees today spend nearly 60% of their time communicating, leaving only 40% of their time for creating and innovating. In a world where creativity is the new productivity, digital debt isn&#39;t just an inconvenience — it&#39;s a liability.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI promises to address that liability by allowing employees to focus on the most meaningful work. Increasing productivity, streamlining repetitive tasks, and increasing employee well-being are the top three things leaders want from AI, according to our research. Notably, amid fears that AI will replace jobs, reducing headcount was last on the list.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Becoming an AI-powered organization will require us to work in entirely new ways. As leaders, there are three steps we can take today to get our cultures ready for an AI-powered future:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Choose curiosity over fear&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI marks a new interaction model between humans and computers. Until now, the way we&#39;ve interacted with computers has been similar to how we interact with a calculator: We ask a question or give directions, and the computer provides an answer. But with AI, the computer will be more like a copilot. We&#39;ll need to develop a new kind of chemistry together, learning when and how to ask questions and about the importance of fact-checking responses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fear is a natural reaction to change, so it&#39;s understandable for employees to feel some uncertainty about what AI will mean for their work. Our research found that while 49% of employees are concerned AI will replace their jobs, the promise of AI outweighs the threat: 70% of employees are more than willing to delegate to AI to lighten their workloads.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re rarely served by operating from a place of fear. By fostering a culture of curiosity, we can empower our people to understand how AI works, including its capabilities and its shortcomings. This understanding starts with firsthand experience. Encourage employees to put curiosity into action by experimenting (safely and securely) with new &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.microsoft.com/reinventing-productivity/&quot;>;AI tools&lt;/a>;, such as AI-powered &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bing.com/search?form=MY0291&amp;amp;OCID=MY0291&amp;amp;q=Bing+AI&amp;amp;showconv=1&quot;>;search&lt;/a>;, intelligent writing assistance, or smart calendaring, to name just a few. Since every role and function will have different ways to use and benefit from AI, challenge them to rethink how AI could improve or transform processes as they get familiar with the tools. From there, employees can begin to unlock new ways of working.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Embrace failure&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI will change nearly every job, and nearly every work pattern can benefit from some degree of AI augmentation or automation. As leaders, now is the time to encourage our teams to bring creativity to reimagining work, adopting a test-and-learn strategy to find ways AI can best help meet the needs of the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI won&#39;t get it right every time, but even when it&#39;s wrong, it&#39;s &lt;em>;usefully&lt;/em>; wrong. It moves you at least one step forward from a blank slate, so you can jump right into the critical thinking work of reviewing, editing, or augmenting. It will take time to learn these new patterns of work and identify which processes need to change and how. But if we create a culture where experimentation and learning are viewed as a prerequisite to progress, we&#39;ll get there much faster.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As leaders, we have a responsibility to create the right environment for failure so that our people are empowered to experiment to uncover how AI can fit into their workflows. In my experience, that includes celebrating wins as well as sharing lessons learned in order to help keep each other from wasting time learning the same lesson twice. Both formally and informally, carve out space for people to share knowledge — for example, by crowdsourcing a prompt guidebook within your department or making AI tips a standing agenda item in your monthly all-staff meetings. Operating with agility will be a foundational tenet of AI-powered organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Become a learn-it-all&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I often hear concerns that AI will be a crutch, offering shortcuts and workarounds that ultimately diminish innovation and engagement. In my mind, the potential for AI is so much bigger than that, and it will become a competitive advantage for those who use it thoughtfully. Those will become your most engaged and innovative employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The value you get from AI is only as good as what you put in. Simple questions will result in simple answers. But sophisticated, thought-provoking questions will result in more complex analysis and bigger ideas. The value will shift from employees who have all the right answers to employees who know how to ask the right questions. Organizations of the future will place a premium on analytical thinkers and problem-solvers who can effectively reason over AI-generated content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At Microsoft, we believe a learn-it-all mentality will get us much farther than a know-it-all one. And while the learning curve of using AI can be daunting, it&#39;s a muscle that has to be built over time — and that we should start strengthening today. When I talk to leaders about how to achieve this across their companies and teams, I tell them three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Establish guardrails to help people experiment safely and responsibly. Which tools do you encourage employees to use, and what data is — and isn&#39;t — appropriate to input. What guidelines do they need to follow around fact-checking, reviewing, and editing?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Learning to work with AI will need to be a continuous process, not a one-time training. Infuse learning opportunities into your rhythm of business and keep employees up to date with the latest resources. For example, one team might block off Friday afternoons for learning, while another has monthly “office hours” for AI Q&amp;amp;A and troubleshooting. And think beyond traditional courses or resources. How can peer-to-peer knowledge sharing, such as lunch and learns or a digital hotline, play a role so people can learn from each other?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Embrace the need for change management. Being intentional and programmatic will be crucial for successfully adopting AI. Identify goals and metrics for success, and select AI champions or pilot program leads to help bring the vision to life. Different functions and disciplines will have different needs and challenges when it comes to AI, but one shared need will be for structure and support as we all transition to a new way of working.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The platform shift to AI is well underway. And while it holds the promise of transforming work and giving organizations a competitive advantage, realizing those benefits isn&#39;t possible without a culture that embraces curiosity, failure, and learning. As leaders, we&#39;re uniquely positioned to foster this culture within our organizations today in order to set our teams up for success in the future. When paired with the capabilities of AI, this kind of culture will unlock a better future of work for everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>