<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Video Quick Take &ndash; Google&rsquo;s Gautam Ramdurai on Emerging Consumer Behavior - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM GOOGLE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/video-quick-take-googles-gautam-ramdurai-on-emerging-consumer-behavior]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6328969026112&quot;}&quot; js- target=&quot;video-player-page&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;正在加载.. . &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt; p>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Harvard Business Review 研究和特殊项目高级编辑 Todd Pruzan 最近采访了谷歌亚太区广告营销集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai，采访了新一期的 HBR Video Quick Take。由于当今的每个企业都需要驾驭一系列复杂的因素来推动可持续和盈利增长，同时牢记这样做的核心仍然是了解客户以及他们如何做出决策，Pruzan 与 Ramdurai 谈到了对新兴消费者行为的新见解&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;很多关于消费者行为的事情似乎都在持续发生变化。您现在看到亚太地区的消费者行为发生了哪些变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span >;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;我们现在发现的东西很吸引人。尤其需要注意的是，2023 年与 2020 年甚至 2022 年的真正不同之处在于。我们知道这场大流行病从根本上改变了很多事情，但我认为随着我们走出大流行病，其他危机正在介入：政治动荡、气候变化和生活成本危机。当所有这些类型的公共危机同时发生时，我们需要开始考虑它们所产生的总体影响。答案是：我们正在进入一个真正的混合世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;想想在大流行期间每个人是如何上网的。但是，随着我们从大流行中走出来，当你想到你的杂货店购物时，你是如何决定哪些物品是在商店购买的，哪些是在网上购买的？即使是最简单的决策，每个人的头脑中都会进行这种复杂的计算，这仅仅是因为决策本身的因素数量以及您从中获取信息的渠道数量。例如，考虑与您交互的设备数量，然后将其乘以您使用的渠道数量，从 Google 搜索到 YouTube 再到任何其他视频平台再到报纸。您可以进出在线和离线世界。甚至在网络世界中，也有如此多的多样性，你试图找到摆脱它的方法。到 2023 年，这将变得非常棘手。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，在整个亚太地区，我们的研究告诉我们，想知道和知道之间的差距——一直存在——从未如此之大。这就是我们所说的置信度差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push (function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt ;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;好吧，信任和信心如今比以往任何时候都更重要，但消费者如何驾驭这种格局？企业如何驾驭它？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;让我们从消费者开始。消费者是聪明的。他们总是比企业更善于与时俱进。因此，消费者所做的是相当快地找到他们的内部微积分。换句话说，每个人都有他们通过的这些决策因素以及他们在做出决策时要寻求的这些信息源。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们举一个想要做某事的人的例子：我有一个三- 岁，所以我一直在想我三岁的孩子什么时候应该骑自行车。那是一个重要的时刻，对吧？因此，当消费者想到“哦，我需要为我的女儿买一辆自行车”时，第一个问题永远不会是“我在哪里买自行车？”相反，它是“孩子骑自行车的合适年龄是多少？”这是一个更基本的生活问题和一个好奇心驱动的问题。你从一个关于孩子骑自行车的正确时间的问题开始，然后慢慢过渡到研究有哪些类型的自行车。您最终会被孩子们第一次尝试学习如何骑自行车的视频所吸引。您很快意识到您还需要购买头盔。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种好奇心路径扩展了消费者寻找正确信息的过程。当消费者浏览所有这些内容时，我们发现他们真正寻找的是六个特定的信心线索。这些线索是噪音中的信号；它们会告诉他们需要知道什么，以便更接近于对自己的决定充满信心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，想象一下您处于信心差距中。你被困在那里，不知道下一步该去哪里。你让好奇心引导你回答下一个问题。我们发现在这个过程中有一些关键信息将所有内容汇集在一起​​。例如，其中一个信心线索是评论。这家生产这种自行车的公司是否经过了良好的审查？这家公司是否以制造安全自行车或整体安全公司而享有盛誉？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他重要因素，例如社会认同。可持续性正变得越来越重要，因此一家公司的可持续性实践正成为越来越重要的购买考虑因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;令人惊讶的是，我们发现了一个额外的隐含线索。这第七个提示实际上是关于平台的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天有大量的数字信息，当我告诉你数字世界正在扩展时，我知道我是在向合唱团布道。人们拥有的信息来源数量比以往任何时候都多，随之而来的是大量虚假信息和错误信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type= &quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;简而言之，平台本身在 2023 年发挥的作用比我们以前看到的要大得多。它们成为关于您对获取信息的平台本身有多信任的第七个线索。这就像查看两个不同的新闻站点并决定您更信任哪个。同样的逻辑现在也适用于平台世界：您查看所有信息或查找信息的平台实际上与品牌或企业本身可能传达给客户的任何其他信心线索一样重要。 &lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;所以平台必须成为一部分你的日常生活。它必须是安全的。它必须是一个你信任的平台，几乎就像你会根据他们过去告诉你的那样相信一个人的话而不是另一个人的话。平台是这里的关键？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;是的，这就是我们在多个平台上看到的，尤其是谷歌和 YouTube。对于像 Google 这样的网站，人们在不确定的时候会去寻找一些东西，它几乎就像一个人类意图的图书馆。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，虽然品牌本身可以查看六个线索，但它不是就是你在这六个信心提示中所说的话。相反，它是您展示同样重要的自信线索的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b >;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;那么媒介真的是信息还是信息的重要组成部分？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;正确。我会说这是其中很大一部分，因为媒体永远不可能是完整的信息。您拥有自己的品牌。你知道它想对世界说话的真相。但我认为现在的复杂性——这可以追溯到我们关于 2023 年与以往相比的独特之处的研究——涉及需要考虑消费者必须经历的微积分。然后我们需要将其与企业必须经历的演算配对。因此，如果消费者没有在正确的时间、正确的地点和正确的媒介中找到正确的信息，他们将退出购买之旅。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;哇，听起来这是一个非常脆弱的交易。&lt;/p>; &lt; h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;当然可以。一切都回到了桌面上。凭直觉——这是我昨天与某人进行的讨论的一部分——你会想，“哦，在不确定的时候，我们会回到我们所知道的事情上。”但我们看到的是，人们实际上会花更多的时间进行研究，即使他们拥有已经使用了很长时间的品牌。因此，几乎就像是大流行病加剧了这种对信任和信心的需求，以至于人们正在将他们久经考验的品牌转移到餐桌的后面。这意味着您不能认为信任是理所当然的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;再次回到交易信任，它不是在人们购买产品时建立的。它是在人们考虑使用产品时构建的；它是在消费者甚至不知道他们需要该产品时构建的。因此，如果您经历了整个消费者旅程，您需要能够在整个过程中建立这些信心线索。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;而且当他们购买了您的产品时，它并没有结束。旅程中更重要的部分是他们实际使用您的产品或服务的时间。客户体验不会在购买按钮处结束。它几乎以多种方式从那里开始。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;如果信任对消费者很重要，那么这如何开始转化为业务成果？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span >;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;在 2023 年，它会产生非常直接的影响。如果消费者正在寻找信息以增强他们购买您的产品或服务的信心，那么您的出现方式就非常重要。如果你没有以正确的方式出现，它会对你的底线产生直接影响。例如，在印度和东南亚，三分之一的消费者决定不购买他们已经在考虑的品牌，因为他们感到有点焦虑。他们对自己的选择没有把握。¹ 所以那是一辆被遗弃的手推车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们也看到信任的积极方面也在很大程度上显现出来。如果您在客户/消费者的整个购买过程和整体购买体验中完成了与他们在一起的工作，并且您已经建立并输入了该信任帐户，那么购买高度信任的品牌的可能性要高出七倍²——而且它不会在购买时结束。在购买前对自己的产品选择充满信心的消费者再次购买该品牌的可能性高出近 20%。³&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，消费者旅程是周期性的，因此您与消费者建立的信任和信心不会改变当他们点击“购买”时结束。它几乎从那里开始。如果你想继续建立信任和信心的良性循环，你需要在任何地方加强，即使他们已经购买了你的产品。我们在数据中非常清楚地看到了这一点。因此，对于 2023 年寻求信心的消费者来说，所有品牌都重新回到桌面上，作为卖家，您可以选择是否要参与交易或旅程。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;企业可以做些什么来跟上客户的需求？您如何看待未来几年的变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span>;&lt;/b >;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;一旦有人获得了做出选择所需的所有信号，我们就认为他们的信心发生了转变：您已经帮助他们找到了生活问题的答案，并且您的产品或服务是其中的一部分。我们认为，聪明且能够推动这种信心转变的企业将在这个非常混乱的未来蓬勃发展——就此而言，现在也是如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是当你开始思考你的企业如何可以帮助他们改变信心，您需要知道显示哪个提示、何时显示以及为谁显示，因为您的所有消费者可能都不相同，而且他们不在同一部分旅程。这些都是移动的目标：正确的提示、正确的消费者、正确的格式、正确的信息、正确的设备以及决策过程中的正确点。开始理解这一点的唯一方法——这些在很多方面都是预测性决策——并大规模地、尤其是对大公司来说，在几毫秒内做到这一点的唯一方法是利用数据和人工智能的力量。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;再一次，这让我们回到了你是想成为一个交易型企业还是一个随着时间的推移建立信任和信心的企业。这是您需要在整个客户体验中进行的投资。营销活动的黄金标准曾经是您每季度只拥有并满足一个 KPI，但我们正在远离这一点。现在的黄金标准是您是否可以吸引同样具有高生命周期价值的新客户。那些曾经是在营销室举行的两次不同的会议，但现在它们被混为一谈。解决这种复杂性的方法是使用数据和 AI。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/ h5>; &lt;p>;Gautam，感谢您的见解。你今天有什么临别的话，特别是关于你将如何为你的女儿找到那辆自行车吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，Group营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;好复杂的问题！购买那辆自行车时存在许多生活问题。在我走这条路时，我需要牢记以下几点：我们知道生活比以前复杂得多，而且我们不知道下一组不确定性会是什么。我们也知道他们会来； &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于一直存在的信心差距，消费者仍会发现自己身处其中，或许还会扩大。也许信心线索会进化。但我认为，如果我们想知道他们需要哪些提示，就必须密切关注消费者的决策。我们的工作是帮助他们转变信心，随着我们走向未来，这只会变得越来越重要。复杂决策制定的世界将继续存在，投资于利用数据和 AI 的力量实现信心转变的能力的企业可能会在这种环境中蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5 >;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;非常感谢您进行精彩的对话以及您的所有意见今天的见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;谢谢，托德，感谢我。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;要了解更多信息，请访问 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkwithgoogle.com/intl/en-apac/marketing-strategies/automation/build-brand-confidence-ai-marketing/?utm_source=twg_partnership_external&amp;amp;utm_medium= referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023-APAC-GML-EVOS-HBR-VQT-HL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Think With Google&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;返回 HBR.org 上来自 Google APAC 的“&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/multiply-your-marketing-with-ai&quot;>;将您的营销与 AI 相乘&lt;/a>;”赞助商内容中心&lt;/em>;&lt; /strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;¹资料来源：Google/Kantar/Quantum，“搜索的情感价值”，印第安纳州、印度尼西亚、越南、马来西亚、菲律宾、泰国、巴基斯坦，2021 年， n=5006 P18M 类别买家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;² 资料来源：爱德曼，“信任，新品牌资产”，2022 年，n=14,000 名消费者来自 14 个国家/地区。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;³ 资料来源：Google/ Ipsos，解码回购，澳大利亚、印度、印度尼西亚、日本、韩国、越南，2023 年，每个市场 n=1500，家用电器、个人护理、健康和福祉产品的买家。&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Three Ways To Use The Customer Perspective As A Measure Of Success - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/three-ways-to-use-the-customer-perspective-as-a-measure-of-success]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358516&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_KPI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;在商业中，你无法改善自己而不是衡量——当今的组织通常使用关键绩效指标 (KPI) 来衡量进展和成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;成功的企业意味着更高的客户满意度、保留率和整体品牌声誉。因此，大多数公司将客户体验列为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superoffice.com/blog/customer-experience-statistics/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;首要业务也就不足为奇了&lt;/a>;。但很多时候，在跟踪和量化进度的过程中，业务领导者最终会优先考虑直接反对以客户为中心的行为的流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;传统的 KPI 包括盈利能力、生产力和流程效率的衡量标准——所有这些这是内部指标。分析这些指标无疑可以给出整体性能的指示。但是，当优先考虑高于一切时，他们可能会错过企业如何为客户提供最大价值的大局。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;消费者越来越多地从与品牌的互动和体验中获取价值。 83% 的消费者关注&lt;a href=&quot;https://khoros.com/resources&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;品牌如何对待他们&lt;/a>;产品，89% 的受访者表示在体验不佳后&lt;a href=&quot;https://harris-interactive.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;转向竞争对手&lt;/a>;。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;因此，随着体验成为更重要的绩效衡量标准，最成功的公司都在每个接触点建立情感联系。由于当今的消费者牢牢掌握着主导权，企业领导者需要拥有正确的工具、流程和以客户为中心的整体文化才能留在游戏中。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size : 11.0pt;&quot;>;作为 KPI 的客户价值&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;虽然效率、生产力和盈利能力将继续很重要，但客户价值正迅速成为分析的真正明星显示。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，衡量客户价值比跟踪传统的 KPI 更复杂。社会价值、品牌声望以及服务或产品提供的情感体验等因素都会发挥作用——所有这些都很难用标准方法量化。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot; >; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div >; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;以下是如何将 KPI 记分卡转向客户价值，从而为成功做好准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;建立哪些 KPI 将为您提供丰富的、以客户为中心的数据。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;客户参与度指标在此阶段很有用，可帮助您更好地分配资源并建立标准来监控和评估——并且，至关重要的是，了解您的客户如何看待您。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一系列良好的客户参与度指标包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;客户满意度得分&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;衡量您的客户满意度分数可以告诉您客户对上次与贵公司的互动有多满意，并让您有机会根据他们的反馈进行改进。净推荐值是您可以用来衡量客户体验的类似指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;流失率&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;您的流失率反映了在特定时期内停止与您开展业务的客户百分比。尽管客户离开的原因多种多样，但您需要了解是否存在一致的主题，以便解决原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;客户生命周期价值&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4 &quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;此 KPI 与客户流失率密切相关。您的客户生命周期价值得分将为您提供贵公司可以从客户那里获得的预期收入，帮助您估算营销计划的未来回报。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt ;&quot;>;让客户价值成为客户绩效指标的中心。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;KPI 是一个很好的起点，但它很容易迷失在数字和从对客户重要的事情上分心。衡量成功的另一种方法是用客户绩效指标 (CPI) 补充这些指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多公司将 KPI 与 CPI 混淆。尽管 KPI 可以有效衡量情绪，但仍然存在 KPI 忽略与客户相关的内容的风险。 KPI 与公司目标有着内在联系，但 CPI 关注 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-performace-indicators-surbhit-suman-banga&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot; noopener&quot;>;客户最关心的是什么&lt;/a>;，例如价值和满意度，这会导致忠诚度和保留率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与客户持续对话是充分利用您的最佳方式消费物价指数。询问他们从您的业务中获得了什么价值，是什么让他们回头，以及是什么影响了他们的购买。提问、倾听、设计、实施——然后再提问。&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;汇集正确的指标、正确的工具和正确的心态。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;这种连续的监控和调整循环需要比从单个接触点收集数据的孤立测量工具更复杂的方法。从以客户为中心的数据中释放价值需要一个分析平台，该平台可以集成、提取和综合来自整个软件堆栈的数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;具有敏捷、直观分析功能的客户关系管理 (CRM) 技术可以产生结果远远超出了管理人员在其组织范围内的画面设置中所看到的。 360 度全方位的业务视图使您能够根据精细的细节做出更大的决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据传统 KPI 来判断您对成功的衡量可能会导致团队有动力执行积极的销售策略以实现目标他们的目标，这可能会破坏良好的客户关系。用 CPI 补充这些指标培养了一种不同类型的问责制，鼓励团队将客户满意度放在首位——这可以带来更好的保留率和更多收入。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size : 11.0pt;&quot;>;The Experience of Customer Experience&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;永远记住，客户体验就是：一种体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;消费者不太感兴趣你的品牌比你。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2019/11/21/consumers-are-hungry-for-an-experience-based-connection-with-your-brand/?sh= 2974384358fe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;他们专注于自己的体验&lt;/a>;。要真正衡量您的品牌对他们生活的影响，您需要审视各个接触点并评估他们的整体体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这不仅仅是数字，但了解您是否触及的唯一方法标记带有数据。您的分析工具和流程需要足够灵活，以帮助您衡量和提供真实的体验，从而培养持久的客户关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm .com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;探索&lt;/a>; Zoho CRM 的直观分析如何帮助您提供持久的客户价值。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovering Where ChatGPT Can Create Value for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_4896946.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然 ChatGPT 影响的速度、规模和范围可能是独一无二的，但潜在的现象一种正在改变商业和社会的大部分领域的新兴技术 &amp;#8212;不是。但是利用新兴技术的力量需要一种新的方法。与设计思维等传统创新方法不同，ChatGPT 提出了根本不同的挑战，因为没有明确的问题需要解决、用户痛点需要缓解或 KPI 需要实现。事实上，ChatGPT 似乎可以解决几乎任何行业、领域或环境中的问题。因此，使用它需要一种不同的技能：涌现性思维，这涉及在没有完全理解需要解决的问题的情况下产生创新想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当 OpenAI 发布其旗舰产品时去年 11 月的产品 ChatGPT，仅用了四天就达到了 100 万用户，两个月就达到了 1 亿用户，超过 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/chatgpt-sets-record- fastest-growing-user-base-analyst-note-2023-02-01/&quot;>;比任何其他科技巨头快 75%&lt;/a>;。 ChatGPT 继续快速发展，最初是一个仅响应用户提示的 AI 聊天机器人。现在，它包括分析数据和解释图像等功能，让从高中生到高级管理人员的每个人都争先恐后地学习 ChatGPT，以便他们能够以新的和富有成效的方式使用它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然速度、规模和 ChatGPT 的影响范围可能是独一无二的，但潜在的现象——一种正在改变大部分商业和社会的新兴技术——却并非如此。但是利用新兴技术的力量需要一种新的方法。与&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/why-design-thinking-works&quot;>;设计思维&lt;/a>;等传统创新方法不同，ChatGPT 提出了根本不同的挑战，因为没有明确的问题需要解决，用户要缓解的痛点，或要实现的 KPI。事实上，ChatGPT 似乎可以解决几乎任何行业、领域或环境中的问题。因此，使用它需要不同的技能：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/326964001_An_Integrated_Model_of_Dynamic_Problem_Solving_Within_Organizational_Constraints&quot;>;紧急思维&lt;/a>;，这涉及在没有完全理解需要解决的问题的情况下产生创新想法&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们两个人（Johnathan 和 Jennifer）最近进行了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886923001289&quot;>;研究&lt;/ a>; 表明这种创新风格的主要思维过程是从理解技术的核心功能开始，&lt;em>;然后&lt;/em>;探索如何使用它来解决不同领域的问题。涌现思维的其他特征包括在不了解成功标准的情况下评估想法、在几乎没有准备或计划的情况下即兴发挥想法，以及改变项目的目标结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些活动往往与促进效率和改进的良好商业实践背道而驰。可靠性，它们甚至可能违反设计思维的一些核心原则，即需要确定一个明确的用户问题来解决，&lt;em>;&lt;/em>; 产生解决方案的想法。然而，在尝试利用 ChatGPT（或任何其他新兴技术）进行创新时，它们也很重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多公司已经开始将 ChatGPT 集成到他们的产品、流程和服务中。通过分析这种新兴的创新格局，我们为领导者确定了三种新兴思维途径，它们可以帮助增加成功实施 ChatGPT 的机会，同时避免潜在的陷阱。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;途径 1：利用当前价值主张&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第一个途径涉及使用 ChatGPT 进一步利用公司已经提供给客户的价值主张。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/instacart-could-do-worse-than-incinerating-32-bln-2023-03-01/&quot;>;Instacart 已发展到 25 亿美元通过专注于为居家客户提供快速、可靠且负担得起的杂货配送服务这一核心价值主张，提高年收入&lt;/a>;。最近，他们&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instacart.com/company/updates/instacart-chatgpt/&quot;>;推出了 ChatGPT 插件&lt;/a>;，旨在通过提高速度和效率来加强这一价值主张在线订购杂货。有了这个插件，客户可以收到准备饭菜的建议，一旦他们找到自己喜欢的东西，ChatGPT 将创建一个新的 Instacart 订单，自动添加所有必要的成分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了追求这条创新之路，从使用 ChatGPT 开始，不要将其针对任何特定的客户问题。这个思考过程可能具有挑战性，因为大多数业务培训都教会我们成为战略思考者，并在花任何时间开发解决方案之前验证客户问题的重要性。然而，从这样的战略目标入手实际上会让我们看不到 ChatGPT 在新的和有价值的应用程序方面的潜力。相反，请以开放的心态开始，深入使用该工具以了解其核心功能。一旦你有了这种理解，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048733320301463&quot;>;人类的自然认知就会接管&lt;/a>;并开始与你可能会遇到的任何相关问题建立联系be aware of.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, one of the core functions of ChatGPT is to interpret and generate natural language text that provides human-like responses to a wide variety of questions, prompts, and requests. Companies can use this function to enhance existing features of products or services that focus specifically on text-based interactions with customers. For instance, the product-management tool Notion now provides customers with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.notion.so/product/ai&quot;>;immediate access to ChatGPT&lt;/a>; at the tap of the spacebar, which activates a prompt to receive an AI response that can be immediately integrated into existing tasks and workflows. As the functions of ChatGPT continue to grow, new possibilities will emerge for how it can be used to further enhance value propositions across a wider range of companies and contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 2: Expanding the Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A second pathway uses ChatGPT to expand a company&#39;s value proposition by solving new problems for customers in a way that complements their current offering. For example, Khan Academy was created in 2006 with the mission of providing all students with a free, world-class education. They&#39;ve since grown to nearly 20 million users per month, primarily by offering short online videos that start with a blank canvas and get filled with colorful, hand-written text. Recently, they integrated ChatGPT into their platform &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.khanacademy.org/sal-khans-2023-ted-talk-ai-in-the-classroom-can-transform-education/&quot;>;by creating a personalized AI tutor called Khanmigo&lt;/a>;. This tool not only helps students by guiding them through online videos and practice questions more effectively, but it can also help teachers by explaining teaching methods and designing lesson plans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can follow the same pathway by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/335242871_Matthew_A_Cronin_and_Jeffrey_Loewenstein_The_Craft_of_Creativity&quot;>;clearly defining your perspective and learning how to change it&lt;/a>;. For emergent thinking, this first involves breaking down a value proposition into three core elements:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;The goals customers are trying to accomplish&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The context in which customers are trying to accomplish those goals&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The specific target demographic of the customers&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once defined, the next step is to assess how ChatGPT&#39;s core functions (see Pathway 1) can help expand each element in new directions. For example, Khan Academy originally focused on &lt;em>;helping&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;K–12 students&lt;/em>; (target demographic) &lt;em>;learn topics at a self-guided pace&lt;/em>; (goal), &lt;em>;done&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;completely online &lt;/em>;(context). Using ChatGPT, they expanded this goal for students by facilitating online learning either through self-guided practice or via an AI tutor, and they also expanded the target demographic to include teachers, helping them accomplish new goals that were not previously possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This two-step definition and expansion process offers a complementary skillset to design thinking, which typically encourages people to think of many different solutions before converging on one to implement. With emergent thinking, however, you apply those same &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/better-brainstorming&quot;>;brainstorming techniques&lt;/a>; to the problem, rather than the solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During this process, it&#39;s key to maintain an open mind and avoid settling on a problem too quickly, which may be particularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/228198146_Performance_Pressure_as_a_Double-Edged_Sword_Enhancing_Team_Motivation_While_Undermining_the_Use_of_Team_Knowledge&quot;>;challenging to do in conditions of uncertainty&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has unleashed an unprecedented level of pressure on companies to act quickly, or else suffer dramatic consequences for their future survival. However, research shows it&#39;s also possible to &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/jpo/article-abstract/7/1/2/5707381&quot;>;withstand these pressures and explore a wider range of innovation options&lt;/a>;. To do that, work with trusted collaborators so you can navigate ambiguity more effectively and take greater risks together.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 3: Exploring a New Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pathway is based on using ChatGPT to explore a completely new value proposition that customers may not even know they need yet. Although this may run counter to traditional methods for innovation, it also aligns with common advice for creating breakthroughs. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/1998-05-25/steve-jobs-theres-sanity-returning&quot;>;when Steve Jobs was asked&lt;/a>; whether Apple did any market research when developing the iMac, he responded: “It&#39;s really hard to design products by focus groups. A lot of times, people don&#39;t know what they want until you show it to them.” This wisdom seems to have been fully embraced by OpenAI, which released ChatGPT to the public and is now discovering countless ways it can be used in various contexts to accomplish new and unforeseen goals. This pathway for innovation represents the purest form of emergent thinking, which has the greatest uncertainty and therefore must also be pursued with the greatest caution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The main challenge comes when trying to converge on a single problem to focus on out of the many dozens identified when brainstorming different goals, contexts, and target demographics (see Pathway 2). When organizations have relatively clearer value propositions — such as increasing the speed of online ordering at Instacart or improving the quality of online education at Khan Academy — it can be easier to filter out problems that seem far-fetched or unlikely to reflect valuable customer needs. However, when customer needs are still unknown and emerging along with the technology, it becomes difficult for teams to agree on a shared direction to pursue. This becomes especially challenging when trying to include the diverse perspectives that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/smarter-collaboration-a-new-approach-to-breaking-down-barriers-and-transforming-work/10535&quot;>;fundamental to innovation&lt;/a>;, because team members can pull the project in different directions &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Extreme-Teaming-Lessons-Cross-Sector-Leadership/dp/1786354500&quot;>;despite their best intentions to collaborate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help overcome these challenges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2343944&quot;>;identify a clear and coherent analogy&lt;/a>; that summarizes the core value proposition. For example, Tome is a startup that&#39;s using ChatGPT to help customers create better presentations out of online documents, videos, and digital content. However, instead of highlighting all the specific benefits they can provide, they&#39;ve described their product as an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20230427180425/https:/beta.tome.app/&quot;>;AI storytelling partner&lt;/a>;.” This simple concept helps integrate many different features into a coherent product experience so that both developers and customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/234021855_When_Is_a_New_Thing_a_Good_Thing_Technological_Change_Product_Form_Design_and_Perceptions_of_Value_for_Product_Innovations&quot;>;easily understand its value&lt;/a>;. By creating an analogy for your product, you can avoid wasting valuable resources creating features that might not support the core value proposition, and you can help customers develop a clear mental model of the various features and why they can be useful.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ChatGPT is an unprecedented technology that has potential to unlock value for millions of customers across many industries. However, pursuing these rewards also comes with considerable risks, as we&#39;re all entering uncharted territory with AI, and we must learn how to use it effectively so it can be leveraged for positive rather than negative outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Build Upon the Legacy of Your Family Business &mdash; and Make It Your Own]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_1009603322.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Sean Murphy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Family companies often have a strong sense of history and tradition. Although these legacies can create advantages, they sometimes leave next-generation leaders feeling handcuffed or constrained by the way their ancestors ran things. To overcome that, they should seek to reformulate the company&amp;#8217;s story in a way that creates advantages for the present.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Founded by Henry Ford &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/about/history.html&quot;>;in 1903&lt;/a>;, the Ford Motor Company rocketed to success by mass-producing reliable, low-priced automobiles. When Henry&#39;s son, &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/articles/history/edsel-ford-biography.html&quot;>;Edsel&lt;/a>;, took the helm in 1918, he championed a different strategy for a new era. He sought to replace the Model T — iconic but outdated — with a more modern design geared to high-end and foreign markets, and later embraced compromise with labor amid the suffering of the Great Depression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But Henry could not let go of Ford&#39;s origin story, undermining his son at every turn. The result was declining sales and years of labor strife that left the company on the brink of collapse by the 1940s. It was only the efforts of Edsel&#39;s son, the more forceful &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.automotivehalloffame.org/honoree/henry-ford-ii/&quot;>;Henry Ford II&lt;/a>;, that saved the auto giant from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In family enterprise, generational transitions often pit one narrative against another: tradition versus innovation, continuity versus change. Indeed, when older generations craft painstaking succession plans or build elaborate constraints into trusts or shareholder agreements, they are really constructing a story: about the values and life lessons that helped them succeed, and that they hope will do the same for their children. Younger generations, however, must often adapt this narrative to their own goals and values, along with the changing world around them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to reconcile conflicting narratives can spell ruin for a family business or the waste of a financial legacy, as it nearly did for the Fords. To avoid this fate, families need to think differently about the stories they tell.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The value of critical distance&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Conventional wisdom holds that family heritage, like wealth and reputation, “belongs” to the older generation. In this telling, succeeding generations are merely stewards or caretakers. They are given an inheritance or entrusted with the family business — and then charged with not frittering it away or screwing it up. Framed this way, a legacy can feel more like a burden than a gift.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, it&#39;s not as simple as that. Research suggests that younger generations &lt;em>;do&lt;/em>; value their family heritage, especially as a source of traditions more motivating than money alone, and are motivated to preserve it. According to a 2021 &lt;a href=&quot;https://home.kpmg/content/dam/kpmg/ca/pdf/2022/02/who-are-the-guardians-of-family-legacy-report-en.pdf&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; of 300 Canadian business owners by the Family Enterprise Foundation, nearly 90% of next-generation family business leaders believe it is important to preserve a legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But younger generations also want something more from that heritage: a sense of purpose, a collective identity for the family, the seeds of new entrepreneurial gambits, permission to go their own way. And as our own &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0894486520941944?journalCode=fbra&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows, next-generation leaders are uniquely positioned to find what they are looking for in the family story.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Older generations often identify closely with the family or the family business, which can actually obstruct key learnings from the past. Eager to protect the family&#39;s reputation, they may downplay scandal or setback rather than learn from it. By contrast, our analysis of 94 family businesses shows that younger generations tend to have more critical distance from the family story. This lets them grapple with its difficult chapters and respond appropriately, whether by making amends for past misdeeds or by reforming business practices going forward. It also frees them to draw insights from their story that can fuel innovation and sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Legacy as a source of purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How, then, can the next generation build on their family legacy while recasting it as their own? Our research and experience suggest four strategies for next-generation leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Seek out role models in the family story.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some next-generation leaders hesitate to embark on risky new ventures outside the traditional scope of the family business. Locating exemplars in the family story can legitimize a new way forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One third-generation CEO used this approach to advance his vision for a more sustainable enterprise. Fredo Arias-King, head of Mexican pine resin producer Pinosa Group, had lamented the disappearance of Mexico&#39;s ancient pine forests that threatened both the industry and the communities that depend on it. Then he stumbled onto the published speeches of his grandfather, company founder José Antonio Arias Álvarez, who had preached environmental stewardship. “I don&#39;t think he could have known just how devastated the forest would eventually become,” said Arias-King, “but somehow my grandfather knew that planting trees would become extremely important.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Affirmed by his grandfather&#39;s words, Arias-King helped found &lt;a href=&quot;https://ejidoverde.com/about-us/&quot;>;Ejido Verde&lt;/a>;, a nonprofit that would later become an independent, for-profit enterprise. By making no-interest loans to farmers and communities, with pine resin as the means of repayment, the organization promotes reforesting through new pine plantations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;2. Forge an identity beyond the founder-entrepreneur.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to revere the family&#39;s wealth creator. For the two adult grandchildren of one founder-entrepreneur — a private equity pioneer who rose from poverty to become one of America&#39;s richest people — that was the problem. They wanted their own children, beneficiaries of a generation-skipping trust, to know the person behind the legacy that would pass to them. So they engaged one of us (John Seaman) to probe beyond the classic rags-to-riches tale they had heard growing up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The founder, they learned, was a gifted yet deeply troubled man. This more nuanced understanding enabled the two generations to have a frank conversation about the issues raised by their ancestor&#39;s life: the obligations of a business to its workers and communities; the consequences of untreated mental illness; and the unfair burden often shouldered by women in wealthy families.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This conversation, in turn, led members of the fourth generation, all in their twenties, to rethink their roles in the family enterprise. One set aside her qualms about joining the family business and put herself on a path to succeed her father as president, but with a determination to nudge the company&#39;s private equity portfolio toward impact investing. Another resolved to pursue her own entrepreneurial dreams outside of the business, rooted in progressive values that were in stark contrast with her great-grandfather&#39;s. Still another joined the board of the family foundation, where she helped steer its grant-making toward her generation&#39;s individual passions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By seeing their founder-entrepreneur in human terms, the family&#39;s younger generation was able to move beyond hero worship to forge their own identities — which promised to make them responsible owners &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;stewards of their ancestor&#39;s wealth and the business that created it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3. Reckon with past wrongs to find a new path forward.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many families have skeletons in the closet —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/how-companies-can-address-their-historical-transgressions&quot;>;scandal or wrongdoing&lt;/a>; they have long concealed or downplayed. (Henry Ford&#39;s history of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/americanexperience/features/henryford-antisemitism/&quot;>;antisemitism&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/how-the-ford-motor-company-won-a-battle-and-lost-ground-45814533/&quot;>;violent confrontations&lt;/a>; with unions are examples of this.) The willingness to confront these darker chapters, it turns out, can be a powerful motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was the case for the Reimann family, owners of consumer goods conglomerate JAB Holding Company and one of Germany&#39;s richest families. The three adult children of Albert Reimann Jr., who ran the company in the 1930s and 1940s, knew they had been born of their father&#39;s affair with an employee, Emilie Landecker. They also knew that Emilie&#39;s Jewish father, Alfred, had been murdered by the Nazis. But it was not until 2019, when they commissioned research on the company, that a more sinister secret emerged: their father and paternal grandfather were themselves ardent believers in Nazi race theory who abused forced laborers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It was the younger generation — Albert Jr.&#39;s grandchildren — who were most adamant about reckoning with this secret. “When I read of the atrocities…sanctioned by my grandfather, I felt like throwing up,” recalled Martin Reimann. “I cannot claim that I was very interested in politics before…But after what happened, I changed my mind.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the insistence of Martin&#39;s generation, the Reimanns paid compensation to former forced laborers and their families. But they did not stop there. They refocused their family foundation on combating antisemitism and strengthening democratic institutions. They also renamed the foundation in honor of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alfredlandecker.org/en&quot;>;Alfred Landecker&lt;/a>;, making him the narrative driver behind the more fundamental change they sought. Far from an isolated act of corporate atonement, then, this was an attempt by the next generation to use lessons from their family heritage to build a more just future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;4. Leverage the family story as a source of competitive advantage.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For some family business entrepreneurs, the next venture can begin with a step back. So it was for British restaurateurs (and sisters) Helen and Lisa Tse, whose family heritage empowered their rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their grandmother, Lily Kwok, had emigrated from Hong Kong in 1956 and settled in Manchester, where she and her daughter Mabel built one of Britain&#39;s first Chinese restaurants. But the business eventually went bankrupt, the victim of racism and Chinese gangs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The story might have ended there. Instead, Helen and Lisa picked up the threads of their family narrative and carried it forward. Abandoning successful professional careers, they established their own Manchester restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sweetmandarin.com/&quot;>;Sweet Mandarin&lt;/a>;, in 2004. But the restaurant only took off when Helen published a best-selling memoir about her grandmother. With this narrative platform, the sisters branched out into other endeavors, like cookbooks and cookery classes, tied to their own life stories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the Tse sisters, family heritage proved to be a source of competitive advantage. By recovering an immigrant&#39;s tale with universal appeal, they gained acceptance outside of their own ethnic communities. And by situating themselves in an entrepreneurial tradition spanning three generations, they created a sense of longevity that evoked quality and trustworthiness, even as they also innovated new products alongside recipes inherited from their grandmother.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Family legacy is not a monologue; it&#39;s a dialogue, a collective story that belongs to the whole family. When families think of legacy in these terms, they empower younger generations to harness that story to their own purposes, drawing strength from their elders. Legacy, in short, becomes not a burden but a blessing — one that can help families sustain wealth and purpose long into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Identify the Right Strategic Goals for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_670123874.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;cyano66/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In setting strategic objectives, companies usually end up with a list of worthy but vague aspirations. The secret to getting a list of clearly defined and measurable objectives is to anchor them in what you, as a company&amp;#8217;s leaders, want to get from your stakeholders. This leads you to defining desired behavioral outcomes, even fairly obvious ones like buying more. The debate can then move to thinking about how to trigger that behavior, and progress toward these outcomes can be described in measures that are in dollars, like revenue; quantities, like units sold; or percentages, like market share. Thinking in this way sounds prosaic, even obvious, but it is an effective way of getting a management team to think clearly about what they need to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann is the CEO of my country&#39;s largest independent, not-for-profit aged-care provider, offering residential aged care, retirement living, and at-home support. It was established well over a hundred years ago and is set in many of its ways. One of these is how strategic objective-setting is conducted. But Ann&#39;s not happy with the process. I asked her, “Why not?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;She explained. “When we get together to discuss our future direction as a business, we invariably get to the point where we need to write down our objectives. If we&#39;re using a facilitator, and we usually do, that person will walk over to a flipchart or whiteboard and write &#39;Objectives&#39; at the top. Then everyone piles in brainstorming to produce a list that&#39;s far too long.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“And you whittle that list down?” I asked.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Yes,” Ann continued. “The discussion and arm-wrestling then start with the aim of reducing the items to about half a dozen. After some considerable time, my exhausted and frustrated colleagues are only too happy to move on to the next agenda item.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann explained how her team was usually not content with the result. “Nor am I,” she added, “because invariably the &#39;Objectives&#39; list contains a hodgepodge of activities, nice-to-haves, and vague statements of intent.” Ann showed me her latest result:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;To become an employer of choice.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To grow the business by opening additional centers.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To maintain stability in resident and client care.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To manage risks and crises effectively.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To secure compliance with regulatory authorities.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To transform operations by adopting additional technology.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Maybe your own endeavors have produced a similar list. You might be wondering: What&#39;s wrong with this? The answer is: Plenty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Any strategy she comes up with will have to specify what the company can do to meet the needs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;each key stakeholder group&lt;/a>;: residents, clients, employees, suppliers, shareholders, and the community. This means that her business will have to take a &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the-volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;position on the factors important to each of those groups&lt;/a>;. For instance, Ann&#39;s management team must set policy on working conditions, pay, organization culture, and so on for employees. What should guide these decisions? And how will Ann know if the decisions are progressing the organization? How will she measure this?&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The answers should be her list of strategic objectives. But Ann&#39;s hodgepodge doesn&#39;t deliver a clear line of sight between the business&#39;s competitive stance for each key stakeholder group and the results. How can you tell if a strategy is working? It&#39;s as though the list of objectives exists in a black hole.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Shift Your Thinking About Objective-Setting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The trick to breaking away is to flip your perspective and ask what your organization wants &lt;em>;from&lt;/em>; its key stakeholders. (This comes as an “aha” moment for most managers.) These will be your strategic objectives. For example, consider revenue from customers, innovation from employees, and support from the community. Your thinking must shift to be outside-in if you are to produce successful strategic objectives. If you picture organization objective-setting this way, you can see how it can be broken into a stakeholder-by-stakeholder exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 1: Identify a behavioral outcome for each stakeholder group.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;To illustrate, let me share a story. One CEO I advise, Stuart, heads up a mutual bank with “members.” I ran a workshop for him and his managers. We identified the credit union&#39;s key stakeholders, one of which was, naturally, members. To break through the traditional brainstorming hodgepodge, I asked the group a seemingly simple question: “What do you want your members to do?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This came as a surprisingly fresh approach to the group and required them to think more deeply. After some discussion, we got this: “To get members to borrow more and to get potential members to become members.” I explained how I call this a &lt;em>;behavioral outcome&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 2: Convert behavioral outcomes into organization objectives.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I then led Stuart&#39;s group to the second step, which is to convert this behavioral outcome to an &lt;em>;organization objective.&lt;/em>; This usually starts with “to increase” or “to decrease.” After careful consideration and debate, the group agreed to: “To increase revenue from current and future members.” Notice “future.” This will be driven by positioning on the strategic factors relevant to members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Why didn&#39;t I just start there at the second step? The reason is that invariably the process falls back into becoming a hodgepodge. Identifying a behavioral outcome for each key stakeholder group first anchors organization objectives, which then become clear and measurable&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 3: Identify measures.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This brings me to the third step: identifying &lt;em>;measures&lt;/em>;, a short list of which is usually referred to as key performance indicators or KPIs. This can be tricky, as all sorts of things become labeled as KPIs in exercises like this. In the past, Stuart&#39;s organization had labeled actions by individuals and program descriptions as KPIs. So, I needed to point out that a key performance indicator is a key performance &lt;em>;measure.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The clincher for Stuart and his group came when I demonstrated that there are only three ways to measure results in business and that they can be neatly summarized by three symbols: $ (or the local currency), # (number of), and % (percentage). No one had condensed results for them in that way before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The advantage of this is that Stuart and his team now have a stakeholder-oriented objective for members that can be measured. Stuart can measure the total revenue generated by new and existing members; the number of new and existing members; and the bank&#39;s percentage of market share. Any strategies aimed at creating competitive advantage — around, for example, product range, customer service, and pricing — can be evaluated using these hard results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I do this for each of an organization&#39;s key stakeholders: customers, employees, suppliers, and so on. It always gets a management group to probe what the organization is really trying to achieve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;Your Objective-Setting Journey&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;If you want to produce clearly targeted strategy, you simply must avoid the standard practice of brainstorming to yield a list of strategic objectives. It leads to a hodgepodge of difficult-to-measure items, as Ann&#39;s experience demonstrates. Instead, rethink your journey by identifying who your key stakeholders are&amp;nbsp;— and what you want from them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This will provide you with clear and measurable outcomes that will help focus your organization&#39;s strategic positions for each of your key stakeholders. Strategic clarity will be your result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Will Working with AI Really Require?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_EdmonDeHaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Edmon de Haro; filonmar/Getty Images (chip); JulieAlexK/Getty Images (glasses)&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities, and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent. To do this effectively, they need to think about where and how this technology will be used to assist people in their work &amp;#8212; where people and machines will collaborate &amp;#8212; and where either people or AI have skills that give them a clear advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Despite concerns about machines replacing human workers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning/&quot;>;research &lt;/a>;challenges the overhyped claims of ascendant AI. In most knowledge-intensive tasks, workers will more likely find themselves augmented &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0007681318300387&quot;>;in partnership with machines&lt;/a>; than automated out of a job. Humans and machines will simultaneously collaborate and compete with one another, like a track team competing in various events. In some events, like the 100-yard dash, teammates compete against each other, but in others, such as the relay race, they work together towards a common goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In such a relationship, humans and AI systems both need distinct competitive and cooperative skills. Competitive skills refer to the unique advantages that either humans or AI possess over the other, while cooperative skills enhance the ability of humans and AI to work together effectively. To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities — and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Humans&#39; competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI may not replace workers in a human-centered workplace, but it could fundamentally transform their work. In order to remain relevant and indispensable, humans need to work &lt;em>;with &lt;/em>;and &lt;em>;against &lt;/em>;the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effectively collaborating with AI systems — working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; them — requires data-driven analytical abilities, but also understanding about the capabilities and limitations of the machines (areas where human intervention is most required), how to interpret and contextualize AI-generated insights, and the ethical considerations of AI-powered decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Data-centric skills:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the results generated by algorithms to inform and support decision-making. A &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/boost-your-teams-data-literacy&quot;>;recent survey&lt;/a>; highlighted (1) the ability to distinguish relevant data and evaluate its credibility, (2) capability to validate results by testing hypotheses through A/B testing, and (3) skill in creating and tailoring clear and comprehensible visualizations to communicate results to multiple stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AI literacy:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how algorithms work, how they can support and augment human decision-making as well as the limitations and biases that may be present in their decision-making processes. Area experts will likely take on the responsibility of developing fairness criteria for algorithmic outcomes that promote equity, especially for vulnerable populations, and continuously auditing algorithmic results against these criteria.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Algorithmic communication:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how to articulate human needs and objectives to algorithms, as well as how to interpret and explain the results generated by algorithms to others is important and &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-digital-mindset-what-it-really-takes-to-thrive-in-the-age-of-data-algorithms-and-ai/10413&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that we often err by talking to machines – even advanced AI tools – as though they were human. We do better when we recognize that we should talk to machines in specific ways that build on their strengths. For example, through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/prompt-engineering-ai-chatgpt-jobs-explained-2023-3&quot;>;“prompt engineering,”&lt;/a>; or crafting prompts to elicit most effective responses from AI systems, humans can teach AI models to produce the desired results for specific tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;People also need to hone the human-centered skills and abilities that cannot be replicated by machines — that help them work &lt;em>;against&lt;/em>; AI partners — such as those rooted in emotional intelligence (eg, communication skills for interacting with other human stakeholders), a strategic and holistic perspective, critical thinking and intuitive decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Emotional intelligence:&lt;/strong>; The ability to recognize one&#39;s own emotions and reflect on them in the context of interacting with algorithms, as well as understanding and communicating the emotional implications of algorithm-generated results. For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-chatbot-workplace-call-centers-5cd2142a?st=6fma808gi52qayz&amp;amp;reflink=article_email_share&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR0oBB-2wT03uN-8OV3kaJGNXqDPKW-ZJ_7hc8KdYMYlHPK3dCrqxJr-GcA&quot;>;human customer service agents&lt;/a>; may not solely rely on scripts or real-time advice provided by the AI agents, but instead personalize solutions by empathetically comprehending the customers&#39; requirements or feelings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Holistic and strategic thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to consider the big picture and understand how algorithmic results fit into the larger context of a problem or decision. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2153353922007507&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, algorithmic inference can inform pathologists, but they still need to consider factors such as patients&#39; medical history, lifestyle, and overall health to arrive at an informed and comprehensive diagnosis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Creativity and outside-the-box thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to think creatively and use algorithms in novel and innovative ways. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/si/en/pages/strategy-operations/articles/AI-in-marketing.html&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, AI systems are used to analyze massive consumer data and identify patterns in the interests and behavior of a target audience, but it is the creative thinking of marketers that will craft a message that resonates with the audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Critical and ethical thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to critically assess machine inferences, and to understand the ethical implications and responsibilities associated with using algorithms, including privacy and accountability. As generative AI such as ChatGPT are increasingly integrated into various products, experts in different business domains are needed to work alongside these systems to continuously address &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/chatbots-got-big-and-their-ethical-red-flags-got-bigger/&quot;>;potential false or biased information &lt;/a>;to which these systems are prone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI&#39;s competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It is not only humans that must acquire new capabilities. While AI systems are rapidly expanding their competitive abilities over humans, they still need to improve their cooperative skills in order to be widely adopted by organizations. In particular, the lack of explainability remains a challenge in high-stakes decisions, hindering accountability and compliance with legal requirements. For example, if the AI&#39;s decision-making process remains opaque to medical professionals, it will impede the adoption of these systems in healthcare, even if these systems deliver near-optimal decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To work effectively with human partners, AI systems need skills such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;NLP (Natural Language Processing):&lt;/strong>; The ability to process, analyze, understand and mimic human language. Systems like ChatGPT excel at interacting with humans because they make it easy for people to ask questions and express themselves in a natural way, including expressing emotions like excitement, frustration, or surprise. The reality, however, is that these systems are far from &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4213593&quot;>;sentient&lt;/a>;. Situations that go beyond a function are best done by a human or with human supervision. For example, AI can analyze and reveal patterns in healthcare data, but it should not replace a physician&#39;s role in providing individualized care to patients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Explainability:&lt;/strong>; The ability to provide humans with clear and understandable explanations of its decision-making process and results. The inherent inscrutability of deep-learning AI is an ongoing challenge that requires multiple solutions, including building an &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/when-and-why-you-should-explain-how-your-ai-works&quot;>;“explainability framework”&lt;/a>; that addresses the risks of AI black boxes to specific industries and organizations. Technological solutions may also involve adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7768142/&quot;>;explainability engines&lt;/a>;, which offer human-readable explanations for AI &#39;systems&#39; decisions and predictions, particularly for critical areas like healthcare and finance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Adaptability and personalization:&lt;/strong>; The ability to learn from previous interactions and personalize responses based on individual users. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3252218/cortana-explained-why-microsofts-virtual-assistant-is-wired-for-business.html&quot;>;personal intelligent assistants&lt;/a>; are growing in importance in helping people tackle information and communication overload. By analyzing a user&#39;s activities, these assistants work collaboratively with workers in an individualized manner, enhancing their productivity in areas such as time management, meeting organization, and communication assistance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Context awareness:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the context in which an interaction is taking place and respond accordingly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2021/03/30/how-chat-commerce-is-changing-e-commerce/?sh=570d87f1142c&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, in e-commerce websites, chatbots that present context awareness can analyze a user&#39;s previous inquiries and purchase history to offer solutions or recommendations that are more pertinent to the customer&#39;s needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI systems continue to present unique competitive advantages, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Analytical capacities:&lt;/strong>; The ability to perform complex calculations, process large amounts of data, and identify patterns and relationships within the data. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/louiscolumbus/2019/08/01/ai-is-predicting-the-future-of-online-fraud-detection/?sh=6cdf5e3174f5&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, AI systems are becoming more competent at detecting fraudulent transactions in massive datasets of credit card transactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Generativity:&lt;/strong>; The ability to generate novel and unique outputs that are not simply reproductions of existing data. Using large models and neural networks to analyze patterns, generative AI is transforming the creation of image, text, and even music that resembles those created by human experts. These systems automated content generation, improve content quality, increase content variety, and offer personalized content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Performance at scale:&lt;/strong>; The ability to scale operations efficiently, handle a large number of real-time transactions and support large-scale applications without sacrificing performance. For example, AI systems have demonstrated superior ability to process &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/financial%20services/our%20insights/ai%20powered%20decision%20making%20for%20the%20bank%20of%20the%20future/ai-powered-decision-making-for-the-bank-of-the-future.pdf&quot;>;thousands of credit card applications&lt;/a>; real-time or offer “&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/algorithmic-management-the-role-of-ai-in-managing-workforces/&quot;>;algorithmic management&lt;/a>;” of thousands of Uber drivers and riders simultaneously, creating a structured and consistent operational framework at an unprecedented scale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Racing with and against the machines&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The challenge for organizations trying to build a strategy for using new and more AI tools lies in designing organizational systems that effectively balance the competitive and cooperative skills of humans and AI. Organizations that seek to strike this balance should consider the following:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Democratize data to foster the continuous development of competitive human and machine skills. &lt;/strong>;AI systems can generate data insights at scale and detect patterns often missed by the human eye, but translating that competitiveness into business growth and agility requires the very human skills of strategic thinking and creativity. To enable this type of collaboration, companies should democratize access to data throughout all levels of their organization. Nearly every role within your organization should be working alongside data analytics to inform how to make the workflows more efficient, make data-driven decisions and ultimately inform a better understanding of how to service the end customer. The more data visibility AI can give your workforce, the greater ability for humans to apply and develop their uniquely competitive skills.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Look outside your own organization&#39;s walls for cooperative human skills. &lt;/strong>;A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/operations/articles/future-of-gig-economy-shared-services-delivery-model.html&quot;>;Deloitte study&lt;/a>; found that nearly half (49%) of traditional workers — full-time employees — updated their skills more than a year ago or have never engaged in skills development, whereas 60% of the alternative workforce — defined as gig workers, freelancers, independent workers, and crowd workers — updated their skills within the past six months. In fact, 44% of alternative workers at large organizations hold a postgraduate degree according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upwork.com/resources/enterprise-companies-need-to-know-freelancers&quot;>;new research by Upwork&lt;/a>;. This is likely due to the fact that most technical skill sets, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/EPYMNBJA&quot;>;research by IBM&lt;/a>;, experience a half-life of 2.5 years. And, according to Upwork&#39;s database, the top in-demand skills are technical and related to web, mobile and software development. If your organization is struggling to keep up with cooperative human skills to work alongside machines, it may be time to engage a broader ecosystem of skills outside your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Don&#39;t let geography limit the skills your company is hiring for.&lt;/strong>; The pandemic ushered in a new era of work as many organizations learned work could be done remotely. Technical work can be done almost anywhere in the world as machines have largely made geography irrelevant to finding the skills you need to cooperate with machines. Enabling remote work strategies will ensure your organization is equipped to capture the ever-changing talent landscape and help you win in the race with and against the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By focusing on the balance of these skills, organizations can reap the benefits of an infinity loop between AI and human competitive skills. In this balance, humans may work toward “coopetition” as an arrangement where parties engage in both cooperative and competitive behavior. In such a relationship with AI systems, humans may leverage both the partnership with machines and their own competitive edge against the machine. This relationship helps to maintain their relevance and indispensability as algorithms are increasingly working as team members or even managers (ie, algorithmic management).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This formulation offered here helps shape the future of education and skill development, by emphasizing the importance of focusing on skills that give humans a competitive advantage over machines, rather than those that we have already lost to machines. For example, the use of calculators and spell checkers no longer serve as our advantage as we surrendered these tasks to technology long ago.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Global Information Sharing Can Help Stop Cybercrime]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_3858085.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The Cybercrime Atlas is an initiative hosted by the World Economic Forum&amp;#8217;s (WEF) Partnership Against Cybercrime. While it&amp;#8217;s still in prototype stages, it&amp;#8217;s being designed to provide a platform for academic analysts, cybersecurity companies, national and international law enforcement agencies, and global businesses to share knowledge about the cybercriminal ecosystem. At its core, the Atlas project is a database about cybercrime. Information could come from government alerts, cryptocurrency analysis companies, platform providers, court records, and publicly available materials &amp;#8212; anything the analysts can identify that might be relevant to understanding the entirety of the criminal ecosystem. Analysts could then use this database to generate multiple different views or maps of various parts of the cybercriminal ecosystem. For example, one analyst might be interested in ransom payments and could use Atlas to help understand how illicit funds are moving. Another might be interested in identifying the platforms that appear to host a large number of criminal actors. Another &amp;#8220;map&amp;#8221; or view might focus on the relationships between different criminal groups. By creating an international information repository based on public data and voluntarily shared information, cybersecurity practitioners can create a tool that will enable them to fight cybercrime more effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Cybercrime is big business. While reliable statistics are difficult to come by, estimates of the global cost of cybercrimes range from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/chart/28878/expected-cost-of-cybercrime-until-2027/&quot;>;trillions to tens of trillions of dollars annually&lt;/a>;. Regardless of the precise figure, cybercrime clearly drains significant resources from the global economy and poses a substantial threat to global security and prosperity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Why has the problem grown so large? Cybercrime has some characteristics that make it difficult for governments to fight:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;It has an inherently transnational structure, while law enforcement operates within national borders.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Some nation-states harbor and protect cybercriminals, while others turn a blind eye, and still others lack the capacity to combat the problem.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Defenders lack systemic knowledge and insights regarding the full extent of cybercriminal activities, which in turn inhibits effective targeting.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Cybercrime groups have evolved from two or three people working together into large, distributed organizations with extensive, complex, and sophisticated infrastructures that are difficult for any single entity to understand.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The global internet&#39;s staggeringly large data volume makes it difficult to separate the malicious activity from the “noise.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The internet allows criminals to scale in the same way that legitimate businesses do, but it also allows them to obfuscate their true numbers, locations, and identities.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Overcoming these challenges will require innovation and adaptation in many areas, such as updating international legal regimes and making operational collaboration between the public and private sectors a regular occurrence. Another key area for innovation includes understanding the nature of the criminal ecosystem.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Understanding the Cybercrime Ecosystem&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While it may seem strange to apply the term “ecosystem” to crime, it aptly describes the way that cyber criminals operate. Cybercriminals are no longer just disaffected individuals wearing hoodies and living in their parents&#39; basements. Instead, they tend to operate in loose, distributed groups and exist within a large network of suppliers, coders, buyers, financiers, and partners. Few criminals conduct an entire operation from beginning to end without any support from someone else. While this complexity provides substantial benefits in terms of efficiency and effectiveness, it also creates an opportunity for law enforcement and defenders, if we can take advantage of it. By relying on an extensive ecosystem to carry out their activities, cybercriminals have made themselves more vulnerable to disruption.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;Managing Cyber Risk&quot; dek=&quot;Exploring the challenges and the solutions.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;Managing Cyber Risk&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Exploring the challenges and the solutions. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s where the Cybercrime Atlas project comes in. The Atlas is an initiative hosted by the World Economic Forum&#39;s (WEF) Partnership Against Cybercrime, designed to mitigate some of the characteristics that make cybercrime difficult to combat. Specifically, the Atlas initiative will provide a platform for academic analysts, cybersecurity companies, national and international law enforcement agencies, and global businesses to share knowledge about the cybercriminal ecosystem. During its initial standup, the WEF will host the secretariat for the project, supported by Fortinet, Microsoft, Paypal, and Santander. Other organizations, such as the Cyber Threat Alliance, will also support the initiative through in-kind donations of time and capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Mapping the Cybercrime Ecosystem &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At its core, the Atlas project is a database about cybercrime. While a database may seem somewhat pedestrian or anticlimactic compared to the size of the task, the power of correlating and combining information should not be underestimated. Further, the information in this database will not just be random bits of data, nor will it be limited to the technical indicators of compromise that cybersecurity companies usually share. Instead, it will bring in a wide range of data types from many different types of sources. Information could come from government alerts, cryptocurrency analysis companies, platform providers, court records, and publicly available materials — anything the analysts can identify that might be relevant to understanding the entirety of the criminal ecosystem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, analysts can use this database to generate multiple different views or maps of various parts of the cybercriminal ecosystem, hence the name “Atlas.” For example, one analyst might be interested in ransom payments and could use Atlas to help understand how illicit funds are moving. Another might be interested in identifying the platforms that appear to host a large number of criminal actors. Another “map” or view might focus on the relationships between different criminal groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These different views will support a wide array of activities, from the private, non-profit, and public sectors. A platform like Microsoft could use Atlas information to support legal action against actors abusing their services, while banks could use a payment map to try to recover stolen money. Law enforcement agencies could use an infrastructure map to identify targets for disruption or seizure.清单还在继续。 Given past experience, the Atlas project will likely support analysis we cannot yet anticipate.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These maps will have several benefits. First, they will identify the places where the criminals are most vulnerable to disruption by highlighting single points of failure. Second, since they will be based primarily on open-source information and private sector information, they will help governments target intelligence and law enforcement resources against the gaps that the private sector can&#39;t fill while avoiding areas where the private sector already has a lot of insight. Such focus would make law enforcement and intelligence collection more efficient and effective. It could even illuminate the makeup of criminal groups, making it harder for a group to seem like 1,000 people when it&#39;s really only 10. It will also provide a Rosetta Stone for understanding the various names attached to a given group by different companies, making it easier to correlate research and findings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By creating an international information repository based on public data and voluntarily shared information, cybersecurity practitioners can create a tool that will enable them to fight cybercrime more effectively. But regular businesses stand to benefit greatly from a project like the Cybercrime Atlas too. Reining in cybercrime would reduce not only the current economic burden of malicious activity like ransomware, but it would also enable businesses to continue expanding the services they offer online. Absent a change in its trajectory, the rampant criminality in cyberspace will inevitably drive some, possibly many, consumers and organizations to pull back from the digital ecosystem. It is not a law of nature that more and more activity will occur in cyberspace, and such a retrenchment is possible if we cannot make cyberspace safer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As of mid-2023, the Cybercrime Atlas is still in the prototype stage. As a leader of an information sharing organization, I have no illusions about the challenges associated with making a project like the Cybercrime Atlas successful. Yet, its foundation is strong and its promise as a tool to help defenders, law enforcement, and other analysts navigate the criminal landscape is large. Given what&#39;s at stake, we have an obligation to use every tool at our disposal to combat the pernicious threat posed by cybercrime.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[To Build a Top Performing Team, Ask for 85% Effort]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_1434391518.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anchiy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;An outdated way of thinking about peak performance is: &amp;#8220;maximum effort = maximum results.&amp;#8221; But research shows that it doesn&amp;#8217;t actually work that way in reality. Here&amp;#8217;s what actually works: The 85% rule, which counterintuitively suggests that to reach maximum output, you need to refrain from giving maximum effort. Operating at 100% effort all of the time will result in burnout and ultimately less-optimal results. While the precise number 85% may just be a rule of thumb, it&amp;#8217;sa helpful one for managers who want to create high-performance teams without burning people out.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Despite some companies&#39; attempts, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/beyond-burned-out&quot;>;we can&#39;t fix today&#39;s burnout culture with a wellness app&lt;/a>;. What it takes, instead, is a mindset and culture shift among managers and organizations everywhere.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The old management mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;An outdated way of thinking about peak performance is “maximum effort = maximum results.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/cne.920180503&quot;>;It doesn&#39;t actually work that way in reality&lt;/a>;, but many managers still believe that it does. They might talk a good game about “practicing self-care,” but their core assumptions are often more akin to a bad 1980s motivational speaker. (Think: “No pain, no gain,” “No guts, no glory,” and “Give it 110%!”)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When managers expect 80+ hours a week from people while offering Friday yoga to combat stress, they unintentionally create a toxic contradiction. It&#39;s a classic example of what we call in psychology a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://dictionary.apa.org/double-bind&quot;>;double bind&lt;/a>;”: Employees can&#39;t talk about the contradiction, and they can&#39;t talk about not being able to talk about it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, many well-intended efforts to end the burnout epidemic don&#39;t actually work. If you think individual overachievers are solely to blame for exhaustion, then you&#39;ll only end up addressing the wrong problem. Consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/mhi/our-insights/addressing-employee-burnout-are-you-solving-the-right-problem&quot;>;McKinsey&#39;s research on burnout&lt;/a>;, which showed that “in all 15 countries and across all dimensions assessed, toxic workplace behavior was the biggest predictor of burnout symptoms and intent to leave by a large margin.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only does this old mindset &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; produce high performance, it also creates a downward spiral of toxicity begetting burnout begetting toxicity. What we need instead is a new management mindset, supported by data, for how to really get the best out of our people. Instead of “maximum effort = maximum results,” a better formula is: “optimal effort = maximum results.” Less effort can actually lead to more success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The new management mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s what actually works: the 85% rule. The 85% rule counterintuitively suggests that to reach maximum output, you need to refrain from giving maximum effort. Operating at 100% effort all of the time will result in burnout and ultimately less-optimal results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, when sprinters are told to accelerate to their 100% level too soon, they end up &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1260/1747-9541.6.3.479&quot;>;running a slower race overall&lt;/a>;. As Carl Lewis, who won nine Olympic gold medals, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elitetrack.com/forums/topic/carl-lewis-interview-with-info-on-tellez-training-methods/&quot;>;explains&lt;/a>;, the notion of “no pain, no gain” is ridiculous. He says, “Your training should be sensible. In many cases it is more important to rest than it is to drive yourself to the point of pain.” Lewis&#39;s coach, Tom Tellez, suggests that the peak performer in sprinting relax their jaw, face, and eyes. “Don&#39;t grit your teeth,” he advises. “If you do, that tension will run all the way down your neck and trunk to your legs.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to build a high-performing team — without burning people out&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;Create a “done for the day” time&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Where possible, managers should establish a “done for the day” time. When managers are ambiguous about the length of workdays, they risk introducing decision fatigue, diminishing returns, or even getting negative returns from their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Toxic managers see setting a reasonable hard stop for the day as impossible. A colleague told me that their boss said in no uncertain terms: “You can&#39;t get ahead here if you want to be home for dinner with your family.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transactional managers see employees having a done-for-the-day time as a necessary evil: “I suppose you need to do what you need to do.” They let people keep to the schedule begrudgingly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transformational managers insist upon a reasonable time for employees to leave work. For example, when a new employee at a private equity firm was eager to make a good impression, he stayed late. After all, he had been trained at previous companies to expect kudos for the extra effort. But this company and manager were different. When his manager saw him still sitting at his desk after everyone else had gone home, he said, “Why are you still here? We don&#39;t stay late here unless there is an absolute emergency. We want you to be fresh tomorrow morning. Please go home.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask for a little less than maximum capacity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effort and fatigue can create confusion for people regarding the quality of their performance. People can mistake the perception of maximum effort with what actually produces maximum results. However, &lt;a href=&quot;https://coachesinsider.com/track-x-country/highest-effort-doesnt-always-equal-highest-performance-article/&quot;>;the highest effort doesn&#39;t always equal the highest performance&lt;/a>;. Managers can take advantage of this by inviting team members to work a little below what they perceive to be their maximum capacity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help coach employees to get to and stay in this sweet spot, managers can ask, “What does it feel like to be at 100% intensity?” and then follow up with: “How can you keep this closer to the 85% level?” This type of&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/ptj/article-abstract/64/3/343/2727707&quot;>; perceived level of exertion&lt;/a>; is a concept used in physical rehab to prevent latent — or hidden — fatigue, but it can also be used by managers to help their employees stay in their sweet spot (see the following figure).&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357760&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/04/W230417_MCKEOWN_PERFORMANCE_85_PERCENT_RULE_EFFORT_PERFORMANCE_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask “how am I making your work more stressful than it needs to be?”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Top performers are typically already self-motivated, so managing them like everyone else will only exhaust them, leading them to become a flight risk. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://osf.io/h6qnf/&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; at the&lt;a href=&quot;https://medicine.yale.edu/childstudy/services/community-and-schools-programs/center-for-emotional-intelligence/&quot;>; Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence and the Faas Foundation&lt;/a>; of over 1,000 US employees found that 20% of employees reported being both highly engaged and having high burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This “engaged-exhausted group” were passionate about their work, but also had a high level of stress and frustration. These were the employees with the highest risk of quitting their jobs — higher even than unengaged employees. This suggests that companies may lose their most capable employees not due to a lack of engagement, but rather because of their high stress and burnout levels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To avoid this, managers can ask their top performers a simple but powerful question — “How am I making your work more stressful than it needs to be?” — and then take the necessary actions to improve upon the situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Encourage 85%-right decisions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When making decisions as a team, don&#39;t push for “100% perfect.” Let people know when an 85%-right decision is acceptable.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886901002021&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; has uncovered two distinct types of perfectionists. The first is “&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/12/the-pros-and-cons-of-perfectionism-according-to-research&quot;>;excellence-seeking&lt;/a>;” perfectionists: people who hold high standards for themselves and others. The second type is “failure-avoiding” perfectionists: people who are consistently anxious that their work is not sufficient or adequate, who fear losing the esteem of others if they fail to attain perfection.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Asking for 85%-right decisions takes unnecessary pressure off your highest-performing employees — and it keeps your team moving forward, rather than waiting for the 100%-right decision before they take action.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Watch out for high-pressure language&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As a manager, it is vital to be mindful of the language you use when communicating with your team. The use of high-pressure terms such as “ASAP,” “NEED,” or “URGENT” in emails or meetings can create excessive stress and pressure for your team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To avoid this, it&#39;s essential to foster open communication about genuine deadlines, the reasons behind them, and the potential trade-offs. Instead of expecting employees to always agree to every request, consider asking them, “What do you need to say no to in order to say yes to this?” By granting autonomy in choosing their projects, you can ensure that your &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/06/how-are-you-protecting-your-high-performers-from-burnout&quot;>;star employees maintain high performance levels while also avoiding burnout&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;End meetings 10 minutes early&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A manager shared this with me recently: “If you can be any kind of manager, be the kind who ends the meeting early.” It struck me as both funny and true.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many employees still feel like they live the “Zoom, eat, sleep, repeat” life that was so common during the pandemic. Certainly, far more meetings are now held on video than ever before. And we know that video “exhaust(s) the human mind and body” &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.stanford.edu/2021/02/23/four-causes-zoom-fatigue-solutions/&quot;>;faster than in-person meetings or just being on the phone&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/brain-research&quot;>;Research from Microsoft&#39;s Human Factors Lab&lt;/a>; found that our brains work differently when we take 10-minute breaks between meetings. That small break stops stress from building up, while back-to-back meetings decrease people&#39;s ability to focus and engage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The researchers asked 14 people to take part in video meetings while wearing electroencephalogram (EEG) equipment to monitor their brain activity. Each person participated in two different types of meeting sessions. On day one, they attended four back-to-back meetings with no breaks in between. On another day, the meetings had 10-minute breaks in between. Here&#39;s what the EEGs showed:&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357852&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/04/W230417_MCKEOWN_PERFORMANCE_85_PERCENT_RULE_BREAKS_360-2.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The cooler colors in the visual representation indicate lower stress levels from having breaks between the meetings. However, those who were deprived of breaks experienced a gradual rise in beta wave activity, indicating a buildup of stress over time, as shown by a shift in colors from cool to hot in the visual. The chart represents the relative difference in beta activity between break and no-break conditions at the beginning of each meeting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By ending meetings 10 minutes early, managers can help keep their employees out of “red brain” and keep them in “blue brain,” where they can do their best thinking.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Set your own intensity level to 85%&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s important that managers also set their &lt;em>;own&lt;/em>; minds to 85% intensity to model to their team that it&#39;s okay not to be stressed out of their minds all the time. When managers say that employees should not work late nights or on weekends, but then send emails at 2 am on Sunday morning, their actions speak louder than their words.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/07/your-bosss-work-life-balance-matters-as-much-as-your-own&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that employees look to their bosses for cues far more than many managers realize. In a curious finding, researchers found that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/intl/blog/work-matters/201005/how-often-do-you-look-at-your-boss-baboons-do-it-every-20-or-30-seconds&quot;>;baboons look to their alpha male “boss” every 20 to 30 seconds&lt;/a>;, and humans may not be so different. So, if you&#39;re going to write emails late and on weekends, at least schedule them to be sent at 9 am Monday morning.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The 85% rule may seem counterintuitive. However, in this time of ongoing, persistent burnout, it has the power of relevancy. As Dr. Stephen Ilardi, a psychologist at the University of Kansas, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Depression-Cure-6-Step-Program-without/dp/0738213888&quot;>;written&lt;/a>;, “Human beings were never designed for the poorly nourished, sedentary, indoor, sleep-deprived, socially-isolated, frenzied pace of 21st-century life.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Certainly, we can do better. Managers who adopt the 85% rule as their new mindset can help to reduce this frenzy while actually improving their team&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Powered Automation As A Route To Boosting Productivity - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/ai-powered-automation-as-a-route-to-boosting-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358514&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_AI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;How AI-powered CRMs are changing the game and solving the customer relationship challenge&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For sales and marketing teams, the residual peaks and troughs of pandemic-era business suggest a challenging future of independent buyers and mounting consumer expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The B2B buyer group is increasingly self-starting. Virtually 100% of tech buyers now want &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.trustradius.com/vendor-blog/2022-b2b-buying-disconnect-the-age-of-the-self-serve-buyer?utm_source=cision&amp;amp;utm_medium=content_syndication&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2022_06_b2bdisconnect&amp;amp;utm_term=v&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;a self-serve experience&lt;/a>;. The demand for digital sales and marketing is growing in tandem, with younger buyers most likely to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitalcommerce360.com/2023/02/20/the-stark-digital-gap-between-b2bs-older-and-younger-buyers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;digital channels to engage and to make purchases&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumer expectations for self-servicing are higher than ever, led by the standouts of customer experience in each industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales and marketing priorities have shifted, no longer going all out on growth but instead juggling &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescommunicationscouncil/2022/12/09/navigating-economic-uncertainty-three-ways-marketing-can-help-sales-in-2023/?sh=4c7845476af3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;customer retention and sustained growth&lt;/a>;. And that puts more pressure on already taxed teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this climate, sales and marketing teams need to be hyperflexible—to interact when, where, and how their customers want. And they need to prioritize personalization, tailoring experiences to meet rising expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By automating tasks and providing real-time data, with artificial intelligence (AI)–powered automation supporting a customer relationship management (CRM) platform, these teams can perform at once-unattainable levels of efficiency and growth.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Doing More with Less&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At many organizations, the customer relationship challenge is to meet new needs while legacy operations and the costs of changing those operations stand in the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But investing in a CRM with AI-enabled automation can shift an organization&#39;s repetitive tasks—composing follow-up emails, scheduling, managing socials—to clear time-sapping jobs from the schedules of employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-enabled CRMs can eliminate silos by collating data from multiple sources to offer sales and marketing teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.infoworld.com/article/3624010/3-ways-ai-improves-crm.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;actionable, data-driven guidance&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When teams can offload menial tasks, they can regain the autonomy to work on value-adding, satisfying responsibilities, such as building relationships with customers and closing deals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And this level of intelligent automation can significantly cut costs. With increased efficiency and productivity, growing businesses can hire staff who can think big and spend on automatable tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Real Relationships, Not Robots &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-powered CRM isn&#39;t all chatbots and no employees. The optimal AI- and automation-powered CRM gives its human workforce the right insights to apply as they believe best suit their customers so sales and marketing teams can offer more engaging, more satisfying experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;An AI CRM platform can strengthen relationship management in three ways:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Automation removes internal friction and accelerates processes among teams and systems, with a customer-facing payoff: connected data and reduced human error help processes go faster.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;By automatically tracking any behavioral changes in customers and prospects, sales and marketing teams can easily understand where each account is along its buyer or customer journey and support it accordingly. AI automation can take that even further, predicting sale probabilities and triggering alerts to notify teams of customers&#39; needs based on their behavior.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;It can serve the workforce with the optimal combination of insights and time. Beyond consolidating customer information into one database, an AI automation–enriched CRM can take on repetitive tasks like scheduling content or following up on low-priority prospects.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Revolutionary Relationship Management&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CRM platforms empowered by AI automation transform the way we work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A sales and marketing team that can easily access actionable insights can just as easily create custom reports and dashboards and measure operations in real time to drive sustainable growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.zoho.com/portal/en/kb/crm/zia-artificial-intelligence/zia/zia/articles/zia-overview&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;conversational AI assistant&lt;/a>; can fetch information and take dictation, providing immediate answers over voice or text chat. Beyond that, AI-powered data mining and machine learning capabilities can yield powerful insights and personalized recommendations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-augmented data can quickly reveal conversion predictions and alert teams to anomalies that might otherwise be harder or take longer to detect, such as drops in new leads or an increase in calls. These capabilities can make a significant impact: a sales and marketing team that once had to wait for reports so it could analyze them to change strategy can instead receive these updates and identify anomalies—and act on them—in real time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;New Efficiencies Without New Disruptions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales and marketing teams are under increasing pressure to achieve both great customer retention and sustained growth. Productivity is key to those efforts. But many organizations are already working as productively as they can in their current modes of operation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To serve customers and prospects better than your competitors can, it&#39;s time to change the game. With AI automation integrated into a CRM platform to connect sales and marketing, data and customers, your organization can gain the bandwidth it needs to accomplish levels of productivity and growth that were until recently unattainable—delighting your customers, leading your sector, and growing your business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;To find out how Zoho CRM can boost your teams&#39; productivity with intelligent automation, &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm.com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;talk to us today&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[7 Ways to Make Employees Feel Respected, According to Research]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/7-ways-to-make-employees-feel-respected-according-to-research]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_07_2417355.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jovana Rikalo/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Treating everyone with respect is the foundation of good leadership. Employees who feel disrespected are more likely to also feel excluded or even inferior. The authors offer seven behaviors, based on their analysis of data collected from more than 4,500 employees, that lead to a demonstration and feeling of respect. These include valuing diversity, staying in touch with individuals&amp;#8217; issues and concerns, building trusted, resolving conflicts, balancing results with a concern for others, encouraging open discussion, and giving honest feedback. Authentic and consistent implementation of these behaviors will help you establish a culture of respect and support.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/7-ways-to-make-employees-feel-respected-according-to-research?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/7-ways-to-make-employees-feel-respected-according-to-research?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;There is one behavior that underlies all good leadership: treating everyone with respect. It&#39;s the fundamental foundation of any relationship, and yet many managers struggle to express it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Data we collected in 2022 from 4,849 employees indicated that only 4% felt disrespected, whereas 86% felt respected. At first blush, this sounds encouraging. Those may seem like good numbers. But, in our view, 4% is far too high. That&#39;s roughly one out of 25 colleagues who feel they are not respected, that they don&#39;t belong, or perhaps even feel inferior. It&#39;s hard to imagine that &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/12/the-value-of-belonging-at-work&quot;>;people who feel this way are able to do their best work or reach their potential&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How can managers and leaders demonstrate respect more consistently? Our research gives some hints on the everyday actions that increase feelings of respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Behaviors that Generate the Most Respect&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We generated correlation coefficients between individual behaviors and ratings from their followers on respect. These coefficients measure, across numerous leaders, the extent to which a negative score on a particular leadership behavior is connected to lower ratings on respect. In comparison, more positive scores on that behavior for another leader reflect more positive scores on respect. The larger the correlation coefficient, the stronger the connection between behavior and respect, which led to their colleagues&#39; conclusion that they were being treated respectfully. This helped us uncover the seven leader behaviors that led to the overall impression of respectful treatment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Valuing Diversity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A common theme we heard from those feeling disrespected is that “I&#39;m different” or “I don&#39;t fit in.” Many leaders actively work hard to hire team members from diverse backgrounds, check their unconscious biases, and ensure they&#39;re open to hearing diverse perspectives and opinions. Others go through the motions assuming they treat everyone equally, completely unaware of their glaring blind spots. Our &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/10/leaders-arent-great-at-judging-how-inclusive-they-are&quot;>;prior research&lt;/a>; showed many leaders tend to under- or overrate their skill in this area.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To establish a groundwork of respect, leaders must be aware that they may not be doing everything they can to show that they value diversity, and make clear that differences are valued.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Staying in Touch with Issues and Concerns of Individuals&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While you may not be at work to find your best friend, you need to maintain a level of familiarity to establish respect. When you are the last to find out about an employee or colleague who is struggling, you might be tempted to rationalize that as one of the downsides of being a leader. After all, how can you know everything that&#39;s going on with everyone, especially when the power imbalance creates social distance?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Realistically, you can&#39;t. But you should be making an effort to convey that you are there for employees who may want to share sensitive issues or deep concerns. Set a goal to stay in contact with people as much as you can, to check in on how they&#39;re doing, and to reiterate your commitment to supporting them when needed. Asking questions such as, ”Are we making it possible for you to balance your work and your personal life?” or “How is your family doing at this moment?” can invite a more personal conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Staying in touch with people in this way conveys respect. While listening to a worker musing about his relationship with his favorite boss, we asked why he appreciated his boss and his response was, “He calls me when he doesn&#39;t need anything.” Those periodic phone calls where the boss conveyed concern only about him and his welfare made all the difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Being Trusted&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In our &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/02/the-3-elements-of-trust&quot;>;research on trust&lt;/a>;, we discovered that if one person on your team distrusts you, it will significantly lower the level of trust from the rest of the team. This is an emotion that&#39;s contagious.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We know that trust is enhanced by three factors: positive relationships, sharing expertise/knowledge, and consistency. When you treat people with respect, regardless of their ancestry, language, culture, religion, or sexual orientation, you are enhancing your relationship, which greatly increases the trust others have in you.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Resolving Conflicts&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Even a small conflict between a few team members can negatively impact the energy of a whole group and become a source of frustration that encourages feelings of disrespect. Too often, when leaders notice conflicts between team members, they vow not to intervene — “I&#39;ll let them work out the conflict themselves; no need for me to get involved” — but then they don&#39;t apply that approach consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Selective peacemaking conveys respect for some and a lack of respect for others. Conflicts in a team are like a small fire in the forest that, if caught early, can be easily put out but, when ignored, can create significant damage. Leaders need to resolve conflicts quickly when they occur. A respectful leader does not step back but &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/how-to-handle-a-disagreement-on-your-team&quot;>;willingly engages in mending conflicts&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Balancing “Getting Results” with a Concern for Others&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When results become more important than the people who deliver them, people feel disrespected. In most situations, this only requires making small exceptions for people (when kids get sick, accidents happen, or someone needs a mental health break), but the impact on satisfaction and engagement will be significant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The best leaders &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/08/managers-compassion-and-accountability-arent-mutually-exclusive&quot;>;balance getting results with the realities facing the people who produce them&lt;/a>;. Organizations and leaders must listen to the pleas to establish a culture that supports better work-life balance. “You can&#39;t freeze and unfreeze culture on demand — it&#39;s earned every day, and not just in one way, but through people processes, commitments, manager accountability, whom you recruit, and whom you reward,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/why-leaders-cant-ignore-human-energy-crisis-kathleen-hogan/&quot;>;writes&lt;/a>; Microsoft Chief People Officer Kathleen Hogan.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Encouraging Open Discussion of Problems and Differences of Opinions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The simple act of asking another person for their opinion is a powerful way to communicate respect. But you can&#39;t just ask — you also have to listen and engage. When a leader is willing to hear different perspectives and dig into problems that concern others, they show they value those team members. You don&#39;t have to think the issue is important (you might even think it&#39;s trivial) or their viewpoint is valid to do this. But moving past those reactions to genuinely listen and ask questions conveys respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can further enhance respect by actively listening to opinions that are contrary to yours. This conveys, “I&#39;m open to a different way of thinking and I want to understand more” and “I hold you in high regard even though we may have differing views.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Giving Honest Feedback in a Helpful Way&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Direct and honest feedback can make people feel respected, as long as it&#39;s delivered in the right way. It ought to fairly reflect the person&#39;s performance. If an employee does 90% of their work correctly and 10% incorrectly, honest feedback would be 90% positive and only 10% corrective. In many cases, leaders give 0% positive and 10% corrective feedback, which implies that all the leader cares about or notices are errors or mistakes. This pointing out of negative behavior — without balancing it with positive feedback as well — makes people feel disrespected.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, respect can mean different things to different people, and the people you lead may care more about some of these behaviors than others. The key is to consider all seven, then select one or two that you believe will matter to your employees, and find authentic ways to do more of that behavior.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Great leaders are well respected, but more importantly, they take deliberate, thoughtful steps to show respect for their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Your Data Strategy Needs to Include Everyone]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_07_1304822843.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;An entirely new &amp;#8220;management paradigm&amp;#8221; for data is needed. As used here, a &amp;#8220;management paradigm&amp;#8221; embodies a common language, a holistic vision of the ways data should contribute, a clearly defined organizational structure showing how data integrates across the organization, along with clear roles and responsibilities for all involved. Eventually, it needs to incorporate corporate culture, relationships with universities and vendors, policy, and anything else that advances, or holds back the effective use of data. The new paradigm employs a more pervasive and integrated approach to using data, analytics, and AI in the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;If the past few decades have confirmed anything, it is the power of data, broadly defined to include activity involving small data, big data, statistics, analytics, and artificial intelligence by employees at every level of sophistication, to help companies improve their performance, in many ways. On one end of the spectrum, artificial intelligence (AI), especially generative AI, promises to transform business and so garners the most excitement. On the other end, &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/most-analytics-projects-dont-require-much-data&quot;>;basic analyses using small amounts of data&lt;/a>; are stunningly effective in helping companies make better decisions, control and improve business processes, better understand customers, and enhance products and services. Read the popular press and you might conclude that data, analytics, and AI are taking over the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, other than for digital natives, a deeper look reveals a far bleaker reality. Despite massive investment, great tools, and plenty of qualified data analysts and scientists, progress in &lt;a href=&quot;https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262047241/working-with-ai/&quot;>;AI is slow, expensive, and uncertain&lt;/a>;. Most data science models are not actually &lt;a href=&quot;https://hdsr.mitpress.mit.edu/pub/2fu65ujf/release/6&quot;>;deployed into production&lt;/a>;, yielding no actual economic value. The &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/08/why-do-chief-data-officers-have-such-short-tenures&quot;>;tenure&lt;/a>; of most Chief Data and Analytics Officers is so short it is unrealistic to expect them to get much done. “Regular people,” those without data in their titles, don&#39;t know what is expected of them and, despite claims to the contrary, fear that analytics and AI will change, even eliminate, their jobs. Most companies eschew small data, robbing themselves of easier-to-obtain business benefits and the chance to build the organizational muscle needed to attack more difficult problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is all too easy to call for “data-driven cultures,” but actually defining and building such cultures is far beyond the ken of most data professionals. &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/action-and-inaction-on-data-analytics-and-ai/&quot;>;Survey data&lt;/a>; suggests that relatively few companies actually have data-driven cultures. Finally, current levels of data quality simply do not support data analysis or science at scale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;It&#39;s Time for Fresh Thinking&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Digging still deeper, it is easy to understand the root causes of these disappointing realities:&amp;nbsp; Companies have essentially “bolted data onto” their organization charts, naming Chief Data and Analytics Officers, establishing Centers of Excellence, and hiring highly-educated data scientists, then turning them loose with few guidelines and little supervision. That some succeed is a testament to the tenacity of the few, who&#39;ve overcome organizational hurdles against long odds. Data leaders are not blind to the issues. They&#39;ve hired data wranglers and engineers to help overcome bad data and &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/why-your-company-needs-data-product-managers&quot;>;product managers&lt;/a>; to help better connect to the business. Still, it all feels like an elaborate (and largely futile) game of “whack-a-mole.”&amp;nbsp; Continuing down the current path is ill-fated.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rather, we suggest that an entirely new “management paradigm” for data is needed. As used here, a “management paradigm” embodies a common language, a holistic vision of the ways data should contribute, a clearly defined organizational structure showing how data integrates across the organization, along with clear roles and responsibilities for all involved. Eventually, it needs to incorporate corporate culture, relationships with universities and vendors, policy, and anything else that advances, or holds back the effective use of data. The new paradigm employs a more pervasive and integrated approach to using data, analytics, and AI in the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But what steps should companies take now to work towards a new paradigm? How should they think about fully integrating data into their business strategies? What targets should they aim for, and what should they do initially? This article builds on our research into hundreds of companies and government agencies wrestling with these questions, work with a couple of dozen of them, and our experience with other relevant paradigms to propose three interconnected steps companies should take now.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use a “Digital Native” as a Guiding Light&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First of all, we propose Google as a candidate “North Star.” After all, data is so much a part of the mainstream at Google that it doesn&#39;t even have a Chief Data or Analytics Officer, though it does have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.co.uk/article/google-chief-decision-scientist-cassie-kozyrkov&quot;>;Chief Decision Officer&lt;/a>;, whose primary mission is spreading the good word about data-driven decisions. Google pioneered &lt;a href=&quot;https://rework.withgoogle.com/subjects/people-analytics/#:~:text=People%20Analytics%20is%20about%20using,and%20direct%20your%20HR%20actions.&quot;>;people analytics&lt;/a>; and is one of few whose &lt;a href=&quot;https://ironcladapp.com/blog/mary-ocarroll-content-roundup/&quot;>;legal operations make extensive use of analytics&lt;/a>;. Analytics and AI are embedded into most of the company&#39;s products and services, and the company&#39;s CEO declared it would be “AI first” back in 2016. It pioneered many of the approaches used in today&#39;s generative AI systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other digital native firms, like Meta/Facebook and Amazon, have similarly pervasive usage of analytics and AI, and our research and consulting in these firms suggests that, unlike in more traditional companies, data leaders don&#39;t have to spend a lot of time evangelizing about the importance of these tools; it is simply taken for granted and viewed as an essential element of the culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A few legacy businesses are adopting similar approaches, but not enough. At DBS Bank, for example, the largest bank in Southeast Asia, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/03/13/dbs-ceo-banks-still-have-strengths-that-fintechs-could-use.html&quot;>;CEO Piyush Gupta argues&lt;/a>; that the bank&#39;s future competitors are not traditional banks, but rather digital native firms like Alibaba, Tencent, and Ant Financial. To compete with those companies, he believes, DBS must collect, manage, and analyze data as well or better than they do. The bank has hired or trained over a thousand data scientists and engineers, developed its own AI applications, adopted a broad AI literacy program, and encouraged development of AI use cases across all business functions and units.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Learn from Other Mainstream Business Functions&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Secondly, for those who may find the idea of following Google&#39;s or DBS&#39;s examples too steep a hill to climb right now, a nearer-term role model found in virtually every organization is the finance organization. Even non-profits and governmental agencies have finance groups. In our collective experience, we feel that finance, perhaps more than any other function, has achieved the goal of going mainstream.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Going mainstream is the antithesis of being a silo; it means being fully integrated with all aspects of the organization. Consider the attributes of most finance organizations:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;The finance organization is clearly seen as strategic, with most Boards of Directors having their own finance committees, and expecting financial reports at every meeting.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The CFO is typically in the “inner circle” of the CEO, and involved in virtually all major decisions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The tenure of CFO&#39;s tends to be much longer than of Chief Data Officers, which as noted above, tends to be quite short. Further, rapid turnover of CFO&#39;s sends a warning signal to Wall Street.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Finance employees are integrated into virtually every facility, operating plant, division, and so on, and have at least a dotted line into corporate finance.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Virtually every manager knows how to conduct basic financial tasks, including preparing a budget, computing ROI, and so forth. Most managers spend a lot of time on financial work.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Finance makes clear what is expected, provides the tools and processes it expects people to follow, and monitors compliance. Following financial procedures is not optional.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Finance goes to enormous lengths to make sure the data it uses, and provides, is of extremely high-quality.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The above list starts with viewing finance as strategic. This would be a significant step forward in taking data mainstream. If learning from and monetizing data are viewed as strategic opportunities, then the organization should consider how to implement each of these bullet points for data.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Finally, Get Everyone Involved&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Lastly, we have enormous sympathy for senior managers. While data analysis has been around for a long time, the technologies themselves are daunting and the hype makes it appear that implementing them is far easier than it actually is. Exacerbating this, the urgency of doing so appears to grow exponentially. It is easy for non-technical employees to get lost in the shuffle. Yet as much as trusted data and dogged implementation of the technology, they are essential! Consider that even elite data scientists cannot truly define a business problem, understand the data, nor deploy a model into a business process without their help. Nor can you make the needed improvements to data.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Admittedly, we are bullish on data over the long-term. We see the potential to decrease the drudgery in billions of jobs, augment others, and create whole new, high-paying jobs (we are just as aware of the downside risks). At the same time, we think people are smart to be fearful — after all, drudge jobs put food on the table for billions of people world-wide. Obviously, it would be best if senior leaders could eliminate such fears, but we think that unlikely for most companies. Still, we advise senior leaders to acknowledge the fear, just as senior leaders who don&#39;t get serious about data very soon should be doubly fearful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, we advise senior leaders to recruit as many regular people involved as possible into their data effort. Practically everyone can bring &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/most-analytics-projects-dont-require-much-data&quot;>;small data and basic analytics to improve their team&#39;s performance&lt;/a>;. Such efforts build skill and confidence and collectively can make a real difference. And for many companies, they appear to be pre-requisite for taking on bigger data and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/stop-tinkering-with-ai&quot;>;more advanced techniques&lt;/a>;. Finally, many regular people find small data empowering and so are more than happy to join the fun.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Urgency Is in Order&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Companies can, of course, manage themselves however they please; though of course they should strive to do so in ways that make it easier to conduct its most important work. After all, even the smallest company is a complicated place. One implication is that some things get more and better attention than others. Up until 10 years ago, the relative lack of attention around data made sense — it simply was not in the mainstream, nor did it need to be. This makes considerably less sense today. Just hiring chief data and analytics officers is no longer enough. Companies must make some significant changes to the management paradigms for data and their most senior leaders must lead the charge.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>