<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[A Game Plan for Funding Carbon Offsets]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_-537715290_-1363813940.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;插图：Edmon de Haro； Baloncici/Getty Images（烟囱）； Vitalina/Getty Images（蝴蝶）&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp ;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;最常见的碳补偿类型是基于自然的补偿，例如森林。不幸的是，虽然排放物会在大气中保留大约 1,000 年（可能更长），但一棵树只能在其 10 年左右的生命周期内去除碳，这意味着作为碳抵消而种植的森林必须保持至少十次重新种植树木以&amp;#160;匹配它抵消的排放量。大多数企业都不愿意以这种方式占用资本，但此类项目可以（并且已经）通过永久债券融资，这对投资者来说是有吸引力的投资，例如大学捐赠基金的负债流很长，可以延伸到很远的未来。永久债券等金融工具的使用可以为抵消生产者提供大量可用资本，刺激抵消生产和现货市场的创建，从而最终可靠地抵消排放。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/ a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot; font-weight: 400;&quot;>;2015 年 9 月，耶鲁大学 Beinecke 善本和手稿图书馆的馆长前往阿姆斯特丹，在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.yale.edu /2015/09/22/living-artifact-dutch-golden-age-yale-s-367-year-old-water-bond-still-pays-interest&quot;>;1648 年 5 月 15 日发行的债券&lt;/a>; .在债券发行时，借款人（一家荷兰自治水务机构）承诺向持有人&lt;em>;永久&lt;/em>;支付利息。出售债券所得的现金已用于支付防止海平面上升的基础设施项目。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;此类永久债券可能在当今应对气候变化的斗争中发挥作用通过为将无限期清除和储存碳的项目提供资金来改变。碳清除可用于抵消碳排放负债（或&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/accounting-for-climate-change&quot;>;电子负债&lt;/a>;），从而帮助企业和其他组织实现净-零目标。永续债券还可以支持有效的&lt;em>;现货市场&lt;/em>;在去除抵消方面的发展，刺激它们的生产和使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;永续债券有助于解决许多碳抵消的持续时间与它们要抵消的电子负债的持续时间之间的关键不匹配。正如我们在 7 月至 8 月的《哈佛商业评论》印刷文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/accounting-for-carbon-offsets&quot;>;碳补偿核算&lt;/a>;”中指出的那样，&amp;nbsp;来自温室气体的电子负债排放对金融市场构成特殊挑战，因为今天产生的排放预计会在大气中存留 1,000 多年，持续时间远远长于典型的金融负债。鉴于此，我们确定可抵消碳排放资产（E 资产）也需要&lt;em>;无限期&lt;/em>;持续时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;某些 E - 通过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usgs.gov/news/featured-story/making-minerals-how-growing-rocks-can-help-reduce-carbon-emissions&quot;获取碳捕获和储存等资产>;地下矿化&lt;/a>;明确符合这一标准，但此类电子资产目前并不常见。今天更为普遍的是基于自然的抵消 (NBO)，例如原始造林计划，由于森林的&lt;em>;有限&lt;/em>;（未补充）生命周期（可能少于 100 年），持续时间通常较短。那么，问题在于 NBO 是否可以用于抵消 E 负债：如果不能，那么今天提供的大多数清除抵消只是长期排放负债的预付款。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font -weight: 400;&quot;>;对于无限期 NBO，发行人必须承诺永久管理标的（森林）资产——也就是说，在森林的组成树木自然腐烂或被疾病、火灾等毁坏时重新种植森林. 为了资助这项行动，抵消提供者不仅需要资金来购买土地和植树，还需要提供可预测的永久性支出。换句话说，他们必须将筹集到的任何资金的一部分投资于捐赠基金，其回报可以用于为森林管理提供资金，从而使碳无限期地被封存（定义为 1,000 年，这是一个合理的科学估计今天排放的碳将在大气中停留多长时间）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;此外，鉴于无限期的承诺，发行人想要限定其目前交付的一部分（或“已赚取”）清除抵消，因为可以立即完全抵消购买者的电子负债，因此必须单独（明显更大）留出一部分可用的已赚取抵消，以抵消未来的固碳承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;所有这些都意味着向 NBO 抵消生产者提供资金的人可以期望他们的投资回报相对较低，尽管是永久分配的。个人抵消购买者（通常是营利性企业）不会发现以这种方式占用自己的资金有吸引力。但这样的投资可能对那些需要捐赠来支付未来可预测债务的机构很有吸引力，比如大学和教堂。投资将采取永久债券的形式——例如荷兰水务局发行的债券——或具有固定股息的优先股。普通股可能不适合为无限期移除抵消提供资金，因为投资者通常希望获得有保证的回报，以永久锁定资本且上涨空间有限。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;考虑一下，作为一个关于永久债券方法如何运作的假设示例，加拿大的一个土著部落希望出售原始森林中的可净电子资产，并将在其土地上种植并无限期管理。为此，它必须筹集资金来开发和维护森林。部落可以发行永久债券，并将部分资本投入永久性金融捐赠基金。部落使用捐赠的利息来支付管理森林的费用。随着森林的抵消成为“赚取的”——也就是说，树木成熟并吸收碳——部落可以出售这些电子资产的一部分来支付费用，包括永久债券的利息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;让我们假设 20 兆吨的 CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; 当量 (MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e) 从森林当前的树木中“捕获”年和未来 100 年都将如此，但树木必须至少再种植 10 次才能抵消 1,000 年的 E-liability。为分配此承诺的风险，部落可以将今年补偿的 2 MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e 永久“赚取”（即 20 Mt 除以 10）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;如果有足够多的 NBO 抵消生产商和足够的需求，可净抵消可以出售到流动性市场，从而将森林的未来风险分配给一系列抵消购买者和帮助部落履行其利益义务。明年的现货买家可能与今年的不同，事实上，数百年后的现货买家可能会有很大不同，但通过共同贡献永续债券的利息成本，他们分担了 NBO 的长期时间序列风险.只要可净抵消的现货销售收益和捐赠回报超过债券的利息支出和持续的森林管理成本，该计划对部落来说就是有利可图的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400; “>;很有可能，375 年前没有人预料到荷兰海堤管理债券会在今天向 3,500 英里外的新英格兰大学图书馆支付利息。同样，我们无法预测金融市场将如何发展以满足排放责任管理的需要。但此处列出的途径提出了一个可行的市场解决方案，以减轻当今碳排放的长期后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt; div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Company Prepared for the Effects of Wildfires?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_1258513476.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Angela Weiss/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;今天的野火和烟雾可以传播数百英里，模糊了工作场所内外发生的劳动力之间的界限健康。现在是雇主制定计划以应对这一问题和其他气候变化驱动的健康问题的时候了。作者建议采取六项行动：1）将全球野火与当地健康联系起来； 2) 收集和评估空气质量数据，为劳动力咨询制定阈值； 3) 确定企业响应团队中的主要利益相关者并激活您的指挥中心； 4) 确定何时对户外工作者采取行动； 5) 确定如何支持室内办公室员工； 6) 为您的员工制定沟通和教育计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your -company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for- the-effects-of-wildfires?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;野火。几代人以来，这个词一直让中小农村社区心存恐惧。现在，由于北美部分地区被烟雾笼罩，美国城市和总部设在那里的公司也开始意识到自己也很脆弱。上周，东海岸城市从&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/live/2023/06/07/us/canada-wildfires-air-quality-smoke&quot;>;纽约&lt;/a>;到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/air-quality-toronto-fires-smoke-1.6868010&quot;>;多伦多&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-wildfire-smoke-canada-updates-june-7/&quot;>;蒙特利尔&lt;/a>;看到空气质量迅速下降到世界上最差的一些，因为&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.wsj.com/articles/smoke-air-quality-nyc-northeast-canadian-wildfires-6b5ffc01&quot;>;加拿大野火产生的烟雾&lt;/a>;向南飘去。这意味着美国企业界的讨论已经超越了室内空气循环或过滤，也涵盖了室外空气质量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;空气质量差会影响 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ishn.com/ articles/113569-how-poor-iaq-impacts-employee-safety-and-productivity&quot;>;员工健康和生产力&lt;/a>;，来自&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/news /press-releases/office-air-quality-may-affect-employees-cognition-productivity/&quot;>;认知功能&lt;/a>;和较差的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w20648&quot; >;集中&lt;/a>;以降低&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/09/air-pollution-is-making-office-workers-less-productive&quot;>;生产力&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https:// iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/ab8b8c&quot;>;情绪&lt;/a>;。它还会加剧健康状况，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7503605/&quot;>;哮喘&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2022.926534/full&quot;>;焦虑&lt;/a>;并导致&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unicef.org/mongolia/media/2926/file/UNICEF-旷工-ENG-final.pdf&quot;>;旷工&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9554460/&quot;>;出勤&lt;/a>;和&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.graduateinstitute.ch/sites/internet/files/2021-04/HHW_2020.pdf&quot;>;请假&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;野火和烟雾扰乱了企业旅行，推迟公司活动，并让员工去看医生以解决一系列相关的健康问题，包括呼吸困难。不幸的是，未来可能还会有更多——&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epa.gov/climate-indicators/climate-change-indicators-wildfires&quot;>;气候变化&lt;/a>;意味着野火季节增加长度、频率和烧伤面积。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一名在国际组织工作并为公司领导提供建议的医生，我们看到雇主对员工健康和空气质量问题最佳实践的询问迅速增加。人力资源团队正在回答员工和领导者提出的复杂问题——许多人觉得没有准备好正确的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这让人想起 2020 年 3 月 Covid 的高峰期，当时领导者问：这是一个问题吗我们需要回应吗？我需要知道什么？我现在需要采取什么行动？以下是雇主在解决这个持续存在的问题时要考虑的六项行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.将全球野火与当地健康联系起来。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;空气污染可以伤害任何人。但对于特定的员工群体及其家庭成员来说，这更危险。这包括婴幼儿、65 岁以上的老年人、孕妇、任何在户外锻炼或工作的人，以及患有糖尿病、肺病或心脏病等现有疾病或慢性疾病的人。在浓烟条件下，所有员工无论年龄或健康状况如何都可能面临风险。影响可能是身体上的，也可能是心理上的，尤其是对于那些经历了从家中和工作场所撤离的野火创伤的员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;烟雾可以从最初的火区传播数千英里，这意味着其他地方的野火世界将影响您公司运营所在当地社区的员工。野火产生的烟雾包含复杂的污染物混合物，例如细颗粒物。这些颗粒肉眼看不见，但会深入我们的肺部和血液，有时会对健康造成严重影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有证据表明某些污染物处于安全暴露水平，这意味着烟雾会影响员工&#39; 健康甚至在非常低的水平。随着当地烟雾浓度的增加，您的员工面临的健康风险通常也会增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.收集和评估空气质量数据。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;通常可以通过空气质量指数 (AQI) 找到数据，这是一种在空气污染达到危险水平时向公众发出警告的系统。在美国，环境保护署 (EPA) 发布全年 AQI 预报，并通过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airnow.gov/&quot;>;地图&lt;/a>;显示污染水平如何在一天中变化和移动，其他国家也有类似的资源。这种“实时”信息可以帮助雇主在影响员工和客户的当前室外空气质量出现在头版新闻之前对其进行量化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们还建议与医生等医疗保健专家合作或医疗顾问制定与这些水平相符的劳动力咨询的特定阈值。这样做将帮助您采取措施保护您的员工免受不健康的空气污染，并使他们能够主动寻求适当的支持以确保他们的健康和安全。与医疗保健指导相结合的特定阈值还将使管理人员能够根据公司政策与团队进行沟通并指导他们的团队。一旦您的组织了解如何使用空气质量数据并设置监测阈值，这将有助于在正确的时间和地点触发您的企业响应。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.激活您的指挥中心。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;确定在达到 AQI 阈值时需要召集哪些人来响应，尤其是在员工的身体健康和安全受到直接威胁的情况下。与野火相关的当地疏散&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/12/how-kaiser-permanente-prepares-for-disasters&quot;>;风险特别高&lt;/a>;，尤其是当数十万人同时撤离时，如 &lt; a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/dec/11/southern-california-wildfires-blaze&quot;>;南加州&lt;/a>;。您的公司响应团队可能包括受影响地区的当地业务负责人、沟通专家、医疗顾问、人力资源负责人，甚至涉及更广泛的企业问题的风险从业人员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您的多学科方法可能看起来类似于治理模型 &lt; a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/leader/early/2020/04/07/leader-2020-000244.full.pdf&quot;>;在 Covid 大流行期间开发&lt;/a>;并将确保及时信息源源不断地流入和流出正确的利益相关者，包括高管和董事会。它还将使快速、全面的决策制定和相关的企业响应成为可能。这可能包括满足职业健康和安全标准以及不同员工群体（如室内和室外工人）的法规遵从性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4.关注户外工作者，并遵守法规。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;根据您所在的行业，野火烟雾中的户外工作受 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/ niosh/topics/firefighting/wffsmoke.html&quot;>;职业健康与安全&lt;/a>;标准和监管机构，如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/ 1910.134&quot;>;职业安全与健康管理局&lt;/a>; (OSHA)。长时间的工作时间表和体力劳动需求可能会影响工人的暴露风险和健康反应。地理很重要，因为地方法规不同。例如，加利福尼亚州的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dir.ca.gov/title8/5141_1.html&quot;>;紧急法规&lt;/a>;适用于 AQI 大于 151 的工作场所，或者如果员工预计&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;雇主应了解当地的空气质量法规，并采取措施限制户外工作人员的暴露，尤其是当工作环境中或周围有野火烟雾时。这可能包括将工作任务重新安置或重新安排到无烟或烟雾较少的区域或一天中的时间，尽可能减少体力活动，为工人提供经常在无烟场所休息的机会，并在需要时提供特殊住宿。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在某些情况下，应考虑使用个人防护装备 (PPE)，例如合身的 N95 呼吸器，以限制工人的接触。当美国雇主要求使用呼吸保护装置来限制接触烟雾时，这应该作为综合呼吸保护计划的一部分，如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/ standardnumber/1910/1910.134&quot;>;OSHA 呼吸防护标准&lt;/a>;。 （如果使用是自愿的，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134AppD&quot;>;其他 OSHA 标准&lt;/a>;适用。）&lt;/p>; &lt; h2>;&lt;strong>;5.支持室内办公室员工。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;对于室内办公室工作人员来说，空气质量可能出乎意料地复杂。与&lt;a href=&quot;https://deloitte.wsj.com/articles/staying-compliant-in-an-era-of-hybrid-and-remote-work-c0e0938e&quot;>;家庭办公室&lt;/相关的公司安全标准a>; 和&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalguardian.com/global-digest/at-home-duty-of-care&quot;>;工人旅行&lt;/a>;近年来有所增加。虽然雇主的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1741438/does-employers-duty-care-extend-commuting&quot;>;注意义务&lt;/a>;是否延长是有争议的对于员工上下班的旅程，通勤很重要，特别是如果员工需要在严重的室外空气污染中穿梭往返办公室。采取全面的“员工体验之旅”方法可以帮助校准受灾严重地区或存在特定个人健康风险因素的员工群体的潜在风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于许多办公楼都配备了先进的供暖、通风、和空调 (HVAC) 系统以及优化的最低效率报告值 (MERV) 评级，在野火季节，办公室的空气质量可能优于普通家庭的空气质量。雇主可能需要采取额外措施来减少暴露于野火烟雾中并保护住户免受野火烟雾的伤害。这可能包括安装配备高效微粒空气 (HEPA) 过滤器的空气净化器，确保窗户和其他建筑物开口保持关闭以减少内部的整体烟雾暴露，在再循环环境中运行 HVAC 系统，或暂时减少数量提供给建筑物的室外空气。如果您目前租用办公空间，请与您的房东联系，以确保他们优化对室内工作人员的保护。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;更广泛地说，考虑安全、医疗和心理健康保险，以在危机时刻确保您的员工安全.这包括为全体员工提供全面保护，无论他们是上下班还是在室内或室外工作。在您当地公司后院的家中工作的员工可能需要与您以前只为国际旅行者考虑的相同的 24/7 疏散保险。这种保险同样适用于野火，也适用于其他自然灾害，如洪水或飓风，此时公司通常会提供食物和水、住所或紧急疏散等援助。在许多公司，这种额外的覆盖层需要心态转变，但今天值得这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6.广泛沟通和教育。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;根据野火的范围和规模及其对您的组织的影响，考虑应该主动沟通的内容（例如，您的组织了解并积极响应当地空气质量恶化）和被动反应（例如，人力资源部关于需要住宿的非常具体的个人情况的信息）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;教育是任何与野火和空气质量相关的沟通计划的重要组成部分，因此请保持警惕您的员工接触野火烟雾的症状。更轻微和更常见的症状包括头痛、轻度咳嗽、眼睛酸痛和流泪，以及鼻子、喉咙和鼻窦刺激。更严重但不太常见的症状包括头晕、胸痛、剧烈咳嗽、呼吸急促、喘息，甚至心律不齐。鼓励员工向医疗保健提供者寻求护理，并在有哮喘发作、中风或心脏病发作风险等严重情况时考虑紧急医疗护理。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在发生严重的野火事件时，沟通可能包括解决直接的身体健康和安全威胁，并扩展到围绕空气质量和呼吸健康的长期实践。当空气质量水平处于不同阈值时，为个别员工提供有关如何保护他们的健康的指导会有所帮助。例如，在更高层次上，可以引导员工避免长时间在户外剧烈活动，远离人流量大的区域。这也可能意味着推迟或取消某些公司和团队建设活动，或将户外聚会转移到室内。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.canada.ca/en/health-canada/services/publications/healthy-living/how-prepare-wildfire-smoke.html#:~:text=Checklist%20for%20wildfire% 20smoke%20season%20preparedness,-Are%20you%20or&amp;amp;text=Do%20you%20have%20an%20adequate%20supply%20of%20food%20and%20water,a%20break%20from%20the%20smoke%3F&quot;>;准备清单&lt;/a>; 可以提供帮助并可能涵盖家庭、办公室和个人医疗准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天的野火和烟雾可以传播数百英里，模糊了工作场所内外发生的事情之间的界限劳动力健康。现在是解决这个问题和其他气候变化驱动的健康问题的时候了。寻找新资源，试验新方法，并将其转化为富有成效的企业行动以支持员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Your Boss Gives You Bad Feedback, Badly]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_12_1434150794.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当收到过于苛刻、过于友善或不诚实的反馈时，很难控制自己的情绪。我们都在为反馈而苦苦挣扎，因此请多多关照拥有强烈情绪的自己，以及发起艰难对话的其他人。作者介绍了人们以造成伤害和引发强烈情绪的方式提供反馈的三种最常见方式，以及当您收到反馈不佳时要采取的五个关键步骤。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;听说你在工作中表现不佳可能会让人感觉很糟糕。这不会让你“防御”或“关闭反馈”。这只是意味着你是人，而且你关心自己的表现——这都是好事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;即使你从经理、同事或员工那里收到友好、明确的反馈，学习起来仍然很困难你可以做得更好。对自己说：“这很不舒服，但没关系。我的反应会过去。”然后做一些能让你暂时忍受不适的事情。冥想、散步或写日记。提醒自己这个人给你反馈是因为他们关心帮助你&lt;em>;。 &lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是当这个人不关心你，或者反馈不佳时会发生什么？如果这个人粗鲁、麻木不仁或不清楚怎么办？现在不是批评批评的时候。但是，您如何应对自己对不同类型反馈的情绪反应呢？摆脱对批评性反馈的不满的唯一方法是通过。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Mollie 和 Liz 是工作情绪方面的专家，Kim 是工作中反馈方面的专家。 Kim 的&lt;a href=&quot;https://review.firstround.com/radical-candor-the-surprising-secret-to-being-a-good-boss&quot;>;彻底坦率&lt;/a>; 框架解释了三种最常见的方式人们以一种造成伤害并引发强烈情绪的方式提供反馈：令人讨厌的攻击性、操纵性的不真诚和毁灭性的同理心。我们一起确定了五个关键步骤，当您收到反馈不佳时要采取的措施：&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;说出您的情绪。&lt;/strong>;弄清楚您的感受和不感受判断自己。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;区分麦子和谷壳。&lt;/strong>;即使反馈不好，也要在反馈中寻找有用的东西。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;奖励坦率的人&lt;/strong>;——即使您不同意。请注意，这并不意味着假装同意。有时，对您不同意的反馈的最好奖励是尊重地解释原因。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;就反馈提供反馈。&lt;/strong>;与对方讨论他们提供的影响。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;钓鱼或割饵。&lt;/strong>;弄清楚您是否可以继续改善这种关系，或者这是否是您需要避免的人。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;与大多数建议一样，这说起来容易做起来难。以下是如何在面对三种常见类型的糟糕反馈时应用这些步骤。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;令人讨厌的攻击性反馈&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当有人大喊大叫或使用贬低性语言时，你应该怎么做？例如，有人曾经用手指戳着 Kim 的脸，大喊道：“你是我见过的最咄咄逼人的女人！”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种反馈通常会让我们感到困惑愤怒、恐惧、防御和焦虑。除了以下步骤之外，如果您觉得自己在工作中受到欺凌或辱骂，在您感到安全的情况下，将其上报给可信赖的领导或人力资源代表也很重要。如果上班时没有人让您感到安全，则表明您要开始寻找新工作了。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.说出你的情绪。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;给自己一分钟。如果您发现自己的情绪难以抗拒，请尝试为自己创造空间或将自己完全从这种情况中解脱出来。你可以这样说，“我想稍后再谈这个”或“我对你的反馈反应很强烈，我需要一点时间。” Liz 已经学会用 1（好）到 10（愤怒或恐慌）的等级来评估她的情绪。她打算等到她稳定到 3 或 4 后再采取行动甚至回应。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2.把麦子和谷壳分开。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一旦你冷静下来，想想说了什么，而不是怎么说的。是否有一些信息，无论传授得多么糟糕，对你有用或能帮助你成功？有些人永远不会告诉你他们在想什么，直到他们非常生气以至于他们无法很好地沟通。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可能是因为你不同意反馈的内容以及它的交付方式。没关系。但要挑战自己，找出对方所说的一件事，甚至他们所说的某一方面，你可以同意。可能有一整蒲式耳的谷壳而只有一粒小麦。找到那个谷物，并利用它来发挥你的优势！&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.奖励坦率的人。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;如果您同意任何反馈，请进行更改并让对方了解您所做的不同之处。如果您不同意，请尊重地解释原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4.就反馈提供反馈。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;有没有办法传达他们的言行如何影响您？在某些情况下，分享过于苛刻的交付如何影响您在工作中表现出色的能力可能会很有效。例如，在 Liz 和 Mollie 领导的一个研讨会中，一位参与者分享说她的老板过去常常对她大吼大叫。有一天，她终于对他说：“我知道你现在很不高兴，但你一吼我，我就无法专心工作了。”她的老板道歉并意识到他无意中损害了她的表现。他的爆发变得不那么频繁了。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5.鱼还是鱼饵。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;当然，有时当您与对方谈论他们所说的话如何影响您时，您会了解到对方是想让您不高兴。在那些情况下，告诉他们他们给你的感觉是行不通的。为什么要告诉他们他们成功地惹恼了你？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，限制你与此人互动的次数。有一次 Kim 告诉她的老板他很无礼；他回答说他很生气，因为她没有足够的屈膝，或者欣赏他比她有多么优越。她放弃了。正如&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/i-hate-my-boss/id1148704291?mt=2&quot;>;电视编剧伊丽莎白·克拉夫特建议&lt;/a>;，“如果有人交给你一杯真正的毒药，你不会喝的——所以不要喝口头上的毒药。如果有人在工作中对你造成负面影响，那就不要接受。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;操纵性的虚伪反馈&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当人们担心自己的声誉而不是帮助你改进时，他们可能会说他们不是真正的意思。有时人们对你说的话会让人感到被动攻击，或者他们当面称赞你但在背后批评你。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们有时都会这样做。金承认她有一个直接下属，她向他提供了操纵性的虚伪反馈。他的工作充满了粗心大意的错误。他很受欢迎，而且非常敏感。如果她指出错误，他哭了怎么办？担心她作为领导者的声誉而不是她直接下属的表现，她会对他说些类似的话，“哦，亚历克斯，这是一个很好的开始。你太不可思议了。也许你可以做得更好一点。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果有人给你的赞美感觉更像是自我安慰而不是真实的东西，你该怎么办？ How can you encourage them to say what they really think?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Name your emotion.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When confronted with this behavior, it&#39;s easy to feel confused.如果您发现对方当面说好话，背后说坏话，您可能会感到愤怒、背叛或不信任。深吸一口气。 Figure out how you&#39;re feeling.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Remember, you&#39;re trying to get feedback that will help you grow.试着让发表评论的人澄清他们的意思。 You might say, “Can you share a bit more about what you mean by that?” or “What would you recommend I do differently?” By asking for more detail, you help prevent miscommunication and give yourself an opportunity to address any underlying issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It might be that the person is simply conflict avoidant. You might make them feel more comfortable sharing if you say something like: “I feel like you have valuable feedback for me, but I&#39;m not sure what you&#39;re trying to communicate. Can you tell me what you&#39;re thinking more directly?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another tactic is to tell the person that you&#39;re working on improving something, and ask them to help you: “I&#39;ve been told I interrupt a lot. Can you help me by passing me this pen if you notice me interrupting someone during the meeting?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Reward the candor.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When a well-intentioned person has a hard time giving feedback, it&#39;s especially important to prove to them that not only is it safe to give you feedback, but that they&#39;ll be rewarded richly if they do.当他们的反馈导致您采取行动时，他们所承担的风险就得到了回报。 Saying thanks is never enough —&amp;nbsp;you need to fix the problem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But when a person praises you to your face and criticizes you behind your back, it&#39;s really hard to reward that kind of passive aggression because you&#39;re not supposed to know what they think. You could ask: “Is there something I could do differently so next time you can tell me what you really think?你告诉我你认为演讲进行得很顺利，但我听说你告诉其他人这很糟糕。 I promise not to bite your head off if you tell me when I&#39;m not hitting the mark. In fact, I&#39;ll be grateful because your feedback is exactly what I need in order to do better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Now that you&#39;re talking, you can ask the person if they can commit to talking to you directly rather than behind your back in the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Fish or cut bait.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If the person apologizes and seems sincere, you can begin to rebuild trust.但是，如果他们以进一步削弱信任的方式做出回应，请努力调节您的情绪，以减少他们的行为对您的影响。尝试一种称为时间距离的假想时间旅行技术。 “Imagine it is a day, a week, or a year later,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://msande.stanford.edu/research-impact/stories-voices/faculty/faculty-spotlight-bob-sutton&quot;>;says Bob Sutton&lt;/a>;, author of books including &lt;em>;The No Asshole Rule&lt;/em>;. “And you are looking back on it, and it really didn&#39;t last that long or wasn&#39;t nearly as bad as it seemed at the time.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Ruinously Empathetic Feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Sometimes you get the sense the person is so worried about hurting your feelings or offending you that they won&#39;t tell you what they really think. They care, but they&#39;re not challenging you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The part of Kim that was reluctant to tell her popular and sensitive employee Alex when his work wasn&#39;t good enough because of her concern for her reputation as a leader was manipulative insincerity; the “too nice” part of her that was reluctant to tell Alex what he needed to know because she was afraid of hurting his feelings was ruinous empathy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Name your emotion.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When someone is overly nice about their feedback, you may feel unsure about their intentions, or frustrated that they&#39;re not telling you what you need to know to improve. You may wonder if they think you can&#39;t handle the feedback.也许这会让你生气。也许他们毁灭性的同理心让你觉得他们很软弱，也许这让你感到厌恶。 Emotional responses to ruinous empathy vary widely.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;You might say, “While I appreciate that you think I&#39;m doing a great job, I know that there is always room for improvement. When I repeatedly don&#39;t get any constructive feedback from you, it makes me feel like you&#39;re holding back. The only way I can improve is if you give me candid feedback.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You may then need to sit through the other person&#39;s discomfort.许多给出过分好的反馈的人会试图避免说任何批评的话。 They might repeat, “No really, you&#39;re doing great.” Their discomfort might make you feel that you should let them off the hook.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Push back against this instinct and stick with the conversation until you get a genuine response. Kim 推荐的一种技巧是在说其他话之前数到六。这迫使对方忍受沉默。 After six seconds, if they still can&#39;t come up with anything else in the moment, suggest finding a time to meet again.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Reward the candor.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This is really important if you ever want to get more feedback from the person.热情洋溢地表示感谢。如果您同意反馈，请解决问题，然后询问您是否纠正过度或不足。如果您不同意，请先寻找他们所说的您可以同意的内容。然后，恭敬地解释为什么你不同意其余的。 If possible, agree to do it their way — even if you disagree. Maybe they&#39;re right and you&#39;re wrong. Even so, explaining your reasoning and still deferring to them is a sign of respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Having demonstrated how helpful their feedback was, tell them you&#39;ll be asking for more. Let them know that while you appreciate their concern for your feelings, when they fail to tell you things that would help you do better work, it hurts your ability to succeed, and it doesn&#39;t improve your relationship. Reassure them that you really do want them to be candid with you, and that you not only can take it, but will appreciate it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Fish or cut bait.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Encouraging others to give you feedback often demands patience and takes work.但不是每个人都会提供给你。 If you&#39;ve taken all the steps suggested above, and the person still will not share any direct feedback, look to others for candor. If your boss seems constitutionally unable to give real performance feedback and their boss is not holding them accountable, start looking for a new boss.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s difficult to manage your feelings when getting feedback that feels too harsh, overly nice, or somehow dishonest. We all struggle with feedback, so extend a little grace to yourself for having strong emotions, and to the other person for initiating a difficult conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Large Language Models Reflect Human Judgment]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_10_1448510799.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Artificial intelligence is based around prediction.但决策既需要预测，也需要判断。这就为人类留下了一个角色，可以判断哪些类型的结果更好，哪些更差。但是大型语言模型代表了一个关键的进步：OpenAI 已经找到了一种方法，通过聊天使用一种简单的人类反馈形式来教授其 AI 人类判断。 That opens the door to a new way for humans to work with AI, essentially talking to them about which outcomes are better or worse for any given type of decision.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Artificial intelligences are prediction machines.他们可以告诉你今天下雨的概率，但他们不能告诉你是否应该带把伞。那是因为带伞的决定需要的不仅仅是预测——如果下雨的概率是 10%，有些人会选择带伞，而其他人则不会。为什么不同的人面对同样的信息会有不同的表现呢？因为他们有不同的偏好。在这种情况下，有些人比其他人更关心弄湿。只有您或熟悉您的人才能判断带伞的成本和收益。 Making that decision for you requires both a prediction and a judgment based on your preferences.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;AIs excel at prediction but they do not possess judgment.可以肯定的是，有许多我们知道回报或可以轻松解决的决定。从根本上说，我们知道驾驶员在大多数情况下应该做什么——加速、刹车、转弯——因为我们知道不做正确事情的后果。但是要求谷歌给你关于新洗碗机的建议，它能做的最好的事情就是预测哪些页面可能提供你正在寻找的信息。告诉你该做什么是不够幸运的。同样，虽然你可能担心你的雇主会使用人工智能来决定你是否应该被解雇，但机器并不是最终的负责人。 AI might provide a prediction about your performance, but it is your employer who applies judgment and decides whom to fire.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;It was for this reason that, in our 2018 book &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Prediction-Machines-Economics-Artificial-Intelligence/dp/1633695670&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Prediction Machines&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, we saw a role for reward function engineers whose job it would be to “determine the rewards to various actions, given the predictions that AI makes.”人工智能预测可以改进如此多的决策，以至于了解这些预测和相关决策的奖励函数工程师将在人工智能采用持续快速发展的过程中提供熟练的补充。但奖励函数工程的创新进展缓慢。 There has been little progress in developing tools to codify appropriate human judgment into machines before they are deployed at scale. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Until recently.大型语言模型 (LLM)，尽管看起来很智能，但仍然只是预测机器。 But they are transforming the way AI assists in decision-making because they are changing the way humans provide judgment. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Ask ChatGPT to rewrite a paragraph more clearly for a certain audience, and it does not give you options or a lecture on grammar and rhetoric.它给你一个段落。 It is impressive, but the real miracle here is that ChatGPT could write the paragraph &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;you wanted&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;.写一段话会涉及到大量的回报和风险问题。写作是否诚实（与事实一致）、无害（不包括可能冒犯的词语）和有帮助（实现段落的目标）？想想最后一个。这些模型是根据人们现有的文字进行训练的。所产生的段落的核心是一遍又一遍地使用一种“自动完成”来编写。当我们的手机自动完成时，它们会做得很好但并不完美。那么，ChatGPT 是如何产生比普通人更好的书面结果的呢？ ChatGPT 如何能够从所有内容（无论好坏）中判断质量？ More generally, why didn&#39;t it develop into the toxic cesspool that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;Microsoft&#39;s Tay chatbot turned into after a day on Twitter&lt;/a>;?&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Some people, such as &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://writings.stephenwolfram.com/2023/02/what-is-chatgpt-doing-and-why-does-it-work/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Stephen Wolfram&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, believe that LLMs are uncovering some fundamental rules of grammar. Yes, that can make the writing readable, but it surely can&#39;t make it clear and compelling.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;A &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2203.02155&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;2022 paper from OpenAI researchers&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; provides an important clue.该论文描述了如何采用原始的、未修改的 LLM，并将其用于向真实的人提供输出。 For the most part, the people were asked to &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;use their judgment to rank several alternative outcomes&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; to the same prompt.仔细指定了排名标准（即，优先考虑乐于助人、诚实和无害）。 It turns out that with clear instructions and some person-to-person training, different people could quite readily agree on those things.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Those rankings were then used to tweak or “fine tune” the algorithm.该模型学习了人类的判断，并根据正负强化进行了调整。排名靠前的作品获得了积极的提升。那些没有受到负面影响的人。有趣的是，即使对于在数十亿页上训练的模型，只有几千个以排名响应形式出现的人类判断示例，人工智能也开始为所有排名靠前的查询生成结果。即使对于那些看起来与评估者排名相去甚远的查询，也会发生这种情况。 Somehow, human judgment on writing quality spread quite far throughout the model.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The evaluators were effectively reward function engineers.但与统计模型不同，其输出可能会让很多人反感，LLM 以通俗易懂的语言进行交互——任何人都可以帮助教授模型判断。换句话说，任何会说话或打字的人都可以成为奖励功能工程师。 ChatGPT 背后的惊人发现是，通过相对较少的努力，奖励函数工程师能够训练 LLM 变得有用和安全。这就是 OpenAI 能够推出面向消费者的模型的方式，该模型在发布到野外时没有受到其前辈缺陷的影响。这种将人类判断转化为机器的简单方法增强了人工智能的性能。这台机器现在不仅能够预测可能的单词序列，还能将奖励函数工程师的判断应用于这些序列，以增加它们对读者的吸引力。 The discovery of an easy method for machines to apply human judgment — the complement to any AI prediction machine in specifying the risks and rewards in a wide variety of circumstances — made all the difference.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;For many decisions, specialized reward function engineers will be needed to deploy AI prediction machines at scale. The discovery of this intuitive approach for codifying human judgment into machine — fine-tuning via reinforcement learning from human feedback — may unlock many valuable applications of AI where human judgment is difficult to codify in advance but easy to implement when you see it.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Will Accelerate the Circular Economy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_12_1295939564.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Almost Green Studio/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Despite living on a planet with finite resources, our economy remains largely linear and full of single-use products. The shift toward a circular economy, where companies recover or recycle resources, has hit roadblocks, including low value of used products and high recycling costs. Harvard&amp;#8217;s D^3 Institute recently highlighted how digital tools and AI can help overcome these hurdles. They discussed three key strategies: extending the life of products, using fewer materials in production, and using more recycled materials. These tech-enabled strategies promise significant financial returns, but unlocking their full potential will need serious investment. Simply put, it&amp;#8217;s high time businesses recognized the potential of turning waste into wealth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The global economy still functions in a linear manner and is characterized by the extraction, production, consumption, and disposal of materials. This is a problem given that we live on a planet with finite resources. Yet the shift to a circular economy, in which businesses recover or recycle resources used in their value chain, has remained elusive, despite offering &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.summaequity.com/assets/Reports/PDF/230417-Investing-in-a-circular-and-waste-free-Europe.pdf&quot;>;trillions of dollars in value creation&lt;/a>;. Barriers include the low residual value of used products, an inability to collect materials, prohibitive costs of separating and processing materials, and lack of traceability of products and materials that are being recycled.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To accelerate the pace of innovation and learning, the Digital, Data, and Design (D^3) Institute at Harvard Business School recently hosted an &lt;a href=&quot;https://environment.harvard.edu/event/d3-catalyst-circular-economy-conference&quot;>;event focused on the circular economy&lt;/a>;, where entrepreneurs and business leaders shared how they&#39;re using digital tools and artificial intelligence to remove those barriers and create entirely new markets and business models. Specifically, the conference helped identify three main ways to achieve a more circular economy: increasing product utilization, material efficiency, and use of recycled materials.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Product Utilization&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Product utilization seeks to extend the useful life of a product, such as through sharing economy platforms, product refurbishment programs, or enhancing product duration. One new way companies are extending the life of the product is through over-the-air software updates that increase the residual value of a product. Take the example of the iPhone. Today, the iPhone constitutes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/the-used-smartphone-market-is-booming-surprisingly-thats-good-news-for-apple/&quot;>;80% of the market&lt;/a>; among 300 million or so phones in the secondhand market. A primary reason for this success, Marcelo Claure, former CEO of Sprint and Softbank International, explained at the event, is the forward compatibility of the iOS operating system, which ensures a user can access the app ecosystem and all the new features that Apple releases, maintaining iPhones&#39; appeal as a high-quality product in the secondhand market. Over-the-air updates of software is becoming the norm for more products — even cars. As a result, we expect an increase in the residual value of used products and an increase in product utilization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Contrary to the belief that prolonging product lifespan might hinder sales growth and therefore firms should implement a planned obsolescence strategy, leading firms perceive enhanced product utilization as a mechanism for reaching new consumers, enhancing customer satisfaction, and building business models that monetize their efforts to create more durable products through services. Apple now has &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/02/03/apple-says-it-now-has-935-million-paid-subscriptions/&quot;>;935 million subscribers&lt;/a>; in its services segment, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://investor.apple.com/sec-filings/sec-filings-details/default.aspx?FilingId=16157374&quot;>;has grown&lt;/a>; to almost $80 billion in revenues and runs at close to double the gross margin compared to the hardware business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another opportunity to extend the useful life of products is through the product-as-a-service model, where companies retain ownership of a product while consumers pay for its use. Advancements in data and tracing technology has enabled better information flow to facilitate this business model. For example, SuperCircle developed a digital infrastructure that enabled circularity in the fashion industry by integrating customer purchase data with warehouse and distribution systems to trace the lifecycle of clothing. Entrepreneur Chloe Songer, cofounder of SuperCircle, explained how they partner with apparel brands like Reformation to create a customer experience that allows for goods to be returned for a credit or discount, while also facilitating the logistics infrastructure for aggregating and selling these clothes to the recycling sector. Identifying the consumer as a temporary owner of a long-lived asset opens up a world of opportunities to continue engaging customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Material Efficiency&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Material efficiency, which refers to making products with fewer materials, is not a novel concept for many firms that have long pursued a lean operating model, characterized by minimizing waste in production processes. However, with recent breakthroughs in artificial intelligence and innovative technology, material efficiency is witnessing the emergence of even more opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, our conference heard how entrepreneur Shelly Xu&#39;s SXD Zero Waste applies artificial intelligence to redesign garment mockups that generate less pre-consumer waste from offcuts during apparel production. The result is the creation of sweaters, dresses, or pants with close to zero waste in fabric and about 55% lower cost, as opposed to 10–30% waste in traditional designs. Successful entrepreneurial solutions will be those that invest time in educating B2B customers about the potential for cost savings and the need to revise legacy processes that traditionally result in more waste, such as fashion design.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The “tough-tech” segment, using breakthrough science, engineering, and technology, also has the potential to create solutions that both reduce the material impact of existing supply chains and create “drop-in” solutions that can be incorporated into existing supply chains. An example of an entrepreneur in this space is Luciano Bueno, who founded GALY, a firm that grows cotton from cells in a lab using 80% fewer resources compared to traditional agriculture. An important part of the innovation journey in tough tech involves educating investors on the longer innovation cycles and the need for iteration on the path to scalability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Recycled Materials&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Perhaps the most well-known element of a circular business model involves minimizing the use of virgin materials as a percentage of a product&#39;s total materials. For instance, Apple&#39;s products now incorporate 20% recycled materials. Beyond reducing carbon emissions, the use of more recycled materials helps companies increase “materials security,” which is particularly concerning for industries reliant on rare minerals such as lithium and cobalt. Increasing recycled materials is also a key solution for reducing carbon intensity in hard-to-abate industries like cement and steel. However, Joy Chen and Per Anders Enkvist from McKinsey highlighted that the availability of recycled materials is currently limited, and sometimes more expensive than virgin materials. Technological enhancements to increase the availability of high-quality recycled materials and reduce costs therefore are huge opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In particular, scaling up material recovery and separation is key to making recycled material more available and affordable. Bjørn Arve Ofstad, CEO of Norsk Gjenvinning, the largest waste management company in the Nordics, explained that this sector needs an upstream feedstock, technology to sort and process the waste to be used downstream, and a downstream taker. This process needs to be done at an industry scale where materials are accessed at the right time, price, and quality. Robotics can facilitate this sorting process at lower cost. For example, Apple developed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/iphone-terminator-apples-daisy-teardown-robot-can-rip-your-phone-apart-in-18-secs/&quot;>;Daisy&lt;/a>;, a state-of-the-art robot that can breakdown an iPhone into reusable components in 18 seconds, including rare minerals such as cobalt, gold, and platinum.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Opaque supply chains represent significant barriers to understanding the breakdown of materials at end-of-life for recovery and sorting. Maria McClay, from Google, explained how in 2019 Google piloted a solution to use machine learning and analytics to provide a more comprehensive view of impact along the textile value chain, and in 2021 was able to expand the offering to other brands. Another solution described by Hari Nair from Procter &amp;amp; Gamble is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pg.co.uk/blogs/HolyGrail/&quot;>;HolyGrail project&lt;/a>; that uses digital watermarks in products to make the sorting of recyclables easier at the end of life.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Investing in the Trillion-Dollar Opportunity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To support the adoption and scaling of these digitalization-enabled solutions, we need investment to fund the trillion-dollar opportunity. Yet asset allocators in circularity face a “pattern recognition” challenge, where the capability to identify promising opportunities is still evolving. Venture capital funds have been hesitant to invest in early-stage companies with significant capital expenditure needs, which is often the case in circular solutions. On the other hand, private equity funds have been reluctant to invest in early-stage startups. One solution, described by Andrew Merino of Generate Capital, is the emergence of multi-sector, sustainability-focused funds that bridge the gap between traditional venture capital and private equity. To tap the full investment potential of a circular economy, investors need to develop in-depth sectoral expertise and innovation in investment structures.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Video Quick Take &ndash; Google&rsquo;s Gautam Ramdurai on Emerging Consumer Behavior - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM GOOGLE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/video-quick-take-googles-gautam-ramdurai-on-emerging-consumer-behavior]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div data-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;6328969026112&amp;quot;}&quot; js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;Loading... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Todd Pruzan, Senior Editor for Research and Special Projects at Harvard Business Review, recently interviewed Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager, Ads Marketing, Google Asia Pacific, for a new episode of HBR Video Quick Take. Since every business today needs to navigate a complex matrix of factors that drive sustainable and profitable growth while keeping in mind that the core of doing so is still about understanding customers and how they make decisions, Pruzan spoke with Ramdurai about new insights into emerging consumer behavior across the Asia-Pacific region.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;So much about consumer behavior seems to be in continual motion. What kinds of changes are you seeing in consumer behavior across Asia-Pacific right now?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;The things that we&#39;re finding right now are fascinating. And what&#39;s particularly important to notice is what is truly different about 2023 versus, say, 2020 and even 2022. We know the pandemic fundamentally shifted so many things, but I think as we&#39;ve come out of the pandemic, other crises are stepping in: political turmoil, climate change, and the cost-of-living crisis. When all these kinds of public crises come together, we need to start thinking about the total effect they have. And the answer is this: We are entering a truly hybrid world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Think about how everyone went online during the pandemic. But then, as we&#39;ve come out of the pandemic, when you&#39;ve thought about your grocery shopping, how have you decided which items to buy in store versus which items to buy online? There&#39;s this complex calculus that goes on in everyone&#39;s head for even the simplest of decisions just because of the number of factors in the decision itself and the number of channels you&#39;re getting information from. For example, think about the number of devices you interact with, and then multiply that by the number of channels you use, from Google Search to YouTube to any other video platform to newspapers. You navigate in and out of the online and offline worlds. And even within the online world, there&#39;s so much multiplicity, and you try to find your way out of it. That is getting very tricky in 2023.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So across Asia-Pacific, our research tells us that the gap between wondering and knowing — which has always existed — has never been this wide. And that&#39;s what we refer to as the confidence gap.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;OK, so trust and confidence are big factors today more than ever, but how are consumers navigating this landscape? How are businesses navigating it?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s start with consumers. Consumers are smart. They&#39;ve always been better at keeping up with the times than businesses will ever be. So what consumers have done is found their internal calculus fairly quickly. In other words, everyone has these decision factors that they go through and these information sources that they&#39;re going after to make their decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s take an example of someone wanting to do something: I have a three-year-old, so I have been thinking about when my three-year-old should be riding a bike. And that&#39;s a big moment, right? So when a consumer thinks, “Oh, I need to buy a bike for my daughter,” the first question is never “Where do I buy bikes?” Rather, it is “What is the right age for children to ride bikes?” It&#39;s a more foundational life question and a curiosity-driven question. You start with a question regarding the right time for a child to ride a bike, and then you slowly transition into researching what kinds of bikes there are. You end up getting sucked into videos of kids trying to learn how to ride a bike for the first time. You quickly realize you need to purchase a helmet as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This curiosity path expands the process during which consumers are finding the right information. And as consumers are navigating all this, we found that what they truly look for are six particular confidence cues. These cues are signals amid the noise; they are things that will tell them what they need to know to get closer to being confident in their decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So imagine you&#39;re in the confidence gap. You&#39;re stuck there and don&#39;t know where to go next. You&#39;re letting your curiosity guide you to the next questions. We found there are key pieces of information that bring everything together during this process. One of the confidence cues, for example, is reviews. Is this company that manufactures this particular bike well reviewed or not? Does this company have a reputation for being a company that makes safe bikes or a safe company overall?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are other things that matter too, such as social proof. And sustainability is becoming more important, so a company&#39;s having sustainability practices is becoming a bigger and bigger piece of purchase consideration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Surprisingly, we found an additional, implicit cue. This seventh cue is really about platforms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today there is a plethora of digital information, and I know I am preaching to the choir here when I tell you that the digital world is expanding. The number of information sources people have is more than they have ever had before, and with all that comes a lot of disinformation and misinformation.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In short, the platforms themselves are playing a much bigger role in 2023 than we have seen them do before. They become this seventh cue regarding how much trust you have in the platform itself where you are getting your information. It&#39;s like looking at two different news sites and deciding which one you trust more. That same logic is now moving on to the world of platforms: The platform where you look at all your information or find your information is actually as important as any of the other confidence cues that the brands or the businesses themselves might communicate to their customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;So the platform has to be part of your daily life. It has to be safe. It has to be a platform that you trust, almost the way you would trust the word of one person over another based on what they&#39;ve told you in the past. The platform is key here?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Yes, and that&#39;s what we&#39;re seeing across multiple platforms, especially Google and YouTube. With a site like Google, where in times of uncertainty people go to find out something, it&#39;s almost like a library of human intentions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So while there are six cues that the brands themselves can look at, it&#39;s not just about what you say in those six confidence cues. Rather, it&#39;s where you show up with those confidence cues that&#39;s equally important.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;So the medium really is the message or a big part of it?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Correct. I would say it is a big part of it, because the medium can never be the full message. You own your brand. You know the truth that it wants to speak to the world. But I think the complications right now — and this goes back to our research on what is unique about 2023 versus ever before — involve needing to think about the calculus that the consumers have to go through. Then we need to pair that with the calculus that the businesses have to go through. So if the consumer doesn&#39;t find the right information, at the right time, in the right place, and in the right medium, they&#39;re going to drop out of their purchase journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Wow, it sounds like that&#39;s a pretty fragile transaction there.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Absolutely. And everything is back on the table. Intuitively — and this is part of a discussion I was having with someone yesterday — you would think, “Oh, in times of uncertainty, we&#39;d go back to the things we know.” But what we&#39;re seeing is people are actually spending more time researching even if they have had brands that they&#39;ve used for a long time. So it&#39;s almost like the pandemic has heightened this need for trust and confidence to such an extent that people are moving their tried-and-trusted brands to the back of the table. What that means is you cannot take trust for granted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Again, going back to transactional trust, it&#39;s not built when the person has bought the product. It&#39;s built when the person is thinking of using a product; it&#39;s built when the consumer doesn&#39;t even know they have the need for the product. So if you go through the entire consumer journey, you need to be able to establish those confidence cues across the whole board.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And it doesn&#39;t end when they&#39;ve bought your product. The more important part of the journey is when they&#39;re actually using your product or your service. That customer experience doesn&#39;t end at the buy button. It almost starts there in many ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;If trust is important to consumers, how does this start translating to business outcomes?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;In 2023, it has a pretty direct impact. If consumers are looking for information to build up their confidence about buying your product or your service, how you show up is super important. If you don&#39;t show up the right way, it has direct implications on your bottom line. For example, in both India and Southeast Asia, one in three consumers decided not to buy a brand they were considering already because they felt a little anxious. They were not assured of their choice.¹ So that&#39;s an abandoned cart right there.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And we&#39;re seeing the positive side of trust show up in a big way as well. If you&#39;ve done the job of being with your customers/consumers throughout their buying journey and their overall purchase experience, and you&#39;ve built and fed into that trust account, highly trusted brands are seven times more likely to be purchased² — and it doesn&#39;t end at purchase. Consumers who are confident in their product choices before purchasing are almost 20% more likely to repurchase that brand.³&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Plus, the consumer journey is cyclical, so the trust and confidence you&#39;ve built with your consumers don&#39;t end when they hit “Buy.” It almost starts there. And if you want to continue building that virtuous loop of trust and confidence, you need to step up everywhere, even when they&#39;ve already bought your products. We&#39;re seeing this come through very clearly in the data. So for the confidence-seeking consumer in 2023, all brands are back on the table, and it&#39;s up to you as the seller to choose whether you want to be part of that transaction or journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;What can businesses do to keep up with what their customers need? And how do you see that changing over the next few years?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Once someone has gotten all the signals they need to make their choice, that&#39;s when we think they&#39;ve made a confidence shift: You&#39;ve helped them find the answer to that life question, and your product or service is a part of that. We think businesses that are smart and able to power this confidence shift are the ones that are going to thrive in this very messy future — and present, for that matter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But when you start thinking about how your business can help them make the confidence shift, you need to know which cue to show, when to show it, and whom is it for, because all your consumers are probably not built the same, and all of them are not in the same part of the journey. These are all moving targets: the right cues, right consumers, right formats, right messages, right devices, and right points in the decision journey. The only way to start making sense of this — and these are all predictive decisions in a lot of ways — and to do it at scale, and for large companies, especially, in milliseconds, is by harnessing the power of data and AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Again, this brings us back to whether you want to be a transactional business or a business that builds trust and confidence over time. This is an investment that you need to make across the entire customer experience. The gold standard of campaigns used to be that you&#39;d have and meet just one KPI a quarter, but we&#39;re moving away from that. Now the gold standard is whether you can drive new customers who also have high lifetime value. Those used to be two different meetings in the marketing rooms, but now they&#39;re being mushed together. The way to unpack this complexity is with data and AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Gautam, thank you for your insights. Do you have any parting words today, especially about how you are going to find that bike for your daughter?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;What a complex question! There are many life questions that exist when it comes to buying that bike. I need to keep the following in mind as I navigate that path: We know that life is a lot more complicated and complex than it has been before, and we don&#39;t know what the next set of uncertainties will be. We also know that they will come; there will be more uncertainty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regarding the confidence gap that has always been there, consumers will still find themselves in it, and maybe it will widen. Maybe the confidence cues will evolve. But I think we have to keep our ear to the ground to understand our consumers&#39; decision making if we want to know which cues they need. Our job is to help them make that confidence shift, and that will only become more and more important as we move into the future. The world of complex decision making is here to stay, and the businesses that invest in their ability to make that confidence shift with the power of data and AI are probably the ones that are going to thrive in this environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Thank you so much for a great conversation and for all of your insights today.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Thank you, Todd, for having me.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;To learn more, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkwithgoogle.com/intl/en-apac/marketing-strategies/automation/build-brand-confidence-ai-marketing/?utm_source=twg_partnership_external&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023-APAC-GML-EVOS-HBR-VQT-HL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Think With Google&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Return to the “&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/multiply-your-marketing-with-ai&quot;>;Multiply Your Marketing With AI&lt;/a>;” Sponsor Content Hub from Google APAC on HBR.org&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;¹Source: Google/Kantar/Quantum, “Emotional Value of Search”, IN, ID, VN, MY, PH, TH, PK, 2021, n=5006 P18M category buyers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;² Source: Edelman, “Trust, The New Brand Equity”, 2022, n=14,000 consumers across 14 countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;³ Source: Google/ Ipsos, Decoding Repurchase, AU, IN, ID, JP, KR, VN, 2023, n=1500 per market, Buyers of Home appliances, Personal care, Health and wellbeing products.&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Three Ways To Use The Customer Perspective As A Measure Of Success - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/three-ways-to-use-the-customer-perspective-as-a-measure-of-success]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358516&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_KPI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;In business, you can&#39;t improve what you&#39;re not measuring—and today&#39;s organizations typically measure progress and success with key performance indicators (KPIs).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A successful business is synonymous with higher customer satisfaction, retention, and overall brand reputation. So it&#39;s no surprise that most companies rank customer experience as their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superoffice.com/blog/customer-experience-statistics/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;top business priority&lt;/a>;. But all too often, in their mission to track and quantify progress, business leaders end up prioritizing processes that directly oppose customer-centric behaviors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Traditional KPIs include measures of profitability, productivity, and process efficiency—all of which are internal metrics. Analyzing these metrics can undoubtedly give indications of overall performance. But when prioritized above all else, they risk missing the bigger picture of how a business can provide the most value to customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumers are increasingly deriving value from their interactions and experiences with a brand. Eighty-three percent of consumers pay as much attention to &lt;a href=&quot;https://khoros.com/resources&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;how brands treat them&lt;/a>; as they do to the products, and 89% report &lt;a href=&quot;https://harris-interactive.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;switching to a competitor&lt;/a>; following a poor experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So as experience becomes a more important measure of performance, the most successful companies are creating emotional connections at every touchpoint. With today&#39;s consumers firmly in the driver&#39;s seat, business leaders need to have the right tools, processes, and overall customer-centric culture to stay in the game.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Customer Value as a KPI&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Although efficiency, productivity, and profitability will continue to be important, customer value is rapidly becoming the real star of the analytics show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, measuring customer value is more complex than tracking traditional KPIs. Factors such as social value, brand cachet, and the emotional experience a service or product provides come into play—all of which are harder to quantify with standard methods.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s how to shift your KPI scorecard toward customer value to set yourself up for success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Establish which KPIs will give you rich, customer-centric data.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Customer engagement metrics are useful at this stage, helping you allocate your resources better and establish standards to monitor and assess—and, crucially, understand—how your customer views you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A good range of customer engagement metrics include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Customer satisfaction score &lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Measuring your customer satisfaction score tells you how happy a customer was with their last interaction with your company and gives you a chance to improve based on their feedback. Net promoter score is a similar metric you can use to measure the customer experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Churn rate&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Your churn rate reflects the percentage of customers who stop doing business with you during a specific period. Although customers leave for a variety of reasons, you need to know whether there is a consistent theme so you can address the cause.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Customer lifetime value&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This KPI ties nicely into churn. Your customer lifetime value score will give you the expected revenue your company can generate from a customer, helping you estimate the future return from marketing initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Let customer value take center stage with customer performance indicators.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;KPIs are a great place to start, but it can be too easy to get lost in the numbers and distracted from what matters to customers. Another approach to measuring success is to supplement these metrics with customer performance indicators (CPIs).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many companies confuse KPIs with CPIs. Although KPIs can be an effective measure of sentiment, there&#39;s still a risk that KPIs overlook what&#39;s relevant to customers. KPIs are intrinsically linked to a company&#39;s goals, but CPIs focus on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-performace-indicators-surbhit-suman-banga&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;what customers care about the most&lt;/a>;, such as value and satisfaction, which lead to loyalty and retention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ongoing dialogue with your customers is the best way to get the most out of your CPIs. Ask them what value they derive from your business, what keeps them coming back, and what influences their purchases. Ask, listen, design, implement—and then ask again.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Bring together the right metrics, the right tools, and the right mindset.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;This continuous loop of monitoring and adjusting requires a more sophisticated approach than isolated measurement tools collecting data from single touchpoints. Unlocking value from customer-centric data requires an analytics platform that can integrate, extract, and synthesize data from across the software stack.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Customer-relationship management (CRM) technology with agile, intuitive analytics features can yield results far beyond what managers see in their organization-wide tableau setup. A 360-degree view of your business empowers you to make bigger decisions based on granular detail.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Judging your measurement of success from traditional KPIs risks creating a situation in which teams are motivated to perform aggressive sales tactics to achieve their targets, which can be destructive to good customer relationships. Complementing these metrics with CPIs cultivates a different type of accountability, encouraging teams to achieve customer satisfaction above all else—which can lead to better retention and more revenue.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;The Experience of Customer Experience&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Always remember that customer experience is just that: an experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumers are less interested in your brand than you are. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2019/11/21/consumers-are-hungry-for-an-experience-based-connection-with-your-brand/?sh=2974384358fe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;They&#39;re focused on their own experience&lt;/a>;. To truly measure your brand&#39;s impact on their lives, you need to look past individual touchpoints and evaluate their holistic experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although this is about more than just the numbers, the only way to know whether you&#39;re hitting the mark is with data. Your analytical tools and processes need to be flexible enough to help you measure and deliver authentic experiences that will cultivate lasting customer relationships.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm.com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Discover&lt;/a>; how Zoho CRM&#39;s intuitive analytics can help you deliver lasting customer value.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovering Where ChatGPT Can Create Value for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_4896946.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Although the speed, scale, and scope of ChatGPT&amp;#8217;s impact may be unique, the underlying phenomenon &amp;#8212; an emerging technology transforming vast parts of business and society &amp;#8212; is not. But harnessing the power of emerging technology requires a new approach. Unlike traditional methods for innovation, such as design thinking, ChatGPT poses a fundamentally different challenge because there are no clear problems to address, user pain points to alleviate, or KPIs to achieve. In fact, ChatGPT can seemingly solve problems in almost any industry, domain, or context. Using it, therefore, requires a different skill: emergent thinking, which involves generating ideas for innovation without fully understanding the problem that needs to be solved.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When OpenAI released its flagship product ChatGPT last November, it reached 1 million users in only four days and 100 million users in two months, achieving this milestone more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/chatgpt-sets-record-fastest-growing-user-base-analyst-note-2023-02-01/&quot;>;75% faster than any other tech giant&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has continued to evolve quickly, beginning as an AI chatbot that only responded to user prompts. Now it includes features such as analyzing data and interpreting images, leaving everyone from high school students to C-suite executives scrambling to learn ChatGPT so they can use it in new and productive ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although the speed, scale, and scope of ChatGPT&#39;s impact may be unique, the underlying phenomenon — an emerging technology transforming vast parts of business and society — is not. But harnessing the power of emerging technology requires a new approach. Unlike traditional methods for innovation, such as &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/why-design-thinking-works&quot;>;design thinking&lt;/a>;, ChatGPT poses a fundamentally different challenge because there are no clear problems to address, user pain points to alleviate, or KPIs to achieve. In fact, ChatGPT can seemingly solve problems in almost any industry, domain, or context. Using it, therefore, requires a different skill: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/326964001_An_Integrated_Model_of_Dynamic_Problem_Solving_Within_Organizational_Constraints&quot;>;emergent thinking&lt;/a>;, which involves generating ideas for innovation without fully understanding the problem that needs to be solved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Two of us (Johnathan and Jennifer) recently conducted &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886923001289&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; showing that the main thought process for this style of innovation is to start by understanding the core functions of a technology, &lt;em>;then&lt;/em>; explore how it can be used to solve problems across different domains. Other hallmarks of emergent thinking include evaluating ideas without understanding the criteria for success, improvising ideas with little preparation or planning, and changing a project&#39;s target outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These activities tend to run counter to good business practices promoting efficiency and reliability, and they may even violate some of the core tenets of design thinking — namely the need to identify a clear user problem to address &lt;em>;before&lt;/em>; generating ideas for a solution. Yet, they&#39;re also critical when trying to leverage ChatGPT (or any other emerging technology, for that matter) for innovation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many companies have already started integrating ChatGPT into their products, processes, and services. By analyzing this burgeoning landscape of innovation, we&#39;ve identified three emergent-thinking pathways for leaders that can help increase the chances of implementing ChatGPT successfully while also avoiding potential pitfalls.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 1: Exploiting a Current Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first pathway involves using ChatGPT to further exploit a value proposition a company already provides to customers. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/instacart-could-do-worse-than-incinerating-32-bln-2023-03-01/&quot;>;Instacart has grown to $2.5 billion in annual revenue&lt;/a>; by focusing on the core value proposition of providing fast, reliable, and affordable grocery delivery to customers at home. Recently, they &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instacart.com/company/updates/instacart-chatgpt/&quot;>;launched a plugin for ChatGPT&lt;/a>; that aims to strengthen this value proposition by increasing the speed and efficiency of ordering groceries online. With this plugin, customers can receive recommendations for meals to prepare, and once they find something they like, ChatGPT will create a new Instacart order that automatically adds all the necessary ingredients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To pursue this pathway for innovation, start by using ChatGPT without directing it toward any specific customer problems. This thought process can be challenging because most business training teaches us to be strategic thinkers and verify the importance of customer problems before spending any time developing solutions. However, starting with strategic goals like this can actually blind us to seeing ChatGPT&#39;s potential for new and valuable applications. Instead, start with an open mind and deeply engage with the tool to understand its core functions. Once you have that understanding, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048733320301463&quot;>;natural human cognition will take over&lt;/a>; and start making connections to any relevant problems you might be aware of.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, one of the core functions of ChatGPT is to interpret and generate natural language text that provides human-like responses to a wide variety of questions, prompts, and requests. Companies can use this function to enhance existing features of products or services that focus specifically on text-based interactions with customers. For instance, the product-management tool Notion now provides customers with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.notion.so/product/ai&quot;>;immediate access to ChatGPT&lt;/a>; at the tap of the spacebar, which activates a prompt to receive an AI response that can be immediately integrated into existing tasks and workflows. As the functions of ChatGPT continue to grow, new possibilities will emerge for how it can be used to further enhance value propositions across a wider range of companies and contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 2: Expanding the Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A second pathway uses ChatGPT to expand a company&#39;s value proposition by solving new problems for customers in a way that complements their current offering. For example, Khan Academy was created in 2006 with the mission of providing all students with a free, world-class education. They&#39;ve since grown to nearly 20 million users per month, primarily by offering short online videos that start with a blank canvas and get filled with colorful, hand-written text. Recently, they integrated ChatGPT into their platform &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.khanacademy.org/sal-khans-2023-ted-talk-ai-in-the-classroom-can-transform-education/&quot;>;by creating a personalized AI tutor called Khanmigo&lt;/a>;. This tool not only helps students by guiding them through online videos and practice questions more effectively, but it can also help teachers by explaining teaching methods and designing lesson plans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can follow the same pathway by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/335242871_Matthew_A_Cronin_and_Jeffrey_Loewenstein_The_Craft_of_Creativity&quot;>;clearly defining your perspective and learning how to change it&lt;/a>;. For emergent thinking, this first involves breaking down a value proposition into three core elements:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;The goals customers are trying to accomplish&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The context in which customers are trying to accomplish those goals&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The specific target demographic of the customers&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once defined, the next step is to assess how ChatGPT&#39;s core functions (see Pathway 1) can help expand each element in new directions. For example, Khan Academy originally focused on &lt;em>;helping&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;K–12 students&lt;/em>; (target demographic) &lt;em>;learn topics at a self-guided pace&lt;/em>; (goal), &lt;em>;done&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;completely online &lt;/em>;(context). Using ChatGPT, they expanded this goal for students by facilitating online learning either through self-guided practice or via an AI tutor, and they also expanded the target demographic to include teachers, helping them accomplish new goals that were not previously possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This two-step definition and expansion process offers a complementary skillset to design thinking, which typically encourages people to think of many different solutions before converging on one to implement. With emergent thinking, however, you apply those same &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/better-brainstorming&quot;>;brainstorming techniques&lt;/a>; to the problem, rather than the solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During this process, it&#39;s key to maintain an open mind and avoid settling on a problem too quickly, which may be particularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/228198146_Performance_Pressure_as_a_Double-Edged_Sword_Enhancing_Team_Motivation_While_Undermining_the_Use_of_Team_Knowledge&quot;>;challenging to do in conditions of uncertainty&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has unleashed an unprecedented level of pressure on companies to act quickly, or else suffer dramatic consequences for their future survival. However, research shows it&#39;s also possible to &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/jpo/article-abstract/7/1/2/5707381&quot;>;withstand these pressures and explore a wider range of innovation options&lt;/a>;. To do that, work with trusted collaborators so you can navigate ambiguity more effectively and take greater risks together.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 3: Exploring a New Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pathway is based on using ChatGPT to explore a completely new value proposition that customers may not even know they need yet. Although this may run counter to traditional methods for innovation, it also aligns with common advice for creating breakthroughs. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/1998-05-25/steve-jobs-theres-sanity-returning&quot;>;when Steve Jobs was asked&lt;/a>; whether Apple did any market research when developing the iMac, he responded: “It&#39;s really hard to design products by focus groups. A lot of times, people don&#39;t know what they want until you show it to them.” This wisdom seems to have been fully embraced by OpenAI, which released ChatGPT to the public and is now discovering countless ways it can be used in various contexts to accomplish new and unforeseen goals. This pathway for innovation represents the purest form of emergent thinking, which has the greatest uncertainty and therefore must also be pursued with the greatest caution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The main challenge comes when trying to converge on a single problem to focus on out of the many dozens identified when brainstorming different goals, contexts, and target demographics (see Pathway 2). When organizations have relatively clearer value propositions — such as increasing the speed of online ordering at Instacart or improving the quality of online education at Khan Academy — it can be easier to filter out problems that seem far-fetched or unlikely to reflect valuable customer needs. However, when customer needs are still unknown and emerging along with the technology, it becomes difficult for teams to agree on a shared direction to pursue. This becomes especially challenging when trying to include the diverse perspectives that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/smarter-collaboration-a-new-approach-to-breaking-down-barriers-and-transforming-work/10535&quot;>;fundamental to innovation&lt;/a>;, because team members can pull the project in different directions &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Extreme-Teaming-Lessons-Cross-Sector-Leadership/dp/1786354500&quot;>;despite their best intentions to collaborate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help overcome these challenges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2343944&quot;>;identify a clear and coherent analogy&lt;/a>; that summarizes the core value proposition. For example, Tome is a startup that&#39;s using ChatGPT to help customers create better presentations out of online documents, videos, and digital content. However, instead of highlighting all the specific benefits they can provide, they&#39;ve described their product as an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20230427180425/https:/beta.tome.app/&quot;>;AI storytelling partner&lt;/a>;.” This simple concept helps integrate many different features into a coherent product experience so that both developers and customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/234021855_When_Is_a_New_Thing_a_Good_Thing_Technological_Change_Product_Form_Design_and_Perceptions_of_Value_for_Product_Innovations&quot;>;easily understand its value&lt;/a>;. By creating an analogy for your product, you can avoid wasting valuable resources creating features that might not support the core value proposition, and you can help customers develop a clear mental model of the various features and why they can be useful.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ChatGPT is an unprecedented technology that has potential to unlock value for millions of customers across many industries. However, pursuing these rewards also comes with considerable risks, as we&#39;re all entering uncharted territory with AI, and we must learn how to use it effectively so it can be leveraged for positive rather than negative outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Build Upon the Legacy of Your Family Business &mdash; and Make It Your Own]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_1009603322.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Sean Murphy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Family companies often have a strong sense of history and tradition. Although these legacies can create advantages, they sometimes leave next-generation leaders feeling handcuffed or constrained by the way their ancestors ran things. To overcome that, they should seek to reformulate the company&amp;#8217;s story in a way that creates advantages for the present.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Founded by Henry Ford &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/about/history.html&quot;>;in 1903&lt;/a>;, the Ford Motor Company rocketed to success by mass-producing reliable, low-priced automobiles. When Henry&#39;s son, &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/articles/history/edsel-ford-biography.html&quot;>;Edsel&lt;/a>;, took the helm in 1918, he championed a different strategy for a new era. He sought to replace the Model T — iconic but outdated — with a more modern design geared to high-end and foreign markets, and later embraced compromise with labor amid the suffering of the Great Depression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But Henry could not let go of Ford&#39;s origin story, undermining his son at every turn. The result was declining sales and years of labor strife that left the company on the brink of collapse by the 1940s. It was only the efforts of Edsel&#39;s son, the more forceful &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.automotivehalloffame.org/honoree/henry-ford-ii/&quot;>;Henry Ford II&lt;/a>;, that saved the auto giant from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In family enterprise, generational transitions often pit one narrative against another: tradition versus innovation, continuity versus change. Indeed, when older generations craft painstaking succession plans or build elaborate constraints into trusts or shareholder agreements, they are really constructing a story: about the values and life lessons that helped them succeed, and that they hope will do the same for their children. Younger generations, however, must often adapt this narrative to their own goals and values, along with the changing world around them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to reconcile conflicting narratives can spell ruin for a family business or the waste of a financial legacy, as it nearly did for the Fords. To avoid this fate, families need to think differently about the stories they tell.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The value of critical distance&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Conventional wisdom holds that family heritage, like wealth and reputation, “belongs” to the older generation. In this telling, succeeding generations are merely stewards or caretakers. They are given an inheritance or entrusted with the family business — and then charged with not frittering it away or screwing it up. Framed this way, a legacy can feel more like a burden than a gift.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, it&#39;s not as simple as that. Research suggests that younger generations &lt;em>;do&lt;/em>; value their family heritage, especially as a source of traditions more motivating than money alone, and are motivated to preserve it. According to a 2021 &lt;a href=&quot;https://home.kpmg/content/dam/kpmg/ca/pdf/2022/02/who-are-the-guardians-of-family-legacy-report-en.pdf&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; of 300 Canadian business owners by the Family Enterprise Foundation, nearly 90% of next-generation family business leaders believe it is important to preserve a legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But younger generations also want something more from that heritage: a sense of purpose, a collective identity for the family, the seeds of new entrepreneurial gambits, permission to go their own way. And as our own &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0894486520941944?journalCode=fbra&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows, next-generation leaders are uniquely positioned to find what they are looking for in the family story.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Older generations often identify closely with the family or the family business, which can actually obstruct key learnings from the past. Eager to protect the family&#39;s reputation, they may downplay scandal or setback rather than learn from it. By contrast, our analysis of 94 family businesses shows that younger generations tend to have more critical distance from the family story. This lets them grapple with its difficult chapters and respond appropriately, whether by making amends for past misdeeds or by reforming business practices going forward. It also frees them to draw insights from their story that can fuel innovation and sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Legacy as a source of purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How, then, can the next generation build on their family legacy while recasting it as their own? Our research and experience suggest four strategies for next-generation leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Seek out role models in the family story.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some next-generation leaders hesitate to embark on risky new ventures outside the traditional scope of the family business. Locating exemplars in the family story can legitimize a new way forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One third-generation CEO used this approach to advance his vision for a more sustainable enterprise. Fredo Arias-King, head of Mexican pine resin producer Pinosa Group, had lamented the disappearance of Mexico&#39;s ancient pine forests that threatened both the industry and the communities that depend on it. Then he stumbled onto the published speeches of his grandfather, company founder José Antonio Arias Álvarez, who had preached environmental stewardship. “I don&#39;t think he could have known just how devastated the forest would eventually become,” said Arias-King, “but somehow my grandfather knew that planting trees would become extremely important.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Affirmed by his grandfather&#39;s words, Arias-King helped found &lt;a href=&quot;https://ejidoverde.com/about-us/&quot;>;Ejido Verde&lt;/a>;, a nonprofit that would later become an independent, for-profit enterprise. By making no-interest loans to farmers and communities, with pine resin as the means of repayment, the organization promotes reforesting through new pine plantations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;2. Forge an identity beyond the founder-entrepreneur.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to revere the family&#39;s wealth creator. For the two adult grandchildren of one founder-entrepreneur — a private equity pioneer who rose from poverty to become one of America&#39;s richest people — that was the problem. They wanted their own children, beneficiaries of a generation-skipping trust, to know the person behind the legacy that would pass to them. So they engaged one of us (John Seaman) to probe beyond the classic rags-to-riches tale they had heard growing up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The founder, they learned, was a gifted yet deeply troubled man. This more nuanced understanding enabled the two generations to have a frank conversation about the issues raised by their ancestor&#39;s life: the obligations of a business to its workers and communities; the consequences of untreated mental illness; and the unfair burden often shouldered by women in wealthy families.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This conversation, in turn, led members of the fourth generation, all in their twenties, to rethink their roles in the family enterprise. One set aside her qualms about joining the family business and put herself on a path to succeed her father as president, but with a determination to nudge the company&#39;s private equity portfolio toward impact investing. Another resolved to pursue her own entrepreneurial dreams outside of the business, rooted in progressive values that were in stark contrast with her great-grandfather&#39;s. Still another joined the board of the family foundation, where she helped steer its grant-making toward her generation&#39;s individual passions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By seeing their founder-entrepreneur in human terms, the family&#39;s younger generation was able to move beyond hero worship to forge their own identities — which promised to make them responsible owners &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;stewards of their ancestor&#39;s wealth and the business that created it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3. Reckon with past wrongs to find a new path forward.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many families have skeletons in the closet —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/how-companies-can-address-their-historical-transgressions&quot;>;scandal or wrongdoing&lt;/a>; they have long concealed or downplayed. (Henry Ford&#39;s history of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/americanexperience/features/henryford-antisemitism/&quot;>;antisemitism&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/how-the-ford-motor-company-won-a-battle-and-lost-ground-45814533/&quot;>;violent confrontations&lt;/a>; with unions are examples of this.) The willingness to confront these darker chapters, it turns out, can be a powerful motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was the case for the Reimann family, owners of consumer goods conglomerate JAB Holding Company and one of Germany&#39;s richest families. The three adult children of Albert Reimann Jr., who ran the company in the 1930s and 1940s, knew they had been born of their father&#39;s affair with an employee, Emilie Landecker. They also knew that Emilie&#39;s Jewish father, Alfred, had been murdered by the Nazis. But it was not until 2019, when they commissioned research on the company, that a more sinister secret emerged: their father and paternal grandfather were themselves ardent believers in Nazi race theory who abused forced laborers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It was the younger generation — Albert Jr.&#39;s grandchildren — who were most adamant about reckoning with this secret. “When I read of the atrocities…sanctioned by my grandfather, I felt like throwing up,” recalled Martin Reimann. “I cannot claim that I was very interested in politics before…But after what happened, I changed my mind.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the insistence of Martin&#39;s generation, the Reimanns paid compensation to former forced laborers and their families. But they did not stop there. They refocused their family foundation on combating antisemitism and strengthening democratic institutions. They also renamed the foundation in honor of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alfredlandecker.org/en&quot;>;Alfred Landecker&lt;/a>;, making him the narrative driver behind the more fundamental change they sought. Far from an isolated act of corporate atonement, then, this was an attempt by the next generation to use lessons from their family heritage to build a more just future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;4. Leverage the family story as a source of competitive advantage.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For some family business entrepreneurs, the next venture can begin with a step back. So it was for British restaurateurs (and sisters) Helen and Lisa Tse, whose family heritage empowered their rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their grandmother, Lily Kwok, had emigrated from Hong Kong in 1956 and settled in Manchester, where she and her daughter Mabel built one of Britain&#39;s first Chinese restaurants. But the business eventually went bankrupt, the victim of racism and Chinese gangs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The story might have ended there. Instead, Helen and Lisa picked up the threads of their family narrative and carried it forward. Abandoning successful professional careers, they established their own Manchester restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sweetmandarin.com/&quot;>;Sweet Mandarin&lt;/a>;, in 2004. But the restaurant only took off when Helen published a best-selling memoir about her grandmother. With this narrative platform, the sisters branched out into other endeavors, like cookbooks and cookery classes, tied to their own life stories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the Tse sisters, family heritage proved to be a source of competitive advantage. By recovering an immigrant&#39;s tale with universal appeal, they gained acceptance outside of their own ethnic communities. And by situating themselves in an entrepreneurial tradition spanning three generations, they created a sense of longevity that evoked quality and trustworthiness, even as they also innovated new products alongside recipes inherited from their grandmother.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Family legacy is not a monologue; it&#39;s a dialogue, a collective story that belongs to the whole family. When families think of legacy in these terms, they empower younger generations to harness that story to their own purposes, drawing strength from their elders. Legacy, in short, becomes not a burden but a blessing — one that can help families sustain wealth and purpose long into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Identify the Right Strategic Goals for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_670123874.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;cyano66/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In setting strategic objectives, companies usually end up with a list of worthy but vague aspirations. The secret to getting a list of clearly defined and measurable objectives is to anchor them in what you, as a company&amp;#8217;s leaders, want to get from your stakeholders. This leads you to defining desired behavioral outcomes, even fairly obvious ones like buying more. The debate can then move to thinking about how to trigger that behavior, and progress toward these outcomes can be described in measures that are in dollars, like revenue; quantities, like units sold; or percentages, like market share. Thinking in this way sounds prosaic, even obvious, but it is an effective way of getting a management team to think clearly about what they need to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann is the CEO of my country&#39;s largest independent, not-for-profit aged-care provider, offering residential aged care, retirement living, and at-home support. It was established well over a hundred years ago and is set in many of its ways. One of these is how strategic objective-setting is conducted. But Ann&#39;s not happy with the process. I asked her, “Why not?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;She explained. “When we get together to discuss our future direction as a business, we invariably get to the point where we need to write down our objectives. If we&#39;re using a facilitator, and we usually do, that person will walk over to a flipchart or whiteboard and write &#39;Objectives&#39; at the top. Then everyone piles in brainstorming to produce a list that&#39;s far too long.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“And you whittle that list down?” I asked.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Yes,” Ann continued. “The discussion and arm-wrestling then start with the aim of reducing the items to about half a dozen. After some considerable time, my exhausted and frustrated colleagues are only too happy to move on to the next agenda item.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann explained how her team was usually not content with the result. “Nor am I,” she added, “because invariably the &#39;Objectives&#39; list contains a hodgepodge of activities, nice-to-haves, and vague statements of intent.” Ann showed me her latest result:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;To become an employer of choice.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To grow the business by opening additional centers.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To maintain stability in resident and client care.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To manage risks and crises effectively.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To secure compliance with regulatory authorities.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To transform operations by adopting additional technology.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Maybe your own endeavors have produced a similar list. You might be wondering: What&#39;s wrong with this? The answer is: Plenty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Any strategy she comes up with will have to specify what the company can do to meet the needs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;each key stakeholder group&lt;/a>;: residents, clients, employees, suppliers, shareholders, and the community. This means that her business will have to take a &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the-volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;position on the factors important to each of those groups&lt;/a>;. For instance, Ann&#39;s management team must set policy on working conditions, pay, organization culture, and so on for employees. What should guide these decisions? And how will Ann know if the decisions are progressing the organization? How will she measure this?&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The answers should be her list of strategic objectives. But Ann&#39;s hodgepodge doesn&#39;t deliver a clear line of sight between the business&#39;s competitive stance for each key stakeholder group and the results. How can you tell if a strategy is working? It&#39;s as though the list of objectives exists in a black hole.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Shift Your Thinking About Objective-Setting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The trick to breaking away is to flip your perspective and ask what your organization wants &lt;em>;from&lt;/em>; its key stakeholders. (This comes as an “aha” moment for most managers.) These will be your strategic objectives. For example, consider revenue from customers, innovation from employees, and support from the community. Your thinking must shift to be outside-in if you are to produce successful strategic objectives. If you picture organization objective-setting this way, you can see how it can be broken into a stakeholder-by-stakeholder exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 1: Identify a behavioral outcome for each stakeholder group.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;To illustrate, let me share a story. One CEO I advise, Stuart, heads up a mutual bank with “members.” I ran a workshop for him and his managers. We identified the credit union&#39;s key stakeholders, one of which was, naturally, members. To break through the traditional brainstorming hodgepodge, I asked the group a seemingly simple question: “What do you want your members to do?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This came as a surprisingly fresh approach to the group and required them to think more deeply. After some discussion, we got this: “To get members to borrow more and to get potential members to become members.” I explained how I call this a &lt;em>;behavioral outcome&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 2: Convert behavioral outcomes into organization objectives.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I then led Stuart&#39;s group to the second step, which is to convert this behavioral outcome to an &lt;em>;organization objective.&lt;/em>; This usually starts with “to increase” or “to decrease.” After careful consideration and debate, the group agreed to: “To increase revenue from current and future members.” Notice “future.” This will be driven by positioning on the strategic factors relevant to members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Why didn&#39;t I just start there at the second step? The reason is that invariably the process falls back into becoming a hodgepodge. Identifying a behavioral outcome for each key stakeholder group first anchors organization objectives, which then become clear and measurable&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 3: Identify measures.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This brings me to the third step: identifying &lt;em>;measures&lt;/em>;, a short list of which is usually referred to as key performance indicators or KPIs. This can be tricky, as all sorts of things become labeled as KPIs in exercises like this. In the past, Stuart&#39;s organization had labeled actions by individuals and program descriptions as KPIs. So, I needed to point out that a key performance indicator is a key performance &lt;em>;measure.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The clincher for Stuart and his group came when I demonstrated that there are only three ways to measure results in business and that they can be neatly summarized by three symbols: $ (or the local currency), # (number of), and % (percentage). No one had condensed results for them in that way before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The advantage of this is that Stuart and his team now have a stakeholder-oriented objective for members that can be measured. Stuart can measure the total revenue generated by new and existing members; the number of new and existing members; and the bank&#39;s percentage of market share. Any strategies aimed at creating competitive advantage — around, for example, product range, customer service, and pricing — can be evaluated using these hard results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I do this for each of an organization&#39;s key stakeholders: customers, employees, suppliers, and so on. It always gets a management group to probe what the organization is really trying to achieve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;Your Objective-Setting Journey&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;If you want to produce clearly targeted strategy, you simply must avoid the standard practice of brainstorming to yield a list of strategic objectives. It leads to a hodgepodge of difficult-to-measure items, as Ann&#39;s experience demonstrates. Instead, rethink your journey by identifying who your key stakeholders are&amp;nbsp;— and what you want from them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This will provide you with clear and measurable outcomes that will help focus your organization&#39;s strategic positions for each of your key stakeholders. Strategic clarity will be your result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Will Working with AI Really Require?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_EdmonDeHaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Edmon de Haro; filonmar/Getty Images (chip); JulieAlexK/Getty Images (glasses)&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities, and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent. To do this effectively, they need to think about where and how this technology will be used to assist people in their work &amp;#8212; where people and machines will collaborate &amp;#8212; and where either people or AI have skills that give them a clear advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Despite concerns about machines replacing human workers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning/&quot;>;research &lt;/a>;challenges the overhyped claims of ascendant AI. In most knowledge-intensive tasks, workers will more likely find themselves augmented &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0007681318300387&quot;>;in partnership with machines&lt;/a>; than automated out of a job. Humans and machines will simultaneously collaborate and compete with one another, like a track team competing in various events. In some events, like the 100-yard dash, teammates compete against each other, but in others, such as the relay race, they work together towards a common goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In such a relationship, humans and AI systems both need distinct competitive and cooperative skills. Competitive skills refer to the unique advantages that either humans or AI possess over the other, while cooperative skills enhance the ability of humans and AI to work together effectively. To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities — and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Humans&#39; competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI may not replace workers in a human-centered workplace, but it could fundamentally transform their work. In order to remain relevant and indispensable, humans need to work &lt;em>;with &lt;/em>;and &lt;em>;against &lt;/em>;the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effectively collaborating with AI systems — working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; them — requires data-driven analytical abilities, but also understanding about the capabilities and limitations of the machines (areas where human intervention is most required), how to interpret and contextualize AI-generated insights, and the ethical considerations of AI-powered decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Data-centric skills:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the results generated by algorithms to inform and support decision-making. A &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/boost-your-teams-data-literacy&quot;>;recent survey&lt;/a>; highlighted (1) the ability to distinguish relevant data and evaluate its credibility, (2) capability to validate results by testing hypotheses through A/B testing, and (3) skill in creating and tailoring clear and comprehensible visualizations to communicate results to multiple stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AI literacy:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how algorithms work, how they can support and augment human decision-making as well as the limitations and biases that may be present in their decision-making processes. Area experts will likely take on the responsibility of developing fairness criteria for algorithmic outcomes that promote equity, especially for vulnerable populations, and continuously auditing algorithmic results against these criteria.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Algorithmic communication:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how to articulate human needs and objectives to algorithms, as well as how to interpret and explain the results generated by algorithms to others is important and &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-digital-mindset-what-it-really-takes-to-thrive-in-the-age-of-data-algorithms-and-ai/10413&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that we often err by talking to machines – even advanced AI tools – as though they were human. We do better when we recognize that we should talk to machines in specific ways that build on their strengths. For example, through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/prompt-engineering-ai-chatgpt-jobs-explained-2023-3&quot;>;“prompt engineering,”&lt;/a>; or crafting prompts to elicit most effective responses from AI systems, humans can teach AI models to produce the desired results for specific tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;People also need to hone the human-centered skills and abilities that cannot be replicated by machines — that help them work &lt;em>;against&lt;/em>; AI partners — such as those rooted in emotional intelligence (eg, communication skills for interacting with other human stakeholders), a strategic and holistic perspective, critical thinking and intuitive decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Emotional intelligence:&lt;/strong>; The ability to recognize one&#39;s own emotions and reflect on them in the context of interacting with algorithms, as well as understanding and communicating the emotional implications of algorithm-generated results. For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-chatbot-workplace-call-centers-5cd2142a?st=6fma808gi52qayz&amp;amp;reflink=article_email_share&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR0oBB-2wT03uN-8OV3kaJGNXqDPKW-ZJ_7hc8KdYMYlHPK3dCrqxJr-GcA&quot;>;human customer service agents&lt;/a>; may not solely rely on scripts or real-time advice provided by the AI agents, but instead personalize solutions by empathetically comprehending the customers&#39; requirements or feelings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Holistic and strategic thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to consider the big picture and understand how algorithmic results fit into the larger context of a problem or decision. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2153353922007507&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, algorithmic inference can inform pathologists, but they still need to consider factors such as patients&#39; medical history, lifestyle, and overall health to arrive at an informed and comprehensive diagnosis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Creativity and outside-the-box thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to think creatively and use algorithms in novel and innovative ways. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/si/en/pages/strategy-operations/articles/AI-in-marketing.html&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, AI systems are used to analyze massive consumer data and identify patterns in the interests and behavior of a target audience, but it is the creative thinking of marketers that will craft a message that resonates with the audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Critical and ethical thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to critically assess machine inferences, and to understand the ethical implications and responsibilities associated with using algorithms, including privacy and accountability. As generative AI such as ChatGPT are increasingly integrated into various products, experts in different business domains are needed to work alongside these systems to continuously address &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/chatbots-got-big-and-their-ethical-red-flags-got-bigger/&quot;>;potential false or biased information &lt;/a>;to which these systems are prone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI&#39;s competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It is not only humans that must acquire new capabilities. While AI systems are rapidly expanding their competitive abilities over humans, they still need to improve their cooperative skills in order to be widely adopted by organizations. In particular, the lack of explainability remains a challenge in high-stakes decisions, hindering accountability and compliance with legal requirements. For example, if the AI&#39;s decision-making process remains opaque to medical professionals, it will impede the adoption of these systems in healthcare, even if these systems deliver near-optimal decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To work effectively with human partners, AI systems need skills such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;NLP (Natural Language Processing):&lt;/strong>; The ability to process, analyze, understand and mimic human language. Systems like ChatGPT excel at interacting with humans because they make it easy for people to ask questions and express themselves in a natural way, including expressing emotions like excitement, frustration, or surprise. The reality, however, is that these systems are far from &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4213593&quot;>;sentient&lt;/a>;. Situations that go beyond a function are best done by a human or with human supervision. For example, AI can analyze and reveal patterns in healthcare data, but it should not replace a physician&#39;s role in providing individualized care to patients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Explainability:&lt;/strong>; The ability to provide humans with clear and understandable explanations of its decision-making process and results. The inherent inscrutability of deep-learning AI is an ongoing challenge that requires multiple solutions, including building an &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/when-and-why-you-should-explain-how-your-ai-works&quot;>;“explainability framework”&lt;/a>; that addresses the risks of AI black boxes to specific industries and organizations. Technological solutions may also involve adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7768142/&quot;>;explainability engines&lt;/a>;, which offer human-readable explanations for AI &#39;systems&#39; decisions and predictions, particularly for critical areas like healthcare and finance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Adaptability and personalization:&lt;/strong>; The ability to learn from previous interactions and personalize responses based on individual users. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3252218/cortana-explained-why-microsofts-virtual-assistant-is-wired-for-business.html&quot;>;personal intelligent assistants&lt;/a>; are growing in importance in helping people tackle information and communication overload. By analyzing a user&#39;s activities, these assistants work collaboratively with workers in an individualized manner, enhancing their productivity in areas such as time management, meeting organization, and communication assistance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Context awareness:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the context in which an interaction is taking place and respond accordingly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2021/03/30/how-chat-commerce-is-changing-e-commerce/?sh=570d87f1142c&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, in e-commerce websites, chatbots that present context awareness can analyze a user&#39;s previous inquiries and purchase history to offer solutions or recommendations that are more pertinent to the customer&#39;s needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI systems continue to present unique competitive advantages, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Analytical capacities:&lt;/strong>; The ability to perform complex calculations, process large amounts of data, and identify patterns and relationships within the data. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/louiscolumbus/2019/08/01/ai-is-predicting-the-future-of-online-fraud-detection/?sh=6cdf5e3174f5&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, AI systems are becoming more competent at detecting fraudulent transactions in massive datasets of credit card transactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Generativity:&lt;/strong>; The ability to generate novel and unique outputs that are not simply reproductions of existing data. Using large models and neural networks to analyze patterns, generative AI is transforming the creation of image, text, and even music that resembles those created by human experts. These systems automated content generation, improve content quality, increase content variety, and offer personalized content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Performance at scale:&lt;/strong>; The ability to scale operations efficiently, handle a large number of real-time transactions and support large-scale applications without sacrificing performance. For example, AI systems have demonstrated superior ability to process &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/financial%20services/our%20insights/ai%20powered%20decision%20making%20for%20the%20bank%20of%20the%20future/ai-powered-decision-making-for-the-bank-of-the-future.pdf&quot;>;thousands of credit card applications&lt;/a>; real-time or offer “&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/algorithmic-management-the-role-of-ai-in-managing-workforces/&quot;>;algorithmic management&lt;/a>;” of thousands of Uber drivers and riders simultaneously, creating a structured and consistent operational framework at an unprecedented scale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Racing with and against the machines&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The challenge for organizations trying to build a strategy for using new and more AI tools lies in designing organizational systems that effectively balance the competitive and cooperative skills of humans and AI. Organizations that seek to strike this balance should consider the following:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Democratize data to foster the continuous development of competitive human and machine skills. &lt;/strong>;AI systems can generate data insights at scale and detect patterns often missed by the human eye, but translating that competitiveness into business growth and agility requires the very human skills of strategic thinking and creativity. To enable this type of collaboration, companies should democratize access to data throughout all levels of their organization. Nearly every role within your organization should be working alongside data analytics to inform how to make the workflows more efficient, make data-driven decisions and ultimately inform a better understanding of how to service the end customer. The more data visibility AI can give your workforce, the greater ability for humans to apply and develop their uniquely competitive skills.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Look outside your own organization&#39;s walls for cooperative human skills. &lt;/strong>;A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/operations/articles/future-of-gig-economy-shared-services-delivery-model.html&quot;>;Deloitte study&lt;/a>; found that nearly half (49%) of traditional workers — full-time employees — updated their skills more than a year ago or have never engaged in skills development, whereas 60% of the alternative workforce — defined as gig workers, freelancers, independent workers, and crowd workers — updated their skills within the past six months. In fact, 44% of alternative workers at large organizations hold a postgraduate degree according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upwork.com/resources/enterprise-companies-need-to-know-freelancers&quot;>;new research by Upwork&lt;/a>;. This is likely due to the fact that most technical skill sets, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/EPYMNBJA&quot;>;research by IBM&lt;/a>;, experience a half-life of 2.5 years. And, according to Upwork&#39;s database, the top in-demand skills are technical and related to web, mobile and software development. If your organization is struggling to keep up with cooperative human skills to work alongside machines, it may be time to engage a broader ecosystem of skills outside your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Don&#39;t let geography limit the skills your company is hiring for.&lt;/strong>; The pandemic ushered in a new era of work as many organizations learned work could be done remotely. Technical work can be done almost anywhere in the world as machines have largely made geography irrelevant to finding the skills you need to cooperate with machines. Enabling remote work strategies will ensure your organization is equipped to capture the ever-changing talent landscape and help you win in the race with and against the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By focusing on the balance of these skills, organizations can reap the benefits of an infinity loop between AI and human competitive skills. In this balance, humans may work toward “coopetition” as an arrangement where parties engage in both cooperative and competitive behavior. In such a relationship with AI systems, humans may leverage both the partnership with machines and their own competitive edge against the machine. This relationship helps to maintain their relevance and indispensability as algorithms are increasingly working as team members or even managers (ie, algorithmic management).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This formulation offered here helps shape the future of education and skill development, by emphasizing the importance of focusing on skills that give humans a competitive advantage over machines, rather than those that we have already lost to machines. For example, the use of calculators and spell checkers no longer serve as our advantage as we surrendered these tasks to technology long ago.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>