<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How Ecodesign Can Help the Environment and Your Bottom Line - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM SIEMENS]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/how-ecodesign-can-help-the-environment-and-your-bottom-line]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359826&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Header-visual_HBR.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;虽然已经签署了许多建设循环经济的承诺在世界范围内，工业消耗的资源仍然多于可再生的资源。如今，需要 1.75 个地球才能满足全球需求。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，只有 7% 多一点的材料被保留下来供进一步使用，其余的则被送往废物处理（这一顺序称为“资源的线性使用”）。因此，未来将会出现更多的供应风险和价格高峰，从而使经济增长面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;资源的线性使用危及我们的环境。根据&lt;a href=&quot;https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/biodiversity-report&quot;>;艾伦·麦克阿瑟基金会最近的一项研究&lt;/a>;，自然资源的开采导致了气候变化和 90% 以上的生物多样性丧失。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，人类有充分的理由迅速行动起来，在全球企业中实施循环经济原则。通过这样做，我们可以将资源消耗与绝对增长脱钩。我们可以事半功倍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;循环经济和生态设计&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从线性经济成功过渡到循环经济的关键是什么？是产品设计。产品生命周期中高达 80% 的环境影响是由其设计决定的。这就是生态设计的用武之地。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生态设计是如何工作的？&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync ()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;而传统产品开发主要侧重于在可用性、安全性、成本、质量等因素上，生态设计强调生态因素。这意味着找到重复利用材料的方法，同时最大限度地提高产品的安全使用和价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与传统的产品设计方法不同，生态设计考虑了整个产品生命周期，包括资源提取、采购、原型设计、系列生产、多种产品使用、生命周期结束阶段以及所有物流和运输过程。生态设计产品开发远远超出了公司的范围，从“摇篮到坟墓”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;实施生态设计对于任何组织来说都是一项重大变革。使战略发挥作用需要高层管理人员的承诺，这意味着团队必须接受新的思维和工作方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;稳健的生态设计：三个阶段&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;2020 年，西门子在其开发流程中引入了一种专用的整体生态设计方法，称为稳健生态设计 (RED)。借助 RED，西门子旨在系统地找出实现相同或更大客户价值的方法，同时消耗更少的能源和资源，最大限度地减少非天然物质向环境的传播，并以循环方式管理所需的技术和生物资源。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;在生产环保产品的过程中，西门子的设计部门遵循三步法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，团队明确与环境相关的客户要求，例如能源效率或产品寿命和监管目标，例如欧盟的循环经济行动计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，他们收集整个生命周期中所有进出物质和能源流的综合数据，包括空气、水和土壤的排放以及取自大自然的资源。随后，他们量化了不同设计的环境影响和对人类健康的影响，并将这些结果向利益相关者公开。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; >;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;最后，他们提出了环境优化设计规范的建议，这些规范不需要在安全或质量等方面进行权衡。建议可能包括增加回收材料的使用或进行更改，以便于重复使用、维修、翻新、再制造或回收。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;数字化如何促进生态设计&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有些人可能会争辩说，在产品设计中添加新的环境参数并不会让决策变得更容易。在某种程度上，这是事实。组织可能面临更多相互冲突的要求，例如更强的材料可以延长产品的使用寿命，但也需要更多的能源密集型流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，数字化和模拟可以解决这些挑战。现实生活中产品的“数字双胞胎”可以模拟产品的可修复性或坚固性，而不会浪费现实生活中的资源。它们还可以通过模拟生产过程来支持工厂减少能源和资源消耗、CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; 排放和废物产生。面向未来的组织需要引入技术和专业知识，帮助他们将这些强大的工具与其运营相集成。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;数字化还允许组织在不泄露战略秘密的情况下共享排放数据。在像 Esttainium 这样的开放式跨行业网络中，制造商、供应商和客户可以交换值得信赖的产品碳足迹数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;有意义的策略&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生态设计不仅仅是保护气候和生物多样性的问题。这也是一种明智的商业策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过采用生态设计原则，公司可以同时降低成本、最大限度地减少浪费并获得竞争优势。潜在的好处是巨大的，包括通过诸如一切即服务 (XaaS) 等创新业务模式节省数十亿美元的材料成本和新的收入来源。开放生态系统中的跨行业合作可以进一步放大环境和经济优势。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;跨入循环经济实践是一项重大转变。因此，要让您的可持续发展努力变得有价值，并专注于产品设计，因为这样您才能最大限度地发挥对您的利润和我们的环境的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;了解有关生态设计和环境的更多信息西门子白皮书中的如何建立“循环优势”&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siemens.com/global/en/company/sustainability/environment.html?stc= decg211247&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;生态设计：倍增影响，塑造世界&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;。 &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[To Get Better Customer Data, Build Feedback Loops into Your Products]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;丹尼尔·克里尔 (Daniel Creel) 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;由于人工智能（包括机器学习算法）的可用性不断提高，现在可以有意创建&lt;em>;客户数据反馈循环&lt;/em>;大多数产品和服务。这意味着，当公司收集更多客户数据时，它可以将这些数据输入机器学习算法以改进其产品或服务，从而吸引更多客户，生成更多客户数据。对于某些产品来说，这很容易；但对于某些产品来说，这很容易。对于其他人来说，需要找到更具创造性的方法来设计数据反馈循环。本文介绍了如何执行此操作。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer -data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data- build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;用户数据和人工智能的结合通常会创建数据反馈循环。这意味着，当公司收集更多客户数据时，它可以将这些数据输入机器学习算法以改进其产品或服务，从而吸引更多客户，生成更多客户数据。以搜索引擎为例：在谷歌上搜索并点击提供的链接的人越多，谷歌收集的数据就越多，这使得其算法能够提供更准确和相关的搜索结果，吸引更多的用户和搜索，等等&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这样的数据反馈循环可以帮助创建&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/01/when-data-creates-competitive-advantage&quot;>;可持续的竞争优势&lt;/a>;，前提是&lt;a href=&quot;https://platformchronicles.substack.com/p/six-questions-to-evaluate-data-enabled&quot;>;存在某些条件&lt;/a>;。但这些数据反馈循环的强度可能差异很大，公司可以在其产品或服务中做出深思熟虑的选择来加强它们。如何做到这一点是本文的重点。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;并非所有数据反馈循环都是一样的&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;有些产品天生就具有非常强大的数据反馈循环。想想智能恒温器，用户的每次温度调节都会提供有价值的数据信号，设备可以使用该信号来实现更好的个性化。或者谷歌地图，每个用户选择的路线和到达目的地所需的时间有助于算法改进其路线推荐和交通预测。或者 Spotify，其推荐系统直接从用户的选择中学习哪些推荐歌曲包含在他们的播放列表中以及他们收听这些歌曲的频率。这些反馈循环如此强大的原因是，用户在消费产品的自然过程中揭示了他们的偏好的清晰且明确的信号，这些信号被用来进一步改进这些用户的产品或服务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一方面，产品的数据反馈回路自然较弱。它们的使用情况很难跟踪，或者不会透露有关用户偏好的有用信息，或者很难且缓慢地收集用户的信息反馈。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于汽车、家具等传统“哑”产品来说，这显然是正确的。和衣服：它们没有数字连接，因此创建客户数据反馈循环的唯一方法是通过焦点小组和调查手动收集反馈，这只能对未来的产品发布有所帮助。对于反馈循环涉及很长的学习和改进周期的产品也是如此，例如金融机构的信用评分系统（反馈主要来自违约，需要数年时间才能实现）或风险投资（需要数年时间才能实现）不太明显的是，即使是一些收集大量用户数据的数字产品也可能具有薄弱的数据反馈循环。这意味着它们的大部分价值来自预编程和内部数据训练，并且不会通过向用户学习而增加太多（如果有的话）。例如，Fitbit 等流行的可穿戴设备，&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.whoop.com/&quot;>;Whoop&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://to.nutrisense.io/&quot;>;Nutrisense&lt;/a>; 和 &lt;a href=&quot;https://ouraring .com/&quot;>;Oura&lt;/a>; 尽管提供了大量数据洞察，但其数据反馈循环相当薄弱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑一下最新的 Fitbit 智能设备，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .fitbit.com/global/us/products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;Charge 5&lt;/a>;，具有令人印象深刻的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/ products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;功能列表&lt;/a>;。该跟踪器可测量用户的各种数据（心率、运动速度和距离、睡眠、皮肤温度），并提供有价值的见解，例如心率变异性、在不同心率区域花费的时间、有氧健身得分、锻炼准备得分，睡眠质量得分。然而，这些见解似乎并没有随着使用量的增加或用户的增加而变得更好。它们是跟踪器所测量内容的简单汇总统计数据，或者是 Fitbit 跟踪器测量的用户数据与基于 Fitbit 系统中预先编程的现有研究的相关参考点之间的比较结果。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;例如，Fitbit &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.fitbit.com/articles/en_US/Help_article/2096.htm&quot;>;解释&lt;/a>;“有氧健身得分取决于您的静息心率、年龄、性别、体重和其他个人信息。”同样，准备得分 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/technology/daily-readiness-score#:~:text=Your%20Daily%20Readiness%20Score%20uses,to%20gauge %20your%20energy%20levels.&amp;amp;text=Heart%20rate%20variability%20(HRV)%20is,contribute%20to%20a%20high%20score。&quot;>;基于&lt;/a>;测量的用户最近的睡眠模式由跟踪器——大概与一些稳定的参考点进行比较。换句话说，这些是对用户“真实”状态的估计，但它们不会随着更多的使用数据而改善，仅仅是因为 Fitbit 无法弄清楚其估计与“真实”状态的接近程度并进行调整&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，可穿戴设备可能会通过一些有限的方式根据每个用户或其他用户的使用数据来提高为该用户提供的价值。在最基本的层面上，任何连接的产品都可以了解哪个用户界面更具吸引力（例如，通过 A/B 测试），这在技术上是数据反馈循环的一种形式，尽管是有限的——大多数产品的赌注。 p>; &lt;p>;可穿戴设备可以分析相关性来推荐行为。例如，用户就寝时间与睡眠质量之间的相关性，可以用来推荐最佳就寝时间；或者用户锻炼的时间和睡眠质量之间的关系，可以用来推荐最佳的锻炼时间。在这些情况下，当用户根据建议调整自己的行为时，可穿戴设备会获得一些关于这是否有帮助的反馈，因此可以通过向用户学习来进一步改进。尽管如此，这种类型的过程需要来自大量用户的大量数据，而可穿戴设备提供商可能永远不会真正知道相关性在多大程度上意味着因果关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，考虑大型语言模型的数据反馈循环（ LLM），例如 Open AI 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://chat.openai.com/&quot;>;Chat GPT&lt;/a>; 或 Google 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://bard.google.com/&quot;>;Bard&lt; /a>;.这些模型从网络中获取大量数据，并使用机器学习模型来生成用户问题的答案。在这些模型的早期版本中，它们的功能很大程度上取决于发布前的“内部”培训和测试——随着更多用户或更多使用，它们的答案质量只会在一定程度上提高。事实上，在撰写本文时，有两种主要机制可以围绕法学硕士创建数据反馈循环：&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;用户单击答案末尾的“赞成”或“反对”按钮。 （大多数用户可能大多数时候都会忽略这一点。）&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;用户会提出后续问题，这可能表明答案是否令人满意。 （在大多数情况下，这种推断可能很困难。）&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;请注意与常规搜索（在 Bing 或 Google 上）的区别，用户选择要单击的显示链接提供了更清晰的信息搜索结果相关性的信号。当然，随着法学硕士的更新并开始采用更可靠的方法来生成数据反馈循环，情况可能会发生巨大变化——我们将在下一节讨论这个主题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;如何增强数据反馈循环&lt; /strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;那么关键的问题是，对于那些数据驱动的学习反馈循环本身并不强大的产品，可以采取哪些措施来增强它们？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>; （重新）设计产品以创建自然的数据反馈循环。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;理想情况下，人们希望（重新）设计产品或服务，以便客户在自然过程中使用该产品，正在创建数据来表明该产品对用户的有用/有效程度。然后，提供商可以使用这些数据来提高产品或服务的质量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，法学硕士可以添加新功能，允许用户将他们认为最有帮助的回复保存并组织到文件夹中收藏夹（类似于书签）并删除那些不想保留的内容。他们可以添加文档创建功能（类似于 Microsoft Word），在其中复制和编辑 LLM 回复。他们还可以创建挑战游戏（人工智能与用户）和排行榜，人工智能和用户寻求回答问题，用户对答案进行投票。等等。这个想法是为用户创造机会，提供关于法学硕士答案感知质量的可靠信号，然后可用于改进他们的算法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fitbit 和其他可穿戴设备可以添加标准化的健身测试或挑战（例如，跑一英里或做三组，每组 20 个仰卧起坐）并测量用户前后的总时间、心率和其他生物特征。这将使可穿戴设备的人工智能在观察更多用户的更多数据时更准确地预测用户锻炼的准备情况。这反过来会促使用户越来越依赖可穿戴设备来决定何时锻炼。当然，这仍然依赖于对未观察到的用户行为的假设，但关键是设备需要对用户进行某种准实验，以获得可以帮助他们学习和提高的数据。&lt;/p>; &lt; h3>;&lt;strong>;与其他产品集成以创建数据反馈循环。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在许多情况下，重新设计实际产品或服务以设计反馈循环可能具有挑战性（如可穿戴设备示例所示）多于）。实现相同目标的另一种方法是将您的产品与客户已经使用或可能使用的其他现有产品集成。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，Fitbit（或 Whoop 或 Oura）可以与智能恒温器集成，以使可穿戴设备能够在用户睡眠期间自动控制环境温度。这将使可穿戴设备的人工智能能够调整温度并确定其对可穿戴设备测量的用户睡眠质量的影响。客户使用可穿戴设备的次数越多（即佩戴它睡觉），可穿戴设备就越接近为任何给定用户找出理想的温度模式。这可以通过在用户睡觉时自动试验多种不同的温度模式来实现。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;或者，可穿戴设备可以与提供标准化锻炼的 Peloton 或 Tonal 集成，以便 Fitbit 的 AI 可以将用户的生物识别数据与用户的生物识别数据关联起来。锻炼的类型和强度。相对于上述选项（可穿戴设备只是要求用户执行特定锻炼）的优点是，可以在这里观察实际的锻炼行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，法学硕士可以与他们的任何软件或工具集成。例如，他们可以与内容创建/编辑软件（例如 Google Docs、Substack、Salesforce）集成，这将使他们能够观察答案的哪些部分最终用于用户创建的内容中并使用这些数据来改进他们的答案。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;以侵入性最小的方式询问用户反馈，让他们清楚地了解这样做的好处。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;不过，对于对于许多产品来说，找到这种使用户反馈与产品使用固有的方式（直接或通过集成）可能很困难或不可能。除此之外，下一个最佳选择是明确询问用户反馈。大多数在线产品和服务都在一定程度上做到了这一点。如上所述，法学硕士在生成每个答案后都会要求用户表示赞成或反对； Netflix 会要求用户在观看每条内容后点赞或反对，以改进其推荐系统；亚马逊要求买家对他们购买的产品进行评分； Airbnb 要求旅行者和房东互相评价，等等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，要求明确反馈的困难在于获取有用的信息，同时又不会给用户带来太多不便。没有人喜欢被“只占用你三分钟时间”的调查所困扰，或者看到每隔一个屏幕就会弹出反馈民意调查（“你向你的朋友推荐我们的可能性有多大？”）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了尽可能简单轻松地请求用户反馈之外，它还有助于向用户清楚地传达反馈如何尽可能使他们个人受益（例如，“通过对这部电影进行评级，Netflix 将能够为您提供更好的推荐”您可能会喜欢的其他电影”）。这确保了他们有动力提供诚实的反馈。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;让人类参与到循环中。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在最小化数据反馈循环的同时制造数据反馈循环的重要方法用户的反馈负担是让人类参与到循环中来补充（甚至取代）用户反馈。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexi.com/&quot;>;Alexi&lt;/a>; 就是一个很好的例子，这是一项为律师事务所提供的人工智能法律研究服务。客户可以&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexsei.com/howitworks&quot;>;提交法律问题&lt;/a>;以及任何相关案件事实，Alexi 会发回一份包含答案的法律研究备忘录，并附有摘要相关判例法和诉讼。这些备忘录由 Alexi 的人工智能生成，然后由 Alexi 的内部法律团队（即循环中的人员）进行审查和修改（必要时）。因此，Alexi 的人工智能可以从客户查询和内部团队更正提供的隐式反馈中学习，而不会给客户带来负担。这在这里很有效，因为客户不期望立即得到答案。 （Alexi 承诺在 24 小时内给出答复，在这种情况下，这是一个非常合理的周转。）他们也不会像 Chat GPT 或 Bard 用户那样每天提出数百个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个善用人类的例子这个循环是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.grammarly.com/&quot;>;Grammarly&lt;/a>;，一个人工智能驱动的写作助手，可以帮助用户提高语法、拼写、标点符号和风格。当用户在任何应用程序或网站（例如文字处理、电子邮件、社交媒体、通信应用程序）中写作时，Grammarly 会实时提供建议。用户可以选择接受或拒绝建议的编辑，这显然有助于改进算法并创建数据反馈循环。不过，Grammarly 还使用人工审阅者来检查 AI 模型提出的建议并审查模棱两可的情况（用户拒绝了建议的编辑，但不清楚他这样做的原因），而不是询问用户反馈。&lt;/p>; &lt;基于人工智能的产品或服务的其他例子，在循环中使用人类来补充或取代用户反馈，包括社交媒体平台上的内容审核（人类审核员参与人工智能遇到困难的最复杂的情​​况），人工智能-动力放射学服务，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gleamer.ai/&quot;>;Gleamer&lt;/a>;（人类专家补充人工智能诊断，并纠正系统自动写入的诊断中的任何问题）和人工智能- 支持的安全服务，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deepsentinel.com/&quot;>;Deep Sentinel&lt;/a>;（人工智能检测威胁并决定何时升级到人类警卫，然后人类警卫可以决定人工智能是否做出了正确的决定）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，人机交互方法的主要弱点是它不能很好地扩展到数十万或数百万客户或具有非常高的服务。使用频率和快速周转时间的期望。没有多少公司能够像 Meta 为 Facebook 那样聘请超过 15,000 名内容审核员。这就是为什么大多数在循环中雇用人员的公司都试图最大限度地减少人员在此过程中所需的时间。尽管如此，“人机交互”方法在产品/服务的早期阶段非常有效，此时学习曲线最陡。我们希望，随着人工智能系统的学习，人类参与的需求会随着时间的推移而迅速减少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•••&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能，包括机器学习算法，意味着现在大多数产品和服务都可以有意识地创建数据反馈循环。对于某些产品来说，这很容易；但对于某些产品来说，这很容易。对于其他人来说，需要找到更有创意的方法来设计数据反馈循环——通过集成或对用户反馈的侵入性最小请求，为用户带来好处。当它们强大时，这些反馈循环可以创造一种形式的网络效应（更多的用户带来更多的数据，这使得产品更好，进而吸引更多的用户，等等）并增强竞争优势。&lt;/p>; &lt;!- - 引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Factors That Make for a Great Employee Experience]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_200021503-002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;戴利和牛顿/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;数十年的业务战略促使领导者将大部分业务精力集中在客户体验上。虽然优先考虑客户而不是员工可以推动短期收入增长，但这将使公司在长期员工保留和敬业度方面付出代价。作者和同事对来自世界各地、跨多个行业的数千名员工和高管进行了一项新研究。通过回归分析，他们确定了创造更好的员工体验的五个最重要的因素：相互信任、最高管理层问责制、员工价值观与公司愿景的一致性、认可成功以及无缝技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=es&quot;>;阅读en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt; /div>; &lt;p>;我们听说过这样的格言：快乐的员工会带来快乐的客户，但新数据揭示了员工体验的影响有多么重要，以及如何利用它来促进组织发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;数十年的业务战略促使领导者将大部分业务精力集中在客户体验上。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4215010&quot;>;哥伦比亚大学最近的一项研究&lt;/a>;发现“高管们[在财报电话会议上]谈论客户的频率是原来的 10 倍比员工。当他们这样做时，高管们会将客户视为机会，将员工视为风险。”即使公司谈论良好的员工体验游戏，他们实际上仍然会根据客户体验采取行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然优先考虑客户而不是员工可以推动短期收入增长，但这将使公司在长期员工保留方面付出代价和参与度。根据我和我的 Salesforce 同事进行的研究，公司可以通过改善员工体验&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想确定员工体验的关键驱动因素，以帮助高管改善员工体验。对于我即将出版的书，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Experience-Mindset-Changing-Think-Growth/dp/059354269X&quot;>;&lt;em>;体验心态&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，我和我的同事对来自世界各地、跨多个行业的数千名员工和高管进行了一项新研究。通过回归分析，我们确定了创造更好员工体验的五个最重要因素：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1。相互信任&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;信任有两种：员工对组织的信任和组织对其员工的信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相互&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/begin -with-trust&quot;>;信任&lt;/a>;会赋予员工权力。它表明了管理层对其员工的信心，从而增强了员工对领导层和彼此之间的信任。它还可以激励员工、促进创造力和协作、提高保留率并减少风险规避，所有这些都有助于实现盈利。这种授权和信任在苹果公司和丽思卡尔顿公司等公司都很明显，在苹果公司，商店员工无需申请特殊批准即可解决许多客户问题；在丽思卡尔顿酒店，员工可以花费高达 2,000 美元来解决客人问题，无需管理层批准。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;相互信任也有助于员工感到被倾听。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/hybrid-work-making-it-fit-with-your-diversity-equity-and-inclusion -strategy&quot;>;根据麦肯锡&lt;/a>;的说法，这种包容性会让员工留在公司的可能性增加 47%，并且他们会竭尽全力互相帮助的可能性增加 90%。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;当总部位于多伦多的金融贷款公司 Clear Co 开始经历高速增长时，首席执行官 Michele Romanow 希望&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/whats-next-podcast/enter- the-dragons-den-with-serial-entrepreneur-michele-romanow&quot;>;在保持其创业文化的同时实现流程现代化&lt;/a>;。因此，她设置了一个电子邮件收件箱，其标题为“我们所做的愚蠢的事！”并向员工询问有关简化业务和消除可预防的挫折的想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据 Romanow 的说法，这个简单的练习实现了两个目标。首先，它让员工有一种主人翁意识，并参与改善他们的日常生活并帮助公司。其次，它创建了一个反馈循环，允许领导层建立员工信任，同时在问题转移之前发现并解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2.高管问责制&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;高管问责制与信任密切相关，意味着确保公司领导层对企业及其员工做出承诺并做出回应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在一个层面上，问责制是关于愿意提出问题并积极倾听答案。领导者无法满足他们不了解的员工需求。更广泛地说，它涉及文化：具有强大高管责任感的企业了解员工体验的重要性并优先考虑它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司的言论和行动之间往往存在差异。我们在研究中发现，虽然 49% 的高管认为他们的公司擅长根据员工反馈采取行动（老实说，这个数字很低），但只有 31% 的员工同意这一观点。 That gap can swallow growth, momentum, and talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Create a culture in which everyone understands that employee experience is a collective responsibility. Hilton, for example, established cross-functional teams that ensure a formal, structured way for the C-suite to keep tabs on employee experiences. As Chris Silcock, Hilton&#39;s EVP and chief commercial officer, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/salesforce/2020/11/05/how-hilton-uses-the-golden-rule-to-drive-commercial-success/?sh=4661f676733c&quot;>;has observed&lt;/a>;, “How you treat your team members guides how they treat your customers.” Hilton has repeatedly been named one of Fortune&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greatplacetowork.com/best-companies-to-work-for&quot;>;Best Companies to Work For&lt;/a>;.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At your company, this could look like an experience advisory board to help break down traditional barriers and facilitate brainstorming and ideation; a center of excellence to deliver best practices where there are knowledge or skills gaps; employee resource groups to provide peer-to-peer counseling and boost career development; or “voice of the employee” surveys to solicit and gather employees&#39; needs, wants, and expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Alignment of employee values and company vision&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Employees want to align with their company&#39;s values, but that makes the C-suite responsible for clearly enunciating them — and then making sure corporate actions are consistent with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Clear goals with well-defined milestones and success metrics connect employees to their company&#39;s mission and help them understand their role in advancing it. We found in our research that ensuring employees feel valued and core to the company vision is a significant driver of reported increases in revenue. However, only 36% of employees reported feeling that way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A company culture that supports an experience mindset understands the intrinsic connection between what it does internally for employees and how that translates into its customers&#39; experiences. Airbnb, for example, hired the first head of employee experience at a major US corporation, in 2013. “Culture is simply a shared way of doing something with passion,” CEO Brian Chesky wrote then in a Medium post titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@bchesky/dont-fuck-up-the-culture-597cde9ee9d4&quot;>;Don&#39;t F*^k Up the Culture&lt;/a>;.” “The stronger the culture, the less corporate process a company needs. When the culture is strong, you can trust everyone to do the right thing.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Alignment is a major part of that culture, starting before employees even join Airbnb. The company conducts two separate “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegrowthfaculty.com/blog/Employeeexperiencestaffretention?recacheSoql=true&quot;>;core values interviews&lt;/a>;” run by team members outside of the hiring function so they can assess cultural fit independent of the job opening&#39;s specific needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4. Recognizing success.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As the activist and philanthropist &lt;a href=&quot;https://chopra.com/articles/what-you-appreciate-appreciates&quot;>;Lynne Twist has observed&lt;/a>;, “What you appreciate appreciates.” Recognition can be a &lt;a href=&quot;https://focus.kornferry.com/employee-recognition-the-secret-ingredient-to-high-employee-engagement-asean/&quot;>;cost-effective way to boost employee engagement&lt;/a>;, which has positive spillover effects on loyalty, retention, and productivity. Workers who believe their success will be recognized are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quantumworkplace.com/future-of-work/importance-of-employee-recognition&quot;>;2.7 times more likely to be highly engaged&lt;/a>; than peers who don&#39;t, according to the employee engagement firm Quantum Workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Praise is not the sum total of recognition, of course. It also involves identifying and nurturing potential, giving employees the skills needed to grow. &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/use-purpose-to-transform-your-workplace&quot;>;Unilever&lt;/a>;, for example, created a leadership development program encompassing the entire organization. In leadership development workshops, employees create individually tailored “future fit plans,” each focused on a purpose that&#39;s both important to the individual and in keeping with company goals. The result? Ninety-two percent of those who attended a workshop said that their jobs inspire them to go the extra mile, while only 33% of those who had not attended felt the same way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;5. Seamless technology to reduce employees&#39; day-to-day friction&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Too often, executives throw technology at problems as a way to fix company performance, productivity, and costs but give too little thought to how it fits into the rest of the organization&#39;s infrastructure, existing processes, and people&#39;s workflows. As engineer and management consultant W. Edwards Deming put it almost 40 years ago, “Eighty-five percent of the reasons for failure are deficiencies in the systems and process rather than the employee. The role of management is to change the process rather than badgering individuals to do better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/survey-employees-want-business-technologies-to-be-more-collaborative&quot;>;common employee complaint&lt;/a>; is the sheer volume of applications they need to navigate between to do their work. &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.mulesoft.com/ty-report-connectivity-benchmark.html#loaded&quot;>;Enterprises use an average&lt;/a>; of more than 1,000 different applications, only 29% of which are integrated (ie, communicate with one another).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Technology is not an end in itself but a tool for increasing productivity and reducing effort. And yet our research shows that technology is one of the most poorly rated dimensions of employee experience: Fewer than one in three employees said their company&#39;s technology works effectively, and fewer than one in four said they&#39;re equipped with seamless technology. Even the C-suite gets this: Only 52% of executives said that their company provides employees with tech that works effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Can you imagine asking your customers to toggle between multiple tabs just to place an order with you? Probably not — most companies work hard to reduce this kind of friction for customers. Yet that&#39;s what we ask of our employees every day when the systems they use aren&#39;t integrated. The result is reduced satisfaction and a terrible employee experience. We must ensure that both the customer experience and employee experience get equal resources. Saving customer time nets out little or no gain if you&#39;re shifting that effort to your employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Revitalize the Employee Experience&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 and the Great Resignation inspired workers to reevaluate their priorities and empowered them to act. That has spurred companies to relearn what was once a given: that their most valuable resource is their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What began as a wakeup call for how leaders can save their companies from a talent exodus can also be an opportunity for growth and competitiveness — but only if they learn to balance their customers&#39; experiences with those of their workers by focusing on trust, C-suite accountability, alignment, recognition, and technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These five elements are intertwined. Each builds on the others to establish a stronger employee experience and unleash new value. Happy workers make happy customers, and managing the nexus between the two will make leaders and investors happy, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The State of Globalization in 2023]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_1383390211.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Grizelj/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Plummeting flows of trade, capital, and people at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic prompted a wave of speculation about the end of globalization, and Russia&amp;#8217;s invasion of Ukraine brought even more predictions of a retreat toward national self-sufficiency. But, according to research for the latest DHL Global Connectedness Index, international flows show no signs of a sustained downturn. The data shows a broad pattern of decoupling between the US and China, but the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China do not &amp;#8212; at least yet &amp;#8212; indicate a broader split between rival blocs. Nor is there evidence that globalization is giving way to regionalization. While companies do need to adjust for heightened geopolitical tensions, they should not abandon global strategies. Corporate deglobalization, in fact, could be a riskier path than making focused adjustments to mitigate geopolitical risks.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Three key questions lie at the heart of debates about whether global crises and escalating geopolitical tensions have begun to reverse globalization: Has the growth of cross-border trade, capital, information and people flows gone into reverse? Are geopolitical tensions fracturing the world economy into rival blocs? And is globalization giving way to regionalization? The answer to all three questions — despite evidence of US-China decoupling — is still “no.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This result — decoupling without deglobalization — implies that most multinational firms should respond to elevated geopolitical tensions with focused adjustments to their global strategies and risk management. While the public-policy environment has become less conducive to globalization, the resilience of global flows cautions against more dramatic strategy changes predicated on the notion that markets will become substantially less globalized.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Has the Growth of Global Flows Gone into Reverse?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Plummeting flows of trade, capital, and people &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/will-covid-19-have-a-lasting-impact-on-globalization&quot;>;at the beginning&lt;/a>; of the Covid-19 pandemic prompted a wave of speculation about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://foreignpolicy.com/2020/04/03/coronavirus-end-globalization/&quot;>;end of globalization&lt;/a>;, and Russia&#39;s invasion of Ukraine brought even more predictions of a retreat toward &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/ukraine-speeds-global-rush-self-sufficiency-2022-03-09/&quot;>;national self-sufficiency&lt;/a>;. But international flows show no signs of a sustained downturn.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;DHL Global Connectedness Index&lt;/a>;, developed by our team at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://stern.nyu.edu/globalization&quot;>;NYU Stern Center for the Future of Management&lt;/a>;, measures the “depth” of globalization by comparing the growth of international flows to the growth of domestic economic activity. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/global-en/delivered/globalization/global-connectedness-index.html#parsysPath_download_box_copy_co&quot;>;latest report&lt;/a>; shows that the globalization of trade, capital, and information flows was already above pre-pandemic levels by 2021 and that the recovery of international people flows accelerated in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360176&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_INDEX_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;Source: DHL Global Connectedness Index 2022&quot; title=&quot;Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;626&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International trade rebounded quickly after &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/will-covid-19-have-a-lasting-impact-on-globalization&quot;>;plummeting at the beginning&lt;/a>; of the pandemic. The volume of world trade in goods &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-november-2022&quot;>;reached 10%&lt;/a>; above pre-pandemic levels in mid-2022, and trade in services was also back above &lt;a href=&quot;https://documents.worldbank.org/en/publication/documents-reports/documentdetail/099444311022220882/idu026d6c21108fa504c770ae550637a6bc89aa7&quot;>;pre-pandemic levels&lt;/a>;. Preliminary data &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;indicate&lt;/a>; the value of world exports as a share of GDP rose in 2022, matching the &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/NE.EXP.GNFS.ZS&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>; set in 2008. In late 2022, slowing global economic growth caused trade &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-march-2023&quot;>;to weaken&lt;/a>;, but the International Monetary Fund (IMF)&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;latest forecast&lt;/a>; still calls for trade to grow at a modest 2.4% pace in 2023 before accelerating to a more typical (3.5%) rate in 2024.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International business investment also recovered swiftly from declines at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic. Foreign direct investment (FDI) flows, which reflect companies buying, building, or reinvesting in operations abroad, collapsed in 2020, but were &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;back above pre-pandemic&lt;/a>; levels in 2021. FDI flows, like trade, &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/system/files/official-document/diaeiainf2022d5_en.pdf&quot;>;weakened&lt;/a>; after the start of the war in Ukraine, but there are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oecd.org/daf/inv/investment-policy/FDI-in-Figures-April-2023.pdf&quot;>;no signs&lt;/a>; of a collapse similar to the one at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other measures of corporate globalization affirm that businesses are not broadly retreating from foreign markets, even as FDI flows remain below historical peak levels. Payments for the use of foreign intellectual property &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BM.GSR.ROYL.CD&quot;>;continue to grow&lt;/a>;, while the cross-border share of M&amp;amp;A transactions is &lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;holding steady&lt;/a>;, and the share of global output generated by the foreign operations of multinational firms has just &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;slipped back&lt;/a>; modestly from a record high set in the mid-2000s.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While the Covid-19 pandemic temporarily reduced trade and capital flows, it caused a spike in the growth of international data flows. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://techblog.comsoc.org/2022/09/19/telegeography-global-internet-bandwidth-rose-by-28-in-2022/#:~:text=According%20to%20Telegeography%2C%20Global%20internet,%2Dyear%20CAGR%20of%2029%25.&quot;>;growth rate of international internet traffic&lt;/a>; doubled in 2020 as in-person interactions were replaced by online activity, and it continued growing at 20% to 30% per year in 2021 and 2022. More than twice as much data crossed national borders in 2022 compared to 2019.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International people flows suffered the worst blow from the Covid-19 pandemic, but they are on their way to making a full recovery. The latest UN forecast &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.e-unwto.org/doi/abs/10.18111/wtobarometereng.2023.21.1.2&quot;>;predicts&lt;/a>; the number of people traveling to foreign countries will be just 5% to 20% below its pre-pandemic level in 2023. Migration has also proven resilient, with the share of people living outside of their birth countries &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldmigrationreport.iom.int/wmr-2022-interactive/&quot;>;continuing to rise&lt;/a>;, even in 2020.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, data on the growth of global flows strongly rebuts the notion of a mass retreat from international to domestic activity. Most types of international flows are at or near all-time highs, and the weakness of some flows, such as trade, in late 2022 and early 2023, primarily reflects slowing global economic growth following large interest rate increases aimed at curbing inflation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Are Geopolitical Tensions Fracturing the World Economy into Rival Blocs?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As tensions continue to escalate between the US and China, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/06/shifting-geopolitical-tectonic-plates-straight-talk&quot;>;there is a growing fear&lt;/a>; that a new cold war could lead to a costly bifurcation of the world economy. The latest data on international flows do show a broad pattern of decoupling between the US and China, but the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China do not — at least yet — indicate a broader split between rival blocs, an outcome that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/News/Articles/2023/03/25/032623md-china-development-forum-remarks&quot;>;IMF has warned&lt;/a>; would “leave everyone poorer and less secure.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To measure US-China decoupling, the DHL Global Connectedness Index report examines 11 types of trade, capital, information, and people flows, and finds that the US and China have both substantially reduced their focus on flows with each other since 2016. The share of US flows that were to or from China declined in eight out of 11 categories, falling on average from 9.3% to 7.3% (weighted average using our index&#39;s flow weights). The share of China&#39;s flows with the US fell in seven out of 10 categories, dropping on average, from 17.8% to 14.3%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Measuring the US China Decoupling. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360174&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Measuring the US China Decoupling. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The extent of US-China decoupling, however, should not be overstated. The US and China are still connected by larger combined trade, capital, information, and people flows than any other pair of countries without a common border. And the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.piie.com/blogs/realtime-economics/five-years-trade-war-china-continues-its-slow-decoupling-us-exports&quot;>;dollar value&lt;/a>; of trade between the US and China grew to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/foreign-trade/balance/c5700.html&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>; in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even more importantly, at a global level, the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China indicate no meaningful fragmentation of the world economy into rival blocs. Close allies of the US and China (as classified by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.capitaleconomics.com/clients/publications/china-economics/china-economics-focus/mapping-decoupling&quot;>;Capital Economics&lt;/a>;) have not substantially reduced the shares of their flows with the rival bloc. In some areas, such as imports and scientific research collaboration, US allies have even increased the share of their flows with China and its allies, while the US has pulled back from those exchanges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360175&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_ALLIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;Sources: IMF Direction of Trade Statistics, UN Comtrade, fdi Markets, Thomson Reuters, IMF CPIS, Clarivate Web of Science, UN DESA International Migrant Stock, UN WTO Tourism Statistics, Capital Economics&quot; title=&quot;Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1157&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs.-->;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Has Globalization Given Way to Regionalization?&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rising geopolitical tensions — along with supply disruptions during the Covid-19 pandemic — have also prompted many observers to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;predict a shift&lt;/a>; from globalization to regionalization. In other words, many expect that a rising proportion of international flows will take place within rather than between regions. Data on actual flow patterns, however, do not show that such a shift has (yet) taken place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We prefer to analyze the possibility of rising regionalization by measuring the average distance traversed by international flows, since the more common measure — the share of flows happening within regions — &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;yields very different results&lt;/a>; depending on where one chooses to draw the region boundaries. If international flows were becoming more regionalized, they would take place over shorter distances, on average. In fact, trade and many other types of flows have tended to take place over longer distances. The main exception to this pattern involves people flows, due to a higher proportion of travel taking place between nearby countries during the Covid-19 pandemic. Capital flows also took place over shorter distances in 2020 and 2021, but it is still unclear whether that reflects a meaningful shift toward more regionalized investment patterns, since the volatility of these flows often results in short-term fluctuations of a similar magnitude.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- No Evidence that Globalization Is Giving Way to Regionalization. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360177&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_NO_REGIONALIZATION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- No Evidence that Globalization Is Giving Way to Regionalization. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Trade flows even stretched out over longer distances in 2020 and 2021, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eiu.com/n/campaigns/the-great-unwinding-covid-19-supply-chains-and-regional-blocs/&quot;>;contrary to predictions&lt;/a>; that pandemic-related disruptions would prompt greater reliance on nearby suppliers. The &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;key driver of this pattern&lt;/a>; was the resilience of Asian manufacturing, leading to more trade between Asia and distant regions. Preliminary data also show an increase in the average distance over which countries traded in 2022, due in part to effects of the war in Ukraine on trade patterns and commodity prices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It remains an open question whether world trade will become substantially more regionalized in the future. Many companies are &lt;a href=&quot;https://supplychaindigital.com/supply-chain-risk-management/nearshoring-happening-faster-than-expected-says-gartner&quot;>;focused on nearshoring&lt;/a>; to produce goods closer to their customers, and major supply-chain reconfigurations can take several years to execute. Governments in many countries are supporting these regionalization efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the other hand, the fact that international flows are already highly regionalized limits the scope for large increases in regionalization. As shown above, more than half of trade already takes place within roughly continent-sized regions. In addition, many companies, rather than nearshoring, have adopted other strategies to boost resilience, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/how-covid-19-is-reshaping-supply-chains&quot;>;digitization and dual sourcing&lt;/a>;. Meanwhile, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/d739cd47-e434-43c3-9b4e-472bcef4abaf&quot;>;container shipping costs&lt;/a>; have come back down while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/01/31/world-economic-outlook-update-january-2023&quot;>;inflation remains high&lt;/a>;, boosting the attractiveness of low-cost sources that may be located in distant regions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Geopolitical Turbulence and Global Strategy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While global flows have remained resilient, the public policy environment has become more challenging for global business. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heritage.org/index/trade-freedom&quot;>;Trade protectionism&lt;/a>; has increased, &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;international investments&lt;/a>; face heightened scrutiny on national security grounds, &lt;a href=&quot;https://itif.org/publications/2021/07/19/how-barriers-cross-border-data-flows-are-spreading-globally-what-they-cost/&quot;>;data-flow restrictions&lt;/a>; are proliferating, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hinrichfoundation.com/research/article/wto/international-trading-system-threatened-by-erosion-of-trust/&quot;>;international institutions&lt;/a>; struggle to function amid strained relations among their member countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Core principles of global strategy can &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-new-global-road-map-enduring-strategies-for-turbulent-times/10172&quot;>;help business leaders navigate&lt;/a>; this turbulent environment. The key &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbsp.harvard.edu/product/2620BC-PDF-ENG&quot;>;business drivers of globalization&lt;/a>; — more growth and innovation, coupled with lower costs and better diversified risks — remain strong, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/strategy-and-corporate-finance/our-insights/global-flows-the-ties-that-bind-in-an-interconnected-world&quot;>;new technologies&lt;/a>; continue to expand international opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But the challenges and risks of operating across geopolitical divides &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/how-companies-can-navigate-todays-geopolitical-risks&quot;>;have increased&lt;/a>;. Global strategists often find it useful to think of such shifts as changing the &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;metaphorical distance&lt;/a>; between countries. Rising tensions put more distance between geopolitical rivals, and they bring friendly countries closer together, at least in relative terms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the foundational concepts of global strategy is that domestic firms have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1075425312000543?casa_token=y_2Xo8t1_UwAAAAA:29n5LgCrPdVFnV9rfY1GksXnPbZQZ6OscJKksAyd7DAw_sK87s3-jNyiDEMdoYmWEnRmQRY&quot;>;home-court advantage&lt;/a>; over foreign firms, and firms that have to &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;bridge less distance&lt;/a>; — not only geographically but also politically — are usually advantaged over firms that have to bridge greater distance. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/41411007&quot;>;firm&#39;s unique assets&lt;/a>; — technologies, brand value, and so on — &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1017/9781316678503.007&quot;>;exert a large influence&lt;/a>; over how much distance it can bridge successfully. So does the &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;sensitivity of its business&lt;/a>; to geopolitics and other sources of cross-country distance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders should examine how strong their competitive positions are in countries that are becoming more — and less — distant, to see if they need to rebalance their geographic portfolios. Remember that shifting geopolitical relationships can create opportunities as well as challenges. A company may be able to win business away from competitors from geopolitical adversaries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If a company has strong-enough advantages to compete across geopolitical divides, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/the-strategic-challenges-of-decoupling&quot;>;changes to how it operates&lt;/a>; in politically distant markets may be required. A common approach is to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-based-managers-gain-more-autonomy-from-global-companies-ac8f66d3&quot;>;afford more autonomy&lt;/a>; to local managers, to better tailor operations to increasingly divergent conditions. This can be useful, but it is important not to overestimate how far a foreign company can go to be regarded as a local player. When push comes to shove, a company&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/the-cosmopolitan-corporation&quot;>;home base is still central&lt;/a>; to its perceived — and often real — allegiances.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As many Western firms operating in Russia saw after the full-scale invasion of Ukraine, tensions can escalate to a point where there is no alternative to exiting a market. Companies with large operations across geopolitical divides should be prepared for the contingency of a gradual decoupling turning into a sudden separation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news, though, is that most companies do not need to fundamentally restructure their global strategies to prudently address geopolitical tensions. As we have seen, US-China decoupling has not — at least yet — begun to split the world economy into rival blocs, globalization has not given way to regionalization, and most types of international flows continue growing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Decoupling without deglobalization generally calls for focused adjustments to global strategies not only because of the resilience of global flows but also because most international business already takes place between nearby and friendly countries. The US, for example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bea.gov/news/2023/us-international-trade-goods-and-services-december-and-annual-2022&quot;>;imported&lt;/a>; 66% more from Canada and Mexico in 2022 than it did from China, and 35% more from Europe. Globally, half of the flows measured on the DHL Global Connectedness Index take place inside major world regions, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/content/dam/dhl/global/dhl-spotlight/documents/pdf/10-years-lessons-gci-2021-report.pdf&quot;>;three times more&lt;/a>; than one would expect in a world where the distance and differences between countries had no effects. Nearshoring and friendshoring are actually longstanding features of globalization, and increases that address specific vulnerabilities would be consistent with the “interdependence without overdependence” that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wto.org/english/news_e/spno_e/spno32_e.htm&quot;>;WTO Director-General Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala envisions&lt;/a>; as the “future of trade.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Focused adjustments to how companies operate internationally also align well with the increasingly prevalent view in policy circles that “de-risking” is a better response to geopolitical tensions than complete decoupling. European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen proposed this emphasis on “de-risking” &lt;a href=&quot;https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/speech_23_2063&quot;>;in a March 2023 speech&lt;/a>; that characterized most EU-China trade as “mutually beneficial and &#39;un-risky&#39;” but highlighted the EU&#39;s problematic reliance on China for 98% of its supply of rare earths, 97% of its lithium, and 93% of its magnesium. Less than two months later, the US and other large advanced economies &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/05/20/g7-hiroshima-leaders-communique/&quot;>;formally embraced&lt;/a>; “de-risking, not de-coupling” at the May 2023 G7 Summit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bottom line is that companies do need to adjust for heightened geopolitical tensions, but they should not abandon global strategies on the assumption that US-China decoupling will necessarily lead to deglobalization. Corporate deglobalization, in fact, &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/abandoning-globalization-will-only-hurt-us-businesses&quot;>;could be a riskier path&lt;/a>; than making focused adjustments to mitigate geopolitical risks. Another principle of global strategy is that firms should align their strategies with the globalization of their markets. As long as markets are not de-globalizing, firms that retreat from globalization may put their competitive positions at risk.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[In Uncertain Times, Embrace Imperfectionism]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_10_1192111806.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Gety Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Change is accelerating, with uncertainty and threat of disruption in every industry segment. The pace of change and rise of global winner-take-all competition means that conventional product-market-structure approaches to strategy, as well as core competencies thinking, are difficult to implement in practice and may yield misleading answers. Under today&amp;#8217;s conditions, the authors argue that real-time problem solving should be the heart of strategy development rather than theoretical frameworks, and they present a framework for this approach. This approach requires companies to look at strategy through multiple lenses or vantage points, typically anchoring these outside the company in its ecosystem or beyond. Looking at your business through the eyes of your suppliers, customers, current rivals, and potential outside entrants will give you much more perspective on both threats and opportunities than you will get from staying inside your company&amp;#8217;s prevailing mindsets and routines. It should also seek to generate new data on these perspectives through experimentation, augmenting this new data by crowdsourcing external ideas and technologies to bring collective intelligence to bear.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;If you are an Amazon customer, chances are you have encountered household names such as Amazon Prime and Zappos. It&#39;s less likely that you would have noted the baby steps Amazon took to expand beyond its core business into consumer financial services.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The acquisition of TextPayMe, the investment in Bill Me Later, the hiring of a team from GoPago, and the launch of a remote card payment device, Amazon Local Register were modest moves that involved little financial outlay and attracted relatively little attention at the time. They also ended in apparent failure, with TextPayMe closing in 2014, Local Register withdrawing from the market in the face of competition from Square, and Bill Me Later being acquired by rival PayPal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet today Amazon is a powerhouse in consumer finance, boasting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/611981/us-amazon-payments-awareness-usage/&quot;>;a 24% user share in the US for its pan-economy Amazon Pay service&lt;/a>;, and is positioned to develop further as a global finance player. How did the company craft success at scale from a series of pint-sized and seemingly unpromising moves?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The answer is that Amazon is an imperfectionist, a concept we&#39;ve developed over several decades of helping companies and nonprofits, and one that we believe is vital for organizations striving to prosper in today&#39;s uniquely uncertain economic environment. As we will explain, imperfectionism is an approach in which companies grow not by following a strategic framework or plan, but through multiple and frequent experimentation in real time, incrementally building up valuable knowledge, assets, and capabilities on the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Why a New Approach Is Required&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We all experience it: Change is accelerating, with uncertainty and threat of disruption in every industry segment. Artificial intelligence, programmable biology, robotics and other technologies are transforming existing industries and spawning new ones. External shocks cut across boundaries and impact all businesses, even those that appear to enjoy structural advantages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this volatile and fluid environment, established approaches to strategy development no longer work. There is no stable industry structure or new market equilibrium to return to. The pace of change and rise of global winner-take-all competition means that conventional product-market-structure approaches, as well as core competencies thinking, are difficult to implement in practice and may yield misleading answers. The player to topple a dominant company in a particular space is more likely to enter from outside with a &lt;em>;de novo &lt;/em>;approach than to be an existing rival. Just look at the battle of Instagram, Quibi, and TikTok in the short-form video social media space — the now-winning player was unknown five years ago. &amp;nbsp;We need responsive strategy approaches to match external volatility.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One repercussion of this changed environment is that most company strategic planning processes are unsuited to an uncertain and fast changing world, leaving many management teams stuck in a nervous wait-and-see posture.&amp;nbsp; Other company leaders avoid stasis by making panicky bets, including “leap before you look” acquisitions in an attempt to “own” new spaces, typically with little success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What should you do instead?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Embrace the Imperfect &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As we describe in our book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Imperfectionists%3A+Strategic+Mindsets+for+Uncertain+Times-p-9781119835677&quot;>;&lt;em>;The Imperfectionists&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, Amazon didn&#39;t wait for a moment of strategic clarity, nor did it use its large balance sheet to acquire an indigestible bank. It edged out into uncertainty by taking small steps: investing in young companies with interesting technologies, hiring a team from a failed fintech, and launching internally developed services and tools. It ran multiple, parallel initiatives and learned what worked and what didn&#39;t. It built valuable capabilities and assets with moves that were mostly low consequence and reversible. There is no notion of strategic frameworks in its approach to building a major financial services business. &amp;nbsp;The end result is what we term a staircase of initiatives, a pragmatic revealed strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359260&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_STAIRCASE_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This step-by-step approach was no accident — Amazon followed the same modus operandi in its entry to commercial finance and in its creation and dominance of cloud computing. It now appears to be doing something similar in health care.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Under today&#39;s conditions, we believe that real-time problem solving, not theoretical frameworks, should be the heart of strategy development. This starts with a hypothesis, often framed as an audacious question that when answered will provide strategic insight on the first steps of a solution staircase.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Strategy development then moves to seeing things through multiple lenses or vantage points, typically anchoring these outside the company in its ecosystem or beyond. Looking at your business through the eyes of your suppliers, customers, current rivals, and potential outside entrants will give you much more perspective on both threats and opportunities than you will get from staying inside your company&#39;s prevailing mindsets and routines.&amp;nbsp; Perspective-taking workshops at all levels of the organization can help surface novel observations that can be the nucleus of a new strategic path.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next it seeks novel data on these perspectives via experimentation, augmenting this new data by crowdsourcing external ideas and technologies to bring collective intelligence to bear. To be sure, few organizations are adept at having others toil in their garden, but one path to accessing fresh capabilities is crowdsourcing new technologies and approaches.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This leads to a pragmatic plan to step into uncertainty, gathering more information from small moves, while adding capabilities and assets, laying off risk to others where possible, and learning from mistakes and successes. It involves recognizing that strategic decisions are probabilistic wagers, and moves are made commensurate with an assessment of the odds.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large enterprises, in particular, struggle with this. They are often reluctant to think in terms of probabilities that, in turn, gives rise to a powerful form of risk aversion, as documented in a &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/your-company-is-too-risk-averse&quot;>;2020 HBR article&lt;/a>; by Dan Lovallo, Tim Koller, Robert Uhlaner, and the Nobel laureate Daniel Kahneman. They found that that managers insist on making risk-averse choices even where favorable odds are clear. A starting point to overcome this deep-set bias is to insist that all discussions of strategies include probability estimates and ranges of potential outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359259&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_IMPERFECTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Our research suggests that this approach to strategy under uncertainty is being effectively employed not just by the likes of Amazon but by other savvy firms and nonprofits alike. Here are four examples, each illustrating one of the four main components of the process.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Invisalign: Seeing Through New Lenses&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Until the early 1990s, orthodontic braces had hardly changed for decades.&amp;nbsp; Incremental improvements came from inside the practice of dentistry, but significant innovation was missing. Kelsey Wirth and Zia Chishti, MBA students at Stanford Business School with no qualifications in dentistry, worked to apply a fresh and different lens to orthodontics.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Zia only had the financial means to correct his teeth as an adult, shortly before business school.&amp;nbsp; When he finally got his braces off, he noticed something interesting: His retainer was almost invisible, but it still moved his teeth, which he could feel if he forgot to wear it for a few days. This small insight inspired a revolutionary hypothesis: If a simple plastic retainer could move teeth a little, perhaps the technology could be improved to move teeth a lot, but without affecting a person&#39;s appearance as much as conventional braces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Chishti and Wirth proposed a series of transparent, custom-manufactured removable plastic alignment retainers, developed through software-designed treatment plans. They called their solution Invisalign, emphasizing that the aligners would be inconspicuous to others. By changing to a new set every few weeks, the patient&#39;s teeth would gradually move into the desired position without the need for metal braces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By looking at the problem of straightening teeth through these novel customer and technology-centered lenses, Zia and Kelsey made orthodontic treatment less painful, less embarrassing, and more affordable. &amp;nbsp;Today the company has transformed orthodontics and has a market capitalization over $15 billion.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;SpaceX: Relentless Experimentation&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Everyone knows about software companies using A/B testing to refine products. But could this approach create strategic success in the ultimate heavy industry? In only two decades, SpaceX has massively transformed near-Earth space travel through relentless experimentation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;SpaceX engineers have learned to make small moves that add up to big improvements by repeatedly testing new hypotheses. This rapid test-and-improve approach enables them to acquire new information at a reasonable cost and to more quickly travel down the experience curve. They refer to their decision system as “fly, test, fail, fix” and accept that failure (“unplanned disassembly”) is a necessary part of testing the boundaries of what is possible. They&#39;ve pioneered lower-cost 3D printing for rocket components, as well as making more components re-useable, and shifting away from expensive external contracting, with 80% of components produced in-house.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moving down the cost curve required substantially increased frequency of launches. During the 30-year period of its space shuttle program, NASA averaged 4.5 flights per year. In 2021 Space X launched 31 rockets in orbit, up from 26 the prior year. &amp;nbsp;In early 2022 it was launching three to five missions per month.&amp;nbsp; More frequent launches and other innovations have dramatically reduced the cost of putting a kilogram of mass into space. &amp;nbsp;For the period from the 1970s to the early 2000s, this cost was largely unchanged, costing an average of $54,550 per kilo. &amp;nbsp;SpaceX has slashed the per-kilo cost down to $2,720, a reduction of 95%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;TNC FishFace: Tapping Collective Intelligence&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The Nature Conservancy (TNC), a global conservation organization interested in protecting endangered fish stocks, was searching for effective strategies to implement conservation measures onboard fishing boats at sea. TNC wondered if digital techniques could be deployed by fishing boats to identify endangered species that they could return to the sea while still alive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But TNC did not have the necessary AI skills to develop a solution itself, so it decided to crowdsource solutions via Kaggle, an online platform that hosts machine-learning competitions. The TNC competition attracted 2,293 entries over five months with a $150,000 prize. After selecting a winning entry, TNC now has a prototype operating with 90% to 95% accuracy.&amp;nbsp; It is called FishFace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To solve the complex fisheries regulatory compliance problem, TNC anchored outside its own organization&#39;s capabilities, inviting the best AI developers in the world to provide a novel strategic solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI swarm platforms are a variant of this approach and are particularly useful for predicting uncertain events. &amp;nbsp;A study&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;at Stanford medical school found that groups of doctors using Swarm AI algorithms were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/swarm-ai-system/&quot;>;22% more accurate&lt;/a>; in making diagnoses than the most advanced deep-learning algorithm that only used historical data. &amp;nbsp;The difference is that participants in swarms “think together” in real time and converge on solutions through interactions governed by algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Quibi versus TikTok: Anchoring Inside vs. Outside&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In each of these examples, a substantial part of the strategic insight that led to breakthrough strategic ideas is the idea of anchoring outside the conventional boundaries of the industry.&amp;nbsp; Getting this right isn&#39;t easy — consider the experiences of Quibi.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Quibi was a short-form streaming platform launched with great fanfare in April 2020; by December 1, the company was dissolved at a loss of more than $1 billion.&amp;nbsp; An A list of investors included Alibaba, Disney, Google, and Goldman Sachs. &amp;nbsp;An all-star management cast was led by Meg Whitman, the former CEO of eBay and Hewlett Packard, and Jeffrey Katzenberg of Dreamworks. Investors were sure that this was a team of insiders who knew what the market wanted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The Quibi app was downloaded 4.5 million times during the second quarter of 2020, but by the third quarter of 2020 Quibi had only 710,000 paying subscribers and it was losing 90% of early users after their free trials expired. Quibi was anchored inside the old Hollywood model and failed just as short-form video competitor TikTok was explosively rising, with 315 million downloads in the first quarter of 2020.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The difference?&amp;nbsp; TikTok embraced the collective intelligence of its users with a highly sophisticated AI-curation of user-provided content.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you look in retrospect at Amazon&#39;s stepped entry into consumer financial services or the other examples above, they look like the work of a master strategist. But that disguises the reality: There were many small moves to build the capabilities and assets that supported those positions, including missteps and failures along the way. Strategically nimble organizations explicitly map potential pathways into new areas and update their models with their experiences. They understand the difference between modest cost, reversible strategic moves that build position and bet-the-farm decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Ways to Become a More Collaborative Leader]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_08_1484644095.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In today&amp;#8217;s fast-paced corporate landscape, most highly experienced leaders entering an organization are driven by a desire to make a significant impact and drive meaningful change. However, the approach they adopt in championing new ideas becomes the differentiating factor between success and failure. Unfortunately, when faced with resistance, some leaders become frustrated and disengaged or even choose to leave the organization. Affecting lasting change is not a solitary quest, but an inherently shared effort. It requires embracing a collaborative mindset that respects and includes diverse perspectives, maintains a strategic focus, and patiently navigates the complexities of organizational dynamics. It&amp;#8217;s not about surrendering your passion or advocacy but leveraging them in a more inclusive, strategic, and ultimately effective way. The author recommends shifting your mental model from that of a crusader to that of a collaborative leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-ways-to-become-a-more-collaborative-leader?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When “Kathy,” a former client of Luis&#39;s, got hired as a VP at a fintech company, she wanted to have an impact. She saw things that could be better, had ideas about how to change them, and was hungry to get down to the business of making those changes. She approached change-making like a crusader, driven by her passion for what she believed in. She expressed her ideas fervently,&amp;nbsp;making impassioned speeches during team meetings. She fearlessly pointed out what was going wrong and what could be better. And as someone who was seen as not being afraid to “speak truth to power,” she adopted the role of advocate for less-vocal or more junior team members. While on occasion these pitches landed and led to short-term change, she was much more frequently frustrated at the lack of action that resulted. Worse, this approach made her increasingly isolated in the organization, feeding a vicious cycle that made it increasingly difficult for her to affect change.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In today&#39;s fast-paced corporate landscape, most highly experienced leaders entering an organization are driven by a desire to make a significant impact and drive meaningful change. However, the approach they adopt in championing new ideas becomes the differentiating factor between success and failure. Unfortunately, when faced with resistance, some leaders become frustrated and disengaged or even choose to leave the organization. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14697010500082902&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; that this is particularly true for leaders who are hired specifically to be “change agents.” Moreover, the leadership training and research firm Leadership IQ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leadershipiq.com/blogs/leadershipiq/35354241-why-new-hires-fail-emotional-intelligence-vs-skills&quot;>;found&lt;/a>; that 46% of newly hired executives fail within the first 18 months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recognizing the need for a transformative approach that would allow her to advocate for her ideas without alienating others, Kathy needed to shift her mental model from that of a crusader to that of a collaborative leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The crusader approach: Passionate but isolating&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A crusader is a leadership style described in the book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Built-Growth-Builder-Personality-Business/dp/1633692760&quot;>;&lt;em>;Built for Growth&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;. The crusader embodies a passionate advocacy for their vision, values, and goals. Their decisions are guided by a set of core beliefs and values. They tackle change directly and forcefully, driven by a profound sense of purpose that fuels their willingness to voice their opinions, even in the face of opposition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While this approach can initially instill confidence and self-efficacy as leaders witness the short-term positive impact of their ideas, it often proves counterproductive in the long run. The crusader leader is often perceived as closed minded, inflexible, and overly passionate. While passion can be a positive trait, it becomes detrimental when accompanied by predictable negative behaviors. Crusader leaders tend to:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Speak up frequently and vehemently, sometimes to the point of dominating conversations.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Interrupt others or answer questions with their viewpoint. In other words, they don&#39;t always listen to understand.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Be outspoken about their opinions, often pushing their own agenda without considering other perspectives.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Exhibit visible and frequent frustration when faced with resistance, doubling down on justifying or defending their approach, often assuming that pushback stems from ignorance rather than a genuine divergence of viewpoints.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Are you a crusader leader?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As you reflect on your leadership style, you might recognize some traits of a crusader. Even though there&#39;s no single reason why someone might adopt this approach, it can be driven by various factors, each with its own set of consequences. It&#39;s important to be introspective and understand the root cause and impact of your leadership style so you can adopt a more balanced one. Here are some key indicators of crusader approach:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You&#39;re passionate.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Leaders who are passionate about an issue may display behavior that can be misinterpreted as inflexible and defensive. They often have considerable expertise in an area. They believe passionately that their way is the best way forward, which makes them less likely to accept or consider alternative perspectives. This leads to exhaustion, as &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/dont-let-passion-lead-to-burnout-on-your-team&quot;>;research has shown&lt;/a>; that prioritizing passion above all else can be ineffective and harmful.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You get frustrated by the slow pace of a particular change.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Crusader leaders see themselves as needing to single-handedly push hard to make progress, adopting a tightly focused approach and losing the opportunity to recruit supporters and collaborators to help make lasting change. Their sense of urgency is not shared by the group they&#39;re trying to influence.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;You&#39;ve seen the crusader approach work in the past. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some leaders default to the crusader style because they&#39;ve seen its immediate results in past situations. They&#39;ve witnessed how this approach can achieve impressive results, overwhelming dissent and driving to decisions — in the short term. But in the longer term, these tactics can backfire and undermine the crusader&#39;s ability to achieve lasting change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to make the shift from a crusader to collaborative leader&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A more effective approach to driving change in the workplace involves adopting the mindset of a collaborator. Instead of doggedly pursuing a myopic perspective, collaborators focus on building relationships, understanding organizational dynamics and reasons for resistance, and using this knowledge to advocate for change in a shared, strategic manner. Here are six ways to become a more collaborative leader:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Understand the organizational culture.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Whether we like it or not, how influential we are is ultimately in the hands of those we want to influence. And influence is highly context dependent. Instead of sticking to your guns and putting yourself out there without understanding the context you&#39;re operating in, a better approach is to identify how things work in your organization. Look for clues about what works and what doesn&#39;t. In meetings, pay attention to which behaviors are rewarded and which aren&#39;t as effective. Watch the most effective leaders in the organization and consider asking them how they might approach a particular situation. Is their approach different from yours? When you understand the “rules” of the game, you&#39;ll be in a much better position to play it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Choose your battles.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Crusaders tend to advocate for changing big things — things that, to their frustration, are complex and require a winning coalition. And in some instances, the crusader isn&#39;t the right person to make those changes. For instance, suppose you&#39;re a manager at a software company and notice inefficiencies in both the software development process and the company&#39;s recruitment strategy. While your passion and drive may urge you to tackle both issues, overhauling the recruitment strategy might be more complex, requiring collaborative efforts and a broad coalition to address effectively. Fighting the recruitment battle can lead to frustration, burnout, and an erosion of credibility if changes don&#39;t materialize quickly. And most likely, the recruitment team will respond defensively to your initiative. Instead, focus your energy and resources on streamlining the software development process, an area where you can make a significant and meaningful impact given your expertise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Seek feedback.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Others often see us more objectively than we see ourselves. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Self-Insight-Roadblocks-Detours-Knowing-Psychology/dp/0415654173/&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; has shown that people don&#39;t realize how they behave in certain situations, or they misremember their actions, leading to an inaccurate perception of themselves. Crusaders, often consumed by their vision, may overlook crucial details or perspectives, leading to an incomplete view of the situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be relentless about asking for feedback and suggestions to better understand how your approach is being perceived and what you can do next time to become more effective. This is a transformative (and often sobering) step for a crusader transitioning to a collaborative leadership style. It not only cultivates self-awareness, but also gives you a comprehensive understanding of your actions&#39; consequences, including potential negative effects on team dynamics, morale, and productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Develop and leverage relationships.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s crucial to build and foster a winning coalition of individuals who can support your ideas. Imagine the organization as a heavy wagon that&#39;s difficult to stop or steer in a different direction from the outside. Instead of trying to push or pull the wagon alone, leaders should get on the wagon and work with the drivers to steer it from the inside. This approach requires building relationships and coalitions within the organization to gain support for ideas and create a sense of shared ownership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An easy way to “get on the wagon” is to align your ideas with other people&#39;s as a way to gain supporters and allies. For example, let&#39;s say you&#39;re a scientist who is concerned about high staff turnover rates. During a meeting, a colleague from HR discusses their goal of increasing employee engagement. Instead of pushing your staff retention concern independently, you could propose a joint project that addresses both concerns — for example, a pilot program in your department that integrates strategies to enhance employee engagement that might reduce turnover rates. By doing so, you&#39;re integrating your initiatives with the needs and concerns of your HR colleague, making it easier for others to support yours and their proposal.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Be open to other perspectives.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To gain influence, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/09/3-ways-to-grow-your-influence-in-a-new-job&quot;>;you must also be open to being influenced&lt;/a>;. Nobody wants to “negotiate” with someone who isn&#39;t open to other perspectives and can only see the world through their own limited view. Instead, try to cultivate genuine curiosity about other ways of seeing challenges and solutions. Instead of digging in or restating your preferred approach, ask open questions of colleagues who don&#39;t share your view and try to identify shared perspectives. While you might see a straight line between the problem and solution based on your perspective and expertise, others may not see the trajectory as clearly and will struggle to enact the desired strategy as a result. Even the right decision can lead to the wrong outcome if you&#39;re unsuccessful in creating a shared understanding of how to successfully implement the change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Focus on long-term goals.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Building lasting change requires maintaining focus on the long-term objective. Sometimes, being a crusader is warranted and appropriate, particularly when urgent action is needed and you have the authority to make a change. However, these situations tend to be few and far between. If you want to achieve ambitious lasting change, it&#39;s unlikely to happen all at once, and you most likely can&#39;t do it by yourself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Confront your crusader self with these three questions: Is this problem mine to solve? Do I need to solve it alone? Do I need to solve it now? With this focus, you can apply the right level of long-term vision to the things that really matter, including letting go of fighting every battle along the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;. 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The need for change is inevitable in any organization, but the approach to driving change is a determinant of its success or failure, as Kathy, our passionate crusader, realized. Affecting lasting change is not a solitary quest, but an inherently shared effort. It requires embracing a collaborative mindset that respects and includes diverse perspectives, maintains a strategic focus, and patiently navigates the complexities of organizational dynamics. It&#39;s not about surrendering your passion or advocacy but leveraging them in a more inclusive, strategic, and ultimately effective way.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the Construction Industry Be Disrupted?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_08_1299614411.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Dan Reynolds Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Construction is often maligned as the industry that technology left behind. Industry observers routinely deride the lack of technological sophistication in the construction industry, and have pigeon-holed it as old-fashioned and lagging behind more forward-looking and purposeful industries such as manufacturing. But that view ignores where the industry has advanced &amp;#8212; specifically, in information management systems that have created significant gains. Moreover, it fails to take into account why automation and robotics don&amp;#8217;t work on jobsites, which is that they&amp;#8217;re often a poor fit for the dynamic environments that bear little resemblance to factory floors. Understanding why some tech takes root and why some doesn&amp;#8217;t, however, is essential to making smart investments in new tools and systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 1910, the French artist Villemard created a series of illustrations imagining life in the year 2000. In one of his drawings, an architect &lt;a href=&quot;https://wearereplicants.wordpress.com/2011/03/10/french-artist-villemards-vision-of-the-future/&quot;>;sits in a booth pushing buttons on a console&lt;/a>; to manipulate a series of machines operating in the usual debris of a construction site. The various machines cut, shape, lift, and place stone blocks to build a house. There are no human laborers in his projection — mechanization has made them obsolete.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Villemard&#39;s vision has not panned out, however. On the contrary, industry observers routinely deride the lack of technological sophistication in the construction industry, and have pigeon-holed it as old-fashioned and lagging behind more forward-looking and purposeful industries such as manufacturing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This story has been told and told again. In the wake of the post-WWII housing boom, the editors of &lt;em>;Fortune&lt;/em>; published a 1947 article titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biblio.com/book/fortune-magazine-volume-xxxvi-number-2/d/1489550271&quot;>;The Industry Capitalism Forgot&lt;/a>;,” in which they mocked homebuilding&#39;s “feudal character” and “picayune scale.” In 2006, MIT Professor John Fernandez summed up the conventional wisdom when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/books/edition/Material_Architecture/AtMrBgAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;dq=the+slowest+of+all+industries+of+such+scale+in+implementing+proven,+scientifically+sound+technological+innovation&amp;amp;pg=PA11&amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;>;he wrote&lt;/a>;: “It is widely believed that construction is the slowest of all industries of such scale in implementing proven, scientifically sound technological innovation.” A decade later, McKinsey consultants &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/reinventing-construction-through-a-productivity-revolution&quot;>;continued the drumbeat&lt;/a>;, blaming limited productivity improvements on “poor project management and execution … underinvestment in skills development, R&amp;amp;D, and innovation.” In early 2023, University of Chicago economists Austan Goolsbee and Chad Syverson published an article titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w30845&quot;>;The Strange and Awful Path of Productivity in the US Construction Sector&lt;/a>;” in which they concluded that aggregate data “demonstrate a large and decades-long decline in construction sector productivity.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Anecdotes about the opposition to change paint a similar picture. Regardless of the era, workers who worried that labor saving devices might deepen the inherent insecurity of life in the trades sometimes frowned on the introduction of new machinery on the construction jobsite. Carpenter Joseph Emanuello &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/j.ctv941wxz.19?seq=2&quot;>;recalled&lt;/a>; the first time he encountered electric circular saws: “One guy took the Skilsaw on the roof of the building and threw it off. He said, &#39;The saw&#39;s too fast, I&#39;m going to cut by hand.&#39;” The hesitancy to adopt innovation extended to the contractor&#39;s office. When John Tocci, fresh out of engineering school, bought an expensive mainframe computer for his multi-generational family general contracting firm in 1983, his father — the owner — looked at the bulky item and grumbled, “When that freaking thing can lay brick, I&#39;ll learn how to use it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But it is easy to exaggerate the level of resistance. In 1993, a researcher conducted interviews with tradesmen about their attitudes toward technological innovation. With few exceptions, they welcomed new tools that made the work safer and less physically demanding and, for the most part, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/23746019&quot;>;their pride in increased production outweighed their fears of displacement&lt;/a>;. In general, construction has adopted an evolutionary, not revolutionary, pace of change.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not everyone wants it to stay that way, however: Villemard has contemporary followers who continue to envision a fully mechanized future for construction, just over the horizon. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.roboticsbusinessreview.com/construction/more-than-7000-robots-will-work-in-construction-by-2025-report-says/&quot;>;2019 report by Tractica&lt;/a>;, a technology market intelligence firm, declared that construction is “ripe for disruption” due to its history of technological underdevelopment and predicts that the purchase of construction robots will increase tenfold by 2025. Gaurav Kikani, vice president of Built Robotics, suggests that there will be “an explosion of robotics” that will replace the eight-hour workday with automated activity around the clock. A recent global survey indicated that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forconstructionpros.com/construction-technology/article/21451998/abb-group-robotic-automations-potential-to-enhance-productivity-efficiency-and-safety-on-construction-sites&quot;>;81% of construction businesses&lt;/a>; will introduce or increase their use of robotics and automation in the coming decade. In a 2020 report, McKinsey &amp;amp; Co. futurists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/McKinsey/Industries/Capital%20Projects%20and%20Infrastructure/Our%20Insights/The%20next%20normal%20in%20construction/The-next-normal-in-construction.pdf&quot;>;predict that 45% of the industry&#39;s value chain&lt;/a>; will shift from traditional processes in the next 15 years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What both the optimists and pessimists struggle with, however, is why some technologies take root in the industry — often creating significant gains in productivity — and why others, such as worksite robots, don&#39;t. Understanding this point will help construction companies and the firms that supply them predict which investments will pay off and which will end up as curiosities that sit gathering dust.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why Certain Tech Doesn&#39;t Take Hold&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many of the inventions breathlessly touted by the industry press remain on the fringes of the industry. State-of the-art six-axis articulated robots may have transformed the auto industry, but their stationery character does not work on a construction site. A robot that is immobile and cannot adjust to the rough terrain and multi-story nature of a building project is functionally useless. Autonomous earth-moving machinery can dig out and prepare foundations. Robots can do simple layout. Drones can navigate job sites and record daily progress. Exoskeletons can relieve the burden of lifting heavy items and YouTube videos portray the wonders of 3D printing. Yet many of these advances remain novelty items, available only to a minority of firms that have the resources and inclination to experiment with equipment and systems that have not consistently been proven to be quality- or cost-effective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“People think robots are intelligent. They&#39;re getting better, but they&#39;re still pretty dumb,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/db2b5d64-10e7-11e8-a765-993b2440bd73&quot;>;says Jeremy Hadall&lt;/a>;, chief technologist for robotics and automation at the United Kingdom&#39;s Manufacturing Technology Centre. “Robots have a place in building productivity in the construction industry, but you have to be realistic about what they can do. Are we going to see completely automated robotic building sites in 10 years? No.” Similarly, Erin Bradner, Director of Robotics at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autodeskresearch.com/groups/robotics-lab&quot;>;Autodesk Robotics Lab&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/charlestowersclark/2020/01/10/construction-co-bots-need-to-be-smarter-more-adaptive-part-two/?sh=126d2c296a79&quot;>;suggests the current level of sophistication of co-bots may be exaggerated&lt;/a>;: “They&#39;ll stop when they encounter an obstacle, but you don&#39;t want your project stopping every time a person sneezes.” Reza Akhavian, a professor of engineering at San Diego State University, received a $691,000 National Science Foundation grant to study robotics in construction. “Currently and for the foreseeable future, the field of robotics in general, and construction robotics in particular, are not even close to a state in which robots can replace human workers,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive.com/news/contech-conversations-sdsu-professor-says-robots-not-close-to-replacing/600771/&quot;>;Akhavian argues&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reluctance to embrace new technology is based on more than the irascible and retrograde attitudes of industry players. Robots and other forms of automation are costly and require an extended time frame before offering a satisfactory return on capital. Given the decentralized nature of the industry and the predominance of small and medium-sized firms, few owners have the financial capacity to purchase expensive paraphernalia that may only provide a profit in the very long term. And while large general contractors may have more cash on hand, subcontractors employ the bulk of the workforce. There is little motivation for one well capitalized company to invest in a technology that will ultimately benefit another smaller firm.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, companies in other industries have traditionally been motivated to spend capital on automation and expensive new procedures to reduce escalating labor costs. Unfortunately, construction executives found simpler ways to cut labor costs through the misclassification of employees as independent contractors, cash compensation, and reduced wages and safety standards — all components of &lt;a href=&quot;https://lwp.law.harvard.edu/files/lwp/files/erlich_ilrr_final_article_11.28.20.pdf&quot;>;a successful crusade to undermine the union sector&lt;/a>; in many parts of the country. There is less incentive to buy robots to replace high-priced labor when the labor itself is not as pricey.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Construction&#39;s Digital Transformation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Still, the digital revolution in the twenty-first century has propelled construction, particularly the architectural functions and project management systems. Building Information Modeling (BIM), a software process that transforms traditional blueprints into digital images, has introduced the critical factor of coordination into the previously siloed products from the various design disciplines — architectural, structural, mechanical, electrical, civil — and allowed the management team to essentially build a project twice: once virtually on the office desktops and tablets and a second time with the actual trades workers and materials in the field. Jeff Gouveia, Executive Vice-President of Suffolk Construction, described the pre-BIM work style to me in an interview: “Prior to modeling, coordination was done with a light table with a clear piece of plastic over it. You overlaid 2D drawing on top of 2D drawing on top of 2D drawing. You got them just right, taped them in the corner, made sure that they were in the right scale, and then you basically started circling conflicts, where a piece of ductwork or pipe went into a column or a beam.” Modeling allows for the advance visualization of an entire development from site-work to finish hardware.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Modeling may reduce total construction costs, but it requires upfront investments on a scale that is only available to larger general contractors and a narrow slice of elite subcontractors that can afford the software and, above all, the hiring and training of highly computer-literate staff. Institutional owners like universities and hospitals that expect their projects to last decades are more likely to accept the initial costs of modeling than developers who tend to focus on the bottom line, just surviving through the warranties and short-term flipping goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While BIM initially just involved the professionals, modeling has since filtered down to workers in the field to offer suggestions and critiques of the unfolding designs. Gouveia describes the transition on a standard task like laying out the sleeves for plumbing and electrical pipes through a concrete deck. “Before, you&#39;re unrolling the drawings, the wind is blowing, you&#39;ve got a piece of rebar on one side, and you&#39;ve got a brick on the other side, and you&#39;re trying to hold it down. Then you&#39;re scaling it and going over and using your tape. Now, someone&#39;s got a laptop or a tablet or an iPad, with the model on there, with that floor laid out. You&#39;re laid out in a matter of 90 minutes, whereas before that would have taken maybe five hours.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though currently limited to larger projects, digitization and modeling will continue to penetrate further into the industry. The 2021 $1.2 trillion Infrastructure Investment and Jobs Act (ILJA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive.com/news/construction-tech-praise-110-million-infrastructure-bill-push-for-more/610126/&quot;>;included $100 million&lt;/a>; for advanced digital construction management systems and related technologies. While the language in the bill is non-specific, the funds are expected to support advanced digital management tools, 3D modeling, drone visualization, and data analysis. In 2016, the use of BIM was mandated on public projects in the United Kingdom and the National Institute of Building Sciences (NIBS) hosted a meeting in early 2021 to consider adopting a BIM standard for the US Modeling is expanding beyond three dimensions to incorporate 4D (scheduling), 5D (cost) and even 6D (facility management).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the job site, foremen have company-issued tablets as part of their tool kit so plans and modifications can be transmitted instantaneously. The old reliable gang boxes that housed workers&#39; tools for overnight storage now can also have Wi-Fi, printers and flat screens on the underside of the lid to display the latest shop drawings electronically. Most union training programs have incorporated CAD and BIM into their curricula. New young entrants into the industry from diverse demographic and socio-economic backgrounds may be able to translate their home computer expertise into modeling proficiency in the field. “We are always going to need mechanics to assemble stuff,” John Tocci told me in an interview. “but the mechanic of the future will also be the video game guy.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While Villemard&#39;s vision may now seem like the stuff of science fiction, there have been steady if undramatic steps to transform the industry. It takes far fewer trades workers to erect a skyscraper than it did even a decade or two ago. Tools and materials are constantly upgraded and BIM represents a novel and exceptional method to design and build a project. Turbulent change is unlikely, however, in an industry that remains fundamentally decentralized. The ability to invest in game-changing technologies is limited to the upper tier of the contracting community. For the foreseeable future, the vast majority of small and medium-sized subcontractors and trades workers will adjust and adapt, not disrupt.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;This article is adapted from the author&#39;s book, &lt;/em>;The Way We Build: Restoring Dignity to Construction Work.&lt;em>; It is the first part of a two part series.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Responsible Computing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_4689448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;For businesses, technology has a variety of interconnected impacts including unintended consequences, data risks, and appropriateness of technological uses, as well as broader environmental concerns. The authors offer a systemic Responsible Computing Framework that integrates environmental challenges including energy consumption and emissions with many other social and governance aspects. It is a practical blueprint that firms can use to make their IT more green, ethical, trustworthy, and sustainable, based on six pillars that leaders need to address for their business to become a responsible computing provider: data centers, infrastructure, code, data, systems, and impact. For each they provide several KPIs that leaders should focus on.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Over the past few years, IBM has spoken to hundreds of chief technology officers (CTOs) reflecting a cross-section of industries for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/thought-leadership/institute-business-value/en-us/c-suite-study/cto&quot;>;a series of Architecture Decision Points reports&lt;/a>;. Clearly, business leaders recognize that technology will be a central part of delivering the future enterprise. However, they are also well aware that society is looking to businesses to prove they can live by the values they espouse — and computing has a key role to play. And these same CTOs mentioned that the societal impact of technology is keeping them up at night.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For businesses, technology has a variety of interconnected impacts including unintended consequences, data risks, and appropriateness of technological uses, as well as broader environmental concerns. Leaders are worried about introducing vulnerabilities to their companies, about deploying systems with harmful biases, about how AI will be perceived internally and by the public, and about the environmental impact of using certain technologies. These issues are all connected, though they&#39;re often discussed separately. If companies want to ensure they are responsible users of technology, they need a holistic approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Developed at IBM in conjunction with our CTO outreach, we have created a systemic &lt;a href=&quot;https://responsiblecomputing.net/&quot;>;Responsible Computing Framework&lt;/a>; that integrates environmental challenges including energy consumption and emissions with many other social and governance aspects. It is a practical blueprint that firms can use to make their IT more green, ethical, trustworthy, and sustainable. Our Responsible Computing Framework highlights six pillars that business leaders need to address for their business to become a responsible computing provider: data centers, infrastructure, code, data, systems, and impact. For each we provide several KPIs that can be used to provide comparisons.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Data Centers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first pillar of responsible computing is the physical infrastructure you need to develop and deliver IT services — whether or not you run data centers yourself. The global power capacity of data centers has grown by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/02/23/2390642/0/en/The-Global-Data-Center-Market-Size-to-Reach-288-30-Billion-by-2027-Arizton.html&quot;>;43% in the last three years&lt;/a>;, and inefficiency is a significant problem: the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nrdc.org/sites/default/files/data-center-efficiency-assessment-IP.pdf&quot;>;average server&lt;/a>; runs at 12% to 18% of its capacity but draws 30% to 60% of maximum power. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;International Energy Agency (IEA)&lt;/a>; predicts that the energy use of global data centers will jump from 1% of worldwide electricity demand to more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-06610-y&quot;>;more than 20%&lt;/a>; in just over a decade.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To measure the impact of your data centers, you need to consider the energy sources, energy use related to cooling&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; and water usage, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techtarget.com/searchdatacenter/feature/Words-to-go-6-key-data-center-sustainability-metrics&quot;>;track KPIs for each&lt;/a>;. If you don&#39;t run your own data centers, most mature cloud services providers, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sustainability/&quot;>;AWS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://newsroom.ibm.com/IBM-Cloud-Carbon-Calculator-Aims-to-Help-Organizations-Address-Greenhouse-Gas-Emissions-to-Advance-their-Sustainability-Objectives&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/how-microsoft-measures-datacenter-water-and-energy-use-to-improve-azure-cloud-sustainability/&quot;>;Microsoft&lt;/a>; measure this as part of their service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider the carbon footprint, or the amount of CO2 that was emitted in generating the energy used by data centers. Consider how much carbon dioxide a data center produces every day (carbon usage effectiveness); how clean the energy consumed by the data center is (technology carbon efficiency); and how much renewable energy is generated onsite (green energy coefficient).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, there&#39;s the efficiency footprint, or how optimized the data center is for its computing infrastructure. To measure this, you can look at the how much energy is used specifically by a data center&#39;s infrastructure, how much energy in the data center is reused elsewhere in the facility, and the HVAC system&#39;s effectiveness, or the overall efficiency of the cooling system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, there is the amount of water used by data centers as part of their operation, or water footprint. This requires breaking down how water is used, considering infrastructure, power generation, and how much gets recycled for other purposes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By having a clear picture of your power sources, cooling, and water usage of your data centers, business leaders can start to critically think about addressing the issue. How can you move to sustainable energy sources? How can you use carbon offsets? Would moving your infrastructure to a cooler climate save energy? Could you use the heat generated by your infrastructure for another purpose? How can you save water?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Infrastructure&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second pillar is reducing the environmental impact of computation. This requires that you assess the whole computing ecosystem you work in, not just your own infrastructure, including the hardware, software, and networks required to develop, test, deliver, monitor, control, and support IT services. While most manufacturers share this information when asked, there are also multiple industry initiatives, such as from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.itu.int/en/ITU-D/Environment/Documents/Toolbox/GEM_2020_def.pdf&quot;>;International Telecommunication Union&lt;/a>;, to standardize data and develop best practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider the computing hardware in use now. This can be measured by power usage KPIs, such as the average electricity consumption per hardware unit, how often computing hardware is used, and the proportion of hardware in use over a month compared to what is installed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, you need to understand the greenhouse gas emissions per unit of hardware, or unit carbon footprint. This KPI measures the total greenhouse gas emissions generated by a single hardware unit over the different stages of its life cycle — from the original extraction of resources through manufacturing of precursors and the making of the unit, its operation, and then the emissions of disposal once it is superseded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, measure the amount of waste that computing generates. This can include how much hardware is sent to landfill versus refurbishment, reuse, resale, or salvage (e-waste rate). It can also feature an assessment of your plastic footprint, calculated either by the total weight of plastic used or by the types of plastic polymers used, and their potential end destinations or likelihood of being recycled.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you have considered your infrastructure, you can start to consider actions to address your computing impact. What technologies could you use that reduce power per unit? How can you get more bang for your buck — for example, through consolidation, rationalization, or removing systems you don&#39;t use? How about using your spare capacity for other purposes? How can you recycle or reuse more effectively?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Code&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The third pillar is the efficiency of your code, and the potential environmental, societal, and economic impact of the code in use. This involves bringing responsibility to the level of individual developers and ensuring the development of responsible design principles or architectures that will help them make the right choices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Key to understanding how responsible code works are “function points,” which are a way of expressing the amount of business functionality that code provides. There are a wide range of software tools (both &lt;a href=&quot;https://owasp.org/www-community/Vulnerability_Scanning_Tools&quot;>;open source&lt;/a>; and commercial) that can assist organizations in their analysis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Start by measuring how efficient the function points are, such as page size or HTTP requests per process. You should also measure the carbon impact of each function point — the electricity consumption for an entire system, individual function points, or even for individual processes within a function point. Measuring the security of function points, such as the number of identified vulnerabilities, is also vital.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, take a close look at your code architecture. How scalable is it? How easy is it for the code to be moved to another platform? The time taken or cost to integrate function points in one system with ones in other systems is also a valuable KPI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, measure the quality of your code — for instance, the number of defects per function point — and its maintenance and rework attributes. You should also measure the reliability of your code, such as the average uptime per quarter for an entire system, function point, or even individual process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you understand the efficiency of function points, as well as the overall architecture and quality then you can start to consider how to improve. Should you use open or proprietary code? How secure is your code? How open is your code? Does making code reusable do more harm than good? Could you reduce the resolution of calculations through approximate computing?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Data&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The fourth pillar of responsible computing is the privacy, transparency, sharing, and acquisition of data. This pillar directly addresses your duty to understand the ethical, legal, and social responsibility of processing data across its lifecycle and allows the leader to take or delegate ownership and accountability on the protection and privacy of the data and its usage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thankfully there is significant work going on in this area, and we suggest one KPI: the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ictworks.org/responsible-data-maturity-model/&quot;>;Responsible Data Maturity Model&lt;/a>; which provides insight into how data is being managed in your business across 15 domains (awareness &amp;amp; capacity, policy &amp;amp; governance, accountability, partnership, inventory, privacy, legal, risk, minimization, transfer, security, sharing, combining, retention, and incident response).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With this analysis you can understand how each domain can be improved, and also how to track improvement. Do you have sufficient data governance in place? Are you aware of all the data that your business is responsible for? Who is responsible for what data? What are your current data and legal risks? How quickly do you respond to data incidents?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Systems&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Responsible systems are those that are fair, accountable, and transparent. This fifth pillar asks business leaders to understand their “systems” — the integrated sets of hardware, data, code, models, and services used in work— and the ethical implications of using them. At the core of this pillar is the fairness — or bias — that the systems within your organization have, and how accountable your firm is for what those systems do in your name.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider how one of your systems may discriminate against or harm people based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or disability. Measure this through comparing the outcomes between groups. More sophisticated comparisons can recognize that groups differ in more than one dimension. Another approach can measure how many complaints are received about the system fairness and how they are addressed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, determine which systems have specific individuals assigned as responsible for outcomes, and measure compliance with regulations, what means of legal redress are available, and how liable the business is for any harms that may have happened. These perspectives will help you make these systems more transparent. By having a clear picture of how fair, accountable, and transparent your systems are, you can start to critically think about addressing the issue. How can we reduce bias in our systems? How can we minimize our exposure to liability? Who is responsible for what system?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An important KPI is the analysis of the number of outcomes from the systems that are auditable, and another is how explainable system outcomes are. Furthermore, measure the number of knowledge artifacts that explain the goals, methods, and limitations of your systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Impact&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pillar considers how technology can be used for good — for example, to address social mobility or exclusion. But just because your organization can do something, doesn&#39;t mean it should. We suggest the best way to have responsible impact is to consider your computing in the context of the UN&#39;s 17 Sustainability Development Goals (SDGs). Some impacts are more general, such as enabling gender equality in hiring (SDG 5), providing decent work (SDG 8), or reducing inequality in income (SDG 10). KPIs here can consider how IT investment has led to such impacts by looking at before and after statistics. Similarly, actions to meet climate change goals (SDG 13) can be measured through KPIs such as the carbon impact per employee, per customer, and per SKU (stock taking unit).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, other impact measures will be specific to industries. For instance, the type of impact your IT use can have in agriculture is different to retail. Agricultural firms can measure how their IT investments have reduced the amount of water required to irrigate the crops (SDG 6). Similarly, retail firms can measure how their IT investments have enabled more sustainable consumption and production (SDG 12).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you have insight into how your computing impacts your performance on the SDGs, then you can start to critically evaluate how to improve in the future. How can your IT help to save lives, or improve life, in a similar way? How can you create new jobs, or help people develop new skills? How could you help speed up the response to disasters or emergencies?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Way Forward&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;World events since the pandemic and geopolitics have shown business leaders very clearly that their workers need protection, and that their supply chains are shakier than they thought. That has focused attention on corporate responsibility and how we use scarce resources. In IT specifically, the new normal is all about being fast, efficient, effective, and responsible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The task facing business leaders is to position their firms for both scale and success while taking an ethical and responsible approach to how, where, and why they use IT. The CTOs we spoke to agreed that achieving real and lasting change requires a holistic approach that encompasses every aspect of the computing ecosystem, from emissions and materials right through to ethical sourcing, data stewardship, and social responsibility work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, business leaders can&#39;t do it all on their own. They need to ensure that the entire IT function is aligned behind their responsible computing vision. Every member of the IT function will need to appreciate the ethics that underpin the responsible computing vision, as well as being accountable for their actions. This will require a professionalized IT function that has both the competence to be able to deliver on the vision, as well as the inclusivity to ensure diversity of opinion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond the IT function, the entire C-suite, employees, suppliers, partners, and customers will need to be more mindful about how they consume and conserve valuable resources—which means offering them the right incentives to do so. Everyone will have a part to play: infrastructure experts and application developers, but also professionals in sales, marketing, operations, finance, procurement, and facilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, it&#39;s a big task, but the reward will be greater trust in the organization — and, ultimately, a better world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Science-Backed Ways to Improve Your Well-Being at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_1326122153.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;background: white&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #282828&quot;>;Employee well-being is an organizational issue, not just an individual one. Many factors impact and influence it, including your workload and flexibility, your manager, and the culture within your team. But while you may not have the ability to change your organization or your boss, there are some simple, science-backed things you can do daily to improve your emotional fitness and well-being. This article covers six&lt;span style=&quot;background: white&quot;>; simple yet surprisingly powerful emotional fitness practices to help you better manage stress and improve your well-being&lt;/span>;.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In the past two and a half years, I&#39;ve given more than 360 virtual and in-person talks, workshops, and seminars about emotional fitness, well-being, and avoiding burnout. I&#39;ve had the privilege of working with people from every kind of industry, including doctors on the frontlines of Covid, employees at large and small companies, and nonprofit professionals. And I&#39;ve had the gift of staying connected with many of them to learn about which emotional fitness practices had a positive impact on their well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And here&#39;s my big learning: When it comes to improving well-being at work, small things make a big difference if you practice them consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear: Employee well-being is an organizational issue, not just an individual one. Many factors impact and influence it, including your workload and flexibility, your manager, and the culture within your team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But while you may not have the ability to change your organization or your boss, there are some simple, science-backed things you can do daily to improve your emotional fitness and well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I define emotional fitness as the skill of creating a more supportive relationship with yourself, your thoughts and emotions, and other people. When you improve your physical fitness, you improve your ability to handle physical challenges. When you improve your emotional fitness, you improve your ability to handle emotional challenges with less struggle, stress, and overwhelm.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are six simple yet surprisingly powerful emotional fitness practices to help you better manage stress and improve your well-being:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Check in with yourself daily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Ask yourself: &lt;em>;How am I doing today? How am I feeling?&lt;/em>; Don&#39;t judge your answers or immediately try to “fix” how you&#39;re feeling. Just become aware.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I shared this practice during a recent keynote and a young woman came up to me afterward to say that she&#39;d heard me talk about it before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“At that time, I was feeling so burned out,” she told me. “I wasn&#39;t sure it would make a difference, but I decided to give this daily check-in a try. I was surprised at how much it helped me feel better. Instead of being consumed by my feelings of stress or overwhelm, I become aware of them and now feel more in control.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Research supports what she experienced: People who practice emotional awareness are &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmcpsychology.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40359-021-00593-8&quot;>;more likely to report greater well-being&lt;/a>;. Becoming aware of your difficult feelings reduces the intensity with which you experience them and gives you an opportunity to do something to support yourself to feel a little better.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Take a few short, quality breaks during the day. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The key word here is “quality.” This means doing something that helps you disconnect from work, refuel, and recharge. Scrolling social media or reading the news is not a quality break, and neither is catching up on your to-do list.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The human brain needs to take a break every 90 to 120 minutes to function at its best and avoid accumulated stress and overwhelm. Microsoft recently conducted a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/brain-research&quot;>;large-scale study&lt;/a>; and found that &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort&quot;>;taking five- to 10-minute breaks between meetings&lt;/a>; significantly reduced accumulated stress and overwhelm and improved focus.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My favorite way to disconnect from work during the day is to take a short walk outside. As mountains of research show, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27100368/&quot;>;it boosts your mood&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/dont-underestimate-the-power-of-a-walk&quot;>;improves focus and motivation&lt;/a>;, and has lots of health benefits if you do it consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice acceptance to focus on what you can control. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Acceptance involves two steps: First, acknowledge the situation with clarity, focusing on the facts you know to be true. Second, identify one step you could take to move forward with less stress and struggle.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We tend to underestimate how much ruminating on stressful situations drains our energy. Practicing these two steps of acceptance when you find yourself caught in a loop of negative thoughts helps to focus your attention on what you can control and take a productive action, however small. This &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/small-wins-and-feeling-good&quot;>;small win&lt;/a>; gives your brain a sense of progress, which feels good and often motivates you to find other useful steps you can take.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the women who participated in my leadership program where we learned the skill of acceptance told me recently that it&#39;s been her main go-to skill during the ongoing challenges and uncertainty at work. “Whenever I become overwhelmed with stress about work situations, the economy, or things with my team, I pause, take a breath, and ask myself what step I could take to move forward given how things are and what is in my control. Asking this question as a team has also been helpful for our team focus and stress level,” she told me.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Prioritize micro-moments of connection with colleagues.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Make it a point to greet your colleagues with genuine enthusiasm when you&#39;re on a call or when you see them for the first time during the day. In virtual meetings, where there is a tendency to just dive into the agenda, begin by asking everyone to share something good from their week so far. Be intentional about reaching out to a colleague to just check in, without focusing your conversation on work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re all starved for human connection after the years of pandemic isolation and it&#39;s negatively impacting our well-being. As human beings, we&#39;re wired to connect, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6125010/&quot;>;studies&lt;/a>; show that social support and feeling connected improve mental health and reduce stress and anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, take the initiative and create a daily moment of connection with a colleague. It doesn&#39;t take a lot of effort or time, but you&#39;ll feel uplifted and help the other person feel less alone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice gratitude to counter your brain&#39;s negativity bias. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you don&#39;t have one, create a daily gratitude practice, which can be as simple as writing down three things you appreciate every morning or in the evening.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Developing a grateful mindset is always beneficial for your well-being, but even more so during these uncertain times. Uncertainty is extremely stressful and energy-draining — it&#39;s the hardest thing for the human brain to handle. When your brain encounters uncertainty, it focuses on finding possible danger and enters the &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/09/our-brains-were-not-built-for-this-much-uncertainty&quot;>;“fight or flight state”&lt;/a>; so it can protect you. This can lead to increased anxiety and rumination about negative outcomes and worst-case scenarios.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By practicing gratitude, you ask your brain to widen its lens and focus its attention on things that are positive, meaningful, or comforting. The goal isn&#39;t to deny the difficulties you might be facing, but to remind yourself that they are not the entirety of your life. This fuels your emotional energy and helps improve your resilience, which is your ability to positively adapt amidst challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice active rest outside of work. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Finally, it&#39;s important to spend time outside of work doing things you love. Spend time on your favorite hobby. Dedicate time to reading or gardening. Try a new creative activity, like watercolor or writing. The key is to do something that actively fuels your energy and feeds parts of you other than just your work self. (In contrast, zoning out in front of Netflix for hours is not active rest, although watching an episode of your favorite show from time to time is a great option.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I picked up painting after my own burnout, and having something that allows me to completely disconnect from work and feed the creative/artist part of myself has been a huge gift for my well-being. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/43532701_On_the_Role_of_Passion_for_Work_in_Burnout_A_Process_Model&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>; of burnout in nurses supports what I&#39;ve found to be true in my experience: Nurses who spent time actively resting when they weren&#39;t working, either by engaging in hobbies or spending time with friends or family, were less likely to burn out than nurses who weren&#39;t intentional about disconnecting from work after their shift was finished.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As the cliche goes: “You are not your job.” Even, and perhaps especially, if you&#39;re passionate about your work, you need to be intentional about doing things you enjoy outside of work. If your productivity-obsessed brain objects, remind yourself that active rest is an investment in your ability to bring your full capacity to your work for a long period of time.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Managers Can Dismantle &ldquo;Benevolent Marginalization&rdquo;]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_4689448-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jayme Burrows/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While there is a growing recognition of the significance of diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, many firms fail to break down the subtle barriers obstructing progress because they engage in patronizing behavior that the authors call &amp;#8220;benevolent marginalization.&amp;#8221; Drawing on insights from a decade of research on benevolent discrimination experienced by women and individuals with disabilities in the workplace, the authors propose three key strategies to help discard such protectionism while forging a path toward genuine inclusion: shifting the focus from help to empowerment, engaging allies in non-managerial roles, and creating supportive spaces by handing over responsibilities for shaping their own professional lives to marginalized individuals.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;The old proverb about teaching people to fish so they can eat for a lifetime, rather than gifting a fish that lasts just a day, also applies to how organizations can empower, rather than merely help, disadvantaged groups.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;There has been a remarkable surge in diversity initiatives at companies, fueled by belief in the benefits of a diverse workforce and the collective fight against discrimination. As organizations strive to build inclusive workplaces, they often try to tackle overt discrimination and negative stereotypes against disadvantaged groups.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Yet these well-intentioned efforts often include a key oversight: Many DEI initiatives are founded on the flawed assumption that disadvantaged groups are helpless without assistance from those in power. Such protectionist beliefs give rise to the frequently overlooked yet deeply concerning phenomenon of benevolent marginalization, whereby good intentions can lead to harm.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Benevolent marginalization occurs when a dominant group paternalistically controls a weaker or marginalized group while portraying their actions as supportive and in solidarity with that group. Behind the façade of well-intentioned actions aimed at uplifting marginalized groups, a subtle power imbalance persists. Managers may even expect gratitude for their affectionate and helpful efforts, while those who are marginalized find themselves pressured into accepting or internalizing the subordinating order as the norm and even expressing gratitude in return. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Our analysis draws upon over a decade of extensive research conducted in diverse contexts. We utilized interviews, archival documents, and observations of individuals navigating subtle forms of marginalization. We also examined the pivotal role of internal activists and managers who actively support and become allies to overcome benevolent marginalization&lt;i>;.&lt;/i>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Subtle Discrimination Perpetuates Gender Inequality&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Benevolent marginalization manifests as subtle discrimination that impacts various groups and makes them unlikely to intervene or dissent, thereby hindering their advancement and perpetuating organizational inequality.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Imagine the scenario of &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/06/dismantling-benevolent-sexism&quot;>;benevolent sexism&lt;/a>;. Despite the decline of overtly sexist attitudes, women still face subtle forms of discrimination that may contribute to their underrepresentation in executive positions. Women are often stereotyped as the “weaker sex” needing chivalrous protection, but this seemingly favorable treatment conceals male dominance and can have negative consequences. When women are shielded from challenging assignments at work, for example, it inadvertently encourages stereotypes and fosters self-doubt, ultimately hampering their professional performance.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/AMBPP.2021.10710abstract&quot;>;three-year study&lt;/a>; examining benevolent sexism, we took a closer look at women-only networking initiatives. These initiatives, touted as essential components of diversity guidelines within organizations, are often devised by male managers to assist women. However, women frequently perceive them as a superficial attempt or mere tokenism aimed at fulfilling diversity quotas and creating a facade of inclusivity. Many such initiatives place the burden of overcoming gender disparities on women, often treating them as a homogenous group while failing to address the underlying systemic bias that fuels gender inequality. Paradoxically, in our study, these women frequently found themselves obligated to participate in such initiatives, only to experience feelings of patronization and occasional polite dismissal. They also encountered instances of “mansplaining,” where men condescendingly or patronizingly explain the intricacies of networking, assuming women to have lesser or inferior knowledge of the subject. These experiences can result in women feeling disillusioned and disengaged from such initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Yet, a remarkable transformation can occur when women take charge of these initiatives and tailor them to meet their individual needs. This can be achieved through collaborating with women across different levels of seniority to foster an inclusive networking environment that promotes diverse voices, offers mentorship and sponsorship opportunities, and creates spaces where women can openly and genuinely engage.&lt;i>; &lt;/i>;Our research suggests that women need to adopt a strategic, long-term perspective in their networking endeavors, prioritize follow-ups to build strong relationships, delineate tangible goals for professional advancement, and engage in ongoing evaluation and improvement of these initiatives. As a result, women can gain a sense of empowerment and find their voices to collectively combat gender inequality head-on.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;“Ableist Assumptions” Hinder Efforts to Help Workers with Disabilities&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Let us explore another compelling example: benevolent ableism, which refers to well-intentioned but problematic behaviors such as pity, protectiveness, and patronization toward employees with disabilities. Managers, guided by ableist assumptions, often impose their own definitions of disability, attempting to create “inclusive” environments that reinforce ableist norms in organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2020.1689&quot;>;longitudinal study&lt;/a>; of sheltered workshops, published in the Academy of Management Journal, disabled workers report that many inclusion initiatives at work are based on power imbalances rooted in pity. Sheltered workshops provide employment to disabled workers in segregated facilities with limited exposure to the broader public under the guise of care and protection. We show that well-intentioned managers often devise inclusion initiatives based on simplified assumptions that all workers with disabilities share identical needs of help and assistance — a paternalistic or even infantilizing approach that perpetuates inequality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, a transformational moment may occur when these managers confront their own fallibility, let go of their defensive positions, abandon their patronizing behaviors, and provide opportunities to people with disabilities to bring out their untapped potential. This requires a change in communication from telling to listening and a change in behavior to promote inclusive practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One example of a patronizing initiative in this context involved assigning jobs that could be carried out within the confines of the sheltered workshop, limiting public engagement. These jobs encompassed metal processing, industrial assembly, packaging, and shipping. In contrast, a successful inclusive practice involved establishing a farmer&#39;s market in consultation with these workers and their representatives. Engaging directly with people from outside the sheltered workshop environment while selling farm produce gave these workers newfound self-belief, autonomy, and a sense of empowerment. This experience was a moment of epiphany that boosted workers&#39; confidence in their abilities to perform tasks they had never envisioned or been given the responsibility to perform. Managers also realized that they had unwittingly stifled the potential of some of these workers while trying to be protective and creating a secluded environment. This shift marked a profound turning point as managers transitioned from guardians to true allies of workers with disabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Three Key Strategies to Tackle Benevolent Marginalization at Work&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In creating inclusive workplaces, managers need to invest time and resources in understanding and dismantling benevolent marginalization to ensure that equality in organizations becomes more than just a buzzword.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After studying this phenomenon across diverse settings, we present three key insights that serve as tools for managers aiming to go beyond good intentions:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Shift your perspective from help to empowerment.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In the pursuit of creating inclusive workplaces, the traditional approach of providing help can unintentionally reinforce unequal power dynamics. Managers must view disadvantaged individuals as equal colleagues. However, this is often easier said than done. Our findings reveal that practitioners may resist change, seeking to preserve deeply entrenched structures and the benefits they bring.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, managers need to call out and confront such resistance to pave the way to a profound shift from protectionism toward self-determination and empowerment. This requires introspection that can prompt managers to scrutinize and challenge their own paternalistic assumptions and biases. Managers must recognize and address the often-hidden power dynamics at play when interacting with people with whom they have a significant power differential. Building trust, actively listening, and gaining awareness of the emotions behind their behaviors are crucial steps. Seeking candid feedback from colleagues, mentors, or coaches about one&#39;s paternalistic behaviors is vital for self-reflection, sensitization, and remediation. Lastly, it is important to display empathy toward marginalized perspectives, even when they differ from one&#39;s own, and refrain from making decisions on their behalf, regardless of good intentions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Harness allies in non-managerial roles.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effectively addressing benevolent marginalization across an organization means tailoring initiatives that align with the unique interests of disadvantaged individuals. However, doing so requires the help of others beyond managers or designated diversity officers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is critical to leverage the power of intermediaries, such as support staff, close&amp;nbsp;colleagues, and friends, who are closer to the experiences and challenges faced by their marginalized peers. Identifying and designating these allies involves seeking out individuals who&amp;nbsp;are known to have actively supported marginalized communities. One way to select these allies is by letting marginalized groups participate in anonymous voting. This allows them to choose and elect individuals they trust and believe in as champions of inclusion based on their proven dedication and commitment. For example, at the sheltered workshop, workers with disabilities were given the opportunity to vote for their allies, who subsequently collaborated with management to improve inclusion initiatives. This approach is also seen in academia, where committees are frequently selected through voting to represent the interests of junior or disadvantaged faculty members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Organizations also need to recognize and reward allies who actively contribute to creating an inclusive environment. Managers can implement allyship programs or resource groups that offer tailored training and toolkits for allies, equipping them with the necessary skills to support marginalized peers. This comprehensive guidance should address issues such as identifying invisible bias, uncovering instances of benevolent marginalization, and actively advocating for and amplifying the voices of marginalized peers in their day-to-day interactions and decision-making processes. More generally, organizations can establish confidential feedback channels or suggestion boxes where support staff and colleagues can provide input on potential improvements to policies and practices to avoid paternalistic behaviors. By regularly reviewing and taking action based on this feedback, organizations demonstrate their commitment to “walk the talk” on inclusivity.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Create supportive spaces by handing over responsibilities to disadvantaged individuals.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Overcoming benevolent marginalization requires the creation of both formal and informal supportive or “safe” spaces in the workplace where marginalized groups can freely express themselves and expose behaviors they perceive as paternalistic or patronizing. However, it is not enough to unite marginalized employees in, say, an employee resource group (ERG) and expect them to form an empowering collective without further support. True inclusion demands a recognition of the diverse experiences and unique needs of&amp;nbsp;everyone within these spaces, and these individuals must have the choice to shape these spaces themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations must relinquish control and hand over the reins to disadvantaged individuals to shape their own professional lives. By doing so, organizations can become confidence-building, encouraging, and inspiring environments to challenge the status quo and overcome existing paternalistic norms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Building effective diversity programs can be a challenging endeavor, especially when hidden barriers hinder progress despite the best intentions. While by no means exhaustive, these three evidence-based strategies offer a solid starting point for advancing true inclusion. Shifting perspectives from help to empowerment, identifying hidden allies, and handing over responsibilities to create supportive spaces are crucial steps toward giving a platform to those who have long felt silenced or not listened to and creating a workplace where everyone feels heard and valued.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Let the Urgency of Your Customers&rsquo; Needs Guide Your Sales Strategy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Adrià Voltà&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When companies are creating profiles of possible target customers, there is a dimension they often overlook: the urgency of the need for the offering. This article provides a process for segmenting prospective customers in this fashion and creating a sales strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Many business leaders believe that they fully understand their best target customers. They&#39;ve developed clear profiles (aka personas) that are richly detailed with well-researched parameters, such as standard characteristics (eg, age, education level, years at the company, role) or firmographic (eg, annual revenues, number of employees, industry, geography, years in business). While such characteristics are important, they ignore another crucial characteristic: urgency of need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A company that offers a software-as-a-service billing solution for small and mid-sized private dental practices may focus on classic demographics, such as the size of the practice (number of employees or number of dentists), the age of the practice (since older practices may more likely have outdated systems), or the amount of insurance billing the practice does each year.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These variables are useful in helping to produce a list of prospects, but they don&#39;t determine which of these dental practices the sales team should call on first. If, however, the company added data that reflects which of these practices&#39; needs is most urgent — say, those that have advertised for billing and claims administration help more than twice in the past year (suggesting that they are struggling to keep up with billing) — salespeople would be able to prioritize their attention on these prospects.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Four Segments&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This needs-based approach entails segmenting potential customers into four segments:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Urgent&lt;/strong>;. The customer recognizes that it has an immediate need. &lt;em>;(We just had another billing person quit!)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Non-urgent.&lt;/strong>; The customer recognizes the need, but it isn&#39;t a high priority at this time. &lt;em>;(We realize that our billing needs are changing and our current system will need to be revamped. We plan to start looking into this in the next year.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Currently met&lt;/strong>;. The customer believes it already has an adequate solution to address the need at this time but recognizes it may not be a long-term solution. &lt;em>;(We have an older billing system in place that still does the trick for now.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;None&lt;/strong>;. The customer simply has no need nor expects such need anytime soon. &lt;em>;(Our small practice has a limited number of patients who pay out of pocket. Since all payments are made at the time of service, we simply don&#39;t need a complex new billing system.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;This focus on the urgency of target customers&#39; needs may sound like common sense, but we have found in our work with B2B companies — from mid-sized firms to Fortune 50 giants in an array of industries such as financial services, enterprise information technology, utilities, industrial solutions, and health care technology — that they often fail to consider this dimension. Here is a process a firm can employ to apply this approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Identify new customers.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To identify prospects outside of your existing customer base, you can use available information. One is a source we mentioned: help-wanted ads that reflect a particular need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there are plenty of others. For instance, if a company sells inventory management solutions, a source of valuable data might be manufacturing industry merger-and-acquisition data, which could reveal companies with an urgent need to change or merge systems such as those for managing inventories. If a company sells quality-management solutions, a source of valuable data could be companies that are getting hammered for poor quality on social media.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gather the necessary information.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Identifying your customers&#39; true urgency of needs requires looking beyond your typical demographic and firmographic profiling. This starts with an outreach initiative to talk to customers and prospects. The purpose is to ask questions to identify new target customer parameters that may be impacting the customer&#39;s urgency of needs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Frustrations. &lt;/strong>;How urgent is the need to resolve these frustrations? Which frustration would best accelerate success if resolved?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Goals. &lt;/strong>;Are your goals clear, consistent, reasonable, and measurable? Have your goals shifted recently?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Roadblocks. &lt;/strong>;What keeps you from reaching your goals? (ie, What keeps you up at night?) What is the magnitude of the impact of these roadblocks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Environmental and situational factors. &lt;/strong>;Are you experiencing any industry consolidation, organizational or executive management changes or instability, competitive changes, regulatory changes, and so on? What is the magnitude of the impact of these factors?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Technology factors. &lt;/strong>;Are there new or changing technologies that will impact your ability to achieve your goals? Are you at risk due to technology end-of-life issues or incompatibility?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assess your firm&#39;s ability to serve lower-level segments.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once a company has performed its needs-based segmentation effort, it should seek to answer the following questions about each of the four levels. The findings will dictate the sales and marketing strategy, level of investment and resource allocations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 1. Urgent need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;How quickly can we meet their need? How can we best serve them? Is the market opportunity large enough to focus only on these prospective customers? Given the customer&#39;s urgency, how do we price our products to optimize margins without damaging relationships by appearing exploitive?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 2. Non-urgent need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Can we convince them that their need is more urgent than they currently believe? How do we effectively stay in touch with them so we remain top of mind when they perceive that their need has become urgent?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 3. Need currently met&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Should we walk away from these prospects? If so, when and how do we touch base with them to see if their needs have changed? Or is there an opportunity to continue to work to convince them that their need is either more significant than they realize or could be much better addressed? If so, what&#39;s the best approach to get them to reconsider their current situation and recognize their true need and its urgency?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 4. No need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Should we completely remove these contacts as any potential prospect? Is there some other need we may be able to address for them — perhaps with another product? Should we be in contact on a planned basis to see if their situation has changed? How do we best do that?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The ideal customers are those who clearly understand and recognize they have an urgent need for your offering. However, if that opportunity is not enough to meet the company&#39;s sales volume target, it may be necessary to extend efforts beyond Level 1. Gaining the attention of these additional target customers, challenging their perceptions of their needs, and educating them on how your offering could benefit them will require resources. Consequently, a critical assessment is required to determine whether the opportunity outweighs the investment necessary to address customers in these other levels.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Test your new targets.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Before committing to a complete revamp of how your salespeople are prioritizing opportunities, select one or two experienced salespeople to help you test your new target customer parameters. Identify a few prospects that align to your revamped target profiles, and see how the selected salespeople are able to penetrate them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Revamp your sales messaging and training.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Include prospective customers&#39; level of need in your sales messaging — the language that the sales team uses in its interactions with customers. Revamp your sales tools (materials such as brochures, technical papers, and customer testimonials used in the selling process) to include the urgency of need. And teach salespeople how to read and react to the prospective customer&#39;s level of need and adapt their language appropriately.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By adding urgency of need to target customers&#39; profiles, companies can do more than differentiate their offerings more effectively. They can also identify new growth opportunities and successfully pivot away from slowing or tightening markets. They can accelerate the sales of new products. Last but not least, they can turn underachieving sales teams into strong performers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>