<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Where Should Your Company Start with GenAI?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/where-should-your-company-start-with-genai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_09_AlexWilliam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;亚历克斯·威廉的插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司正在努力思考从何处开始使用生成式人工智能。作者的观点是：案例研究基于由 3,000 多名 GenAI 从业者组成的不断增长的全球社区，指出了一种新的工作类别，比“知识工作”更精确、更可操作。他们称之为“WINS Work”任务、职能、可能是整个公司或行业的场所——依赖于对文字、图像、数字和声音 (WINS) 的操作和解释。该框架可以帮助领导者识别他们的业务对新技术变化的脆弱程度，并规划他们的应对措施。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/09/where-should-your-company-start-with-genai?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/where-should- your-company-start-with-genai?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;为了更好地理解生成式人工智能 (GenAI)，请通过双焦点镜片来观察它。通过顶层视角，人们可以看到一些迫在眉睫的重大问题的长远视角，例如准确性、隐私和偏见，以及 GenAI 对“知识工作者”甚至整个经济的潜在影响 &lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/generative-ai-could-raise-global-gdp-by-7-percent.html&quot;>;失业&lt;/a>;和社会&lt;a href=&quot;https://www. pwc.com/us/en/tech-effect/ai-analytics/managing-generative-ai-risks.html#:~:text=And%20not%20thoroughly%20reviewing%20your,with%20customers%20and%20reputational%20damage .&quot;>;风险&lt;/a>;。虽然这一观点很重要，但我们一遍又一遍地听说，它对高管和董事会成员没有帮助，因为很难将数以百万计的就业机会将受到影响的一般见解转化为这对他们今天的企业意味着什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是为什么我们还建议通过底部镜头查看 GenAI，并观察正前方的情况。在这里，领导者可以发现企业当今面临的来自 GenAI 的直接机遇和威胁。然而，在采取这种观点时，领导者可能还需要调整他们的目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的案例研究基于由 3,000 多名 GenAI 从业者组成的不断壮大的全球社区，指出了一种新的工作类别，比“知识工作”更精确、更可操作。我们将其称为 WINS 工作：任务、职能甚至整个公司或行业都依赖于文字、图像、数字和声音 (WINS) 的操作和解释的地方。心脏外科医生和厨师是知识工作者，但不是 WINS 工作者。软件程序员、会计师和营销专业人员都是 WINS 工作人员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;GenAI 有潜力成为 WINS 工作的强大工具。它可以生成新的散文、计算机代码、图像、旁白、音乐和视频，以及摄取和总结、批评、改进和重新格式化几乎任何方式的文档或分析。您的企业（在许多情况下是整个企业）内的每个 WINS 任务、子流程和端到端流程都应评估 GenAI 的潜在影响力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;我的公司付款有多紧急关注 GenAI？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们相信公司最简单的方法是问自己两个简单的问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;我们的成本基础中有多少是由 WINS 工作组成的?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如今 WINS 输入的数字化程度如何？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-363806&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images /article_assets/2023/08/W230905_BAIER_WINS_WORK_AI_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener &quot;>;在数据与图表中查看更多 HBR 图表视觉效果 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;将您的公司绘制在 2×2 矩阵上，问问自己它落在哪里。通过查看公司整体成本基础，然后按职能，并估计 WINS 工作的百分比，可以完成顶层分类。例如，软件开发、客户服务、营销和研发只是WINS工作水平较高的四个领域。下面详细介绍了每个竞争地位。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;严酷考验&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;WINS 工作成本比例较高且高度数字化的行业处于“严酷考验”，必须了解并立即拥抱 GenAI。软件、娱乐、专业服务、金融服务、教育等都在严峻考验中，因为迅速采用 GenAI 的竞争对手将变得更好、更快、更便宜。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;GenAI 的工具提供了新的、创造性的答案以及从简历到营销等各种内容的表达方式。可以把它想象成肖像摄影中的摄影力量。虽然肖像画以前只有富人才能使用——这是一种由训练有素的工匠慢慢创作的艺术品——但摄影从根本上扩大了市场，改变了肖像画的整个概念（想想自拍）及其经济学。在伟大的天才手中，摄影成为一种新的艺术形式。同样，软件开发、剧本写作、电影制作、报税、会计等都可能面临巨大的成本压力——并且最终将经历大规模转型。这些活动可能会也可能不会完全自动化，但正如您今天永远不会雇用不使用 Excel 的会计师一样，拥有 GenAI 功能可能会成为许多任务的赌注。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;握住杠杆&lt; /h2>; &lt;p>;“掌握杠杆”的公司能够在成本、时间和质量方面获得优势，即使他们的成本基础并未严重偏向 WINS 工作，并且他们的客户端产品或可交付成果也不是 WINS也没有数字化。例如，Moderna 最近&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.modernatx.com/media-center/all-media/blogs/moderna-launches-ai-academy-all-employees&quot;>;要求&lt;/a>;所有员工接受 GenAI 工具培训。他们相信，尽管他们的产品是分子或治疗干预措施，但这是提高 WINS 员工生产力的基本技能。在我们的 GenAI 学习社区中，我们发现 GenAI 在响应 RFP 时非常适合支持投标准备。销售速度对于所有人来说都是一个关键的绩效变量，即使是那些 WINS 员工很少的公司也是如此。许多 SG&amp;A 职能、研发的关键方面，甚至整个端到端产品开发和供应职能都可以利用 GenAI。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;下一个产品&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;品类我们框架中的“下一个队列”可能会提供一个机会，将当今尚未数字化的任务进行数字化以创造机会。例如，许多领先的家居装饰公司正在投资他们所谓的“数字前门”，使客户能够参与识别和购买过程。 GenAI 将实现新的定制水平，帮助客户采取行动，以更加现实和富有想象力的方式设想家居装饰，从而为那些处于领先地位的公司带来更好的体验、更大的客户吸收率和更少的回报。&lt;/p >; &lt;h2>;在阳台上&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;对于“在阳台上”的公司，我们认为低数字化和有限的 WINS 工作是当今价值创造过程的特征。这些行业通常拥有大量低技能劳动力，或者当涉及高技能时，技能的本质更多地在于创造实物产品或服务。图 2 给出了四个象限中每个象限的行业样本。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-363807&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08 /W230905_BAIER_WINS_WORK_AI_INDUSTRIES_360.png&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看更多 HBR 图表在数据与视觉 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;与需要数年时间才能看到回报的大量资本支出和技术支出不同，GenAI 即使在早期阶段，通常可以在采用当年就增加 EBITDA，因为近期生产力的提升非常引人注目。随着时间的推移，这些举措可能会产生战略投资机会，以创建防御性资产或竞争性护城河。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;法律和风险问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;使用这些工具时，至关重要对重要和高风险的决策进行人工审查。今天的 GenAI 模型有时会产生“幻觉”并给出错误的答案。因此，目前，员工应该使用它来增强（而不是完全自动化）高风险任务。随着时间的推移，创新者将找到改进和增强核心模型的方法，以提高准确性。此外，如果您使用的是 ChatGPT 等开放访问模型之一，请制定明确的政策，规定何时允许数据和查询成为其知识库的一部分以及何时将其保密。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;从哪里开始&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了推动您的 GenAI 计划，我们建议采用以下方法：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;1.充分了解整套 GenAI 工具，这些工具可以推动公司和行业的生产力、变革和创新。这不是课堂练习。这更类似于游泳。您无法通过听讲座或观看视频来学习游泳。卷起袖子，潜入泳池，游上几圈。了解这些工具的工作原理以及它们的功能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2.董事会/首席执行官应任命一个跨职能团队，从任务、子流程和流程级别开始进行实际实验并报告进度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;3.让跨职能的业务/技术/财务团队检查您是否以及在哪里可以总结早期实验的经验教训。发现你“握住控制杆”的位置。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;4.对 WINS 类别和当前数字化的成本驱动因素进行战略审查，以评估广泛投资 GenAI 的紧迫性。查明您的公司是否处于“严峻考验”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;5.如果您发现自己处于“严峻考验”或“手握杠杆”，请制定一个与 6 至 24 个月的改进计划相关的测试和学习策略。我们相信，在您所在行业的竞争强度加剧之前，您还有多少时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;6.如果您是“下一个”，请明智地利用 GenAI，并开始将所有 WINS 工作数字化，以便您处于领先地位。您将成为下一个“严酷考验”的人，如果您不改变自己的行业，其他人就会改变。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;7.对于那些“在阳台上”的人，请继续学习。虽然事情对您来说不太紧迫，但 GenAI 工具的出现将使您的业务变得更轻松、更快捷，就像 Excel 和 Word 取代了计算器和打字机一样。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;通过双焦镜头观察 GenAI&lt;/h2>; &lt;p >;正如我们一开始所说的，我们提倡所有企业领导者都应该戴上 GenAI 双焦眼镜，不仅通过顶部镜片看远处，而且也许更紧迫和重要的是通过底部镜片看近处。从历史上看，一家颠覆性公司大约需要五到七年的时间才能改变行业模式。 Uber 2009 年成立五年后，纽约市出租车牌照价格在 2014 年达到约 1,000,000 美元的峰值。到 2017 年，其价值为 250,000 美元或更少，并持续下降。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;严重依赖 WINS 工作的公司需要立即采取行动，在 36 至 60 个月内抵御更激烈的竞争并克服颠覆性竞争对手。不要陷入高成本、陈旧流程、数据劣势、人才流失和昂贵资本的困境。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Makes a Great Corporate Purpose Statement]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/what-makes-a-great-corporate-purpose-statement]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_11_1437553268_175488496.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR 工作人员/Marina Demeshko/kentarcajuan/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption= &quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;精心设计的目的声明确实很重要。它不仅代表了组织的愿望，还向员工发出了公司代表什么的信号。这是真正嵌入和激活真实目的道路上至关重要的第一步。然而，由于缺乏关于他们应该追求的焦点、范围和表达形式的指导，领导者常常难以阐明适当且鼓舞人心的目的陈述。作者对世界各地领先组织的目的陈述进行了详细分析，并开发了一个诊断框架，领导者可以使用它来帮助制定适合其具体情况的最佳目的陈述。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/what-makes-a-great-corporate- Purpose-statement?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/09/what-makes-a-great-corporate- Purpose-statement?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;各行业的组织越来越需要他们的投资者、客户、员工和更广泛的利益相关者清晰地表达了企业宗旨。目的不是为了利润最大化；而是为了实现目标。这是组织存在的原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;目的陈述应清楚地解释组织将如何为人类、社会或环境目标做出贡献。它必须是可信的、真实的和鼓舞人心的。然而，我们看到许多目的陈述，在我们看来，这些目的陈述的范围从模糊（例如达美航空的“提升世界”）到宏伟（例如思科的“为所有人创造一个包容性的未来”）到平淡无奇（例如迪卡侬的“为所有人创造一个包容性的未来”）。对人们有用”）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;拥有一份精心设计的目的声明确实很重要。它不仅代表了组织的愿望，还向员工发出了公司代表什么的信号。这是真正嵌入和激活真实目的道路上至关重要的第一步。然而，由于缺乏关于他们应该追求的焦点、范围和表达形式的指导，领导者常常难以阐明适当且鼓舞人心的目的陈述。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们对 66 个目的进行了详细分析来自世界各地领先组织的声明。我们考虑了这些陈述是否表述清楚、与组织的核心活动密切相关，以及它们的可信程度。我们与高级领导和员工进行了交谈，并审查了最佳实践建议。基于这些对有效和无效的见解，我们开发了一个诊断框架，领导者可以使用它来帮助制定适合其具体情况的最佳目的声明。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;制定有意义的目的声明的框架&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;用于制定有意义的目的声明的框架&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; h2>; &lt;p>;我们的框架 SABRE 确定了目的陈述内容的四个维度（即目的意味着什么）和目的陈述的一个维度&lt;em>;表述&lt;/em>;（即如何声明本身的措辞）。领导者可以根据每个维度评估他们当前或拟议的目的声明。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;社会&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;任何目的声明的基础都是对具体的、紧迫的人类、社会或环境问题的明确提及(s) 组织寻求解决或缓解问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们经常看到目的陈述只是以非常笼统的方式提及这些问题，或更糟糕的是，根本没有提及它们。事实上，我们分析的 68% 的陈述属于后一类。我们还看到围绕绩效或利润愿望制定的目的声明。此类声明指向使命或目标，但不是目的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;飞利浦提供了明确的社会效益声明的一个很好的例子：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;在飞利浦，我们的目的是通过有意义的创新来改善人们的健康和福祉。我们的目标是到 2030 年每年改善 25 亿人的生活，其中包括服务欠缺社区的 4 亿人。作为一家技术公司，我们以及我们的品牌授权商始终怀着一个信念为人们进行创新：总有一种方法可以让生活变得更美好。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;对于那些努力阐明其公司产品和服务的人来说，服务促进社会或公共利益，将目的与公司的运营方式联系起来可能更现实。例如，食品零售商阿尔迪的宗旨是“通过公平和高效的方式为我们的客户提供价值和质量。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;真实&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;员工和外部利益相关者，包括客户和投资者会想知道他们是否可以相信您的目的陈述准确而诚实地反映了组织的真实目标，并且他们会在组织内部和周围寻找线索来指导他们的评估。例如，如果组织宣称的目的是改善健康，但仍继续销售烟草产品，利益相关者将得出结论，该目的未通过真实性测试。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;员工可能特别容易接受不真实的目的声明。当他们认为既定目标与组织生活的日常现实不匹配时，我们发现他们会感到失望，从而导致失去参与度，甚至可能决定退出。在定期员工调查中添加有关目的陈述的问题将有助于领导者发现其不足之处。当一家公司被揭露在其目的声明中歪曲自己时，客户和投资者同样不为所动，从而引发&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kcl.ac.uk/business/assets/research/literature-review- Purpose-washing.pdf&quot;>;对目的清洗的指控&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;贝莱德的目的声明给人真实的感觉，因为它植根于公司的业务和运营方式：“作为一家全球投资管理公司贝莱德的宗旨是帮助每个人体验财务福祉，并受托于我们的客户。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，真实性并不是固定的 — 某一天看似真实的目的可能会在下一个负面影响时变得不真实。宣传。例如，大众汽车公司此前曾表示公司致力于提供可持续汽车，创造更美好的未来，但在 2015 年被曝光&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nrdc.org /stories/what-greenwashing&quot;>;篡改排放测试&lt;/a>;，导致“柴油门”丑闻、巨额罚款以及世界各地信任度的降低。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;可信&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;有些目的陈述过于宏大，以至于无法实现。不幸的是，正是因为这个原因，我们分析的许多陈述都未能通过可信度测试。诸如“改善世界”之类的模糊愿望可能值得称赞，但利益相关者会问：如何做？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最好的陈述清楚地表明组织可以现实地部署其资源并衡量其实现目标的进度。例如，阿斯利康 (Astra Zeneca) 的声明“我们突破科学界限，提供改变生活的药物”，显示了可信度维度上的实力，因为很容易想象一家制药公司正在开发重要的新药。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;相关受益人&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;最有效的目的陈述明确表明社会和环境的哪些部分将受益。不幸的是，有些声明根本没有提及任何具体受益人，因此仍然很抽象。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，玛氏的声明“我们明天想要的世界始于我们今天如何做生意”，未能澄清谁是受益者尤其将受益于该公司的产品。另一方面，Apple 的宗旨声明使预期受益者（其客户）更加明确：“通过创新的硬件、软件和服务为客户带来最佳的用户体验。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;参与&lt;/h3 >; &lt;p>;SABER 的最后一个部分解决了声明的措辞方式。最好的目的陈述是有吸引力的、鼓舞人心的，既能吸引心灵，也能吸引思想。出于各种正当理由，它们令人难忘。当陈述太长时，它们就会变得不清楚并且失去对人们注意力的控制。当然，您可能想要更详细地解释目的的含义，但标题声明必须有力。考虑一下通用磨坊公司简短而引人入胜的宗旨声明：“制造世界喜爱的食品。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;将其放在一起&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们相信一个组织可以制定满足所有这些标准的声明。以诺和诺德为例：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我们的目的是推动变革，战胜糖尿病和其他严重的慢性疾病，例如肥胖、罕见血液和内分泌疾病。我们通过开拓科学突破、扩大药物获取范围以及努力预防和最终治愈糖尿病来实现这一目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;诺和诺德明确阐述了他们要解决的社会问题。该声明与该组织的核心目标一致，我们可以看到该公司如何部署资源来实现这些目标。受益人已被命名，声明简洁且富有抱负。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过使用 SABRE 框架指导目的声明讨论，领导者可以朝着实现鼓舞人心、真实、可操作的目的迈进，该目的将向内部和外部明确说明。外部利益相关者将如何帮助解决当今的根本挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Think Strategically About a Career Transition]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a-career-transition]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6336768663112&quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;加载中... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption= &quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;职业转型是艰难的。我们中的许多人很难想象一个与我们现有的角色截然不同的新角色。而一旦行动起来，就很难顺利进行。 Herminia Ibarra 随时为您提供帮助。这位伦敦商学院教授开始意识到职业变动是多么具有挑战性，并且她对如何提高成功率有一些想法。伊瓦拉是我们哈佛商业评论《工作新世界》一集的嘉宾。她是古巴人，在耶鲁大学获得硕士和博士学位。在担任伦敦商学院组织行为学教授之前，她曾是哈佛商学院和欧洲工商管理学院 (INSEAD) 的教员。谈话的重点是职业转型，她认为，当人们对他们是有策略的。还讨论了：网络和她对“真实性”的有些争议的看法。在工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a -career-transition?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a-career-transition?language=pt&quot; >;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;对于我们大多数人来说，重塑我们的职业生涯和我们自己是一项极其艰巨的任务。正如伦敦商学院教授 Herminia Ibarra 指出的那样，您可能知道您不想再做什么，但不确定下一步您实际上想要做什么。她说，人们“当他们不确切知道自己在搜索什么时，就不知道如何搜索”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;比试图找出下一步职业更重要的是更广泛地思考关于你可能的自我，然后同时探索其中几个可能的自我。这就是拥有多元化网络有很大帮助的地方。虽然我们大多数人讨厌社交，但伊瓦拉也提供了如何在这方面做得更好的建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的视频系列“工作新世界”的这一集中，《哈佛商业评论》主编 Adi Ignatius 坐下来与多产作家、职业转型专家 Ibarra 一起讨论：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;如何顺利、成功地从一种职业过渡到另一种职业&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;在工作场所保持真实，不限制自己的成长和发展&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;如何突破孤立的网络，真正与那些能够为您带来新机会的人建立联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ibarra 的两本书将于下个月推出更新版本：&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.amazon.com/Working-Identity-Updated-Preface-Unconventional-ebook/dp/B0BTMQ97ZG/&quot;>;工作身份：重塑职业生涯的非常规策略&lt;/a>; &lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;&lt;a href =&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Leader-Updated-Global-Bestseller-Preface-ebook/dp/B0BTMQN19H/&quot;>;像领导者一样行动，像领导者一样思考&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;。&lt;/ p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;赫米尼亚，欢迎。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight =&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作新世界&quot; dek=&quot;前几集&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt; a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The新工作世界&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 前几集 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA： &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;非常感谢。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想谈谈很多关于职业转变的事情，但我想先介绍一下背景，我知道你的观点是，这是一个职业不断重塑的时代。您认为为什么会这样？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我研究职业重塑已有 20 多年了。第一版&lt;em>;工作身份&lt;/em>;已经是 20 年前的事了，而且这一趋势还在不断加速。如果说有什么不同的话，那就是我们正在重塑自己，并进一步重塑我们的职业生涯。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有四件事促成了这一点。我们的寿命越来越长，随着我们寿命的延长，我们不想从 40 岁开始一直滑下去，因为我们很容易再工作 40 年。我们希望充分利用它。这是一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;二是技术。我不必对此多说，但它正在改变一切。它正在扰乱工作。它正在创造新的就业机会。它使我们能够在任何地方工作。它为能够重塑自己创造了一个非常有趣的环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三个是我们的公司、组织、我们的工作场所：它们也不断受到干扰。这创造了机遇，但也带来了挑战。例如，我们最近在科技界看到了大规模的裁员浪潮。现在，金融行业的人们正在努力应对高利率以及这对他们的产品意味着什么，这样的例子不胜枚举。我们不再像以前那样长时间呆在工作岗位上，无论是出于选择还是被迫，因为我们被要求离开工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第四个趋势，这个趋势已经持续了很长时间，我们对工作的期望发生了很大变化。它曾经提供稳定的生活。 [现在]我们想要从工作中得到一切。我们想要激情，我们想要目标。我们想要自我实现。我们想要灵活性。我们对他们的要求太多，而且越来越不耐烦，如果得不到这些东西，我们就想继续前进。&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;The New World of Work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href=&quot;/ resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 订阅我们的每周通讯 &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; 工作新世界 &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 关于人才、技术和商业未来的坦诚对话。为订阅者准备的特别电子邮件系列。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>;签名向上&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 感谢您注册，&lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>; &lt;/span>;！ &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 您可以查看我们的&lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;其他新闻通讯&lt;/a>;或通过管理您的&lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;随时选择退出电子邮件首选项&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果职业重塑，如果重塑的需求是当代商业世界的一个标准方面，为什么我们在尝试实现它时遇到这么多麻烦？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是我学到的一件事，这真的很难。这真的很难，比人们想象的要花更长的时间。有几件事。一是大多数人知道他们不想再做什么，但他们并不确切知道他们想做什么。因为他们没有答案，我会回过头来讨论这个问题，所以他们不知道该怎么办。当他们不确切知道自己在搜索什么时，他们就不知道如何搜索。这就是其中之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个是，我们所做的就是我们是谁。这是一种非常重要的感觉，它是我们身份的一部分。即使失去一份我们不喜欢的工作也是一个巨大的损失，因为这是我们所做的事情，这是与我们共度时光的人，这是我们的时间的结构。我们已经做到了这一点。我们对此进行了投资。心理失落感是一个很大的障碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后一点是，特别是从职业生涯中期开始，当我们改变职业时，我们就会转向不同的领域。它不是线性的，在更高层次上更加相似。这是不同的东西。我将这些转变称为制度化不足。我的意思是步骤不明确，你不知道需要多长时间。你没有和其他人步调一致地做这件事。目前还不清楚谁是榜样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你想成为律师事务所的合伙人，你就知道步骤是什么。这可能很困难，但您知道步骤是什么和时间表。如果你是一名律师，想成为一名艺术企业家，那么这还没有制度化。没有什么特别的教育项目可供您参加。不同的人以不同的方式进入这个领域。目前还不清楚。这更加未知。目前还不清楚如何解决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所以我想回到你谈到的第一点，那就是我们我们不太擅长弄清楚我们的可能性是什么。我认同这一点。我做过的大部分工作，都会有人来找我说，你愿意做 X 吗？ And even when it&#39;s a career shift, it&#39;s like, I didn&#39;t think of it, somebody else did. It&#39;s worked out fine, I love my job. But there&#39;s a lack of agency that I think a lot of people feel in terms of getting control what I want to do with my work life, with my career. Is there advice on how to think clearly about possible next steps?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;ve got loads of it. One of the things is, we&#39;ve got to get away from thinking that if you don&#39;t know the answer, if you don&#39;t know the goal or the target career, you should just wait and reflect until you&#39;ve figured it out in your head. That&#39;s actually not how we figure it out.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s great when people come to you with propositions. It can be dangerous too because sometimes those things are too close to what you were doing already. And if you do want to make a change, they may not be the best fit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much more important than trying to figure it out is to experiment. And instead of thinking, “What&#39;s the one ideal job for me?”, [ask], “What might be 10, or what might be six organizations, or what might be five different pathways I could take?” And start exploring them in parallel, simultaneously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You learn as you go along. Sometimes the things you thought you wanted don&#39;t pan out to be. Or you dream them to be, for example. Sometimes it&#39;s harder and it takes longer. You&#39;ve got to do something else in parallel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first clear bit of advice and way of doing this successfully is to come up with a list of possibilities. I call them your possible selves. And start exploring one, two, ideally more than one, in parallel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I had a conversation with a headhunter at one point, and they were asking me about my job. I told them it ticks all my boxes. I feel good about it. I feel like I&#39;m doing something important. And I said, “Everyone feels that, right?” And the person said nobody feels that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re in a situation like that, you&#39;re very lucky. I&#39;m interested about the extent to which people feel satisfied in their work. How much satisfaction can we expect from our work? It&#39;s work and it&#39;s not necessarily our life, although it&#39;s a part of it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From your experience and research, how many of us feel generally satisfied in our jobs? Is it the norm or do we have to accept something less?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The general surveys show a lot of dissatisfaction. That comes and goes, there&#39;s periods of that and there&#39;s sectors. It&#39;s important to think that a job is not monolithic. I love my job, it ticks all my boxes too, but there&#39;s parts of my job I really don&#39;t like, that feel like grunt work. There&#39;s parts I love, and every job is like that. It is a matter of proportion. It&#39;s by and large, are you mostly doing the things that you find fulfilling?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are lots of people out there who are not satisfied. They may have been, but over time, either they have changed or their organization has changed, or the people with whom they work have changed, and they&#39;re no longer happy about those elements. They don&#39;t feel as challenged. They don&#39;t like and respect the people they work with. They don&#39;t align with the organization&#39;s mission. All of those things create a dissatisfaction. And my sense, from talking to my students, from doing my research, is that there&#39;s a lot of people who are dissatisfied out there today.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I want to build on that with a question that&#39;s come in from Hassam in Rotterdam. How do you envision the evolution of the “employee experience” in a world increasingly dominated by hybrid work models?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I do not have a crystal ball.我不知道。 All I know is that organizations are still trying to figure it out. They&#39;re still playing with different ways and trying to understand the employee experience. But that&#39;s a question I can&#39;t answer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Alright, here&#39;s another question, this is from Ellie from Switzerland. How should we think about the balance? If you switch careers, you jeopardize some of the seniority you&#39;ve built up, and the benefits and positives that you&#39;ve accrued. How can we avoid that or how can we think about that trade off?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s another big question, am I going to have to start at the bottom? Or is there a way not to do that? It depends on what you go on to do next, right?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One person I&#39;ve been interviewing extensively over the last couple years was chief compliance officer at her organization, and she&#39;s become a documentary filmmaker. She had to start at the bottom, as an apprentice. It depends.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other people move into something that&#39;s more adjacent, maybe doing it more entrepreneurially. And they don&#39;t have to, they can really leverage the skillset and the experience that they&#39;ve had, albeit in a very different role and setting. It depends a lot.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;People try to solve this by going back to school, and that can help a lot by rounding you out. But what everyone forgets is that it&#39;s not always up and up. So you&#39;re seeing, “Okay, I&#39;m here. If I make a change, I&#39;m going to be here. Whereas I can continue moving up,” and that may well not be the case.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The world is changing, jobs are disappearing, and if you&#39;re not happy and productive in what you&#39;re doing, the curve could well be declining too, and you&#39;ve got to take that into account.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The other topic that seems to be on everyone&#39;s mind is AI. We&#39;re always wondering if technology will take our jobs. And sometimes it does. With generative AI, we&#39;re all asking about it with a heightened sense of concern.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Are you thinking about this, how this changes or accelerates everything you&#39;re thinking about?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re thinking about it as an institution at London Business School. I&#39;m trying to use it as much as I can. I&#39;m interested in how it&#39;s changing people&#39;s jobs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From my perspective, what I&#39;m interested in is how it&#39;s going to transform how people work together. Who does what? What organizations emerge? We don&#39;t know the answers to those questions. We know we need to be asking big questions about alignment with values. We know, from the whole wave of digital transformation, that there&#39;s the technological part, but then there&#39;s the whole other part, which is how it&#39;s used. Is the organization able to use it? Are people able to adapt and make the most of it? All of those things remain to be seen. But certainly, it is worth experimenting with, keeping an eye on it, studying, asking the good questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So here&#39;s a question related to technology. This is from Bhaskaran in Bangalore. Bhaskaran says that after working for 21 years in HR they decided to move to a smaller organization, expecting it to be nimble, agile and all that. It turned out to be highly toxic. Bhaskaran longs for a new role and organization, but has this constant fear of uncertainty. How does one deal with this inevitable fear of uncertainty when one is thinking about making a move?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Completely understandable. Unfortunately, often the process of making a career change can be one step forward, two steps back. Now you&#39;ve learned something, and I think part of what you&#39;ve learned is that you need to really research much more carefully the context you&#39;re going to, and get a flavor of them as much as you possibly can. Now you&#39;ve learned to inquire much more about culture, to talk to the people, to research the organization. All of that is really important.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s one of the reasons why, in studies I&#39;ve done, oftentimes the uncertainty of “I don&#39;t know what I want, I don&#39;t know how long this is going to take,” starts to get at people. And then all of a sudden an option comes up, an offer, with this smaller, more nimble firm, and it&#39;s the savior. So they take it, because otherwise they&#39;re still in the throes of “What am I going to do?”, without researching it as much as they might. Without really asking, “What matters to me?” It&#39;s really important to make time for that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In any case, you&#39;re out of there. And so, by necessity, you&#39;re going to deal with uncertainty, but maybe research a bit more carefully.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re talking about two things. One is how to think about a career transition moment, how to be proactive and smart about that. But then, alright, you&#39;ve made the move. How do you transition successfully into this new role?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;d love to hear you talk a little bit more about that. We&#39;ve made the move from Company A to Company B. How long should we give ourselves? How tough should we be on ourselves? Should we read &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/First-90-Days-Strategies-Expanded/dp/1422188612&quot;>;The First 90 Days&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;? How do we transition successfully?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The First 90 days remains the Bible on that topic. What he says to start with, which also goes to the previous question, is the first 90 days actually starts way before, with doing your homework and talking to people and finding out the stakeholders. There&#39;s this lovely idea about, I think it&#39;s the five conversations that you need to be able to have with your boss or whoever your key stakeholders are about what the expectations are about how you&#39;re going to be measured, about the key topics, so that you&#39;re going in recognizing the interdependence between your success and that of other people in the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s shift gears to talk about authenticity, another topic that you have researched and written a lot about. Most conversations that I have about leadership at some point evolve into a conversation about the need for total authenticity at work. My sense is you have a more complicated take on all this. How should leaders think about the authenticity question?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This total authenticity stuff drives me nuts. What is total authenticity? Is it to say whatever crosses your mind? Is it to dress how you might dress at home on a Sunday to go take a walk in the park?这意味着什么？ I think there&#39;s a lot of fluff in all of this. What&#39;s the definition of authenticity? Is it a trait? Is it an outcome, a process of learning about yourself and trying to be as much yourself as possible?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I don&#39;t think it&#39;s a trait. I think it is a process of learning. We want to be authentic. Nobody likes a fake. Nobody follows a fake. It&#39;s bad for your mental health. I&#39;m all for it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The question I ask is how can you define authenticity in a way that doesn&#39;t condemn you to being as you always have been? We grow, we evolve. We&#39;re multiple. We have different facets, different aspects of who we are that play out. And we need to be able to express that complexity and also ask, “What does it mean to be authentic when I&#39;m learning?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s great when it&#39;s habitual behavior. You know how to do that. But when you&#39;re learning, you haven&#39;t figured it out yet. People tend to confuse habitual behavior with authenticity. The minute they&#39;re out of the comfort zone, “Oh, that&#39;s not really me. I&#39;m not so authentic.” The comment usually is, “That&#39;s not me.” Well, it&#39;s not you now and you haven&#39;t tried it. And sometimes trying these things that help you to learn, they feel inauthentic. And if that&#39;s the price of learning, I think it&#39;s well worth paying it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;br>; When some people talk about being authentic at work, I think they want to be open about who they are, their personal life, maybe their sexual orientation. If they have a kooky sense of humor, they want to be able to bring that. On the one hand, absolutely, you need to learn new skills and soft skills and hard skills. But people feel they would derive a deep sense of happiness if they could be “authentic” at work in the ways that I was talking about.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For me, that&#39;s much more about a sense of belonging and being able to figure out, “Do I belong here or do I have to hide what&#39;s important about me in order to be effective here?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Back to bringing your whole self to work: workplace relationships are relationships. And in relationships, people get to know each other. And the minute that you meet somebody, you do not tell them everything about you, your personal life, professional life, strengths, doubts, anguishes, all this. You don&#39;t do that. You get to know people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s very important that we treat authenticity in that way. We&#39;re building relationships. And as we build relationships, we want to be able to disclose. Self-disclosure is what builds relationships. That&#39;s really important, but it&#39;s not about in every moment being able to broadcast everything about myself in a way that doesn&#39;t respect the building of relationships at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think some of it is generational. My generation tended not to broadcast everything. I think some of the subsequent generations are more comfortable with that, expect that, and are comfortable with that. And part of the intergenerational workplace dynamic is all of us being comfortable with that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The other thing about the complexity is that in the workplace we&#39;re also assessing each other for potential. Who&#39;s going to do well, who&#39;s going to advance? We talk a lot about authenticity in the context of being able to be vulnerable and to express vulnerability. But vulnerability doesn&#39;t get coded the same way when it&#39;s expressed by a man versus a woman, or assertiveness doesn&#39;t get coded the same way when it&#39;s expressed by a Black person versus a white person. All of these complexities come into play, which we really need to take into account because we each want to put our best foot forward and be able to accomplish our goals within the organizations where we work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What is the ideal profile of a leader in 2023? What are the skills or experience you think matter most?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You guys at HBR have been putting out the headlines on this, and there&#39;s a very common drumbeat, and it&#39;s been on for a while, which is about the importance of soft skills and people skills. We&#39;ve been talking about that for a long time. The pandemic accelerated that, and really all the complexity of leading today, because ultimately what we&#39;ve seen in a really deep way is that the problems organizations face, they&#39;re big problems. They&#39;re adaptive problems. That means there isn&#39;t a simple solution to them, and you need to harness everyone&#39;s energy and brains and hearts in order to solve them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You really have to be able to get people on board, get them to tell you what they think, get them to work outside their comfort zones, and all that requires a set of people skills that most managers today who are successful and who get to the top haven&#39;t necessarily developed because they have been rewarded for delivering results in any which way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Delivering results is still important. What ends up happening is as people get more senior and they start to look promising, they get a lot of nudges, which is, it&#39;s really time now to think about how to cultivate this other side, which has more to do with how you connect with people, how you bring out the best in them, how you create a context in which there is psychological safety. All of that has become much more important, not because it&#39;s nice to have, but because the requirements for learning in our organizations have become so much greater.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From your research, is your sense that many leaders have those skills or that very few do?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;ve got a couple different bases of knowledge on this. One is the executives that I teach. They&#39;ll all say, “I&#39;m great at getting accountability and driving results, and I&#39;m a bit of a micromanager and my coaching skills are not so great.” That&#39;s my most common profile. As you probably know, we worked on this with a couple of colleagues from Spencer Stuart, which led to an article last year, &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-leadership-odyssey&quot;>;“The Leadership Odyssey”&lt;/a>; in HBR, where we were able to use Spencer Stuart&#39;s recruitment data for the C-Suite.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The way we framed it is most of the executives in succession processes, candidates, had plenty of developmental opportunities when it came to these people skills. We ended up having a look at how it is that they come to recognize that it will really stand in the way of what they want to accomplish if they don&#39;t develop these skills and how they go about it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One topic I want to make sure we speak about is networking. Networking seems simple enough, but a lot of us struggle to even start to build effective and meaningful networks. Do you have thoughts on how to do this better?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A quick ad: &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive&quot;>;a brand new article on HBR yesterday on the challenges of networking as an executive&lt;/a>;. What is it that makes it particularly hard for senior people to network who have their own challenges?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Anyway, this topic is of endless fascination to me, Adi, because I started working on this in the 80s when I was doing my PhD research, and have been following it since.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The headline is most of us are bad at it. Most of us are bad at it. Some people are very good, but most of us are bad, and you can look to social psychology to explain a big share of the why. The big share of the why is that the way we are built, we are drawn to spontaneously build relationships with people who are like us and with whom we bump into on a regular basis because their office is next door.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The way I summarize it is the mechanisms are similarity and proximity. That&#39;s what builds our networks. We&#39;re narcissistic and lazy. We like people like us. It&#39;s easier to talk to them, and since we don&#39;t have a lot of time, we&#39;re going to get to know the people who are easy to get to know because they&#39;re next door.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That means our networks are insular. They&#39;re not good. They don&#39;t help us get new jobs. They don&#39;t help us step up to bigger roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;ve got to work on it, but working on it is really aversive too, and you&#39;ve published some great research on how that works. It makes us feel a little bit dirty, a little bit disingenuous, a little bit utilitarian, using people when we approach building relationships in a more strategic way. It gets in the way of our sense of meritocracy. It gets in the way of our sense of self-reliance, but we know from my research and that lots of other people are vital for getting jobs, changing careers, and being effective and innovative as a leader in the roles which you have already.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Any tips on how to build a network that isn&#39;t the person in the cubicle next to you?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The tips are all really simple. Make an effort, join a project, take a course, use an extracurricular activity, make referrals, connect to people, speak at events.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Don&#39;t do all of it all at the same time, but pick a few things. The thing is we don&#39;t make time for it because, just like in your example, you&#39;re waiting for stuff to come to you. These are things that you need to take the initiative on, but it&#39;s very easy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A great one is to just pick a few people you&#39;ve lost track of, connect to them, write to them, say, “Hey, I&#39;m thinking about this. It&#39;d be great to catch up with you and have a conversation about it. How about it?” Very easy to do. It&#39;s just that we don&#39;t.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I want to come back to one thing you talked about, which was constant learning, constant adaptation. I think a lot of us are trained to get that next job, and then we have it and we bring our old selves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I thought it was interesting that you&#39;re saying we need to continually evolve and that authenticity is an elastic concept in that sense.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;OK, we&#39;re in a role as a leader, middle manager, whatever. How do we adapt? How do we evolve? How do we not just get stuck in that routine that we bring from day one? How do we keep evolving?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s a life cycle to all of this. One thing I would say is you&#39;ve just started a new role. I wouldn&#39;t worry about reinventing yourself. You&#39;ve been hired for who you are. Exploit that and make sure to connect to the stakeholders and everything else, but you&#39;re not looking to reinvent yourself here. You&#39;re really looking to leverage everything that you bring to that role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What people forget is that expectations of you change quickly, and environments also change quickly. The danger point is really more like a year or two or three, depending on how fast-moving your situation is, when you think you&#39;ve got it covered, but people have stepped up in their expectations of you or the environment has changed a lot.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What becomes really important here, the main thing I say to people is, think about how you&#39;re defining your job, where you&#39;re spending your time, what you&#39;re allocating time to, and can you think of it more as a portfolio in which some slivers of your time you&#39;re going to spend learning new things, exploring new things, getting involved in projects that give you a more strategic view of the organization, something adjacent to what you normally do, but something that really allows you to keep expanding the frontier as opposed to settling into a comfort zone that&#39;s going to make you much more vulnerable to the what-got-you-here-won&#39;t-get-you-there phenomenon.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Working your network, people get comfortable. There&#39;s a set of usual suspects that you keep turning to, no fresh blood, and you become very insular in your views.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Herminia, we&#39;re out of time, but I want to really thank you for being on the show. It&#39;s great to see you again and great to connect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thank you so much, Adi.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:55:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Black Police Officers Combat Systemic Racism at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_25_73979724.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Darrin Klimek/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;If you&amp;#8217;re a member of an historically marginalized group, enacting change in an organization can be challenging. This is likely even more difficult if your organization is known for bias and even violence against your own group. This is the position many Black police officers are in, and researchers wanted to better understand the strategies they use to advocate for anti-racism despite the numerous roadblocks. This article looks at why Black police officers choose the job, how they challenge racism, and how they sustain their efforts. It also offers suggestions for employees in other fields can continue to fight for change in their own companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The 2014 shooting death of Black teenager &lt;a href=&quot;https://rfkhumanrights.org/michael-brown-case-urges-justice-reform&quot;>;Michael Brown&lt;/a>; by a white police officer in Ferguson, Missouri, was an early event that propelled the Black Lives Matter movement to national prominence and elevated discussions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/identities/2019/8/9/20798921/michael-brown-ferguson-uprising-police-violence-reform&quot;>;race and policing&lt;/a>; in the United States. In the summer of 2020, the murder of George Floyd sparked a racial reckoning &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2020/12/30/950053607/in-2020-protests-spread-across-the-globe-with-a-similar-message-black-lives-matt&quot;>;in the US and around the world&lt;/a>; that further magnified calls for police reform. Consequently, police departments around the country have begun to adopt anti-racist organizational policies, like offering &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/03/training-police-departments-to-be-less-biased&quot;>;diversity training&lt;/a>; and increasing recruitment of officers who are members of &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/simple-changes-to-job-ads-can-help-recruit-more-police-officers-of-color&quot;>;racial minority groups&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, relying solely on &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/06/are-your-organizations-dei-efforts-superficial-or-structural&quot;>;top-down strategies&lt;/a>; like these is not adequate to effectively combat systemic racism in policing. This is complicated by the fact that individuals from marginalized groups (for example, Black individuals or women) can &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1467-9221.2004.00402.x?casa_token=s9Iz78o8iXYAAAAA:8raiiLrqWip9SvhixeLcUgoMB_o2FMC6_qVx4GV_bFGYFPHKRGFtCqE7KzJsoudY6UFewQR_IGkPFUDC&quot;>;hold biases against members of their own group&lt;/a>; and may be socialized to &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1540-6210.2008.00905.x?casa_token=EfotWb6z5jEAAAAA:xC_ZxCBpnKSckZY2VRAEJc65udbL8AiZUeDAF9YjWKFdqIUf_LE1nGRsKHIOo8MjerFqJouVEk3Rlg&quot;>;reinforce systems of discrimination and inequity&lt;/a>; — a point which is particularly pertinent when considering the &lt;a href=&quot;https://abcnews.go.com/US/tyre-nichols-case-diversity-policing-address-police-brutality/story?id=96768457&quot;>;killing of Tyre Nichols&lt;/a>; that involved five Black officers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In light of this, our author team wanted to better understand the bottom-up strategies that officers may use to combat systemic racism. In particular, we were curious about the experiences of Black police officers who, instead of going with the status quo, actively seek to combat racism within policing. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2023-21994-001&quot;>;recent work&lt;/a>;, published in the Journal of Applied Psychology, aimed to deeply understand the anti-racism efforts of Black law enforcement officers who chose to be champions of reform within an institution that has a reputation for &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12111-013-9246-5&quot;>;perpetuating racism against Black communities&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our research draws on insights gleaned from 48 interviews with Black police officers who are at the fore of anti-racism. We learned why they joined &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/why-so-many-organizations-stay-white&quot;>;law enforcement&lt;/a>;, how they challenged racism as police officers, and how they sustained their anti-racism efforts in the face of continuous racial discrimination both within their organizations and society writ large. Based on our findings, we also outline guidelines for employees in other industries who are motivated to engage in such social change efforts. Although not reflective of the experiences or actions of all Black police officers, our study shows how their anti-racism efforts can foster lasting change for both police organizations and Black communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why do Black police officers join law enforcement?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When organizations or occupations are known for being an unwelcome — often dangerous — place to work for members of a marginalized group, it follows that members of these groups would attempt to avoid experiences of racism by choosing not to work in that organization or occupation. Yet, the officers in our study intentionally chose to join and fight racism within exactly these types of environments — why?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Officers explained that they chose to challenge racism from within policing because it is one of the most prominent societal institutions that continues to perpetuate race-based discrimination against Black individuals. Indeed, numerous officers in our study explained a direct connection between their first- or secondhand experiences of racism from police and their choice to enter law enforcement. As Chief Williams explained, “I made the decision to become a police officer because I was a victim of police brutality when I was 14 … [I told myself], &#39;I&#39;m going to try and stop those kinds of things from happening to anyone, regardless of who they were&#39; … I knew I had to do something to make a difference.” (All names of participants have been changed to protect their identities.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As this example shows, the direct or indirect encounters with racism in policing that would presumably deter Black individuals from joining police organizations actually motivated many of our participants to enter law enforcement, with the goal of driving change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do Black police officers challenge racism?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Fueled by the motivation to combat racism in policing from the inside out, officers leveraged their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpr.org/2020/10/02/black-and-latino-officers-bring-their-own-experiences-with-racism-to-the-job/&quot;>;unique position&lt;/a>; as members in both law enforcement and the Black community, simultaneously working to reduce racism in policing &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; remediate the effects of racism in the Black community. This dual approach enabled officers in our study to more holistically combat racism by tackling multiple facets of the system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Three combinations of organizational and community focused anti-racism strategies emerged in our data as especially impactful in policing.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Educating within and across police organizations and communities.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;First, we found that many Black officers believed racism in law enforcement could be attributed to white officers&#39; lack of knowledge about the Black community. As such, several officers in our study attempted to remedy this knowledge gap by sharing the cultural values and norms of Black communities with their white colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At times, these efforts were reactive — in response to racist incidents they witnessed or experienced themselves. For example, Sergeant Scott recalled witnessing a white colleague become defensive after misinterpreting the mannerisms of a Black community member as aggression. This was the impetus to educate his colleague about communication norms in the community and positively reshaped how the white colleague interacted with Black community members thereafter. Sergeant Scott explained, “Today if you talk to the Black families that he deals with, they love him. He&#39;s very empathetic … [The white officer told me] &#39;I wasn&#39;t always like this. I didn&#39;t understand. It took somebody else to explain it to me for me to understand.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At other times, efforts to educate white colleagues were proactive. For example, Lieutenant Allen initiated changes to the police academy curriculum, explaining, “I&#39;ve taken out 40 hours of things that were not necessary and added 40 hours of cultural diversity training … [because] we need to figure out how to communicate and connect with people that are different from us.” These examples speak to the importance of educating colleagues in police organizations — both proactively and reactively — about the Black community.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to educating white officers, participants in our study described how important it was to demystify law enforcement by sharing strategies and principles that underlie law enforcement policies and decisions with community members. Senior Police Officer Richardson made himself available to community members as a resource because “a lot of the people in the community do not know the laws [such as] traffic laws [or] penal codes.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Promoting and demonstrating respect for Black community members.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Across nearly every interview, officers emphasized the importance of promoting respect for Black individuals within law enforcement and in the Black community. For example, participants frequently described encountering racism in their day-to-day work. In these instances, holding white officers accountable for their racist behavior was critical. Officer Edwards overheard white officers disparaging the lifestyles of Black community members and reported it to his supervisor, saying, “I went to the lieutenant, my lieutenant went to their lieutenant. I brought it up like, &#39;They&#39;re over there talking about Black people,&#39;” and consequently, the group of white officers was reprimanded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regarding their interactions with Black community members, law enforcement officers in our study took extra care to demonstrate &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/do-your-employees-feel-respected&quot;>;respect&lt;/a>; through behaviors they viewed as humanizing and dignifying. They shared examples of showing the respect that they felt was owed to each community member. As Officer Miller said, “I feel like I can be nice and still arrest you … I don&#39;t have to be mean or treat you as less than a person to enforce the law.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Uplifting Black individuals in the police organization and the community.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Finally, the officers we spoke with often described how one of the most powerful and rewarding strategies to combat racism in their workplace was to support Black individuals at work — via recruiting, promoting, and mentoring other Black officers — and in the community by going above and beyond for Black community members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Officer Baker recognized that her Black junior colleagues were likely experiencing challenges during the George Floyd protests, such as being suddenly ostracized by white officers, that were unique to being a Black officer. She intentionally reached out to mentor them, saying, “I was able to be supportive … let them know that there is nothing wrong with them and that how they&#39;re being treated by our white partners … has nothing to do with us Black officers.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Within the Black community, officers often reported also going above and beyond in their service to support the community members. Officer Pierce told us that he stops to help citizens with flat tires whenever he can because this shapes community members&#39; perceptions of police: “Now that woman has a totally different attitude about police officers … she didn&#39;t really like police officers in light of everything that&#39;s been going on. I threw off her game because she wanted to hate us.” These efforts not only helped Black community members have a greater sense of trust in law enforcement, but also created a sense of reciprocity wherein these community members were willing to help officers do their jobs more effectively by, for example, sharing information that could help solve an investigation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In all, these efforts were especially effective in officers&#39; eyes because they performed two simultaneous and necessary functions: They moved toward fostering police officers&#39; respect for Black community members and toward repairing the Black community&#39;s trust in law enforcement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do Black police officers sustain their anti-racism efforts?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unsurprisingly, Black officers encountered significant roadblocks and backlash for their efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, by virtue of entering an organization that has a history of perpetuating racism, Black officers were likely to suffer through the negative consequences of racism while also working to combat it. Officers reported racial slurs from colleagues, getting left on the side of the road in dangerous weather by white officers, and being informally prohibited from sitting with the white officers at mealtimes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, officers described that by entering law enforcement, they experienced stigma from Black individuals given the institution&#39;s reputation for being deeply devastating to the Black community. For example, officers remembered being called a “traitor” or a “sellout” by Black community members because of their profession.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, officers experienced retaliation for their anti-racism efforts in both overt and subtle forms such as explicit acts of bullying — like having tires slashed — or career advancement opportunities that were inexplicably delayed. These challenges tended to be particularly pronounced in the wake of police-related &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/supporting-employees-after-violence-against-their-community&quot;>;mega-threats&lt;/a>; (negative events that are both related to an identity and command significant media attention, like the murder of George Floyd) that brought police brutality toward Black community members to the forefront of national attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The combination of being rejected at work &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;in the community was extremely troubling, with officers experiencing significant stress, isolation, and even suicidal thoughts. In fact, many endured periods of time when they seriously considered quitting. This raises the question: How did these employees persevere and continue combatting racism in law enforcement?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There were two key factors. The first, counterintuitively, was the very racism that was causing the stress. Officers explained how these experiences highlighted that their efforts were very much still needed. As Detective Coates explained, “I know that I&#39;m needed … I know that I can&#39;t change a lot of these people&#39;s minds, but I can change [some] through my actions.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The second factor was seeing glimpses of evidence that their anti-racism efforts were making a positive impact. For instance, Officer Pierce successfully advocated to recruit new officers from Historical Black Colleges and Universities (HBCUs); Chief Davis described receiving an apology email from a white officer who had said something offensive to him in the past; and Lieutenant Allen wrote an open letter to a racist officer and shared it within his department, causing the officer to resign. As Senior Police Officer King noted, “I stay motivated and encouraged seeing change being made for the better. I&#39;ll stay motivated and encouraged knowing the fact that a simple thank you, a simple gesture, a simple conversation is changing someone&#39;s life for the better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond the changes taking place in law enforcement, the officers also described instances of positive change in their communities. Senior Corporal Adams bought lunch for a Black citizen who was nervous interacting with a police officer, explaining, “It totally took his guard down … He was talking about fishing and hunting and all that stuff after that.” Detective Coates shared how citizens would share tips and information when they trusted that the information would be dealt with fairly. In a particularly poignant example, one officer responded to a call for a young Black woman experiencing a mental health crisis, and after he and his partner stayed in touch with her, she eventually invited them to her high school graduation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For these officers, combating racism drove their entry into law enforcement, shaped their choices each day, and led to glimpses of transformation that provided them with a better understanding of their impact — this played a critical role in sustaining the anti-racism motivation needed to continue this work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What can we learn from Black police officers?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Policing is, of course, different from other work settings in many ways, and not every experience or lesson will transfer. Yet, we believe that some of the strategies that motivate Black officers to engage in and sustain anti-racism efforts within policing can help other historically underrepresented employees and their allies fight for change in their own organizations. Although it is incumbent on organizations to address racism and other systemic issues at the policy level, we see three key ways that their strategies can be especially useful to those aiming to drive change in other work settings.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Clarify your “why.”&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The officers in our study had a clear purpose, which not only guided their choice of policing as an occupation, but sparked motivation during challenging periods. This clarity of purpose is likely to be similarly powerful across occupations for those passionate about driving social change, meaning that a sharp focus on such motivation — “Why is this meaningful to me personally? Why is this important for society more broadly?” — is a worthwhile starting point and a critical touchpoint as the work continues.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Leverage your unique set of identities.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Our research participants recognized how being both Black and a police officer uniquely positioned them to drive change in ways that others could not. Though at times contentious, their simultaneous membership in the Black community and the police organization prompted others&#39; receptivity to their actions. Having a footing in each of these worlds also enabled officers to address the problematic behavior and support those most impacted by it. Carefully considering one&#39;s unique position and access to stakeholders may similarly unlock effectiveness in other occupations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Anticipate setbacks and celebrate progress.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It was clear to officers that there are significant roadblocks to enacting change. They described sustaining their anti-racism by having a plan in place to navigate roadblocks, reframing mega-threats as indications that their work is greatly needed, and celebrating glimpses of the changes they were aiming to create. Anticipating the backlash and envisioning what small steps toward success will look like may similarly enable those driving for social change in any occupation to sustain engagement in the face of challenges and setbacks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In recalling his efforts to educate colleagues about the Black community, Deputy Chief Taylor described the moments that sustained his anti-racism motivation: “When you see the light go on, it&#39;s a wonderful thing because now it opens up [white officers&#39;] eyes to a whole other world out there that they didn&#39;t think previously existed.” The anti-racism strategies and challenges that emerged in our research highlight the day-to-day, often unrecognized anti-racism work that employees like Deputy Chief Taylor shoulder above and beyond the demands of their formal work roles. Importantly, our research shows that employees do not need to have discretion over policies or be in a formal leadership role to combat racism; they can make an impact through their anti-racist actions each day at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smaller Companies Must Embrace Risk Management]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_08_125412697.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Caroline Purser/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;SMEs do not have the same regulatory pressures that can lead larger companies to measure and mitigate their risks, but they also have fewer buffer resources to resist unexpected shocks. They are one large potential incident away from bankruptcy. That&amp;#8217;s why SMEs can benefit from taking three actions: designing controls proportionate to the risks at stake, analyzing the lessons from success (not only from failures), and using risk management to boost and protect business performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s an unfortunate stereotype that risk management is boring. Risk managers are pessimistic clerks. Compliance officers are scaremongers. Too many managers think this way. As a result, risk management is an unloved and misunderstood discipline. Until disaster strikes, risk management is, for most, a painstaking and costly chore.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In an increasingly volatile world, however, risk management has never been so important. Nonetheless, risk managers struggle to make their voice heard in the face of more immediate and commercial pressures. This is especially true in small- and medium-sized companies — organizations with entrepreneurial cultures, fewer regulatory demands, and more resource constraints. These businesses tend to view risk management as an expensive luxury — and they may be more exposed to risks as a result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This article presents a more enlightened approach to risk management based on two decades of applying, researching, and teaching risk management to academic and professional audiences. It will help managers — including those at SMEs — to better understand risks and apply effective, positive risk management techniques. It&#39;s a framework that relies on three actions: designing controls proportionate to the risks at stake, analyzing the lessons from success (not only from failures), and using risk management to boost and protect business performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management is proportionate &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Proportionality means that small risks require small fuss; big risks demand big focus. Daily risks are acceptable, such as: forgetting an email attachment, double paying a modest invoice, missing a deadline on an internal report. Errors and slips like these simply show how busy we are. They are understandable oversights in fast-moving enterprises, especially SMEs where teams are lean and resources scarce.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;Conversely, extreme risks deserve greater care: a phishing link starting a cyber-attack, the loss of key intellectual property in an innovative start-up, a bacterial infection in the water supply of a care home. Neglecting real dangers costs millions, heartaches, and lives — and that&#39;s when we regret not being more vigilant, more careful, more &lt;em>;boring&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet, organizations often miscalculate risks. Smaller incidents are the most frequent; they raise attention but do not matter. From a &lt;a href=&quot;https://orx.org/download/annual-operational-risk-loss-reports-2022&quot;>;sample&lt;/a>; of 500,000 operational losses in banks over the years, data show that incidents from the smallest size category are the most frequent (61%) but the least damaging overall (6% of the total loss severity). The real damage comes from largest, rarest incidents: each year, the top 0.3% of incidents cause on average 63% of the total losses. Despite this imbalance, risk managers and businesses dedicate more time and attention to the small issues, rather than preventing serious damage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Risk management is costly when over-applied. For example, excessive cyber protections slow down computers and logins, and double checks of every single payment and transactions wastes time that could be better used for creative activities. Credibility comes from restraint. Risk managers are respected when they show pragmatism in their calls for prudence. Competent risk managers prepare for severe and plausible scenarios while tolerating limited mishaps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Proportionate risk management reduces the inefficiencies arising from either too much control or too little control. Being too cautious leads to slowness, rigidities, and opportunity costs. Carelessness causes accidents, instability, and remediation costs. Non-financial risks have a risk-return trade-off &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.semanticscholar.org/paper/Measuring-and-Managing-Operational-Risk-in-the-An-Chapelle-Crama/5920d87080830026d615a39cb9e63ba143fe5ef4&quot;>;like their financial equivalents&lt;/a>;. Saving costs by lifting some operational controls to increase productivity is a reward for operational risks. Effective risk managers and astute business leaders have a clear view of how much risk they are prepared to accept, and for which benefits. The concept is widely referred to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bis.org/review/r151023i.htm&quot;>;risk appetite&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management celebrates success &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It is a good risk management practice to dissect the root causes of accidents, especially those with the largest potential damage. However, when focusing on past losses and future mistakes only, risk managers fail to recognize and reinforce the causes of success. Looking back to the causes of failures is valuable, but it can create resistance through implied criticism.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a senior risk officer of a clearing house in London stormed out of a workshop when some of the causes of the loss discussed were identified as a consequence of his management style. He vetoed further exercises and was let go six months later, for other reasons. The firm in question has now closed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Reflecting on success stories is inspiring. “&lt;em>;Why did we win?”&lt;/em>; creates more enthusiasm for analysis than “&lt;em>;Why did we lose?&lt;/em>;” Dissecting past achievements is encouraging and insightful. Successes are there, but often overlooked: on Monday morning, no one notices the IT migration that ran smoothly over the weekend, nor praises the absence of customer complaints, thanks to the efficient performance of staff. The &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1998-12834-004&quot;>;negativity bias&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; of the human brain means that negative experiences imprint on our memory more quickly and last longer than positive ones. Deliberate reflection on past victories is a welcome counterbalance to the common risk management focus on what went wrong.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are accepted rules for effective risk management: vigilance is key, and rapid intervention reduces impact. “&lt;em>;If you see something, say something&lt;/em>;” is the New York City Subway&#39;s motto to prevent terrorist attacks. “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btp.police.uk/police-forces/british-transport-police/areas/campaigns/see-it-say-it-sorted/&quot;>;&lt;em>;See it, say it, sorted&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;” is the equivalent for the London Underground.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For SMEs, discipline and vigilance are also essential for success. Start-ups need more than great ideas to thrive; they depend on the relentless attention of their founders, who must continually monitor performance and be alert on what could go wrong. The international expansion of a nascent brand requires rigorous planning, market knowledge, thorough due diligence, and competent managers who can fix a myriad of potential issues before they turn into disasters. Such as in personal life, the early detection of a theft, a fire, or an illness can make all the difference between a fright and a tragedy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Praising good risk management practices reinforces winning behaviors and avoids undue criticism, and positive risk managers become mentors, not doomsayers. Welcome and accepted, risk management becomes an ingredient of achievement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management protects performance &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managing risks is inseparable from managing performance. Positive risk management aims to capture the upside of uncertainty, and to prevent the downside as much as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Dream big, risk big: taking risks is necessary, even desirable. But it takes method. Stunt actors are great risk managers, otherwise they would not survive their first movie. Entrepreneurs must balance dare with caution, or they are destined to fail. Firms and governments must watch and respond to threats, or they will create havoc for themselves and others, as we have witnessed too many times. When risk management fails, organizations go down. The Great Financial Crisis, Covid-19, or the recent collapse of Silicon Valley Bank all find their source in the failure of risk management.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Risk management is a condition for ambition: the more ambitious the objective, the more important risk management is to achieve it. Hotels and resorts require flawless processes for a satisfactory customer experience; fintech banks must be first-class cybersecurity experts to operate; healthcare providers need impeccable patient safety procedures to survive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Particularly for smaller firms, growth comes with risks, and fast-growing start-ups generate operational risks faster than revenues, as complexity increases more rapidly than size. Only those with sound risk management systems will become the Google, Amazon, Disney, or McDonald&#39;s of tomorrow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With the growing focus on climate change, financial regulators and investors such a BlackRock &lt;a href=&quot;tcfd:%20https://www.fsb-tcfd.org&quot;>;expect&lt;/a>; organizations to understand, assess and communicate their exposure to climate-related risks. However, what is now required for climate-related risks is valid for all types of business exposures: to protect its business model and performance, managers need to oversee all the relevant changes to their operating environment. For instance, blockchain innovations and cryptocurrencies are most relevant to payment platform providers, while the mining conditions of cobalt and the availability of rare earth elements are essential to monitor for lithium-ion battery producers. Generative AI scares many, but used wisely (with proper risk management), this tool can be a fantastic productivity booster to be embraced rather than fought.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Conclusion&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;SMEs do not have the same regulatory pressures that can lead larger companies to measure and mitigate their risks, but they also have fewer buffer resources to resist unexpected shocks. They are one large potential incident away from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By being positive about risk management, professionals can bring an inspiring narrative to their discipline, recognizing the value of taking risks and the necessity of protecting performance. A constructive dialogue between optimists and pessimists, between those who dare and those who prefer caution, powerful engine for business growth without booms and busts. In the pursuit of success and happiness, we need to decide what we can gamble on, and what we cannot afford to lose.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Skills the Next Generation of Data Scientists Needs to Develop]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sept23_08_1298126402.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Westend61/Getty Images; Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As reliance on data and analytics continues to expand across industries from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source=prnewswire&amp;#38;utm_medium=referral&amp;#38;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;agriculture&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/&quot;>;manufacturing&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed-data-network-partnerships&quot;>;health care&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial-services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot;>;financial services&lt;/a>;, it stands to reason that the next generation of data leaders will have far-reaching roles that impact strategy, decision-making, operations, and countless other functions.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Once a year, I teach a course to aspiring data scientists. At the beginning of the first class, I ask my students what they hope to learn. Often, their answers are “analyze data” or “build good models.” Compare those responses to the workshops I run with practicing data scientists who speak in different terms when discussing what they do. They call it “solving problems” — a step in the right direction — but even that is too narrow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As reliance on data and analytics continues to expand across industries from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source=prnewswire&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;agriculture&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/&quot;>;manufacturing&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed-data-network-partnerships&quot;>;health care&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial-services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot;>;financial services&lt;/a>;, it stands to reason that the next generation of data leaders will have far-reaching roles that impact strategy, decision-making, operations, and countless other functions. To help prepare this new talent, I have developed a framework composed of four key areas of skills and capabilities that will help current and future data scientists hone their abilities to add maximum value to a business. This is done by ensuring that data science work is seen as important and indispensable by their business-function counterparts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Using this framework, and with greater understanding of what each area of business entails, today&#39;s data scientists and those entering this field can see how their knowledge and experiences stack up — and where they need more development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Problem Spotting: Seeing the real issue&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As they delve into analytics across the business, data leaders have a front row seat to nearly every operation and function. This provides them with a unique vantage point for both solving problems and identifying new ones. Here&#39;s a real-world example. The head of guest relations for a mid-range hotel chain was getting flak from upper management for low ratings on their check-in process. Surveys revealed that guests thought check-in was poorly managed, took too long, and didn&#39;t provide the results they wanted — specifically, a seamless and pleasurable experience. Management also found that people who rated check-in poorly had a lower rate of returning to the hotel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The guest relations department reached out to the data analytics team to figure out the root of the check-in problem. Even when they looked at customer demographics, the kinds of rooms they wanted, and whether they checked in at the front desk, at a kiosk, or on their phone — plus time of day, time of year, and whether customers were in the loyalty program — the data team couldn&#39;t put their finger on the underlying cause.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Then an employee suggested they look at customer surveys that had been collected on a rolling basis. Some natural language text analytics teased out some themes — namely, the hotel infrastructure was not optimal. Guests would have problems with the Wi-Fi, room keys occasionally wouldn&#39;t work, furniture was broken, or rooms weren&#39;t clean when they arrived. These problems were not directly related to check-in, but guests attributed them to the check-in process because that&#39;s what they remembered. Bottom line — the problem was with how the hotel was being managed, not the check-in process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Solving the problem that is in front of you can mean missing out on opportunities to help the business improve in other ways. Those who work with data often have access to deep, unique insights into numerous aspects of the business. To become adept at problem-spotting, data leaders need to embrace that big-picture view and gain deeper insights, with greater transparency around what matters most to business leaders. In this way, data leaders can add value by identifying problems that otherwise escape notice.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Problem Scoping: Gaining clarity and specificity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once a problem has been spotted, the next step is determining its scope — that is, gaining clarity into the nature of the problem and how analytics can help solve it. This is especially important if a business leader has approached the data team with a vague concern or challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In my classes and my workshops, we practice scoping with an exercise. I assume the role of a product or strategy or marketing leader with a well-defined problem in my head. For instance, perhaps I manage customers, and want to be able to identify which customers are at risk of giving low net promoter score (NPS) ratings so that we can intervene and improve their experience. Any reasonable data scientist would know how to select the right data and data science techniques to solve this problem. But business leaders rarely speak like this. And so I scope the problem using exaggerated jargon and overly general terms. It goes something like this: “We&#39;re struggling to hit our customer sat targets — we need to zero in on our go-to-market strategies. It could be a pipeline issue, but we just don&#39;t have alignment. I think we&#39;re playing in the right sandboxes, now we just need to know the who and the why. Sound good?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A student, in the role of the data scientist, practices asking clarifying questions — perhaps starting with, “What do you mean by &#39;alignment?&#39;” and “How are we measuring customer sat targets?” and “What measures indicate that we&#39;ve been successful (or not)?” What ensues is an iterative process of extracting information to help craft a well-defined problem that can be solved with data analytic tools and concepts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In my Chief Analytics Officer work with clients, one of the most important (and challenging) parts of my job is to take what&#39;s in a business leader&#39;s head and turn it into a well-scoped business problem. I have a checklist of probing questions that I ask, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;What, precisely, is the problem we&#39;re trying to solve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What outcomes, if improved, would indicate that the problem has actually been solved?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What data would ideally be available to solve the problem, and what data are actually available?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will the analysis lead to a solution?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Answering the last question is arguably the most important part, as it will determine the appropriate analytic technique — eg, some simple insights or a more formal predictive or causal inference model. Here, I run through many “what-if” scenarios with the business team; for example, “What if the results show this, or that? How will that help you make a better decision?” Often, business leaders try to push this question off, suggesting we can consider actions once analytic results are available. That&#39;s a mistake — knowing how the analysis will translate into a solution is a key part of formulating the analytic plan.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;To excel at problem-scoping, data leaders need good communication skills to talk through the problem with the business leader to arrive at the requisite specificity that will enable data analytics tools and concepts to meaningfully contribute to the business. Only then can the problem be turned over to the data team for analysis.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Problem Shepherding: Getting updates, gathering feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once the problem is identified and scoped out, many data analysts go into isolation and only emerge when they have found a solution. This approach is highly problematic. To be most effective, the process requires a great deal of information sharing and setting of expectations — or what I call problem shepherding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For data leaders, this means empowering their team to get more comfortable with providing &lt;em>;preliminary&lt;/em>; results to the business team. Each exchange then becomes an opportunity to gather feedback. For example, “Are these initial results of interest to the business team?” and “Are we defining terms correctly?” From one update to the next, the results come together with sequential updates until the project is concluded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This approach runs counter to how some data scientists prefer to work. Sometimes they get enamored with their models and their creative problem-solving techniques, and they can&#39;t wait for the big reveal. But “big reveals” are a bad practice — in danger of backfiring. Too much surprise in a final presentation can put the audience on the defensive.原因？ Surprising results often prompt people to start questioning the underlying data and methods.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Every data model requires assumptions (eg, what to do with missing data, how to treat outliers, etc.). If data teams actively working on analyses don&#39;t disclose and discuss their assumptions ahead of time — and, instead, wait until the end — the business team is going to pile on the questions and nitpick the weaknesses. However, by bringing the business team into decision-making along the way, they will buy into the results and commit their trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many business leaders have shared with me that the best final data deliverables are those in which there are no surprises. They&#39;ve been working closely with the data team all along, and the final deliverable or presentation is simply a culmination of their work to date. This is how problem-shepherding gets buy-in through collaboration, exposing the difficult choices that data scientists need to make.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Problem-shepherding sets up a process of providing regular updates and gathering feedback from the business team. Data scientists and team leaders who are strong in this area are able to encourage and facilitate candid discussions that ensure the final deliverable hits the mark with the business team — with no surprises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4. Solution Translating: Speaking in the language of the audience&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At this point, we transition from problem to solution, the success of which depends on how well data leaders and their teams have executed on the first three steps. More than determining a final answer, the data team must also deliver a solution that&#39;s understandable and, therefore, actionable.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This isn&#39;t just about putting the data in a chart or another visual display. Rather, the solution — whether data insights or a new course of action recommended by the model — must be conveyed in language the business team can understand. One tool I&#39;ve recommended is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-go-from-awful-awesome-presenting-data-analytics-joel-shapiro/&quot;>;two-page data analytics memo&lt;/a>;, which highlights the most important elements of the problem to be solved. While two pages may seem highly condensed, especially compared to the hefty reports that data teams often generate, brevity is the power behind this secret weapon.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The two-page limit can avoid the temptation to go on and on about details of the data analysis and encourage focus on the recommendations being made and the evidence for them. I&#39;m certainly not alone in advocating for shorter memos. Amazon founder Jeff Bezos required executives to present their ideas in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/04/23/what-jeff-bezos-learned-from-requiring-6-page-memos-at-amazon.html&quot;>;six-page memos&lt;/a>; (versus a PowerPoint presentation) that could be easily digested and discussed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Solution translation requires data leaders to step back and consider how to make the most impact with their analyses and recommendations. By using simple language, while not compromising the complexity, data leaders who excel in this area can deliver the equivalent of an elevator speech to engage business leaders with compelling and understandable solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As data and analytics become increasingly embedded in business decision-making and solutions, data teams must move well beyond merely solving the problems they&#39;ve been assigned. Data leaders and their teams must focus instead on the terms “collaboration and communication.” This means becoming more adept at broader roles that help them spot the real problem, scope out its nature and importance, shepherd the process with periodic updates, and deliver and translate solutions that will truly make an impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Inside PepsiCo&rsquo;s Effort to Reach Net Zero Emissions]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1316393475.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;For corporations like PepsiCo, most greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions originate in the supply chain, which is challenging to manage. PepsiCo believes three elements &amp;#8212; expectations, economics, and enablement &amp;#8212; are essential for effective supply-chain engagement and action. Clear expectations guide supplier partners, while understanding the economic realities aids in creating profitable GHG reductions. Lastly, enabling suppliers through support and resources can facilitate a smoother transition towards shared net-zero goals. PepsiCo&amp;#8217;s plan reflects these principles, forging a path toward a sustainable and resilient future.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Setting a net-zero goal is just the start of a climate strategy. The pressure is now on to deliver substantive progress. For many companies, the vast bulk of greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions lie outside the walls of their businesses in their supply chain – called “Scope 3” emissions. Having visibility to, quantifying, and ultimately managing these emissions is difficult. While these impacts lie outside of a company&#39;s direct control, stakeholder expectations, reporting frameworks and business demands require large corporations to activate their partners and deliver progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reward is high, if you can get it right. It&#39;s not just about delivering a reduced planetary impact but also building a value chain that enables our future growth and is resilient in the face of climate change. The global climate crisis was the catalyst to launch our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pepsico.com/who-we-are/our-commitments/pepsico-positive&quot;>;PepsiCo Positive (pep+) &lt;/a>;transformation and set a goal to become net zero by 2040. Since then, PepsiCo has taken supply-chain relationships to new levels of collaboration and built a range of strategies designed to bring supplier partners along on our journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fundamentally, PepsiCo&#39;s business is rooted in agriculture. Climate change will affect crops, and it will impact farmers and the yields they can deliver. We must have a clear strategy for the business to both manage our impact on the climate and make our company more resilient and competitive going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Internally, we are constantly working to embed net-zero thinking into our teams. For example, PepsiCo incentivizes progress by making Scope 1 and 2 emissions reductions part of the compensation review process for the top 200 executives at the company, and we are working toward being able to more accurately quantify Scope 3 emissions so that we can include that metric in the future as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;In our value chain, with more than 100,000 suppliers of varying sizes and capabilities, a one-size-fits-all approach will not achieve the needed impact towards net zero.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are many approaches to take, and we have learned lessons along the way. But we believe there are three fundamental elements – expectations, economics and enablement – that you must get right in order to have successful supply-chain-partner engagement and, more importantly, supply-chain-partner action.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Expectations&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Setting clear and consistent expectations with supply-chain partners is the foundation for success. Companies must let suppliers know emissions reductions are important, particularly when it is something that will be measured over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our agricultural supply chain, for example, farmers have different levels of understanding around emissions. Some are aware of climate change and its impacts, while for others, it isn&#39;t even on their radar screens. As leaders, we must provide clear and consistent guidelines for our suppliers and other supply-chain partners, so they can understand their role in our journey now and into the future. We set out these expectations at our annual Global Supplier Summit and are asking our partners to take four specific, near-term actions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Report Scope 1 &amp;amp; 2 emissions to us by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Set, or commit to setting, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sciencebasedtargets.org/how-it-works&quot;>;a science-based target (SBT)&lt;/a>; by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Convert PepsiCo&#39;s portion of electrical load to renewable electricity, where available, by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;For agricultural suppliers, collaborate with us to develop an action plan for sustainable ingredients and to build regenerative agriculture acres by the end 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Setting an SBT for emissions reductions provides a clear structure and framework. Tracking data across the value chain is vital to understanding the breadth and pace of progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a big shift for some of our suppliers&#39; operations. In some cases, this is not just about investment but also about making changes in the way they operate. More than ever, supplier relationships need to move from transactional to partnership. That&#39;s where companies can use their scale and knowledge to help suppliers&#39; transition – acting as partners and providing support along the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Economics&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When engaging supply-chain partners, companies often make the mistake of supporting them only with financial incentives (or disincentives). While economics are certainly critical, they come into play only after the foundation and expectations have been set.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the most powerful things to do is clarify for suppliers the economic realities and tradeoffs that come with GHG reductions. Decarbonization can be expensive, but the reality is it won&#39;t always cost more. Reducing inputs, such as water and fertilizer, minimizing plastic use, and investing in renewable energy can all save money. Companies can help their suppliers do the math and understand the concrete ways they can come out ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies must also consider how to better structure partnerships to lead toward a sustainable transition. Long-term agreements that incentivize and support sustainable transformation can be a great catalyst. PepsiCo signed a seven-and-a-half-year strategic commercial agreement with ADM to share costs and resources and closely collaborate on projects that aim to significantly expand regenerative agriculture by up to 2 million acres by 2030 across our shared North American supply chains. The length of the contract helps to instill confidence to invest in sustainable practices as well as achieving carbon reduction goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Enablement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When it comes to net zero, the challenges are too complex and interconnected to leave implementation up to chance. As partners, we have offered guidance to help enable our suppliers as they navigate the interplay of strategies so that they can more easily make progress against our shared goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, we&#39;ve created programs to guide on setting SBTs and have provided resources that outline different options for emissions reductions, particularly in moving to renewable electricity, as this can vary based on each supplier&#39;s situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies, like PepsiCo, can also help solve sustainability challenges by using their scale and networks to invest in, and scale-up, promising start-ups and leverage relationships with some of the largest companies in the world.&amp;nbsp; In doing so, making them more cost-efficient and accessible to our partners. For agriculture technologies, we are doing trials of promising solutions on demonstration farms around the world and investing in suppliers that we believe can make a real impact. For farmers, proven approaches are key to achieving buy-in and implementing solutions quickly and effectively. Through our pep+ REnew program, we are also working towards helping our supply-chain partners with aggregated buys of renewable energy to create scale and cost efficiencies that individual suppliers cannot achieve on their own.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Creating a sustainable value chain is difficult, but with the right approach, it is a powerful means to meet sustainability goals, create a more resilient organization and fuel improved business performance. At PepsiCo, that&#39;s our end game, and the three fundamental elements – expectations, economics and enablement – will set us, as well as our supply chain partners, on the path to truly sustainable growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop Overworking After Vacation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1438950079.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;After a vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for &amp;#8220;lost&amp;#8221; time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&amp;#8217;re still valuable to the organization. Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? The authors offer several strategies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As summer winds down and many of our coaching clients and research participants are returning from vacation, we&#39;re seeing increased levels of return-to-work anxiety. As one client, “Leslie,” put it:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Coming back from vacation almost makes [it] seem not worth it. For me, it&#39;s like psychologically accelerating from a cruising pace of 30 mph to a speed of 80 so I can get through my inbox, catch up on all the meetings I missed, and reconnect with my neglected clients. And that&#39;s on top of the guilt I&#39;ve been feeling about overburdening my team while they&#39;ve been covering for me.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to respond to these intense feelings like Leslie did, by throwing yourself into &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest&quot;>;overworking&lt;/a>;, overcompensating, and overachieving the minute you disable your out of office responder — especially in work cultures that don&#39;t exactly encourage time off in the first place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, there&#39;s a healthier, more balanced approach that can help you ease back into your routine without losing all the stress-reducing and performance-enhancing benefits of unplugging from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Time Off Is Essential&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s be clear that taking periodic breaks in order to reset and recover from work stress (what researchers refer to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;work recovery&lt;/a>;) isn&#39;t a “nice to have” — it&#39;s essential for sustained performance and growth. Just as athletes engage in regular periods of rest and recovery in order to perform at their best and avoid injury, workers need periods of time away from their jobs to recuperate from the strain of work and replenish their physical and mental energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that those who don&#39;t take the opportunity to rest, recharge, and recover are at higher risk of exhaustion, low motivation, poor performance, and burnout, while those who engage in regular periods of work recovery enjoy better sleep, higher job satisfaction, more engagement, and higher job performance. Human bodies and brains simply aren&#39;t built to endure chronic stress, and there&#39;s plenty of evidence showing how disconnecting from the strains and demands of work not only lowers stress, but increases &lt;a href=&quot;https://kops.uni-konstanz.de/server/api/core/bitstreams/63f6ae78-86f7-47fc-96b1-17654a0d2bf6/content&quot;>;productivity&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8733151/&quot;>;boosts creativity&lt;/a>;. Even &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9432722/&quot;>;micro-breaks&lt;/a>; taken throughout the workday, such as stretching, doing some deep breathing exercises, or stepping outside for some fresh air, can halt the stress cycle and return you to baseline.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the clear benefits of time away, however, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/03/30/how-americans-view-their-jobs&quot;>;nearly half&lt;/a>; of American workers don&#39;t take all the paid time off their employer offers. Chief among their reasons are worries that they&#39;ll fall behind, or that time off will hurt their chances for advancement or even increase their risk of losing their job, as well as guilt over coworkers having to take on additional work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These are sentiments we hear often, including from our senior executive clients, who frequently express a fear of losing momentum if they step away. Part of our role as executive coaches is empowering clients to invest in themselves and their performance with the practice of regular work recovery.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Resisting the Urge to Overwork After Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Post-vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for “lost” time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&#39;re still valuable to the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? Here are some strategies that have worked for our research participants and clients:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Shift to a performance mindset.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;High performance and sufficient recovery were never meant to function separately, yet in the corporate world, performance tends to be overemphasized while recovery is overlooked. Rather than treating time away as a last resort only &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; you&#39;re depleted and unproductive, or as a special reward when your to-do list is finally done, take a cue from top athletes and include work recovery as &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-to-recover-from-work-stress-according-to-science&quot;>;an essential component&lt;/a>; of a high-performance strategy. Work recovery works best when it&#39;s practiced regularly and consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Prevent or ease “reentry shock.”&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;“Reentry shock” refers to the discombobulation you feel when you transition from a place of calm and equilibrium to one that pulls you into the frazzle and fray. You can prevent this by using buffers. Schedule a free day between your return from vacation and your return to work so you can mentally and physically prepare for the change in environment. Keep your calendar light just after your return, which will give you a chance to reacclimate and avoid overwork. For example, one of our clients has a two-day “no meetings” buffer after his return.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Bring some vacation magic home with you.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;What exactly was it during your period of recovery that helped you decompress and feel more like yourself? Was it exercise? Reconnecting with loved ones? An artistic pursuit or hobby that&#39;s neglected during the work week? Simply enjoying some unscheduled leisure time? As much as possible, build these activities and conditions into your normal weekly routine. Remember, even small doses of downtime make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Before saying yes to new requests when you return to work, consider what&#39;s getting in your way of saying no.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Are you concerned about not being recognized, rewarded, or promoted? If so, stop, breathe, and check your assumptions. It may be possible to get the recognition and rewards you&#39;re looking for without overcommitting yourself and sacrificing your health and well-being. If you can&#39;t identify the problem areas — or if you need help figuring out what to do about them — consider working with a coach.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Review, communicate, and maintain your boundaries.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Returning from a recovery period is a great time to review and refresh your work boundaries. Let everyone know when you will and will not be available for work, and if work demands begin to creep past your role or your comfort level, speak with leadership about shifting responsibilities, or see if you can delegate. Boundaries should help define others&#39; expectations of your role, and they should protect your downtime and allow you to mentally detach from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Leave a toxic work environment that discourages time away or that rewards employees for excessive hours and self-sacrifice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This kind of unhealthy work environment will leave you ripe for exhaustion and burnout. If you can&#39;t leave right away, start creating an exit strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Preventing the Urge to Overwork Before Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Next time you&#39;re planning to take time off, try in advance to make things easier for future you. Weeks before you leave, arrange for who&#39;s covering your responsibilities during your absence, and include their contact information in your out-of-office message. Set clear expectations for when/if you should be contacted during vacation. Structure a reentry routine ahead of time so you can plug into an existing process and more easily get back into work mode. Finally, consider conducting a premortem before finalizing your plans. What specific challenges or failures&amp;nbsp;might you expect or imagine?&amp;nbsp;What were their main causes? What was not yet accounted for? And ultimately, what additional preventive steps can you take now? This simple but powerful process helps further refine your pre–time off planning, which can prevent most reentry problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Periodic time away from work is one of the best ways to ensure that you&#39;ll be able to sustain your energy and productivity. With some planning before your time away and some sensible guardrails after your return, you can bring all the stress-lowering benefits of work recovery back with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Accelerating Digital Integration in Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_06_16aIvW0lxOk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Unsplash; A Mokhtari/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Regional integration, similar to the European Union&amp;#8217;s, has been cited as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration. Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate Africa&amp;#8217;s digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 2021, the combined &lt;a href=&quot;https://statisticstimes.com/economy/africa-gdp.php#:~:text=GDP%20of%20Africa&amp;amp;text=The%20African%20economy%2C%20comprising%2054,largest%20economy%20in%20the%20world.&quot;>;GDP of Africa&#39;s 54 countries&lt;/a>; was less than 15% of the United States&#39; GDP. The continent consists of many relatively small countries, economies, and markets, which is a disadvantage on the world stage, where countries with huge populations and GDPs wield the most influence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. Regional integration, similar to the European Union&#39;s, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/news-and-events/importance-of-regional-and-continental-integration-for-africas-development-18773&quot;>;been cited&lt;/a>; as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this context, “digital integration” refers to creating shared systems and standard rules for digitalization across Africa. It entails digital cooperation, particularly in finance, governance, and security. In practice, digital integration will feature concepts such as a harmonized digital financial system, consistent continent-wide laws for digital activities, and shared regulatory technology like identity verification, electronic taxation, and business registration systems. Among other things, digital integration will facilitate optimal trade, resulting in cost savings, better information flow for improved participation in global commerce, and greater market access, particularly for small businesses, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/edar2022&quot;>;dominate trade in Africa&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate this digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Private Sector Collaboration&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many private African organizations have successfully established themselves across national boundaries, driven by profit-making ambitions and unrestricted by bureaucracy or politics. Despite inherent challenges, corporations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/organizations/naspers-limited&quot;>;Naspers&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtn.com/about/&quot;>;MTN Group&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ecobank.com/group/about-us/history&quot;>;Ecobank&lt;/a>;, for example, have found ways to expand across national borders. They can serve as reference points and potential partners for the digital integration of Africa&#39;s economies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fostering digital integration requires collaborations between these private players, governments, and regional bodies. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://papss.com/&quot;>;Pan-African Payment and Settlement System&lt;/a>; (PAPSS) demonstrates that this approach is feasible. While PAPSS is the product of a partnership between the African Union and the African Export-Import Bank, it depends on a network of some of Africa&#39;s largest private commercial banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A centralized payment and settlement system for intra-African commerce, officially introduced in January 2022, PAPSS facilitates continental commerce and deeper economic integration. It enables payments for intra-African trade transactions in local currencies (Africa has roughly 42 currencies), reducing expenses and accelerating trade settlement and payment. Before PAPSS, the typical payment route between two African countries required that an African currency be first exchanged for dollars, pounds, or euros and then swapped a second time for a different African currency. This raises the cost of intra-African currency transactions by an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/09/Digital-Journeys-Africa-freeing-foreign-exchange-wellisz&quot;>;estimated $5 billion&lt;/a>; each year.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Building for Interoperability&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Building continent-wide digital systems will take time and significant resources, but immediately prioritizing interoperability could create the foundation for digital integration. Thus, public digital systems being built in African countries should be interoperable — that is, have capabilities for the exchange and use of information with other similar systems in other countries. Inevitably, some economies and sectors move faster than others with digitalization. Therefore, building with interoperability in mind will allow for easy integration in the near future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With identity systems, for example, an ideal scenario would be for ID obtained in Nigeria to be easily digitally verifiable by a bank in Namibia. This would be possible if Nigeria&#39;s digital identity system had the capacity for interoperability. Moreover, interoperable ID systems across the continent would allow for continent-wide know-your-customer systems, enabling access to financial services anywhere in Africa and thus making intra-African commerce easier.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, interoperable public systems require significant policy and regulatory interventions. Governments and regional bodies must address challenges such as harmonizing standards, enhancing current legal frameworks, and adopting cybersecurity, consumer, and data protection regulations to facilitate successful interoperability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Power and Internet&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Digital integration has no chance if digital services are only accessible to a fraction of the population, as in many African countries. While physical infrastructure like roads, rails, and ports connecting the continent is critical to Africa&#39;s physical integration, power and the internet will determine the success of digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many African countries still have less than half of their population as internet users, with countries such as Burundi and the Central African Republic having &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1124283/internet-penetration-in-africa-by-country/&quot;>;less than 15%&lt;/a>; internet penetration. Similarly, 600 million people, or&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/africa-energy-outlook-2022/key-findings&quot;>; 43% of the entire African population&lt;/a>;, do not have access to electricity, with the majority living in sub-Saharan Africa. Therefore, accelerating universal access to power and the internet should become a priority.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Africa desperately needs digital integration, but it&#39;s critical to recognize its inherent difficulties — for example, concerns about sovereignty and divergent national objectives. What&#39;s more, active steps toward digital integration require deliberate government commitment, which requires governments to recognize their importance and have the resources to pursue them.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Negotiate Your Salary in the Age of Pay Transparency Laws]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_06_7aWvQdR36Y0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&amp;#8217;s possible. But how should you negotiate for yourself when a pay band is exceptionally large? In this article, the author shares insights from two experts on compensation and negotiation. They recommend not focusing on &amp;#8220;fairness&amp;#8221; &lt;/span>;when making your case, but rather &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;focusing the conversation on yours and the employer&amp;#8217;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Having more information to gauge your worth should, in theory, give you more leverage in salary negotiations. But the reality is complicated. Companies could be less willing to stray from their set ranges, and you might feel hesitant to push for fear of looking unreasonable. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;How should you approach salary conversations in this new era of pay transparency laws? What&#39;s the best way to advocate for yourself when the pay band is exceptionally large? And is it better to be direct or subtle? &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;What the Experts Say&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/3-new-us-employment-regulations-that-companies-should-prepare-for-now&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pay transparency laws&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; vary from state to state,&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; but in a nutshell, they require employers to disclose information about pay, such as salary ranges, in job postings or in offers to candidates. The aim is to create more visibility in pay practices and &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/how-salary-transparency-can-help-you-and-your-workplace&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;help close gender and racial wage gaps&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For job seekers, the upshot is more agency in salary negotiations, says D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;avid Buckmaster, the author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Pay-Raise-Stronger-Businesses/dp/1665098317&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Fair Pay&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, who&#39;s worked on employee compensation projects for companies including Nike and Starbucks&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. Before these laws existed, Buckmaster says that compensation was like a mysterious black box. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Job candidates&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; were in the dark about what comparable employees made and how the company benchmarked salaries to the rest of the market,” he says. “Now, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;having a pay range takes away some of those unknowns.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The downside is that it can cause job seekers to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;hyper-fixate on salary&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, rather than the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/negotiating-your-next-job&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;big picture of an employment offer&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, according to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Victoria Medvec, a professor at the Kellogg School of Management at Northwestern and author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Negotiate-without-Fear-Strategies-Maximize/dp/1119719097&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiate Without Fear&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Your pay is a piece of it, but there are other aspects of the job to consider like your role, responsibilities, benefits, and flexibility,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here are some tips to help you navigate the conversation and get the compensation you deserve.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Appreciate your newfound power.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-ask-for-what-you-want-and-get-it&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating your salary&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; requires information, tact, confidence — and the right mindset, says &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec.&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “Knowledge is power, and&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;y&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ou now have an advantage because you know what&#39;s possible.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While some salary bands might seem too broad to be useful, they underscore the power of negotiation, she says. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The range exists because &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiation is a dynamic interaction between the employee and employer and &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;some people do it more effectively.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;After all, she says, it&#39;s not &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/how-women-can-get-what-they-want-in-a-negotiation&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;just about being willing to ask for more&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, it&#39;s also about having the information and self-assurance to make your case.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Don&#39;t get in your own head and don&#39;t be intimidated or discouraged — even if a certain number feels out of reach, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;adds Buckmaster. For example, if you make $70,000 and you&#39;re being offered a comparable job with a listed range of $100,000-$150,000, you might feel as if you can&#39;t ask for the top of the range. But the fact is, your current salary has little bearing on what another company is willing to pay you, he says: “What you made before &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;doesn&#39;t matter.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do your research.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your goal is to go into the negotiation with an objective, realistic understanding of how the employer views your market value. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This requires some homework to figure out where you might land within the company&#39;s published&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; compensation &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;bands: at the top, in the middle, or toward the bottom. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Before pay transparency laws existed, people may have assumed that HR has been randomly throwing darts at a dartboard to determine what people got paid, but there&#39;s rigor behind the numbers,” says Buckmaster. He says that behind the listed range lies an “approval matrix” that&#39;s invisible to candidates. “Every company has a trigger point that requires extra approvals to justify placing someone at the very top of the range.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;on&#39;t be disheartened; rather, use that &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/work-speak-the-right-way-to-negotiate&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;knowledge to make a compelling case&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; for yourself. Visit j&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ob search websites and databases, such as Glassdoor, Ladders, and Salary.com, and talk to recruiters and industry colleagues. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Take a good, hard look at your experience and qualifications and be honest about your work history. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Evaluate your actual job level and the scope of your past responsibilities. De-emphasize titles. Being a director at a startup is not the same as being one at a large company,” Buckmaster says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Be savvy about the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many, but not all, &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/04/15-rules-for-negotiating-a-job-offer&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;salary negotiations take place&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; after the company has extended an offer. But you might consider signaling your salary expectations earlier in the process if you think your pay ought to be on the high-end of the range, says Buckmaster. He suggests saying something along the lines of, “I&#39;m looking forward to seeing the offer and trust that my starting position in your pay range will align with my significant experience doing this work at XYZ company.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Once the company has made an offer, the opportunity to negotiate for more is usually quite narrow, so Buckmaster advises making your case wisely. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Don&#39;t go back multiple times, otherwise it might affect your reputation on the way in,” he says. “You don&#39;t want to come across as being challenging to work with.” Make your argument concise, crisp, and reasonable. “Most companies don&#39;t want to have custom, complicated negotiations with everyone who comes in.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;State your case…&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating a higher salary requires clearly articulating why you&#39;re worth more. Medvec recommends&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; focusing on your &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;differentiators: your background, skill set, and special abilities that match the company&#39;s needs. You&#39;ve &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/5-ways-to-stand-out-in-your-next-job-interview&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;already outlined your past achievements&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; in the hiring process&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, of course. Now it&#39;s time to talk about how you&#39;ll add value in the future — and how that should be reflected in your pay. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec suggests laying out how you&#39;ll help the company generate new lines of revenue, cut costs, attract talent, or enter new markets. “Talk about your exact role and responsibilities, including what specifically you&#39;ll be doing,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pinpointing how &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/10/to-land-a-great-job-talk-about-why-you-love-your-work&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;you&#39;re going to tackle their challenges&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; puts you in a stronger position, she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Bear in mind that approval matrix, adds Buckmaster. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Help the recruiter tell your story internally,” he says. “Make their job easier with solid arguments oriented around the business. Otherwise they&#39;re going to have a hard time getting it approved.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;… and bring your A-game if you&#39;re aiming extra high.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While it&#39;s possible to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiate above the stated pay range, your case has to be bulletproof. Many companies are comfortable with roughly 5% of their employees being paid over the maximum, according to Buckmaster. Pay bands are not an exact science and “sometimes people break the system and end up with higher salaries,” he says. This can happen for many reasons. Perhaps the new hire is joining a smaller company, or maybe their manager is more like a peer, or maybe the new employee is taking on a specialized role, or perhaps they know esoteric coding language that the company needs. “Or it could be that they&#39;re uniquely gifted and hard to get,” he says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;A word of warning though: If you&#39;re paid over the maximum, you might be ineligible for salary increases in the future, so be sure to inquire about the company&#39;s policies. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For senior roles, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; recommends booking a half hour with an employment lawyer in the city where the company is based. “Find out not just how much others ask for, but also what&#39;s in their contracts, like stock, equity, and employment guarantees,” she says. “It will be an expensive 30 minutes, but well worth it for senior-level jobs.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t focus on “fairness,” but rather mutual interests.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;P&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ay-transparency laws were created to help ensure equitable compensation, but it&#39;s not a good idea to frame your individual negotiation around fairness, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;according to Medvec. “Don&#39;t create a rationale based on what&#39;s right or what&#39;s fair,” she says. Instead, “reference information about what others earn to anchor your request, but keep the conversation focused on the employer&#39;s interests.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For example, Medvec recommends saying something along the lines of: “I know from publicly available information that this role pays up to $190,000. I believe I&#39;m at the top end of that pay range because I&#39;m uniquely positioned to do XYZ, and I&#39;m confident in what I bring to the table. But I&#39;m also comfortable getting a base salary of $160,00 with a $50,000 annual bonus when I achieve the objectives that are important to you.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This way, you&#39;re making strategic compromises that benefit both you and the organization.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Principles to Remember&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Appreciate your newfound advantage. Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&#39;s possible.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Carve out time to do your homework so you can build a strong argument for the salary you want.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Make sure the recruiter can tell your story to the decision-makers by framing your argument in terms of the business.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Doubt yourself even if a certain number feels out of reach. If you think you&#39;re worth it, make a strong, rational case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Belabor what&#39;s fair or what&#39;s right; &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;rather, focus the conversation on yours and the employer&#39;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;M&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ake the mistake of assuming you can negotiate indefinitely; companies usually have a clear process and don&#39;t want a drawn-out back-and-forth.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is India the World&rsquo;s Next Great Economic Power?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_05_638755428.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/anand purohit/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Is India&amp;#8217;s economic rise inevitable? There&amp;#8217;s good reason to think that this latest round of Indo-optimism might be different than previous iterations, but the country still has major challenges to address to make good on this promise. In terms of drivers, demand &amp;#8212; in the form of a consumer boom, context appropriate innovation, and a green transition &amp;#8212; and supply &amp;#8212; in the form of a demographic dividend, access to finance, and major infrastructure upgrades &amp;#8212; are helping to push the country forward. This is facilitated by policy reforms, geopolitical positioning, and a diaspora dividend. Even so, the country faces barriers to success, including unbalanced growth, unrealized demographic potential, and unrealized ease-of-business and innovation potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 2002, India&#39;s government launched a ubiquitous international tourism campaign known as “Incredible India.” Were it to launch a similar campaign today, it might as well be called “Inevitable India.” Not just enthusiasts within the country, but a chorus of global analysts, have declared India as the next great economic power: Goldman Sachs has predicted it will become the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html&quot;>;world&#39;s second-largest economy by 2075,&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/c9de715e-2e29-4a7f-880b-1509c04bf11b&quot;>;FT&#39;s Martin Wolf suggests&lt;/a>; that by 2050, its purchasing power will be 30% larger than that of the US&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have been through similar surges of Indo-optimism before. But the on-the-ground reality has continued to frustrate even the most ardent of India&#39;s champions. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/04/28/india-revolutions-economy-growth-future/&quot;>;bold predictions&lt;/a>; that it would overtake China (an economy still five times larger than India&#39;s), to McKinsey&#39;s 2007 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/asia-pacific/the-bird-of-gold&quot;>;“bird of gold”&lt;/a>; promise of the Indian consumer that never quite panned out, to deregulation followed by policy reversals and crises of confidence in doing business with India, to devastating periods through the pandemic, the country&#39;s promised inevitable rise has remained elusive. What&#39;s different now?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are several positive trends converging, from different sides of the Indian business ecosystem: demand, supply, and the system-wide facilitating factors; in combination, they can transcend economic cycles, macro shocks, and policy reversals. Some are new, and the older ones are reaching critical mass and they can finally reinforce each other to create a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/the-flywheel.html&quot;>;growth flywheel&lt;/a>;. But as with all flywheels, it is important to remain vigilant about rattling noises and burning smells, and in India&#39;s case, these exist in abundance. It&#39;s essential for both business and government leaders to pay attention and act before the flywheel breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Demand&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Three forces are converging on the demand side to fuel India&#39;s economic growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Consumer boom&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The starting point for any discussion of India&#39;s promise is, invariably, the promise of the Indian consumer. With 1.4 billion people and myriad unmet needs, India&#39;s growth is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html&quot;>;driven mainly&lt;/a>; by domestic consumption and investments. Real wages are expected to grow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/01/apac-salary-asia-leads-2023-real-wage-growth-jumps-in-india-china.html&quot;>;at 4.6%,&lt;/a>; whereas disposable income will continue to grow in excess of &lt;a href=&quot;https://tradingeconomics.com/india/disposable-personal-income&quot;>;15%&lt;/a>;. Industries that are mature in the West are fast-growing in India: Private health insurance, for example, has almost &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/advisor/in/health-insurance/health-insurance-statistics/&quot;>;tripled between 2015 and 2021&lt;/a>;, while consumer durables were expected to grow between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisil.com/en/home/newsroom/press-releases/2022/09/volume-vault-to-lift-consumer-durables-revenue-15-18-percent.html&quot;>;15% and 18%&lt;/a>; this year.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Context-appropriate innovation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;International companies have struggled to grasp what constitutes India&#39;s “middle class” and craft the appropriate value propositions. While &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/middle-class-nearly-1/3rd-of-indias-population-to-be-2/3rds-by-2047-report/articleshow/95239621.cms&quot;>;some analysts&lt;/a>; argue that one out of every three Indians is “middle class,” only &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrinks-and-poverty-spreads-while-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;66 million&lt;/a>; are genuinely “middle income” by global standards, while a whopping &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrinks-and-poverty-spreads-while-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;1.16 billion&lt;/a>; are low income. However, many in this second group constitute a vast &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/be53790c-ea16-4e5c-9410-bac189fb2636&quot;>;aspirational consuming class&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This has many implications. For one, competing in India means selling at much lower price points, which in turn requires reconfiguring activities, production, and supply chains in ways that are hard for competitors to mimic. India&#39;s best-selling car is Wagon R, priced at $7,000 and made by Japan&#39;s Suzuki, a company whose &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/10/31/business/corporate-business/suzuki-india-market-share/&quot;>;41% market share&lt;/a>; in India is an outlier in the auto industry globally.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.firstpost.com/entertainment/explained-why-netflix-is-failing-big-time-in-india-10580421.html&quot;>;Netflix discovered&lt;/a>; through its stumbles in the country, it takes more than low prices to win in India. Localizing the content, working in multiple Indian languages, and leveraging synergies across products that Indian consumers want, as Amazon or Disney can do, is essential. In a very different sector, McDonald&#39;s, has incorporated vegetarian options, Indian snacks, and menus for multi-generational families, building a contextualized value proposition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Those that can crack the code of the Indian consumer are handsomely rewarded: Many McDonald&#39;s franchisees in India are billionaires. The home appliances manufacturer Havells introduced a product line with “India-friendly” offerings such as water purifiers and compressor-less air coolers, relevant to both the Indian consumers&#39; needs and affordability. Since its listing 30 years ago, &lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/havells-india-ltd/stocks/companyid-10507.cms&quot;>;Havells&#39;&lt;/a>; profits have grown 826 times, and its market cap has jumped 5,800 times.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Green transition&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A burgeoning new source of demand growth comes from India&#39;s urgent need for a green transition. The scale of its economic potential means that its energy demand will be enormous. As the third-largest energy-consuming nation, it is already &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investindia.gov.in/sector/renewable-energy#:~:text=India&#39;s%20installed%20renewable%20energy%20capacity,additions%20of%209.83%25%20in%202022.&quot;>;4th in the world&lt;/a>; in renewable energy installed capacity. The country has set &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/india-s-clean-energy-transition-is-rapidly-underway-benefiting-the-entire-world&quot;>;ambitious targets&lt;/a>;: installing 500 gigawatts of renewable energy capacity, producing 5 million tons of green hydrogen annually, cutting emissions by 45%, along with a billion tons of CO2 — all by 2030. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Mission_2070_A_Green_New_Deal_for_a_Net_Zero_India_2021.pdf&quot;>;2021 report&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;by the World Economic Forum projects 50 million net new “green economy” jobs in India — which means more consumers — and $15 trillion in economic opportunity by 2070, with $1 trillion by 2030.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Supply&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;There are several positive forces converging on the supply side as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Demographic dividend&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;One part of the supply-side story is old news: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_in/india-at-100/reaping-the-demographic-dividend&quot;>;By 2030&lt;/a>;, India&#39;s working-age population is expected to be 1.04 billion with a dependency ratio to be the lowest in its history at 31.2%, contributing just under a quarter of the incremental global workforce. The working-age population bulge is expected to last till 2055.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The “Asian Miracle” was built on harnessing this trend: Japan entered this sweet spot in 1964, South Korea in 1967 and China in 1994. Additionally, India also has the largest pool of English-speaking STEM graduates in the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Access to finance&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;India&#39;s financial markets are in a better state than ever before. With the China opportunities cooling, investors need alternatives, and India comes closest. The MSCI India Index is up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/india-investing-china-stocks-growth-exports-demographics-31252a80&quot;>;12%&lt;/a>; this year, compared to 2% for the MSCI Emerging Markets Index.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bank balance sheets are &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/with-stronger-balance-sheets-indias-banking-sector-at-an-inflection-point/articleshow/96702845.cms&quot;>;stronger&lt;/a>; and credit markets are functioning well. It&#39;s telling that many Indian banks are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/finance/banks/news/indian-banks-better-placed-than-their-us-peers-due-to-attractive-valuations-and-stickier-deposits/articleshow/98859627.cms&quot;>;valued higher&lt;/a>; than US peers. &amp;nbsp;HDFC Bank — which merged with its parent, mortgage lender HDFC — has a market capitalization of $171 billion, making it the 4&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 13.3333px;&quot;>;th &lt;/span>;largest financial company in the world. Even before the merger, the 29-year-old upstart was more valuable than the 154-year-old Goldman Sachs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The change can be seen even in the traditionally underfinanced informal sector, comprising over 86% of India&#39;s workforce. Avendus, a leading Indian investment bank, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avendus.com/crypted_pdf_path/msme-lending-report-formattedvf-img-642a719b97ccc-.pdf&quot;>;calculated&lt;/a>; that Indian small-and-medium-enterprise sector&#39;s total demand for debt is $1.5 trillion. Of this, $725 billion is unaddressable because of lack of collateral, and formal credit is only available to the tune of $289 billion. This is motivating lenders to deepen their offerings. New-to-credit customers are at 34% up from 9% of customers for small business lenders in 2017. Loans by small business lenders have jumped 43% annually in the past two years.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Infrastructure upgrades, both physical and digital&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A critical barrier that sticks in the mind of anyone who has visited India is its lagging infrastructure. Historically, &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/programmes/from_our_own_correspondent/9483756.stm&quot;>;investing in handouts&lt;/a>; may have been more politically expedient, but the current administration&#39;s popularity gives it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/modi-should-focus-on-people-not-just-big-projects/2023/02/06/ceb85dc4-a66b-11ed-b2a3-edb05ee0e313_story.html&quot;>;greater leeway&lt;/a>; to invest in infrastructure. Capital expenditure as a percentage of total government expenditure has increased from 11% in 2010 to a projected 22% this year. Infrastructure expenditure this year will see a 33% hike to $122 billion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The outcomes have been striking. India has been adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;10,000 km of highway&lt;/a>; annually. Since 2014, the number of Indian airports has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;doubled&lt;/a>; and an upgraded train system will have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;new high efficiency “freight corridors&lt;/a>;” connecting the economic centers of India.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, one of most distinctive changes has been in the digital infrastructure. With &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/info-tech/indias-internet-subscribers-increased-to-88125-million-as-of-march-end-trai-report/article67219636.ece&quot;>;881.25 million&lt;/a>; internet subscribers, India has the second-highest internet-enabled population in the world behind China&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://english.scio.gov.cn/m/pressroom/2022-11/07/content_78506468.htm&quot;>;1.05 billion&lt;/a>;. Riding on this access, there is a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-case-for-investing-in-digital-public-infrastructure&quot;>;digital public infrastructure&lt;/a>; — a model being studied by other countries — that combines a population-scale unique identity system, a payments interface that makes digital payments seamless, and a data management system, whereby citizens can access essential documents online, such as tax documents, vaccination certificates, etc. All of this helps make public services and credit more easily accessible to a wider swath of the population.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As an indicator of the resulting change, India has &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/gadgets-news/india-tops-world-ranking-in-digital-payments-beats-china-by-huge-margin-report/articleshow/100944643.cms&quot;>;topped the list&lt;/a>; for digital payments beating China by a huge margin. Interestingly, India&#39;s payments are more than the digital payments made in the next four leading countries combined.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Facilitators&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;On top of these forces in motion, there are several system-wide facilitators in the mix.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Domestic policy reforms&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many &lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/india/1734728/india-may-soon-achieve-modis-ease-of-doing-business-goal&quot;>;regulatory and policy reforms&lt;/a>; have been put in place, from implementation of the 2016 Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code to the elimination of more than 39,000 regulations to foster ease of doing business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many other reforms, such as construction permits and power connections, are the domain of state governments and there is a drive towards change at these levels as well. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/05/11/how-indias-states-compete-for-investment&quot;>;State governments are competing&lt;/a>; by helping speed up the process of setting up businesses, providing incentives for investment and even attracting clusters of competing companies, which enables more business-friendly environments in more regions across the country.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Geopolitical sweet spot&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Another transformation is a more distinctive geopolitical positioning for India, triggered, most significantly, by the growing rift between China and Western economies, particularly the US This is translating into new business opportunities for India, most visibly — the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-65784719&quot;>;manufacturing of Apple&#39;s smartphones&lt;/a>;. With a goal of producing 20 million iPhones a year, 50,000 new jobs will be created by one such project alone. In addition, when it comes to military-grade technology used for space launches, there is greater confidence in India as a host than China and there is already a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/04/business/india-space-startups.html&quot;>;thriving ecosystem&lt;/a>; in place. India has hosted &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_foreign_satellites_launched_by_India&quot;>;111 international space launches&lt;/a>; since 2020, and successfully &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/science/india-moon-landing-photos.html&quot;>;landed a rover on the moon&lt;/a>; in late August.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To consider another prominent example, chipmaker, Micron Technology, &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.micron.com/news-releases/news-release-details/micron-announces-new-semiconductor-assembly-and-test-facility&quot;>;announced&lt;/a>; plans to build a new assembly and test facility, as part of moves to diversify beyond China. In fact, the new president of the World Bank has suggested that there is a narrow window for India to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-should-cash-china-plus-one-strategy-world-bank-chief-2023-07-19/#:~:text=In%20recent%20years%2C%20many%20companies,World%20Bank%20chief%20last%20month.&quot;>;“cash in”&lt;/a>; on the growing trend behind companies seeking to diversify their supply chain and manufacturing beyond a massive dependence on China.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Diaspora dividend&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It is interesting to note that both the CEO of Micron Technology and the World Bank chief are Indian-born, which brings us to the third key facilitator: the Indian diaspora, now the world&#39;s largest and influential in ways that it had never been before. In the business world alone it is telling that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/06/12/indias-diaspora-is-bigger-and-more-influential-than-any-in-history&quot;>;25 of S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a>; company CEOs are Indian-born. Beyond this, senior management ranks of numerous companies are populated by Indians. It&#39;s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://m.economictimes.com/tech/startups/indians-are-driving-the-us-startup-story-nfap-study/india-is-the-leading-country-of-origin-for-immigrant-founders-of-us-unicorns/slideshow/93165270.cms&quot;>;leading country of origin&lt;/a>; for immigrant founders of US unicorns. These connections help build global connectivity to Indian business and facilitate India&#39;s integration into global value chains.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Barriers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While these factors reinforce each other, many barriers remain – and they could cause the multiplier effect to stall. Consider three major bumps in the road and the actions needed.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unbalanced growth&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Despite impressive growth numbers at the national level, the economic benefits have been highly unequal. The top 10% of Indians hold &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;77%&lt;/a>; of the national wealth. Almost &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;2 people every second&lt;/a>; are pushed into poverty because of health care costs alone. India&#39;s population density — amongst the highest in the world — exacerbates the zero-sum nature of resource allocation and environmental stresses. Regional imbalances — southern and western India growing 12% faster than northern and eastern India — will magnify over time. Superimpose on this linguistic fault-lines, new inter-regional tensions could surface. Handling these will require deft management of the political economy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other imbalances are growing because of divisive politics. An increasingly assertive form of &lt;a href=&quot;https://frontline.thehindu.com/columns/india-this-side-ganesh-devy-putting-the-useless-to-use-the-divisive-politics-of-the-word-hindutva/article67045226.ece&quot;>;Hindutva ideology&lt;/a>; is overshadowing core issues such as job-creation, enhancing productivity and shared economic benefits. The root cause of this problem was a belief in large sections of society that what started as affirmative action projects in a newly independent India should have had sunset clauses leading to discontent over minority appeasement by political leaders. The pendulum has now swung in the other direction creating new challenges of exclusion and identity politics. For many India-watchers it hasn&#39;t helped that India has declined in its position on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rsf.org/en/index&quot;>;World Press Freedom Index&lt;/a>;. Consequently, potentially, bottled-up sentiments in large sections of the disaffected and minority segments of the population can explode, triggering a downward spiral. Such developments can undermine objectives of shared prosperity. For international investors and trade partners, this can add a risk premium of majoritarianism in a country with as much religious, linguistic and socio-cultural diversity as India. More significantly, these developments exhaust political capital, which can otherwise be leveraged for social and economic transformation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are at least two solutions to these challenges. One is of political parties moving away from identity politics to inclusive growth and job-creation as the most reliable means of winning over the widest swath of the country&#39;s vast population. Two, India sees a constant flow of state-level elections, which distorts public dialogue by skewing it away from longer-term economic growth-oriented perspectives. Streamlining and bunching elections will give breathing space to public discourse and push political leadership and voters toward longer-term horizons.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unrealized demographic potential&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/india/despite-world-beating-growth-indias-lack-jobs-threatens-its-young-2023-05-30/&quot;>;Less than half&lt;/a>; of urban workers have full-time jobs, while far too much of India&#39;s employment is in under-productive informal sectors. Education, skill-building, and health care are grossly inadequate. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://do3n1uzkew47z.cloudfront.net/siteassets/pdf/ISR_Report_2023.pdf&quot;>;India Skills Report 2023&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;found only half of young Indians are employable. Even the “crown jewels” technology services sector is vulnerable; demand for outsourcing is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/ai-why-india-risks-falling-behind-in-the-tech-race/d8236bc2-16bb-11ee-9de3-ba1fa29e9bec_story.html&quot;>;falling&lt;/a>; and the labor-cost arbitrage model will be disrupted by secular shifts towards cloud computing and AI for coding and routine functions. Alarmingly, India&#39;s female labor participation rate has been in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/SL.TLF.CACT.FE.ZS?locations=IN&quot;>;steady decline&lt;/a>;, having dropped from 32% in 2005 to 19% in 2021.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Emulating, say, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.rmresults.com/a-spotlight-on-vietnams-transformation-in-education&quot;>;Vietnam&lt;/a>;, public and private investment in upskilling must be prioritized, which could add &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dw.com/en/india-youth-lack-skills/a-56879385&quot;>;$570 billion&lt;/a>; to the Indian economy. A major handicap has been manufacturing — a key jobs creator in comparable economies — which has plateaued at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot;>;13.3% of GDP&lt;/a>;. The current infrastructure thrust, policy reforms, geopolitical drivers and capital influx could help unlock Indian manufacturing, but the barriers discussed here must be removed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In emerging sectors, the surge of potential in AI could be an opportunity for India to take leadership in a cutting-edge area, given the &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/50-global-hubs-for-top-ai-talent&quot;>;emergent AI talent hubs&lt;/a>; in the country that can be massively expanded, paired with the &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/01/which-countries-are-leading-the-data-economy&quot;>;vast pools of data&lt;/a>; that accumulate in India. Cultural and organizational changes are needed to create on-ramps for women in the workforce and retain them. Such projects have long gestation periods, so a focused and disciplined long-term plan is required.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unrealized ease-of-business and innovation potential&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Doing business in India has improved, but many challenges remain. Land acquisition can stall construction projects and the courts are slow-moving institutions. Land records may be non-existing or outdated and environmental clearances have created additional barriers. On top of this, contract enforcement remains challenging. According to an index created by The Economist, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/05/02/the-2023-crony-capitalism-index&quot;>;India ranks 10th&lt;/a>; in the prevalence of crony capitalism, in spite of the large-scale liberalization of the past three decades. A legacy of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot;>;protectionism&lt;/a>; still persists.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;India&#39;s state capacity needs change. Contrary to popular perception, the Indian state is not big and bungling, but weak and waning. Institutions — from regulators to civic bodies to the judiciary — often juggle conflicting demands and are playing catch-up to market and social realities. Many important decisions are made with a crisis as a frame of reference and India&#39;s story of victories is often of individual heroism amidst institutional failure. Making India&#39;s state machinery cutting-edge may well be India&#39;s pivotal project.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In sum, while barriers remain, the positive forces can, indeed, create a domino effect: “Inevitable India” is within reach. India&#39;s greatest challenge will be to make its inevitability tangible and believable to the many constituencies that wish to see India succeed. To get from “Incredible India” — aimed at tourists — to now bring the global economy to its door, India next campaign ought to be “Credible India.”&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>