<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Managing Anxiety When There&rsquo;s No Room for Error]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_27_57363406.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;fStop 图片 - Brian Cassie/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当您的工作岗位必须不惜一切代价避免错误时 &amp;#8212;想想医疗、安全、金融和运输行业——人们很容易害怕制作一个。但有一些方法可以建设性地降低潜在错误的风险并减少您的焦虑。首先，区分严重和不太严重的潜在错误，并重点关注前者。然后采用系统和习惯来减轻这些威胁。获得他人的支持来解决您的弱点，同时找到发挥您优势的解决方案。与关注相同问题的其他人合作。解决任何自我破坏行为，例如不寻求帮助。通过消除大部分小错误的小行动，减少因小错误担忧而造成的干扰。最后，考虑一种你可以犯一些无后果错误的爱好。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres -no-room-for-error?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在某些领域，错误是正常的，而且代价也不是很高。如果设计师在制作精美的封面图片之前多次重新开始，发明家在找到可行的原型之前尝试了一百个原型，或者企业家从一个想法转向另一个想法，那么这并不重要。关于客户的反馈。在这些角色中，失败是成功之路的一部分。在其他情况下，风险可能会受到一个人较低级别的责任的限制。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是那些期望完美的角色呢？没有人希望他们的神经外科医生犯错误，或者他们的刑事辩护律师休息一天。会计师不能向美国国税局、美国证券交易委员会或任何其他监管机构提交有缺陷的财务报表。一些安全角色专注于监视潜在威胁，成功意味着永远不会错过任何威胁。你的工作可能属于这一类。或者，也许工作中出错的后果并不那么严重，但你觉得这是因为老板刻薄、裁员迫在眉睫或根深蒂固的焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你如何应对这种感觉你根本就不能搞砸吗？我的建议是使用策略来减少犯严重错误的机会，同时减少对此的担忧。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;焦虑的基础知识&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;让我们从焦虑如何产生的一些基本背景开始。首先，过度思考并不能解决问题。它让我们陷入瘫痪，而不是让我们动员起来。其次，人们常常沉迷于一种特定类型的错误或威胁，而忽视其他类型的错误或威胁，因为恐惧会缩小我们的注意力。最后， &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/gretchenrubin_one-of-my-aphorisms-is-action-is-an-antidote-activity-6651614263683137537-w-8Y?trk=posts_directory&quot;>;行动是焦虑的解药&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;错误代价高昂或危险的工作（例如医学、会计、工程或安全）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse. com/books/316156/the-anxiety-toolkit-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;有时会吸引天生认真负责、勤奋且善于把事​​情做好的人。但对于已经具有这种性格类型的人来说，时刻保持谨慎可能会很困难。这有点像父母“小心”的告诫会让本来就谨慎或焦虑的孩子变得更加紧张。如果您的培训或机构专注于消除错误，这可能会加剧您的完美主义和焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是您可以采取的措施来减轻紧张感。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;区分大和小小错误&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果你考虑一下你可能犯的每一个错误，它会让你分心，忽略那些你最应该害怕的错误。如果你经常采取行动来减少犯最严重错误的风险，你的精神负担就会减轻。要确定要优先考虑哪些风险，请考虑那些容易想到的风险以及经常被忽视的风险，例如机会成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他一些人们看不到的、有些相关的主要风险类别。一是前国务卿唐纳德·拉姆斯菲尔德所说的“未知的未知”：来自意想不到的情况的风险，以至于不会被考虑。另一个是“你不知道你不知道什么”，指的是你没有意识到的盲点，或者&lt;a href=&quot;/2012/05/discover-what-you-need-to-know ”当您认为自己完全理解某件事，但实际上没有理解时&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建立适当的机制来减轻这些风险。例如，每月安排一次与同事的会议，讨论您如何处理困难案例，以此发现您遗漏的任何潜在风险。在你的日历上安排一个定期会议，并期望你将讨论复杂的决策，将确保这一切得以完成。考虑一些例子，并询问您在自己的角色中可能会遇到哪些类似情况：也许您不知道学生可能会以与您预期不同的方式解释指令，从而导致您的实验室出现危险情况。您不知道手术室中的巡回护士会使用他们熟悉的程序，而不是您经常使用的程序，从而导致混乱或错过重要步骤。您不知道软件提供商会在重要截止日期的前一天推出有缺陷的更新并破坏您所依赖的系统。您现在可以做什么来确保不犯这些错误？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;谨慎的人可以重新训练自己寻找并规避最严重的风险。但这需要一种超越他人通常做法的心理能力，并能够容忍不确定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;采用降低风险的系统和习惯&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;而不是思考通过意志力减少错误，永远不会有糟糕的一天，创建不依赖于那种不切实际的机器人完美的系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有证据表明，诸如 &lt;a href=&quot;/podcast/2010 /01/using-checklists-to-prevent-fa.html&quot;>;例如，清单可以减少错误&lt;/a>;，但&lt;a href=&quot;/2010/02/draftwhat-sort-of-checklist-sh&quot; >;在特定领域未得到充分利用&lt;/a>;。如果您正在寻找灵感，请考虑如何调整在其他行业或角色中采取的行动。例如，心脏监护仪和呼吸机等医疗设备通常包含冗余传感器和警报器，以检测故障并提供及时警报。您的角色如何才能更早地收到或自动重复警告信号？航空等行业对未遂事件有严格的报告要求。如果一篇文章因重大事实错误而即将付印，或者一个项目在工作人员通宵达旦后才勉强按时完成，您是否应该这样做？什么是最有用的并且真正专注于学习而不是指责？ &lt;a href=&quot;https://toddkashdan.com/the-art-of-insubordination/&quot;>;自学科学&lt;/a>;如何建立多元化的团队，分享相反的观点，勇敢地表达担忧，并进行健康的辩论。创建一种奖励人们征求和积极强化不寻常观点的文化。当有人指出您不知道的事情时，请特别注意鼓励他们将来继续这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;获得支持来解决您的弱点&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当我还是一名治疗师时，我的弱点始终是记录保存。我讨厌记录。我的大脑运转得很快，感觉录音一直在拖慢我的速度。我更喜欢将所有精力投入到与客户面对面的互动中。如果我再次担任这个角色，我将不再尝试自己在该领域进行改进，并接受我需要一个支持人员来让我保持记录的正轨。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，如果您&#39;如果你是唯一知道如何扮演关键角色的人，而你又不擅长将你的流程系统化，那么你可能会得到帮助来做到这一点。如果你不是最好的沟通者，但正在向客户或老板做一个必须获胜的推销，你可以请导师、朋友，甚至是具有更多这些技能的人工智能聊天机器人来帮助你更有说服力吗？同样，如果冲突管理不是强项，但团队内讧可能会导致关键项目脱轨，也许您可​​以聘请一位顾问，您可以根据需要提供建议，甚至可能实施建议。或者，如果您凌乱的办公室确实存在丢失文件的风险，那么请专业的组织者进来，每隔几个月就给您一个新的开始。请记住，帮助您避免错误的不仅仅是您自己的意志力和勤奋。您可以招募一群同事 - 甚至朋友、家人和技术 - 来帮助您。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;发挥您的优势&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I &lt;a href =&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/645534/stress-free-productivity-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;经常争论&lt;/a>;利用你的优势来减轻你的劣势，这可以延伸到如何避免错误。例如，如果你在视觉上有创造力，你可以创建视觉提醒，或者如果幽默是一种优势，那么幽默的。只需谷歌“有趣的航空公司安全视频”即可找到如何让人们注意严肃的安全建议的示例。如果你善于交际并且善于与人相处，你会如何利用这种天赋来获取其他人通常保守秘密的信息，比如告诉你为什么你可能不想与某个特定的个人或团体合作？相比之下，如果你比较内向，你如何利用你的自然倾向去倾听和观察而不是说话，以注意到迫在眉睫的问题，或者让人们更有可能信任你，愿意透露担忧或错误，而不必担心你会告诉你其他的？考虑一下您的最大优势如何帮助您解决特定问题。为了确定自己的不寻常优势，您可以问自己一个问题：您愿意做哪些 95% 的人不愿意做的事情？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;解决自我破坏行为&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h2>; &lt;p>;当我们对某件事感到非常焦虑时，我们经常会进行自我破坏，从而增加担心的事情发生的可能性。例如，您知道自己有弱点，但您不会寻求可以帮助您解决的导师或主管，因为您不想引起人们的注意。或者，由于尴尬和耻辱，或者您认为自己应该坚持下去，因此您不会为自己的抑郁症寻求缓解，但这会增加在糟糕的一天犯错误的机会。或者你讨厌浪费钱，所以你不会尝试可能解决问题但不能保证的选项。或者你是一个完美主义者，所以你不会寻求解决可以改进但完美似乎不可能的问题。发挥创意来克服自我破坏，并&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/be-kinder-to-yourself&quot;>;富有同情心地与自己交谈&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;与关注相同问题的其他人合作&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当您考虑错误时，您可能主要是在个人或团队层面上这样做。 “我怎样才能防止自己或同事弄错这件重要的事情呢？”但为了寻求更好的解决方案——以及与你有同样恐惧的团体的友情——可以考虑参与更大的努力，以减少你所在领域的错误，比如加入一个负责投诉和纪律处分的委员会，或者为你所在领域的人员制定新的指导方针。角色。教学通常也会改善我们自己的实践，因此请考虑寻找机会向他人传授您的工作是如何以最小化或消除错误的方式完成的。在行业会议上就此撰写演讲或主持小组讨论。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;通过采取简单的行动来减轻这些风险，从而减少小威胁的干扰&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;尽管大多数你的注意力应该集中在最大的威胁上，一些简单的策略可以减少犯小错误的风险，这样它们就不会分散你的注意力。您需要采取简单的措施来帮助减少小问题的发生频率，然后接受您无法消除所有小问题的事实。摘取低垂的果实。例如，如果医生担心忘记患者和家庭成员的姓名，他们可能会在互动过程中做笔记时将姓名写在每页的顶部。解决潜在的小错误，从而释放你的思维能力来思考和防止更大的错误。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;考虑一种允许你犯错误的爱好&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;为了让你的生活更加平衡，你可能想要从事一项不会因为错误和错误的开始而付出代价的活动。例如，我最近开始从事蔬菜园艺，并且对低成功率完全可以接受的兴趣感到耳目一新。毕竟，一包一百颗种子只需几美元。朋友的朋友是一位狂热的冲浪者，他满足于错过或放弃数十次波浪，最终得到一些好的冲浪机会，这是他作为初创公司首席财务官的日常工作的一个很好的解药，他试图确保公司不会运转没钱了。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;当人们期望完美而错误代价高昂时，人们很容易害怕犯错误。你可能会因此失眠或者逃避领导和增加的责任。但有一些方法可以建设性地降低潜在错误的风险并减少您的焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Manage Your Team&rsquo;s Workload After Layoffs]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_98413121-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Susanne Walstrom/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;在裁员的情况下，幸存下来的人通常会接手被解雇的同事留下的工作。与此同时，这些被解雇的幸存者常常在幸存者内疚、焦虑和士气低落中挣扎。简而言之，裁员之后，那些能给予的人越来越少的人会被要求更多。当涉及到关键人才的倦怠和保留时，这会导致灾难。在本文中，作者概述了正确调整&lt;span data-markjs=&quot;true&quot;>;团队工作负载大小的四种策略。&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt; br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;面对经济不确定性收入增长放缓，公司继续宣布裁员，影响数千名员工。这些裁员已经超出了科技行业的范围&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-companies-conducting-layoffs-in-2023-heres-the-list-11673288386&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;其他行业&lt;/a>;对于裁员受害者来说无疑是一场悲剧。但对于留下来的工人来说，它们也很糟糕。裁员幸存者经常与裁员带来的心理影响作斗争，包括内疚，焦虑和抑郁&lt;/a>;。在&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/what-c​​ompanies-still-get-wrong-about-layoffs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;信任和士气下降&lt;/a>;的情况下，他们他们也仍处于紧张状态，恐惧地等待着新一轮的削减。通常情况下，裁员幸存者会接手被解雇的同事留下的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;简而言之，当公司能够给予的员工越来越少时，他们往往会向员工提出更多的要求。当涉及到倦怠、关键人才的保留以及团队的长期成功时，这种动态会导致灾难。为了团队的健康和绩效，必须评估裁员后团队的能力，并采取重要措施来调整团队的工作量。具体方法如下：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;确定要推迟的项目和计划&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在超负荷状态下，埋头苦干以减少工作量是一种自然的压力反应。然而，退后一步并确定您的团队应该在哪些方面投入宝贵的时间和精力至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;首先与您的团队创建一份包含所有正在进行的计划和项目的全面列表，并讨论每个计划的内容一个人解决、创造或改进。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;接下来，根据这些计划的预期影响和每个项目对组织的潜在利益对这些计划进行排名。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;最后，确定哪些计划可以推迟但不能实施。与暂时暂停可能会产生后果且难以逆转的情况相比，稍后可以轻松恢复。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;由于&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/07/how-susceptible-are-you-to -the-sunk-cost-fallacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;沉没成本谬误&lt;/a>;，我们不愿意放弃已经投资的策略或行动方针。然而，许多项目可以在接到通知后轻松暂停和恢复。承认这一区别将使您和您的团队能够克服这种谬论并更快地做出决策，以便您可以专注于最关键的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，当您选择要推迟的项目时，请确保保留一个或多个项目面向未来的项目。这些项目通常是团队灵感和动力的源泉，为他们的工作注入能量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;与老板协调管理你的“货架空间”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;超市和零售店自然地受到货架空间的限制，除非删除现有产品，否则无法添加新产品。领导者应该应用类似的原则来管理团队的工作量，但很少这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下次你的老板向你的团队提出某些要求时，询问新的要求是否需要立即关注。如果确实如此，请让您的经理帮助您在团队的其他任务中优先考虑该请求。例如，您可能会说：“团队还在致力于这三项其他举措。有没有可以放弃或推迟的项目来为这个项目腾出空间？”给你的老板一个选择可以给他们一种&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33400628/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;控制感&lt;/a>;这比断然拒绝更有效。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，养成主动共享任何请求的估计资源需求的习惯。大多数领导者都没有意识到团队为满足他们的需求所付出的努力和费用。当您主动与老板沟通资源需求时，他们的询问会变得更加挑剔，从而显着减少您团队的工作量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;发掘团队的全套人才&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;团队通常不知道他们队伍中的全套技能、知识和能力。当您最需要这些人才时，如果这些人才得不到利用，就会损害团队的生产力和绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;要解决此问题并释放团队的潜力，请安排一次会议来发掘团队中的所有人才。给团队成员 10 分钟的时间反思并写下他们的才能和技能。接下来，要求每个团队成员与团队分享他们的列表。当他们这样做时，鼓励团队添加他们在同事身上认识到的但他们没有提到的额外才能或技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这个简单的练习让人大开眼界，揭示隐藏的才能并帮助团队识别当他们需要帮助时，他们的首选同事。这也为所有参与者提供了一种充满活力的体验，因为同事很少以直接和集中的方式讨论和承认彼此的才能和技能。根据我们与 30 多个团队和数百名参与者一起推动这项练习的经验，每个参与者都拥有令人振奋的经历，因为他们拥有自己不知道的或被同事认为理所当然的才能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这个简单的练习可以显着提高团队的参与度和生产力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;简化、简化、简化&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;面对繁重的工作负载，团队常常忽视简化的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;根据 &lt;a href=&quot;https://webinar.gartner.com/463005/agenda/session/1092611&quot;>;Gartner 数据&lt;/a>;，27% 的员工和 38% 的经理对不断出现的问题感到不知所措。信息负担不断加重。与您的团队讨论如何简化沟通和信息过载。例如，同意将任何书面记录（例如提案或会议预读）限制为一页摘要，以清楚地强调其在当前背景下的相关性可能会有所帮助。此外，在会议或聊天中——意见经常泛滥并出现不必要的复杂性——鼓励参与者将他们的想法提炼为本质。通过询问“你能用两句话概括你的建议的本质吗？”来提示团队成员抓住问题的症结。当您与团队讨论任何工作流或产品时，不断地挑战自己，通过询问“我们如何缩短或简化这个过程？”来简化它？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二个经常被忽视的领域是寻求内部客户的意见您为他们提供的解决方案或服务中可以简化哪些内容。令人惊讶的是，他们的观点可以阐明您的团队可能忽视的不必要的复杂性。例如，荷兰公司 AFAS Software 定期与客户举行会议，专门讨论他们应该从软件解决方案中删除哪些功能或元素。这种积极主动的方法可确保他们的软件保持最新状态，并且避免不必要的复杂性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;裁员对每个相关人员来说都是困难和压力的。但通过实施上述策略，您可以帮助您的团队免受工作超负荷的破坏性影响。您的努力将有助于消除消耗性的低价值工作，确保您的团队能够专注于最关键的工作，并提高他们的士气和参与度。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out for These 3 Gender Biases in Performance Reviews]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anja Sušanj 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;绩效评估过程中经常会出现三种偏见，对女性的影响尤其严重，尤其是当她们选择利用所提供的灵活性时通过混合和远程工作。这些偏见是&lt;em>;经验偏见&lt;/em>;，它会导致审阅者高估那些易于定义的任务； &lt;em>;邻近偏见&lt;/em>;，这导致他们认为在他们周围的人做着最重要的工作；以及群体内/群体外偏见，这导致他们对他们认为属于他们认同的群体的人给予优惠待遇。本文基于作者对一家大型跨国咨询集团的研究，解释了这些偏见的本质，并提供了如何克服这些偏见的建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt; div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a >; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;由于女性继续承担大部分照护负担，许多人受益于混合和远程工作的灵活性，这使她们能够继续成为全职劳动力的一部分，同时花更多的时间在家里。从理论上讲，这是个好消息，因为全职员工往往晋升的频率更高，而解雇的频率则更少——但是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the- Hybrid-workplace&quot;>;实际上&lt;/a>;情况并非如此。为什么？因为当女性今天利用混合和远程工作选项时，她们会受到&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/6-ways-to-make-performance-reviews-more-fair&quot;>;偏见&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp ;这会渗透到绩效评估过程中，并导致他们被评判&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-gender-bias-corrupts-performance-reviews-and-what-to-do-about-it&quot;>;不公平&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在最近为一家在全球拥有数十万名员工的跨国公司进行的咨询项目中，我亲眼目睹了这个问题。在该项目期间，公司（我将其称为 HAPI Consulting，以保持匿名）正在进行大规模重组，我向首席执行官、他的高管和董事会报告。在他们的支持下，我收集并分析了混合工作环境（大流行前和大流行后）中的绩效评估数据，并在这种背景下确定了三种损害女性及其职业前景的特定偏见。我将在下面依次探讨它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;经验偏差&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我观察到的第一个偏差就是我们所说的&lt;a href=&quot;/2015/05/fooled-by-experience&quot; >;&lt;em>;经验偏见&lt;/em>;，&lt;/a>;其中一个方面是高估了易于定义的任务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我发现，这种形式的偏见在 HAPI 的绩效评估中很普遍咨询——由于重组，许多员工被迫暂停日常工作。在那段时期，评审者评判员工的标准是他们如何选择重新集中精力。总体而言，男性选择了更容易被认可的工作。他们将更多时间花在引人注目的外部任务上，例如在行业会议上发言以及接受记者、博主和播客的采访。当涉及到短期成功衡量标准时，这些任务很容易审查。与此同时，&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/research-women-took-on-even-more-invisible-work-during-the-pandemic&quot;>;女性&lt;/a>;将更多时间花在不太明显的内部任务上，例如增强团队凝聚力以帮助项目重回正轨，并为团队成员提供心理上安全的空间来提出问题并处理公司正在进行的重组要素。这些任务的时间表较长，并且在短期内更难以评估。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些选择容易产生偏见。例如，很容易理解在重大会议上发表演讲的人（可能是男性）如何立即为公司提供可衡量的利益。事实上，男性在户外活动中发言的可能性是女性的三倍。但是，衡量和评估某人（可能是女性）为修复团队动力或防止最终可能影响数百或数千名员工的根深蒂固的问题而开始进行的长期工作有多容易？不用说，考虑到经验偏见的本质，HAPI Consulting 的评审员在绩效评审中更频繁地赞扬这些人在工作中取得了成功。更具体地说，与女性同时评价男性和其他女性时相比，评价其他男性的男性对他们的评价平均比女性高 12%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在领导层的支持下，我测试了几种干预措施，旨在帮助公司的审阅者纠正这种偏见。虽然一些干预措施失败了，但有两项干预措施在统计上有显着机会（置信区间为 95% 或以上）减少该公司的偏见。然后要求他们跟踪每周所做的事情，并在团队其他成员和上级主管可以看到的虚拟白板上进行。通过这种方式，那些为团队凝聚力等不太容易定义的结果做出贡献的人仍然可以指出他们随着时间的推移所做的努力的记录，让所有人都可以看到。该白板可以记录重要的工作，即使它不容易用传统的目标和指标来描述。这在绩效评估时很有帮助。即使员工未能达到上次绩效评估中设定的目标，仍然记录了他们的所有努力和成就，根据事后调查结果，这有助于评估者更好地理解绩效的价值。 （大多数）女性从事的模棱两可的内部工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二个旨在帮助员工更好地描述自己的努力。本周初，对于他们正在开展的每个项目，员工被要求在虚拟白板上提供两种不同的估计：每项任务需要多长时间才能完成及其难度级别（高、中或低）。例如，员工可能会确定他们一周要处理的三个项目，并根据任务类型和估计难度分配他们计划在每个项目上花费的时间。在每周结束时，员工被要求重新审视他们的估计，注意他们的时间实际分配情况以及任务最终的难度，并反思他们的预测与“实际”之间差异的原因。这种做法使员工能够回顾他们记录的预测，反思记录所显示的内容与他们的看法相比，并微调他们准确描绘自己努力的能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最初，数据结果表明，女性对任务所需时间的估计更为准确，尽管她们经常高估任务的难度。与此同时，人们低估了一项任务所需的时间和难度。干预后，女性准确识别任务难度的可能性增加了 28 倍，而男性准确识别任务难度的可能性增加了 12.5 倍。此外，男性准确估计任务所需时间的可能性是女性的 7 倍，而女性在这方面没有显着差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;邻近偏差&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;另一种形式的偏差我观察到的偏见是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/employee-relations/pages/preventing-proximity-bias-in-a-hybrid-workplace.aspx&quot;>;&lt;em >;邻近偏见&lt;/em>;，&lt;/a>;，或者认为在你的物理轨道上的人做最重要的工作的倾向。混合工作环境加剧了这种偏见，并对 HAPI Consulting 的女性不利，因为男性比女性更有可能进入办公室。评论者倾向于对女性远程工作时所做的事情表示怀疑，或者至少是困惑，而他们倾向于对男性进行无罪推定，并认为他们更专注、更有效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;女性进入办公室的次数与男性一样多，审查人员给她们分配的成就水平在统计上比男性分配的成就水平低 3%。当女性进入办公室的人数多于男性时，评论者似乎认为她们这样做只是因为她们在照顾自己，并希望“在谈判桌上占有一席之地”以捍卫自己在公司重组中的地位。相反，当进入办公室的男性人数高于平均水平时，他们会被视为强有力的领导者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了解决邻近偏见问题，我对员工进行了一项调查，以衡量他们对以下几种选择的偏好：更多的在线聚会、每个人都应该在办公室的“主播日”，或者更多的异地团队建设机会。员工们希望公司设立一个主播日，公司也这么做了。这种干预导致邻近偏差在统计上显着下降，这在下一个绩效评估周期中可以观察到。除了让员工每周在虚拟白板上发布他们当前的项目之外，团队还被要求举行每周会议，在会议期间他们将讨论上周的三项成就、本周的目标以及他们在工作中面临的三项挑战。试图实现它们。通过让每个人都在做的工作得到更加平等的关注，无论他们在哪里做，这些会议帮助公司抵制邻近偏见。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;群体内/群体外偏见&lt;/h2>; &lt;p >;渗透到远程工作绩效评估中的第三种偏见是&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2000-08465-006&quot;>;&lt;em>;in-group/out-group偏见&lt;/em>;，&lt;/a>;或给予您认为属于&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11752497/&quot;>;您认同的群体&lt;/一个>;。毫不奇怪，远程工作的员工，尤其是那些离开办公室并跨州工作的员工，越来越多地被视为外部群体的成员，而且他们的年度绩效评估分数平均低 20 %。集团内部人员将获得福利，包括纵向晋升、横向晋升（为员工提供学习新技能和承担更有价值的任务的新机会，使他们能够更好地进行纵向晋升）以及奖金（例如股权）在公司里。男性和女性都会受到这种形式的偏见的影响，但由于男性往往更容易被视为领导者，因此他们比女性更容易加入内部群体。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了增加一种领导感为此，该公司发起了一项名为“我是 HAPI 咨询，我们是 HAPI 咨询”的活动。该活动的一个要素是要求员工回答简单、有时甚至是愚蠢的问题，以便团队能够了解他们之间的共性。例如，在会议上提供最新情况时，员工可能还必须补充问题“狗还是猫？”的答案。或“今年你的愿望清单上有什么？”这样的问题提供了一些每个人都可以分享的难忘时刻，无论他们是在办公室还是远程工作，他们让更多的人体验到-集体时刻。引人注目的是，这种做法使员工对内部群体的归属感提高了 14%，并使员工对&lt;em>;其他&lt;/em>;员工属于内部群体的看法提高了 17%。在绩效评估时，评估者还被要求回忆起他们与要评估的人的一件共同点。我们发现，这种简单的干预措施（意味着从共同点开始评估）将公司绩效评估中的性别歧视减少了几个百分点。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;男性和女性对工作场所的体验往往不同，无论是面对面还是虚拟。为了在动态环境中为您的公司吸纳并支持最优秀的人才，请务必仔细查看数据，警惕本文中讨论的三种偏见，并找出导致您高估努力的做法某些群体的。您从中获得的见解不仅可以帮助您更公平地对待女性，而且还可以减少可预见的意外，提高工作时间，并提高顺利领导团队和您的公司取得成功的效率。&lt;/p>; &lt; !-- 引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[28 Questions to Ask Your Boss in Your One-on-Ones]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1398880959.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;NicoElNino/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;经理与其直接下属之间良好的一对一会议可以满足员工的实际和个人需求，有利于他们的绩效、成长和良好发展- 存在，以及他们的团队和更广泛的组织的成功。然而，由于经理通常是主持这些会议的人，因此员工的需求经常被忘记。然后由员工提出问题以获得他们需要的关注。作者的观点是：研究指出了可以推动最佳对话的二十八个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28 -questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions- to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当 Brianna 开始担任新角色时，她被告知她将与她的经理 Jayden 定期进行一对一会议（1:1）。她对这个消息表示欢迎；她认为这是一个与新老板结盟、支持和指导的绝佳机会。但她的希望很快就破灭了。在他们的初次会面中，杰登只关注项目更新，然后给她分配了一些额外的任务。这种模式持续了几周，布丽安娜经常在会议结束时感到自己的发展受到微观管理和得不到支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可悲的是，这个故事是我们在 1 的研究中从员工那里听到的许多故事的综合体。 : 经理与其直接下属之间的 1 联系。正如我们中的一个人（史蒂夫）在一本新书中所描述的，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Glad-Met-Art-Science-Meetings/dp/0197641873&quot;>;&lt;em>;很高兴我们相遇： 1:1 会议的艺术与科学&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;一次好的一对一会议可以满足员工的实际和个人需求（实用：信息、指导、一致；个人：需要得到考虑、尊重、信任和支持）。因此，这些会议是员工成长和支持的重要来源，并促进团队和更广泛的组织的繁荣和成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，只有当会议包含以下频繁对话时，这些好处才能实现： a href=&quot;/2022/11/make-the-most-of-your-one-on-one-meetings&quot;>;满足这些员工需求&lt;/a>;。由于一对一通常是由经理推动的，因此他们通常会专注于解决他们而不是员工最关心的问题。尤其如此，因为经理们很少接受有关如何良好召开这些会议的培训，因此他们常常只是重复他们自己经历过的功能失调的做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你处于布丽安娜的位置 - 如果你的老板是1:1 的方式让你感到不受支持和无人倾听——你应该感到自己有能力将对话引向你的需求。您可以通过提出巧妙的问题来做到这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;要问的问题&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;基于已发表的研究以及我们从近 200 名员工收集的有关重要主题的数据，以 1:1 的方式提出，我们确定了七个大类中的 28 个关键问题，以帮助您从与老板的沟通中获得最大价值。您可以使用、改编这些内容，并将其转化为您认为合适的声音。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;寻求指导和意见&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;使用这些问题向您的经理寻求有关任何任务或任务的帮助。您遇到困难的项目，或表达您对额外资源、投入或支持的需求。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;我在 X 方面遇到了一些挑战和挣扎。您能帮我考虑如何导航吗并成功解决 X 问题？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您能否就如何获得更多支持（人员、时间、资金）来帮助解决 Y 问题提出任何想法和想法？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您认为如何我的想法Z？您对如何改进有什么建议吗？或者，您是否有我应该考虑的替代想法？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;明确优先事项和期望&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;为了确保您步入正轨并高效工作，请确保您和您的团队经理在同一页面上。要求澄清从他们的角度来看哪些任务需要你最集中的关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;4&quot;>; &lt;li>;鉴于我的任务，我现在应该优先考虑什么，你可以吗帮助我理解原因吗？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;当您审查我的工作量时，我是否承担了正确的项目和任务？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;从您的角度来看，我是否有望实现我的目标和您的期望？是否有必要重新调整重点？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;对于我正在从事的项目，我是否可能遗漏了任何背景信息？例如，进行项目 X 的​​原因是什么？&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;与组织及其战略保持一致&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;提出问题以理解您的角色与组织更广泛的战略目标以及领导者思考未来的方式有何关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;8&quot;>; &lt;li>;树上（或其他方面）正在发生什么组织的各个部分）这对我在执行关键任务时了解是否有帮助？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;为了更好地帮助我了解总体情况，我正在做的工作或您刚完成的任务如何让我适应更广泛的目标和战略？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;鉴于其对我的角色的潜在影响，您认为管理团队正在研究或认为我目前应该了解什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;作为一家公司，您认为我应该了解哪些新的战略重点？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;寻求成长机会和职业发展&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;来与您围绕您的职业短期和长期目标进行思考（无论多么不成熟）的会议，并询问您的经理您应该采取哪些步骤来实现这一目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;12&quot;>; &lt;li>;我会重视您的建议。我可以做些什么来让自己做好准备，以获得更大的机会或追求我的 X 兴趣？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;当您思考组织的发展方向时，您对我应该如何改进和发展以实现最佳协调有什么想法吗？ ？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您认为我有哪些优势？它们对未来有何帮助？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;从您的角度来看，我下一步的职业发展目标应该是什么？您为什么这样做推荐该职位？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我们如何确保充分利用我的技能来支持团队和组织？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我们如何确保我的全部潜力得到充分发挥实现了吗？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;获取有关您绩效的反馈&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;与您的经理联系，了解您的绩效情况。您不应该将每次会议都变成正式的绩效评估，但如果您的经理自己没有这样做，定期检查和校准很重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;18&quot;>; &lt;li>;我是吗？满足您的期望吗？我很高兴了解您对我的工作表现的看法。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;关于我在 X 或 Y 任务上的表现，您可以与我分享哪些反馈？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您觉得当涉及到 A 或 B 时，我有哪些地方被忽视了？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;当你反思我在工作中所做的事情时，我应该开始、停止或继续做什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ ol>; &lt;h3>;建立关系&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一对一是您与经理建立和培养关系的关键场所。在会议开始或结束时分配时间与您的经理亲自联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;22&quot;>; &lt;li>;您今天过得怎么样？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;事情进展得怎么样？你总体来说？你还好吗？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;工作之外你对什么事情感到兴奋？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;关于我，你有什么想了解的吗？ （如果需要，请准备好说“我不愿意分享这一点，但是您应该了解我的其他信息。”）&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;提供支持&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;考虑如何帮助你的经理实现他们的目标并履行他们的职责。管理者需要帮助、保证和支持来优化他们的效率和绩效。就像您期望经理支持您一样，看看您可以如何向他们伸出援手。这也将增加您在 1:1 中获得所需内容的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;26&quot;>; &lt;li>;接下来 X 天您的优先事项是什么？我可以做些什么来帮助您解决这个问题？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我可以在哪里为您提供支持？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;有什么事情可以让您彻夜难眠吗？&lt;/li>; &lt; /ol>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;如何使用问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;对于每次一对一会议，选择一个或两个要关注的类别。您无法在每次会议中都解决所有问题，因此您需要在给定时间轮换或选择最相关的问题。同样，从问题中谨慎选择——不需要一次问所有问题。随着时间的推移，您只需从所有类别中进行抽样即可。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不要犹豫，跟进经理对您问题的答复。一个好的后续行动通常只是简单地问“为什么？”您将收集有关日常工作背后的基本原理、动机、假设和总体情况的战略见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与经理进行良好的一对一会议对于您的成功以及您的成功至关重要。您的团队和组织。提出正确的问题以确保这些会议为您提供所需的内容，这会对您的工作体验产生巨大影响 - 帮助您保持敬业度，加深您对自己在组织中的角色和地位的理解，并改善您与经理的关系 - 而不是&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot; https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style= &quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies That Replace People with AI Will Get Left Behind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1300035600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;piranka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司将人工智能融入其运营的速度如此之快，以至于在收益到来之前失业人数可能会增加。白领工人在短期内可能尤其容易受到影响。这种采用的速度为公司提供了加快创新步伐的机会，但是＆#8212;如果有足够多的公司继续进攻，那么我们就不必担心人工智能失业。采用大胆的偏见和创业心态将有助于公司找到充分利用这一时刻的敏捷性，从而保护就业机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;之后经过一番讨论，关于人工智能取代工作岗位的争论正在形成共识。从历史上看，我们从未经历过新技术带来的宏观失业，因此人工智能&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/long-run-ai-job-creator-destroyer-babak-pahlavan %3FtrackingId=6uoHh%252F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%253D%253D/?trackingId=6uoHh%2F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%3D%3D&quot;>;从长远来看不太可能让&lt;/a>;许多人失业 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com /2023/05/24/artificial-intelligence-ai-eric-schmidt-demographic-crisis-babies-labor-shortage/&quot;>;尤其是&lt;/a>;大多数发达国家的劳动年龄人口正在下降。然而，由于公司正在以非常快的速度采用 ChatGPT 和其他生成式人工智能，我们可能会看到 &lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/podcast/ripple-effect/rise-of-ai-are-robots- take-our-jobs-lynn-wu/&quot;>;短期内会导致大量工作岗位流失&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将人工智能与二十世纪初电力的兴起进行比较。工厂花了几十年的时间才将每台机器的蒸汽动力中央传动轴转换为电动机。他们必须重新组织布局才能利用新的电力技术。这个过程发生得很慢，以至于经济有时间进行调整，只有新工厂首先采用电机。随着电力创造新的就业机会，蒸汽动力工厂的下岗工人可以转移。更多的财富创造了全新的行业来吸引工人，同时也带来了更高的期望。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;二十世纪中叶计算机的传播也发生了类似的情况。它的发展速度比电气化更快，但仍然足够慢，足以防止大规模失业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能不同，因为公司将其整合到运营中的速度如此之快，以至于在收益到来之前失业可能会增加。白领工人在短期内可能尤其容易受到伤害。事实上，评论员正在描述由英伟达等先进芯片制造商推动的“人工智能淘金热”，而不是泡沫。高盛&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65102150&quot;>;最近预测&lt;/a>;公司将使用它来消除美国和欧洲当前所有工作任务的四分之一。这可能意味着数以千万计的人失业——尤其是那些认为自己的专业知识&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-negative-impact-middle-class-white- Collar-workers-2023-5?utm_medium=newsletter&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Insider%20Today%2C%20June%202%2C%202023&amp;amp;utm_term=INSIDER%20TODAY%20SEND%20LIST%20-%20ALL%20ENGAGED&quot;>;给了他们工作保障&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这留下了两种降低这种风险的可能性。首先是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/23/business/jobs-protections-artificial-intelligence.html&quot;>;政府介入&lt;/a>;，要么放慢速度人工智能的商业应用（极不可能），或者提供特殊福利计划来支持和再培训新失业者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是还有另一种经常被忽视的可能性，这种可能性不会因政府干预而产生意想不到的后果。一些公司正在迅速将生成式人工智能集成到他们的系统中，不仅是为了自动化任务，而且是为了让员工能够做比以前更多的事情，即提高他们的工作效率。对企业流程进行&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-ai-is-helping-companies-redesign-processes&quot;>;彻底的重新设计&lt;/a>;可能会激发各种新的价值创造。如果许多公司都这样做，那么作为一个社会，我们将创造足够的新就业机会来摆脱短期失业陷阱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是他们会吗？即使是最不积极进取的公司也往往很擅长削减成本。然而，创新是另一回事。过去我们不担心这个，因为我们有足够的时间让一些激进的公司逐步改变行业。随着时间的推移，他们不断创新，以弥补失业的缓慢损失。这项创新创造了新的就业机会并保持了较低的失业率。但从宏观经济角度来看，我们没有足够的时间来进行人工智能转型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，依赖政府的替代方案是让许多公司以足够快的速度进行创新，以与人工智能相同的速度创造新的就业机会。整个经济消除了现有的经济。生成式人工智能正在商业和社会中快速传播，但这种速度也意味着企业加快创新步伐的机会。如果我们有足够多的公司以这种方式进攻，那么我们就不必担心人工智能失业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，公司不会——也不应该——为了秩序而倾向于人工智能。解决宏观经济问题。但幸运的是，他们有充分的商业理由这样做。从人工智能中创造机会的公司也将实现长期繁荣。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;利用人工智能发起攻势&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们已经可以指出那些寻求人工智能创新的积极进取的公司。埃隆·马斯克 (Elon Musk) 已成为可重复使用火箭和电动汽车领域的开拓者，现在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/twitter-elon-musk-linda-yaccarino-spacex-244f0125?mod=series_elonmuskcompanies&quot; >;承诺制作&lt;/a>; Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-wants-to-see-an-ai-rival-to-google-microsoft-a299e27f? mod=hp_lista_pos1&quot;>;与微软和谷歌一样是人工智能领域的领导者&lt;/a>;。然而，马斯克是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/does-elon-musk-have-a-strategy&quot;>;一个著名的异常者&lt;/a>;，并且 Twitter 上的评判还没有定论。那么，对于一家公司来说，进攻人工智能意味着什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了回答这个问题，让我们看看是什么让公司能够善于应对我们现在所看到的各种变化。我们中的一员 (Tabrizi) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Going-Offense-Playbook-Perpetual-Innovation/dp/1646871375/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679313&amp;amp;sr=1 -1&quot;>;组建了一个研究团队&lt;/a>;，对2006年至2022年间拥有良好数据的26家规模较大的公司进行了研究。随着时间的推移，团队将公司分为高、中、低敏捷性和创新性组，并对每个组进行可比较的数据和案例研究。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;是什么让敏捷、创新的公司与那些保持中立或创新的公司区分开来。防守？该团队将敏捷创新的差异化因素缩小为八个驱动因素：存在的目的、对客户需求的痴迷、对同事的皮格马利翁式影响、即使扩大规模后的创业心态、大胆的偏见、激进的协作、控制的准备节奏，并双峰运行。大多数领导者都赞扬这些属性，但事实证明，随着时间的推移，大型组织很难维持其中任何一个属性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tabrizi 写道&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/how-microsoft-became-再次创新>;其他地方&lt;/a>;讲述了微软如何通过彻底改革其层级结构并寻求与 Open AI 等合作伙伴关系，成为企业领导者。但由于这些驱动因素，其他公司也对人工智能做了类似的事情。让我们重点关注两个最重要的驱动因素——大胆的偏见和创业心态。将这些驱动因素落实到位可以使公司深入敏捷创新，因为这些力量会在整个组织中发生变化。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;大胆的偏见&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;任何在不久的将来投资人工智能的公司很可能会从中赚钱。然而，单纯的投资可能只能带来增量收益。这些数字可能看起来不错，尤其是在削减成本方面。但该公司将错过通过创造巨大价值或可防御的未来利基市场来获得巨大收益的机会。从长远来看，谨慎投资并不能保护您免受竞争，当然也无法帮助我们应对所面临的宏观经济挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是任何新技术的问题：您可以谨慎行事，也许做得很好。大公司讨厌风险，&lt;a href=&quot;/2000/03/meeting-the-challenge-of-disruptive-change&quot;>;这就是为什么&lt;/a>;他们像运转良好的机器一样以可承受的成本生产可靠的产品。这也是为什么他们中的许多人通过收购初创公司来外包创新的原因——即使这种方法也常常会带来胆怯的改进。所有成功的组织，尤其是规模较大的组织，都倾向于将风险和勇气降至最低。但正如 Brené Brown &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Rising-Strong-Reckoning-Rumble-Revolution/dp/0812995821/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679119&amp;amp;sr=1-7 &quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;，“你可以选择勇气，也可以选择舒适，但你不能两者都选择。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大胆已经成为企业的陈词滥调，领导者抗议太多，但我们需要企业真正认真地对待人工智能——拥抱风险，而不是最小化风险。以 Adob​​e 为例，其 Photoshop 程序长期以来一直占据摄影设计市场的最大份额。随着生成式人工智能的出现，Adobe 本可以谨慎行事，在小范围内采用它，同时等待看看该技术的效果如何。这就是柯达在数码摄影方面所做的事情，以及摩托罗拉在数字电话方面所做的事情。相反，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/search/results/content/?fromMember=%5B%22ACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ%22%5D&amp;amp;heroEntityKey=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_profile%3AACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH 6erPefJ5euQ&amp;关键字=jj% 20delgado%F0%9F%A4%99&amp;amp;position=0&amp;amp;searchId=a8067e47-50fe-43fd-a269-0d80da62e1f5&amp;amp;sid=8k2&amp;amp;update=urn%3Ali%3Afs_updateV2%3A(urn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A70667925984 46743552%2CBLENDED_SEARCH_FEED% 2CEMPTY%2CDEFAULT%2Cfalse)&quot;>;Adobe 已将&lt;/a>;生成式 AI 深入 Photoshop 中，普通用户可以创建以前无法创建的各种视频。 Adobe 可能将 AI 视为一种威胁或干扰，但它在没有 AI 的情况下继续改进 Photoshop。但其领导者有勇气积极投资人工智能，以提升用户的能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在技术的更深层次上，芯片制造商 Nvidia 一直在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg. com/opinion/articles/2023-06-03/chips-inside-nvidia-s-30-year-ride-to-overnight-ai-success?sref=bsFVYL6k&quot;>;因提供最佳半导体而成为头条新闻&lt;/a>;人工智能芯片。在外人看来，该公司可能看起来很幸运，在正确的时间拥有了正确的技术。但英伟达目前的成功并非偶然：在过去十年中，它积极获取和开发人工智能领域的专业知识，包括创建定制芯片和软件。我们预计这种进取精神将继续下去，不仅为 Nvidia 提供更高价值的产品，而且比简单的成本削减更好地利用人工智能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大胆并非每次都有效。但是，对于克服企业层级中根深蒂固的风险厌恶情绪，大胆的偏见至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;创业心态&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与大胆类似，对于成功的人工智能同样重要的是，采用初创公司的心态，无论您的公司成立时间或规模如何。初创公司擅长广泛关注市场并快速满足客户当前的需求。大公司拥有资源来利用这些机会，但它们通常行动缓慢，障碍众多（而且缺乏勇气），因此初创企业能够更快地进入市场。开放人工智能，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johanmoreno/2022/12/29/openai-positioned-itself-as-the-ai--leader-in-2022-but- can-google-supersede-it-in-23/?sh=b69aaa953216&quot;>;用 ChatGPT 击败&lt;/a>; Google，两全其美：创业心态摆脱了阻碍 Google 的犹豫，但拥有充足的资源由微软和其他投资者提供。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;创业心态不仅仅在于勇气和灵活性；还在于勇气和灵活性。它还涉及对伟大成就的坚定承诺，这是一种应对巨大挑战的英雄之旅。初创公司想要创造一些非凡的东西，而不是按照可预测性大规模生产出优质产品（尽管这是一个完全值得的目标）。因此，他们非常重视环顾四周，灵活地与他人合作。他们摒弃现有的结构和偏见，无论历史有多长、受人尊敬，以便完成需要做的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;电子商务巨头亚马逊在拥抱人工智能方面展现了创业心态。随着十多年前技术的发展，该公司&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/how-amazon-made-alexa-smarter/&quot;>;看到了创建一个机会&lt;/a>; “智能扬声器”作为网络的新界面。亚马逊在人工智能方面没有专业知识，但它通过招聘、收购和内部开发获得了所需的知识。结果是 Echo 扬声器和 Alexa 数字助理，它的作用远远超出了简单地帮助人们订购更多商品。它为许多领域的增值（和就业）开辟了新的渠道。亚马逊继续在 Alexa 之外积极投资人工智能，首席执行官 Andy Jassy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/amazons-alexa-head-defends-companys-work-on -ai-amid-chatgpt-boom.html&quot;>;说&lt;/a>;该技术承诺“改变和改善几乎所有客户体验。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•• •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司不可能一夜之间采用这些驱动因素，但他们可以开始认真致力于新的可能性。这些驱动力中的大多数人也在为自己的职业生涯寻找目标和成就的个人层面上工作。他们可以拥抱大胆、采取创业心态和其他必要条件。与公司一样，员工可以通过获得必要的技能和经验来积极投资人工智能，从而不仅可以保护他们的职业生涯，还可以增加价值&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-boom-share-profits- workers-productivity-wages-2023-5?inline-endstory-related-recommendations=&quot;>;at a higher level&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of corporate life has quite properly been about churning out reliable products at low cost. What we need now, to prevent mass unemployment, is for many firms to break out of this discipline and speed up the AI future. The great danger is that most companies will play it safe, make the easy investments, and do fine in the short term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Humanity never thrives when it fears innovation. Imagine if the first humans feared fire; yes, they got burned sometimes, but without harnessing the power of it, we might have gone extinct. We think the same applies to AI. Rather than fear it, we need to harness its power. We must put it in the hands of every human being, so we collectively can achieve and live at this higher level.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Your New Leadership Role with the End in Mind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_22_Carlo_Cadenas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Carlo Cadenas&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To successfully step into a new role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance &amp;#8220;now-forward&amp;#8221; planning with &amp;#8220;future-back&amp;#8221; visioning. That is, you must start with the end in mind, envisioning what you want to accomplish during this era of your leadership and what needs to happen before for can take the next step. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When taking on a new leadership role, it&#39;s&amp;nbsp;natural to focus on the immediate challenges of making a successful transition, including accelerating your learning, building relationship with stakeholders, and securing early wins. However, it is essential to complement this “now-forward” planning with “future-back” thinking about your desired destination and what it will take to get there. As Stephen Covey expressed in his best-selling book, &lt;em>;The Seven Habits of Highly Effective People&lt;/em>;, you want to “start with the end in mind.” This means envisioning what you want to accomplish in the new role so you will be ready to move beyond it and then working backward to map out how you will get there. In so doing, you can shape your early actions to lay the foundation for long-term success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The starting point is to engage in what Dan Ciampa, the noted executive coach, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.danciampa.com/more-designated-successors.php&quot;>;defined as “era planning&lt;/a>;.” Your era is the anticipated duration of time you think you will be in the new position. Of course, you may end up staying longer or leaving earlier, but try to make a rough guess about when you will have accomplished enough to be “done.” You&#39;ll want to ask yourself two key questions: “As I wrap up this job, what will be true?” and “What will be possible?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Envisioning &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Your Leadership Legacy &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first question — “What will be true?”&amp;nbsp;— asks you to outline the legacy you aspire to create and the story you will tell about your achievements. Focus on what you want to be remembered for in your new position and what you want your team and peers to say about your leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider key areas such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Performance outcomes:&lt;/strong>; What are the tangible results — for example, in terms of increased productivity or profitability — you will achieve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Organizational transformation:&lt;/strong>; How will you reshape the team and its culture?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Innovation:&lt;/strong>; What will you do to foster creativity and develop new areas for growth?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Talent development:&lt;/strong>; How will you hire and train people to take the organization into the future?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Distill these into a concise, written personal narrative. Then, think about what you need to do, starting now, to realize this legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Creating&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>; Future Possibilities &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second question — “What will be possible?” — encourages you to envision futures beyond your current role and strategize the steps you&#39;ll take to turn them into viable options. This process involves identifying multiple potential paths forward and pinpointing the skills you&#39;ll need to acquire and the connections you&#39;ll need to establish over the course of this era to make those viable options. By exploring different scenarios and actively planning your development, you&#39;ll be better equipped to adapt and seize emerging opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take these steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Create a list of potential futures, considering logical next steps in your organization and your industry, as well as less conventional but still attractive options that would take you in different directions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Assess whether there are skill gaps you need to close to achieve some or all of those futures by reflecting on your existing strengths and areas for improvement.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Identify the bridges — the steps and connections — that would allow you to transition from your current role to your desired future options. These might include expanding your professional network, deepening your industry knowledge, or engaging in what Ken Banta and Orlan Boston &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/the-strategic-side-gig&quot;>;described as “strategic side gigs&lt;/a>;,” such as teaching or working on boards of directors.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Develop a plan for how you&#39;ll acquire the skills and build the bridges to make the potential futures you have identified realistic options, setting specific goals and holding yourself accountable for achieving them.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As Peter Drucker said, “The best way to predict the future is to create it.” By imagining multiple potential futures and working toward them, you&#39;ll create real options for yourself when you&#39;re ready to move on from your current role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To successfully step into a new leadership role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance “now-forward” planning with “future-back” visioning. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Roles Could Generative AI Play on Your Team?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_22_1273134318.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Normform/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The recent advances in ChatGPT are merely the first application of new AI technologies. As such, companies and leaders need to think about the various applications outlined here and use the framework described in the article to develop applications for your own company or organization. In the process, they will discover new types of GPTs. By classifying these different GPTs in terms of potential value to businesses and the cost of developing them, applications that begin with a single human initiating or participating in the interaction (GroupGPT, CoachGPT) will probably be the easiest to build and should generate substantial business value, making them the perfect initial candidates. In contrast, applications with interactions involving multiple entities or those initiated by machines (AutoGPT, BossGPT, and ImperialGPT) may be harder to implement, with trickier ethical and legal implications.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The frenzy surrounding the launch of Large Language Models (LLMs) and other types of Generative AI (GenAI) isn&#39;t going to fade anytime soon. Users of GenAI are discovering and recommending new and interesting use cases for their business and personal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/04/14/upshot/up-ai-uses.html&quot;>;lives&lt;/a>;. Many recommendations start with the assumption that GenAI requires a human prompt. Indeed, &lt;em>;Time&lt;/em>; magazine recently proclaimed “prompt engineering” to be the next hot job, &lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/6272103/ai-prompt-engineer-job/&quot;>;with salaries reaching $335,000&lt;/a>;. Tech forums and educational websites are focusing on prompt engineering, with Udemy already offering a course &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.udemy.com/course/master-prompt-engineering-with-chatgpt&quot;>;on the topic&lt;/a>;, and several organizations we work with are now beginning to invest considerable resources in training employees on how best to use ChatGPT.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, it may be worth pausing to consider other ways of interacting with GPT technologies, which are likely to emerge soon. We present an intuitive way to think about this issue, which is based on our own survey of GenAI developments, combined with conversations with companies that are seeking to develop some versions of these.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Framework of GPT Interactions&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A good starting point is to distinguish between who is &lt;em>;involved in the interaction&lt;/em>; — individuals, groups of people, or another machine — and &lt;em>;who starts the interaction,&lt;/em>; human or machine. This leads to six different types of GenAI uses, shown below. ChatGPT, where one human initiates interaction with the machine is already well-known. We now describe each of the other GPTs and outline their potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;CoachGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;is a personal assistant that provides you with a set of suggestions on managing your daily life. It would base these suggestions not on explicit prompts from you, but on the basis of observing what you do and your environment. For example, it could observe you as an executive and note that you find it hard to build trust in your team; it could then recommend precise actions to overcome this blind spot. It could also come up with personalized advice on development options or even salary negotiations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CoachGPT would subsequently see which recommendations you adopted or didn&#39;t adopt, and which benefited you and which ones didn&#39;t to improve its advice over time. With time, you would get a highly personalized AI advisor, coach, or consultant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations could adopt CoachGPT to advise customers on how to use a product, whether a construction company offering CoachGPT to advise end users on how best to use its equipment, or an accounting firm proffering real-time advice on how best to account for a set of transactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To make CoachGPT effective, individuals and organizations would have to allow it to work in the background, monitoring online and offline activities. Clearly, serious privacy considerations need to be addressed before we entrust our innermost thoughts to the system. However, the potential for positive outcomes in both private and professional lives is immense.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;GroupGPT &lt;/strong>;would be a bona fide group member that can observe interactions between group members and contribute to the discussion. For example, it could conduct fact checking, supply a summary of the conversation, suggest what to discuss next, play the role of devil&#39;s advocate, provide a competitor perspective, stress-test the ideas, or even propose a creative solution to the problem at hand.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The requests could come from individual group members or from the team&#39;s boss, who need not participate in team interactions, but merely seeks to manage, motivate, and evaluate group members. The contribution could be delivered to the whole group or to specific individuals, with adjustments for that person&#39;s role, skill, or personality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The privacy concerns mentioned above also apply to GroupGPT, but, if addressed, organizations could take advantage of GroupGPT by using it for project management, especially on long and complicated projects involving relatively large teams across different departments or regions. Since GroupGPT would overcome human limitations on information storage and processing capacity, it would be ideal for supporting complex and dispersed teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;BossGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;takes an active role in advising a group of people on what they could or should do, without being prompted. It could provide individual recommendations to group members, but its real value emerges when it begins to coordinate the work of group members, telling them as a group who should do what to maximize team output. BossGPT could also step in to offer individual coaching and further recommendations as the project and team dynamics evolve.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The algorithms necessary for BossGPT to work would be much more complicated as they would have to consider somewhat unpredictable individual and group reactions to instructions from a machine, but it could have a wide range of uses. For example: an executive changing job could request a copy of her reactions to her first organization&#39;s BossGPT instructions, which could then be used to assess how she would fit into the new organization — and the new organization-specific BossGPT.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the organizational level companies could deploy BossGPT to manage people, thereby augmenting — or potentially even replacing — existing managers. Similarly, BossGPT has tremendous applications in coordinating work across organizations and managing complex supply chains or multiple suppliers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies could turn BossGPT into a product, offering their customers AI solutions to help them manage their business. These solutions could be natural extensions of the CoachGPT examples described earlier. For example, a company selling construction equipment could offer BossGPT to coordinate many end users on a construction site, and an accounting firm could provide it to coordinate the work of many employees of its customers to run the accounting function in the most efficient way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AutoGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;entails a human giving a request or prompt to one machine, which in turn engages other machines to complete the task. In its simplest form, a human might instruct a machine to complete a task, but the machine realizes that it lacks a specific software to execute it, so it would search for the missing software on Google before downloading and installing it, and then using it &lt;a href=&quot;https://autogpt.net/auto-gpt-vs-chatgpt-how-do-they-differ-and-everything-you-need-to-know/&quot;>;to finish the request&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a more complicated version, humans could give AutoGPT a goal (such as creating the best viral YouTube video) and instruct it to interact with another GenAI to iteratively come up with the best ChatGPT prompt to achieve the goal. The machine would then launch the process by proposing a prompt to another machine, then evaluate the outcome, and adjust the prompt to get closer and closer to the final goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the most complicated version, AutoGPT could draw on functionalities of the other GPTs described above. For example, a team leader could task a machine with maximizing both the effectiveness and job satisfaction of her team members. AutoGPT could then switch between coaching individuals through CoachGPT, providing them with suggestions for smoother team interactions through GroupGPT, while at the same time issuing specific instructions on what needs to be done through BossGPT. AutoGPT could subsequently collect feedback from each activity and adjust all the other activities to reach the given goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike the above versions, which are still to be created, a version of AutoGPT has been developed and was rolled out in April 2023, and it&#39;s quickly gaining broad acceptance. The technology is still not perfect and requires improvements, but it is already evident that AutoGPT is able to complete a set of jobs that requires the completion of several tasks one after the other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We see its biggest applications in complex tasks, such as supply chain coordination, but also in fields such as cybersecurity. For example, organizations could prompt AutoGPT to continually address any cybersecurity vulnerabilities, which would entail looking for them — which already happens — but then instead of simply flagging them, AutoGPT would search for solutions to the threats or write its own patches to counter them. A human might still be in the loop, but since the system is self-generative within these limits, we believe that AutoGPT&#39;s response is likely to be faster and more efficient.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ImperialGPT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;is the most abstract GenAI — and perhaps the most transformational — in which two or more machines would interact with each other, direct each other, and ultimately direct humans to engage in a course of action. This type of GPT worries most AI analysts, who fear losing control of AI and AI “going rogue.” We concur with these concerns, particularly if — as now — there are no strict guardrails on what AI is allowed to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the same time, if ImperialGPT is allowed to come up with ideas and share them with humans, but its ability to act on the ideas is restricted, we believe that this could generate extremely interesting creative solutions especially for “unknown unknowns,” where human knowledge and creativity fall short. They could then easily envision and game out multiple black swan events and worst-case scenarios, complete with potential costs and outcomes, to provide possible solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the potential dangers of ImperialGPT, and the need for tight regulation, we believe that ImperialGPT will be slow to take off, at least commercially. We do anticipate, however, that governments, intelligence services, and the military will be interested in deploying ImperialGPT under strictly controlled conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Implications for your Business&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;So, what does our framework mean for companies and organizations around the world? First and foremost, we encourage you to step back and see the recent advances in ChatGPT as merely the first application of new AI technologies. Second, we urge you to think about the various applications outlined here and use our framework to develop applications for your own company or organization. In the process, we are sure you will discover new types of GPTs that we have not mentioned. Third, we suggest you classify these different GPTs in terms of potential value to your business, and the cost of developing them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We believe that applications that begin with a single human initiating or participating in the interaction (GroupGPT, CoachGPT) will probably be the easiest to build and should generate substantial business value, making them the perfect initial candidates. In contrast, applications with interactions involving multiple entities or those initiated by machines (AutoGPT, BossGPT, and ImperialGPT) may be harder to implement, with trickier ethical and legal implications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You might also want to start thinking about the complex ethical, legal, and regulatory concerns that will arise with each GPT type. Failure to do so exposes you and your company to both legal liabilities and — perhaps more importantly — an unintended negative effect on humanity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our next set of recommendations depends on your company type. A tech company or startup, or one that has ample resources to invest in these technologies, should start working on developing one or more of the GPTs discussed above. This is clearly a high-risk, high-reward strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In contrast, if your competitive strength is not in GenAI or if you lack resources, you might be better off adopting a “wait and see” approach. This means you will be slow to adopt the current technology, but you will not waste valuable resources on what may turn out to be only an interim version of a product. Instead, you can begin preparing your internal systems to better capture and store data as well as readying your organization to embrace these new GPTs, in terms of both work processes and culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The launch and rapid adoption of GenAIs is rightly being considered as the next level in the evolution of AI and a potentially epochal moment for humanity in general. Although GenAIs represent breakthroughs in solving fundamental engineering and computer science problems, they do not automatically guarantee value creation for all organizations. Rather, smart companies will need to invest in modifying and adapting the core technology before figuring out the best way to monetize the innovations. Firms that do this right may indeed strike it rich in the GenAI goldrush.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Leadership Teams Navigate Uncertain Times]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_21_816813440.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While we don&amp;#8217;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&amp;#8217;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&amp;#8217;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand &amp;#8212; and reward &amp;#8212; high-performing leadership teams. Based on his conversations with more than 100 clients across industries, PWC US Chair and Senior Partner Tim Ryan has identified seven factors that set these teams apart: 1) They create a &amp;#8220;company-first&amp;#8221; culture; 2) They think and act across the enterprise; 3) They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business; 4) They free up the right people for the hard stuff; 5) They&amp;#8217;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills; 6) They encourage healthy debate, but avoid undermining fellow leaders; and 7) They strive to be humble and objective.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Whether it&#39;s inflation, rising interest rates, supply-chain disruptions, geopolitical tensions — there is a lot happening in the global economy. And on top of those forces, consumer expectations are increasing, competition is intense and investors are raising the bar. There&#39;s never been a more challenging time to be a CEO or member of senior management.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the complexities, it is no surprise that some companies are performing exceptionally well, a lot are doing just ok and there are others struggling to keep up. Based on my latest discussions with more than 100 clients across industries, what I&#39;ve seen is that the outperforming companies have leadership teams with the following seven factors in common:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They create a “company-first” culture.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Senior leadership teams are typically made up of individuals who are highly skilled in their domain — but what&#39;s different at high-performing companies is these leaders embrace a company-first culture. This means doing what&#39;s right for the business and your people, instead of driving individual agendas or objectives. One CEO of a high-performing industrial company shared that being part of his leadership team is like being on a sports team: “The team comes first, not the star individual.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They think and act across the enterprise&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-performing teams recognize that their role extends beyond the individual unit they manage, and they operate across silos. One CEO of a leading digital bank shared with me that his team&#39;s enterprise-focused mindset drove a reimagined customer experience resulting in industry-leading efficiency ratios. They achieved this by sharing data across the enterprise and committing to one set of data governance rules.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Too often CEOs and senior leadership focus the majority of their time on running the business, while the portfolio and business-model reinvention takes a back seat. Strong companies are putting the bold reimagining of their business at the top of the agenda.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bold actions include running the business with unparalleled discipline, managing costs, simplifying wherever you can, and pulling on every lever to win. Taking bold action also involves reshaping portfolios while reinventing the back, middle and front offices—with a sense of urgency.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One CEO of a pharmaceutical company, who was looking to innovate and disrupt their industry, implemented a bold new business model powered by a cutting-edge commerce and marketplace platform in a matter of months. This resulted in a direct, better way to reach customers, increased margins, and greater trust and transparency across their entire value chain.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They free up the right people for the hard stuff. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Reinventing your business is a full-time job and needs dedicated minds who aren&#39;t also focused on managing other day jobs. High-performing leadership teams find the time to focus on the hard stuff and delegate the day-to-day operations to others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A CEO of a major energy company put one of his top business leaders in charge of their enterprise-wide business model transformation to both enable its success and send a clear message to all stakeholders of the importance of the transformation. While it&#39;s difficult to have a leader step away from the work they are doing to take on a transformation effort, the dedicated focus makes all the difference. The energy company&#39;s transformation leader has since positioned the company for significant value accretion and cost optimization through standardization and simplification, all while driving leadership commitment, organizational readiness and business outcome sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They&#39;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-quality teams are inclusive in all ways. This means inclusive of genders and ethnicities, but also of diverse views, backgrounds, and skill sets. It&#39;s critical to have a breadth of leaders in your C-suite that bring forth differentiated expertise and perspectives to enable an organization to innovate more robustly and accelerate transformations. It&#39;s why top leadership teams have a chief technology officer, chief people officer and chief communications officer at the table.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one instance, a CEO of a major technology company shared with me that too many companies lack a diversity of skills in the C-suite, particularly when it comes to technology. As a result, senior management might not be able to identify what the “art of the possible” is when transforming their business and how different tools, like emerging technologies, could help. In these cases, leadership teams focus on building a “faster horse and buggy”&#39; rather than reimagining what&#39;s next.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They encourage healthy debate but avoid undermining fellow leaders. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Good teams have healthy debates, transparently talk about pros and cons and explore alternatives together. Before transformation efforts begin, they spend a lot of time agreeing on the desired outcomes and business requirements of the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Getting leadership teams to engage in open, honest discussions is critical. One CEO of a major industrial company shared with me that she never imagined the amount of time she needed to spend helping her team “get along.” What I took from her comment is that leadership is about coaching the team to share their various points of view, challenge each other with healthy debate, and come together once a decision is made to row in the same direction.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They strive to be humble and objective. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Humility is critical at the CEO and senior levels of any company because it filters down to every level of the organization. It helps fight complacency. Most companies have a lot to be proud of, but if the focus is always on the success of the past instead of the opportunity for the future, other companies will quickly pass you by.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, some leaders struggle with objectively assessing their current performance and where their company and results truly stand. Leading companies are constantly challenging themselves and use objectivity to both drive performance, keep the competition in the rearview mirror and shareholder activists at bay.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I recently spoke with a CEO from a consumer technology company about the importance of having the right people on your company&#39;s board and the critical role the board plays in bringing an outside-in perspective. Board members are in the advantageous position to help the C-suite look around corners, prepare for potential challenges, and discover blind spots.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While we don&#39;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&#39;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&#39;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand — and reward — high-performing leadership teams. They&#39;ll drive outsized growth, increase shareholder value, and likely have a little more fun along the way — working together and sharing the successes of a team that is creating more value for their customers, employees, and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Brand-Influencer Partnerships Reach Gen Z]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1479691532.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Authenticity is among Gen Z&amp;#8217;s most important values. They feel empowered to ask and answer their own questions in a variety of social forums on any topic &amp;#8212; from beauty to health to home improvement to technology to science. And their view of authority has expanded from traditional sources, like academic institutions or reputable editorial voices, to perceived influence. The author offers five lessons for brands who want to tap into this era of influencers and make authentic connections with Gen Z.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;If you haven&#39;t heard about Alix Earle, it may simply be a matter of time. This young influencer — who just graduated from the University of Miami — has more than 5 million followers on TikTok and was recently signed by United Talent Agency (UTA), one of the top three firms that represent talent globally across the media and entertainment ecosystem. She has leveraged her personal brand to partner with beauty companies like Tarte and Rare Beauty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Watching the myriad of Alix Earle videos online makes her formula quite clear. She has model-like beauty, checking the box for sheer aesthetics. She&#39;s perfected the “get ready with me” (GRWM) format (among others), a short-form video in which she goes from natural beauty to flawless perfection, displaying professional yet replicable makeup techniques and product use. As she applies her look during “selfie” videos, she offers a mix of storytelling, humor, vulnerability, aspiration, relatability, and product mentions in a fast-talking, effortless monologue. She feels just approachable enough to be just another college student.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That approachability is why Earle resonates so much with Gen Z. Authenticity is among this generation&#39;s most important values. As &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-knowhttps:/www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-know&quot;>;recent EY research highlights&lt;/a>;: “After an era of fake news and filtered photos projecting the &#39;perfect life,&#39; Gen Z is over it.” They feel empowered to ask and answer their own questions in a variety of social forums on any topic — from beauty to health to home improvement to technology to science. And their view of authority has expanded from traditional sources, like academic institutions or reputable editorial voices, to perceived influence — as demonstrated by Earle&#39;s meteoric rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Studying Alix Earle&#39;s success offers brand marketers five powerful lessons for how to tap into this era of influencers — and make authentic connections with Gen Z.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Find the right influencers for your brand&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Simply force-ranking top influencer lists is not the answer. Brands want to find the person or people who reach their target audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once brands define the category in which they compete, marketers can look for the influencers who have the most engagement and who have a voice and style that resonates with the brand. AI and other tools to analyze data can help you figure this out — for example, data analytics can reveal followers, creative approaches, and communities in common between influencers and brands. There are also companies, from Gallery Media, for example, to leading talent agencies, who curate influencers and manage more complex relationships and execution for brands.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Create brand stories for mobile consumption&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gen Z fills their spare moments by scrolling through their algorithmically driven, personalized “for you” feeds on their phones, filled with photos, videos, and memes. Ideally, brands should empower the influencers they work with to create content that is short, compelling, and made for mobile.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Embracing vulnerability and openness, like Earle does in short one- to three-minute stories, enables brands to connect with younger generations in a way that&#39;s personally relevant and authentic. However, brands must understand that this is not a 30-second scripted television spot, and the influencers will take the story in a direction of their own choosing. This is a complement to other brand storytelling — not a replacement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Motivate consumers to make brand content their own&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unlike previous generations, Gen Z does not “broadcast” their posts to social networks writ large. They share more often with far fewer people via “private stories.” Engagement is much higher because of the frequency and the intimacy of these posts, and with this shift, we also see Gen Z moving away from prior generational behaviors of broadcasting their happy moments widely on their social media accounts to sharing more raw moments like personal crisis and tears in more private circles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A young person who sees a beauty product in a GRWM video from Earle on TikTok who subsequently endorses that product with their friend group in their private story on Snap is an example of how the brand journey goes from high-profile social media influence to deeply personal influence. A brand must earn the right to access this sacred space — and it must understand the opacity and new risks of these more personally intimate venues.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Cross boundaries to stand out&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s going to take new sources of inspiration and creativity to stand out as generative and conversational AI are applied in creative contexts at scale. As all influencers now have access to the same technology to drive research, enhance ideas, and accelerate production, forward-thinking brands will look to differentiate through human originality or true celebrity. The bar for real creativity will only get higher, requiring unorthodox juxtapositions of brands or new invitations to consumers to co-create. Our current definition of influence may shift rapidly as AI manipulates both the targeting and creative driving the algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Avoid clone culture&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As marketers, we may prize the opportunity to drive consumption at all costs by engineering trends to have velocity through influencers. But if we succeed too much on the science of it all, are we creating trend echo chambers that contradict our commitments to diversity and inclusion, or cloning repeat behaviors within certain social archetypes? And if influence relies on at least the veneer of originality, will it be harder as everyone uses similar AI-driven insights? Brands drive their commercial ambition with precision using a combination of creativity and data (or art and science), but increasingly, they may seek to broaden strategies to find new audiences, voices, and inspiration to diversify their base of consumers and ideas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The creator economy is thriving, creative, and valuable, particularly as technology-enabled economic models motivate strong talent to make it a true professional endeavor. Brands that harness its new dynamics to create value will differentiate themselves and drive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/cmo?WT.mc_id=14001454&amp;amp;AA.tsrc=pr&quot;>;exponential growth&lt;/a>;. The key to success is to lean into the newest sources of influence along with all the latest dynamics of risk and reward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;The views reflected in this article are the views of the author and do not necessarily reflect the views of Ernst &amp;amp; Young LLP or other members of the global EY organization.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Can Help Stressed-Out Managers Be Better Coaches]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_21_1433543804.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;SvetaZi/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The expectations placed on managers to assess and guide their employees&amp;#8217; performance have increased, a trend amplified by generational shifts and remote work. Employees want frequent, personalized, one-on-one coaching, but managers are constrained by their already heavy burdens. New AI tools show promise to improve the efficiency and effectiveness of managerial coaching &amp;#8212; but first, common sources of fear and mistrust must be overcome. Based on research and case studies, the authors present five steps to ensure the use of AI-assisted coaching enhances the lives of both managers and employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Middle managers are receiving pressure from their leaders to &lt;a href=&quot;https://workforceinstitute.org/our-2023-workplace-predictions/&quot;>;spend more time developing and coaching&lt;/a>; their direct reports. The pressure is also coming from below, as employee &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/all-things-work/pages/performance-management-evolves.aspx&quot;>;expectations have risen&lt;/a>; for real-time, personalized feedback, particularly among those early in their careers or who were onboarded remotely. The challenge is satisfying these demands without incurring even higher levels of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/357404/manager-burnout-getting-worse.aspx&quot;>;middle manager burnout and stress&lt;/a>;. Based on our research and advisory work, we foresee new AI tools making it easier for managers to provide high-quality coaching more efficiently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Employees want more coaching, but managers are out of capacity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;OC Tanner&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octanner.com/global-culture-report/2023/leadership-at-risk.html&quot;>;2023 Global Culture Survey&lt;/a>; found that leaders whose supervisory responsibilities — including training employees — had increased over the past year showed a 21% higher rate of anxiety, which increased the odds of burnout by a staggering 520%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the potential for overload, managers generally want to coach their employees because they know it&#39;s beneficial. In fact, managerial coaching has been shown to increase &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/01492063211003951&quot;>;job satisfaction&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://bpspsychub.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/joop.12402&quot;>;knowledge sharing&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/hrdq.21175&quot;>;performance&lt;/a>; — all outcomes that organizations (and managers!) want.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The AI opportunity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our review of the field indicates that AI-based managerial coaching is not yet commonplace, so we offer two case examples to demonstrate how it might work in your organization:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Eleos Health&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Eleos Health is a behavioral health technology company that Katherine studied in depth as part of her ethnographic &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyt.2022.990370/full&quot;>;research&lt;/a>;. The Eleos platform uses HIPAA-compliant software to record and analyze conversations between therapists and clients. In addition to saving time for therapists in note-taking, the platform&#39;s AI automatically identifies relevant evidence-based techniques and summarizes key moments in conversations between therapists and clients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One therapist explained: “After each session, the Eleos platform analyzes the counseling techniques I used and provides a helpful summary. This gives me a great sense of where I left off with that patient and what interventions I should use next time to best help them.” In this way, the AI platform enables therapists to make self-directed improvements in their work without having to rely so heavily on supervisors for guidance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, the AI platform can facilitate more useful checkpoints between therapists and their supervisors when they do need to meet. For example, it can be used to quickly synthesize or extract relevant client session data when discussing a complex case, reducing reliance on memory or notes. As one supervisor told Katherine, “New therapists often have questions … Eleos&#39; analyses allow me to zero in on key moments in their session visits, or on techniques the therapists have used, as well as patient progress over time, so that our coaching time together can be spent most productively.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Gong&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A second example comes from Gong, which has developed an AI platform for sales teams. Gong&#39;s platform unobtrusively captures live interactions between agents and prospective clients. While the conversation is unfolding, AI is crunching data in the background, examining how variables like pace, topic, tone, and turn-taking compare to best practices at that company. This data is used to provide insights and advice to sales agents in real time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moreover, Gong&#39;s AI can automatically create a library of high-quality examples of recorded sales conversations to serve as a resource for independent learning. This has been found to be especially helpful for new employees, who can listen to exemplary sales calls at their own pace, rather than relying on direct training from others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Identifying essential onboarding content and providing sales reps with real-time advice during sales calls saves managers hours of time that used to be spent listening to new employees&#39; calls to help them understand what works and what doesn&#39;t in the sales process. The result is efficient knowledge transfer. As one Gong user told us, “The platform empowers me to improve my skills and share best practices with fellow sales reps. I find that AI-based knowledge-sharing through feedback and metrics leads to continuous improvement for the entire team.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Understanding potential challenges&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re not endorsing any particular tool or company, but we do encourage HR and people managers to be on the lookout for AI options that could enhance managerial coaching in their organizations. Other companies in this space include &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/aclk?sa=l&amp;amp;ai=DChcSEwiTpMbD1r3-AhUv5uMHHSv6CJkYABABGgJ5bQ&amp;amp;sig=AOD64_22a36n60RhrD3gwoHexVSlB_b0HA&amp;amp;q&amp;amp;adurl&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiy477D1r3-AhXXkYkEHSXLCgYQ0Qx6BAgIEAE&quot;>;Beamery&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humu.com/&quot;>;Humu&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultureamp.com/?_gl=1*td4rop*_up*MQ..&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwi46iBhDyARIsAE3nVrY95mViC1V0iVh7byxvuAVNebyAoaKUOfSTaQAgP1hJzXQFE0X73XUaAhsGEALw_wcB&quot;>;Culture Amp&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterup.com/platform&quot;>;BetterUp&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.skillsoft.com/meet-skillsoft-percipio&quot;>;Skillsoft&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/ibm-transforms-human-resources-ai.aspx&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;. We expect new offerings will continue to emerge, including those embedding generative AI capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you shop around, assess your workforce&#39;s readiness for adopting an AI-assisted coaching system. Keep in mind that evaluating someone&#39;s work and trying to improve it are already &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90753495/how-to-manage-the-anxiety-of-giving-negative-feedback&quot;>;emotion-laden processes&lt;/a>;; adding technology to the mix can amplify anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One well-documented phenomenon is “&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2155&quot;>;algorithm aversion&lt;/a>;”: people&#39;s reluctance or unwillingness to trust algorithms more than human judgment. This can be even more potent when the algorithm is judging an employee&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;efficacy&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, introducing a new source of evaluation can potentially create a social distance between managers and their employees, especially if there are concerns about bias, transparency, and privacy. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1002/smj.3322&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; showed that employees resented AI-based feedback, even if it was objectively helpful, if they were not apprised ahead of time that their manager was using it. This study speaks to the importance of not only considering factors such as cost, accuracy, and timing when evaluating an AI-assisted coaching tool, but also the human factors that can influence its success or failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Five steps for successful AI-assisted coaching&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To ensure that AI-assisted coaching initiatives achieve the best possible outcomes for both employees and managers, we recommend the following steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Establish psychological safety and trust&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Decades of research show that a trust-based relationship between parties is essential for effective feedback and coaching. This is &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0008125619867910?casa_token=AcqTP9eZ4YQAAAAA:EDc0DKjUi5MDT8xnmyBu_pLBv4WWtMd7sUp9EyoG4MRqu3zvEk5LKvc58CvLSBchVrOz9BtWnrw&quot;>;even more essential&lt;/a>; when dealing with the “black box” of AI-generated assessments. In a new study, for example, employees who felt their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90762918/ai-can-hurt-worker-morale-when-managers-dont-have-these-specific-skills&quot;>;managers had their best interests at heart&lt;/a>; were more willing to accept AI-generated recommendations — even ones they didn&#39;t initially agree with. Managers can &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/make-it-safe-for-employees-to-speak-up-especially-in-risky-times&quot;>;create psychological safety&lt;/a>; and trust in the tool by clarifying the rationale for the AI integration, giving assurances as to how employee data will be used, and encouraging people to speak up about problems or questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Engage employees in design and implementation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For the best quality as well as the most buy-in, it&#39;s critical to &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-on-the-front-lines/&quot;>;be inclusive of employees throughout the exploration and adoption process&lt;/a>;. Microsoft found in a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/four-ways-leaders-can-empower-people-for-how-work-gets-done&quot;>;survey of 4,500 global executives&lt;/a>; that giving people a say in technological initiatives goes a long way toward keeping them satisfied and engaged with the tools. Ideally, employees will be involved down to the level of &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;determining the performance metrics&lt;/a>; and type of coaching that will be generated by AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Give employees some control over their data and participation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Giving employees agency over how they engage with AI-assisted coaching systems helps alleviate scrutiny and privacy concerns. For example, Eleos Health&#39;s platform allows clinicians to opt out of using the platform for specific patient sessions. Another recommended approach is to form an employee-inclusive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/hr-gets-help-vetting-ai-tools.aspx&quot;>;AI governance board&lt;/a>; to ensure transparency in what data is being collected, how it&#39;s being used, and what safeguards are in place to protect employees&#39; privacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Streamline and customize the output&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Typically, AI tools allow managers to customize the data displays and analyses generated; we recommend organizations take full advantage of these features. At the start of a rollout, for example, it might be helpful to focus the output on only a few performance metrics until people feel more comfortable with the tool.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers can also customize the quality of the feedback to reflect specific employee needs — for example, by having the output provide &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/how-ai-driven-nudges-can-transform-an-operations-performance&quot;>;more encouraging feedback during employee onboarding&lt;/a>;. In one &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0022242920956676&quot;>;study&lt;/a>;, the AI coaching tool was found most effective for moderately skilled employees, as less-skilled employees sometimes found the feedback overwhelming (too many suggestions), while more-skilled employees sometimes found it lacking in nuance. What employees want is personalized coaching, so it&#39;s important to pick an AI tool that&#39;s flexible enough to accommodate the array of people and situations in your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Train managers intensively&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many managers could benefit from &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/most-managers-dont-know-how-to-coach-people-but-they-can-learn&quot;>;basic training in effective coaching&lt;/a>;, including how to embed genuine empathy and compassion in the process. Integrating AI tools will require additional &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/technology-skills-employees-should-have-fdc6c0ba&quot;>;upskilling of managers&lt;/a>;. They should be trained not only in technical know-how but in how to translate AI-generated data sensitively and competently to employees. AI tools may also prove useful for training new managers by providing practice cases and other forms of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.yu.edu/facultynews/wp-content/uploads/sites/13/2022/05/Flaherty_2022_J-of-SW-Education.pdf&quot;>;experiential learning&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI tools hold special promise for increasing the frequency, personalization, and accuracy of coaching, without increasing the burden on managers. These gains are not guaranteed, however. To be successful, it&#39;s critical to integrate AI technology in a way that leads to a better &lt;em>;human&lt;/em>; experience for both managers and employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Where Religious Identity Fits into Your DEI Strategy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/Jun23_03_1383510658.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/golero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies generally avoid acknowledging religious differences at work because they fear doing so creates legal risk.这是短视的。 People&amp;#8217;s religious identity is a form of diversity, so religion must be part of any company&amp;#8217;s DEI strategy. These seven best practices will help companies embrace religious diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;It is time for companies to get religion. Even as diversity work has become pervasive in corporate cultures, religious identity is too often left out. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;review of the Fortune 100&lt;/a>; companies demonstrates that a very small percentage include religion or interfaith engagement in their approach to diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many corporations shy away from such engagement out of a fear of legal entanglement, or a worry that it might open the floodgates to proselytization and disagreement. But including religion in your DEI efforts can create belonging among employees and help them better serve a wider range of customers. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;recent research&lt;/a>; and practice show that honoring religious identity not only leads to greater employee engagement, but also has benefits beyond employee morale.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are seven best practices companies should adopt to positively engage with and benefit from religious diversity in the workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Change your mindset from “religion is a risk” to “religion is an asset.”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup-international.bg/en/36009/religion-prevails-in-the-world/&quot;>;Sixty-two percent of people in the world define themselves as religious&lt;/a>;, and even more say they believe in God. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgespan.org/getmedia/0952bd65-31a2-4d9a-97b0-5926ef1f48e6/elevating-the-role-of-faith-inspired-impact-in-the-social-sector-jan-2021.pdf&quot;>;Seventy-seven percent of Americans say religion is very or somewhat important&lt;/a>; in their lives. Roughly 30% of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgespan.org/getmedia/0952bd65-31a2-4d9a-97b0-5926ef1f48e6/elevating-the-role-of-faith-inspired-impact-in-the-social-sector-jan-2021.pdf&quot;>;social sector organizations in the United States have a faith affiliation&lt;/a>; and are providing critical services for people of all religious or nonreligious backgrounds. At the same time, as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crs/highlights/2021-hate-crime-statistics&quot;>;hate crimes related to religion are on the rise nationally&lt;/a>;, many Americans view religion as a topic not fit for the workplace, citing interpersonal conflicts, tensions among peers, safety concerns, and legal conflicts as possible outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies that openly acknowledge and engage religious diversity as an asset, however, can strengthen team cohesion and improve performance. Accenture, for example, is designated as the number one Global 500 “faith and belief friendly company,” according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/redi-index-2023&quot;>;2023 Religious Equity Diversity and Inclusion (REDI) Index&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;.&lt;/u>; Accenture offers inclusive holiday policies and religious literacy training, among other hallmarks. At the first annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://marriott.byu.edu/event/faithatworkcomp/speakers&quot;>;Faith &amp;amp; Belief @ Work case competition&lt;/a>;, held at Brigham Young University in February, Sumreen Ahmed, a global change management lead at Accenture, &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/2/post/2023/02/four-areas-where-the-impact-of-faith-in-systems-cannot-be-ignored.html&quot;>;spoke to the power of engaging religious diversity&lt;/a>;: “If leaders want to create an environment where people are not only incentivized to come to work but also where they can thrive for the greater good, they need to start by understanding what matters most.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Treating religion as an asset and giving employees permission &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-talk-about-religion-at-work&quot;>;to talk about religion&lt;/a>; at work is the first step to harnessing the power of religious diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Articulate clear guidelines for engaging religious diversity inside your company.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Americans say they &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prri.org/spotlight/corporate-america-leads-in-exposing-americans-to-diversity/&quot;>;encounter religious diversity at work&lt;/a>; more than in any other sphere of their lives. As we argue here, diverse identities and perspectives in the workplace &lt;em>;can&lt;/em>; lead to stronger teams and greater outcomes, but if not engaged properly, they can also lead to misunderstanding and conflict.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Religious inclusion at work must respect the dignity of all employees: those who choose to express their religious identities, those who claim no religious identity, and those who choose not to disclose their religious identity. Establishing a set of principles that detail how a company will engage religion can mitigate anti-religious or interreligious bias, prevent potential interpersonal tensions from escalating, and encourage innovative ways to activate religious diversity for the benefit of all. Tips for creating a framework include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Link the framework to existing company values&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Underscore the positive contributions of religious identity and diversity&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Acknowledge support for expressing religious identities in the workplace&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Establish guardrails to ensure equal treatment across diverse groups&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Encourage opportunities for collaboration across religious, spiritual, and secular identities&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Lift up professional development resources available to employees to deepen knowledge of diverse religious traditions&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Cecilia Persson-Ramos, DEI ERG leader at Intuit, proactively adopted a set of principles last summer to guide the company&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.intuit.com/blog/life-at-intuit/building-inclusion-empowering-confidence-through-religious-accommodations/&quot;>;faith-based ERGs&lt;/a>;. Included in the principles is support for each ERG as it observes its particular religious practices, while also encouraging ERGs to work with one another on collaborative events. “We&#39;ve already started to see the impact,” she told us. “Members feel seen and heard and there&#39;s increased cooperation for the good of the whole community.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Develop religious literacy to recognize religious diversity.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Companies can grow their businesses by cultivating an eye for issues related to religious expression. Just ask Martha Moore, who developed &lt;a href=&quot;https://about.nike.com/en/newsroom/releases/nike-victory-swim-collection-official-images-and-release-date&quot;>;Nike&#39;s Victory Swim Collection&lt;/a>; after noticing Muslim women sitting on the shore instead of going in the water while on a beach vacation. She &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/culture/on-and-off-the-avenue/nike-takes-the-plunge-into-modest-swimwear&quot;>;recognized a market&lt;/a>; for modest swimwear for hundreds of millions of Muslim women around the world by paying attention — and generated millions in revenue for Nike as a result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Meeting the needs of a particular religious community can also serve to elevate a brand and build loyalty among a subset of customers. For example, Google offers a &lt;a href=&quot;https://qiblafinder.withgoogle.com/intl/en/desktop/finder&quot;>;qibla finder&lt;/a>; to help Muslims anywhere in the world orient &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whyislam.org/kaba/&quot;>;toward the Kaaba&lt;/a>; in Saudi Arabia for their &lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/uae/why-do-muslims-pray-five-times-a-day-and-what-does-it-signify/articleshow/94053372.cms?from=mdr&quot;>;five daily prayers&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the same time, neglecting to recognize religious expression at work can lead to legal consequences. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/faces-eeoc-samantha-elauf&quot;>;EEOC v. Abercrombie&lt;/a>;, the Supreme Court ruled 8–1 in favor of Samantha Elauf, the young Muslim woman who wasn&#39;t offered a job at an Abercrombie store in Tulsa, OK because &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/02/us/supreme-court-rules-in-samantha-elauf-abercrombie-fitch-case.html&quot;>;her hijab didn&#39;t comply with Abercrombie&#39;s “look policy&lt;/a>;.”&amp;nbsp;In the majority opinion, &lt;a href=&quot;https://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/575/14-86/#tab-opinion-3413626&quot;>;Justice Scalia held&lt;/a>; that it is incumbent upon the employer to know when an article of clothing is related to religious expression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies are responsible, under the law, for equipping team members with the skills to effectively recognize and accommodate religious identity in the workplace. More than that, having an eye for religious diversity can lead to new product development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Know the law — but not for the reasons you think.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Risk is frequently cited as one of the biggest barriers to religious engagement for C-suite leaders. However, not engaging religious identity as part of corporate culture is the riskier choice. Provided that is pursued in a respectful and equitable manner, the benefits for a company in openly engaging religious identity at work outweigh the risks of breaking what some see as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;“church-state” firewall&lt;/a>;, or the secular tone of the corporate setting&lt;strong>;. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Andrea Lucas, a commissioner at the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/eeoc-commissioner-andrea-lucas&quot;>;is an outspoken advocate&lt;/a>; for engaging religious identity in the workplace as the best way to avoid a lawsuit. The EEOC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/laws/guidance/section-12-religious-discrimination&quot;>;Compliance Manual on Religious Discrimination&lt;/a>; offers up-to-date guidelines and practical case studies to support business leaders as they navigate tricky issues related to religion at work. According to Lucas, it&#39;s companies that avoid religious identity that end up in challenging positions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies should advocate for education around legal risks and remedies and seek ways that religious inclusion can be a brand builder, not a risk minefield.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Provide meaningful and flexible accommodations for employees&#39; diverse religious practices.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many aspects of religious expression intersect with company policies, like time off and scheduling. Here&#39;s how some companies have provided accommodations:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Holidays:&lt;/strong>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/are-non-christian-employees-represented-in-your-holiday-policies&quot;>;When creating time off policies&lt;/a>;, companies can offer floating holidays, giving employees the flexibility to choose which holidays are meaningful to them, whether religious or secular. &lt;a href=&quot;https://static.googleusercontent.com/media/about.google/en/belonging/diversity-annual-report/2023/static/pdfs/google_2023_diversity_annual_report.pdf?cachebust=d0bd616&quot;>;Google took it one step further&lt;/a>; and made an inclusive scheduling guide for employees on accommodating diverse religious practices.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Dietary restrictions:&lt;/strong>; Adherence to different religious traditions often includes dietary restrictions: Some Hindus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/07/08/eight-in-ten-indians-limit-meat-in-their-diets-and-four-in-ten-consider-themselves-vegetarian/#:~:text=For%20example%2C%20Hindu%20texts%20often,teachings%2C%20meanwhile%2C%20prohibit%20pork&quot;>;do not eat beef&lt;/a>;, some Muslims and Jews &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sun-sentinel.com/2016/07/07/halal-or-kosher-no-pork-muslims-and-jews-have-common-ground/&quot;>;do not eat pork&lt;/a>;, some Mormons &lt;a href=&quot;https://pacific.churchofjesuschrist.org/why-mormons-dont-drink-alcohol-tea-and-coffee#:~:text=In%20the%20Word%20of%20Wisdom,see%20D%26C%2089%3A8).&quot;>;do not drink caffeine or alcohol&lt;/a>;, and some Buddhists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/buddhist-diet&quot;>;are vegetarian&lt;/a>;. At Interfaith America, we gather dietary restrictions during the onboarding process, which are then populated into a shared document available to all managers who order food for work events.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Spaces for observance:&lt;/strong>; Companies can provide a designated prayer or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workitdaily.com/things-didnt-know-working-nike/3-you-re-given-summer-fridays&quot;>;meditation space&lt;/a>; in the office for employees of any faith or tradition to pray or reflect. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibtimes.com/keep-faith-work-3685588&quot;>;Texas Instruments provides 24/7 access to serenity rooms&lt;/a>; at several of their campuses.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;Offer ongoing religious diversity skill-building opportunities for all employees.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rev. David Keck, chaplain at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University in Daytona Beach, Florida, tells the story of a fellow faculty member who, when he was a commercial pilot, was alerted by his crew before takeoff to a man who was moving his body rhythmically and speaking a foreign language. Rather than succumb to knee-jerk racial profiling and/or anti-religious bias, the pilot drew on his religious literacy to ascertain that the man was simply praying with his whole body, as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.myjewishlearning.com/article/physical-movement-in-jewish-prayer/&quot;>;Orthodox Jews &lt;/a>;(and many others!) do daily. The pilot reassured his crew and the flight took off as scheduled. Keck prompts the students in his Religion, Conflict, and Peace class to imagine how the story would have turned out differently — and likely led to unfavorable news headlines — had the pilot not been familiar with Jewish prayer practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From interns to senior executives, employees across every sector need skills and knowledge to engage religious diversity to be successful in their roles. Sixty percent of companies in North America &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benefitscanada.com/news/bencan/68-of-north-american-employers-have-a-formal-dei-program-survey/#:~:text=More%20than%20two%2Dthirds%20(68,surveys%20by%20Leger%20Marketing%20Inc.&quot;>;offer regular diversity &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benefitscanada.com/news/bencan/68-of-north-american-employers-have-a-formal-dei-program-survey/#:~:text=More%20than%20two%2Dthirds%20(68,surveys%20by%20Leger%20Marketing%20Inc.&quot;>;trainings&lt;/a>; for their employees, but few include a robust focus on religion. Best practice pedagogy from Interfaith America&#39;s 20-year history of training and equipping leaders to engage religious diversity includes case studies, storytelling, and practical application to inspire and equip team members for success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Upskilling a company&#39;s workforce to meaningfully engage religious diversity in a nuanced and constructive way will pay dividends across the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Support interfaith ERGs and other employee-led efforts to engage religious diversity.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.interfaithbusinessnetwork.com/podcast/episode-2&quot;>;Interfaith Employee Resource Groups (ERGs&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;)&lt;/u>; are one important tool for creating an inclusive workplace culture. According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/redi-index-2023&quot;>;2023 REDI Index&lt;/a>;, only 8.6% of Fortune 500 companies publicly report having faith-oriented ERGs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salesforce&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.salesforce.com/company/equality/equality-groups/#eq-sf-fh&quot;>;Faithforce&lt;/a>; is one example of a best-in-class employee-led interfaith effort to build belonging across diverse identities. From the beginning, Faithforce leadership made it clear that their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.salesforce.com/blog/faith-inclusion-workplace/&quot;>;goal was not proselytizing or politics&lt;/a>;, but focused instead on engaging religion as part of the company&#39;s diversity efforts. Farah Siddiqui, cofounder and global president of Faithforce from 2017 to 2021 (and now supporting faith inclusion at Google) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.interfaithamerica.org/religion-at-work-how-to-get-dei-right/&quot;>;shares lessons learned&lt;/a>; with leaders looking to jumpstart interfaith engagement in their workplaces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Hallmarks of high-impact interfaith ERGs include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;A clear charter naming what it is and is not appropriate behavior&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.equinix.com/blog/2023/05/05/equinix-faithconnect-welcomes-those-from-all-beliefs/&quot;>;Celebrations of religious holidays&lt;/a>; to support team members and educate others&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Events focused on &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.aa.com/american-stories/american-stories-details/2017/Faith-and-Love-Religious-diversity-groups-find-common-message-during-roundtable-discussion/default.aspx&quot;>;exploring shared values&lt;/a>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Resources explaining diverse religious traditions&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Community collaborations &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/729586950?embedded=true&amp;amp;source=vimeo_logo&amp;amp;owner=56118460&quot;>;in response to a humanitarian crisis&lt;/a>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;American corporations have long sought to avoid religious engagement in the workplace, fearing legal risks and the unfamiliar terrain of engaging the multiplicity of religious traditions in an ever-increasingly diverse workforce. By proactively engaging religious diversity at work, companies prevent crises, broaden brand loyalty, strengthen company culture, and increase team cohesion and effectiveness.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>