<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How to Proactively Defuse Tension on Your Team]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_691050121.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;未解决和未解决的人际关系紧张和有害行为可能导致组织失败。它们会影响团队绩效、协作和生产力，在团队之间造成运营摩擦，并导致员工感到疏离、不信任和没有动力。虽然工作中的冲突是不可避免的，但我们通常有自己的代理机构来主动根除问题，并以同理心、责任心、自我意识和勇气阻止问题迅速升级。作为首席人力官的作者提供了五个步骤来做到这一点：1）根除有害行为和紧张，2）寻求理解，而不仅仅是被理解，3）评估干预的正确时间，4）寻求帮助， 5) 修复伤害；修复信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on- your-team?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>; Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;作为首席人事官，我亲眼目睹了未解决和未解决的人际关系紧张和不良行为如何导致组织失败。微妙的种族歧视、对项目可交付成果的争论，或者对被认为不公平的优势的八卦，都会对团队绩效、协作和生产力产生负面影响，在团队之间造成运营摩擦，并导致员工感到不敬业、不信任和没有动力。这些问题可能由多种因素引起，包括个性和观点的差异、种族、阶级&lt;strong>;、&lt;/strong>;和性别特权、工作和沟通方式、权力失衡和/或缺乏透明度和清晰度&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-navigate-conflict-with-a-coworker&quot;>;工作中的人际冲突是不可避免的&lt;/a>; ，我们常常忘记我们自己的机构来根除问题，并以同理心、责任感、自我意识和勇气阻止问题迅速升级。这样做会让人感到害怕和危险，尤其是当你是一名初级团队成员或属于一个或多个代表性不足的群体时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最近，一位年轻的有色人种女性表达了保留意见，她是我所在组织的一颗冉冉升起的新星关于加入一个可以显着提升她的职业生涯的新团队。在与团队经理的谈话中，当他对社交活动中员工的种族隔离问题发表了麻木不仁的评论时，她感到很困扰。由于担心她的职业生涯以及可能存在种族敌对或不舒服的工作环境，这位经理可能不尊重她的身份和经历，她向人力资源业务合作伙伴寻求指导，后者将她介绍给了我。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们讨论了她期望的结果是加入团队，同时让经理对他的言论的影响负责，并鼓励他改进他的行为。我让她选择直接解决这个问题，或者在谈话中得到我的支持，优先考虑她的安全和尊严。深思熟虑后，她选择了直接参与。我指导她如何自信而深思熟虑地表达自己。随后，她分享了一个积极的结果——经理表现出同理心，真诚地道歉，并承诺与整个团队公开承认不屑一顾的评论。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据这名员工和其他许多人的经历，我在我的职业生涯中一直担任教练，如果您在工作场所目睹或经历伤害，您可以&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;采取以下五项措施来减少或停止人际关系紧张和有害行为：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;强>;1。确定紧张的根本原因。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在处理工作场所的人际摩擦时，第一步是确定根本原因——紧张的真正来源。艾米·埃德蒙森 (Amy Edmondson) 在她的&lt;em>;无所畏惧的组织&lt;/em>;一书中探讨了组织中缺乏心理安全感的代价，包括有毒的工作环境、倦怠和人力资本损失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;消除不健康的因素降低个人和团队的安全、舒适度和绩效的行为要求我们面对需要改变的东西。在如何运行项目、与哪些合作伙伴合作以及绩效衡量方面的权力不平衡和意见分歧往往是误解、分歧和合作崩溃的根本原因。在这些情况下，初级员工、有色人种女性和代表性不足的员工往往害怕说出冲突，因为害怕遭到报复或受到负面评价。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在上面的例子中，紧张的根本原因是经理对种族不敏感的评论，导致人们担心工作环境可能充满敌意或不舒服，缺乏尊重，并无视这位有色人种女性和其他人的生活经历。通过以支持、同理心和勇气来处理此类情况，我们可以发现并解决紧张局势的根本原因，并防止它们对个人的福祉和职业发展产生负面影响。重要的是要认识到这种方法可能并不总是可行或安全的。在这种情况下，该员工相信如果谈话偏离正轨，我会进行干预。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.寻求理解，而不仅仅是被理解。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;职业关系是充满误解的人际关系。在压力大的时刻，一个错误的、无意的词，尤其是那些受性别和种族偏见影响的词，可能会在同事之间造成深深的隔阂。要建立共识，重要的是要为他人的意见留出空间，对复杂和微妙的情况产生同理心，并承担起在同事之间培养安全感和信任感的责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这种情况下，经理拥抱连接、学习和成长的机会，寻求理解他们的言行的影响，而不是采取防御姿态。这种反应表明愿意承认错误并努力改变，而不用担心显得无能或被取消。经理没有转移或抱怨领导挑战，而是将团队的福祉放在首位。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过帮助经理看到并理解她的担忧，该员工表现出了非凡的同理心。尽管她不理会这位经理是公平的，但她认识到了成长的机会并参与了建设性的对话。这种方法使她能够在解决经理对不敏感评论缺乏认识的问题上主张她的代理权。她选择了一种协作方式，让其他人可以学习和改进。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他们的互动生动地展示了开放、安全和信任的沟通的变革力量，突出了当双方处理棘手问题时积极改变的巨大潜力，带着真实的理解和被理解意图进行不舒服的对话。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.评估干预的正确时间。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;说点什么和不说点什么都是会产生深远影响的选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有时，干预可以在当下或短期内发生在那之后。如果你单独与某人分享冒犯性、诽谤性或贬损性评论，并且觉得有可能说出可能被误解或针对你的武器，请等到周围有其他人可以提供支持或向人力资源部报告或匿名热线。或者，如果你觉得舒服，你可以试着说，“当你说 ___ 时，我感觉 ____”或“我确定你不是那个意思，但我不太喜欢那个评论。”接收反馈的人可能需要了解他们的言行的影响。等待时间过长可能会导致负面情绪在您和他人的内心挥之不去并不断滋长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果该员工没有分享她的担忧，或者如果该经理以防御和报复的方式做出回应，就会错失培养健康员工的机会和繁荣的工作环境。此外，这可能会延续一种恐惧文化，给她和其他有类似恐惧的员工带来负担，最终阻碍他们在整个职业生涯中的成长和幸福。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4.寻求帮助。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;随着我在职业生涯中的进步，我渴望能够利用自己的权威地位来挑战有害行为的领导者。当我自己担任领导角色时，我意识到责任落在我身上，以身作则来体现我想要的行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您在处理棘手情况或组织的冲突解决、申诉和纪律程序，求助于您的人力资源团队。我理解接触时的犹豫，尤其是当你与 HR 的关系不牢固时。尽管如此，人力资源部还是要提倡员工的发言权、代理权和安全性。他们可以帮助您收集信息、了解根本原因并确定适当的行动。人力资源合作伙伴可以促进建设性对话，指导您和其他相关人员，并找到解决行为问题的主动解决方案。谨慎处理此选项很重要，因为它可能会加剧团队成员之间的紧张或不适。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/featured %20insights/diversity%20and%20inclusion/women%20in%20the%20workplace%202022/women-in-the-workplace-2022.pdf&quot;>;Women in the Workplace 2022&lt;/a>;，LeanIn 和麦肯锡关于该州的年度报告美国企业中的女性，整体女性，尤其是黑人女性和残疾女性，经常在工作中遭受微侵犯，例如她们的判断力受到质疑或因举止受到批评。从工作场所的可用资源中寻求支持可以在促进繁荣和健康的职业生涯方面产生重大影响。让同事、经理和领导承担责任对于解决和减轻这些有害经历至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个例子中，员工向 HR 寻求指导以应对这种复杂情况。通过利用可用资源，她使自己能够有效地解决问题，从而使她和团队中其他人的体验发生重大变化。她主动寻求帮助、乐于接受反馈并进行自我反省，这对取得积极成果发挥了关键作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5.修复伤害；修复信任。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;重复的伤害行为，例如微妙的&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/research-the-real-time-impact-of-microaggressions&quot;>;微攻击&lt;/ a>;, 会严重影响幸福感、工作场所满意度和生产力。要从误解、不一致的观点或期望、伤人的语言、滥用权力或背信而引起的人际关系紧张中痊愈，受伤害的人必须感到被倾听、被尊重和被重视。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据 Kay Pranis 的说法，恢复性司法的全国领导者，承担责任并采取措施纠正造成的损害并防止其再次发生需要 &lt;a href=&quot;https://irp.cdn-website.com/76b5fa75/files/uploaded/Kay%20Pranis% 20Article%20for%20March%20Blog.pdf&quot;>;五个要素&lt;/a>;：&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;承认您的行为造成了伤害。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;承认您在这些行为中有代理权.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;了解您的行为对任何受到影响的人的全部影响。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;采取措施修复伤害并做出补偿。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;确定影响行为的模式或习惯导致造成伤害并采取措施改变这些习惯。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;修复伤害可以通过多种方式体现：承认伤害、表达悔意、承认有罪并承诺通过新政策改变行为，承诺或协议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为有色人种女性，我听到过相当多的冒犯、不安或伤害我的评论，很遗憾，我也曾对其他人做过同样的事情。每当我成为微攻击的目标时，我都会在与同事打交道之前先收拾好自己的想法和情绪，用“我”的陈述自信地回应，并经常以友善和幽默的方式回应以缓和紧张情绪。例如：“当你在回顾会议上重申我的建议时，却没有表扬我，我觉得自己被从我们的谈话中抹去了。我希望我们有健康的工作关系。你能帮我理解为什么你忽略了我的贡献吗？”或者：“当你把我当成地板上的另一个拉丁裔时，我觉得你看不到我们。而且我认为我非常令人难忘！”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我无意中做出不敏感的评论时，例如对某人性别歧视，我会立即以谦逊的态度接近受影响的人。我真诚地倾听以了解我的话的影响并表示衷心的道歉，同时对我的言行承担全部责任。如果我重复这种行为，我也鼓励他们给我打电话，因为我致力于从错误中吸取教训并不断成长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;需要明确的是，这不是女性、BIPOC 或边缘化群体成员的责任社区教育他们的同事如何促进健康的互动。要主动建立更有意义的关系，请问自己以下问题：我如何才能专注于对方所说的内容，而不仅仅是关注他们的说话方式或外表？我还需要知道什么才能理解我的同事试图传达的内容，而不是驳斥或回避他们所说的内容？在解决某人令人不安的评论之前，问问自己：我是在回应被关闭、忽视或冒犯，还是在努力做到正确？如果双方都愿意，有一些回应方式可以导致建设性对话和共同理解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尤其必须解决重复的伤害行为。麻省理工学院斯隆管理学院 &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/toxic-culture-is-driving-the-great-resignation/&quot;>;2022 年的一项研究&lt;/a>;发现有毒的企业文化对员工流动率的影响是薪酬的 10 倍。承担责任意味着了解团队之间广泛的观点和经验，并主动识别紧张的根源。一个好的起点是问问自己，“我需要听到什么，我需要说什么，我希望看到什么结果？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个例子中，经理采取了必要的修复他麻木不仁的评论最初破坏的信任的步骤。他通过承认自己的言论造成的伤害并进行公开对话来表现出责任感。通过积极努力了解他的话的影响并提出采取切实措施改变他的行为，他成功地开始修复与新员工的信任，并且很可能修复他与更广泛团队的关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们中的许多人都想改变工作环境，让每个人都能茁壮成长，但有时，我们害怕搞砸、说错话或做得不够。解决人际关系紧张和毒性需要持续、积极的努力，以培养同理心、意向性和勇气。通过确定紧张局势的真正根源、寻求理解、评估何时进行干预、在必要时让中立的第三方参与进来以及快速且经常地修复伤害和信任，您可以防止冲突升级并建立更强大、更紧密、更有效的关系团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Game Plan for Funding Carbon Offsets]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_-537715290_-1363813940.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;插图：Edmon de Haro； Baloncici/Getty Images（烟囱）； Vitalina/Getty Images（蝴蝶）&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp ;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;最常见的碳补偿类型是基于自然的补偿，例如森林。不幸的是，虽然排放物会在大气中保留大约 1,000 年（可能更长），但一棵树只能在其 10 年左右的生命周期内去除碳，这意味着作为碳抵消而种植的森林必须保持至少十次重新种植树木以&amp;#160;匹配它抵消的排放量。大多数企业都不愿意以这种方式占用资本，但此类项目可以（并且已经）通过永久债券融资，这对投资者来说是有吸引力的投资，例如大学捐赠基金的负债流很长，可以延伸到很远的未来。永久债券等金融工具的使用可以为抵消生产者提供大量可用资本，刺激抵消生产和现货市场的创建，从而最终可靠地抵消排放。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/ a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot; font-weight: 400;&quot;>;2015 年 9 月，耶鲁大学 Beinecke 善本和手稿图书馆的馆长前往阿姆斯特丹，在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.yale.edu /2015/09/22/living-artifact-dutch-golden-age-yale-s-367-year-old-water-bond-still-pays-interest&quot;>;1648 年 5 月 15 日发行的债券&lt;/a>; .在债券发行时，借款人（一家荷兰自治水务机构）承诺向持有人&lt;em>;永久&lt;/em>;支付利息。出售债券所得的现金已用于支付防止海平面上升的基础设施项目。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;此类永久债券可能在当今应对气候变化的斗争中发挥作用通过为将无限期清除和储存碳的项目提供资金来改变。碳清除可用于抵消碳排放负债（或&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/accounting-for-climate-change&quot;>;电子负债&lt;/a>;），从而帮助企业和其他组织实现净-零目标。永续债券还可以支持有效的&lt;em>;现货市场&lt;/em>;在去除抵消方面的发展，刺激它们的生产和使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;永续债券有助于解决许多碳抵消的持续时间与它们要抵消的电子负债的持续时间之间的关键不匹配。正如我们在 7 月至 8 月的《哈佛商业评论》印刷文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/accounting-for-carbon-offsets&quot;>;碳补偿核算&lt;/a>;”中指出的那样，&amp;nbsp;来自温室气体的电子负债排放对金融市场构成特殊挑战，因为今天产生的排放预计会在大气中存留 1,000 多年，持续时间远远长于典型的金融负债。鉴于此，我们确定可抵消碳排放资产（E 资产）也需要&lt;em>;无限期&lt;/em>;持续时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;某些 E - 通过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usgs.gov/news/featured-story/making-minerals-how-growing-rocks-can-help-reduce-carbon-emissions&quot;获取碳捕获和储存等资产>;地下矿化&lt;/a>;明确符合这一标准，但此类电子资产目前并不常见。今天更为普遍的是基于自然的补偿 (NBO)，例如原始造林计划，由于森林的&lt;em>;有限&lt;/em>;（未补充）生命周期（可能少于 100 年），持续时间通常较短。那么，问题在于 NBO 是否可以用于抵消 E 负债：如果不能，那么今天提供的大多数清除抵消只是长期排放负债的预付款。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font -weight: 400;&quot;>;对于无限期 NBO，发行人必须承诺永久管理标的（森林）资产——也就是说，在森林的组成树木自然腐烂或被疾病、火灾等毁坏时重新种植森林. 为了资助这项行动，抵消提供者不仅需要资金来购买土地和植树，还需要提供可预测的永久性支出。换句话说，他们必须将筹集到的任何资金的一部分投资于捐赠基金，其回报可以用于为森林管理提供资金，从而使碳无限期地被封存（定义为 1,000 年，这是一个合理的科学估计今天排放的碳将在大气中停留多长时间）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;此外，鉴于无限期的承诺，发行人想要限定其目前交付的一部分（或“已赚取”）清除抵消，因为可以立即完全抵消购买者的电子负债，因此必须单独（明显更大）留出一部分可用的已赚取抵消，以抵消未来的固碳承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;所有这些都意味着向 NBO 抵消生产者提供资金的人可以期望他们的投资回报相对较低，尽管是永久分配的。个人抵消购买者（通常是营利性企业）不会发现以这种方式占用自己的资金有吸引力。但这样的投资可能对那些需要捐赠来支付未来可预测债务的机构很有吸引力，比如大学和教堂。投资将采取永久债券的形式——例如荷兰水务局发行的债券——或具有固定股息的优先股。普通股可能不适合为无限期移除抵消提供资金，因为投资者通常希望获得有保证的回报，以永久锁定资本且上涨空间有限。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;考虑一下，作为一个关于永久债券方法如何运作的假设示例，加拿大的一个土著部落希望出售原始森林中的可净电子资产，并将在其土地上种植并无限期管理。为此，它必须筹集资金来开发和维护森林。部落可以发行永久债券，并将部分资本投入永久性金融捐赠基金。部落使用捐赠的利息来支付管理森林的费用。随着森林的抵消成为“赚取的”——也就是说，树木成熟并吸收碳——部落可以出售这些电子资产的一部分来支付费用，包括永久债券的利息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;让我们假设 20 兆吨的 CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; 当量 (MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e) 从森林当前的树木中“捕获”年和未来 100 年都将如此，但树木必须至少再种植 10 次才能抵消 1,000 年的 E-liability。为分配此承诺的风险，部落可以将今年补偿的 2 MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e 永久“赚取”（即 20 Mt 除以 10）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;如果有足够多的 NBO 抵消生产者和足够的需求，可净抵消可以出售到流动性市场，从而将森林的未来风险分配给一系列抵消购买者和帮助部落履行其利益义务。明年的现货买家可能与今年的不同，事实上，数百年后的现货买家可能会有很大不同，但通过共同贡献永续债券的利息成本，他们分担了 NBO 的长期时间序列风险.只要可净抵消的现货销售和捐赠回报的收益超过债券的利息支出和持续的森林管理成本，该计划对部落来说就是有利可图的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400; “>;很有可能，375 年前没有人预料到荷兰海堤管理债券会在今天向 3,500 英里外的新英格兰大学图书馆支付利息。同样，我们无法预测金融市场将如何发展以满足排放责任管理的需要。但此处列出的途径提出了一个可行的市场解决方案，以减轻当今碳排放的长期后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Company Prepared for the Effects of Wildfires?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_1258513476.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Angela Weiss/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;今天的野火和烟雾可以传播数百英里，模糊了工作场所内外发生的劳动力之间的界限健康。现在是雇主制定计划以应对这一问题和其他气候变化驱动的健康问题的时候了。作者建议采取六项行动：1）将全球野火与当地健康联系起来； 2) 收集和评估空气质量数据，为劳动力咨询制定阈值； 3) 确定企业响应团队中的主要利益相关者并激活您的指挥中心； 4) 确定何时对户外工作者采取行动； 5) 确定如何支持室内办公室员工； 6) 为您的员工制定沟通和教育计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your -company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for- the-effects-of-wildfires?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;野火。几代人以来，这个词一直让中小农村社区心存恐惧。现在，由于北美部分地区被烟雾笼罩，美国城市和总部设在那里的公司也开始意识到自己也很脆弱。上周，东海岸城市从&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/live/2023/06/07/us/canada-wildfires-air-quality-smoke&quot;>;纽约&lt;/a>;到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/air-quality-toronto-fires-smoke-1.6868010&quot;>;多伦多&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-wildfire-smoke-canada-updates-june-7/&quot;>;蒙特利尔&lt;/a>;看到空气质量迅速下降到世界上最差的一些，因为&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.wsj.com/articles/smoke-air-quality-nyc-northeast-canadian-wildfires-6b5ffc01&quot;>;加拿大野火产生的烟雾&lt;/a>;向南飘去。这意味着美国企业界的讨论已经超越了室内空气循环或过滤，也涵盖了室外空气质量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;空气质量差会影响 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ishn.com/ articles/113569-how-poor-iaq-impacts-employee-safety-and-productivity&quot;>;员工健康和生产力&lt;/a>;，来自&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/news /press-releases/office-air-quality-may-affect-employees-cognition-productivity/&quot;>;认知功能&lt;/a>;和较差的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w20648&quot; >;集中&lt;/a>;以降低&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/09/air-pollution-is-making-office-workers-less-productive&quot;>;生产力&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https:// iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/ab8b8c&quot;>;情绪&lt;/a>;。它还会加剧健康状况，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7503605/&quot;>;哮喘&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2022.926534/full&quot;>;焦虑&lt;/a>;并导致&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unicef.org/mongolia/media/2926/file/UNICEF-旷工-ENG-final.pdf&quot;>;旷工&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9554460/&quot;>;出勤&lt;/a>;和&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.graduateinstitute.ch/sites/internet/files/2021-04/HHW_2020.pdf&quot;>;请假&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;野火和烟雾扰乱了企业旅行，推迟公司活动，并让员工去看医生以解决一系列相关的健康问题，包括呼吸困难。不幸的是，未来可能还会有更多——&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epa.gov/climate-indicators/climate-change-indicators-wildfires&quot;>;气候变化&lt;/a>;意味着野火季节增加长度、频率和烧伤面积。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一名在国际组织工作并为公司领导提供建议的医生，我们看到雇主对员工健康和空气质量问题最佳实践的询问迅速增加。人力资源团队正在回答员工和领导者提出的复杂问题——许多人觉得没有准备好正确的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这让人想起 2020 年 3 月 Covid 的高峰期，当时领导者问：这是一个问题吗我们需要回应吗？我需要知道什么？我现在需要采取什么行动？以下是雇主在解决这个持续存在的问题时要考虑的六项行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.将全球野火与当地健康联系起来。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;空气污染可以伤害任何人。但对于特定的员工群体及其家庭成员来说，这更危险。这包括婴幼儿、65 岁以上的老年人、孕妇、任何在户外锻炼或工作的人，以及患有糖尿病、肺病或心脏病等现有疾病或慢性疾病的人。在浓烟条件下，所有员工无论年龄或健康状况如何都可能面临风险。影响可能是身体上的，也可能是心理上的，尤其是对于那些经历过从家中和工作场所撤离的野火创伤的员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;烟雾可以从最初的火区传播数千英里，这意味着其他地方的野火世界将影响您公司运营所在当地社区的员工。野火产生的烟雾包含复杂的污染物混合物，例如细颗粒物。这些颗粒肉眼看不见，但会深入我们的肺部和血液，有时会对健康造成严重影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有证据表明某些污染物处于安全暴露水平，这意味着烟雾会影响员工&#39; 健康甚至在非常低的水平。随着当地烟雾浓度的增加，您的员工面临的健康风险通常也会增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.收集和评估空气质量数据。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;通常可以通过空气质量指数 (AQI) 找到数据，该指数是一种在空气污染达到危险水平时向公众发出警告的系统。 In the US, the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) issues year-round AQI forecasts with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airnow.gov/&quot;>;maps&lt;/a>; showing how pollution levels change and move throughout the day, and other countries have similar resources. This “real-time” information can help employers to quantify current outdoor air quality that impacts both their employees and customers far before it hits front-page news.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend working with health care experts such as physicians or medical consultants to develop specific thresholds for workforce advisories that go along with these levels. Doing so will help you take steps to protect your employees from unhealthy levels of air pollution and enable them to proactively seek appropriate supports for their health and safety. Specific thresholds paired with health care guidance will also prepare managers to communicate with and guide their teams in line with corporate policy. Once your organization understands how to use air quality data and sets monitoring thresholds, it will help trigger your corporate response at the right time and place.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Activate your command center.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Identify who needs to be brought together to respond when AQI thresholds are met, especially if there is an immediate physical health and safety threat to employees. Wildfire-related local evacuations &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/12/how-kaiser-permanente-prepares-for-disasters&quot;>;are particularly high stakes&lt;/a>;, especially when hundreds of thousands evacuate all at once as seen in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/dec/11/southern-california-wildfires-blaze&quot;>;Southern California&lt;/a>;. Your corporate response team may include local business leaders in impacted areas, communications specialists, medical advisors, HR leaders and even risk practitioners given broader enterprise issues involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your multi-disciplinary approach may look similar to governance models &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/leader/early/2020/04/07/leader-2020-000244.full.pdf&quot;>;developed during the Covid pandemic&lt;/a>; and will ensure timely information is continuously flowing to and from the right stakeholders, including executives and the board. It will also enable rapid, holistic decision-making and related corporate response. This may range from meeting occupational health and safety standards to regulatory compliance for different employee segments like indoor versus outdoor workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Focus on outdoor workers, and comply with regulation.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Depending on your industry, outdoor work exposure to wildfire smoke is regulated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/firefighting/wffsmoke.html&quot;>;occupational health and safety&lt;/a>; standards and regulatory bodies like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134&quot;>;Occupational Safety and Health Administration&lt;/a>; (OSHA). Long work schedules and physical work demands may impact a worker&#39;s exposure risk and health response. Geography matters, as local regulations differ. For example, California&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dir.ca.gov/title8/5141_1.html&quot;>;emergency regulation&lt;/a>; applies to workplaces where AQI is greater than 151 or if employees are expected to be exposed to wildfire smoke.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers should know their local air quality regulations and take action to limit outdoor workers&#39; exposure, particularly when wildfire smoke is in or around the work environment. This may include relocating or rescheduling work tasks to smoke-free or less smoky areas or times of the day, reducing levels of physical activity when possible, providing workers with frequent breaks in places that are free from smoke, and offering special accommodations where required.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some situations, the use of personal protective equipment (PPE), such as well-fitted N95 respirators, should be considered to limit workers&#39; exposure. When US employers require use of respiratory protection to limit exposure to smoke, this should occur as part of a comprehensive respiratory protection program as outlined in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134&quot;>;OSHA Respiratory Protection Standard&lt;/a>;. (When use is voluntary, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134AppD&quot;>;other OSHA standards&lt;/a>; apply.)&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Support indoor office employees.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Air quality can be unexpectedly complex for indoor office workers. Corporate safety standards related to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://deloitte.wsj.com/articles/staying-compliant-in-an-era-of-hybrid-and-remote-work-c0e0938e&quot;>;home office&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalguardian.com/global-digest/at-home-duty-of-care&quot;>;worker travel&lt;/a>; have been elevated in recent years. And while it is arguable whether an employer&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1741438/does-employers-duty-care-extend-commuting&quot;>;duty of care&lt;/a>; extends to the employee journey to and from work, the commute matters, especially if an employee needs to navigate significant outdoor air pollution to get to and from the office. Taking a holistic “employee experience journey” approach can help calibrate potential risks for employee segments in hard-hit local areas or where there are specific individual health risk factors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As many office buildings have advanced heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC) systems and optimized Minimum Efficiency Reporting Value (MERV) ratings, the air quality at the office may be superior to that of the average home during wildfire season. Employers may need to take additional actions to reduce exposure to and protect occupants from wildfire smoke. This may include installing air cleaners equipped with high-efficiency particulate air (HEPA) filters, ensuring that windows and other building openings are kept closed to reduce overall smoke exposure inside, operating HVAC systems in the re-circulate setting, or temporarily reducing the amount of outdoor air supplied to the building. If you currently lease office space, engage your landlord to ensure that they optimize protection of your indoor workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More broadly, consider security, medical, and mental-health coverage to keep your people safe in times of crisis. This includes extending fulsome protection to the entire workforce, whether they commute or work indoors or outside. Employees working from home in your local corporate backyard might need that same 24/7 evacuation coverage you previously only considered for international travelers. This coverage applies equally to wildfires as it does to other natural disasters, like flooding or hurricanes, when companies often provide assistance such as food and water, shelter, or emergency evacuation. At many companies, this extra layer of coverage requires a mentality shift, but it is one worth making today.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6. Communicate and educate broadly.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Depending on the scope and scale of a wildfire and its impact on your organization, consider what should be communicated proactively (eg, that your organization is aware of and actively responding to worsening local air quality) and reactively (eg, messaging from HR in relation to very specific individual circumstances requiring accommodations).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Education is an important part of any communication plan related to wildfires and air quality, so alert your employees to symptoms of wildfire smoke exposure. Milder and more common symptoms include headaches, mild cough, sore and watery eyes, and nose, throat, and sinus irritation. More serious but less common symptoms include dizziness, chest pains, severe cough, shortness of breath, wheezing, and even irregular heartbeat. Encourage employees to seek care from a health care provider and consider urgent medical attention if warranted for severe cases such as risks for asthma attacks, stroke, or heart attack.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the case of severe wildfire events, communication may include addressing immediate physical health and safety threats and extend to longer-term practices around air quality and respiratory health. Providing individual employee guidance on what to do to safeguard their health when air quality level is at different thresholds can help. For example, at higher levels, employees can be guided to avoid prolonged vigorous activity outdoors and stay away from high-traffic areas. It may also mean postponing or cancelling certain corporate and team-building events, or moving outdoor gatherings indoors. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.canada.ca/en/health-canada/services/publications/healthy-living/how-prepare-wildfire-smoke.html#:~:text=Checklist%20for%20wildfire%20smoke%20season%20preparedness,-Are%20you%20or&amp;amp;text=Do%20you%20have%20an%20adequate%20supply%20of%20food%20and%20water,a%20break%20from%20the%20smoke%3F&quot;>;Preparedness checklists&lt;/a>; can help and may cover home, office, and personal medical preparedness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today&#39;s wildfires and smoke can travel hundreds of miles, blurring the lines between what happens within and outside the workplace when it comes to workforce health. Now is the time to get ahead of this and other climate change-driven health issues. Source new resources, pilot novel approaches, and translate them into productive corporate action to support employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Your Boss Gives You Bad Feedback, Badly]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_12_1434150794.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;It&amp;#8217;s difficult to manage your feelings when getting feedback that feels too harsh, overly nice, or somehow dishonest. We all struggle with feedback, so extend a little grace to yourself for having strong emotions, and to the other person for initiating a difficult conversation. The authors present the three most common ways people deliver feedback in a way that causes harm and elicits strong emotions, as well as five key steps to take when you get poorly delivered feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/when-your-boss-gives-you-bad-feedback-badly?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Hearing about what you&#39;re not doing well at work can feel bad. That doesn&#39;t make you “defensive” or “shut down to feedback.” It just means you&#39;re human and that you care about your performance — both good things.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even when you receive kind, clear feedback from a manager, peer, or employee, it can still be difficult to learn what you could be doing better. Say to yourself: “This is uncomfortable, and that&#39;s okay. My reaction will pass.” And then do something that allows you to sit with the discomfort for a while. Meditate, take a walk, or journal. Remind yourself that the person is giving you feedback because they care about helping you&lt;em>;. &lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But what happens when the person doesn&#39;t care about you, or when the feedback is poorly delivered? What if the person was rude, insensitive, or unclear? Now is not the time to criticize the criticism. But how can you navigate your own emotional responses to different types of feedback? The only way out of feeling bad about critical feedback is through.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Mollie and Liz are experts in emotions at work and Kim is an expert in feedback at work. Kim&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://review.firstround.com/radical-candor-the-surprising-secret-to-being-a-good-boss&quot;>;radical candor&lt;/a>; framework explains the three most common ways people deliver feedback in a way that causes harm and elicits strong emotions: obnoxious aggression, manipulative insincerity, and ruinous empathy. Together, we&#39;ve identified five key steps to take when you get poorly delivered feedback:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Name your emotion.&lt;/strong>; Figure out how you&#39;re feeling and don&#39;t judge yourself.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/strong>; Look for something helpful in the feedback even if it wasn&#39;t delivered well.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Reward the candor&lt;/strong>; — even if you disagree. Note that this doesn&#39;t mean pretending to agree. Sometimes the best reward for feedback you disagree with is a respectful explanation of why.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/strong>; Talk to the person about the impact of their delivery.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Fish or cut bait.&lt;/strong>; Figure out if you can continue to improve the relationship or if this is someone you need to avoid.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;As with most advice, this is much easier said than done. Here&#39;s how to apply these steps in the face of three common types of poorly delivered feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Obnoxiously Aggressive Feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;What should you do when someone is yelling or using disparaging language? For example, a person once gave Kim some feedback by jabbing his finger in her face as he yelled, “You are the most aggressive woman I ever met!”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This type of feedback usually makes us feel a mix of anger, fear, defensiveness, and anxiety. In addition to the steps below, if you feel that you&#39;re being bullied or verbally abused at work, it&#39;s important to escalate that to a trusted leader or HR rep if you feel safe doing so. If there&#39;s nobody you feel safe going to at work, it&#39;s a sign to start looking for a new job.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Name your emotion.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Give yourself a minute. If you find your emotions are overwhelming, try to create space for yourself or remove yourself from the situation entirely. You might say something like, “I&#39;d like to come back to this later” or “I&#39;m having a strong reaction to your feedback, and I need a moment.” Liz has learned to evaluate her emotions on a scale from 1 (okay) to 10 (enraged or panicking). She aims to wait until she&#39;s settled down to a 3 or 4 before taking action or even responding.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Once you&#39;re calm, think about what was said, not how it was said. Is there some information, no matter how terribly imparted, that can be useful to you or help you succeed? Some people will never tell you what they&#39;re thinking until they&#39;re so angry that they aren&#39;t able to communicate it well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It may be the case that you disagree with the content of the feedback as well as the way it was delivered. That&#39;s okay. But challenge yourself to find one thing the person said, or even one aspect of what they said, that you can agree with. There may be a whole bushel of chaff and only one grain of wheat. Find that grain, and use it to your advantage!&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Reward the candor.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If you agree with any of the feedback, make changes and update the person on what you&#39;re doing differently. If you disagree with it, offer a respectful explanation of why.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Is there a way to relay how their words and actions impacted you? In some situations, it may be effective to share how an overly harsh delivery affects your ability to perform well on the job. In a workshop Liz and Mollie led, for example, a participant shared that her boss used to yell at her frequently. One day she finally said to him, “I know that you&#39;re upset right now, but when you yell at me, I&#39;m not able to focus on my work.” Her boss apologized and realized that he was inadvertently hurting her performance. His outbursts became much less frequent.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Fish or cut bait.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Of course, sometimes when you talk to the person about how what they said impacted you, you&#39;ll learn the person is trying to upset you. In those cases, telling them how they made you feel won&#39;t work. Why tell them they succeeded in upsetting you?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, limit how much you interact with the person. Once Kim told her boss he was being disrespectful; he replied he was offended that she didn&#39;t genuflect enough, or appreciate how superior he was to her. She quit. As &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/i-hate-my-boss/id1148704291?mt=2&quot;>;TV writer Elizabeth Craft advises&lt;/a>;, “If someone handed you a literal glass of poison, you would not drink it — so don&#39;t drink the verbal poison. If someone&#39;s coming at you negatively at work, just don&#39;t ingest.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Manipulatively Insincere Feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When people are worried about their own reputation more than helping you improve, they may say things they don&#39;t really mean. Sometimes people say things to you that feel passive aggressive, or they praise you to your face but criticize you behind your back.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We all do this sometimes. Kim confesses that she had a direct report to whom she gave manipulatively insincere feedback. His work was riddled with careless mistakes. And he was popular and very sensitive. What if he started to cry when she pointed out the mistakes? Worried about her reputation as a leader rather than her direct report&#39;s performance, she&#39;d say something to him along the lines of, “Oh, Alex, this is a great start. You are so incredible. Maybe you can make this a little better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What can you do if someone is giving you praise that feels more like an ego salve than something real? How can you encourage them to say what they really think?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Name your emotion.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When confronted with this behavior, it&#39;s easy to feel confused. If you find out the person is saying nice things to your face and bad things behind your back, you may feel angry, betrayed, or mistrustful. Take a deep breath. Figure out how you&#39;re feeling.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Remember, you&#39;re trying to get feedback that will help you grow. Try asking the person making the comment to clarify what they meant. You might say, “Can you share a bit more about what you mean by that?” or “What would you recommend I do differently?” By asking for more detail, you help prevent miscommunication and give yourself an opportunity to address any underlying issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It might be that the person is simply conflict avoidant. You might make them feel more comfortable sharing if you say something like: “I feel like you have valuable feedback for me, but I&#39;m not sure what you&#39;re trying to communicate. Can you tell me what you&#39;re thinking more directly?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another tactic is to tell the person that you&#39;re working on improving something, and ask them to help you: “I&#39;ve been told I interrupt a lot. Can you help me by passing me this pen if you notice me interrupting someone during the meeting?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Reward the candor.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When a well-intentioned person has a hard time giving feedback, it&#39;s especially important to prove to them that not only is it safe to give you feedback, but that they&#39;ll be rewarded richly if they do. When their feedback results in your action, the risk they took has paid off. Saying thanks is never enough —&amp;nbsp;you need to fix the problem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But when a person praises you to your face and criticizes you behind your back, it&#39;s really hard to reward that kind of passive aggression because you&#39;re not supposed to know what they think. You could ask: “Is there something I could do differently so next time you can tell me what you really think? You told me you thought the presentation went well, but I heard you told others it was terrible. I promise not to bite your head off if you tell me when I&#39;m not hitting the mark. In fact, I&#39;ll be grateful because your feedback is exactly what I need in order to do better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Now that you&#39;re talking, you can ask the person if they can commit to talking to you directly rather than behind your back in the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Fish or cut bait.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If the person apologizes and seems sincere, you can begin to rebuild trust. But if they respond in a way that erodes trust further, aim to regulate your emotions so that their behavior affects you less. Try an imaginary time-travel technique called temporal distancing. “Imagine it is a day, a week, or a year later,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://msande.stanford.edu/research-impact/stories-voices/faculty/faculty-spotlight-bob-sutton&quot;>;says Bob Sutton&lt;/a>;, author of books including &lt;em>;The No Asshole Rule&lt;/em>;. “And you are looking back on it, and it really didn&#39;t last that long or wasn&#39;t nearly as bad as it seemed at the time.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Ruinously Empathetic Feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Sometimes you get the sense the person is so worried about hurting your feelings or offending you that they won&#39;t tell you what they really think. They care, but they&#39;re not challenging you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The part of Kim that was reluctant to tell her popular and sensitive employee Alex when his work wasn&#39;t good enough because of her concern for her reputation as a leader was manipulative insincerity; the “too nice” part of her that was reluctant to tell Alex what he needed to know because she was afraid of hurting his feelings was ruinous empathy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Name your emotion.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When someone is overly nice about their feedback, you may feel unsure about their intentions, or frustrated that they&#39;re not telling you what you need to know to improve. You may wonder if they think you can&#39;t handle the feedback. Maybe that makes you angry. Maybe their ruinous empathy makes them seem weak to you, and maybe that makes you feel disgusted. Emotional responses to ruinous empathy vary widely.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Separate the wheat from the chaff.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;You might say, “While I appreciate that you think I&#39;m doing a great job, I know that there is always room for improvement. When I repeatedly don&#39;t get any constructive feedback from you, it makes me feel like you&#39;re holding back. The only way I can improve is if you give me candid feedback.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You may then need to sit through the other person&#39;s discomfort. Many people who give overly nice feedback will try to wriggle out of saying anything critical. They might repeat, “No really, you&#39;re doing great.” Their discomfort might make you feel that you should let them off the hook.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Push back against this instinct and stick with the conversation until you get a genuine response. One technique Kim recommends is to count to six before saying anything else. This forces the other person to endure the silence. After six seconds, if they still can&#39;t come up with anything else in the moment, suggest finding a time to meet again.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Reward the candor.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This is really important if you ever want to get more feedback from the person. Be effusive in your thanks. If you agree with the feedback, fix the issue, and then ask if you over or under-corrected. If you disagree, first look for something they said that you can agree with. Then, respectfully explain why you disagree with the rest. If possible, agree to do it their way — even if you disagree. Maybe they&#39;re right and you&#39;re wrong. Even so, explaining your reasoning and still deferring to them is a sign of respect.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Offer feedback on feedback.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Having demonstrated how helpful their feedback was, tell them you&#39;ll be asking for more. Let them know that while you appreciate their concern for your feelings, when they fail to tell you things that would help you do better work, it hurts your ability to succeed, and it doesn&#39;t improve your relationship. Reassure them that you really do want them to be candid with you, and that you not only can take it, but will appreciate it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5. Fish or cut bait.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Encouraging others to give you feedback often demands patience and takes work. But not everyone will offer it to you. If you&#39;ve taken all the steps suggested above, and the person still will not share any direct feedback, look to others for candor. If your boss seems constitutionally unable to give real performance feedback and their boss is not holding them accountable, start looking for a new boss.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s difficult to manage your feelings when getting feedback that feels too harsh, overly nice, or somehow dishonest. We all struggle with feedback, so extend a little grace to yourself for having strong emotions, and to the other person for initiating a difficult conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Large Language Models Reflect Human Judgment]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_10_1448510799.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Artificial intelligence is based around prediction. But decision making requires both prediction and judgment. That leaves a role for humans, in providing the judgment about which types of outcomes are better and worse. But large language models represent a key advance: OpenAI has found a way to teach its AI human judgment by using a simple form of human feedback, through chat. That opens the door to a new way for humans to work with AI, essentially talking to them about which outcomes are better or worse for any given type of decision.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Artificial intelligences are prediction machines. They can tell you the probability it will rain today, but they cannot tell you whether or not you should pack an umbrella. That&#39;s because the umbrella decision requires more than just prediction — if the probability of rain is 10%, some people will choose to carry an umbrella, but others won&#39;t. Why will different people behave differently even though they are faced with the same information? Because they have different preferences. In this case, some people care much more than others about getting wet. Only you or someone who knows you well can judge the costs and benefits of carrying an umbrella. Making that decision for you requires both a prediction and a judgment based on your preferences.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;AIs excel at prediction but they do not possess judgment. To be sure, there are many decisions where we know the rewards or can work them out easily. Fundamentally, we know what a driver should do in most situations — accelerate, brake, turn — because we know the consequences of not doing the right thing. But ask Google to give you advice on a new dishwasher, and the best it can do is predict which pages are likely to provide the information you are looking for. It isn&#39;t feeling lucky enough to tell you what to do. Likewise, while you might be worried that your employer will use an AI to determine if you should be fired, the machine isn&#39;t ultimately responsible. AI might provide a prediction about your performance, but it is your employer who applies judgment and decides whom to fire.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;It was for this reason that, in our 2018 book &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Prediction-Machines-Economics-Artificial-Intelligence/dp/1633695670&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Prediction Machines&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, we saw a role for reward function engineers whose job it would be to “determine the rewards to various actions, given the predictions that AI makes.” AI prediction could improve so many decisions that the reward function engineers who understood those predictions and the decision at stake would provide a skilled complement as AI adoption continued apace. But innovation in reward function engineering has been slow. There has been little progress in developing tools to codify appropriate human judgment into machines before they are deployed at scale. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Until recently. Large language models (LLMs) are, for all their seeming intelligence, still just prediction machines. But they are transforming the way AI assists in decision-making because they are changing the way humans provide judgment. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Ask ChatGPT to rewrite a paragraph more clearly for a certain audience, and it does not give you options or a lecture on grammar and rhetoric. It gives you a paragraph. It is impressive, but the real miracle here is that ChatGPT could write the paragraph &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;you wanted&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;. There are a ton of reward and risk issues that go into writing a paragraph. Will the writing be honest (consistent with the facts), harmless (not including words that might offend), and helpful (accomplishing the goal of the paragraph)? Just think about that last one. These models are trained on existing writing by people. The paragraph produced is, at its core, written using a type of “autocomplete” over and over again. When we have our phones autocomplete, they do a good but not perfect job. So how is it that ChatGPT is able to produce written outcomes that are so much better than what the average person can do? How was ChatGPT able to judge quality from all of the content, good and bad, it was trained on? More generally, why didn&#39;t it develop into the toxic cesspool that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;Microsoft&#39;s Tay chatbot turned into after a day on Twitter&lt;/a>;?&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Some people, such as &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://writings.stephenwolfram.com/2023/02/what-is-chatgpt-doing-and-why-does-it-work/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Stephen Wolfram&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, believe that LLMs are uncovering some fundamental rules of grammar. Yes, that can make the writing readable, but it surely can&#39;t make it clear and compelling.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;A &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2203.02155&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;2022 paper from OpenAI researchers&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; provides an important clue. That paper describes how raw, unmodified LLMs were taken and used to offer up outputs to real people. For the most part, the people were asked to &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;use their judgment to rank several alternative outcomes&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; to the same prompt. The ranking criteria were carefully specified (ie, prioritize helpfulness, honesty, and harmlessness). It turns out that with clear instructions and some person-to-person training, different people could quite readily agree on those things.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Those rankings were then used to tweak or “fine tune” the algorithm. The model learned human judgment and adjusted based on positive and negative reinforcement. Writings that ranked highly received a positive bump. Those that did not got a negative hit. Interestingly, even for a model trained on billions of pages, with just a few thousand examples of human judgment in the form of ranked responses, the AI began producing outcomes for all queries that were highly ranked. This occurred even for queries that seemed far from the ones the evaluators had ranked. Somehow, human judgment on writing quality spread quite far throughout the model.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The evaluators were effectively reward function engineers. But unlike with a statistical model, the output of which can be offputting for many people, LLMs interact in plain language — anyone can help teach the model judgment. In other words, anyone who can speak or type can be a reward function engineer. The amazing discovery behind ChatGPT was that with comparatively little effort, reward function engineers were able to train LLMs to be useful and safe. This is how OpenAI was able to launch a consumer-facing model that did not suffer from the flaws of its predecessors when released into the wild. This simple method of codifying human judgment into machines supercharged AI performance. The machine was now imbued with the ability to not only predict word sequences that were likely, but also to apply the reward function engineers&#39; judgment to those sequences to increase their appeal to readers. The discovery of an easy method for machines to apply human judgment — the complement to any AI prediction machine in specifying the risks and rewards in a wide variety of circumstances — made all the difference.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;For many decisions, specialized reward function engineers will be needed to deploy AI prediction machines at scale. The discovery of this intuitive approach for codifying human judgment into machine — fine-tuning via reinforcement learning from human feedback — may unlock many valuable applications of AI where human judgment is difficult to codify in advance but easy to implement when you see it.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Will Accelerate the Circular Economy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_12_1295939564.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Almost Green Studio/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Despite living on a planet with finite resources, our economy remains largely linear and full of single-use products. The shift toward a circular economy, where companies recover or recycle resources, has hit roadblocks, including low value of used products and high recycling costs. Harvard&amp;#8217;s D^3 Institute recently highlighted how digital tools and AI can help overcome these hurdles. They discussed three key strategies: extending the life of products, using fewer materials in production, and using more recycled materials. These tech-enabled strategies promise significant financial returns, but unlocking their full potential will need serious investment. Simply put, it&amp;#8217;s high time businesses recognized the potential of turning waste into wealth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The global economy still functions in a linear manner and is characterized by the extraction, production, consumption, and disposal of materials. This is a problem given that we live on a planet with finite resources. Yet the shift to a circular economy, in which businesses recover or recycle resources used in their value chain, has remained elusive, despite offering &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.summaequity.com/assets/Reports/PDF/230417-Investing-in-a-circular-and-waste-free-Europe.pdf&quot;>;trillions of dollars in value creation&lt;/a>;. Barriers include the low residual value of used products, an inability to collect materials, prohibitive costs of separating and processing materials, and lack of traceability of products and materials that are being recycled.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To accelerate the pace of innovation and learning, the Digital, Data, and Design (D^3) Institute at Harvard Business School recently hosted an &lt;a href=&quot;https://environment.harvard.edu/event/d3-catalyst-circular-economy-conference&quot;>;event focused on the circular economy&lt;/a>;, where entrepreneurs and business leaders shared how they&#39;re using digital tools and artificial intelligence to remove those barriers and create entirely new markets and business models. Specifically, the conference helped identify three main ways to achieve a more circular economy: increasing product utilization, material efficiency, and use of recycled materials.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Product Utilization&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Product utilization seeks to extend the useful life of a product, such as through sharing economy platforms, product refurbishment programs, or enhancing product duration. One new way companies are extending the life of the product is through over-the-air software updates that increase the residual value of a product. Take the example of the iPhone. Today, the iPhone constitutes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/the-used-smartphone-market-is-booming-surprisingly-thats-good-news-for-apple/&quot;>;80% of the market&lt;/a>; among 300 million or so phones in the secondhand market. A primary reason for this success, Marcelo Claure, former CEO of Sprint and Softbank International, explained at the event, is the forward compatibility of the iOS operating system, which ensures a user can access the app ecosystem and all the new features that Apple releases, maintaining iPhones&#39; appeal as a high-quality product in the secondhand market. Over-the-air updates of software is becoming the norm for more products — even cars. As a result, we expect an increase in the residual value of used products and an increase in product utilization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Contrary to the belief that prolonging product lifespan might hinder sales growth and therefore firms should implement a planned obsolescence strategy, leading firms perceive enhanced product utilization as a mechanism for reaching new consumers, enhancing customer satisfaction, and building business models that monetize their efforts to create more durable products through services. Apple now has &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/02/03/apple-says-it-now-has-935-million-paid-subscriptions/&quot;>;935 million subscribers&lt;/a>; in its services segment, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://investor.apple.com/sec-filings/sec-filings-details/default.aspx?FilingId=16157374&quot;>;has grown&lt;/a>; to almost $80 billion in revenues and runs at close to double the gross margin compared to the hardware business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another opportunity to extend the useful life of products is through the product-as-a-service model, where companies retain ownership of a product while consumers pay for its use. Advancements in data and tracing technology has enabled better information flow to facilitate this business model. For example, SuperCircle developed a digital infrastructure that enabled circularity in the fashion industry by integrating customer purchase data with warehouse and distribution systems to trace the lifecycle of clothing. Entrepreneur Chloe Songer, cofounder of SuperCircle, explained how they partner with apparel brands like Reformation to create a customer experience that allows for goods to be returned for a credit or discount, while also facilitating the logistics infrastructure for aggregating and selling these clothes to the recycling sector. Identifying the consumer as a temporary owner of a long-lived asset opens up a world of opportunities to continue engaging customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Material Efficiency&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Material efficiency, which refers to making products with fewer materials, is not a novel concept for many firms that have long pursued a lean operating model, characterized by minimizing waste in production processes. However, with recent breakthroughs in artificial intelligence and innovative technology, material efficiency is witnessing the emergence of even more opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, our conference heard how entrepreneur Shelly Xu&#39;s SXD Zero Waste applies artificial intelligence to redesign garment mockups that generate less pre-consumer waste from offcuts during apparel production. The result is the creation of sweaters, dresses, or pants with close to zero waste in fabric and about 55% lower cost, as opposed to 10–30% waste in traditional designs. Successful entrepreneurial solutions will be those that invest time in educating B2B customers about the potential for cost savings and the need to revise legacy processes that traditionally result in more waste, such as fashion design.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The “tough-tech” segment, using breakthrough science, engineering, and technology, also has the potential to create solutions that both reduce the material impact of existing supply chains and create “drop-in” solutions that can be incorporated into existing supply chains. An example of an entrepreneur in this space is Luciano Bueno, who founded GALY, a firm that grows cotton from cells in a lab using 80% fewer resources compared to traditional agriculture. An important part of the innovation journey in tough tech involves educating investors on the longer innovation cycles and the need for iteration on the path to scalability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Recycled Materials&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Perhaps the most well-known element of a circular business model involves minimizing the use of virgin materials as a percentage of a product&#39;s total materials. For instance, Apple&#39;s products now incorporate 20% recycled materials. Beyond reducing carbon emissions, the use of more recycled materials helps companies increase “materials security,” which is particularly concerning for industries reliant on rare minerals such as lithium and cobalt. Increasing recycled materials is also a key solution for reducing carbon intensity in hard-to-abate industries like cement and steel. However, Joy Chen and Per Anders Enkvist from McKinsey highlighted that the availability of recycled materials is currently limited, and sometimes more expensive than virgin materials. Technological enhancements to increase the availability of high-quality recycled materials and reduce costs therefore are huge opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In particular, scaling up material recovery and separation is key to making recycled material more available and affordable. Bjørn Arve Ofstad, CEO of Norsk Gjenvinning, the largest waste management company in the Nordics, explained that this sector needs an upstream feedstock, technology to sort and process the waste to be used downstream, and a downstream taker. This process needs to be done at an industry scale where materials are accessed at the right time, price, and quality. Robotics can facilitate this sorting process at lower cost. For example, Apple developed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/iphone-terminator-apples-daisy-teardown-robot-can-rip-your-phone-apart-in-18-secs/&quot;>;Daisy&lt;/a>;, a state-of-the-art robot that can breakdown an iPhone into reusable components in 18 seconds, including rare minerals such as cobalt, gold, and platinum.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Opaque supply chains represent significant barriers to understanding the breakdown of materials at end-of-life for recovery and sorting. Maria McClay, from Google, explained how in 2019 Google piloted a solution to use machine learning and analytics to provide a more comprehensive view of impact along the textile value chain, and in 2021 was able to expand the offering to other brands. Another solution described by Hari Nair from Procter &amp;amp; Gamble is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pg.co.uk/blogs/HolyGrail/&quot;>;HolyGrail project&lt;/a>; that uses digital watermarks in products to make the sorting of recyclables easier at the end of life.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Investing in the Trillion-Dollar Opportunity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To support the adoption and scaling of these digitalization-enabled solutions, we need investment to fund the trillion-dollar opportunity. Yet asset allocators in circularity face a “pattern recognition” challenge, where the capability to identify promising opportunities is still evolving. Venture capital funds have been hesitant to invest in early-stage companies with significant capital expenditure needs, which is often the case in circular solutions. On the other hand, private equity funds have been reluctant to invest in early-stage startups. One solution, described by Andrew Merino of Generate Capital, is the emergence of multi-sector, sustainability-focused funds that bridge the gap between traditional venture capital and private equity. To tap the full investment potential of a circular economy, investors need to develop in-depth sectoral expertise and innovation in investment structures.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Video Quick Take &ndash; Google&rsquo;s Gautam Ramdurai on Emerging Consumer Behavior - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM GOOGLE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/video-quick-take-googles-gautam-ramdurai-on-emerging-consumer-behavior]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6328969026112&quot;}&quot; js- target=&quot;video-player-page&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;正在加载.. . &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt; p>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Harvard Business Review 研究和特殊项目高级编辑 Todd Pruzan 最近采访了谷歌亚太区广告营销集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai，采访了新一期的 HBR Video Quick Take。由于当今的每个企业都需要驾驭一系列复杂的因素来推动可持续和盈利增长，同时牢记这样做的核心仍然是了解客户以及他们如何做出决策，Pruzan 与 Ramdurai 谈到了对新兴消费者行为的新见解&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;很多关于消费者行为的事情似乎都在持续发生变化。您现在看到亚太地区的消费者行为发生了哪些变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span >;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;我们现在发现的东西很吸引人。尤其需要注意的是，2023 年与 2020 年甚至 2022 年的真正不同之处在于。我们知道这场大流行病从根本上改变了很多事情，但我认为随着我们走出大流行病，其他危机正在介入：政治动荡、气候变化和生活成本危机。当所有这些类型的公共危机同时发生时，我们需要开始考虑它们所产生的总体影响。答案是：我们正在进入一个真正的混合世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;想想在大流行期间每个人是如何上网的。但是，随着我们从大流行中走出来，当你想到你的杂货店购物时，你是如何决定哪些物品是在商店购买的，哪些是在网上购买的？即使是最简单的决策，每个人的头脑中都会进行这种复杂的计算，这仅仅是因为决策本身的因素数量以及您从中获取信息的渠道数量。例如，考虑与您交互的设备数量，然后将其乘以您使用的渠道数量，从 Google 搜索到 YouTube 再到任何其他视频平台再到报纸。您可以进出在线和离线世界。甚至在网络世界中，也有如此多的多样性，你试图找到摆脱它的方法。到 2023 年，这将变得非常棘手。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，在整个亚太地区，我们的研究告诉我们，想知道和知道之间的差距——一直存在——从未如此之大。这就是我们所说的置信度差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push (function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt ;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;好吧，信任和信心如今比以往任何时候都更重要，但消费者如何驾驭这种格局？企业如何驾驭它？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;让我们从消费者开始。消费者是聪明的。他们总是比企业更善于与时俱进。因此，消费者所做的是相当快地找到他们的内部微积分。换句话说，每个人都有他们通过的这些决策因素以及他们在做出决策时要寻求的这些信息源。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们举一个想要做某事的人的例子：我有一个三- 岁，所以我一直在想我三岁的孩子什么时候应该骑自行车。那是一个重要的时刻，对吧？因此，当消费者想到“哦，我需要为我的女儿买一辆自行车”时，第一个问题永远不会是“我在哪里买自行车？”相反，它是“孩子骑自行车的合适年龄是多少？”这是一个更基本的生活问题和一个好奇心驱动的问题。你从一个关于孩子骑自行车的正确时间的问题开始，然后慢慢过渡到研究有哪些类型的自行车。您最终会被孩子们第一次尝试学习如何骑自行车的视频所吸引。您很快意识到您还需要购买头盔。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种好奇心路径扩展了消费者寻找正确信息的过程。当消费者浏览所有这些内容时，我们发现他们真正寻找的是六个特定的信心线索。这些线索是噪音中的信号；它们会告诉他们需要知道什么，以便更接近于对自己的决定充满信心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，想象一下您处于信心差距中。你被困在那里，不知道下一步该去哪里。你让好奇心引导你回答下一个问题。我们发现在这个过程中有一些关键信息将所有内容汇集在一起​​。例如，其中一个信心线索是评论。这家生产这种自行车的公司是否经过了良好的审查？这家公司是否以制造安全自行车或整体安全公司而享有盛誉？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他重要因素，例如社会认同。可持续性正变得越来越重要，因此一家公司的可持续性实践正成为越来越重要的购买考虑因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;令人惊讶的是，我们发现了一个额外的隐含线索。这第七个提示实际上是关于平台的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天有大量的数字信息，当我告诉你数字世界正在扩展时，我知道我是在向合唱团布道。人们拥有的信息来源数量比以往任何时候都多，随之而来的是大量虚假信息和错误信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type= &quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;简而言之，平台本身在 2023 年发挥的作用比我们以前看到的要大得多。它们成为关于您对获取信息的平台本身有多信任的第七个线索。这就像查看两个不同的新闻站点并决定您更信任哪个。同样的逻辑现在也适用于平台世界：您查看所有信息或查找信息的平台实际上与品牌或企业本身可能传达给客户的任何其他信心线索一样重要。 &lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;所以平台必须成为一部分你的日常生活。它必须是安全的。它必须是一个你信任的平台，几乎就像你会根据他们过去告诉你的那样相信一个人的话而不是另一个人的话。平台是这里的关键？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;是的，这就是我们在多个平台上看到的，尤其是谷歌和 YouTube。对于像 Google 这样的网站，人们在不确定的时候会去寻找一些东西，它几乎就像一个人类意图的图书馆。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，虽然品牌本身可以查看六个线索，但它不是就是你在这六个信心提示中所说的话。相反，它是您展示同样重要的自信线索的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b >;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;那么媒介真的是信息还是信息的重要组成部分？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;正确。我会说这是其中很大一部分，因为媒体永远不可能是完整的信息。您拥有自己的品牌。你知道它想对世界说话的真相。但我认为现在的复杂性——这可以追溯到我们关于 2023 年与以往相比的独特之处的研究——涉及需要考虑消费者必须经历的微积分。然后我们需要将其与企业必须经历的演算配对。因此，如果消费者没有在正确的时间、正确的地点和正确的媒介中找到正确的信息，他们将退出购买之旅。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;哇，听起来这是一个非常脆弱的交易。&lt;/p>; &lt; h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;当然可以。一切都回到了桌面上。凭直觉——这是我昨天与某人进行的讨论的一部分——你会想，“哦，在不确定的时候，我们会回到我们所知道的事情上。”但我们看到的是，人们实际上会花更多的时间进行研究，即使他们拥有已经使用了很长时间的品牌。因此，几乎就像是大流行病加剧了这种对信任和信心的需求，以至于人们正在将他们久经考验的品牌转移到餐桌的后面。这意味着您不能认为信任是理所当然的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;再次回到交易信任，它不是在人们购买产品时建立的。它是在人们考虑使用产品时构建的；它是在消费者甚至不知道他们需要该产品时构建的。因此，如果您经历了整个消费者旅程，您需要能够在整个过程中建立这些信心线索。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;而且当他们购买了您的产品时，它并没有结束。旅程中更重要的部分是他们实际使用您的产品或服务的时间。客户体验不会在购买按钮处结束。它几乎以多种方式从那里开始。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;如果信任对消费者很重要，那么这如何开始转化为业务成果？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span >;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;在 2023 年，它会产生非常直接的影响。如果消费者正在寻找信息以增强他们购买您的产品或服务的信心，那么您的出现方式就非常重要。如果你没有以正确的方式出现，它会对你的底线产生直接影响。例如，在印度和东南亚，三分之一的消费者决定不购买他们已经在考虑的品牌，因为他们感到有点焦虑。他们对自己的选择没有把握。¹ 所以那是一辆被遗弃的手推车。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们也看到信任的积极方面也在很大程度上显现出来。如果您在客户/消费者的整个购买过程和整体购买体验中完成了与他们在一起的工作，并且您已经建立并输入了该信任帐户，那么购买高度信任的品牌的可能性要高出七倍²——而且它不会在购买时结束。在购买前对自己的产品选择充满信心的消费者再次购买该品牌的可能性高出近 20%。³&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，消费者旅程是周期性的，因此您与消费者建立的信任和信心不会改变当他们点击“购买”时结束。它几乎从那里开始。如果你想继续建立信任和信心的良性循环，你需要在任何地方加强，即使他们已经购买了你的产品。我们在数据中非常清楚地看到了这一点。因此，对于 2023 年寻求信心的消费者来说，所有品牌都重新回到桌面上，作为卖家，您可以选择是否要参与交易或旅程。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;企业可以做些什么来跟上客户的需求？您如何看待未来几年的变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span>;&lt;/b >;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;一旦有人获得了做出选择所需的所有信号，我们就认为他们的信心发生了转变：您已经帮助他们找到了生活问题的答案，并且您的产品或服务是其中的一部分。我们认为，聪明且能够推动这种信心转变的企业将在这个非常混乱的未来蓬勃发展——就此而言，现在也是如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是当你开始思考你的企业如何可以帮助他们改变信心，您需要知道显示哪个提示、何时显示以及为谁显示，因为您的所有消费者可能都不相同，而且他们不在同一部分旅程。这些都是移动的目标：正确的提示、正确的消费者、正确的格式、正确的信息、正确的设备以及决策过程中的正确点。开始理解这一点的唯一方法——这些在很多方面都是预测性决策——并大规模地、尤其是对大公司来说，在几毫秒内做到这一点的唯一方法是利用数据和人工智能的力量。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;再一次，这让我们回到了你是想成为一个交易型企业还是一个随着时间的推移建立信任和信心的企业。这是您需要在整个客户体验中进行的投资。营销活动的黄金标准曾经是您每季度只拥有并满足一个 KPI，但我们正在远离这一点。现在的黄金标准是您是否可以吸引同样具有高生命周期价值的新客户。那些曾经是在营销室举行的两次不同的会议，但现在它们被混为一谈。解决这种复杂性的方法是使用数据和 AI。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/ h5>; &lt;p>;Gautam，感谢您的见解。你今天有什么临别的话，特别是关于你将如何为你的女儿找到那辆自行车吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，Group营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;好复杂的问题！购买那辆自行车时存在许多生活问题。在我走这条路时，我需要牢记以下几点：我们知道生活比以前复杂得多，而且我们不知道下一组不确定性会是什么。我们也知道他们会来； &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于一直存在的信心差距，消费者仍会发现自己身处其中，或许还会扩大。也许信心线索会进化。但我认为，如果我们想知道他们需要哪些提示，就必须密切关注消费者的决策。我们的工作是帮助他们转变信心，随着我们走向未来，这只会变得越来越重要。复杂决策制定的世界将继续存在，投资于利用数据和 AI 的力量实现信心转变的能力的企业可能会在这种环境中蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5 >;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;非常感谢您进行精彩的对话以及您的所有意见今天的见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;谢谢，托德，感谢我。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;要了解更多信息，请访问 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkwithgoogle.com/intl/en-apac/marketing-strategies/automation/build-brand-confidence-ai-marketing/?utm_source=twg_partnership_external&amp;amp;utm_medium= referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023-APAC-GML-EVOS-HBR-VQT-HL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Think With Google&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;返回 HBR.org 上来自 Google APAC 的“&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/multiply-your-marketing-with-ai&quot;>;将您的营销与 AI 相乘&lt;/a>;”赞助商内容中心&lt;/em>;&lt; /strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;¹资料来源：Google/Kantar/Quantum，“搜索的情感价值”，印第安纳州、印度尼西亚、越南、马来西亚、菲律宾、泰国、巴基斯坦，2021 年， n=5006 P18M 类别买家。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;² 资料来源：爱德曼，“信任，新品牌资产”，2022 年，n=14,000 名消费者来自 14 个国家/地区。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;³ 资料来源：Google/ Ipsos，解码回购，澳大利亚、印度、印度尼西亚、日本、韩国、越南，2023 年，每个市场 n=1500，家用电器、个人护理、健康和福祉产品的买家。&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Three Ways To Use The Customer Perspective As A Measure Of Success - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/three-ways-to-use-the-customer-perspective-as-a-measure-of-success]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358516&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_KPI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;在商业中，你无法改善自己而不是衡量——当今的组织通常使用关键绩效指标 (KPI) 来衡量进展和成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;成功的企业意味着更高的客户满意度、保留率和整体品牌声誉。因此，大多数公司将客户体验列为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superoffice.com/blog/customer-experience-statistics/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;首要业务也就不足为奇了&lt;/a>;。但很多时候，在跟踪和量化进度的过程中，业务领导者最终会优先考虑直接反对以客户为中心的行为的流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;传统的 KPI 包括盈利能力、生产力和流程效率的衡量标准——所有这些这是内部指标。分析这些指标无疑可以给出整体性能的指示。但是，当优先考虑高于一切时，他们可能会错过企业如何为客户提供最大价值的大局。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;消费者越来越多地从与品牌的互动和体验中获取价值。 83% 的消费者关注&lt;a href=&quot;https://khoros.com/resources&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;品牌如何对待他们&lt;/a>;产品，89% 的受访者表示在体验不佳后&lt;a href=&quot;https://harris-interactive.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;转向竞争对手&lt;/a>;。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;因此，随着体验成为更重要的绩效衡量标准，最成功的公司都在每个接触点建立情感联系。由于当今的消费者牢牢掌握着主导权，企业领导者需要拥有正确的工具、流程和以客户为中心的整体文化才能留在游戏中。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size : 11.0pt;&quot;>;作为 KPI 的客户价值&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;虽然效率、生产力和盈利能力将继续很重要，但客户价值正迅速成为分析的真正明星显示。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，衡量客户价值比跟踪传统的 KPI 更复杂。社会价值、品牌声望以及服务或产品提供的情感体验等因素都会发挥作用——所有这些都很难用标准方法量化。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot; >; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div >; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;以下是如何将 KPI 记分卡转向客户价值，从而为成功做好准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;建立哪些 KPI 将为您提供丰富的、以客户为中心的数据。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;客户参与度指标在此阶段很有用，可帮助您更好地分配资源并建立标准来监控和评估——并且，至关重要的是，了解您的客户如何看待您。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一系列良好的客户参与度指标包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;客户满意度得分&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;衡量您的客户满意度分数可以告诉您客户对上次与贵公司的互动有多满意，并让您有机会根据他们的反馈进行改进。净推荐值是您可以用来衡量客户体验的类似指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;流失率&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;您的流失率反映了在特定时期内停止与您开展业务的客户百分比。尽管客户离开的原因多种多样，但您需要了解是否存在一致的主题，以便解决原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;客户生命周期价值&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4 &quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;此 KPI 与客户流失率密切相关。您的客户生命周期价值得分将为您提供贵公司可以从客户那里获得的预期收入，帮助您估算营销计划的未来回报。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt ;&quot;>;让客户价值成为客户绩效指标的中心。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;KPI 是一个很好的起点，但它很容易迷失在数字和从对客户重要的事情上分心。衡量成功的另一种方法是用客户绩效指标 (CPI) 补充这些指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多公司将 KPI 与 CPI 混淆。尽管 KPI 可以有效衡量情绪，但仍然存在 KPI 忽略与客户相关的内容的风险。 KPI 与公司目标有着内在联系，但 CPI 关注 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-performace-indicators-surbhit-suman-banga&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot; noopener&quot;>;客户最关心的是什么&lt;/a>;，例如价值和满意度，这会导致忠诚度和保留率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与客户持续对话是充分利用您的最佳方式消费物价指数。询问他们从您的业务中获得了什么价值，是什么让他们回头，以及是什么影响了他们的购买。提问、倾听、设计、实施——然后再提问。&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;汇集正确的指标、正确的工具和正确的心态。&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;这种连续的监控和调整循环需要比从单个接触点收集数据的孤立测量工具更复杂的方法。从以客户为中心的数据中释放价值需要一个分析平台，该平台可以集成、提取和综合来自整个软件堆栈的数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;具有敏捷、直观分析功能的客户关系管理 (CRM) 技术可以产生结果远远超出了管理人员在其组织范围内的画面设置中所看到的。 360 度全方位的业务视图使您能够根据精细的细节做出更大的决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据传统 KPI 来判断您对成功的衡量可能会导致团队有动力执行积极的销售策略以实现目标他们的目标，这可能会破坏良好的客户关系。用 CPI 补充这些指标培养了一种不同类型的问责制，鼓励团队将客户满意度放在首位——这可以带来更好的保留率和更多收入。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size : 11.0pt;&quot;>;The Experience of Customer Experience&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;永远记住，客户体验就是：一种体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;消费者不太感兴趣你的品牌比你。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2019/11/21/consumers-are-hungry-for-an-experience-based-connection-with-your-brand/?sh= 2974384358fe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;他们专注于自己的体验&lt;/a>;。要真正衡量您的品牌对他们生活的影响，您需要审视各个接触点并评估他们的整体体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这不仅仅是数字，但了解您是否触及的唯一方法标记带有数据。 Your analytical tools and processes need to be flexible enough to help you measure and deliver authentic experiences that will cultivate lasting customer relationships.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm.com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Discover&lt;/a>; how Zoho CRM&#39;s intuitive analytics can help you deliver lasting customer value.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovering Where ChatGPT Can Create Value for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_4896946.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然 ChatGPT 影响的速度、规模和范围可能是独一无二的，但潜在的现象一种正在改变商业和社会的大部分领域的新兴技术 &amp;#8212;不是。但是利用新兴技术的力量需要一种新的方法。与设计思维等传统创新方法不同，ChatGPT 提出了根本不同的挑战，因为没有明确的问题需要解决、用户痛点需要缓解或 KPI 需要实现。事实上，ChatGPT 似乎可以解决几乎任何行业、领域或环境中的问题。因此，使用它需要一种不同的技能：涌现性思维，这涉及在没有完全理解需要解决的问题的情况下产生创新想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当 OpenAI 发布其旗舰产品时去年 11 月的产品 ChatGPT，仅用了四天就达到了 100 万用户，两个月就达到了 1 亿用户，超过 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/chatgpt-sets-record- fastest-growing-user-base-analyst-note-2023-02-01/&quot;>;比任何其他科技巨头快 75%&lt;/a>;。 ChatGPT 继续快速发展，最初是一个仅响应用户提示的 AI 聊天机器人。现在，它包括分析数据和解释图像等功能，让从高中生到高级管理人员的每个人都争先恐后地学习 ChatGPT，以便他们能够以新的和富有成效的方式使用它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然速度、规模和 ChatGPT 的影响范围可能是独一无二的，但潜在的现象——一种正在改变大部分商业和社会的新兴技术——却并非如此。但是利用新兴技术的力量需要一种新的方法。与&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/why-design-thinking-works&quot;>;设计思维&lt;/a>;等传统创新方法不同，ChatGPT 提出了根本不同的挑战，因为没有明确的问题需要解决，用户要缓解的痛点，或要实现的 KPI。事实上，ChatGPT 似乎可以解决几乎任何行业、领域或环境中的问题。因此，使用它需要不同的技能：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/326964001_An_Integrated_Model_of_Dynamic_Problem_Solving_Within_Organizational_Constraints&quot;>;紧急思维&lt;/a>;，这涉及在没有完全理解需要解决的问题的情况下产生创新想法&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们两个人（Johnathan 和 Jennifer）最近进行了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886923001289&quot;>;研究&lt;/ a>; 表明这种创新风格的主要思维过程是从理解技术的核心功能开始，&lt;em>;然后&lt;/em>;探索如何使用它来解决不同领域的问题。涌现思维的其他特征包括在不了解成功标准的情况下评估想法、在几乎没有准备或计划的情况下即兴发挥想法，以及改变项目的目标结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些活动往往与促进效率和改进的良好商业实践背道而驰。可靠性，它们甚至可能违反设计思维的一些核心原则，即需要确定一个明确的用户问题来解决，&lt;em>;&lt;/em>; 产生解决方案的想法。然而，在尝试利用 ChatGPT（或任何其他新兴技术）进行创新时，它们也很重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多公司已经开始将 ChatGPT 集成到他们的产品、流程和服务中。通过分析这种新兴的创新格局，我们为领导者确定了三种新兴思维途径，它们可以帮助增加成功实施 ChatGPT 的机会，同时避免潜在的陷阱。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;途径 1：利用当前价值主张&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第一个途径涉及使用 ChatGPT 进一步利用公司已经提供给客户的价值主张。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/instacart-could-do-worse-than-incinerating-32-bln-2023-03-01/&quot;>;Instacart 已发展到 25 亿美元通过专注于为居家客户提供快速、可靠且负担得起的杂货配送服务这一核心价值主张，提高年收入&lt;/a>;。最近，他们&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instacart.com/company/updates/instacart-chatgpt/&quot;>;推出了 ChatGPT 插件&lt;/a>;，旨在通过提高速度和效率来加强这一价值主张在线订购杂货。有了这个插件，客户可以收到准备饭菜的建议，一旦他们找到自己喜欢的东西，ChatGPT 将创建一个新的 Instacart 订单，自动添加所有必要的成分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了追求这条创新之路，从使用 ChatGPT 开始，不要将其针对任何特定的客户问题。这个思考过程可能具有挑战性，因为大多数业务培训都教会我们成为战略思考者，并在花任何时间开发解决方案之前验证客户问题的重要性。然而，从这样的战略目标入手实际上会让我们看不到 ChatGPT 在新的和有价值的应用程序方面的潜力。相反，请以开放的心态开始，深入使用该工具以了解其核心功能。 Once you have that understanding, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048733320301463&quot;>;natural human cognition will take over&lt;/a>; and start making connections to any relevant problems you might be aware of.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, one of the core functions of ChatGPT is to interpret and generate natural language text that provides human-like responses to a wide variety of questions, prompts, and requests. Companies can use this function to enhance existing features of products or services that focus specifically on text-based interactions with customers. For instance, the product-management tool Notion now provides customers with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.notion.so/product/ai&quot;>;immediate access to ChatGPT&lt;/a>; at the tap of the spacebar, which activates a prompt to receive an AI response that can be immediately integrated into existing tasks and workflows. As the functions of ChatGPT continue to grow, new possibilities will emerge for how it can be used to further enhance value propositions across a wider range of companies and contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 2: Expanding the Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A second pathway uses ChatGPT to expand a company&#39;s value proposition by solving new problems for customers in a way that complements their current offering. For example, Khan Academy was created in 2006 with the mission of providing all students with a free, world-class education. They&#39;ve since grown to nearly 20 million users per month, primarily by offering short online videos that start with a blank canvas and get filled with colorful, hand-written text. Recently, they integrated ChatGPT into their platform &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.khanacademy.org/sal-khans-2023-ted-talk-ai-in-the-classroom-can-transform-education/&quot;>;by creating a personalized AI tutor called Khanmigo&lt;/a>;. This tool not only helps students by guiding them through online videos and practice questions more effectively, but it can also help teachers by explaining teaching methods and designing lesson plans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can follow the same pathway by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/335242871_Matthew_A_Cronin_and_Jeffrey_Loewenstein_The_Craft_of_Creativity&quot;>;clearly defining your perspective and learning how to change it&lt;/a>;. For emergent thinking, this first involves breaking down a value proposition into three core elements:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;The goals customers are trying to accomplish&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The context in which customers are trying to accomplish those goals&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The specific target demographic of the customers&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once defined, the next step is to assess how ChatGPT&#39;s core functions (see Pathway 1) can help expand each element in new directions. For example, Khan Academy originally focused on &lt;em>;helping&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;K–12 students&lt;/em>; (target demographic) &lt;em>;learn topics at a self-guided pace&lt;/em>; (goal), &lt;em>;done&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;completely online &lt;/em>;(context). Using ChatGPT, they expanded this goal for students by facilitating online learning either through self-guided practice or via an AI tutor, and they also expanded the target demographic to include teachers, helping them accomplish new goals that were not previously possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This two-step definition and expansion process offers a complementary skillset to design thinking, which typically encourages people to think of many different solutions before converging on one to implement. With emergent thinking, however, you apply those same &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/better-brainstorming&quot;>;brainstorming techniques&lt;/a>; to the problem, rather than the solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During this process, it&#39;s key to maintain an open mind and avoid settling on a problem too quickly, which may be particularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/228198146_Performance_Pressure_as_a_Double-Edged_Sword_Enhancing_Team_Motivation_While_Undermining_the_Use_of_Team_Knowledge&quot;>;challenging to do in conditions of uncertainty&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has unleashed an unprecedented level of pressure on companies to act quickly, or else suffer dramatic consequences for their future survival. However, research shows it&#39;s also possible to &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/jpo/article-abstract/7/1/2/5707381&quot;>;withstand these pressures and explore a wider range of innovation options&lt;/a>;. To do that, work with trusted collaborators so you can navigate ambiguity more effectively and take greater risks together.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 3: Exploring a New Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pathway is based on using ChatGPT to explore a completely new value proposition that customers may not even know they need yet. Although this may run counter to traditional methods for innovation, it also aligns with common advice for creating breakthroughs. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/1998-05-25/steve-jobs-theres-sanity-returning&quot;>;when Steve Jobs was asked&lt;/a>; whether Apple did any market research when developing the iMac, he responded: “It&#39;s really hard to design products by focus groups. A lot of times, people don&#39;t know what they want until you show it to them.” This wisdom seems to have been fully embraced by OpenAI, which released ChatGPT to the public and is now discovering countless ways it can be used in various contexts to accomplish new and unforeseen goals. This pathway for innovation represents the purest form of emergent thinking, which has the greatest uncertainty and therefore must also be pursued with the greatest caution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The main challenge comes when trying to converge on a single problem to focus on out of the many dozens identified when brainstorming different goals, contexts, and target demographics (see Pathway 2). When organizations have relatively clearer value propositions — such as increasing the speed of online ordering at Instacart or improving the quality of online education at Khan Academy — it can be easier to filter out problems that seem far-fetched or unlikely to reflect valuable customer needs. However, when customer needs are still unknown and emerging along with the technology, it becomes difficult for teams to agree on a shared direction to pursue. This becomes especially challenging when trying to include the diverse perspectives that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/smarter-collaboration-a-new-approach-to-breaking-down-barriers-and-transforming-work/10535&quot;>;fundamental to innovation&lt;/a>;, because team members can pull the project in different directions &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Extreme-Teaming-Lessons-Cross-Sector-Leadership/dp/1786354500&quot;>;despite their best intentions to collaborate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help overcome these challenges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2343944&quot;>;identify a clear and coherent analogy&lt;/a>; that summarizes the core value proposition. For example, Tome is a startup that&#39;s using ChatGPT to help customers create better presentations out of online documents, videos, and digital content. However, instead of highlighting all the specific benefits they can provide, they&#39;ve described their product as an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20230427180425/https:/beta.tome.app/&quot;>;AI storytelling partner&lt;/a>;.” This simple concept helps integrate many different features into a coherent product experience so that both developers and customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/234021855_When_Is_a_New_Thing_a_Good_Thing_Technological_Change_Product_Form_Design_and_Perceptions_of_Value_for_Product_Innovations&quot;>;easily understand its value&lt;/a>;. By creating an analogy for your product, you can avoid wasting valuable resources creating features that might not support the core value proposition, and you can help customers develop a clear mental model of the various features and why they can be useful.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ChatGPT is an unprecedented technology that has potential to unlock value for millions of customers across many industries. However, pursuing these rewards also comes with considerable risks, as we&#39;re all entering uncharted territory with AI, and we must learn how to use it effectively so it can be leveraged for positive rather than negative outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Build Upon the Legacy of Your Family Business &mdash; and Make It Your Own]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_1009603322.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Sean Murphy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Family companies often have a strong sense of history and tradition. Although these legacies can create advantages, they sometimes leave next-generation leaders feeling handcuffed or constrained by the way their ancestors ran things. To overcome that, they should seek to reformulate the company&amp;#8217;s story in a way that creates advantages for the present.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Founded by Henry Ford &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/about/history.html&quot;>;in 1903&lt;/a>;, the Ford Motor Company rocketed to success by mass-producing reliable, low-priced automobiles. When Henry&#39;s son, &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/articles/history/edsel-ford-biography.html&quot;>;Edsel&lt;/a>;, took the helm in 1918, he championed a different strategy for a new era. He sought to replace the Model T — iconic but outdated — with a more modern design geared to high-end and foreign markets, and later embraced compromise with labor amid the suffering of the Great Depression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But Henry could not let go of Ford&#39;s origin story, undermining his son at every turn. The result was declining sales and years of labor strife that left the company on the brink of collapse by the 1940s. It was only the efforts of Edsel&#39;s son, the more forceful &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.automotivehalloffame.org/honoree/henry-ford-ii/&quot;>;Henry Ford II&lt;/a>;, that saved the auto giant from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In family enterprise, generational transitions often pit one narrative against another: tradition versus innovation, continuity versus change. Indeed, when older generations craft painstaking succession plans or build elaborate constraints into trusts or shareholder agreements, they are really constructing a story: about the values and life lessons that helped them succeed, and that they hope will do the same for their children. Younger generations, however, must often adapt this narrative to their own goals and values, along with the changing world around them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to reconcile conflicting narratives can spell ruin for a family business or the waste of a financial legacy, as it nearly did for the Fords. To avoid this fate, families need to think differently about the stories they tell.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The value of critical distance&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Conventional wisdom holds that family heritage, like wealth and reputation, “belongs” to the older generation. In this telling, succeeding generations are merely stewards or caretakers. They are given an inheritance or entrusted with the family business — and then charged with not frittering it away or screwing it up. Framed this way, a legacy can feel more like a burden than a gift.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, it&#39;s not as simple as that. Research suggests that younger generations &lt;em>;do&lt;/em>; value their family heritage, especially as a source of traditions more motivating than money alone, and are motivated to preserve it. According to a 2021 &lt;a href=&quot;https://home.kpmg/content/dam/kpmg/ca/pdf/2022/02/who-are-the-guardians-of-family-legacy-report-en.pdf&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; of 300 Canadian business owners by the Family Enterprise Foundation, nearly 90% of next-generation family business leaders believe it is important to preserve a legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But younger generations also want something more from that heritage: a sense of purpose, a collective identity for the family, the seeds of new entrepreneurial gambits, permission to go their own way. And as our own &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0894486520941944?journalCode=fbra&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows, next-generation leaders are uniquely positioned to find what they are looking for in the family story.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Older generations often identify closely with the family or the family business, which can actually obstruct key learnings from the past. Eager to protect the family&#39;s reputation, they may downplay scandal or setback rather than learn from it. By contrast, our analysis of 94 family businesses shows that younger generations tend to have more critical distance from the family story. This lets them grapple with its difficult chapters and respond appropriately, whether by making amends for past misdeeds or by reforming business practices going forward. It also frees them to draw insights from their story that can fuel innovation and sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Legacy as a source of purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How, then, can the next generation build on their family legacy while recasting it as their own? Our research and experience suggest four strategies for next-generation leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Seek out role models in the family story.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some next-generation leaders hesitate to embark on risky new ventures outside the traditional scope of the family business. Locating exemplars in the family story can legitimize a new way forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One third-generation CEO used this approach to advance his vision for a more sustainable enterprise. Fredo Arias-King, head of Mexican pine resin producer Pinosa Group, had lamented the disappearance of Mexico&#39;s ancient pine forests that threatened both the industry and the communities that depend on it. Then he stumbled onto the published speeches of his grandfather, company founder José Antonio Arias Álvarez, who had preached environmental stewardship. “I don&#39;t think he could have known just how devastated the forest would eventually become,” said Arias-King, “but somehow my grandfather knew that planting trees would become extremely important.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Affirmed by his grandfather&#39;s words, Arias-King helped found &lt;a href=&quot;https://ejidoverde.com/about-us/&quot;>;Ejido Verde&lt;/a>;, a nonprofit that would later become an independent, for-profit enterprise. By making no-interest loans to farmers and communities, with pine resin as the means of repayment, the organization promotes reforesting through new pine plantations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;2. Forge an identity beyond the founder-entrepreneur.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to revere the family&#39;s wealth creator. For the two adult grandchildren of one founder-entrepreneur — a private equity pioneer who rose from poverty to become one of America&#39;s richest people — that was the problem. They wanted their own children, beneficiaries of a generation-skipping trust, to know the person behind the legacy that would pass to them. So they engaged one of us (John Seaman) to probe beyond the classic rags-to-riches tale they had heard growing up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The founder, they learned, was a gifted yet deeply troubled man. This more nuanced understanding enabled the two generations to have a frank conversation about the issues raised by their ancestor&#39;s life: the obligations of a business to its workers and communities; the consequences of untreated mental illness; and the unfair burden often shouldered by women in wealthy families.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This conversation, in turn, led members of the fourth generation, all in their twenties, to rethink their roles in the family enterprise. One set aside her qualms about joining the family business and put herself on a path to succeed her father as president, but with a determination to nudge the company&#39;s private equity portfolio toward impact investing. Another resolved to pursue her own entrepreneurial dreams outside of the business, rooted in progressive values that were in stark contrast with her great-grandfather&#39;s. Still another joined the board of the family foundation, where she helped steer its grant-making toward her generation&#39;s individual passions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By seeing their founder-entrepreneur in human terms, the family&#39;s younger generation was able to move beyond hero worship to forge their own identities — which promised to make them responsible owners &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;stewards of their ancestor&#39;s wealth and the business that created it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3. Reckon with past wrongs to find a new path forward.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many families have skeletons in the closet —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/how-companies-can-address-their-historical-transgressions&quot;>;scandal or wrongdoing&lt;/a>; they have long concealed or downplayed. (Henry Ford&#39;s history of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/americanexperience/features/henryford-antisemitism/&quot;>;antisemitism&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/how-the-ford-motor-company-won-a-battle-and-lost-ground-45814533/&quot;>;violent confrontations&lt;/a>; with unions are examples of this.) The willingness to confront these darker chapters, it turns out, can be a powerful motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was the case for the Reimann family, owners of consumer goods conglomerate JAB Holding Company and one of Germany&#39;s richest families. The three adult children of Albert Reimann Jr., who ran the company in the 1930s and 1940s, knew they had been born of their father&#39;s affair with an employee, Emilie Landecker. They also knew that Emilie&#39;s Jewish father, Alfred, had been murdered by the Nazis. But it was not until 2019, when they commissioned research on the company, that a more sinister secret emerged: their father and paternal grandfather were themselves ardent believers in Nazi race theory who abused forced laborers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It was the younger generation — Albert Jr.&#39;s grandchildren — who were most adamant about reckoning with this secret. “When I read of the atrocities…sanctioned by my grandfather, I felt like throwing up,” recalled Martin Reimann. “I cannot claim that I was very interested in politics before…But after what happened, I changed my mind.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the insistence of Martin&#39;s generation, the Reimanns paid compensation to former forced laborers and their families. But they did not stop there. They refocused their family foundation on combating antisemitism and strengthening democratic institutions. They also renamed the foundation in honor of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alfredlandecker.org/en&quot;>;Alfred Landecker&lt;/a>;, making him the narrative driver behind the more fundamental change they sought. Far from an isolated act of corporate atonement, then, this was an attempt by the next generation to use lessons from their family heritage to build a more just future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;4. Leverage the family story as a source of competitive advantage.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For some family business entrepreneurs, the next venture can begin with a step back. So it was for British restaurateurs (and sisters) Helen and Lisa Tse, whose family heritage empowered their rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their grandmother, Lily Kwok, had emigrated from Hong Kong in 1956 and settled in Manchester, where she and her daughter Mabel built one of Britain&#39;s first Chinese restaurants. But the business eventually went bankrupt, the victim of racism and Chinese gangs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The story might have ended there. Instead, Helen and Lisa picked up the threads of their family narrative and carried it forward. Abandoning successful professional careers, they established their own Manchester restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sweetmandarin.com/&quot;>;Sweet Mandarin&lt;/a>;, in 2004. But the restaurant only took off when Helen published a best-selling memoir about her grandmother. With this narrative platform, the sisters branched out into other endeavors, like cookbooks and cookery classes, tied to their own life stories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the Tse sisters, family heritage proved to be a source of competitive advantage. By recovering an immigrant&#39;s tale with universal appeal, they gained acceptance outside of their own ethnic communities. And by situating themselves in an entrepreneurial tradition spanning three generations, they created a sense of longevity that evoked quality and trustworthiness, even as they also innovated new products alongside recipes inherited from their grandmother.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Family legacy is not a monologue; it&#39;s a dialogue, a collective story that belongs to the whole family. When families think of legacy in these terms, they empower younger generations to harness that story to their own purposes, drawing strength from their elders. Legacy, in short, becomes not a burden but a blessing — one that can help families sustain wealth and purpose long into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Identify the Right Strategic Goals for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_670123874.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;cyano66/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In setting strategic objectives, companies usually end up with a list of worthy but vague aspirations. The secret to getting a list of clearly defined and measurable objectives is to anchor them in what you, as a company&amp;#8217;s leaders, want to get from your stakeholders. This leads you to defining desired behavioral outcomes, even fairly obvious ones like buying more. The debate can then move to thinking about how to trigger that behavior, and progress toward these outcomes can be described in measures that are in dollars, like revenue; quantities, like units sold; or percentages, like market share. Thinking in this way sounds prosaic, even obvious, but it is an effective way of getting a management team to think clearly about what they need to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann is the CEO of my country&#39;s largest independent, not-for-profit aged-care provider, offering residential aged care, retirement living, and at-home support. It was established well over a hundred years ago and is set in many of its ways. One of these is how strategic objective-setting is conducted. But Ann&#39;s not happy with the process. I asked her, “Why not?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;She explained. “When we get together to discuss our future direction as a business, we invariably get to the point where we need to write down our objectives. If we&#39;re using a facilitator, and we usually do, that person will walk over to a flipchart or whiteboard and write &#39;Objectives&#39; at the top. Then everyone piles in brainstorming to produce a list that&#39;s far too long.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“And you whittle that list down?” I asked.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Yes,” Ann continued. “The discussion and arm-wrestling then start with the aim of reducing the items to about half a dozen. After some considerable time, my exhausted and frustrated colleagues are only too happy to move on to the next agenda item.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann explained how her team was usually not content with the result. “Nor am I,” she added, “because invariably the &#39;Objectives&#39; list contains a hodgepodge of activities, nice-to-haves, and vague statements of intent.” Ann showed me her latest result:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;To become an employer of choice.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To grow the business by opening additional centers.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To maintain stability in resident and client care.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To manage risks and crises effectively.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To secure compliance with regulatory authorities.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To transform operations by adopting additional technology.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Maybe your own endeavors have produced a similar list. You might be wondering: What&#39;s wrong with this? The answer is: Plenty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Any strategy she comes up with will have to specify what the company can do to meet the needs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;each key stakeholder group&lt;/a>;: residents, clients, employees, suppliers, shareholders, and the community. This means that her business will have to take a &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the-volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;position on the factors important to each of those groups&lt;/a>;. For instance, Ann&#39;s management team must set policy on working conditions, pay, organization culture, and so on for employees. What should guide these decisions? And how will Ann know if the decisions are progressing the organization? How will she measure this?&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The answers should be her list of strategic objectives. But Ann&#39;s hodgepodge doesn&#39;t deliver a clear line of sight between the business&#39;s competitive stance for each key stakeholder group and the results. How can you tell if a strategy is working? It&#39;s as though the list of objectives exists in a black hole.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Shift Your Thinking About Objective-Setting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The trick to breaking away is to flip your perspective and ask what your organization wants &lt;em>;from&lt;/em>; its key stakeholders. (This comes as an “aha” moment for most managers.) These will be your strategic objectives. For example, consider revenue from customers, innovation from employees, and support from the community. Your thinking must shift to be outside-in if you are to produce successful strategic objectives. If you picture organization objective-setting this way, you can see how it can be broken into a stakeholder-by-stakeholder exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 1: Identify a behavioral outcome for each stakeholder group.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;To illustrate, let me share a story. One CEO I advise, Stuart, heads up a mutual bank with “members.” I ran a workshop for him and his managers. We identified the credit union&#39;s key stakeholders, one of which was, naturally, members. To break through the traditional brainstorming hodgepodge, I asked the group a seemingly simple question: “What do you want your members to do?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This came as a surprisingly fresh approach to the group and required them to think more deeply. After some discussion, we got this: “To get members to borrow more and to get potential members to become members.” I explained how I call this a &lt;em>;behavioral outcome&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 2: Convert behavioral outcomes into organization objectives.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I then led Stuart&#39;s group to the second step, which is to convert this behavioral outcome to an &lt;em>;organization objective.&lt;/em>; This usually starts with “to increase” or “to decrease.” After careful consideration and debate, the group agreed to: “To increase revenue from current and future members.” Notice “future.” This will be driven by positioning on the strategic factors relevant to members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Why didn&#39;t I just start there at the second step? The reason is that invariably the process falls back into becoming a hodgepodge. Identifying a behavioral outcome for each key stakeholder group first anchors organization objectives, which then become clear and measurable&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 3: Identify measures.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This brings me to the third step: identifying &lt;em>;measures&lt;/em>;, a short list of which is usually referred to as key performance indicators or KPIs. This can be tricky, as all sorts of things become labeled as KPIs in exercises like this. In the past, Stuart&#39;s organization had labeled actions by individuals and program descriptions as KPIs. So, I needed to point out that a key performance indicator is a key performance &lt;em>;measure.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The clincher for Stuart and his group came when I demonstrated that there are only three ways to measure results in business and that they can be neatly summarized by three symbols: $ (or the local currency), # (number of), and % (percentage). No one had condensed results for them in that way before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The advantage of this is that Stuart and his team now have a stakeholder-oriented objective for members that can be measured. Stuart can measure the total revenue generated by new and existing members; the number of new and existing members; and the bank&#39;s percentage of market share. Any strategies aimed at creating competitive advantage — around, for example, product range, customer service, and pricing — can be evaluated using these hard results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I do this for each of an organization&#39;s key stakeholders: customers, employees, suppliers, and so on. It always gets a management group to probe what the organization is really trying to achieve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;Your Objective-Setting Journey&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;If you want to produce clearly targeted strategy, you simply must avoid the standard practice of brainstorming to yield a list of strategic objectives. It leads to a hodgepodge of difficult-to-measure items, as Ann&#39;s experience demonstrates. Instead, rethink your journey by identifying who your key stakeholders are&amp;nbsp;— and what you want from them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This will provide you with clear and measurable outcomes that will help focus your organization&#39;s strategic positions for each of your key stakeholders. Strategic clarity will be your result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>