<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Transform Business Operations with Process Mining]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/transform-business-operations-with-process-mining]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sept23_28_596456570.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;贝恩德·沃格尔/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;我们采访的最高效的公司使用流程挖掘来大规模生成运营洞察、识别流程效率低下、定义有针对性的行动并衡量流程改进 &amp;# 8212；所有这些都会导致价值实现。完全接受这种级别的流程管理通常是一项重大的文化变革。领导者描述了从以英雄为中心的公司到以流程为中心的公司的文化历程。我们的目标是建立高效的流程，执行一致、顺利，而不是依靠本地英雄来拯救世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/transform-b​​usiness-operations-with-process-mining?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/transform-b​​usiness-operations -with-process-mining?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;流程挖掘是从一个学术概念演变而来的（首先&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vdaalst.com /publications/p128.pdf&quot;>;于 2001 年发布&lt;/a>;）是一种用于分析、监控和改进过程性能的流行软件工具。正如我们在&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/04/what-process-mining-is-and-why-companies-should-do-it&quot;>;上一篇文章&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot; https://link.springer.com/book/10.1007/978-3-030-40172-6&quot;>;书&lt;/a>;，流程挖掘分析企业事务系统事件的日志以创建流程的详细图片，从而提供实际流程的数字孪生。它正在迅速取代以前理解业务流程的观察性和主观方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;流程挖掘最初是一种用于临时调查流程性能问题的工具，但现已发展成为一个用于监控和改进运营的平台大规模流程执行，以提高流程效率并帮助实现业务价值。作为无可争议的、基于事实的实际流程可视化，它为规模化运营转型提供了独特的事实来源。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的研究重点是业务背景和成功背后的关键成功因素。大型组织中的流程挖掘。我们采访了 11 家公司的流程挖掘领导者。我们中的一位（Lars）在担任客户顾问期间观察到许多其他使用 Celonis（该技术的领先提供商）来扩展流程挖掘的努力。现在有很多流程挖掘软件供应商，包括 Microsoft 和 SAP 等老牌公司，我们在这项研究中还采访了其他供应商的客户。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;使用流程挖掘的背景&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们发现了两种替代环境，公司将流程挖掘应用于其业务并随着时间的推移进行扩展。其中之一涉及在其业务中广泛采用流程导向的公司；另一种情况是那些试图更加注重流程但尚未完全做到这一点的公司内部。在过去的几十年中，流程导向在流程改进和再造工作中变得有些流行，但许多公司尚未将其业务的流程视图完全制度化。以流程为导向的公司拥有明确定义的端到端流程（例如订单到现金和采购到付款）、这些流程的所有者以及明确的目标和绩效指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些公司我们采访了一些既定流程导向的公司（主要是中欧的公司），他们正在使用流程挖掘来超越传统的业务流程建模，进行挖掘并改进基于流程的操作的实际执行。他们用它来大规模生成运营见解、识别流程效率低下、定义有针对性的行动并衡量流程改进——所有这些最终都会导致价值实现。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有强大流程导向的公司正在使用流程挖掘来进一步灌输端到端流程的理念，激发更好的流程执行，并减少整个企业流程的变化和复杂性。两个小组都发现该技术很有用，尽管没有强大流程导向的公司的流程挖掘领导者必须花费更多时间宣传该技术并招募业务赞助。完全接受流程管理通常是一种重大的文化变革，我们采访的一家大型全球航运和物流公司就证明了这一点。其流程领导者描述了从一家以英雄为中心的公司到一家流程公司的文化之旅。目标是建立高效的流程，并实现一致、平稳的流程执行，而不是依靠本地英雄来拯救世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;扩展的关键成功因素&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;有多种可能的因素可能会推动流程挖掘计划的成功扩展。我们已经确定的一些包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;高管对流程挖掘和持续支持理念的认可&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;企业所有权来推动其领域内的项目&lt;/li>; &lt; li>;创建卓越中心（CoE）——一个专门的团队来加速流程挖掘&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;变革管理、培训和用户社区发展&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将流程挖掘与战略目标和内部联系起来程序&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;强调流程挖掘中的业务价值实现（价值优先）&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;实时集成和数据访问，并连接到馈送系统&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;运营流程执行工作嵌入到持续管理中。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;当我们与采访的流程挖掘领导者讨论这些因素时，我们询问哪些因素在他们自己的组织中最重要。最常见的反应是高管的支持——首先招募高管发起人，确保他们的持续支持，并推动整个组织对新项目的采用。在消费产品公司 Reckitt，流程挖掘计划从一开始就得到了首席执行官、首席财务官和 CIDO 的支持。他们不仅赞助该计划，还将其与战略优先事项联系起来，并通过可衡量的 KPI 管理转型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;企业所有权是高管支持的较低版本，几位流程挖掘领导者也提到过这一点。业务利益相关者或流程所有者需要理解并支持挖掘、分析流程绩效数据并采取行动的想法，否则它根本不会发生或成为日常实践。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在百事公司，业务利益相关者将流程挖掘视为创建一家完全不同的公司使命的关键推动者，作为其数字化转型战略的一部分。默克拥有明确的流程来参与新业务领域，以建立所有权。其中包括介绍现有的默克示例，作为该业务领域的痛点、重要资源和改进潜力的参考和讨论。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;几位流程领导者还提到了高度重视价值的重要性。流程挖掘是有成本的——例如软件和组织支持——对于大多数公司来说，确保计算、验证和实现从中产生的价值非常重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关注业务价值意味着最有价值的项目优先考虑，从而产生积极的商业案例。例如，在医疗保健公司 Cardinal Health，每年都有明确的流程挖掘价值目标。流程挖掘团队每月报告每个项目的真实实际值，并且财务组织和业务利益相关者必须同意它们。进入第二年，康德乐的流程挖掘工作就超额实现了 2.5 倍的价值目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些流程挖掘领导者（通常领导该技术的 CoE）承认，此类中心对于加速发展至关重要采用。然而，如果没有一定程度的高管支持和有能力的团队，它们一开始就不会成立。糖果和宠物食品巨头玛氏提到，其成功的主要因素是找到适合流程挖掘的人才——能够将技术和业务领域连接起来的人。个人需要能够编码、构建数据模型、咨询、理解需求、部署和支持流程改进。毫不奇怪，他们很难找到。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了使流程挖掘成为运营转型的强大驱动力，它总是回到人身上。变革管理是欧洲一家制药巨头的关键因素。它有专门的流程挖掘社区计划，包括每两周一次的全体会议、个人发展内部培训课程、展示最佳实践成功案例以及持续的社区活动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;从见解到行动&lt;/强>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们采访的流程挖掘领导者一致认为，重要的是超越对流程如何执行的洞察（流程挖掘的初衷），转向可持续改进的行动。从软件的角度来看，从洞察到行动涉及特定类型流程的目标应用程序和问题领域，例如保留应付账款中的现金或改善应收账款中的现金流（两者在衰退经济体中都很流行）、提高采购中的供应商可靠性以及构建供应链；弹性，或优化库存水平。许多公司还专注于识别并加快订单管理流程中缓慢或低质量的交付。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从管理角度来看，我们采访的公司采取了各种措施，以便将见解转化为行动。在北欧和波罗的海电信公司 Telia 公司，多种因素共同推动了行动。其 CoE 专注于寻找对流程挖掘感兴趣并愿意尝试的合适业务部门。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在许多情况下，Telia 首席运营官为他们敞开了大门。中心工作人员还努力确定该业务领域的合适人员与他们合作，并让他们参与数据驱动的流程改进。他们咨询了内部客户，以确定他们想要解决的流程问题。最终目标是在运营中使用流程挖掘的见解并每天推动价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;流程挖掘的未来&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;此外在询问流程挖掘领导者是什么让他们的组织取得成功（以及什么在这方面没有什么帮助）时，我们还询问了他们未来的流程挖掘和运营转型计划。一些公司专注于利用技术创新；另一些则专注于技术创新。其他人致力于充实流程挖掘的组织基础设施。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在技术方面，Mars 专注于确定自动化分析的进步如何使流程挖掘在整个组织中更易于使用和扩展。目标是无缝生成定制的见解和建议，从而推动业务价值。同样，多方希望人工智能能够帮助用户识别重大改进杠杆并支持更好的流程执行。 BMW 致力于让组织中的几乎每个人都可以使用流程挖掘，目前正在对 80,000 名员工进行数字技能培训，以支持流程挖掘和其他用户发起的活动。 Cardinal Health 希望在其基本流程挖掘软件中添加对任务挖掘和执行管理技术的关注。默克正在致力于以对象为中心的流程挖掘，以实现流程的 3D 视角，并通过数字流程孪生促进跨孤岛改进。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在流程挖掘的组织开发方面，包括过滤器在内的多个组织制造商曼胡默尔希望扩大流程挖掘的用户社区以及有助于改进流程的流程管理组织。 Ingka（宜家零售商）同样希望建立一个由流程挖掘从业者和拥护者组成的社区。其流程挖掘领导者预计，这家全球家具零售商最终将使每个国家都能拥有自己的流程挖掘沙箱进行试验，以及全球范围内的一组联合流程挖掘 CoE。 Mars 希望建立一个超级用户联合网络，而 Telia 则旨在帮助公民开发人员实现流程自动化。 Cardinal Health 与制药和医疗器械公司网络合作，希望扩展流程挖掘以跨组织优化流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>;这些公司提供的证据表明流程挖掘是一项将持续存在的技术。现在有多家供应商提供它，大公司正在构建技术和组织基础设施来支持它，并且许多公司正在从中获得可观的价值。见解正在转化为行动，最终为组织的高层、底层和绿线提供价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Ways to Develop Talent for an Unpredictable Future]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/5-ways-to-develop-talent-for-an-unpredictable-future]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_09_1582805042.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;designer491/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;我们可能不知道明天的工作会是什么样子，但我们可以有把握地假设，当人们更加好奇、情商更高、适应力更强时， 、有动力、聪明，他们通常会更好地了解完成这些工作所需的知识，并提供技术无法替代的任何人类价值。组织需要专注于扩展人们的才能，而不是押注于专家或强迫人们进入特定的领域。我们需要的不仅仅是重新技能或提升技能，而是预技能：也就是说，能够培养面向未来的人才并重塑人们的能力。在我们知道明天的工作和需求技能是什么之前，我们就已经开始了职业生涯。本文提出了五项广泛的建议，帮助您的员工为不确定的未来做好准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/为不可预测的未来开发人才的 5 种方法？ language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/5-ways-to-develop -talent-for-an-unpredictable-future?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;尽管围绕人工智能和工作自动化有许多标题党的标题和末日般的恐慌，但数据相当清晰：正如我在我的最新书中强调的那样，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Human-Automation-Quest-Reclaim-Unique-ebook/dp/B099KQV3ZJ&quot;>;&lt;em>;我，人类：人工智能，自动化，以及重新找回使我们与众不同的追求&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;您因人工智能而失业的可能性比&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/3- human-super-talents-ai-will-not-replace&quot;>;另一个人&lt;/a>;使用人工智能，特别是如果你自己不使用人工智能的话。从这个意义上说，人工智能时代并不是什么新鲜事。就像以前的颠覆性技术一样，人工智能正在消除一些工作岗位，但反过来又创造了更多新的工作岗位，这迫切需要人类。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;正如我们最近的万宝盛华报告所述，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .manpowergroup.com/en/news-releases/news/58-of-employers- believe-artificial-intelligence-and-virtual-reality-will-be-job-creators&quot;>;58％的雇主&lt;/a>;看到人工智能作为新就业岗位的净创造者。问题在于，因工作自动化而失业的人（例如，实体店经理）不会自动获得由技术创造的所有新工作（例如，网络安全分析师、数字营销人员或人工智能伦理学家）。据&lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10796-022-10308-y&quot;>;世界经济论坛&lt;/a>;称，到 2025 年，一半员工将需要重新培训才能跟上随着新技术的发展，这个数字早于当前的生成式人工智能热潮。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;正如斯坦福大学的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LNX_6gzLIvI&quot;>;Erik Brynjolfsson&lt;/a >; 据估计，组织在技术上每花费一美元，就需要在人才和相关流程上额外投资九美元，例如识别具有合适技能和潜力的人员；培养正确的技能；启用适当的变更管理流程；并为人们&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potial&quot;>;发挥潜力&lt;/a>;创造条件。事实上，正如我和我的同事 Becky Frankiewicz 和我&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/digital-transformation-is-about-talent-not-technology&quot;>;指出的&lt;/a>;，数字化转型的成败并不是真正的数字化转型。技术，但人的因素：人才。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作的未来&quot; dek=&quot;您的公司会吗适应还是被抛在后面？” cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black ;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;工作的未来&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？ &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;所以，我们需要的不仅仅是重新技能或提升技能，而是&lt;em >;预技能——也就是说，在我们知道明天的工作和需求技能是什么之前，能够培养面向未来的人才并重塑人们的职业生涯。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;预技能-为未知的未来培养员工技能&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如何做到这一点？尽管没有人知道确切的秘诀，尤其是因为没有关于未来的数据，但我们可以从宏观历史趋势进行推断，并从最近的经济和人力资本模式中吸取教训，提出五项广泛的建议：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 >;1) 关注潜力&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;随着当前技能、专业知识和绩效的生命周期缩短，建议聘用和提拔人员以实现&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.myhrfuture.com /digital-hr-leaders-podcast/how-ai-can-unlock- human-pottial-and-make-work-more-meaningful&quot;>;他们&lt;em>;可以&lt;/em>;做什么&lt;/a>;，而不是做什么他们过去做过。&lt;/em>;。这意味着优先考虑软技能 - 例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.learnabilityquotient.com/&quot;>;学习能力&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;/2015/12/assessment-whats-your-curiosity- profile&quot;>;好奇心&lt;/a>;、复原力和适应能力 - 高于硬技能 - 例如编程或数据挖掘 - 专注于基础&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/ iops.12001&quot;>;就业能力的要素&lt;/a>;，而不是当前的技术专长或过去的就业经历，这两者仍然主导着现代招聘方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;简单地说，我们可能不知道明天的工作会是什么样子但我们可以有把握地假设，当人们更具好奇心、情商更高、适应力更强、更有动力、更聪明时，他们通常会更有能力学习完成这些工作所需的知识，并提供技术无法替代的任何人类价值。潜力的一个优势是我们拥有可靠且经过验证的方法来衡量它，特别是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Talent-Delusion-Intuition-Unlocking-Potential/dp/0349412480&quot;>;心理评估工具&lt;/a>;，它也可以用来&lt;em>;开发&lt;/em>;人们的潜力，特别是通过规范和&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2019-21619-003&quot;>;数据驱动的反馈&lt;/a>;，帮助他们识别他们现在的位置和他们需要的位置之间的差距（见下一点）。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2）提供关键反馈&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;甚至在之前人工智能到来后，人们对于将人们的才能和潜力与最佳职业选择结合起来已经存在很多困惑和误解。现在事情变得更加复杂，大多数员工（和经理）都想知道他们将来会做什么，他们的经验和专业知识 - 以及他们在职业生涯中投入的所有时间和金钱 - 是否仍然相关，如果所以，在哪里。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;共享数据驱动的反馈（来自评估、内部数据和同行评级）并帮助人们了解他们的兴趣和技能如何成为组织的未来资产是关键。这意味着将&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;领导者视为教练或人才经纪人&lt;/a>;，他们的主要工作是主动培养人们的才能，并利用他们的才能充分的潜力。请记住：大多数人&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Talk-Three-Powerful-Feedback/dp/1912555093&quot;>;反馈被剥夺&lt;/a>;，并且令人震惊的&lt;a href= “https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1996-02773-003&quot;>;三分之二的反馈干预措施&lt;/a>;未能产生理想的结果。关键是告诉人们他们&lt;em>;需要&lt;/em>;听什么，即使他们&lt;em>;不想&lt;/em>;听，最重要的是，你告诉他们一些他们不知道的事情这可以激励他们变得更好。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;至关重要的是，仅仅向人们提供有关他们技能差距的反馈是不够的；还需要更多的反馈。组织还需要激励他们发展相关技能，同时提供最高效、最具吸引力和影响力的计划来发展这些技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3) 关注人才扩展&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;而不是押注于人才扩张专家或强迫人们进入特定的领域，专注于拓宽或扩展人们的才能。这意味着&lt;em>;不&lt;/em>;发挥&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/01/strengths-based-coaching-can-actually-weaken-you&quot;>;人们的优势&lt;/a>;，而是帮助他们发展&lt;em>;新的&lt;/em>;优势，因此它们变得更加多才多艺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们都有一种自然的倾向，让世界适应我们当前的技能，这样我们就可以“用更少的钱做更多的事” ”并针对懒惰效率进行优化，而不是延伸目标或获取新技能。事实上，除非你的员工在任何专业领域都处于前 1%（根据定义，这只能适用于极少数人），否则他们将更容易成为万事通，尤其是因为随着您学习的每一项新任务或技能，都会有许多与其他任务、工作和职业相关的新的基础技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这也将增加多样性和包容性。正如哈佛大学的 Joseph Fuller 和 Christina Langer 以及 Burning Glass Institute 的 Matt Sigelman &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/skills-based-hiring-is-on-the-rise&quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;：“向技能的转变基于招聘的招聘将为大量潜在员工提供机会，近年来，这些潜在员工经常因学位膨胀而被排除在考虑之外。”如果组织抱怨无法找到多元化和创造性的人才，他们应该停止在相同的地方和方式中寻找人才。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4) 投资于中层管理人员&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-reenergize-your-team-when-morale-is-low&quot;>;艾米·埃德蒙森和我&lt;/a>;最近指出，管理者掌握着释放人类潜力的钥匙在工作中，尤其是当面临的挑战是振兴、重新激发和重新构想人才时。即使在人工智能时代之前，中层管理人员的作用就至关重要，占团队的 30% 到 40% &lt;/a>;，但该角色的复杂性大大增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从历史上看，经理是具有经过验证的技术专长和作为个人贡献者的过去出色表现的人。如今，他们不仅需要了解“经典”管理任务（雇用合适的人员，给他们正确的任务和方向，利用反馈来激励他们，并提高团队绩效），还需要了解一些非常复杂的具体新挑战，例如作为&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/how-to-manage-a-hybrid-team&quot;>;管理混合&lt;/a>;和虚拟团队，&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/a-guide-to- Building-psychological-safety-on-your-team&quot;>;创造心理安全&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/5-strategies-to-infuse-di-into-your-organization&quot;>;提升 DEIB &lt;/a>;（包括雇用和激励与自己不同的人），以及帮助人们&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require&quot;>;管理人员-人工智能时代&lt;/a>;，包括引发的所有不确定性和压力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;简而言之，从未有过更好的&lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/the-case-for -investing-a-lot-more-in-middle-managers-in-1850548862&quot;>;有时间投资&lt;/a>;中层管理人员，特别是利用关键的软技能，这些技能可能使他们能够适应未来跟上技术进步并推动组织期望从新创新中实现价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5) 投资于领导技能&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;如果您担心人工智能推动的未来，但仍然认为人类将成为图片的一部分，那么你应该担心对你的领导者进行预先培训，因为他们（仍然）将负责制定和销售公司的战略，并在明天的不确定时期推动其文化的演变。在某种程度上，这仍然是关于提拔具有正确软技能（根据步骤 1）的个人并发展这些技能。这也是关于&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/08/hire-leaders-for-what-they-can-do-not-what-they-have-done&quot;>;继续前进&lt;/a>;并了解当今的顶级领导者可能不适合未来，尤其是因为他们的成功是建立在复制过去行之有效的基础上的，这往往是改变或学习新事物的障碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;重要的是，投资于领导力意味着利用使人们能够有效协作并成为高绩效团队的技能。这不是为了将个人提升到高级职位或荣耀地位，更不是为了通常支持的人气竞赛&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/10/what-science-says-about-identifying-high-pottial-employees&quot;>;“高潜力”提名&lt;/a>;——更确切地说，它是关于人们必须具备的品质，以激励、激励和带领他人进入一个肯定会包括人工智能的未来，但理想情况下也应该被定义为人类人工智能时代。这是当今领导力面临的严峻挑战。如果组织能够升级其领导力选拔系统，从复制过去的成功经验转向选择和培养未来的技能，那么所有其他挑战都将变得更容易。特别是，这意味着不再强调“文化契合度”、过去的表现和技术专长等因素，而是更多地关注学习能力、好奇心、正直和人际交往能力。更重要的是，如果组织真正对利用多样性感兴趣，他们必须优先考虑&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/what-makes-an-inclusive-leader&quot;>;包容性&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.businessinsider.com/key-attributes-inclusive-leader-professor-business-psychology?r=US&amp;IR=T&quot;>;领导力&lt;/a>; 和认知多样性，打破领导力概况的同质性。&lt;/p >; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;技术总是在变化，但为了确保这些变化实际上是一种进化（即促进进步），我们必须尽一切努力使人类能够开发和部署相关人才来收获技术的潜在好处。尽管这绝不是理所当然的，但我们应该对我们的物种继续适应其自身技术发明的能力充满信心。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Middle Market Companies Can Avoid a Liquidity Crisis]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/how-middle-market-companies-can-avoid-a-liquidity-crisis]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_06_1551147627.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;PM Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;经理们倾向于将流动性视为财务问题，但面对销售和运营团队的行为，管理者往往将流动性视为财务问题。以及他们如何沟通和合作——可以直接影响公司的现金状况。为了改善这种工作关系，重点是协调团队、提高预测质量、将预测映射到供应链，并优化盈利能力而不是可预测性。遵循这些步骤可以减少公司的营运资金需求并增加收入和现金流。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href= &quot;/2023/10/how-middle-market-companies-can-avoid-a-liquidity-crisis?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/how -middle-market-companies-can-avoid-a-liquidity-crisis?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;现在不是缺钱或长期持有的时候库存，或两者兼而有之：当利率&lt;a href=&quot;https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/FEDFUNDS&quot;>;是一年前的两倍&lt;/a>;并且很难找到循环信贷时，情况就不同了。当&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/07/10/world-economic-outlook-update-july-2023&quot;>;国际货币基金组织项目&lt; /a>; 明年世界发达经济体将仅增长 1.4%。当预测和平衡供需比以往任何时候都更加困难时，情况就不是这样了，供需受到大流行的冲击，尚未恢复平衡。当&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.uscourts.gov/news/2023/07/31/bankruptcy-filings-rise-10-percent&quot;>;企业破产数量&lt;/a>;低于与去年相比增长了 23%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;即使没有破产，许多原本可行的公司也可能面临因成本上升、大流行导致的客户行为变化、挥之不去的供应链问题、不稳定的商业环境下销售的不确定性，以及寻找短期资金几乎肯定的困难。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;流动性通常被视为财务问题，但事实上，运营发挥着重要作用。在预防或解决现金问题方面发挥主导作用。改进运营、销售和财务协同运作方式的公司可以产生现金和息税折旧摊销前利润 (EBITDA)，而且数量通常相当多，而且速度非常快。加强销售和运营规划使公司能够在不受外部干扰的情况下掌握自己的命运——这在目前是一种特别有用的能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;中型市场公司通过进行这种转型可以获得很多好处。我们已经看到公司在短短几个月内将营运资本提高了 20-30%，并且 EBITDA 大幅增加。例如，一家私募股权拥有的维生素和营养补充剂制造商的 EBITDA 增长了 10%，这主要是因为其海外销售和分销（其大部分增长潜力所在）与美国的制造业务更加紧密地联系在一起。这有助于降低生产和运输成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;出于同样的原因，糟糕的销售和运营规划的影响严重打击了中间市场。部分原因是这些公司如果需要外部资本就会处于不利地位。在 AlixPartners 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://features.alixpartners.com/turnaround-transformation-survey-2023/&quot;>;2023 年调查&lt;/a>;中，96% 的扭亏为盈和重组专家表示，中间市场最有潜力当今资本限制带来的风险。中型企业也受到威胁，因为它们经常向大型跨国公司销售产品，而大型跨国公司越来越多&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/some-companies-are-take-longer-to-pay-suppliers-尽管- recovery-11623058200&quot;>;稍后使用他们的实力向供应商付款，&lt;/a>;在某些情况下试图锁定他们在大流行期间赢得的轻松条款。由于中间市场公司往往多元化程度较低，因此更容易受到冲击。而且，由于它们的规模，它们的“流动性跑道”——现金短缺演变成危机之前的时间——比大公司短。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;每家公司都有某种调整供应和供应的流程。要求。在较小的公司中，这通常是非常非正式的：销售带有预测，首席财务官对其进行折扣，生产增加一些作为缓冲，每个季度人们都会进行调整。许多企业拥有更复杂的流程，但往往比较僵化，对市场的微弱信号反应迟钝，如果业务出乎意料地好，就会导致生产中的消防演习；如果情况不佳，就会出现减价销售。在这两种情况下，该流程的重点都是平稳管理生产，而不是产生现金和利润。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所需要的（尤其是中间市场）是一个转变的销售和运营规划流程，以实现这一目标使管理人员能够调整运营以增加现金生成和盈利能力。这种转变有四个要素：运营、销售和财务之间保持一致的团队。 &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当这些团队协调一致时，他们&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;就能够了解公司如何使用和产生现金。 “对齐”是关键词。运营和销售计划应该在跨职能的“作战室”中进行管理，但除非所有参与者都明确受到影响现金生成和利润的项目的激励，否则它不会起作用，而这些项目通常不属于 KPI 运营和销售轨道。在大多数公司中，运营团队的衡量标准是货物成本、缺陷率、机器利用率等；销售团队倾向于跟踪和奖励销量，并针对促销等提供特殊奖励。这些激励措施应该改变，以包括现金和营运资本衡量标准（例如，库存天数、平均折扣、应收账款平均未清天数）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;预测也需要重新预测，因此他们对预测水平进行了建模生产和销售的情况会影响企业的所有三个视图：损益表、现金流量表和资产负债表。该团队还需要了解整个企业的流动性需求、流动性的最大威胁以及最大的现金来源，即哪些产品或业务线消耗或产生最多的现金。这些揭示了您可以利用哪些杠杆。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;更严格和灵活的预测。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;首席财务官将销售团队的预测下调&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/03/ to-maximize-growth-get-sales-and-finance-in-sync&quot;>;高达 25%&lt;/a>;，部分原因是销售团队往往过于乐观，他们的预测有时不够站得住脚。另一个问题是他们的时间范围。根据我们的经验，最好建立滚动的中长期（3-14 个月）需求视图，使用它们来生成足够可靠的三个月预测，以便您可以做出采购和营销决策，并对其进行调整每周或每月。太远了，计划就不可靠；太远了，计划就不可靠。太接近，您就无法采取战略性行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不要忘记（正如许多公司所做的那样）使用客户流失和忠诚度数据来测试、验证和调整预测。您需要通过四种方式调整对需求的看法：首先，为了清楚地了解现金和 EBITDA 的来源（或不来源），建立利润和数量的图景；您想知道哪些产品和客户提供最多和最少的利润，并且&lt;a href=&quot;/1987/09/manage-customers-for-profits-not-just-sales&quot;>;密切关注&lt;/a>;遵守他们的命令和行为。其次，&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/setting-your-annual-budget-amid-economic-uncertainty&quot;>;正如您应该根据总体预算制定的那样，&lt;/a>;为长期观点创建情景 - 例如，需求会是高、中还是低，或者如果销售突然转向您销售的最低价格或利润最低的商品，会发生什么。第三，预先确定可以告诉你某个场景是否即将发生的指标；这将使忽略警告变得更加困难。最后，使用月度和季度审查不仅可以跟踪计划的预测，还可以重新验证其前提。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;同样严格的供应图。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;应包括材料、组件、和劳动力的可用性。除此之外，您还需要确定交货时间最长的组件或供应品，或者您对上游条件的了解告诉您要警惕价格或供应冲击的组件或供应品。许多提供商帮助公司建立供应链“控制塔”，以近乎实时地跟踪可用性和定价，通常是在人工智能的帮助下。这些曾经几乎是跨国公司的专属领域，但现在大多数中型市场的预算都可以承受。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;优化盈利能力而非可预测性的运营。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;运营计划保证不间断地生产利润最低的产品并不好。凭借您现在掌握的有关产品和客户盈利能力的知识、更好的现场信息流以及强大的跨职能团队，您现在可以利用您的运营所需的任何灵活性将生产从一个地点或产品转移到另一个地点或优先考虑来自盈利客户的订单。您可以对库存管理进行类似的更改。从战略角度来看，库存可以是一种流动性消耗，也可以是一种新的客户获取工具——“坏”或“好”库存——并进行相应的管理。从长远来看，您可以重新调整资本支出方向，以提高对现金和利润最直接影响的领域的运营灵活性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;像这样的计划释放了 1700 万美元的营运资金 - 减少了约180 天——对于一家总部位于密西西比河谷、销售额达 20 亿美元的消费品公司。由于大型在线零售商突然抢走了当地商店的业务，新冠疫情对其供应链造成严重破坏，并导致需求大幅波动，该公司的业务失去了平衡。它的预测模型被拍摄；由于无法知道销售额来自何处，一个业务部门支付了近 100 万美元的逾期交货罚款和空运费用。根据猜测，工厂生产了错误的产品组合，采购部门采购的某些零部件太少，而另一些零部件采购过多，导致满足率（按时全额完成订单的百分比）从 95% 骤降至 75% 左右。为了满足订单需求，运营团队储备了比公司所需多 1200 万美元的成品库存。以前解决这个问题的尝试都是零散的——供应和零部件、生产计划、预测——而不是系统地解决。我们与他们合作建立了一个粗略的产能模型，可以比以前提前几个月揭示潜在的供需失衡；提高预测团队的分析技能；并制定每月一次的销售和运营规划会议的节奏，让数据和决策者齐聚一堂。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•••&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果没有系统性的观点，这场游戏中每个参与者的激励和良好意愿——采购、生产和销售——几乎总是会导致游戏失去平衡。运营团队处于将系统整合在一起的独特位置，因为他们首先感受到痛苦，表现为仓库没有被清空或订单无法满足。当现金和 EBITDA 出现痛苦时，已经晚了——有时已经太晚了。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Help Your Employees Develop the Skills They Really Need]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/help-your-employees-develop-the-skills-they-really-need]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_06_532771834.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;史蒂夫·陈/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;工作的未来不是由技术决定的，而是由培养技能和投入所需的教育、接触和经验的正确组合决定的。他们去工作，创造一个生产力大大提高的工作场所和经济。在本文中，作者推荐了“70/20/10”学习模式，其中只有 10% 的学习来自正式指导（教育），20% 来自社会学习或指导（接触），70% 来自动手、体验式实践和反馈（经验）。通过采用这种模型，组织可以确保员工不仅了解新技能，而且可以在不同的环境中有效地应用它们。这是工作流程中最容易被忽视的关键 70% 的学习，也是培养未来成功所需技能最需要的部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/help-your-employees-develop-the-skills-they-really-need?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/help-your-employees-develop-the-skills-they-really-need?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在颠覆的时代，唯一可行的策略就是适应，这一点在今天尤其如此。一代人之前，技能价值的半衰期是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20190127- humanics-a-way-to-robot-proof-your-职业生涯>;大约26年&lt;/a>;。现在，半衰期通常&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/reskilling-in-the-age-of-ai&quot;>;不到五年&lt;/a>;。因此，在全球范围内，企业的投资预计将超过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/2022-corporate-training-landscape-training-industry-inc-&quot; >; 今年学习和发展计划投入 3800 亿美元&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但我们需要做得更好。我们知道，经过数十年的尝试，与 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.industryweek.com/operations/continuous-improvement/article/21267990/widespread-lean-adoption-would-make-the-us 相关的技能-more-competitive&quot;>;精益制造&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://pmessentials.us/agile-better-adoption-low/&quot;>;敏捷开发&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;/2022 /12/the-failure-of-the-dei-industrial-complex&quot;>;克服无意识偏见&lt;/a>;（仅举几例）在大多数组织中都没有得到充分采用。事实上，麦肯锡最近的一份报告 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/McKinsey/Business%20Functions/Organization/Our%20Insights/Beyond%20hiring%20How%20companies%20are%20reskilling %20to%20address%20talent%20gaps/Beyond-hiring-How-companies-are-reskilling.pdf&quot;>;发现&lt;/a>;，87% 的受访公司预计在未来五年内会出现技能差距。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;更多培训并不是答案。我们不能简单地将员工派往专注于当前流行的任何熟练程度的研讨会并期望取得成果。重要的是建立连贯的基于技能的战略。我们必须认真思考要针对哪些特定技能，谁必须学习这些技能，以及什么样的教育、经验和接触组合才能有效地创建我们应对未来挑战所需的基于技能的组织。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;例如，在 Todd 担任执行副总裁的软件公司 PKWARE，该公司将超过 1% 的收入投入到销售培训上，重点是围绕特定流程调整团队。虽然员工接受了教育，但未能产生预期的影响，因为员工没有持续获得维持最初改进所需的指导和实时指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type =&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作的未来&quot; dek=&quot;您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black ;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;工作的未来&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？ &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;将其与 Wipro 进行比较，Abhijit 曾担任 Wipro 的首席学习官。保险部门的业务领导者接受了一项特定技能的培训：讲故事。高管们参加了一个文学节，其中&lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/company/corporate-trends/wipro-senior-executives-at-jaipur-literature-festival-to-polish -narration-skills/articleshow/11573005.cms&quot;>;与专业讲故事者接触&lt;/a>;超过三天。每天晚上，他们还参加一个结构化的研讨会，帮助他们处理他们所观察到的情况。返回办公室后，他们在很长一段时间内接受了同事的持续指导，并反过来鼓励他们培训自己的团队讲故事。这不仅有助于传播技能，而且使领导者有机会在教导他人时进一步加深自己的熟练程度。结果是：赢得交易的情况显着改善，收入增长显着提高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;安德斯·爱立信 (Anders Ericsson) 花费了数十年的时间研究专业知识，他指出了 &lt;a href=&quot;/2007/07/the -造就专家&quot;>;刻意练习&lt;/a>;培养世界一流的表演者。仅仅指导是不够的，您还需要练习技能、确定需要改进的领域并接受指导。正是教育、经验和接触的结合才能提高绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;70/20/10 学习模式&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果我们的组织要学习赢得未来所需的技能，我们推荐“70/20/10”的学习模式，结合教育、接触和经验。其工作原理如下：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;10% 正式教学（教育）：&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;这部分学习策略涉及结构化的教育体验，例如 Wipro 高管参加的讲故事研讨会夜晚。其他示例包括专注于特定技能的网络研讨会或面对面课程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;20% 社交学习（接触）：&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;社交学习涉及向他人学习。这就是专业讲故事者在 Wipro 例子中所扮演的角色。其他选择包括指导、辅导或点对点互动。例如，在组织内设立导师计划可以帮助员工向更有经验的同事学习。定期的团队建设活动还可以培养持续学习的文化并有助于提高技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;70% 在工作流程中学习（经验）：&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;这是最重要的学习策略的重要组成部分。它涉及通过现实生活的经验和任务在工作中学习。例如，员工可以通过从事复杂的项目来提高解决问题的能力。定期反馈会议可以帮助员工反思自己的表现并确定需要改进的领域。当讲故事工作坊的参与者继续教导自己的同事并将其应用到他们的业务推介和评论中时，他们获得了宝贵的实践经验，加深了他们讲故事的技巧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这与传统的讲故事有很大不同主要侧重于 MBA 式课堂教学的企业学习方法，例如杰克·韦尔奇时代通用电气在克罗顿维尔管理发展学院闻名的学习方法。为了在 70/20/10 学习模式中取得成功，管理者需要扮演&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;教练&lt;/a>;的积极角色，而不是充当任务负责人，努力指导员工提高绩效。与此同时，学习与发展 (L&amp;D) 部门要做的不仅仅是提供课程；还需要做更多的事情。他们需要与领导者密切合作，设计个性化的学习环境。学习需要具有包容性、持续性和协作性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，作为重振德克萨斯州狭长地带地区计划的一部分，中银银行试图帮助其管理人员从将自己的角色视为绩效转变评估员到技能提升教练。 L&amp;D 团队并没有从预先存在的学习计划开始，而是首先花时间与领导者一起确定绩效改进的任务。然后，这些任务被分解为员工需要学习的技能，L&amp;D 团队指导经理，让他们使用 70/20/10 模型，通过个性化学习计划带头指导员工。九个月内，他们开始看到公司标准业务指标的可衡量结果。该银行首席执行官 Alex O&#39;Brien 表示：“我们采用 70/20/10 模型直接增强了我们的创新能力，使我们能够构建独特的核心软件，使我们在银行业中脱颖而出。”&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;如果我们要争夺未来，我们需要从“人才争夺战”思维转变为基于技能的思维。人才并不是企业可以吸引和竞标的天生财产，而是一种需要培养的能力——无论如何，未来最重要的技能还不存在。就像风险资本家投资和管理公司投资组合一样，企业领导者需要追求技能组合，放弃一些已经过时的技能，同时加倍投资那些开始产生回报的技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;未来工作的多少不是由技术决定的，而是由培养技能并将其运用到工作中所需的教育、接触和经验的正确组合来决定的，从而创造一个生产力大大提高的工作场所和经济。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引文-->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Avoid the Unexpected Consequences of Your DEI Policy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/how-to-avoid-the-unexpected-consequences-of-your-dei-policy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_06_1257013702.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;您即将实施的 DEI 政策实际上会伤害您想要帮助的一些人吗？关于这个问题的新研究表明，是的，如果您未能采取系统级别的观点，这种情况就可能发生。但好消息是，可以通过三种关键方法来避免意外后果。首先，考虑子组。考虑政策旨在帮助的人群中的差异；例如，大多数女性员工的经历是否可能与女性管理者不同。其次，要往大处想。认识到组织中人员之间的互动是多样且复杂的。当政策产生反响时，它们可能会以意想不到的方式伤害群体或子群体。三是密切跟踪。监控政策的推出是否对员工产生任何负面影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10 /how-to-avoid-the-unexpected-consequences-of-your-dei-policy?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/how-to-避免您的 dei-policy 的意外后果？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;虽然许多管理者试图通过实施多样性、公平性来改善员工面临的不平等现象和包容性 (DEI) 政策，&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/07/why-diversity-programs-fail&quot;>;这些政策往往会给员工带来意想不到的负面后果&lt;/a>; - 包括这些政策试图消除的后果帮助。管理者如何避免这种情况？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/epub/10.1177/00018392231174235&quot;>;我的研究&lt;/a>;表明有必要在实施 DEI 政策时，从系统层面看待不平等问题。也就是说，在设计和实施一项政策时，管理者必须考虑它将如何在整个组织中产生反响，以及最终可能会适得其反。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;政策&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在美国中型专业服务机构在我研究的组织中，领导者有一个良好的目标，即实施灵活的工作政策，让员工更好地控制工作地点和时间。该公司已经被员工视为对生活和家庭友好的公司，领导者希望巩固这一点，既因为这将有助于现有员工的福祉，也因为它可以为公司提供招聘方面的竞争优势。领导人还认识到，这些政策尤其可以帮助女性，因为在这个专业组织中 - &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/the-surprising-benefits-of-work-life-support&quot;>;与许多其他组织一样&lt;/a >;——女性比男性承担更多的家庭照顾。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;政策推出后，确实帮助了很多员工。正如预期的那样，我发现该政策特别帮助女性整合和平衡工作和生活需求。例如，它帮助他们打破日程安排，花更多时间陪伴孩子，并减少通勤时间，以便有时间与家人共度时光。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;问题&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;但是，该组织的领导者 - 和我 - 没有预料到灵活工作政策如何伤害了特定的女性群体：女性经理。尽管事实上这些管理者几乎都是改善性别平等的直言不讳的支持者，并倡导和支持各种其他对妇女和家庭友好的举措，包括后备儿童保育、现场日托和女性演讲者系列.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是怎么发生的？我的研究发现，许多女性管理者已经形成了一种注重与下属密切、日常互动的管理风格。例如，许多人每天都会定期去每个下属的办公室，询问他们的工作情况以及是否可以为他们的工作提供任何帮助或指导。其他人会敞开大门工作，以便下属在需要帮助时可以到办公室来。员工赞赏这些经理的努力，不仅因为他们提供了更直接的基于任务的帮助，而且因为随着时间的推移，这些经理变得非常了解他们的员工，并且可以在项目人员配置、职业培训等方面提供定制建议。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;重要的是，女性管理者并不是在真空中发展出这种管理风格的。相反，这似乎反映了她们在工作中面临的刻板印象：她们承受着乐于助人、具有集体性的压力，而不是像男性经理同事那样直接和自信。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从女性经理的角度来看，问题在于：灵活的工作政策将使他们形成的作风难以维持。虽然视频通话是一种选择，但经理们并不认为这是一种简单或自然的激发互动的方式。其他人指出，由于下属的工作时间不同，这意味着如果他们想要为员工提供帮助，他们也需要在更广泛的时间范围内工作。这不仅对任何人来说都很难做到，而且还可能使女性管理者自己的工作与生活冲突变得更加严重，因为这让她们很难有时间陪伴自己的家人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然我的研究专门针对性别，我发现与&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/update-your-dei-playbook&quot;>;其他&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com /doi/pdf/10.1177/00018392231183649&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;强调需要考虑&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2017.0087&quot;>;整个组织有效实施 DEI 工作&lt;/a>;，以及强调考虑&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2017.0062&quot;>;个人如何参与的重要性的研究并在组织系统内相互交互&lt;/a>;。当然，除此之外还要考虑 DEI 政策失败的其他重要原因，例如&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/is-your-dei-progress-undermined-by-attention-inequality&quot;>;各种&lt;/ a>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/to-overcome-resistance-to-dei-understand-whats-driven-it&quot;>;个人层面的偏见&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;避免意外后果来自您的 DEI 政策&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;鉴于 DEI 政策可能会以意想不到的方式在组织中产生反响，并可能破坏在公平和平等相关成果方面来之不易的进展，因此管理者必须预见到此类问题，这一点非常重要。我的研究和其他学者的补充研究（其中一些我在下面详细介绍）提出了三个关键建议，说明管理者如何限制其政策适得其反的可能性。这些建议都源于在设计和实施 DEI 政策时从系统层面看待不平等问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.考虑子群体。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在设计 DEI 政策时，请考虑政策旨在帮助的人群内部的差异。在我的研究中，大多数女性员工（从政策中受益）和女性经理（受到伤害）的经历之间存在重要差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;再举一个例子，想象一下如果经理试图帮助黑人员工通过创建同伴指导计划。该计划可能会为登记的黑人员工提供重要的帮助、建议和工作联系，研究人员发现这些员工&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/20-of-white-employees-have-sponsors-only-5-of- black-employees-do&quot;>;与白人工人相比，拥有内部赞助商的可能性要小得多&lt;/a>;，尽管事实上这种援助是&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-better-approach-to-mentorship #:~:text=%20evidence%20is%20clear%3A%2075,mentor%20are%20happy%20at%20work。&quot;>;对职业成功至关重要&lt;/a>;。然而，如果&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/what-do-black-executives-really-want&quot;>;公司中的高级黑人员工相对较少&lt;/a>;——考虑到系统性种族主义的历史模式，这种情况很常见——那么这几个员工可能每个人都有很多学员。意想不到的结果可能是，高级黑人员工最终花费大量时间指导初级黑人员工，而不是专注于推动自己的职业发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这里的教训并不是 DEI 政策不应该被忽视。当然是介绍了。而是通过更好的规划，这种负面结果是可以预见和遏制的。一旦注意到——无论是在推出之前还是之后——都可以找到解决方案。例如，在我们的例子中，高级黑人员工是否可以免除组织中常见的其他“帮助”职责，以腾出更多时间？或者可以给这些员工更多的&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/update-your-dei-playbook&quot;>;“魅力工作”&lt;/a>;来帮助他们发光发热？一般来说，这里的重点是不要单一地考虑某个特定群体——女性、LGBTQ+ 人群、黑人等——而是要认识到员工不同的组织级别、角色和任务以及他们的&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/06/an-intersection-approach-to-inclusion-at-work&quot;>;交叉身份&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2.着眼大局。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;系统级视角提请人们注意以下事实：&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/todays-most-ritic-workplace-challenges-are-about-systems&quot;>;交互组织中人员之间的联系是多样且复杂的&lt;/a>;。正如我的研究表明，当政策产生反响时，它们可能会以组织领导者和政策设计者完全意想不到的方式伤害群体或子群体。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，旨在防止对有犯罪记录的人的歧视——被许多公司采用，并在美国一百多个州、市和县强制执行——在某些情况下也被发现&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes. com/2016/08/21/upshot/ban-the-box-an-effort-to-stop-discrimination-may-actually-increase-it.html&quot;>;增加对黑人申请人的种族歧视&lt;/a>;，因为当这些政策已经到位，雇主似乎更有可能错误地认为黑人申请人有犯罪记录。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，这里的解决方案不是否认 DEI 政策。相反，在考虑政策如何可能给工人带来意想不到的负面后果时，重要的是要有远大的想法，因为你永远不知道这种后果会在何时何地发生。为此，请&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;召集不同的员工群体集思广益&lt;/a>;引入新的 DEI 可能会带来哪些潜在挑战政策。另请阅读并研究实施类似政策的其他公司的经验，看看他们的政策采用可能会产生什么（如果有的话）意想不到的后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.密切跟踪。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在政策推出时监控该政策是否对员工产生任何负面影响。监控有不同的层次。一是通过焦点小组或匿名意见箱获得有关员工体验的即时定性反馈，让员工可以发表评论而不必担心遭到强烈反对。从长远来看，分析内部管理数据以检查是否存在令人担忧或意外的模式非常重要。这包括查看群体或亚群体（例如，女性与男性，或黑人女性与白人女性）之间在个人职业成功的重要标志（例如绩效评估、工资、奖金和晋升）上是否存在差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些组织甚至在全组织范围内推广之前就开始试点其 DEI 计划，这种努力可以通过在政策正式实施之前发现问题来提高政策质量。 Ericsson, a global telecommunications company, &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/why-you-should-start-ab-testing-your-dei-initiatives&quot;>;tested a policy intervention aimed at improving women&#39;s interest in internal job openings&lt;/a>;. This testing helped Ericsson identify the message that seemed most likely to decrease the gender gap. And before rolling out a flexible work policy more broadly, &lt;a href=&quot;/2009/10/making-time-off-predictable-and-required&quot;>;Boston Consulting Group tested it with smaller groups of consultants&lt;/a>;. Here, it is important to collect data on employees&#39; experiences at baseline (before rollout) to compare with their experiences after policy implementation&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;DEI policies remain important ways to achieve positive improvements in equality within organizations. These three steps — which take a systems-level view of inequality — are purposeful, meaningful changes that managers can enact to design effective and impactful DEI policies. Of course, the research I present here is just a starting point. More is needed — particularly that accounts for different actors&#39; perspectives and the connections between them — to understand how DEI policies can be designed to best help employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A New Approach to Writing Job Descriptions]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/a-new-approach-to-writing-job-descriptions]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_06_4600878.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Juan Moyano/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Traditional job descriptions can&amp;#8217;t keep up with the rate of change in real roles in today&amp;#8217;s organizations. As new technologies disrupt processes and require new skills, and as companies are moving toward more and more project-based work, we are beginning to see the evolution of job descriptions away from static, holistic prescriptions that follow an employee for years to dynamic guidance that changes based on needs. What&amp;#8217;s replacing them are approaches that are more flexible because they&amp;#8217;re based on outcomes, skills, or teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/a-new-approach-to-writing-job-descriptions?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/a-new-approach-to-writing-job-descriptions?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Jobs today are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/the-future-of-jobs-report-2023/&quot;>;changing fast&lt;/a>;, and traditional job descriptions can&#39;t keep up. As new technologies disrupt processes and require new skills, and as companies are moving toward more and more project-based work, we are beginning to see the evolution of job descriptions away from static, holistic prescriptions that follow an employee for years to dynamic guidance that changes based on needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a company that hired an employee for a certain set of tasks might find that four months later, a different set of tasks takes strategic priority. Even though that employee has the right skills for the new tasks, the employee can point to their job description to decline to do the new task by saying that it wasn&#39;t what they were hired to do — or, if they take on the new tasks, their job description becomes quickly out of date.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;p>;This article is one in a series on “Creative Resilience: Leading in an Age of Discontinuity,” the theme of the 15th annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.druckerforum.org/&quot;>;Global Peter Drucker Forum.&lt;/a>; See the conference program &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.druckerforum.org/2023/program/&quot;>;here&lt;/a>;. &lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Because most job descriptions are firmly embedded in the employee&#39;s core area of work, they also tend to encourage silos in the organization by discouraging cross-functional collaboration. Rigid job descriptions also discourage experimentation with new technologies that may have been unimaginable at the time the description was written. And finally, narrow job descriptions can mean that an employee isn&#39;t able to fulfill the full range of their talents at work, leaving them dissatisfied.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In response, companies are starting to approach job descriptions in new, more flexible ways based on outcomes, skills, and teams. I&#39;ll describe each of these in turn, but first let&#39;s look at how job descriptions came to be what we know them as today, and what they do.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why Job Descriptions?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Modern job descriptions can be traced back to the industrial revolution. As factories and other large organizations became more common, there was a need to define roles and responsibilities more clearly to improve efficiency and productivity. This led to the creation of standardized job titles and descriptions, which outlined each position&#39;s tasks, duties, and requirements .&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By the mid-20th century they became even more formalized and detailed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today, job descriptions are used for several purposes:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Recruitment&lt;/strong>;: They help prospective applicants understand whether they would be a good fit for the position by providing a clear outline of what a role involves and what skills and qualifications are required.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Role clarification&lt;/strong>;: They help clarify the responsibilities, tasks, and expectations of a role, helping to avoid role ambiguity and conflict.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Performance management&lt;/strong>;: They serve as a benchmark for assessing employee performance.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;HR management&lt;/strong>;: They help plan employee development, set compensation, and serve as legal documentation.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;So how can job descriptions be made more flexible but still address these needs?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The More-Flexible Approaches&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re seeing three new approaches taking hold as companies grapple with rapidly-changing, project-based roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Outcome-focused role descriptions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some companies are beginning to articulate the outcomes expected from a role rather than the specific tasks or duties the employee is required to perform. This approach provides flexibility for the employee to determine the best way to achieve those results, fostering innovation and initiative and, importantly, allowing them to change their approach as conditions shift.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, instead of a sales manager&#39;s job description listing tasks such as “meet key clients once per quarter ” or “prepare sales reports on a monthly basis,” it would describe outcomes such as “increase regional sales by 15%” and “improve customer retention by 10%.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Google uses results-oriented job descriptions to keep their top talent motivated. Laszlo Bock, the former senior vice president of people operations, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Work-Rules-Insights-Inside-Transform/dp/1455554790&quot;>;explains&lt;/a>;:&amp;nbsp;“At Google, we believe that results-oriented job descriptions are essential for attracting and retaining top talent. When employees know what is expected of them and how they will be measured, they are more likely to be motivated and engaged in their work.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, traditionally, a design ethicist job description might have listed analyzing Google&#39;s search algorithm for bias once per month, or keeping a privacy risk log up to date. But in an outcomes-based job description, a design ethicist is instead given the broader mandate of identifying ethical risks in Google&#39;s products or developing guidelines for the ethical design of products. That gives both the employee and Google leeway for the specific tasks of the design ethicist to change as technologies develop — as generative AI is introduced into Google&#39;s offerings, for instance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Skills-focused role descriptions&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Other companies create dynamic documents that outline the skills and capabilities an employee brings to a position or should aim to develop. With this approach, the emphasis shifts from the tasks a person is supposed to complete to their talents and how those can be applied within company projects.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For a company to execute on this approach means identifying the skills and qualifications needed for each role and developing training programs and career paths that help employees build those skills. The aim is to fully utilize and develop an individual&#39;s abilities and strengths, which can lead to increased job satisfaction as well as performance. It also means that companies can quickly assemble teams of people with the skills and experience needed to tackle specific projects or initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a data analyst with superior visualization skills could seamlessly shift from creating complex data models to crafting visual reports, depending on project needs. The analyst would follow a specialized training regimen tailored to enhance specific skills, such as advanced visualization techniques and data storytelling. By focusing on the analyst&#39;s unique strengths and broader skill set, the organization not only hones their existing expertise but also creates a more well-rounded, versatile professional.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Team-based role descriptions&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Lastly, instead of giving each team member a job description, some companies assign individuals to teams that are given a collective set of objectives, outcomes, and deliverables. It is then up to the team to collectively decide how each member will contribute.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A well known example is Spotify, where employees are part of small, cross-functional teams called “squads,” each of which has a specific mission. Each squad autonomously decides how to meet its objectives best, relying on collective decision-making and their deep knowledge of each member&#39;s strengths and preferences. The teams meet frequently to discuss challenges, assess progress, realign goals, and resolve any conflicts or bottlenecks that result from the task distribution.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Overcoming Challenges&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Beyond simple resistance to change, there are a number of challenges that companies moving away from traditional job descriptions need to address.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The most basic is unclear job and performance expectations. Without a traditional job description, how does an employee know what is expected of them? How can a manager evaluate their performance objectively and follow fair compensation and promotion practices without clear guidelines in hand?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are other ways that managers can work with their teams to define roles and responsibilities and create a shared understanding of what each person is responsible for. For example, let&#39;s say you manage a team of software developers, and your company is shifting to team-based job descriptions. You might work with your team to create a skills matrix that identifies the skills and capabilities of each team member and then use tools like Agile methodology or Kanban boards to help manage workloads and prioritize tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For recruitment, a competency-based interview process is a more effective way to assess a candidate&#39;s suitability for a flexible, dynamic role than a traditional interview, which often focuses on the candidate&#39;s experience and qualifications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For performance evaluations, tools such as 360-degree feedback can help a manager to assess the employee&#39;s performance in various areas, including their skills, capabilities, and contributions to the team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More thorny issues can include legal compliance —such as Fair Labor Standards Act (FLSA) position status in the US — which can be challenging without a formal job description. Creating a “role compliance document” for each employee that provides a broad outline of the job and details such as job classification (exempt or non-exempt) can help here. Also, monitor employee tasks, responsibilities, and actual working hours to ensure that they align with&amp;nbsp;labor&amp;nbsp;guidelines; depending on your circumstances, this could be a periodic review or meticulous record-keeping enabled by modern HR software.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As organizations become more agile and responsive and technology enables new forms of work in the coming years, the trend towards project-based work and the need for more flexible job descriptions will continue. This radical disruption requires a shift in mindset and culture and asks individuals, managers, leaders, and organizations to experiment, learn, and adapt to new working methods. But with the right mindset and approach can lead to a more agile, responsive, and innovative organization better equipped to meet future challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Can You Tell How You Come Across on Zoom?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/research-can-you-tell-how-you-come-across-on-zoom]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_04_-5082558_-6953835.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Pexels&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;If you want to make a good impression and gauge what a colleague actually thinks of you, should you meet in-person or over videoconference? This is the question the authors explored in their research. The answer largely depends on whether you&amp;#8217;re feeling anxious about the social interaction. Most of us &amp;#8212; even the most socially confident &amp;#8212; have moments when we feel a bit more socially anxious than usual. In those cases, setting a meeting on Zoom might level out the playing field, allowing you to be as aware of your impression as someone who is feeling more secure. In brief, Zoom might give everyone an equal opportunity to adequately manage the impression they want to convey, which has important implications for both team leaders and their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/research-can-you-tell-how-you-come-across-on-zoom?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/research-can-you-tell-how-you-come-across-on-zoom?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;You just started a new job. You might be especially curious about your reputation around the office, and the impression you are making on your colleagues. Do people think you&#39;re intelligent and friendly? Inevitably, we all care about the way we come across to others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One reason we care so much about what people think of us is that it sets the basis for impression management. For example, if you realize that your new colleague thinks you are incompetent during your first project meeting, this gives you the opportunity to correct that misperception, which could be done by highlighting how your unique skillset is relevant to the project you&#39;re working on together. Alternatively, if you miss that cue, you might not be able to manage their impression of you, and before you know it, your reputation in the workplace might crystallize.&amp;nbsp;In short, knowing the impressions we make on others is a key step in smoothly navigating our professional and social interactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now that we&#39;re in a hybrid world, these interactions might be just as likely to take place over videoconference as they are in-person, and you might have the leeway to choose whether to meet virtually or face-to-face with a colleague. So, here are the questions we set out to answer with our research: If you want to gauge what a new colleague really thinks of you, which should you choose? Are you a better impression manager in-person or on Zoom?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Research&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In our &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2Fpspp0000457&quot;>;research&lt;/a>;, we tested which of these two assumptions prevailed. To do so, we had 305 people come into our lab before the Covid-19 pandemic (in groups of four to eight) and 555 people join a Zoom session during the pandemic (again, in small groups of three to nine). People would meet one on one with new people for a couple of minutes, just like at a speed-networking event. This resulted in a total of 1,683 unique in-person interactions and 3,068 unique Zoom interactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After each meeting, they reported on how they perceived each other&#39;s personalities. For example, they would be asked: “To what extent do you see this person as intelligent?” Importantly, we also asked them to rate how they think their interaction partner perceived them: “Does this person think I&#39;m intelligent?”&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The Future of Work&quot; dek=&quot;Will your company adapt or be left behind?&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black ;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;工作的未来&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？ &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;It turns out that people are good at knowing how they come across to others after just a two-minute interaction. Importantly, they are equally accurate about the first impression they make on Zoom as in-person. In both contexts, people could tell if their peer saw them as very intelligent and not so friendly. Put differently, our research suggests that people are able to know how they come across to a peer or a new acquaintance on Zoom to the same extent as in-person. In other words, interacting on Zoom does not seem to interfere with people&#39;s ability to know their reputations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What&#39;s more, knowing the impression you make on Zoom related to being liked more by others, as it does in-person. In other words, knowing how you&#39;re coming across to someone else was equally socially beneficial in Zoom interactions as it was in-person. So, knowing others&#39; impressions of us on Zoom seems to operate in the same way and carry the same benefits as it does in-person.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, what does this mean for your next interaction with your new colleagues? Should you think twice before deciding to meet them on Zoom? Contrary to some of our lay beliefs, at least when it comes to impression management, the decision to videoconference (vs. meet in-person) might not bear dramatic consequences for most people. But is this true for everyone?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3260965/&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; that people who feel more socially anxious feel more comfortable online than in person. By being more comfortable, they might be less worried and better able to gauge how they are coming across over Zoom. In fact, in our in-person&amp;nbsp;events, more socially anxious people were less aware of the impression they made (compared to more secure people). But on Zoom, this disadvantage disappeared: Both the more and less anxious people were equally aware of the impressions they made on others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But does this mean that Zoom helps the socially anxious and hurts the secure? It seems that it&#39;s a mix of both. Zoom appeared to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ilr.cornell.edu/news/research/zooming-socially-anxious-research-offers-insights&quot;>;give a little boost to the socially anxious&lt;/a>;, allowing them to know how they were coming across, perhaps because they were more comfortable on Zoom or because they could monitor themselves with the self-view feature. But at the same time, Zoom hindered more secure people&#39;s ability to detect how they came across. Perhaps having the self-view feature made them feel self-conscious, which could have been distracting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Coming back to our main question: Should you plan your next meeting on Zoom or in-person if you want to gauge what a colleague actually thinks of you? The answer to this question largely comes down to how you&#39;re feeling about the interaction and whether you&#39;re feeling anxious about it. Most of us — even the most socially confident — have moments when we feel a bit more socially anxious than usual. In those cases, setting a meeting on Zoom might level out the playing field, allowing you to be as aware of your impression as someone who is feeling more secure. In brief, Zoom might give everyone an equal opportunity to adequately manage the impression they want to convey. This has important implications for both team leaders and their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Implications&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If team leaders are aware that some team members might be feeling more socially anxious, maybe due to a specific context or personality style, it might be helpful to schedule a videoconference call instead of an in-person meeting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is not to say that the long-term solution is to avoid in-person interactions. However, while working up the social confidence to more smoothly navigate face-to-face meetings, more socially anxious people might benefit from using Zoom once in a while — especially for first impressions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employees can now feel more at ease knowing that videoconferencing does not hurt their impression management abilities. This means that instead of spending energy worrying about whether people “get them” on Zoom, they can focus more on the content of the meeting and actively engage with the team&#39;s ideas — and in that way, ultimately make a better impression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Overall then, especially if you are feeling more socially anxious, Zooming once in a while might just be the nudge you need to get back some control over your reputation around the office.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 23:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managers Need to Relearn How Interest Rates Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/managers-need-to-relearn-how-interest-rates-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_05_597318631.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Eric Raptosh Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In the United States, short-term interest rates have been near zero for most of the last 15 years. With cost of capital this low, many managers have paid scant attention to the time value of money &amp;#8212; an essential concept in doing financial analysis. Now, with short-term rates above 5%, older managers need to brush off their instinctive feel for how capital costs affect investment prospects &amp;#8212; and a younger generation of managers needs to learn these skills for the first time.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/managers-need-to-relearn-how-interest-rates-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/managers-need-to-relearn-how-interest-rates-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Imagine a planet where someone turns off gravity for 15 years. During this time, people get used to effortlessly flying around. But then gravity suddenly returns. Those accustomed to flying everywhere now need to navigate a weighted existence on the ground — and relearn basic skills such as walking. Walking may seem like a rudimentary activity, but if people don&#39;t do it for 15 years, muscle memory fades.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That scenario is analogous to the effect of interest rates being near zero for approximately 15 years, then suddenly increasing to the 5% range. Fifteen years is a very long time in a business career. And adjusting to this new interest rate environment will require significant shifts in behavior and mindset for managers and investors alike. Older managers will need to re-build the natural intuition they once had for concepts like &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporatefinanceinstitute.com/resources/valuation/hurdle-rate-definition/&quot;>;hurdle rates&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dcf.asp&quot;>;discounted cash flows&lt;/a>; — and a younger generation, those who entered the workforce after 2008, will need to develop an instinctive feel for these concepts from scratch.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This latter group might be surprised by a simple fact: short-term interest rates aren&#39;t normally near zero. But in 2008, in response to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2007%E2%80%932008_financial_crisis&quot;>;Global Financial Crisis&lt;/a>;, the US Federal Reserve dramatically lowered the federal funds rate to boost the economy, implementing what became known as its “zero interest rate policy,” or ZIRP. Even as the economy recovered from the 2008 recession, the Fed kept rates low for an extended period of time, and then returned to this policy during the Covid-19 pandemic. As a result, short-term interest rates in the US were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macrotrends.net/2015/fed-funds-rate-historical-chart&quot;>;near zero&lt;/a>; from 2008 until 2016, then again for much of 2020 and 2021. Over the last 15 years, they&#39;ve only been above 2% for a brief period in 2018 and 2019.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But now it&#39;s 2023, and ZIRP is over. The benchmark Fed Funds rate is currently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/fed-funds-rate-history/&quot;>;above 5.25%&lt;/a>;. Five-, 10-, and 30-year US Treasuries all now &lt;a href=&quot;https://home.treasury.gov/resource-center/data-chart-center/interest-rates/TextView?type=daily_treasury_yield_curve&amp;amp;field_tdr_date_value=2023&quot;>;yield nearly 5%&lt;/a>;, their highest levels in a very long time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The near-zero level of interest rates, the number of years they stayed at this level, and the pace at which they have since gone up — all of this is essentially unprecedented. But “unprecedented” has been an overused word lately, so there may be a tendency for managers to glaze over and not realize what a massive deviation this is from business as usual.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That would be a mistake. This interest rate shift is a seismic event, affecting any business decision involving multi-year cash flows. “Interest rates are to asset prices … like gravity is to the apple,” in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://buffett.cnbc.com/video/2013/05/04/morning-session---2013-berkshire-hathaway-annual-meeting.html?&amp;amp;start=4028&amp;amp;end=4343&quot;>;words&lt;/a>; of Warren Buffett. “They power everything in the economic universe.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For managers unaccustomed to naturally considering the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/t/timevalueofmoney.asp&quot;>;time value of money&lt;/a>; or the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/c/costofcapital.asp&quot;>;cost of capital&lt;/a>; when deciding what projects or investments to pursue, a lack of awareness of how important these concepts are can lead to dangerously wrong conclusions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One simple way to demonstrate this is to use a thought experiment I first encountered while working at a strategy consulting firm. It&#39;s the type of question consultancies sometimes use in job interviews, to try to understand how candidates think.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Assume a scenario in which:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;You will commute by train to and from work every weekday for the next five years.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;You need a token for each such round trip you take on the train.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Tokens currently cost $1 for each round trip (to and from work).&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Tomorrow, the price is going up to $1.20 — where it will stay for the next five years.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Before the price rises, you can buy as many tokens as you want at today&#39;s $1 price.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Only you can use the tokens you buy, no reselling.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The question is this: How many tokens do you buy at today&#39;s $1 price before the price permanently goes up to $1.20?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many people start with an approach that seems intuitive enough: I should buy as many tokens as I can afford, up to the full five years&#39; worth. Indeed, this seems like a no-brainer, a deal with a guaranteed, risk-free return. If you know you&#39;ll need 1,250 tokens (assuming 250 commutes per year for five years), and you know tokens will cost 20% more if you don&#39;t buy them now, why not buy 1,250 today — and enjoy $250 in savings?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some people try to get more exact: What about accounting for vacations and sick-days? Should I adjust for the post-Covid “work from home on Friday” policy? Is 250 commutes per year the right number, or might it be lower? And so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Those going down this path may get their math right. But they&#39;re not doing the &lt;em>;right&lt;/em>; math. In fact, the correct first question to ask is: What else can I do with my money?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the consulting-style interview, those who ask that question are told that: a) They can put it into a bank savings account that pays interest at an annualized rate of 10%; b) that this is their only investment option; and finally c) that there are no taxes, transaction costs, bank failures, inflation, etc. to worry about.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now what? Let&#39;s see what happens to $1 in the bank. After a year it grows to $1.10. After two years, it grows to $1.21 — slightly higher than the new token price.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This way of thinking, one which appreciates the fact that money has time value, leads to a different answer: You should buy two years&#39; worth of tokens. Money spent today buying any more than that would be better off compounding in the bank. You can then withdraw it as and when needed to buy tokens in the future. Over time, this will leave you better off than buying all the tokens up front — all because of the time value of money.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This very simple idea — the time value of money — underlies common finance concepts such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/n/npv.asp&quot;>;net present value&lt;/a>; (NPV) or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dcf.asp&quot;>;discounted cash flow&lt;/a>; (DCF). Yet even people adept at building complex spreadsheets to precisely compute NPV and DCF figures (eg, for project financing or asset valuation models) often get stumped by the subway token question. They know how to plug discount rates into formulas, but they don&#39;t instinctively know to apply it in everyday situations. And this is particularly true for those who have come into the professional world after 2008, during the ZIRP era.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I don&#39;t blame them. It&#39;s hard to form a practical intuition about the time value of money when things like bank accounts paying meaningful interest haven&#39;t been part of one&#39;s lived experience. Indeed, if and when interest rates are zero, there is no time value of money. In such a world, arguably, buying all the tokens you can makes sense — and by analogy, so does funding all the projects, acquiring all the startups, hiring all the candidates, purchasing all the real-estate, and so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But interest rates are no longer zero. And, to once again borrow the &lt;a href=&quot;https://buffett.cnbc.com/video/1994/04/25/when-interest-rates-matter--and-when-they-dont.html&quot;>;words&lt;/a>; of Warren Buffett: “The value of every business … the value of any economic asset is 100% sensitive to interest rates.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With this in mind, any strategic or financial decision involving multi-year cash flows must be re-examined under new, realistic assumptions for the cost of capital. Since the cost of capital has now gone up considerably compared to what it has been for a long while, updated math will likely show that immediate moves to improve profitability, cash flow, and capital efficiency will &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/capital-is-expensive-again-now-what&quot;>;add more value&lt;/a>; than investments targeted towards producing growth years down the line.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fixing the math above is a necessary start. It may be just as important to also fix institutionalized managerial mindsets developed over the past 15 years. In particular, thanks to the impetus provided by near zero interest rates, &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/allocating-capital-when-interest-rates-are-high&quot;>;“moonshot” thinking has been all the rage&lt;/a>; over this period. But a return to more old school, &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/allocating-capital-when-interest-rates-are-high&quot;>;value-oriented thinking&lt;/a>; is likely needed to succeed in tackling the challenges that lie ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The ZIRP years are over. And as the gravity of interest rates returns, those who have become accustomed to effortless flying must now quickly adapt to life on the ground.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Remedy for the Supplier Onboarding Problem]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/a-remedy-for-the-supplier-onboarding-problem]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_05_1192882537.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Maskot/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Onboarding new suppliers has long been a time-consuming and expensive process. But a new blockchain-based platform that is open to everyone can streamline this crucial activity. The early results are promising.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/a-remedy-for-the-supplier-onboarding-problem?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/a-remedy-for-the-supplier-onboarding-problem?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Supplier onboarding — the process of collecting the information and data required to set up an organization as an approved supplier — is essential to do, but no one likes to do it. It is not uncommon for it to take a month to onboard a new supplier and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ismworld.org/supply-management-news-and-reports/news-publications/inside-supply-management-magazine/blog/2021/2021-03/the-monthly-metric-time-to-on-board-a-new-supplier/&quot;>;can take up to six months&lt;/a>; at many large organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whether 30 days or six months, the pain and delay stem from manual processes that buying organizations use to vet supplier data and documentation such as ISO certifications, bank account information, tax documents, and certificates of insurance. While frustrating, the work is foundational to ensuring new suppliers comply with relevant laws, regulations, and corporate standards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Several digital solutions such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hicx.com/&quot;>;HICX&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.suppliergateway.com/buyers/supplier-risk-management/?utm_term=vendor%20onboarding&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Supplier+Onboarding-+Search&amp;amp;utm_source=adwords&amp;amp;utm_medium=ppc&amp;amp;hsa_acc=7955359281&amp;amp;hsa_cam=19906339380&amp;amp;hsa_grp=148406702315&amp;amp;hsa_ad=653033066318&amp;amp;hsa_src=g&amp;amp;hsa_tgt=kwd-299767053962&amp;amp;hsa_kw=vendor%20onboarding&amp;amp;hsa_mt=b&amp;amp;hsa_net=adwords&amp;amp;hsa_ver=3&amp;amp;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIjfby3Je1gQMVJiCtBh2Kmw6iEAAYAyAAEgJ3zPD_BwE&quot;>;Supplier Gateway&lt;/a>; have emerged to help buying organizations solve the supplier onboarding problem. However, while they automate and make the supplier onboarding experience easier, suppliers still have to go through an onboarding process with each customer. For suppliers with hundreds (or even thousands) of customers, the digital process is better but still far from ideal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;ve examined a potentially better solution: A more holistic supply chain platform approach that helps streamline work across a supply chain ecosystem of trading partners. It&#39;s called &lt;a href=&quot;https://chainyard.com/solutions/trust-your-supplier/&quot;>;Trust Your Supplier&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Promising Remedy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The concept of supply chain platforms is not new. One example is Chinese appliance manufacturer &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-to-turn-a-supply-chain-platform-into-an-innovation-engine&quot;>;Haier&#39;s COSMOPlat&lt;/a>; (which stands for Cloud of Smart Manufacturing Operation Platform). It has been used to increase collaboration and streamline operations ranging from innovation and design to supplying materials and components to solving technical problems and providing new services. While Haier could have just developed the solution to meet the needs of working with its own suppliers, it chose to take a platform approach and open the solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;Other examples are systems developed by Walmart to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/how-walmart-automated-supplier-negotiations&quot;>;automate negotiations with smaller suppliers&lt;/a>; and to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/how-walmart-canada-uses-blockchain-to-solve-supply-chain-challenges&quot;>;manage invoices from and payments to third-party freight carriers&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As part of our research at the University of Tennessee on highly collaborative business partnerships, we had the opportunity to study a creative strategic alliance between IBM and &lt;a href=&quot;https://chainyard.com/&quot;>;Chainyard&lt;/a>;, a digital transformation company that focuses on blockchain solutions. The strategic partnership caught our eye because the parties were teaming up to develop an industry- and company-agnostic platform solution to address supplier onboarding, compliance, and risk-management issues plaguing virtually all companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The result of the partnership: A &lt;a href=&quot;https://image-ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/11488271&quot;>;patent&lt;/a>; jointly held by both Chainyard and IBM and the formal launch of Trust Your Supplier (TYS), a blockchain network solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An essential part of the vision was to create a true blockchain network that would allow a worldwide network of buyers and suppliers — not just IBM and its suppliers — to share trusted, standardized data. Today the TYS blockchain network includes 11 large purchasers (eg, American Express, BT, Lenovo, Nokia, Pearson, and Thermo Fisher) and over 100,000 fully vetted suppliers. In addition, more than 400 million other suppliers have some or a significant part of their data available on TYS through partnerships with third-party compliance organizations on the platform such as Moody&#39;s.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The TYS platform enables buyers and their suppliers to opt into the network. Suppliers create a single digital identity (ie, a “corporate wallet” or “digital passport”) to share with their customers that they can use over and over again without having to enter the data every time for a new customer or when an existing client is doing compliance checks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The TYS platform is showing significant promise for both purchasers and suppliers:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Purchasers&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;By eliminating redundant efforts and streamlining the process, some of the early-adopter purchasing organizations that have used TYS have reported cost savings of nearly $500 per supplier. For an enterprise with tens of thousands of suppliers, this can result in savings of eight figures in the overall management of their supplier base.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Suppliers&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;TYS has reduced the average supplier onboarding time to under a business week, an impressive average reduction of 67%. Once on the network, suppliers can be onboarded with additional companies almost instantly. Quicker supplier onboarding means not having to wait to start work after a deal is sold. And because suppliers manage and control their data only on the network, it eliminates the administrative burden of having to manage the same or similar data across multiple customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A New Era&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We believe a paradigm shift is occurring. Organizations will increasingly adopt platform solutions like COSMOPlat and TYS that will solve systemic supply chain issues for a vast number of players. Supply chain management will be transformed.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are We Seeing a Revival of Union Power?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/are-we-seeing-a-revival-of-union-power]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_05_1713785580.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Mario Tama/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;After decades of decline, American unions are once again challenging employers and using strikes to fight for better contracts. For the first time in recent memory, unions are taking strong, militant stances &amp;#8212; and seem to be making major gains as a result. But how should this moment be understood, and what does it signal about the future of organized labor in the United States? In an interview with HBR, former National Labor Relations Board member Sharon Block explains the significance of new leadership, the legal landscape, and what lessons companies should take from what&amp;#8217;s happening right now.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/are-we-seeing-a-revival-of-union-power?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/are-we-seeing-a-revival-of-union-power?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Over the past few months, the United States has seemingly entered a new era for American unions. After decades of decline, major American unions — including the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/22/business/economy/ups-contract-vote-teamsters.html&quot;>;Teamsters&lt;/a>;, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/article/uaw-strike-explained-ford-stellantis-gm.html&quot;>;United Automobile Workers&lt;/a>;, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2023-05-01/writers-strike-what-to-know-wga-guild-hollywood-productions&quot;>;Writers Guild of America&lt;/a>;, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/article/actors-strike-why.html&quot;>;Screen Actors Guild&lt;/a>; — have taken militant stances in contract negotiations. Thus far, two have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thenation.com/article/society/teamsters-uaw-strike-votes/&quot;>;chalked up&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/business/media/hollywoods-writers-emerge-from-strike-as-winnersfor-now-b6b002d3&quot;>;considerable victories&lt;/a>;. This week, workers at Kaiser Permanente walked off the job in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/health/healthcare/healthcare-worker-strike-kaiser-permanente-b404e9d5?st=tllvmqmhktor0jj&amp;amp;reflink=article_copyURL_share&quot;>;largest strike of health care workers in US history&lt;/a>;. All at once, it seems union power is on the rise again.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Where did this come from, and what does it mean? To answer this, HBR spoke with Sharon Block, a former member of the National Labor Relations Board, who is currently a Professor of Practice and Executive Director of the Center for Labor and a Just Economy at Harvard Law School. The following interview was conducted via Google docs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HBR: Right now, we&#39;re seeing a level of union action that feels unprecedented in recent memory: the Teamsters leveraged a very credible strike threat to win a new contract for UPS workers, Hollywood writers and actors have spent months on strike, and the United Auto Workers are striking against the Big Three automakers. Quickly, how did we get to this point?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Block: I think that there are a couple of trends driving this increased strike activity. First, the public&#39;s sympathies seem to be with workers. Unions are enjoying higher support among the public than they have in decades. That gives confidence to workers considering going out on strike. Also, I believe that unions are considering the leverage that the tight labor market gives them. They are highly motivated to negotiate advantageous contracts now, so they can lock in their enhanced power. Finally, many of the unions that have been engaged in these high profile labor actions are in sectors where big, transformational change is either just on the horizon or already here. For example, the Hollywood strikes have focused on what the impact of AI is going to be in their work and the UAW strike is in part about how the auto industry is going to transition to an EV future. Workers want to have a voice in how these transformations impact them – active unions give them a meaningful seat at the table as decisions are made that will define the future. That suggests to me that these strikes may go on for a while — workers may be celebrating “union victory autumn” for a while.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;When was the last time we saw organized labor flex this kind of muscle?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It has been generations since we have seen this kind of robust labor activity. I haven&#39;t seen this level of action in my career.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Why has it been so long?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The labor movement has been forced to play defense for a long time by trends in our economy, like the move from a manufacturing economy to a service economy, the increasing brazenness of employer opposition to unions and the weakness in our labor laws that often fail to protect workers engaged in collective action. The pandemic — and the huge profits that many corporations made during the pandemic — seems to have awoken a new commitment among workers — both in unions and not — to stand up to employers and demand what they believe they deserve. For workers in unions, that spirit seems to be driving increasing strike activity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;One of the really striking things about this moment is the return of big strikes. The Teamsters didn&#39;t strike, but they seemingly came very close and claimed to win a good contract. Writers and actors, of course, did strike and the writers are claiming to have secured a lot of their demands. And the UAW is using a limited strike tactic — standup strikes — that&#39;s disruptive but also gives them the option to escalate. What&#39;s behind the return of the strike, and what are the implications of seeing these big strikes happening? Or, am I overstating this shift?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I don&#39;t think you are overstating this shift. The data shows that there has been more strike activity this year than we&#39;ve seen in a while. Again, I think some of this activity is being driven by a collective response to the pandemic in which workers are saying, “enough.” Many workers, including UPS drivers and factory workers like auto workers, put their lives on the line to continue to work during the pandemic. As a result, they generated big profits for their employers. They are now demanding their fair share of that success. In addition, I believe that success is contagious. Workers are inspiring each other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;There&#39;s new leadership at both the Teamsters and the UAW, and both of them have promised more hard-knuckle tactics than their predecessors. What&#39;s the significance of this return to a more militant approach, and do you think we can expect to see more of this in the near future?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My perspective is that the new leadership at the Teamsters and the UAW are very attuned to their members — I think in this moment their members want leaders who reflect their desire to stand up for their interests and demand what they believe they deserve. We can see this dynamic even among workers who aren&#39;t in unions — they have come out of the pandemic and into a tight labor market, amidst skyrocketing CEO pay and stock buybacks, demanding higher wages. The new leadership at the Teamsters and UAW are doing what good union leaders do — translating their members&#39; mood and interests into effective strategy to succeed at the bargaining table. Because success is contagious, I do believe that we will continue to see members and their leaders demanding their fair share loudly and proudly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Earlier this year, the Biden administration passed legislation that stopped railroad workers from striking and forced a contract on them. This time, however, the president has promised to show up and walk the picket line with striking UAW workers. How do you understand the politics around organized labor right now? Is there any reason to think that the legal and political environment organized labor is working within might change?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;President Biden&#39;s decision to show up at the UAW Willow Ridge picket line was both unprecedented and unsurprising. President Biden has been saying repeatedly that he wants to be the most pro-union president in history. By visiting striking auto workers, he put his feet where his mouth has always been. In addition, it is important to remember that Biden was in the White House when the Obama-Biden Administration was part of asking the UAW to make incredible sacrifices to save the auto industry. So, it makes sense that now that he is in the White House again, he wants to stand with UAW workers as they ask to share in the companies&#39; success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, Biden&#39;s visit gives him an opportunity to further define his vision for a clean energy future. This visit shows that in his vision, workers have to have a say in how this transformation to an EV future comes about.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I wish I could be more optimistic about the prospect for a change in the legal environment for labor. Before we will see significant labor law reform pass the US Congress, we will need a shift in our political environment. If President Biden and others who are supporting these strikes are rewarded by voters for their commitment to the labor movement, maybe we will see the political change we need to improve the prospect of the kind of labor law reform we need — like the kind of reforms that my colleague Ben Sachs and I proposed in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://clje.law.harvard.edu/clean-slate/&quot;>;Clean Slate for Worker Power project&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Despite hitting record lows in membership, there&#39;s been a big uptick in support for unions in recent years. But when I think of union actions, I mostly think about union drives at places like Amazon and Starbucks. How should we understand the significance of the recent actions by the Teamsters, UAW, etc.? And do they mean anything for other union / unionization efforts?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I believe that success breeds more success. Lots of workers are worrying about the future — is AI going to eliminate their jobs or is their boss using technology to spy on them at work, is climate change going to put them in danger on the job and are their companies going to prioritize stock buybacks over wage increases, leaving them unable to keep up with inflation. With the successful outcomes in so many of these strikes, workers are going to understand in a way maybe they haven&#39;t in a long time that unions are relevant to their lives — that they are a way to have a say in the future. I think all workers want the future to happen with them, not to them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;So, as all of this unfolds, what are you watching for? What do you think the significant longer term effects of this moment might be?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, I&#39;m watching to see how the UAW strike resolves. If the companies and the union can find a way to successfully chart a path to an EV future that protects workers&#39; middle class wages, I hope that will quiet a lot of critics of this strike. I&#39;m also watching a number of campaigns at the state and local level to support innovative legislation that empowers workers. For example, here in Massachusetts SEIU is supporting legislation to create a collective bargaining system for rideshare drivers. In New York, organizations are supporting wage boards for nail salon workers. And California has created a new council, which includes representatives of workers, to set higher labor standards for fast food workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Are there lessons for companies that are watching this unfold? What should leaders be thinking about right now?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I hope that corporate leaders are rethinking the reflex to try to minimize labor costs at the expense of their relationship with their workforce. This summer&#39;s strikes are demonstrating that workers are willing and able to say “enough.” Companies can avoid a lot of public ill will and strife if they think about whether their workers are getting a fair share of the companies&#39; success before increasing CEO pay or embarking on yet another round of stock buybacks.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Fintech Is Making Smaller Suppliers More Resilient]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/how-fintech-is-making-smaller-suppliers-more-resilient]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_04_1193669057.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;tdub303/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Historically, smaller, lower-tier suppliers have had trouble obtaining financing. New fintech platforms are changing that. They are making it easier for them to use assets such as approved invoices, inventories, and purchase orders to access financing from outside investors or focal companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/how-fintech-is-making-smaller-suppliers-more-resilient?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/how-fintech-is-making-smaller-suppliers-more-resilient?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) deeper in the supply chain often find themselves with many financial challenges. They are several layers away from giant &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.myeducator.com/reader/web/1713d/chapter01/mg6i2/#:~:text=Consider%20the%20following%20as%20you,away%20from%20the%20focal%20firm.&quot;>;focal companies&lt;/a>; like Unilever, Siemens, and Dell that can provide supply chain financing. Until now, all support programs that focal companies have provided, such as reverse factoring and dynamic discounting, were only available to their first-tier suppliers.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Enter the next-generation financial technology companies such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://provenance.io/&quot;>;Provenance&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sumup.com/en-us/&quot;>;SumUp&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zeconomy.com/solutions&quot;>;Zeconomy&lt;/a>;. (One of us, Sam, is the founder and CEO of Zeconomy.) These “fintechs” have created game-changing platforms that help SMEs navigate these challenges and tap into previously inaccessible resources. By leveraging these platforms, SMEs can better manage their cash flows and enhance their business operations. Here&#39;s how.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. SME assets can now be digitized.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;SMEs have three core assets that can be used to obtain financing: approved invoices, inventories, and purchase orders. Of these, organizations providing financing prefer approved invoices from larger companies; they are considered low risk because they mean the work has been completed and the shipment has been sent to the buying company. However, when these invoices come from fellow SMEs, financial institutions might consider them much riskier and cast a wary eye. The same is true of purchase orders from other SMEs and SMEs&#39; inventory.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Through the fintech platforms, these SME assets can now be digitized. Once they are, they can be traded in a digital marketplace to match specific asset types to the risk and return profiles of various investors. Similar to the way people playing fantasy football choose players from various teams, investors can assemble portfolios of SME assets. Previously unbankable SME assets can be bundled into diversified investment portfolios.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Connectivity and efficiency are enhanced.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The underlying technology behind the fintech software platform is blockchain. It affords a way for SME assets to get digitally connected with large focal companies. This provides a number of benefits:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Makes it possible for the focal companies to provide financing to these SMEs&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Reduces outside investors&#39; risks in lending to SMEs based on their assets&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Makes it easier for focal companies and first-tier suppliers to provide early payments to SMEs in return for discounts on their purchases from SMEs&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Allows SMEs to obtain better financing terms&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;What is more, the blockchain technology underpinning these transactions provides an added layer of security and transparency for the financial transaction while keeping the confidential and competitive data of suppliers private.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. AI provides cash-flow predictions.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The way fintech platforms can help SMEs manage their cash flows is nothing short of revolutionary. These platforms can automatically compile transactional data and use artificial intelligence (AI) to analyze SMEs&#39; transaction histories and make accurate forecasts of SMEs&#39; future cash flows. This data-driven approach empowers SMEs to optimize their working capital and make more informed decisions, mitigating their risk of insolvency.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;Moreover, these cash flow predictions can give investors more confidence when deciding whether to provide SMEs with financing. For instance, suppose an SME supplier applied for a short-term loan. The fintech platform analyzes the loan application, sets appropriate loan limits, and suggests optimal repayment schedules — all backed by AI-generated cash flow predictions. The end result: The platforms allow SMEs to obtain better offers from more investors than has traditionally been the case.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fintech platforms offer new pathways for SME suppliers to access funds. By digitizing assets and leveraging technology, the platforms can increase SME suppliers&#39; liquidity and lower their cost of financing. And by helping strengthen SMEs, these platforms can help make the entire supply chain more resilient.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>