<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Why Hybrid Work Can Become Toxic]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_27_1425175448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;阿尔瓦雷斯/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;毒性可能是某些工作环境中的一个不幸的现实。有毒文化有五个共同特征：不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待。尽管这些属性无可否认是负面的，但我们并没有绝对的、统一接受的尺度来衡量它们。使事情变得更加复杂的是，混合环境的定义意味着员工在非常不同的环境中体验他们的工作——不同的环境。有些是面对面的，有些是远程的……这些可能会随着时间的推移而变化。因此，混合工作空间并不统一；有些人可能会经历有毒的混合环境，而另一些人则不会。作者提出了混合性可能导致有毒行为的四种机制，以及在混合环境中预防和解决有毒行为的四种策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-有毒? language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-有毒？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;工作中的毒性——无论我们在哪里或如何工作——都是由一系列因素。重要的是要认识到混合和远程工作的某些方面使毒性更有可能发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，让我们快速概述一下“有毒”的实际含义。它并不是指任何健康组织中自然（且必要）的误解、紧张和冲突。它也不是指一次性事件或偶尔出现的混蛋同事。在大多数情况下，最好将这些类型的刺激视为（工作）生活的正常部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，什么实际上被认为是有毒的？唐纳德·索尔 (Donald Sull) 和他的同事进行的一项研究确定了&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-毒-文化/&quot;>;有毒文化：不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待。最近，我与两位该领域的专家同事——哈佛商学院的艾米·埃德蒙森（Amy Edmondson）和奎斯特罗姆商学院的康斯坦斯·哈德利（Constance Hadley）——进行了一次讨论，我们一致认为，毒性也意味着相关行为是普遍存在且持续存在的。我们相信，这就是不良行为上升（或可能下降）到有毒程度的原因。毒性带有一种不可避免的感觉，这也是工作中经历如此痛苦的部分原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管这些属性无可否认是负面的，但没有绝对的、统一接受的尺度来衡量它们——所有五个都是主观的，植根于每个人的经历。让事情变得更加复杂的是，混合环境的定义意味着员工在非常不同的环境中体验他们的工作——有些是面对面的，有些是远程的——而且这些环境可能每天都在变化。因此，混合工作空间并不统一；有些人可能会经历有毒的混合环境，而另一些人则不会。这并不能减轻有毒混合环境对那些经历过这种环境的人的痛苦或损害。然而，这确实意味着某些行为可能是有毒的，即使是善意的——或者至少不是恶意的——行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当与高管谈论毒性时，我鼓励他们这样思考社会科学家，了解混合工作可能导致毒性增加的机制。这是他们应该知道的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;混合工作如何导致毒性&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我的研究和咨询经验使我思考混合性可能导致有毒行为的四种机制.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.远程办公改变动态&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;混合工作意味着，与全职办公室工作相比，更多的沟通将通过电子邮件、短信、电话或视频等技术进行。关于技术介导的沟通影响的研究的早期发现之一是，人们变得更加不拘束，表现出更少的自我监控和自我控制&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/227445694_Reducing_Social_Context_Cues_Electronic_Mail_in_Organizational_Communication&quot; >;通过技术进行交流时&lt;/a>;。换句话说，当我们通过电子方式相互交谈时，我们更有可能脱口而出可能有害的话。想一想您与同事面对面和通过电子方式进行的激烈交流 - 很可能，您更倾向于在电子邮件中插入尖刻的俏皮话，而不是面对面的交流。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这充满活力并不（必然）是成为一个令人讨厌的人。我们都有愤怒、沮丧或激情的时刻，如果处理不当，这些感觉有可能变成有毒的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，在面对面的互动中，另一边的人类这种对话对我们来说更为重要，导致我们大多数人认识到不小心的话可能会付出的代价，并闭口不谈。重点不是我们不应该说出自己的想法（如果我们觉得自己不能说出自己的想法，这对心理安全来说是不利的），而是我们应该好好选择我们的措辞。虽然远程互动带来的自我监控和自我控制的减少并不一定会导致毒性，但它们肯定会更有可能导致&lt;em>;不尊重&lt;/em>;或&lt;em>;辱骂&lt;/em>;（Sull的两种毒性）特征）评论出来。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2。混合性从根本上来说是不平衡的&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;混合性还意味着不同的人在不同的环境中工作。有些人可能在家里，而另一些人可能在办公室——这些地点有着不可否认的差异。办公室里的人有更多的机会获得资源和更高的知名度，通常会因此获得更多的信用和更快的晋升。与此同时，远程工作者常常感到被忽视和回避。尽管这些影响可能是负面的，但如果每个人在某些时候都处于同样的不利地位，那么严格来说它们并不是有毒的。问题在于，有些人（可能是远程/混合员工）&lt;em>;始终&lt;/em>;感到被排除在外——就像我最近共事的一位经理的经历一样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司政策是允许所有员工每周远程工作两天，经理允许她的团队成员选择这些日子。她很快发现她的团队实际上已经根据人们选择上班的日期的不同（但一致）模式进行了分裂。使问题更加复杂的是，团队成员的远程工作选择在很大程度上受到通勤和孩子的学校时间表的影响，这与团队中的人口差异相一致。当一些团队成员觉得自己被排除在另一组在职期间进行的讨论和会议时，问题就出现了。这种分裂导致了人际紧张和冲突，人们感到&lt;em>;被排斥&lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;不受尊重&lt;/em>;（两种毒性特征），并最终导致人员流动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.混合性会降低凝聚力和信任&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/11/a-study-of-1100-employees-found-that-remote-workers-feel-shunned-and-left-out &quot;>;研究表明&lt;/a>;缺乏密切接触会减少联系和信任，而这是健康文化的关键要素。在大流行期间，我与许多远程开始新工作的员工进行了交谈，我一直听说他们不了解同事并感到孤立。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work&quot;>;Microsoft 的研究&lt;/a>;发现远程工作会导致员工的工作规模更小、更少发达的网络。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;远程（以及扩展的混合）工作并不一定意味着组织将具有薄弱或不一致的文化。以Linux为例。它的开源软件开发从第一天起就由一个结构松散的开发人员社区进行，这些开发人员从未见过面，但对该组织的广泛研究发现，它具有强大的社会规范来管理行为。然而，很难否认群体的结构（或缺乏结构）消除或阻碍了我们传统上用来建立、传播和维持文化的许多机制。请注意，Linux &lt;em>;始于&lt;/em>;具有远程、分散的文化。尽管自疫情爆发以来许多公司已经采用远程和混合方式，但他们的文化已经建立，然后进行调整以应对危机。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;文化非常重要，因为它是组织用来避免残酷竞争的指南针&lt;/em>;，在更极端的情况下，&lt;em>;不道德&lt;/em>;行为。需要明确的是，混杂性本身并不会让人们变得更加残酷或不道德（尽管有人可能会认为人与人之间的距离感使他们不太意识到自己行为的负面影响）。然而，在每个社会体系中，我们都会发现一系列行为，而文化通常可以帮助我们控制负面行为。最重要的是，虽然人们不太可能对那些与他们感到亲近和有联系的人表现出不良行为，但远程/混合环境带来的距离使我们更有可能将一些同事视为“我们”，而不是“我们”。他们”——而且更容易对“他们”表现不佳。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4。混合性使得解决问题变得困难&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;远程和混合工作中还有一个更关键的挑战：我们与同事面对面的互动较少，而且研究表明解决争议更加困难（例如那些围绕有毒行为）几乎。想象一下尝试通过 Zoom 与某人讨论敏感话题，并担心从他们正在寻找的位置到他们回复的速度等所有事情。 &lt;em>;他们是否全神贯注于我？我确定我的诚意是通过视频传达的吗？他们的反应缓慢是因为他们不同意还是只是落后了？&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我们面对面时，我们有更多的人际工具可供使用。我们拥有更好的数据，因为我们可以更轻松地读取面部表情并看到镜头外的行为。我们还拥有更好的工具，因为面对面的互动使我们能够同步合作解决分歧。邻近效应（本质上，我们喜欢与我们有更多接触的人）意味着所有这一切都是从更密切的关系开始的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个值得一提的问题是微侵犯，有些人会出现这种情况有人认为，在偏远地区，这种情况发生的频率较低，因为我们彼此相处的时间较少。不过，我要提醒领导者和员工对混合环境中的微侵犯迹象（通常反映在&lt;em>;不包容&lt;/em>;等有毒行为中）保持警惕。虽然这些设置可能发生微侵犯的接触点较少，但它们并不能消除微侵犯发生的基础，也不能阻止微侵犯在其他渠道出现，例如 Slack、消息应用程序或视频会议。实际上，混合工作可能会掩盖问题而不解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;领导者可以做什么&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我建议领导者通过四种方式处理混合工作中的有毒行为：教育、奠定基础，进行持续对话，并快速干预。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;教育员工&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;避免混合团队中有毒行为的第一步是帮助人们了解这种行为是如何产生的。你可能会想，“他们当然知道不要无礼、辱骂或不包容”，但这不是问题所在。与您的员工坐下来讨论这些结果是如何作为混合工作安排和决策的意外后果而发生的。提醒他们，毒性与行为有关——重要的不是你的意图是什么，而是别人如何看待你的行为。一个好的起点是要求员工反思他们可能经历过的有毒混合工作行为（例如，感觉自己经常被排除在社交群体之外，或者在 Slack 上阅读他们认为辱骂或不尊重的评论）。此步骤的目标不是识别特定问题或指责，而是提高员工的自我意识，并增加寻找有毒行为或其前因的眼睛的数量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;奠定基础&lt;/ h3>; &lt;p>;正如本杰明·富兰克林的名言，​​“一盎司的预防胜过一磅的治疗。”您可以采用的最有效的工具之一是具有针对有毒行为的内置抗体的文化。尤其要注重促进同理心和心理安全。以同理心为核心的文化鼓励员工考虑自己的行为对同事的影响，从而增加员工在做出可能令他人不安的行为之前发现自己的可能性。反过来，包含心理安全的文化对于同理心无法阻止的情况至关重要。我们并不总是认识到我们行为的影响，建立心理安全感可以确保员工能够说出他们认为有毒的行为。研究为促进&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/empathy-rules&quot;>;同理心&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;心理安全&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;进行持续的对话&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;因为混合工作的体验在员工之间是不同的，并且随着时间的推移而变化（有人今天可能在办公室，周围都是同事，明天独自在家），毒性是一个不断变化的目标。管理这种活力的唯一真正有效的方法是持续的过程——而基石是重复的、持续的对话。我鼓励混合团队和组织定期进行检查，鼓励每个人提出担忧或标记不良经历。对于频率没有硬性规定，因为它取决于组织的混合环境的动态程度：变化越多、越快，这些对话应该越频繁。作为起点，目标是每月检查一次并根据需要进行调整。如果您希望人们诚实地分享，请确保心理安全基础到位，并且不要将这些对话视为肤浅的打勾练习。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;快速干预&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;即使有对问题的良好理解、积极的文化基础以及持续的讨论，混合工作仍然可能会导致员工认为有害的行为。有毒环境的一个大问题是它们往往会变得更糟：有毒行为要么自我繁殖，滋生更多毒性，要么导致心怀不满的员工脱离工作，由于需要重新分配工作量而造成新的紧张局势。要打破恶性循环，不仅要密切关注不良行为，还要做好发现不良行为的准备，帮助各方开展对话，努力达成双方都能接受的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;假设您注意到类似经理的情况，他的团队在在家办公期间分裂。在这种情况下，召开一次团队会议并分享您对这种情况可能会让人感到排斥的担忧。事实可能是，你的担忧并没有被分享——但你仍然在建立对这个问题的认同和所有权，这样如果它确实成为一个问题，以后就更容易解决。但是，如果您已经认识到某些团队成员正在出现的担忧，那么您可以通过一个论坛来讨论并集体解决该问题，以免问题进一步发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center; ”>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;毒性可能是某些工作环境中的一个不幸的现实。虽然混合工作不一定比面对面工作更容易产生毒性，但重要的是要认识到混合工作引入了一些可能产生毒性的不同机制。牢记这些可以帮助领导者在不良行为发生时（最好是在不良行为发生之前）识别、防范和消除不良行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt; div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Why Employees Accept Lower Pay at Mission-Oriented Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_AnChen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;陈安插画&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当今的公司可能会宣传他们的工作如何造福于人类福祉或“让世界变得更美好。” ;最近的研究表明，这可能会给工人带来潜在的经济损失，因为它会阻止他们就更高的工资进行谈判。在五项研究中，求职者一致表示，他们担心向这些公司要求更高的工资会被视为贪婪或不恰当。这表明他们意识到了一种常见的偏见，即动机纯粹性偏见，即管理者认为对工作的物质奖励（如薪酬）感兴趣的员工的积极性低于那些受内在奖励（如工作性质）激励的员工。事实上，研究表明，外在动机和内在动机共同作用，可以预测高绩效。求职者应该投资培养自己的谈判技巧，这样当公司使用社会影响框架时，他们就不会被甩掉。组织应该培训管理者了解动机纯度偏差。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research -why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees- Accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在一个有趣的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com /watch?v=B8C5sjjhsso&quot;>;HBO 情景喜剧《硅谷》的一集&lt;/a>;，一位笨拙的初创公司创始人接连推销他们的公司，宣称公司“让世界变得更美好”。这部讽刺喜剧凸显了公司宣传其工作如何造福人类福利的现象已变得多么普遍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种趋势——学者们称之为&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/ abs/10.1287/orsc.2017.1172?&quot;>;社会影响框架&lt;/a>; — 似乎正在上升。我们在招聘启事、公司网站和消费者广告中都看到了这一点，营利性和非营利性组织都希望雇用“充满热情”和“以使命为导向”的员工，寻求“产生影响”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;如此强调社会影响并非没有道理。其一，它可以反映组织做出积极改变的热切愿望。它还可以通过灌输更大的自我价值感和意义来&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2008-00266-008&quot;>;激励&lt;/a>;员工。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;也就是说，在我们最近在&lt;em>;组织科学&lt;/em>;上发表的&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1287/orsc.2023.1675&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;中，我们发现组织的使用社会影响框架可能会给工人带来潜在的经济损失，因为它会阻止他们就更高的工资进行谈判。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;感知到的规范违规&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们通过五项实验研究探索了这种效应。处于社会影响框架条件下的求职者一致表示，要求更高的工资可能会被招聘组织视为贪婪且不合适。因此，他们没有进行谈判。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的第一项研究中，我们从在线研究平台招募了 392 名参与者，以调查员工对不同类型的组织信息的态度。大约一半的参与者阅读了一家强调社会影响的公司，而其他人则阅读了更通用的公司描述。我们要求参与者就他们是否愿意协商为该公司提供工作机会以及原因进行开放式回答。我们发现，那些收到包含社会影响框架条件的公司描述的人进行谈判的可能性降低了 32%。这种沉默的最常见原因是参与者认为谈判会被视为自私和反规范，并使他们面临被这份工作拒绝的风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的第二项研究涉及 438 名本科生响应校园内的工作机会，他们将招募同学为教育行业的初创公司工作。学生们观看了一段介绍性视频，视频中所谓的公司创始人兼首席执行官（由训练有素的演员扮演）描述了他的招聘组织。大约一半的参与者观看了创始人强调社会影响的视频，而另一半观看了创始人描述了一个专注于高质量工作和成功的更通用组织的视频。观看视频后，参与者有机会要求更高的工资，而不是接受最初提供的工资。与我们的第一项研究一致，处于社会影响状态的学生进行谈判的可能性降低了 43%。同样，这种效应是由于人们认为表现出对高薪的兴趣会违反组织的员工激励规范而产生的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们在其他三项研究中复制了这些结果。我们发现，这种影响在工作场所模拟以及教育、医疗保健、制造和金融等一系列行业中都存在。我们还发现，社会影响框架在很大程度上影响求职者对金钱工作奖励（例如工资和奖金）的要求。这似乎并没有阻止他们要求假期和医疗保健福利等非金钱奖励。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;关于金钱和做好事的假设&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;什么解释了对金钱工作奖励的影响吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;答案在于人们普遍和长期的信念，即金钱会玷污对工作本身的热爱和行善的企图。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，经理有被证明持有“&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2017.0617&quot;>;动机纯度偏见&lt;/a>;”，他们认为员工对材料感兴趣工作奖励（外在奖励）较少受到工作本身性质（内在奖励）的激励，因此不太值得被雇用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种信念是基于错误的前提。研究表明，外在动机和内在动机&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/a0035661&quot;>;&lt;em>;共同&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;共同预测高工作绩效。此外，一种动机的增加并不意味着另一种动机的减少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，在我们的研究中，求职者似乎表现得好像他们意识到管理层对工人物质利益的偏见奖励。因此，在具有社会影响力的背景下——尤其希望员工受到更高尚的动机（例如更高的目标感）的驱动——求职者会对任何表明他们可能也关心金钱的迹象进行自我审查。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;求职者和招聘经理的要点&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;从马克思主义的角度来看，社会影响框架可能被视为另一种文化趋势，它无意中有利于资本所有者，并在工人的费用。然而，鉴于社会影响框架往往植根于组织为社会做出贡献的真正努力，并且也能让员工受益，因此建议组织停止传达其对更大利益的重视就过于简单化了。因此，我们提出了几项建议，以帮助最大限度地减少接触此类消息的工人的财务损失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从工人的角度来看，求职者可以投资&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-to -evaluate-accept-reject-or-negotiate-a-job-offer&quot;>;培养他们的谈判技巧&lt;/a>;，这样他们就可以避免在组织使用社会影响框架时轻易被抛弃。他们还可以调查那些声称关心人类福利的组织&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-tell-if-a-pottial-employer-has-a-burnout-culture&quot;>;如何对待自己的员工&lt;/a>;。如果一家强调社会影响的公司忽视了员工的福祉、财务或其他方面，那将是具有讽刺意味的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织还可以考虑对经理进行培训，让他们了解他们对员工外在动机的偏见，如上所述，可能是毫无根据的。事实上，例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2014.0898&quot;>;供养家人&lt;/a>;的愿望被发现是一种强烈的愿望工作绩效的预测因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过浪漫化内在动机并条件反射地解雇那些对外在工作奖励表现出任何兴趣的求职者，组织可能会拒绝那些同样对工作充满热情并且很可能一直很优秀的优秀候选人。高绩效者。尤其重要的是，努力采取道德方法开展业务的组织可以避免以马基雅维利式的方式部署社会影响框架，将其作为故意压低薪酬的工具。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/分区>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Companies Can &mdash; and Should &mdash; Recommit to DEI in the Wake of the SCOTUS Decision]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_28_1401985.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;露丝·布莱克/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;美国最高法院禁止在学院和大学采取平权行动，州立法将多样性、公平性和包容性努力纳入校园，以及针对 DEI 的更普遍的攻击，企业正在考虑是否需要改变其 DEI 策略。简短的回答是他们不这样做。但这是审查企业价值观、人事政策并与员工就这些问题进行互动的好时机。第一步应该是记住 DEI 的道德和商业案例。他们仍然很强大。&amp;#160;其次，您可能会重新考虑使用 DEI 标签，正如一些人建议的那样。但考虑到员工对此类举措的支持，请谨慎行事。接下来，审查招聘等人力资源实践（包括为候选人撒下更广泛的网络，因为现在大学的渠道将不再那么多样化）；入职（因为有些学生接触 DEI 的机会比其他学生少）；以及绩效评估、薪酬和晋升（以确保不存在种族偏见）。&amp;#160;最后，与肯定是两极分化的员工队伍进行仔细沟通。提出可信的研究，征求意见，努力弥合分歧。最终，您希望您的组织以符合您组织价值观的方式向前发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/ a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;美国最高法院最近禁止平权行动的决定，特别是在学院和大学中禁止具有种族意识的招生，可能不会直接影响美国的工作场所，但毫无疑问，美国企业界需要考虑这一影响——以及未来潜在的司法裁决和州立法 - 将对其 DEI 实践产生影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;至少，我们在高等教育机构中看到的学生群体构成的任何变化也会影响招聘渠道。例如，当加州大学系统于 1995 年取消平权行动时，加州大学洛杉矶分校的黑人学生比例从 7% 下降（相比之下，美国人口为 13.6%，该州为 6.5%）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;短短三年内达到 3.9%&lt;/a>; 和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epi .org/blog/the-supreme-courts-ban-on-affirmative-action-means-colleges-will-struggle-to-meet-goals-of-diversity-and-equal-opportununity/&quot;>;低于 2%到 2006 年&lt;/a>;。同样，当密歇根大学禁止平权行动时，黑人本科生入学率从 2006 年的 7% 下降（相比之下，该州人口的入学率为 13.6%）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10 /31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;2021 年达到 4%&lt;/a>;。这些案例研究表明，当大学取消平权行动时，它们会产生一个不太多样化的候选人库供雇主利用，而这种情况现在很可能在全国范围内发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;加剧了这种情况，现在还有 &lt; a href=&quot;https://www.bestcolleges.com/news/anti-dei-legislation-tracker/&quot;>;超过 30 项州或地方法案&lt;/a>;针对学校的 DEI 资助、实践和推广。例如，德克萨斯州从 2024 年 1 月 1 日起禁止所有 DEI 办公室、公共机构进行多元化培训和“意识形态宣誓和声明”，这可能意味着在校园招聘的公司需要审查其信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;然而，还有比多元化招聘更重要的事情。作为管理思想领袖和工作场所种族问题的专家学者，我们预计会产生许多额外的连锁反应。该裁决已被解读为邀请 DEI 批评者质疑此类努力的有效性、合法性和必要性。例如，右翼倡导组织消费者研究的执行董事威尔希尔德&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-多样性/&quot;>;已经公开表示&lt;/a>;表示，最高法院关于平权行动的决定“将为像我们这样的团体带来风帆，他们希望摆脱基于种族的雇佣和晋升计划美国企业界。”共和党领导的 13 个州的总检察长也发送了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tn.gov/content/dam/tn/attorneygeneral/documents/pr/2023/pr23-27-letter.pdf&quot;>;致财富 100 强公司首席执行官的一封信&lt;/a>;，警告称，根据 SCOTUS，“多元化、公平和包容”的标签现在“非法且错误”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，大学招生受以下法律管辖： 《民权法案》&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crt/fcs/TitleVI&quot;>;第六章&lt;/a>;，禁止任何计划中基于种族、肤色或国籍的歧视或接受联邦财政援助的活动。 Private employment falls under &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;Title VII&lt;/a>; and is enforced by the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), currently led by Charlotte A. Burrows, who has emphasized that the SCOTUS decision has no bearing on its work. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/statement-eeoc-chair-charlotte-burrows-supreme-court-ruling-college-affirmative-action&quot;>;a statement&lt;/a>;, she said, “It does not address employer efforts to foster diverse and inclusive workforces or to engage the talents of all qualified workers, regardless of their background. It remains lawful for employers to implement diversity, equity, inclusion, and accessibility programs that seek to ensure workers of all backgrounds are afforded equal opportunity in the workplace.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That means most corporate DEI efforts are formally safe for now. However, it&#39;s important for organizations to pay attention to the changing landscape.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Taking a Step Back &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s consider whether we still believe race should be considered when making organizational decisions. That depends in part on whether we believe racism still affects our society. If we do, it seems plausible and just to recommend interventions that consider race. If we don&#39;t (or if we are okay with racism), it would seem implausible and unjust to recommend interventions that consider race. So, we ask you, does racism still affect our society? And do we care?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the systematic oppression of Black Americans, who have long been erroneously held up as the face of affirmative action in the United States (while research shows that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-who-benefits-white-women/70371219007/&quot;>;white women&lt;/a>; are instead the biggest beneficiaries of such policies). Even after the abolishment of slavery in 1865, the United States continued to codify the oppression of Black people in legal, political, and social systems. From the post-war &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/brown-v-board-50th-anniversary/southern-black-codes.html&quot;>;Black Codes&lt;/a>; to the 1896 &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.gov/milestone-documents/plessy-v-ferguson&quot;>;Plessy v. Ferguson&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; SCOTUS decision to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/black-history-month/a-brief-history-of-jim-crow&quot;>;Jim Crow laws&lt;/a>; in the US South, white power structures denied Black people full citizenship and equal protection under the law. Counter measures, including Congressional actions such as the landmark 13th, 14th and 15th Amendments, the Supreme Court&#39;s 1954 Brown vs. Board of Education decision, and the Civil Rights Act of 1964, which finally banned racial discrimination from public places, schools and workplaces, represented progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, having been denied the ability to advance professionally and create wealth for more than a century post-slavery, Black people remain disproportionately underrepresented in professional workplaces and leadership roles. As fellow researchers Tony Mayo and Laura Morgan Roberts have &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/toward-a-racially-just-workplace&quot;>;described&lt;/a>;, they are less likely than their white peers to be hired, developed, and promoted. Other racioethnic populations — Latino, Native American, Pacific Islanders — have faced different types of discrimination and are also underrepresented in higher-earning roles and occupations, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/opub/reports/race-and-ethnicity/2020/home.htm&quot;>;data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://extramural-diversity.nih.gov/diversity-matters/underrepresented-groups&quot;>;industry groups&lt;/a>;. This suggests that racism does still affect our society. The United States is not living up to its founding ideals of allowing all citizens to pursue life, liberty, and happiness in equal measure. We should care — and keep working toward those goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A next question to ask is whether we believe diverse teams benefit organizational performance. Ample research shows that they make &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;smarter decisions&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/the-other-diversity-dividend&quot;>;better investments&lt;/a>;, are &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-investing-in-dei-helps-companies-become-more-adaptable&quot;>;more adaptable&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/how-and-where-diversity-drives-financial-performance&quot;>;drive innovation&lt;/a>; when the corporate culture in which they operate is a supportive, &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/research-to-excel-diverse-teams-need-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychologically safe&lt;/a>; one. Diverse and well-trained workforces and leadership teams are also better suited to interact with diverse employees, customers and vendors. Thus, there is still both a moral and a business case for supporting DEI efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some corporate leaders still might be wondering whether they should rethink their whole DEI strategy in light of recent attacks on affirmative action. The short answer is no. Now is not the time to reverse the commitments they made to racial equity in the aftermath of George Floyd&#39;s 2020 murder. Instead, it&#39;s time to clarify organizational values around DEI, clearly communicate them, and ensure that people management processes are aligned with them. Here, we explain how to go about this at this critical moment in US history.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Rethinking L&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;abels&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given the SCOTUS ruling, other pending state legislation, and the warning from those 13 attorneys general, some legal scholars &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;have suggested&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;that companies preemptively protect themselves by moving away from DEI labels to ones clearly protected by law. For example, instead of a chief diversity officer, you would have a Title VII compliance officer. Another option is to use words like “inclusion,” “belonging,” and “engagement” to emphasize that the goal is improving organizational culture not necessarily racial diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We urge caution on this front because DEI remains important to employees. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.bfldr.com/ZZ11QL2O/at/6bpw94vrt588vtc8gr3fgw5/C001_Benevity_TheStateofWorkplaceDEI_Final.pdf?hsCtaTracking=e0c17c58-a6ca-4e73-978b-87718706789f%7C57928514-8a0c-4227-bf1f-498f3e23c304&quot;>;a 2023 Benevity survey&lt;/a>; found that 95% of people weigh a prospective employer&#39;s DEI efforts when choosing between job offers with similar salary and benefits and that 78% would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; consider working for a company that fails to commit significant resources to DEI initiatives. Employees from historically marginalized backgrounds will almost certainly feel disregarded and devalued if their organizations shy away from DEI labels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, any good DEI strategy requires regular evaluation to ensure it is performing against goals set and having the intended impact on employees. And when faced with a big organizational change or new rules and regulations, leaders should have a system in place to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ellavatesolutions.com/the-ellavate-approach&quot;>;tune-up existing DEI&lt;/a>; strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reviewing Processes &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recruitment&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As highlighted earlier, we can expect a smaller percentage of racially marginalized individuals to be admitted to predominantly white institutions (PWI), so companies still seeking diversity in their candidate pool will need to look elsewhere to find as much of it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One solution is to increase recruiting at institutions such as historically Black colleges and universities (HBCUs), Hispanic-serving institutions (HSIs), and tribal colleges and universities (TCUs). Another is to consider non-traditional pathways such as community colleges and building partnerships with community organizations that focus on racially diverse pipelines, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://oneten.org/about/mission/&quot;>;OneTen&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend a shift to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/skills-based-hiring-is-on-the-rise&quot;>;skills-based hiring&lt;/a>;, a well-established DEI best practice that focuses on matching skills between job candidates and roles instead of focusing on only education and experience. Consider partnering with organizations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://opportunityatwork.org/stars/&quot;>;STARS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlt.org/&quot;>;MLT&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://reachingoutmba.org/&quot;>;ROMBA&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://toigofoundation.org/&quot;>;Toigo Foundation&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fortefoundation.org/site/PageServer&quot;>;Forte Foundation&lt;/a>; (full disclosure: the latter two are clients of Tina) that help identify talent employers need.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Onboarding&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many companies now include DEI education as part of their onboarding programs. But they can no longer make assumptions about employee readiness for these conversations. For example, a student educated at a public institution in Florida is now expressly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wbur.org/onpoint/2023/05/23/what-the-desantis-agenda-means-for-higher-education-in-florida&quot;>;prohibited&lt;/a>; from taking a course that “teaches identity politics, or is based on theories that systemic racism, sexism, oppression, and privilege are inherent in the institutions of the United States.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers might therefore need to implement surveys to understand how much new hires know about DEI and take greater care in explaining to new team members why those principles matter to the organization, not just how they&#39;re implemented.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Performance reviews, pay, promotions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As DEI efforts become more highly scrutinized, there is even more reason to make sure your people processes are equitable. Performance evaluations and pay and promotion decisions should be based on standard and objective data — yet a multitude of research indicates that they remain riddled with bias, especially for members of historically marginalized racioethnic groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; found that 90% of people of color but only 72% of white people received notes about their personalities in their reviews. Now is a good time to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;audit these processes&lt;/a>; so no one can argue that you are favoring people of one race over another.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Communicating Carefully &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2023/06/08/more-americans-disapprove-than-approve-of-colleges-considering-race-ethnicity-in-admissions-decisions/&quot;>;public polling&lt;/a>; is any indication employee reaction to the affirmative action ruling will depend on their race and ethnicity, political affiliation, and how they have seen affirmative action framed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Adept managers should be able to surface and address different opinions, show empathy, create employee feedback and support systems, and regularly communicate about these issues. Tools to use include one-on-one meetings (if a few employees are highly concerned); town halls (if many people are worried); emails (if many people have low-intensity interest); or simply monitoring the situation for now (if awareness remains low among most people.) &amp;nbsp;Conversations might be difficult, but it is important for teams to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/dig-bridge-collectively-act&quot;>;dig into sometimes polarizing topics, bridge divides, and agree on collective action&lt;/a>; where possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A cornerstone of successful communication is to include research from credible outlets but, in these polarized times, it can be challenging to find &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/journalism/2020/01/24/us-media-polarization-and-the-2020-election-a-nation-divided/&quot;>;sources&lt;/a>; trusted by all employees. We recommend identifying multiple ones and explaining the vetting process to employees. Organizations will also benefit from conducting surveys to learn about differing views and identifying and seeking input on informal leaders on all sides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With both facts and opinions in hand, leaders will be better equipped to communicate effective messages about their DEI plans. They might, for example, acknowledge that some employees disagree with race-conscious recruiting, or think DEI efforts should be dropped for legal or cost-saving reasons, but explain that the organization prioritizes the increased innovation that comes from having a more diverse team or simply having a workforce that represents the broader society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is important that everyone engages on this issue. While some organizations relegate DEI to HR and HR alone, this is a mistake. Messaging on — and commitment to — DEI should be understood and communicated by everyone from frontline managers to the CEO, especially now when racial tensions remain high and policies like affirmative action are being questioned.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Moving Forward&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that the media furor over &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions v Harvard University and the University of North Carolina&lt;/em>; has slightly abated, organizations have a moment to strategically reflect on how their DEI efforts may be affected. We believe corporate leaders should resist the urge or pressure to backpedal on DEI commitments. Instead, they should enhance DEI in a manner that complies with the law, aligns with their organizational values, and benefits their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Be a Purpose-Driven Leader Without Burning Out]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1298982699.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;丹尼尔·格里泽尔吉/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;仆人式领导理念 &amp;#8212;将团队的需求置于自己的需求之上为我们带来了一个更加富有同情心、以人为本的工作环境。但在当今的环境下，这会导致倦怠。相反，作者提出了一种更具影响力的哲学，称为“崇高目标领导力”。它将领导者和团队成员联系起来，共同追求对选民产生积极影响的共同目标。在仆人式领导中，传达的信息是：你的角色是服务他人，这使得你很容易专注于取悦他人，而很难拒绝。在崇高目标的领导力中，传达的信息是：你有责任发挥影响力。这需要更多的战略思考来决定你的努力应该放在哪里。作者提出了三个领域，管理者可以将目光转向崇高目标的领导力。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/how-to-be-a- Purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to -be-a- Purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out? language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当罗伯特·格林利夫 (Robert Greenleaf) 创造了短语“&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.greenleaf.org/what-is-servant-leadership/&quot;>;仆人式领导&lt;/a>;”在 1970 年一篇开创性的文章中指出，这是对传统命令与控制领导模式的急需改进。盛行了几个世纪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“仆人式领导首先是仆人。它始于人们想要服务的自然感觉。然后有意识的选择就会让人渴望成为领导者，”格林利夫写道。 “这个人与首先成为领导者的人截然不同，也许是因为需要缓解不寻常的权力驱动力或获得物质财富。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有据可查的研究告诉我们，组织和个人&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-humble-leadership-really-works&quot;>;当领导者关注团队而不是自己时，表现会更好&lt;/a>;。在个人层面上，仆人式领导&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.regent.edu/journal/emerging-leadership-journeys/impact-of-servant-leadership/&quot;>;增加&lt;/a>;追随者的信任和忠诚度，以及对领导者的满意度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，自格林利夫最初的文章发表以来的 50 年里，特别是在过去三年里，发生了很大的变化。仆人式领导背后的叙述越来越平淡，这是有充分理由的：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;严重的倦怠。&lt;/strong>;在当今的环境中，当领导者感到疲倦、过度劳累和压力时，服务可以感觉就像从空杯子里倒水一样。我们告诉经理，“你来这里是为了为你的团队服务。”我们告诉面向客户的团队，“你是来为客户服务的。”总而言之，这让人筋疲力尽。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人们更加忙碌&lt;/strong>;。当格林利夫最初引入仆人式领导时，典型的经理可能会监督一个小型职能团队。他们没有自己的可交付成果，没有参与多个跨职能计划，也没有在一天开始时回复大量隔夜电子邮件。如今，随着中层管理人员的不断精简，领导者通常会&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/how-to-identify-组织的控制权范围&quot;>;11 至 15 名直接下属&lt;/a>;以及他们自己的高风险交付成果。这些疲惫不堪的管理者常常觉得自己没有时间投入到奴役之中。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;工作场所的等级制度已经变得不那么严格了&lt;/strong>;。如今的组织结构图通常更像攀登架，而不是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/stop-offering-career-ladders-start-offering-career-portfolios&quot;>;梯子&lt;/a>;。没有正式权威的领导正在兴起，并引发了一个问题：谁是仆人，谁被服务？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;仆人式领导是进入更加人性化的工作世界的重要踏脚石。但下一个演变即将到来。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/to-retain-employees-give-them-a-sense-of- Purpose-and-community&quot;>;工作场所数据&lt;/a>;（以及我们自己的经验）告诉我们，我们正处于拐点。我们正处于这样一个时刻，正式和非正式的领导者都必须朝着更有目的的领导风格迈进，重点关注组织的工作对现实生活中的人类的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们将这种影响力驱动的理念称为“崇高目标的领导力”。当领导者和团队成员共同追求比他们自己（他们的团队、他们的客户、他们的社区）更大的事业时，他们的目标是积极影响他们的选民（而不是为他们服务）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是这是一种微妙但又明显的转变。在仆人驱动型领导中，信息的核心是：&lt;em>;你的职责是为他人服务&lt;/em>;。这使得很难拒绝，并且领导者（及其团队）很容易做出反应，试图取悦所有人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在崇高目标的领导中，核心信息是：&lt;em>;您的职责是产生影响&lt;/em>;。这需要更多的战略思考来决定你的努力方向。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你的北极星是一个共同的目标时，领导者在这件事上有更多的选择；你不觉得需要取悦所有人。在我们的咨询实践中，我们看到了第一手证据，表明崇高目标的领导力可以有效地推动绩效提升，同时保持服务文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是管理者可以在以下三个领域进行的工作：将他们的镜头转向崇高目标的领导力：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.员工互动&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;经理们经常被教导要向员工提出这样的问题：我能做些什么来帮助你取得成功？您需要我提供什么样的支持？虽然这些都是很好的问题（而且肯定会比咆哮命令得到更好的结果），但善意的领导者发现自己在这些互动中留下了一份令人筋疲力尽的行动项目清单。经过几次这样的经历后，劳累过度的管理者往往会发现，甚至不去询问团队需要什么样的帮助就变得更容易了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与其放弃提供支持的想法，管理者可以创造一种微妙的、通过调整到更高的目标，并提出以下问题来实现强大的转变：&lt;em>;您&lt;/em>;需要什么才能成功实现我们的目标？您需要获得什么帮助？&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;这种微小的语言变化重塑了情感动态。领导者不必独自负责支持员工，而是询问员工他们需要什么才能成功，从而创造一种共同的责任感。领导者有目的地将自己定位为对员工的成果产生积极影响，但他们并不承担支持员工的唯一责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是我们的客户的前后对比。一位副总裁，面对 12 名直接下属和无数的自己的交付成果，已经捉襟见肘。作为仆人式领导感到疲惫不堪且不可能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;副总裁开始询问他们的项目经理，“鉴于我们的目标是积极影响我们的客户，您需要什么样的支持才能按时做好这件事？”项目经理很快确定他们需要其他部门的资源和支持才能按时完成任务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;副总裁是否坚持传统的“你需要我做什么？”双方都会遭受损失。 The VP would have had more on their plate than they could manage, and the project managers wouldn&#39;t have engaged with the other department.着眼于共同目标（成功完成改善客户生活的项目），领导者及其团队成员都会变得更加强大和高效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.决策&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当你的主要关注点是服务时，你就会很容易把注意力集中在取悦他人上&lt;em>; - &lt;/em>;这是一种永无休止且常常徒劳的努力。无论领导者做什么，工作中的许多要素，例如紧迫的期限和具有挑战性的反馈，本质上都是令人不快的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当领导者仅通过试图提供帮助和支持的角度来制定决策时对他们的选民来说，这会导致倦怠。最坏的情况是，它滋生了权利，员工认为领导者的工作就是让他们快乐，什么也不做。这种情绪混乱的总和可能会阻止领导者做出艰难（但正确）的决定。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，领导者可以围绕目标制定决策。例如，在会议中，不要问：你对此有何看法？这对你有用吗？领导们可以问：这会产生什么影响？这将如何影响我们的员工或客户？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;凯瑟琳是一家医疗器械公司的客户成功主管，她利用这种模型将她的团队从抱怨转向采取行动。该团队的部分职能是让客户及时了解交货时间。这包括当客户的订单延迟时给他们打电话。在经历了特别令人沮丧的一天之后，她的团队向凯瑟琳提出了一个请求：他们不想再拨打这些电话。她的团队感叹“有些客户甚至没有注意到他们的订单是否被延迟了！”&lt;/em>;其他人则蜂拥而至，&lt;em>;“我们无法加快送货卡车的速度！打电话有什么意义？如果他们担心，他们就会打电话给我们。”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个仅仅想取悦团队的领导者可能会想让团队停止打电话，或者他们可能会接听电话他们自己。相反，凯瑟琳用问题来重新调整团队以实现更高的目标。她问道：“如果我们的顾客措手不及，不知道订单会延迟，会对他们产生什么影响？如果我们停止主动而只是被动，这会对我们的声誉产生怎样的影响？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种看似简单的视角转变促使团队思考他们的工作如何影响组织的总体目标。这改变了他们的思维过程：他们不再关注自己的反应，而是开始考虑对团队的影响，并将自己视为更大整体的一部分。团队决定继续拨打电话，但轮换职责，这样每个人就不必每天都拨打电话。重新调整团队以实现更高的目标，减轻领导者的压力并增加团队的支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.辅导&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;任何领导者的主要职能都是&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;辅导团队&lt;/a>;。然而，当在可交付成果的基础上添加辅导时，领导者可能很难投入时间来培养员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最近，在我们为酒店行业的一组销售经理举办的辅导计划中，参与者坦言感到不知所措。该组织拥有卓越的文化，管理者通常希望领导他们的团队做好工作。然而，随着旅游业开始蓬勃发展，他们增加了更多的销售人员，经理们发现自己捉襟见肘。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们问经理们：“你们指导谁？”他们的答案几乎是一致的：表现最差的人。然而，销售经理们感叹，尽管他们进行了大量的培训投资，但表现不佳的员工充其量也只表现出了边际进步。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，我们将视角从仆人式领导转向崇高目的领导。我们建议管理者不要问谁最需要辅导，而是问自己：我的辅导时间在哪些方面会产生最大的影响？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;管理者开始从不同的角度看待他们的团队：谁是最值得辅导的？谁学得快？谁与客户关系最密切？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;项目结束后，这些经理开始将更多时间投入到高绩效和中等绩效员工身上。他们亲自指导高绩效员工如何获得最高价值的机会。他们通过团体辅导圈和同伴角色扮演给予中层表现更多的关注。他们并没有放弃对底层的辅导，而是没有花费数小时的辅导时间，而是通过点播课程、自学等方式指导表现较差的人拥有更多的学习成果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;结果很快就出来了：高绩效者变得更好，中等绩效者也得到了改善。同样有趣的是，表现不佳的人做了以下三件事之一：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;努力成为表现中等的人&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;坚持到底，取得与他们在开始时相同的边际进步他们几乎占用了经理所有的辅导时间&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;或者，当面临在自己的发展中拥有一定自主权的挑战时，他们会自我选择退出——这个过程比经理发生得更快、更少的挫败感花费数小时的时间试图指导一名不想提高的球员。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;总体而言，团队创造了创纪录的收入，而且他们对此感到更加满足。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;仆人式领导给我们带来了一个更加富有同情心、以人为本的工作环境。现在是我们进行下一次飞跃的时候了。在当今的环境中，精疲力竭的领导者无休止地试图服务，将难以推动未来增长所需的创新、韧性和意义感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将镜头提升到崇高目标的领导力有能力团结起来员工和管理者追求有所作为。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overcoming Your Fear of Giving Tough Feedback]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1379555.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;胡安·莫亚诺/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;缺乏建设性反馈对您的团队有害，剥夺他们的指导和成长机会。沟通不畅和期望不明确的工作场所是低信任和脱离的滋生地。提供反馈对于成为有效的领导者至关重要。在本文中，作者提供了五种方法来克服您对提供反馈的恐惧。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving -tough-feedback?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“我感觉我要吐了，”Filip在我们的教练课程中向我坦白了。 “提供反馈是领导者每天应该不费吹灰之力就能做到的事情，”他说。 “但对我来说，这感觉就像世界末日。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip 是一家公司的项目管理总监为全球流媒体内容提供商提供翻译服务的公司。 Filip 工作勤奋（有时甚至会犯错），是处理多个优先事项、跨时区、语言和文化协调译员、质量控制专家和客户联络的专家。他有一种在模糊性中蓬勃发展的诀窍，专注于战略目标，而又不会迷失在细节中。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;菲利普也感到自豪他自己始终为团队提供支持，即使这需要承受愤怒的高管的压力。但当向他的直接下属提供反馈时，菲利普坚韧的外表崩溃了。他会担心自己辛辛苦苦建立起来的关系会遭到破坏。他会花好几个小时思考该说些什么&lt;/span>;——&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;有时甚至几天。一想到说出“我有一些反馈给你”这句话，他就感到恶心。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;当- 由 Filip 最聪明的团队成员之一 Angelique 牵头的 stakes 项目失败了，这让他对提供反馈的恐惧成为焦点。两周以来，菲利普一直感觉到有些不对劲。球队的士气低落和表现迟缓让他感到担忧，但他告诉自己安琪莉可最终会振作起来。他从未表达过自己的担忧，而代价是毁灭性的。他们最大的客户现在将转向另一个可以提供更好服务的提供商。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“我本可以阻止这种情况。我应该说出来的。”菲利普告诉我的。他的故事呼应了我从许多高管教练客户那里听到的一个挣扎：我如何克服对提供反馈的恐惧？&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您是否担心会造成紧张、消极情绪厌恶冲突是一种常见特征，管理者也不能幸免。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400; “避免冲突并不能帮任何人忙。当问题得不到解决或被掩盖时，每个人都会受苦，包括你。缺乏建设性的反馈也不利于您的团队，剥夺他们的指导和成长机会。沟通不畅和期望不明确的工作场所是低信任度和脱离感的滋生地。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;以下是如何应对不适感和疏离感的方法。困难对话带来的忧虑，因此您可以说出需要说的话。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;挑战二元思维。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;许多避免对抗的领导者都持有诸如“没有人喜欢事无巨细”或“提出这个问题会破坏我们的工作关系”之类的假设。虽然这些信念可能源于过去被拒绝和失败的经历，但它们反映了不准确的二元思维。事实上，既不会破坏人际关系，也不会赢得“难管的经理”的名声，既自信又直接，这是可能的。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; >;相反，应该关注通过畅所欲言可以获得什么以及清晰沟通的潜在回报。说出您的想法不仅可以帮助您感到更加自信，而且：&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您的输入可能正是推动完成一项具有挑战性的任务所需要的&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-重量：400；” aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您对同事的破坏性行为做出的坦诚评论可能会带来更加和平、高效的工作环境。&lt;/span>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/ li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您的建设性批评可以帮助团队成员在自己的角色中发展和成长，开辟新的职业机会&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt; /ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;当你仔细观察时，你会发现表达你的想法、感受和意见远比把它们埋藏起来并承受后果要有益得多.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;将反馈视为一种工具。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;尽管您也许您会相信，您的团队渴望有意义、坦诚的反馈。而 72% 的员工&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbswk.hbs.edu/item/why-people-crave-feedback-and-why-were-afraid-to-give-it&quot;>;&lt; span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;评价&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“提供关键反馈的经理”对他们的职业发展很重要，只有 5 % 相信管理者会提供此类反馈。同样，当团队成员认为他们的老板不擅长提供诚实的反馈时，他们的敬业度得分&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/overcoming-feedback-phobia-take-the-first-step&quot;>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;通常&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;会急剧下降。但另一方面，在提供诚实反馈方面排名前 10% 的领导者所创建的团队在参与度方面排名前 23%。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;剥夺您的团队成长所需的信息是不公平的。当你将冲突重新定义为领导力中健康、规范的一部分时，你在与他人讨论困难话题时可能会感到的预期焦虑就会减轻。下次你必须提供反馈时，深呼吸并记住，你不是在制造冲突，而是在引导你的员工走向成长。你不是在批评；而是在批评。你在养育。你当然不是一个恶棍；您正在成为他们需要的领导者。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;预测可能发生的情况。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;对未知事物的恐惧或想知道接受者会如何反应可能会阻碍许多领导者发声。如果你的直接下属变得具有防御性并猛烈攻击你怎么办？如果他们开始哭泣怎么办？&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您可以使用最坏情况/最好情况/最有可能来平息焦虑并处理不确定性工具。考虑可能发生的最坏情况。例如，如果你的员工哭了，你会如何处理？也许你会抽出时间。然后考虑可能发生的最好情况，以培养更多的乐观情绪。最后，考虑最有可能发生的情况，通常介于两个极端之间。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;强势开始。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span 风格=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;你还可以通过规划你的开场白来缓解你的思绪旋风。从一开始就掌控一切可以增强信心，并让你在谈话中树立尊重的基调。一旦菲利普意识到他需要与安吉丽克正面解决这个问题，他走近她说：“我很欣赏你的奉献精神和创造力。我想谈论的是一种士气低落的模式，我想了解是否有任何障碍我们可以共同解决。”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;尽可能使用“我”的陈述有助于确保您直接沟通，而不会仅仅因为害怕而犹豫不决或最小化您的担忧。具体也很重要。与其说“你又搞砸了”，不如说“我担心今天的客户会议没有及时拿到文件。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b >;让反馈成为流程的一部分。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;反馈应该是一种定期的仪式，而不是偶尔的爆发。让反馈成为一种习惯，可以确保你内心的微小烦恼和挫败感不会演变成重大冲突。另外，逐渐让自己暴露在可怕的情况下是克服它们的最好方法。作为您角色的一部分，您越多练习在低风险的日常场景中提供反馈，您就会变得越擅长。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;系统化反馈的一个好方法是定期&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones&quot;>;一-与您的团队合作&lt;/a>;。您还可以安排项目汇报，以便团队成员进行反思，或者安排事前剖析，以便人们可以提前讨论任何风险、潜在问题，并详细说明他们将如何相互合作。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;创建积极的反馈文化将使您有机会展示新发现的自信技能，同时加强与团队的融洽和信任。作为领导者，这是您可以期待的最好的事情之一。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div >;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt; a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways Our Brains Undermine Our Ability to Be a Good Leader]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_1464364780.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Orla/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To be successful, researchers at the Neuroleadership Institute have found we must excel across three core domains of great leadership: being future-focused, being good with people, and being able to drive results. And yet, as we develop as leaders, our brains evolve in ways that challenge our ability to excel in these areas. The team analyzed dozens of leadership development programs used by larger organizations and discovered they often fail to equip leaders across all three domains. The good news is that we can be taught to combat these tendencies once we understand why our brains fight us.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Robin, a perennial high achiever, has just been promoted to her first leadership position. But her first few months on the job have been tougher than expected: Her colleagues don&#39;t joke around with her anymore, she&#39;s pulled in different directions, and she&#39;s constantly putting out fires. When one of her top performers suddenly leaves for another opportunity, Robin realizes her team is under-resourced. The pressure takes its toll, and Robin begins to dread Monday mornings. Maybe she just wasn&#39;t cut out to be a leader?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Robin&#39;s story is a familiar one. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90452760/first-time-leaders-need-to-stick-to-these-4-truths-to-succeed&quot;>;Sixty percent&lt;/a>; of new managers fail within the first 24 months. And this isn&#39;t just an issue for new managers: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2020/03/13/why-most-new-executives-fail-and-four-things-companies-can-do-about-it/?sh=6abf27d76730&quot;>;50% to 70%&lt;/a>; of new executives fail in the first 18 months, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be successful, our research at the Neuroleadership Institute has found we must excel across three core domains of great leadership: being future-focused, being good with people, and being able to drive results. And yet, as we develop as leaders, our brains evolve in ways that challenge our ability to excel in these areas. We analyzed dozens of leadership development programs used by larger organizations and discovered they often fail to equip leaders across all three domains. The good news is that we can be taught to combat these tendencies once we understand why our brains fight us.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Focus on the Future &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rather than just doing the work of today, leaders must constantly scan for what&#39;s next and make sure their teams are prepared. This is at odds with how our brains evolved to value the immediate and short-term future. Indeed, in one study, &lt;a href=&quot;https://legacy.iftf.org/americanfuturegap/&quot;>;27%&lt;/a>; of Americans say they rarely or never think about what might happen five years into the future. That&#39;s a concern because anticipating things like industry trends, future skills requirements, and customer needs is central to a leader&#39;s success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to management consultant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/10938&quot;>;Elliott Jaques&lt;/a>;, the higher you go in an organization, the further out you need to think. While a line manager might have to maintain a plan for a quarter, a CEO needs to think about where the business will be in 10 years. Jacques called this concept “time span.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenge, of course, is that thinking about the future is difficult in the best of times. The more people have to think about, the harder it is to notice the quiet signals that can provide insights about possible futures. Our brains also have to battle &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/00345&quot;>;distance bias&lt;/a>;, which causes us to prioritize ideas and decisions closer in time over things further in the future. What&#39;s more, only 16% of the executive leadership programs we studied have outcomes dedicated to thinking about the future, and the numbers are even lower for mid-level and first-time leader programs, at 4% and 6%, respectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, research suggests the habit of thinking about and predicting the future is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;learnable &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;skill&lt;/a>;, and it&#39;s one of many cognitive skills leaders can and should learn as part of leadership training. One way to get started is to block off time each month and map out a “future state” for where you&#39;d like your team to be in three to six months. Using that vision, then work backwards to determine what you&#39;d need to do to get your team to that destination in the next six months.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Your People Are Everything&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders are jugglers — and the things they juggle are often at odds. Take, for example, leaders&#39; overall responsibility: To deliver a business strategy that creates successful outcomes. And yet, they must also be good at connecting with and motivating their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These two tasks are often at odds because people often get promoted to leadership positions &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/transform-your-technical-expertise-into-leadership&quot;>;because of technical competence&lt;/a>;, not personability. Social neuroscientist Matthew Lieberman &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/should-leaders-focus-on-results-or-on-people&quot;>;points out&lt;/a>; that a leader who is both technically competent and highly personable is somewhat of a unicorn. He references one study in which a leader who was seen as focusing on results — which combines strong analytical skills with an intense motivation to move forward and solve problems — only had a 14% chance of being seen as a great leader. If a leader was strong only with social skills — attributes like communication and empathy — they were seen as a great leader even less, only 12%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, for leaders who were strong in both results &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; social skills, the likelihood of being seen as a great leader skyrocketed to 72%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So how many of these unicorns are out there? One of us (David), along with Tricia Naddaff, CEO of Management Research Group, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/your-brain-at-work/201310/find-out-how-many-leaders-are-both-goal-and-people-focused&quot;>;analyzed&lt;/a>; data from thousands of employees in which people rated their bosses on goal focus and people focus. Less than 1% of leaders were rated high on both.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It turns out there&#39;s a neurological reason for this. &lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;Neuroimaging studies&lt;/a>; have shown a seesaw effect exists for the separate brain centers responsible for goal focus and people focus: When one dials up, the other dials down. What&#39;s more, &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0146167207301011&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows that as an individual&#39;s power increases, the brain&#39;s goal-focus network becomes dominant. This process is adaptive because to make effective decisions as a leader, one must often detach from the needs of every individual and view them more as chess pieces than human beings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Getting the right balance between goal and people focus is the key. But according to our research, only 58% of executive leadership programs focus on people outcomes, with 64% and 51% for mid-level and first-time leaders, respectively. Knowing this, leaders can cultivate the right balance by being more intentional about sending the signals to employees that they&#39;re cared for.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Drive Realistic Results &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One of the biggest conundrums of leadership is the way our brains perceive power. As &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ejsp.324&quot;>;individuals perceive themselves&lt;/a>; to be more powerful, they tend to become more optimistic. This often leads to unrealistic targets and inflated expectations, which can cause a disconnect between leaders and their direct reports who are doing the heavy lifting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The result is that leaders become more “&lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;vision-focused&lt;/a>;” and less concerned with detail. Having a sense of power triggers our brain positively and makes us feel good in the same way winning money or getting a reward does. As soon as the brain is triggered this way, it seeks to activate more of those rewards by directing our behavior to power-rewarding activities, like thinking big picture or pursuing goals rather than focusing on details.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news is that by understanding the brain&#39;s tendency to become less detail-oriented and more visionary, you can counteract the urges by seeking other perspectives to stay realistic about the present and set more &lt;a href=&quot;https://neuroleadership.com/your-brain-at-work/putting-people-first&quot;>;people-focused goals&lt;/a>; that are tied to the welfare of others. For example, if you&#39;re embarking on a new project and think it should take three weeks to complete, ask for the perspectives of others who will execute the day-to-day tasks to ensure alignment on how much time it takes to deliver a quality product – and then be open to shifting your timeline, if possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Luckily for Robin, her company invested in a well-designed leadership program that balances all three challenging capabilities. Over the next six months, she gained insights that allowed her to better understand what makes her team tick while learning how to think ahead and balance various aspects of leadership with the tactical demands of the everyday.尽管大脑可能并非天生适合领导力，但通过正确的基于科学的培训和习惯形成，各级领导者都可以度过艰难的星期一，甚至更久。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https ://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Skills Provide a Development Path for Sub-Saharan Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_996888296.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;wilpunt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa is urbanizing with massive rural-urban migration. But unlike the urbanization of the Western world, Sub-Saharan Africa is missing a critical component: industrialized urban cities. Because of this, these urban areas have become overcrowded with substandard housing and severely inadequate infrastructure to cope with unplanned population growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, a new development playbook to solve this problem is already evolving, and it is anchored on the young people equipped with advanced digital skills in Sub-Saharan Africa. These young workers are digitally savvy, creative, and can lead a massive transformation &amp;#8212; if they&amp;#8217;re equipped and supported to unlock their potential. They can export digital skills to Western Europe, United States, and Asia through the unbounded and unconstrained opportunities the internet has provided through &amp;#8220;digital jobs&amp;#8221; from music to software development to prompt engineering. But to scale this and make it a success, changes must be taken into consideration at both the policy level and in implementation in the areas of quality digital education, tax treaties and harmonization, and outsourcing-focused startups.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa is urbanizing with massive rural-urban migration. But unlike the urbanization of the Western world decades and centuries ago, Sub-Saharan Africa is missing a critical component: industrialized urban cities. In other words, unlike in the Western world where industrialization preceded urbanization, Sub-Saharan Africa&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/documents/africas-urbanisation-dynamics-2022-economic-power-africas-cities&quot;>;urban cities&lt;/a>; are growing with marginal manufacturing output and industrial capacities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The implication is huge, as these urban areas have become overcrowded with substandard housing and severely inadequate infrastructure to cope with unplanned population growth. With limited taxes, urbanizing Sub-Saharan African cities are underfunded and could face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unicef.org/wca/press-releases/unicef-who%E2%80%AFcall-end-historic-underfunding-mental-health-services-africa&quot;>;severe challenges on healthcare delivery&lt;/a>; and overall social welfare. And with climate change affecting major cities like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/pidgin/articles/c97je2gzdlwo&quot;>;Lagos&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.africanews.com/2023/05/07/kenya-residents-on-a-mission-to-reduce-flooding-damage/&quot;>;Nairobi&lt;/a>;, the continent needs urgent solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to Statista, on average, the Sub-Saharan African urbanization rate stood at approximately &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/805657/urbanization-in-sub-saharan-africa/&quot;>;41.83%&lt;/a>; in 2021, even when the continent accounts for just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2016/11/23/figures-of-the-week-africa-industrialization-day/#:~:text=The%20average%20share%20of%20manufacturing,at%20just%20under%202%20percent.&quot;>;2% of the global manufacturing output&lt;/a>;. The implication is that those moving to the urban areas in search of economic opportunity aren&#39;t finding it, and that has resulted in high unemployment rates, especially among young people. The Brookings Institution estimates the youth unemployment rate in Africa to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2021/12/08/the-case-for-job-creation-hubs-to-reduce-youth-unemployment-in-africa/&quot;>;about 60%&lt;/a>;, while the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) puts the &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/press-material/facts-and-figures-7&quot;>;poverty rate at above 50%&lt;/a>; in most of the countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenges posed by this rapid “urbanization before industrialization” have been exacerbated by many factors, including an industrialization policy which has looked more backward than forward. For years, Sub-Saharan African leaders have been architecting a strategy to mimic what worked for China, which relies on an expectation that the Western world would outsource low-level factory jobs to Sub-Saharan Africa to stimulate a dynamic manufacturing sector once wages become relatively more expensive in China.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But, &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/09/why-africas-industrialization-wont-look-like-chinas&quot;>;as I&#39;ve noted before&lt;/a>;, it would be a huge mistake if Africa tries to pursue China&#39;s strategy. What worked for China is already expiring with advances in AI and robotics, making it nearly impossible for Western Europe and the United States to ship some of these low-level jobs outside their shores; robots will do the jobs at home. Instead, Sub-Saharan African policymakers must develop a new developmental playbook that takes into account the realities of the present state of the area.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, that new development playbook is already evolving, and it is anchored on the teeming young people in Sub-Saharan Africa. Over the last few years, in the process of running Tekedia Capital, an early-stage venture fund, and Tekedia Institute, a business school with thousands of students, I have collected enormous data on sectors, core economic indicators, freelancing, offshore jobs, and other factors. Based on the datasets, the path I see for the development of the continent goes through young people equipped with advanced digital skills. The young people in sub-Saharan Africa are digitally savvy, creative, and can lead a massive transformation if they&#39;re equipped and supported to unlock their potential, not just regionally but globally. These young people can export digital skills to Western Europe, United States, and Asia through the unbounded and unconstrained opportunities the internet has provided. In other words, while the West outsourced factory jobs to China, soon, they will outsource “&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/the-most-and-least-digital-jobs-and-how-well-they-pay&quot;>;digital jobs&lt;/a>;” in multifaceted ways to Sub-Saharan Africa. These digital jobs are diverse, from music to software development to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/the-hottest-job-in-tech-right-now-is-in-prompt-engineering/&quot;>;prompt engineering&lt;/a>;. For nations like Japan and South Korea where birth rates have remained low, Sub-Saharan Africa provides a readily available talent base, to remotely support their economies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some enabling infrastructures are in existence as the Sub-Saharan African region is experiencing deeper broadband penetration. Alongside a growing terrestrial broadband expansion, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/elon-musks-spacex-starlink-arrives-nigeria-meets-ncc-for-permit/&quot;>;arrival&lt;/a>; of SpaceX Starlink satellite broadband brings many promises on connectivity in both urban and rural areas. And with renewal energy startups, which use solar to provide energy services, young techies are overcoming infrastructure challenges, making it easier for them to participate in the global digital economy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These shifts allow young Sub-Saharan workers to earn income where they are, and once that income is imported, they have the capacities to contribute and transform their local economies at scale. Indeed, some digital experts, after they have made money working for international organizations, decide to start their own companies and, in the process, nurture other young talent. The continent has at &lt;a href=&quot;https://guardian.ng/technology/nigeria-produces-five-of-seven-unicorns-in-africa/&quot;>;least seven unicorns&lt;/a>; — startups valued at least $1 billion — and as they become listed in the public stock exchanges, acquired by large multinational firms, or grow to have abilities to pay good dividends, the wealth created would be used to accelerate development. More so, because of the digital nature of their jobs, there is no requirement to remain in even the urban areas; Andela, a digital skill outsourcing startup, for example, hires workers from anywhere in Sub-Saharan Africa, provided they have good internet service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But to scale this and make it a success, the following must be taken into consideration at both the policy level and in implementation:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Quality digital education: &lt;/strong>;The Covid-19 pandemic demonstrated that many Sub-Saharan African countries are still very low on digital readiness. While many universities in China, the US, and Europe were able to transition to remote learning, many Sub-Saharan African universities could not. Building infrastructures to support the future knowledge economy will be essential for Sub-Saharan Africa to unlock the huge potential of the youth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Tax treaties and harmonization:&lt;/strong>; In leading Sub-Saharan African economies like Nigeria, Ghana, and Kenya, most young people work for some of the leading companies in Europe, US, and Canada. Sub-Saharan African policy makers must ensure these workers are compensated fairly, and that they pay local taxes as required by law. A clear policy that makes it easier for global companies to hire and develop these talents should be part of the region&#39;s development priorities. Also important is making sure that burdensome taxation does not dim the young workers&#39; motivations. That calls for effective implementation and harmonization of tax treaties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Outsourcing-focused startups&lt;/strong>;: Regional and national policies should be developed to deepen the capacities of outsourcing-focused digital companies. These companies, like Andela, valued at excess of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/andela-becomes-a-unicorn-raises-200-million-at-1-5-billion-valuation/&quot;>;$1.5 billion&lt;/a>;, train young people and then export their digital skills to the world, while they remain in the continent. African embassies and missions in Europe, Asia, and North America could support them to connect with major clients, providing pipelines to hire the services of African youth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa has young people to fuel the knowledge economy. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.un.org/ohrlls/news/young-people%E2%80%99s-potential-key-africa%E2%80%99s-sustainable-development&quot;>;According&lt;/a>; to the United Nations, “Africa has the youngest population in the world, with 70% of sub-Saharan Africa under the age of 30.” If the continent educates and trains them in the higher-level digital skills, Sub-Saharan Africa will develop within decades, and will experience its unique version of industrialization.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Journey to Cloud Smart: Executives Share Their Perspectives - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM VMWARE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/07/the-journey-to-cloud-smart-executives-share-their-perspectives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-0&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/hero-1024x682.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;In recent years, a growing number of organizations have turned to multiple public cloud providers to run their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some cases, the situation arises unintentionally, as separate teams prefer different platforms. Other times, it&#39;s the result of a strategic decision from organizations eager to gain the competitive and economic advantages of multiple clouds. These can include higher flexibility, lower costs, a greater capacity to monetize data, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet the journey to multi-cloud adoption can be long and painful. Along the way, many enterprises can face spikes in complexity and cost, not to mention and security concerns.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlocking the true potential of a multi-cloud approach—becoming “cloud smart”—requires being intentional and strategic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Struggle with Multi-Cloud Complexity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Multi-cloud challenges can take business leaders by surprise. Public cloud “looked really, really good on paper,” said William Brown, Cloud and Infrastructure Architect at ice Norway.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“After the initial burst of excitement, there&#39;s this phase of disillusionment—that things aren&#39;t going as well as had been expected,” said Tom Eck, SVP and Distinguished Engineer at Fiserv.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For Christoph Rode, senior vice president of Cloud Platforms at T-Systems (part of Deutsche Telekom AG), multi-cloud adoption led to challenges on several fronts. “You realize costs are spiraling even if you do cost control,” he said. “I need to control my costs. I need to control security, compliance, and I need help.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These experiences are not unique. According to a recent survey of nearly 6,000 IT leaders by Vanson Bourne commissioned by VMware, 70% say they struggle with multi-cloud challenges. Few enterprises have reached the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.vmware.com/reaching-multicloud-tipping-point&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;tipping point&lt;/a>; at which the strategic advantages of multi-cloud outweigh its complexities: 70% of companies have not yet achieved an advanced stage on their journey to multi-cloud adoption.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations experiencing these challenges are missing out on key opportunities around multi-cloud revenue, profitability, and data monetization that can deliver competitive advantages. They are also unable to enjoy multi-cloud data sovereignty and data security advantages that keep customers and employees loyal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Advantages of Being “Cloud Smart”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s a better approach to multi-cloud adoption. One in five organizations surveyed in the report could be considered “cloud smart,” or mature in their approach to multi-cloud. They are taking a planned and strategic approach to digital transformation and multi-cloud implementation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The security of your application, the accessibility of your application from various parts of the world, how you utilize these apps, to me, is really what the start of being cloud smart is,” says Joe Van Ert, system architect at Quality Bicycle Products.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These key factors are what separate cloud-smart organizations from those experiencing challenges with multi-cloud adoption:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Application innovation&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Visibility and cloud spend&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Cloud security&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Data management&amp;nbsp;culture and teams&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Regardless of where an enterprise is on the path to cloud adoption, it can adopt a cloud-smart mindset. Organizations that take this approach and draw on the right technology can reduce complexity and mitigate the challenges that come with juggling multiple clouds. Making the most of available cloud platforms allows businesses to maximize revenue and profitability, securely manage data across borders, and monetize the data at their fingertips.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Learn more about &lt;a href=&quot;http://vmware.com/multi-cloud&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;becoming a cloud-smart organization&lt;/a>;.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:55:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Questions Sales Teams Should Ask After Losing (or Winning) a Deal]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Daniel Creel&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When salespeople lose a deal, most prefer to move on rather than linger over the specifics of the loss. Similarly, when they win a deal, most are quick to celebrate. But very few take the time to assess &lt;em>;why&lt;/em>; they won the business. In the authors&amp;#8217; experience leading and coaching sales teams, they see evidence that a brief, well-pointed sales retrospective, where you unpack the reasons behind a win or a loss, can significantly improve a team&amp;#8217;s future win rate. Beyond the obvious benefits for the sales team &amp;#8212; for whom the process can help identify the best messaging and behaviors to use going forward &amp;#8212; unpacking wins and losses also provides valuable insights for product, marketing, and finance teams. Teams should ask three questions: 1) How would the customer articulate the value of their choice? 2) Who was the most influential voice in and out of the room? 3) Beyond price, what were the key deciding factors in the client&amp;#8217;s decision?&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When he read the email, “We&#39;ve decided to go in another direction,” it was like a punch to the stomach. Brent hung his head trying to absorb the loss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Brent, an account executive at a fintech company, had been so sure that this deal was going to go through that he&#39;d put it on his forecast to close the quarter. He had even mentally spent his commission. As he sat with the reality that he&#39;d lost the deal, he recognized there had been a few signs that the client wasn&#39;t fully engaged. Now, they were going to use someone else.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Brent knew he was going to have to tell his boss. But the last thing he wanted to do was spend a meeting unpacking his own failure. Maybe he could get another deal cooking before they talked and avoid what he was sure would be a painful conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When salespeople lose a deal, most prefer to move on rather than linger over the specifics of the loss. Similarly, when they win a deal, most are quick to celebrate. But very few take the time to assess &lt;em>;why&lt;/em>; they won the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our experience leading and coaching sales teams, we see evidence that a brief, well-pointed sales retrospective, where you unpack the reasons behind a win or a loss, can significantly improve a team&#39;s future win rate. Beyond the obvious benefits for the sales team — for whom the process can help identify the best messaging and behaviors to use going forward — unpacking wins and losses also provides valuable insights for product, marketing, and finance teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenge is for leaders and sellers to dig beneath the traditional competitive analysis of pricing and features, to uncover the nuanced factors that played into the customer&#39;s buying decision. While salespeople may groan at the thought of taking a magnifying glass to the rearview mirror, particularly on a loss that may still be stinging, we find that spending even as little as 10 minutes on a retrospective yields big dividends.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Below are three questions organizations and individuals can use in a sales retrospective. The questions work whether the team won or lost the deal. They are designed to help the team understand the real issues driving customers&#39; buying decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How would the customer articulate the value of their choice?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders can pose the questions to the team after a deal closes or falls through. The process starts by challenging the team to go beyond the solution itself. Instead, focus on how the customers would articulate the effects of implementing their chosen solution, be it yours or your competitor&#39;s. For example, the solution may impact other departments at the client beyond the initial user group that sales traditionally talks to, or it may help the customer accomplish additional internal priorities. Looking beyond the obvious product users helps the team understand their larger impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you lost the deal, digging deeper through this lens will help you frame your positioning to create more urgency next time. If you won the deal, this information will help you take actions to ensure a high-value implementation from the client&#39;s perspective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the fintech firm described above, the sales retrospective revealed that the customer had placed a high value on a few product features, which they deemed must-haves for their internal team. The customer believed the competitor&#39;s offering was more robust in these areas. Getting specific during the retrospective prompted the product team at Brent&#39;s company to make some minor tweaks that put them at parity. Marketing also gleaned information about how to adjust their materials to highlight the changes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unpacking a loss typically helps identify opportunities. But there are also benefits to unpacking a win. Asking the salespeople involved how the customer would articulate the value of your solution creates a shared win for the entire team. In a tight economy, playing up the wins, versus exclusively unpacking losses, reminds your sales team that customers find your solution valuable and that many are still buying.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Who was the most influential voice in and out of the room?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Oftentimes, key decision makers, influencers, and subject matter experts aren&#39;t revealed until after the deal has been decided. Knowing who these people are in a deal that you won prepares you for implementation. Knowing whose voices carried strong weight when you lost a deal helps the sales team address these influencers earlier in the sales process during future pursuits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unpacking a loss more holistically by looking at the players and the value story can help a sales team move beyond the sting of rejection. It&#39;s worth noting that an environment of shame and blame rarely produces great insight. Instead focus on what they can do differently next time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When the fintech firm looked more closely at the decision makers, it became clear that the CIO had made the final call. While most of the sales calls had been with the user group, it was the CIO who identified the must-have features that cost the team the deal. Knowing this prompted sales enablement to create additional training to help the sales team become more skilled at calling on CIOs. The marketing team developed a new deck showcasing how their offering addressed typical CIO challenges, and finance developed models to showcase their net-positive impact over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Beyond price, what were the key deciding factors in the client&#39;s decision?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When a team loses a deal, it&#39;s easy to blame it on pricing. Asking the team to think about why a client makes decisions for reasons other than price will allow them to reflect on the full value of the solution. It will also allow them to take a broader look at how their own offering stacks up in a competitive landscape. When you lose a deal, this question will help your team uplevel their skills by being more attuned to the nuances in the future. Conversely, when you win, unpacking why you won beyond pricing strengthens the team&#39;s confidence, which helps you hold margin going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It can also be helpful to ask the buyers themselves what other factors played into the decision. They may not even be aware of the subtle things that drove their thinking until they&#39;re asked to unpack it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After the loss, the fintech team went back to their client to ask why they choose the competitor, allowing the team to get more detailed information about the perceived product differences. Keeping the conversation neutral without trying to re-pitch the sale created an environment where the client was willing to share. The loss still hurt, but the deep insights they gained directly from a client helped the team adjust their offering going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While the benefits of a sales retrospective are clear, the challenge is often in assessing when to use one. Organizations can have hundreds or thousands of deals in a quarter, and not all warrant introspection. The temptation is to limit retrospectives to large deals that didn&#39;t close at the end of the quarter. However, in our experience, emotions are so high at that time that the utility of retrospectives is usually low.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, we find it helpful for sales leaders to have at least one retrospective per account executive per quarter. That enables the team to gather information that is valuable for multiple functions in the company. Perhaps most importantly, this approach will train the sales team to think about why they actually won or lost independent of a retrospective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regardless of which deals a leader selects to discuss, going from no retrospectives to a few will be a considerable achievement and deliver insights that may change the go-to-market strategy. Through running deeper sales retrospectives, the fintech firm was able to tweak their offering, upskill their sales team, and create a stronger presence with a key set of buyers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For most leaders, it will take time to drive an impact similar to what was achieved in the case study, but along the way, account executives will feel heard, sales will be more effective, and the go-to-market teams will be able to better support sales. Ultimately, this enables leaders to turn small losses into a big win.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Your Employee Isn&rsquo;t Reaching Their Full Potential]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potential]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_56660878.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jeanette Martin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;It can be frustrating to feel that your employees aren&amp;#8217;t taking the initiative to do more with their talents. As their manager, you may even wonder if it&amp;#8217;sa question of knowledge or willpower: Do they not understand what&amp;#8217;s necessary to perform at their best? Or are they just unmotivated? In this article, the authors examine three main reasons why your employee may not be reaching their full potential: personal challenges, interpersonal issues, and leadership problems. It&amp;#8217;s unpleasant to consider, but remember that at least 30% of employees&amp;#8217; performance is the product of how they&amp;#8217;re managed, meaning that your leadership could play a big role in determining whether people are reaching their potential or not. It&amp;#8217;s possible that, despite intending to support and nurture your employee, you may be squelching their talents through micromanagement, overly loose supervision, or poorly communicated objectives, among other managerial sins. The good news about this potentially alarming revelation is that it&amp;#8217;s one area that&amp;#8217;s firmly within your control.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potential?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potential?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;You&#39;ve seen flashes of real competence — maybe even occasional brilliance — in your employee. So why are they failing to live up to that potential?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a leader who cares about cultivating your employees&#39; skills, abilities, and professional growth trajectory, it can be enormously frustrating to feel that they&#39;re not taking the initiative to do more with their talents. At times, you may even wonder if it&#39;s a question of knowledge or willpower: Do they not understand what&#39;s necessary to perform at their best? Or &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/4-reasons-good-employees-lose-their-motivation&quot;>;are they just unmotivated&lt;/a>;?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Obviously, there&#39;s a reason you believe that your employees&#39; “typical performance” (what they usually do) is not as high as their “maximal performance” or capabilities (the best they can do) — so as a first step, it&#39;s important to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/08959280701333289&quot;>;clarify and quantify&lt;/a>; that.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Perhaps you&#39;re thinking of a specific example of their peak performance, such as delivering a compelling presentation under high-stakes circumstances, or particular moments when they&#39;ve demonstrated valuable skills, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1467-8721.ep10768746?journalCode=cdpa&quot;>;intelligence&lt;/a>; (recognizing an important hidden pattern, turning chaos and complexity into order, learning new things), &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691611421204?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;curiosity&lt;/a>; (asking a truly insightful question), or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2015.1030293&quot;>;creativity&lt;/a>; (delivering an unexpected insight, generating original and useful new ideas). They&#39;re obviously capable of performing at that level if they&#39;ve done it once, let alone multiple times.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s essential then, to narrow down the reasons your employee may not be reaching their full potential. We&#39;ve found three main categories to examine: personal challenges, interpersonal issues, or your own leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Personal Challenges&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One reason people fail to reach their full potential is that few people are aware of their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Talent-Delusion-Intuition-Unlocking-Potential/dp/0349412480&quot;>;actual potential&lt;/a>; in the first place. Consider that in any area of expertise, talent, or performance, there is typically less than &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2011-29559-001&quot;>;10% overlap&lt;/a>; between how good people are and how good they think they are. As a leader, you can give a powerful gift to the team members you lead and manage: seeing what they&#39;re capable of, sometimes even before they do, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Talk-Three-Powerful-Feedback/dp/1912555093&quot;>;holding up a mirror&lt;/a>;. Indeed, feedback is a critical catalyst of employee performance, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/buy/1996-02773-003&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows that two-thirds of the time, it either fails to make others better, or even makes them &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/the-feedback-fallacy&quot;>;worse&lt;/a>;!&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Make sure that you&#39;ve specifically praised the times your employee performed at their best, so they&#39;re aware of what “excellent” looks like, and engage them in conversations about what they did to succeed in those moments. Did they nail the speech because they took time to practice and prepare? Did they interview audience members beforehand so they could cite relevant examples? Helping them dig deeper into the reasons behind their success helps show them how to replicate it. In other words, think of yourself &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;as a coach&lt;/a>; rather than a boss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another major driver of people failing to reach their potential is, simply, &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2010-06019-003&quot;>;motivation&lt;/a>;. If you&#39;ve seen your employees perform at a high level in the past, then clearly ability isn&#39;t the problem here — so their current level of motivation is worth investigating. You might check in with your team member to see what&#39;s going on, especially if there&#39;s been a sudden change. Perhaps they&#39;re going through something &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/how-to-manage-an-employee-whos-having-a-personal-crisis&quot;>;challenging in their personal life&lt;/a>;, or are on the pathway to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/do-you-know-burnout-when-you-see-it&quot;>;burnout&lt;/a>; and need to take time off. Or perhaps &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-to-lose-your-best-employees&quot;>;they feel stagnant&lt;/a>; in their role and need new challenges, including stretch goals, which you can &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/02/give-your-employees-specific-goals-and-the-freedom-to-figure-out-how-to-reach-them&quot;>;help them craft&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Interpersonal Issues&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Sometimes your employees&#39; underperformance comes from the circumstances surrounding them — ie, other people. As Boris Groysberg and his colleagues &lt;a href=&quot;/2004/05/the-risky-business-of-hiring-stars&quot;>;have shown&lt;/a>;, star employees who migrate to new firms often fail to replicate their success, because the supportive ingredients that helped propel their rise (such as company-specific knowledge or networks) are no longer in place. Indeed, although organizations typically pay more for external hires than internally promoted employees, external hires typically tend to fail to add as &lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/article/why-external-hires-get-paid-more-and-perform-worse-than-internal-staff/&quot;>;much value&lt;/a>; as internal candidates, not least because many of the conditions that made them successful before may not be there anymore.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, your employee may be hitting a plateau as a result of new team dynamics (perhaps in the aftermath of a colleague departing or joining the team), altered roles or responsibilities, or a perceived lack of recognition or change in status (someone else landing a promotion or bonus). Your employee&#39;s talents may be unchanged — but their ability to execute on them has. If that&#39;s the case, you&#39;ll want to discuss the dynamics honestly and identify opportunities to reframe or mediate the conflict — or shift them to a new role where they&#39;re more likely to succeed.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Leadership Problems&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s unpleasant to consider, but remember that at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Why-Many-Incompetent-Become-Leaders/dp/1633696324&quot;>;least 30% of employees&#39; performance&lt;/a>; is the product of how they&#39;re managed, meaning that your leadership could play a big role in determining whether people are reaching their potential or not. It&#39;s possible that, despite intending to support and nurture your employee, you may be squelching their talents through &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/signs-that-youre-a-micromanager&quot;>;micromanagement&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/06/get-what-you-need-from-your-hands-off-boss&quot;>;overly loose supervision&lt;/a>;, or poorly &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/02/making-sure-your-employees-suc&quot;>;communicated objectives&lt;/a>;, among other managerial sins.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news about this potentially alarming revelation is that it&#39;s one area that&#39;s firmly within your control. By &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/a-refresher-on-ab-testing&quot;>;A/B testing&lt;/a>; strategies around how you communicate with your employee, give feedback, empower them, and manage them, you can directly examine the results of the guidance you provide and evaluate whether the main reason for their underperformance is actually . 。 .&amp;nbsp; you. It&#39;s useful to test strategies that have worked with them in the past, as well as those that have proven effective with other employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All people are unique and no strategy works for everyone. That being said, it&#39;s generally true that when you spend more time with an employee with whom you have a trusting relationship and give them more feedback (including constructive criticism, worthy praise, recognition, and resources), they&#39;ll be more likely to reach their potential than if you do the exact opposite with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, remember that people are humans, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Human-Automation-Quest-Reclaim-Unique-ebook/dp/B099KQV3ZJ&quot;>;humans are not machines&lt;/a>;. This means you shouldn&#39;t expect everybody to perform to their maximum level or full capabilities all their time. In fact, the most creative and talented people on earth — in any field — can be dramatically inconsistent in their performance, since &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2003-02410-016&quot;>;inspiration is a strong driver of results&lt;/a>; and the main fuel for innovative and exceptional work. Cutting people some slack and respecting their natural cycles, while of course &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/hold-your-team-accountable-with-compassion-not-fear&quot;>;holding them accountable&lt;/a>; as appropriate, is what good managers do. Incidentally, the inconsistency or erratic element that underpins work performance may also apply to you — so it&#39;s probably helpful to examine whether &lt;em>;you &lt;/em>;are reaching your own potential, and what could potentially be stopping you from doing so.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Understanding the gaps in your employees&#39; performance — and, perhaps, your own — is an exercise in thoughtfulness and empathy. By examining the possibilities above, you&#39;ll be in a much better position to help guide your team to be at their best more frequently.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Effectively &mdash; and Legally &mdash; Use Racial Data for DEI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_24_RacialData.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Ngadi Smart&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;After the recent US Supreme Court ruling striking against affirmative action in higher education, leaders might be concerned that their DEI initiatives and programs will face additional scrutiny and legal challenge. While reducing liability is a responsible move, the author cautions against letting these efforts lead to a fear-driven abandonment of effective DEI practices. To sustain DEI progress in this time, companies should focus on curtailing the usage of racial data that is the most legally risky, while taking decisive action to continue using racial data to eliminate discrimination, remove bias, and create fairer workplaces. The author illustrates how to curtail this risk, identifies five goals for this data use (to identify disparities, to remove universal barriers, to correct discrimination, to design fair processes, and to demonstrate DEI progress), and offers dos and don&amp;#8217;ts for companies hoping to sustain DEI progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Following the US Supreme Court ruling striking down race-conscious admissions in higher education, some corporate leaders may be concerned that beyond reducing the already low diversity of their hiring pipelines, the ruling might cause their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives and programs to face additional scrutiny and legal challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While reducing liability is a responsible move, leaders should take care to ensure their efforts to protect against legal risk don&#39;t turn into a fear-driven abandonment of effective DEI practices. The key to sustaining DEI progress and commitment through this volatile time lies in acting intentionally: curtailing your usage of racial data that is the most legally risky, while taking decisive action to continue using racial data to eliminate discrimination, remove bias, and create fairer workplaces.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Curtail Legal Risk&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To understand how to best act on this complex topic, it&#39;s important to start with the legal foundations. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ftc.gov/policy-notices/no-fear-act/protections-against-discrimination&quot;>;Title VII of the Civil Rights Act&lt;/a>;, it&#39;s illegal to consider any single candidate&#39;s or employee&#39;s race — even with the intention of creating a more diverse, equitable, or inclusive workforce — in any employment decision. Employers can&#39;t create de facto hiring quotas (eg, “50% of the employees hired in this department must be women”), or “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wilmerhale.com/en/insights/blogs/esg-epicenter/20220524-california-court-strikes-down-law-on-board-diversity&quot;>;reserve seats&lt;/a>;” for employees from certain groups, even in the interest of diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to the law, even after the recent Supreme Court ruling, gender-conscious or race-conscious hiring practices are permitted&lt;em>;,&lt;/em>; but only as part of limited, temporary, and highly structured &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cov.com/en/news-and-insights/insights/2023/07/considerations-for-employers-following-the-eeocs-response-to-the-supreme-courts-ruling-on-race-conscious-college-admissions?utm_source=pardot&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=clientalerts&amp;amp;sc_camp=2D3D522D49CB4CE599B743213715F288&quot;>;voluntary affirmative action programs&lt;/a>;, undertaken only if employers find evidence of company-wide or industry-wide hiring discrimination, only to correct the initial imbalance, and only without “undue harm” on members of non-targeted groups (meaning that employers cannot lay off white workers to hire workers of color).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So long as these guidelines are followed, neither employers nor DEI practitioners need to panic. Removing the word “diversity,” vowing to strip all mentions of race at work, or shutting down race-related affinity groups are harmful overreactions that don&#39;t reflect real legal risks. As it stands, the vast majority of workplace DEI programs are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/2023/06/29/legal-experts-supremecourt-affirmative-action/&quot;>;strongly supported by legal precedent&lt;/a>; and are unlikely to be affected by this Supreme Court ruling.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When done right, DEI programs can &lt;a href=&quot;https://ajg.com/us/news-and-insights/2021/sep/diversity-equity-and-inclusion-an-important-loss-prevention-tool/&quot;>;reduce&lt;/a>; the risk of employment discrimination and hostile work environment claims and can mitigate risk across your organization. However, employers can nevertheless reduce their risk by auditing their existing programs to ensure they don&#39;t run afoul of existing laws. Policies that instruct hiring managers to use the race of individuals as a “tiebreaker” or “plus points” for individual candidates are impermissible under the law. Setting aside concrete numbers or percentages of roles or seats for members of specific social groups is similarly risky. Avoid practices like hard rules forbidding employees not of a particular race from joining employee resource groups or instructing recruiters to fill a position with someone meeting specific demographic criteria (eg, “you must fill this role with a woman of color.”) Essentially, if a policy, process, or practice requires knowing the racial characteristics of an individual to make a decision affecting their employment, you may want to review it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Collect Racial Data to Identify Disparities&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Some leaders may read the preceding paragraph and assume that an easy way to reduce risk is to simply not collect any racial data at all. However, making this conclusion would be throwing the baby out with the bathwater, and could put your company&#39;s DEI progress at risk.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While using the racial data of individuals to influence a hiring decision would be illegal, aggregating racial data for the overall candidate pool to identify overall race-related disparities is well within reasonable grounds. Collecting demographic data in conjunction with an employee engagement survey might reveal racial gaps in meeting participation deserving a closer look. Collecting demographic data in conjunction with HR data might reveal racial gaps in turnover deserving intervention. In other words, collecting demographic data, including race, can reveal adverse impact caused by existing practices, prior discriminatory practices, or historical limitations on the labor pool, all criteria specifically listed by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constangy.com/affirmative-action-alert/increase-diversity-without-violating-the-law&quot;>;Voluntary Affirmative Action Guidelines&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only is this data-driven approach compliant with current guidelines for employers, but it is also highly effective in ensuring DEI initiatives deliver measurable impact. Socially conscious investors, employees, and customers want employers to go beyond public statements of commitment, to take specific actions that remedy real inequities in organizations, industries, and society. Collecting racial data to gain information about inequalities in your organization, your industry, or even society is one of the highest-value DEI-related actions you can take as a leader, and ensures that when you act, you will be working purposefully with a clear goal in mind.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Racial Data to Remove Universal Barriers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A common misunderstanding of DEI initiatives is the assumption that, if a racial disparity is identified, DEI initiatives rectify the disparity by giving marginalized groups preferential treatment — so-called “reverse discrimination.” For example, some managers might assume that if an analysis reveals racial hiring discrimination, DEI initiatives would seek to “give jobs to marginalized people” at the expense of white employees in return.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only would such a crude and zero-sum approach be blatantly illegal; it&#39;s also far from the reality of DEI work. Most effective DEI programs use racial data to identify discriminatory barriers that are compromising fairness and meritocracy in the workplace, and to develop initiatives that remove those barriers &lt;em>;for everyone&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, if an analysis using racial data uncovers disproportionate barriers for Black, Asian, Latine, and Indigenous manager candidates due to the lack of a standard promotions process and high barriers to entry for candidates, a DEI initiative might follow up by working with all leaders to develop a standardized promotions process, train leaders on how to use it and how to interrupt biases, and automatically consider all employees for promotion after three years in a position. These initiatives would have the added benefit of reducing manager favoritism, nepotism, and other unethical practices that might negatively impact workers from any background. Most DEI initiatives follow this pattern: They collect data on marginalized groups to design workplaces that work better for everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Racial Data to Correct Discrimination&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When employers seek out &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/how-to-identify-and-fix-pay-inequality-at-your-company&quot;>;pay equity audits&lt;/a>;, they learn whether employees of different backgrounds are being paid fairly for equal work. If the answer is no, then responsible employers may proactively offer back pay to the affected employees to rectify the inequality. The extra pay isn&#39;t “taken” from the non-affected employees like in a zero-sum game; it&#39;s given from the employer to make things right: expanding the pie, rather than fighting over it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, if an employer uses racial data to identify that white managers are receiving disproportionately more opportunities to take on challenging projects, network, and receive mentorship from senior leaders, in addition to removing universal barriers to opportunity, they might proactively create more opportunities to offer challenging projects, networking, and mentorship to members of marginalized groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the surprising benefits of using data in this way is that it can help your workforce understand the rationale behind your DEI initiatives. Because most people assume that workplaces are inherently fair or are meritocracies until proven otherwise, DEI initiatives (eg, starting an employee resource group with event programming mostly directed at Latine employees) might be met with apathy or &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/fighting-backlash-to-racial-equity-efforts/&quot;>;backlash&lt;/a>; from those anxious about preferential treatment. By grounding DEI work in data (eg, with an analysis showing a relative lack of community, support, and belonging for Latine employees compared to White employees) you can help your workforce understand the importance of DEI programs and take pride in your commitment to supporting your workforce.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Racial Data to Design Fair Processes&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You cannot use individuals&#39; racial information to give them a 30% score bump compared to other candidates. You cannot allocate 30% of positions to members of marginalized racial groups, outside of a highly-bounded voluntary affirmative action program following the guidelines discussed above.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However&lt;em>;,&lt;/em>; you may stipulate that each stage of your hiring process be composed of at least 30% qualified candidates of color before proceeding (a practice known as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.diversitylab.com/pilot-projects/mansfield-overview/&quot;>;Mansfield Rule&lt;/a>;, or the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclusocal.org/en/inclusion-targets-whats-legal&quot;>;Inclusion Rider&lt;/a>;). While these practices typically aim to correct for industry-wide discrimination or limited labor pools, no one candidate has higher or lower odds of being hired than the next candidate. The employer simply takes additional time to intentionally expand the candidate pool before proceeding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Processes like these can be combined with other bias-disrupting practices to further ensure fairness. For example, you can make it clear that any voluntarily shared racial data will not be associated with an individual&#39;s candidacy. You may even require that individuals handling racial data for candidate pool diversity work separately from those who will make employment decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Racial Data to Demonstrate DEI Progress&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Some leaders may invest in DEI initiatives and programs out of the applaudable initial justification that they are “obviously” needed to support the workforce. However, when these initiatives run their course, those leaders can feel unsure what to do next. When times are good, these DEI initiatives are seen as a marker of a successful, people-centered workplace. But when organizations are under financial pressure, face business challenges, and must juggle competing priorities, the lack of a solid justification for DEI can consign it to &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/protecting-dei-progress-when-budgets-are-tight&quot;>;the top of the list for budget cuts&lt;/a>;. Organizations that are neither able to demonstrate an evidence-based reason for DEI programs&#39; existence, nor an evidence-based assessment for DEI programs&#39; effectiveness will never be able to decouple their DEI efforts from short-lived trends and fads.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As for organizations that &lt;em>;can&lt;/em>; initiate DEI programs using data showing racial disparities or unmet needs, racial data can be the single most powerful tool in justifying their continued existence.如果您的&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/to-understand-whether-your-company-is-inclusive-map-how-your-employees-interact&quot;>;网络分析&lt;/a>;或&lt;a href=&quot;https ://www.cultureamp.com/blog/employee-belonging&quot;>;归属感调查&lt;/a>;量化了参与决策过程的种族差距，您可以使用这些调查结果作为设计新决策过程的基本原理，创建咨询委员会向领导者通报情况，并依靠员工资源小组与有色人种员工分享有关他们的意见正在被征求的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过再次运行相同的分析并比较您收到的数据，您&#39;您将能够对您的计划的成功或失败做出强有力的推论，并利用这些发现进一步改进您的 DEI 计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;要记住的原则&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;不要：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;恐慌、放弃 DEI 努力或出于毫无根据的恐惧而损害有效举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;为依赖于了解他们的种族或民族，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;向种族群体成员分配或保留一定比例的理想资源（例如，晋升、职位、任务） ，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;使用人们的种族数据在任何决定中给予他们提升或贬低，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈法律顾问。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;表达对任何角色或职位的种族偏好、标准或限制，无需事先分析显示差异，也无需先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;应该：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;使用种族数据为招聘工作提供信息并使候选人库多样化（例如，通过使用曼斯菲尔德规则）。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;汇总种族数据以保持匿名而不失去群体-级别洞察力。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;利用种族数据来识别组织中的种族不平等和差异。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;引用种族数据来设计消除障碍和纠正歧视的 DEI 工作和举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>; li>; &lt;li>;参考纵向种族数据来显示 DEI 进展、交流 DEI 计划的功效并庆祝您的胜利。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/to-drive-diversity- works-dont-tiptoe-around-your-legal-risk&quot;>;尽早与律师和法律专家合作&lt;/a>;，设计并沟通合法且有效的 DEI 计划。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p >;DEI 的工作不会消失，领导者也知道这一点：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bain.com/about/media-center/press-releases/2023/bain--company-study-shows- 85 的企业领导人将社会问题视为其公司的紧急关注点/&quot;>;根据最近的一项调查，85%&lt;/a>; 将社会问题视为“紧急”问题。员工和消费者仍然期望组织不仅承诺做得更好，而且&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/to-make-having-progress-on-dei-measure-outcomes&quot;>;实现可衡量的成果&lt;/a >; 这可以证明他们的言论并非空话。这样做需要基于证据的 DEI 工作——需要合法有效地收集和使用种族数据以及其他人口统计数据——成为这项工作的新标准。如果做得好，您将能够同时支撑您的法律风险，并加速您的组织向您的选民期望从其 DEI 计划中获得更高的透明度、问责制和有效性标准的过渡。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这只是DEI 的下一步发展是在 1964 年《民权法案》的基础上，为争取工作中更大的多样性、公平性和包容性而进行的长期斗争，并得到了数十年的广泛支持。 How your organization meets the needs of this moment will decide how well you adapt to the next stage in your DEI journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>