<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Removing the Roadblocks That First-Generation Americans Face at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_03_1369183308.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;许多第一代美国人在试图在西方工作场所取得成功时面临文化跷跷板效应。例如，亚裔美国人和太平洋岛民 (AAPI) 社区的成员可能会发现自我推销具有挑战性，因为这违背了他们的价值观。他们从很小的时候就被教导要谦虚，要保持低调，永远不要纠正权威人物，以示尊重。他们希望他们的努力能够不言而喻。但自我推销和表达意见已成为在西方工作场所蓬勃发展所需的关键要素，这显然对某些人有利，对另一些人不利。此外，第一代美国人和其他边缘化社区承受着许多代际、社会和工作场所的创伤，这些创伤造成了心理健康差异，这可能导致他们担心在工作环境中为自己辩护。虽然领导者无法控制员工如何应对社会和代际创伤，但他们有责任营造一种环境，让所有员工都能放心地举手寻求支持。为了成功实现这一目标，组织应密切关注当前员工行为是否确实促进了包容性，或者是否需要修改流程和规范以为所有员工提供公平的环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first- Generation-americans-face-at-at-work?language=es&quot; >;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first- Generation-americans-face-at-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;大约四十年前，当我的家人从印度移民到美国时，他们并没有意识到新世界会带来什么。他们充满希望，这次搬迁将提供以前无法获得的剩余机会。带着这种希望，人们对新社区的接受程度产生了合理的保留，因此他们采用了许多移民家庭采用的策略：同化和繁荣。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;目标不是压制我们的身份。相比之下，则是以一种没有负担的方式与外国人接触新环境。我的父母并没有要求升职，而是耐心地等待，直到他们的辛勤工作最终得到回报——比他们的美国同龄人晚了好几年。他们没有在日常职责中寻求支持，而是默默承担额外的责任来证明自己的价值。我的父母都以他们的利他主义、不朽的承诺和坚定不移的奉献精神作为荣誉徽章——幸福地把这些价值观传递给我，希望我能在我的职业生涯中复制他们的职业道德。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我进入了拥有我父母的高尚道德、无畏精神和正直的员工队伍将带领我完成未来的努力。不幸的是，历史以意想不到的方式重演。我因我的辛勤工作而被剥削。我的界限不断被高层领导侵犯。当我向团队寻求支持时，我感到很震惊，因为我确信这将是软弱的表现，并会损害我的职业形象，最终阻碍成长机会。它造就了我所鄙视的一个版本：缺乏安全感、犹豫不决、极其温顺。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;作为第一代美国人工作&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我的成长岁月是我一直以为我的家庭环境很独特，但事实并非如此。许多第一代美国人在很小的时候就面临着类似的挑战，因为他们要适应两种文化的社会期望，从而导致了一种独特的现象，称为“&lt;a href=&quot;https://srcd.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/” abs/10.1111/cdep.12071&quot;>;移民悖论&lt;/a>;“。由于美国的种族和民族差异，第一代美国人的发展成果、教育成就甚至心理健康挑战不断减少——这对我们的父母提出了挑战甚至新移民也不会面临，因为他们通常在青春期后移民。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了加剧这种体验，第一代美国人还面临&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2022/ 10/26/health/mental-health-children-of-immigrants-wellness/index.html&quot;>;移民内疚&lt;/a>;，因为他们试图拼命地坚持他们继承的传统，同时在他们的家庭无法提供的文化中和谐相处有关的任何指导。适应西方文化，同时感到“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-othering-5084425&quot;>;其他&lt;/a>;”可能会导致无法塑造一个完全落入的身份在两种文化、传统和经验中。虽然我们的家人可能本意是为我们提供他们的智慧和成功的价值观，但它并没有很好地转化为为那些从未与我们分享身份的人建立的工作场所结构。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是许多第一代美国人在试图在工作场所取得成功时面临着文化跷跷板效应。亚裔美国人和太平洋岛民 (AAPI) 社区（以及许多类似文化）发现了它 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-we-need -谈论亚裔美国人心理健康？cid=other-eml-dre-mip-mck&amp;hlkid=a774e1a8976d4a078406df70a8406fd5&amp;hctky=12012649&amp;amp;hdpid=9ae1a3af-4f90-48c7-84bd-0389 613c0228&quot;>;挑战自我推销&lt;/a>;，因为这违背了我们的价值观。我们被教导要谦虚并保持低调。我们从小就被教导永远不要纠正权威人物，以示尊重。与我父母的职业生涯类似，许多 AAPI 社区成员希望他们的辛勤工作能够不言而喻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，为什么工作场所和领导者在寻求创造公平和包容性的工作时需要考虑这一点很重要环境？ &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/savvy-self-promotion&quot;>;自我推销&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/glennllopis/2012/03/19/员工必须直言不讳的六大原因已成为在西方工作场所蓬勃发展所需的关键要素，但这显然对某些人有利，对另一些人不利。此外，第一代美国人和其他边缘化社区承受着许多代际、社会和工作场所的创伤，这些创伤造成了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/culture-competency/education/mental-health-facts# :~:text=Racial%2Fethnic%2C%20gender%2C%20and,of%20awareness%20about%20mental%20health&quot;>;心理健康差异&lt;/a>;，这可能会导致人们担心在工作环境中为自己辩护。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，如果雇主采取致力于优先考虑所有身份和背景的包容性的方法，那么我们就可以在扭曲的成功定义方面取得进展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;领导者如何能够改变叙述并帮助修复有缺陷的系统&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导者无法控制员工如何应对社会和代际创伤。然而，他们有责任营造一种环境，让所有员工都能放心地举手寻求支持。为了成功实现这一目标，组织应密切关注当前员工行为是否确实促进了包容性，或者是否需要修改流程和规范以为所有员工提供公平的环境。根据我与全球组织合作的经验，事实证明，在制定解决方案之前进行关键的暂停是改善包容性的关键因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;评估您的包容性努力&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了了解哪些做法支持包容性，哪些做法不支持包容性，需要进行彻底的评估。在以前的领导角色中，我成功地进行了这项评估，最终通过三个具体维度评估整个组织和管理实践的包容性：作为一个团队共同创造成功，培育有目的的社区，以及评估反馈机制的有效性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这三个维度是进一步了解组织的背景、文化和创建实质性包容性意​​图的综合方法。它还为领导者深入研究现行流程奠定了基础，以确定当前的公司氛围是否整合了第一代员工带来的差异，并允许他们参与决策过程以实现战略目标。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;彻底检查每个维度后，采取行动并优先考虑需要立即关注的特定领域是关键。它将在组织层面培育持续学习和改进的文化，同时创造新的实践，让第一代员工有安全的成长空间。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;作为一个团队共同创造成功&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们从这个维度开始，因为我们传统的工作场所实践通过强调特定的个人行为来定义成功，而不是创造有利于整个员工群体的实践。这种&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/how-to-infuse-liberatory-practices-into-work-practices&quot;>;分而治之&lt;/a>;方法特别阻止第一代员工确定他们的成功是什么样子，进一步说明他们独特的见解不如主导群体重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为领导者，您可以通过首先评估您为自己的团队提供的协作和包容性水平来纠正这些做法。开始修复实践并邀请所有团队成员定义他们的成功是什么样的。通过这样做，您可以让第一代员工放弃以前对完美员工的看法，并创建一种团结的文化，让他们更有可能表达自己的意见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，锻造参与规则、了解与他人的首选沟通方式以及最终确定领导层在项目开始时应提供的支持，从而为每个第一代员工保持界限。最终，如果你不断征求意见，并在商定的时间表上重新讨论有关成功定义的对话，那么与提出担忧相关的耻辱就会慢慢消失。此外，维持这些工作关系并相互承诺满足彼此的需求将有助于实现公平的决策过程并提高所有团队成员的士气。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;培养有目标的社区&lt;/strong>;&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;可以说，这可能是包容性评估中最重要的组成部分，因为它为第一代员工提供了一个避风港，让他们讨论如何应对仅适用于他们的独特工作场所压力源。例如，员工资源小组 (ERG) 对于试图加强包容性努力的组织来说非常受欢迎。然而，他们经常&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/ effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at -work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;达不到要求&lt;/a>;，因为他们缺乏责任感或特定使命。根据我的经验，我看到 ERG 仅仅被用作下班后的社交聚会——这很重要，但并没有在工作场所培养第一代员工应有的纠正做法。为了使这些社区更加有效，我建议寻找一位已经在实践&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/why-inclusive-leaders-are-good-for-organizations-and-how-to-become -one&quot;>;包容性领导力&lt;/a>;以同理心和战略来领导 ERG。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在之前的职位中，我担任业务发起人，并支持推出类似的 ERG，为期六个月行动计划。前两个月只是作为一个社区进行联系——减压并谈论我们的社区如何以特定方式被边缘化。第三个月和第四个月用于过渡到战略。我们研究了以下问题：&lt;em>;我们如何才能赋予自己寻求支持的能力？我们需要领导层采取哪些具体行动，让我们不断感受到自己被赋予了权力，从而为组织带来价值？这些对话通常很困难，有时甚至让人精神疲惫，因为它要求我们中的许多人重新审视我们的移民负罪感在工作场所是如何表现出来的。这就是为什么任何 ERG 的业务发起人都应该具备良好的装备和技能来促进这些对话。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，第五个月和第六个月致力于在具体工作实践中向高级领导层建立一个案例，需要进行修改，以便让我们在工作场所感到受到重视、被包容和受到保护。然后根据我们前几个月的圆桌讨论得出的连贯沟通计划制定了一项具体提案。当我们共同制定这个计划时，ERG 的每位成员都被邀请提供反馈，并对我们想要解决的首要问题进行投票。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在 ERG 社区的集体支持下，我们能够建立跨客户项目的新规范，以解决能力限制，加强与团队的交叉合作，并确定各级问责措施。对于许多 ERG 成员来说，这种成功伴随着对自己职业生涯的独特主人翁意识，而这在以前似乎是陌生的。社区里的人们习惯于保持沉默，回想起我们许多人在面对职场挑战时所承受的代际创伤。然而，这一成功带来了一线希望，即自我推销实际上可以带来切实的成果，从根本上改变企业的运营方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;评估反馈机制的有效性&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h3>; &lt;p>;虽然多年来通过敬业度调查进行员工反馈作为增强包容性的明确措施已变得流行，但许多第一代员工不愿提供他们的见解。由于我们的复杂身份、感觉被排斥以及缺乏与我们认同的榜样，我们感到有必要首先评估工作环境，以确定大声疾呼是否会受到赞扬或惩罚——无论反馈对于改变工作条件是否是必要的。为了解决这个问题，领导者应该积极分析他们正在提倡的文化类型，以便准确了解工作环境。如果没有心理安全这一核心组成部分，员工敬业度调查将仍然是对组织实际情况的错误幻想。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，如果您的目标是通过敬业度调查寻求建议来减少员工倦怠，请评估该类型在寻求反馈之前您所庆祝的行为。如果您要扩大员工全天候工作的能力，允许其他人接受每一个客户需求，或者创建&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90662451/its-very-time-sensitive-why-a-快节奏的工作环境伤害了所有员工&quot;>;错误的紧迫感&lt;/a>;，你没有营造一个包容的环境，让其他人举手寻求支持。事实上，你是在告诉你的员工，这是每个人都必须遵守的黄金法则。第一代员工在解决这些负面工作场所压力源时提供反馈会感到不安全，因为组织无意中支持了这种类型的倦怠行为。无论您的调查意图多么善意，有害的工作环境都会使任何重大变革的努力付之东流，并消除第一代员工的任何信誉。然而，如果最终目标是创造可持续和包容性的工作环境，请尽可能定期指出不良行为，让员工知道这些行为不是对员工的期望。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦仔细检查了工作场所实践，通过敬业度调查、团队论坛甚至一对一会议寻求个人反馈可以进一步证明可以增强第一代员工的能力。这种持续的行动方针实现了一致性的积极循环，鼓励自我倡导，而不是期望第一代员工在没有适当基础的情况下克服他们的保留意见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，当您寻求反馈时，请仔细分析第一代员工的观点。您可能并不总是同意他们的反馈，甚至并不完全理解他们的观点。然而，如果您的最终目标是包容性，那么您仍然有责任尽最大努力实施变革。一旦这个过程开始，一个重要的考虑因素就是不要让反馈闲置。最终，如果反馈被忽视，可能会在您和第一代员工之间造成不信任的环境。请记住，这个特定的群体在提供反馈时会做很多事情来克服他们自己内在的耻辱，希望工作文化能够得到转变。沟通您将如何处理反馈并保持敏捷。您可能需要花一些时间解读第一代员工的反馈，或者进行另一份后续调查问卷，以澄清有关他们工作条件的要点。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align ：中心；&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;随着组织继续通过为所有社区建立包容性来纠正有缺陷的系统，支持那些可能无法为自己辩护的人势在必行。第一代员工正处于一个独特的时刻，需要在新的工作时代运用决心和勤奋，不断在文化之间转换。组织需要创造一个环境，让我们能够摆脱束缚，真正蓬勃发展，以期创造一个更加公平的世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Benefits of Being Bored at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_XLRivrl9mNI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然无聊可能是一种不愉快的感觉，但它也可能是反思您的兴趣、价值观和目标的机会。通过认识您正在经历的无聊类型并找出根本原因，您可以采取措施解决这些问题并找到与周围世界互动的新方法。克服无聊还可以帮助你培养创造力、适应力和适应新情况的能力。因此，与其试图避免或忽视你的无聊，不如考虑将其作为个人成长的宝贵工具和过上更充实生活的方式。基于探索这种情绪的研究主体，作者强调了无聊的一些好处和坏处，并提供了有关如何充分利用无聊的见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;工作无聊？我们都去过那里。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/1745691612456044&quot;>;无聊&lt;/a>;是指想要专注于一项令人满意的活动，但不知何故无法做到这一点的体验。忙碌并不是解药：你可能同时非常忙碌 - 又非常无聊。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在生命的早期，我们就知道无聊并不有趣，随着年龄的增长，我们可能会开始将其视为一种乐趣。浪费时间，或者错过做更有成效的事情（或者至少更有趣）的机会。充其量，无聊被认为是一种令人不愉快的&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691612456044?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;厌恶&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https: //drive.google.com/file/d/152c9TgGipX6UOMCIbfTdrGy_vN6kopCv/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;体验&lt;/a>;，最坏的情况下，会产生一种深深的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www. springer.com/journal/13164&quot;>;毫无意义&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XXpz4j8kTTtUdXJdlak3e3_kuIJLNskz/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;。&lt;/a>;此外，当感到无聊而不适时，时间&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gNy8bUlah9IHjM1CZZjkS6EnRV7AxXzX/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;往往会过得很慢&lt;/a>;，这可能会导致工作日考虑到这一点，毫无疑问，无聊常常会引发强烈的愿望，想要逃离引起它的情况（或工作！）。在当今高度互联的世界中，这种逃离只需轻按一下即可。在您的指尖，您会发现一个充满数据、突发新闻、节目和故事、来自朋友和家人的消息或 GIF、表情包和视频剪辑的世界，帮助您避免感到无聊——至少在表面上是这样。研究表明，使用智能手机不仅会分散注意力，还会提供&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/IJPHM-08-2016-0044/full/html&quot;多巴胺的>;令人上瘾的打击&lt;/a>;，它&lt;em>;暂时&lt;/em>;用快乐取代无聊的不适。然而，这种感觉是短暂的，因为这种无意识的滚动会导致整体心理健康和生活质量的长期下降。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下次当你在工作中感受到那种令人毛骨悚然的无聊感时，在拿起电话之前先暂停一下。无聊可以带来重要的好处，如果你不了解自己的感受和原因，你就会错过它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;工作场所无聊的优点和缺点&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;无聊因某种原因而享有负面声誉。在工作中，它通常被视为一种&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;适得其反的状态&lt;/a>;，会引发不适、对新角色的绝望，或者可能只是渴望这一天结束。工作中的无聊与&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2160&quot;>;高风险的决策&lt;/a>;、代价高昂的错误以及因注意力不集中引发的事故有关或者注意力不集中——更不用说无聊会产生的疲劳了。无聊还会引发其他类型的问题行为，例如“网络闲逛”（即与工作无关的浏览）和幼稚的情绪反应。长时间从事单调的活动甚至会导致&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-pathology-of-boredom/&quot;>;幻觉&lt;/a>;。此外，就幸福感而言，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000187912200118X&quot;>;最近的一项研究发现&lt;/a>;工作中的无聊与倦怠，以及工作满意度下降和辞职欲望增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一方面，最近的研究表明，如果建设性地处理无聊，就会产生很大的“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www” .sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;光明的一面&lt;/a>;。”在这个旨在分散注意力、压垮和过度刺激的世界中，无聊的时刻可以为您的大脑和身体提供暂停或短暂的休息。无聊感可以创造白日梦的空间，可以&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2014.901073&quot;>;孵化创造力&lt;/a>;、新想法和创新。长时间的无聊会促使你反思并问自己：“我走的路正确吗？我做的对吗？”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;利用你的无聊变得更好&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们并不提倡你寻找一天中大部分时间都感到无聊的工作。然而，更好地处理你的无聊——并利用它来做善事——可以帮助你捕捉到它的光明的一面。具体方法如下：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.注意。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;当您感到无聊的不适感时，请避免立即采取行动。事实上，你已经注意到自己很无聊，这意味着你已经成功（暂时）抵制了立即进行无意识滚动的冲动。注意到并命名你的无聊，以便有意识地引导它，这为你提供了发展你的适应能力和利用无聊达到积极目的的潜力的机会。最重要的是，在无聊的时候，不要做出仓促的决定（比如辞职）来逃避不适。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2.破译。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;并非所有的无聊经历都是一样的——&lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11031-013-9385-y&quot;>;研究表明&lt;/ a>; 不同“类型”的无聊在身体和心灵上有不同的表现，从而引发不同的行为。解码您早期感受到的类型可以帮助您制定应对无聊的计划，或防止无聊升级或影响您的决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;问问自己，您的无聊告诉了您什么。难道您只是需要&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research&quot;>;微休息&lt;/a>;，因为您已经连续工作太久而你累了吗？或者也许你的任务变得单调，你正在失去动力和精力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;具体考虑一下你对什么感到厌倦：是你的角色、工作的内容或形式，还是你的工作前景你的工作未来让你感到厌烦吗？你能解读出一种典型的工作类型会引发这种不舒服的感觉吗？这可以是一个考虑您的目标和价值观以及您是否感觉自己正在前进或感到“陷入困境”的机会。当你努力解读自己的无聊时，可以考虑以下五种基于研究的无聊类型：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;无关紧要的无聊。&lt;/strong>;这是更积极的无聊类型之一。它可能感觉像是放松或愉快的疲劳感，反映了对外部世界的普遍冷漠（和退缩）。这种类型的无聊可以帮助促进休息和恢复，尤其是在忙碌的日子里。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;校准无聊。&lt;/strong>;这种无聊稍微令人不愉快，是最常见的类型之一。当你没有完全投入某项任务或活动并且你的思绪开始走神时，就会发生这种情况。它可以表现为徘徊的想法或不知道该怎么做才能改变这种情况，但又想以某种方式摆脱困境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;寻找无聊。&lt;/strong>;这种类型反映了一种焦躁不安和不安的情绪。积极寻找替代行动和干扰来缓解负面经历（例如，通过其他活动、休闲活动、兴趣和爱好）。虽然令人不愉快，但这种类型的无聊会激发活动和对变革的追求，并且通常会产生积极的结果，例如创造力、创新和个人成长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;反应性无聊。&lt;/strong>;反应性无聊会出现在一个人需要执行重复或乏味的任务的情况下（例如陷入漫长而无效的会议而没有逃脱的机会）。这是一种以行动为导向的、非常不愉快的无聊类型，它会导致不安和沮丧，可能会以对他人或无聊的经历更加愤怒或更具攻击性的方式表达出来。经历过这种情况的人可能会持续幻想其他选择，并渴望做出改变或快速逃离。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;冷漠无聊。&lt;/strong>;这可能与不感兴趣、缺乏动力和缺乏动力的感觉有关。对人们通常认为刺激或愉快的活动或事件的情感超脱。冷漠的无聊并不一定伴随着沮丧或不安的感觉，而是一种脱离和冷漠的感觉。它可能是由于慢性压力、抑郁或其他心理健康问题造成的，并可能导致绝望和无助的感觉。经历冷漠无聊的人可能会觉得自己只是在过着平淡的生活，没有任何真正的目的或乐趣。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.决定做什么。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;根据无聊的类型以及它告诉你的关于你自己或你的处境的信息，决定如何应对。也许你的无聊只是让你在一段时间的紧张工作后放松身心。或者它可能告诉你一些关于你的角色本身的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有角色都有某些单调、令人沮丧或无聊的元素，有时必须完成这些任务才能获得“好东西”。如果您发现自己持续感到无聊，请尝试利用无聊来促进改变，也许可以通过参与&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;工作塑造&lt;/ a>; 展现出你真正喜欢的角色元素。例如，这可能涉及对任务的类型、种类、复杂性或重要性进行更改。您可能会通过在工作中寻找、设想和倡导新想法来有意地逃避无聊，这也可以提高您的领导能力和潜力。反思和参与&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23163710/&quot;>;怀旧&lt;/a>;也可以抵消你在无聊时可能感到的无意义感。&lt;/p>; &lt; h3>;4。培养正念的无聊感。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;无聊的时刻可以成为帮助您从快节奏和高度互联的世界中放松下来的机会，让您有机会享受当下。利用无聊的时刻来实现积极的意图，而不是无意识地分心，例如，花点时间呼吸一下，做另一项你觉得模拟的活动，或者只是用心让不适过去。由于无聊可以激发&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20200522-how-boredom-can-spark-creativity&quot;>;创造力&lt;/a>;，您甚至可以将其空间添加为例如，在您需要创新、提出新想法并做到最佳状态之前，您需要在日常工作中留出一些非结构化的时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;虽然无聊可能是一种不愉快的感觉，但它也可能是反思您的兴趣、价值观和目标的机会。通过认识到您正在经历的无聊类型并找出根本原因，您可以采取措施解决这些问题并找到与周围世界互动的新方法。克服无聊还可以帮助你培养创造力、适应力和适应新情况的能力。因此，与其试图避免或忽视无聊，不如考虑将其作为个人成长的宝贵工具以及过上更充实生活的方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/p>;分区>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Ways to Earn the Respect of a More Powerful Colleague]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_03_144694173.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;retales botijero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当您陷入不平等的权力动态时，记住权力的分布不仅是暂时的，而且您可以使其均衡，这会有所帮助。在本文中，作者概述了四种策略，您可以使用这些策略来创造性地把握当下并以不同的方式构建联系，以便您建立应有的尊重并积极改变对自己权力的看法。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language =es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language=pt&quot; >;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;无论我们是否愿意承认，在许多同事关系中都存在权力差异，通常基于各方在组织中的地位以及谁对什么有更多的控制权特定时间的其他需求。例如，其团队最终决定产品线上市时间的工程领导者可能比试图为不耐烦的客户提供服务的销售领导者拥有更大的权力，而成熟且“平淡”的业务部门的领导者可能会始终如一地找到他们的需求IT 部门不再优先考虑，而是急于支持快速增长的部门。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于那些处于“劣势”位置的人来说，这是一种非常令人沮丧的动态 - 但要与同事建立相互尊重的关系（甚至可能要求更多的相对权力），采取措施重新平衡平衡至关重要。如果愿意以创造性的方式维护自己的利益，您就会为自己发展更多的代理权，尤其是在感到被忽视或依赖的时候。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.columbia.edu/~da358 /publications/ames_pushing_up_to_a_point.pdf&quot;>;研究表明&lt;/a>;在人际关系中的自信方面存在“金发姑娘”效应，您可以在过于自信和不够自信之间找到最佳平衡点。如果处理得当，&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/why-we-should-be-disagreeing-more-at-work&quot;>;健康的异议&lt;/a>;可以带来更深的信任和相互尊重。根据我作为跨国公司高级领导者的&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.partnerexec.com/&quot;>;执行教练&lt;/a>;的工作，您可以在人际关系中部署以下四种策略，以更多地分配权力均匀地。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;选择拒绝某些请求。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;拒绝更有权力的同事的请求可能会让人感到难以置信的挑战。但在任何互动中，&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Framing_effect_(psychology)&quot;>;框架效应&lt;/a>;都会发生，各方都会评估谁拥有更大的权力和影响力。由于权力由许多因素组成并且是视情况而定的，即使你发现自己相对于同事来说通常是无能为力的，但确实会出现他们需要你提供某些东西的情况，就像你需要他们一样。即使您过去总是屈服，但在某些时候，利用机会礼貌地拒绝更有权力的人的要求也很重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www. Psychologytoday.com/us/blog/meet-catch-and-keep/201602/4-truths-about-power-in-relationships-include-yours&quot;>;关于关系的研究&lt;/a>;将权力定义为不仅拥有更大的权力影响他人的能力，但对他人影响的&lt;em>;抵抗力&lt;/em>;也较强。因此，下次当你感觉到你的同事对你过度施加权力时（例如，即使你无法联系到他们，但又在最后一刻提出了另一个请求），最好不要立即放弃你的请求。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我曾经指导过一位领导者，她的同事经常把工作推给她，但当其他人需要她的帮助时，她却设法置身事外。这位同事经常引用她与共同老板的互动来证明自己的权力，并在提出纯粹为她服务的请求时放弃他们的名字。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您的处境与我的客户类似，请回复你的同事可以这样说：“我想让你知道我收到了你的请求。我很乐意提供帮助，但目前我还有其他必须履行的承诺。同时，请随时向我发送更多信息，以便我提出其他解决方案。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;理想情况下，您希望传达这样的信息：您希望他们也将有限的时间投入到这段关系中。如果您忠实于做出的最低承诺，那么您就可以自信地坚持作为平等合作伙伴的立场。这不仅会鼓励他们尊重您，还会迫使他们像您一样为这段关系做出必要的牺牲。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;将他们与其他重视您的有权势的人联系起来。&lt;/strong>; &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;改变关系中权力的另一种方法是通过将他们与他们尊敬的其他人联系起来，巧妙地提醒他们你的社会价值，并且与他们建立了关系。这做了三件有价值的事情：首先，它向他们表明（通过社会证明的原则），如果他们敬佩的人看到你的价值，你必须提供一些东西；其次，这可能会扭转你们关系动态的天平，因为你拥有他们想要享受的机会；第三，它发出了一个信号，表明您已经拥有高调的访问权限，因此不必急于寻求他们的认可。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我曾与一位领导者共事，他努力被视为“战略”高管，并且在进行继任计划讨论时，人力资源部门不断淡化更高级别的职位。但事实上，他非常具有创新精神，并渴望为业务更具前瞻性的方面做出贡献；正是因为他非常擅长运营执行，人力资源部和他的老板不想通过晋升来搅局。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了打破这种限制他进步的权力动态，我的客户开始与其他高级领导者建立关系并传播有助于他们业务需求的想法。然后他开始在他的新联系人和人力资源部门以及他的业务部门的一些对他的职业生涯有影响的同事之间进行介绍。通过展示他与其他强大领导者的接触并通过与他人联系来分享，他的品牌开始逐渐提升为企业级领导者的形象。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;帮助他们发现作为领导者的盲点。支持他们的方式。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;即使是最有权势的人也不能完全按照其他人看待他们的方式来看待自己。换句话说，他们和我们其他人一样也有盲点。当您可以帮助他们温和地认识到他们的思维或行为中阻碍其目标的某个方面时，他们就会开始将您视为高度信任的合作伙伴，而不是低于他们水平的人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;我的一位客户是一家科技公司的高级副总裁，她对整个组织内关于首席执行官缺乏果断力以及这如何给员工和团队造成混乱的争论了如指掌。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然她同意总体而言，她对首席执行官对待她的方式感到满意。虽然他比她拥有更大的权力，但她总体上接受了在他的领导下工作并尽可能满足他的期望的想法。毕竟，她想，为什么要冒着与首席执行官的关系的风险，向他提供强硬的反馈，因为她作为信使，可能会适得其反？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但她也认识到，要成为他值得信赖的合作伙伴，她需要无论好坏，都需要真正站在他的立场上，这需要为了他的利益而对他诚实。因此，她决定在下一次一对一的谈话中分享她的观察结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这位高级副总裁说：“我知道为企业和我们的员工做正确的事情对你来说有多重要。有时我们的优势可能会被过度利用，以致成为劣势。我认为，因为你非常关心倾听问题各个方面的意见，所以开始推迟做出决定。我想提供这种可能性，因为你可能太接近这种风格，无法看到它如何影响其他人。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在冒着给首席执行官树立镜子的风险时，高级副总裁赢得了很高的评价来自他的尊重和感激。他们的关系成为值得信赖的顾问之一，而不仅仅是直接报告。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你会见有权势的人，并简单地告诉他们他们以前听到的一切或与你职位上的其他人相同的事情，你就会被遗忘并维持现状。但是，通过走出你的舒适区，友善而自信地指出有权势的人没有注意到的事情，你不仅会变得令人难忘，而且会开始获得他们的影响力和尊重。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong >;让他们为赢得你的关注而工作。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;获得比你更有权力的同事的尊重是一个有趣的悖论：通过让他们为你的认可而工作，你可以获得更多的利益他们的尊重。因此，第四个策略是创造条件，让他们必须向你“出售”他们的价值。基本上，减少为赢得他们的尊重而付出的努力，并让他们承担解释为什么他们应该值得你关注的负担。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多年来，我曾为那些经历过合并或重组的公司的领导者提供过指导，要求许多员工和领导者“重新申请”工作，无论是在他们的部门还是在公司的新部门。这种经历可能会令人不安，不仅因为他们又重新成为与其他人竞争工作的候选人，而且因为与从外部申请新公司不同，他们的声誉先于他们，并提供更主观的信息，这将影响面试官评估时&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多人在这些情况下犯的自然错误是对他们认为会被问到的问题做好过度准备，并尽力回避自己的答案以取悦招聘同事。这似乎是阻力最小的途径，但实际上在对方眼中它们是容易被遗忘且不起眼的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，想办法慷慨地回答，但也不要害怕提出问题他们有点跟不上。当你的同事问你这个经常重复的问题时：“我们为什么要雇用你来做这份工作？”你的第一反应可能是向他们证明你的价值，让他们满意，尽管你和他们都知道大多数人申请工作是因为重组，而不是因为他们想尝试新事物。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，稍稍停顿一下，然后说：“事实上，我还不确定你是否应该雇用我。我想探讨一下我的经验和您对这个团队的发展方向的愿景是否相互契合。当我探索下一步时，您能分享的有关您的管理风格的任何内容都会很有帮助。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;期望掌权者“赢得”您的兴趣而不是认为这是理所当然的，可以带来积极的结果。它不仅可以让您在竞争中脱颖而出，还可以确保您与尊重您的同事一起工作，而不是让您受制于他们的权力和突发奇想。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当您陷入不平等的权力动态时，记住，权力的分配不仅是暂时的，而且你可以平衡它。通过采用这些策略，您可以创造性地把握当下并以不同的方式构建联系，从而建立应有的尊重。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Explain a Gap in Your Resume]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_1105032.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Audshule/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;自疫情爆发以来，大多数雇主对简历差距更加理解，更少歧视。但你必须准备好清楚、自信、不结巴地解释这些差距。掌握自己的职业轨迹意味着为招聘人员和招聘经理连接所有点。自己围绕任何差距进行叙述将有助于使它们不再成为问题。作者讨论了工作经历差距的五个常见原因以及如何在面试过程中掌握差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to- explain-a-gap-in-your-resume?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your -resume?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在每个面试过程中，至少有一次你会被问到某种版本的问题，“你能带我浏览一下你的简历吗？”除了您的技能和经验之外，您还需要能够解释您在工作之间的转换，包括差距。这一点至关重要：当您在讨论简历时忽略工作之间的差距时，您就失去了控制有关工作转变或离开商业劳动力的时间的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;基于我对以下行业就业差距的研究：在我的书《想要→新职业：过渡到新职业或寻找梦想工作的权威手册》中，以下是工作经历差距的五个常见原因，以及如何在新职业生涯中承认差距面试流程：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;在家养育子女&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您从商业劳动力中休假&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/helping-stay-at-home- parents-reenter-the-workforce&quot;>;养育孩子&lt;/a>;，请解释您如何利用这段时间来获得与工作相关的技能、知识或经验。例如，您在孩子的学校做过志愿者吗？组织活动或筹款活动？您是为运动队活动安排旅行的家长吗？所有这些都可以转化为您正在申请的工作。例如，假设您希望继续从事全球筹款事业。你可以告诉面试官，“我花了一些时间来照顾我们的孩子，但我能够在为儿童体育联盟做志愿者、制定筹款目标并帮助团队成功实现筹款配额为儿童提供经济援助的同时，保持自己的技能新鲜。”那些需要它的人。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;丧亲或照顾生病的家庭成员&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您抽出时间去照顾父母或家庭成员，请拥有您花这段时间的选择和他们在一起的重要时光。从工作的角度来审视这段经历。例如，如果您想重新担任客户服务角色，您可以专注于与家人的医疗保健提供者联络的角色：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我请假去护理为了我的父亲。在那段时间里，我能够利用我与多个医疗保健提供者的有效沟通技巧，以及我的组织能力来协调与他的财务规划师、经纪人和法律代表的会议，这让他安心。我想在这份工作中运用同样的解决问题的技能以及在压力下保持冷静的能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;如果您正在申请财务工作，您可以专注于您的角色作为遗嘱执行人：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;在我母亲去世之前，我请了假来陪伴她。我被任命为执行人是因为我高度负责、有组织性并且具有财务头脑。我能够利用我的财务技能以及软技能来协调她的遗产，例如与多个债权人（包括公用事业公司、信用卡公司、医疗机构和银行机构）进行有效沟通。我的技能使我能够快速有效地关闭遗产，现在我希望将我的技能运用到新的挑战中。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h2>;环游世界&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;何时在抽出时间去探索之后回到公司工作环境，专注于你如何利用这段时间来获得新的视角。例如，如果您正在面试一家跨国公司，您可以讨论与来自不同文化的人互动的细微差别，以及体验其他国家的生活如何为您提供许多人在工作场所所没有的视角。如果您正在寻求运营职位，您可以重点关注旅行计划、与损益表相关的预算的效率，以及如何使用批判性思维来确定下一步去哪里。如果您花时间学习第二、第三或第四语言，请解释一下您的会话或流利能力如何使您成为比不会多语言的人表现更好的候选人。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;回到学校&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;也许您回到学校是为了获得 MBA 或博士学位。如果您是全日制学生，请解释您从事的具体项目如何与工作直接相关，以及这些项目以及过去的工作经验将如何让您为该职位带来独特的价值。也许您获得了 MBA 学位并想从事商业运营工作。您为真正的公司做过项目吗？将它们包含在您的简历中，以便您可以在面试时讨论它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您发展了自己的技能&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/5-ways-to-acquire-new-skills-without -going-back-to school&quot;>;无需返回学校&lt;/a>;获得传统学位 - 例如，通过参加课程或获得认证 - 描述这些技能如何应用于未来的工作，并使你与众不同其他候选人。如果您阅读特定书籍是为了获得对您所在领域的新视角或增强您的领导能力，请谈谈您将如何应用您在工作中学到的原则。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;终止雇佣关系&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/what-to-do-after-being-laid-off&quot;>;受到与绩效无关的大规模裁员的影响&lt;/a>;，向面试官解释业务策略发生了变化，您的部门或团队在最新一波裁员浪潮中被解雇。您甚至可以积极地看待不幸的情况：“但这一直是一件幸事，因为我正在考虑寻找新的挑战。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您因表现而被解雇，显然您的雇主并不认为您是这样你的工作很成功，但也许你有不同的观点，或者觉得这个角色不是你所期望的。在这种情况下，您可以解释说这份工作与您想象的不同，并且没有以最有效的方式利用您的技能和能力。始终解释您从这次经历中学到了什么，以及您如何积极工作以确保您的下一步行动更接近您的期望。例如：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;我刚开始工作不久就知道这份工作并不像描述的那样，但既然我对公司做出了承诺，我想尽我最大的努力。最终，我的 A、B、C 技能没有得到有效利用，为业务带来价值。因此，我们友好地分开了，这使我能够花时间找到合适的工作，根据业务需求，我可以带来最大的价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;如果您处于有毒环境中或决定因任何其他原因辞职，不要将这种消极情绪带入工作面试中。从积极的角度看待你离职的原因，例如，“我需要集中时间来找到一份更符合我价值观的工作，但每周工作 60 小时，我找不到时间去做这件事。”最重要的是，永远不要说任何人的坏话，因为这种行为会让你看起来像一个只责备别人而不承担责任的人——而在新公司也可以这样做。现在是走正路的时候了。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;自大流行以来，大多数雇主对简历差距更加理解和更少歧视 - 但你必须准备好清楚、自信、不绊倒地解释这些差距。掌握自己的职业轨迹意味着为招聘人员和招聘经理连接所有点。自己围绕任何差距进行叙述将有助于使它们不再成为问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[13 Principles for Using AI Responsibly]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_200245321-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;鲍里斯·SV/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;人工智能开发的竞争性质给组织带来了困境，因为优先考虑速度可能会导致忽视道德准则、偏见检测和安全措施。与工作场所人工智能相关的已知和新出现的问题包括错误信息的传播、版权和知识产权问题、网络安全、数据隐私，以及快速而模糊的法规。为了减轻这些风险，我们提出了在工作中负责任的人工智能的十三个原则。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/ 13-principles-for-using-ai-responsively?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsively?language =pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;无论你喜欢还是讨厌，人工智能的快速扩张不会很快放缓。但人工智能的失误&lt;a href=&quot;https://cmr.berkeley.edu/2022/01/the-reputational-risks-of-ai/&quot;>;可能会迅速损害品牌声誉&lt;/a>;——问问微软的第一个聊天机器人就知道了，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;泰&lt;/a>;。在科技竞赛中，所有领导者都担心如果自己放慢速度而其他人却没有放慢速度，就会被甩在后面。这是一个高风险的局面，合作似乎有风险，叛逃也很诱人。这种&lt;a href=&quot;https://heritage.umich.edu/stories/the-prisoners-dilemma/&quot;>;“囚徒困境”&lt;/a>;（博弈论中的说法）给负责任的人工智能实践带来了风险。优先考虑上市速度的领导者正在推动当前的人工智能军备竞赛，主要企业参与者都在竞相推出产品，并可能&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies -cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;短期改变关键考虑因素&lt;/a>;，例如道德准则、偏见检测和安全措施。例如，大型科技公司正在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies-cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;解雇人工智能道德团队&lt;/ a>; 正是在最需要采取负责任行动的时候。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样重要的是要认识到人工智能军备竞赛超出了 OpenAI、Google 和 Meta 等大型语言模型 (LLM) 的开发人员的范围。它包括许多利用法学硕士来支持自己的定制应用程序的公司。例如，在专业服务领域，普华永道 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/pwcs-4000-legal-staffers-get-ai-assistant-law-chatbots-gain- steam-2023-03-15/&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>;正在为分布在 100 个国家/地区的 4,000 名律师部署人工智能聊天机器人。这些人工智能助理将“帮助律师进行合同分析、监管合规工作、尽职调查以及其他法律咨询和咨询服务。”普华永道的管理层也在考虑将这些人工智能聊天机器人扩展到他们的税务实践中。这家咨询巨头总共计划向“生成人工智能”（一种强大的新技术）投入 10 亿美元。工具能够提供改变游戏规则的绩效提升。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，毕马威推出了自己的人工智能助手，名为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afr.com/companies/ professional-services/custom-chatgpt-tool-to-help-kpmg-s-consultants-win-new-work-20230321-p5cu3m&quot;>;KymChat&lt;/a>;，这将帮助员工快速找到整个组织的内部专家，将它们围绕即将到来的机会，并根据项目要求和可用人才之间的匹配自动生成提案。他们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://kpmg.com/au/en/home/media/press-releases/2023/03/kpmg-unveils-cutting-edge-private-chatgpt-software-march-2023.html&quot; >;人工智能助手&lt;/a>;“将更好地实现跨团队协作，并帮助公司新员工获得更无缝、更高效的人员导航体验。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slack 还将生成式人工智能融入到开发中&lt;a href=&quot;https://slack.com/blog/news/introducing-slack-gpt&quot;>;Slack GPT&lt;/a>; 的一款人工智能助手，旨在帮助员工更聪明地工作，而不是更辛苦地工作。该平台整合了一系列人工智能功能，例如对话摘要和写作辅助，以提高用户的工作效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些示例只是冰山一角。很快，数亿 Microsoft 365 用户将可以访问 &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work /&quot;>;商务聊天&lt;/a>;，一个让用户参与工作的代理，努力理解他们的 Microsoft 365 数据。员工可以提示助理做所有事情，从根据会议记录和电子邮件通信制定状态报告摘要，到识别策略中的缺陷并提出解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能代理的快速部署就是&lt;a href= “https://fortune.com/2023/04/20/ibm-ceo-work-ai-artificial-intelligence-careers-tech-arvind-krishna/&quot;>;IBM 首席执行官 Arvind Krishna&lt;/a>; 最近写道“人们与值得信赖的人工智能合作将对我们的经济和社会产生变革性的影响……现在是我们拥抱这种伙伴关系的时候了——让我们的员工为人工智能所提供的一切做好准备。”简而言之，组织在安装人工智能驱动的工具方面正在经历指数级增长，而那些不适应的公司则面临着落后的风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;工作中的人工智能风险&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，保持竞争力还给雇员和雇主带来了重大风险。例如，2022 年&lt;a href=&quot;https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000380861&quot;>;联合国教科文组织出版物&lt;/a>;关于“人工智能对女性工作生活的影响”报告称，人工智能例如，在招聘过程中，将妇女排除在晋升之外。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1408.6491&quot;>;报告引用的一项研究&lt;/a>;，其中包括 21 项实验，涉及超过 60,000 个有针对性的招聘广告，发现“将用户的性别设置为‘女性’会导致与选择“男性”作为性别的用户相比，与高薪工作相关的广告实例较少。”尽管人工智能在招聘和聘用方面的偏见众所周知，但它不会很快消失。正如联合国教科文组织的报告接着指出的那样，“一项 &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3450077&quot;>;2021 年研究&lt;/a>;的证据表明，招聘广告因性别而存在偏差。即使广告商想要性别平衡的受众，Facebook 也是如此。”这通常是一个有偏见的数据问题，它将继续影响人工智能工具并威胁关键的劳动力因素，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raconteur.net/responsible-business/ais-threat-to-diversity-equity-包容性/&quot;>;多样性、公平性和包容性&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;歧视性就业做法可能只是生成式人工智能使组织面临的一系列法律风险之一。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bloomberglaw.com/tech-and-telecom-law/openai-hit-with-first-defamation-suit-over-chatgpt-hallucination&quot;>;OpenAI 正面临着第一次因指控 ChatGPT 产生有害的错误信息而提起诽谤诉讼&lt;/a>;。具体来说，该系统生成了一个真实法庭案件的摘要，其中包括对佐治亚州一名电台主持人的挪用公款的捏造指控。这凸显了创建和共享人工智能生成信息对组织的负面影响。它强调了对法学硕士捏造虚假和诽谤性内容的担忧，从而导致声誉受损、信誉丧失、客户信任度下降以及严重的法律后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了与诽谤相关的担忧之外，还存在与&lt; a href=&quot;/2023/04/generative-ai-has-an-intellectual-property-problem&quot;>;侵犯版权和知识产权&lt;/a>;。几个&lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/27/the-current-legal-cases-against-generative-ai-are-just-the-beginning/&quot;>;备受瞩目的法律案件&lt; /a>; 已经出现，生成人工智能工具的开发者因涉嫌不当使用许可内容而被起诉。版权和知识产权侵权的存在，加上此类侵权行为的法律影响，给使用生成式人工智能产品的组织带来了重大风险。组织可能会在不知不觉中参与抄袭、未经授权的改编、未经许可的商业使用以及滥用知识共享或开源内容等活动，从而通过生成人工智能不当使用许可内容，从而使自己面临潜在的法律后果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能的大规模部署也放大了网络攻击的风险&lt;/a>;。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/opinion/Generative-AI-the-next-biggest-cyber-security-threat&quot;>;网络安全专家担心&lt;/a>;可以使用生成式人工智能&lt;a href=&quot;https://consent.yahoo.com/v2/collectConsent?sessionId=3_cc-session_e69b334f-36d8-44b0-9f52-93ea6089aa5a&quot;>;识别和利用业务信息系统中的漏洞&lt;/a>;，给定法学硕士自动编码和错误检测的能力，恶意行为者可以利用它来突破安全障碍。人们还担心员工不小心与第三方人工智能提供商共享敏感数据。一个值得注意的例子是三星员工无意中 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-generative-ai-tools-like-chatgpt-after-april-internal- data-leak/&quot;>;在使用 LLM 审查源代码时通过 ChatGPT 泄露商业秘密&lt;/a>;。由于他们未能选择退出数据共享，机密信息无意中被提供给了 OpenAI。尽管三星和其他公司正在采取措施&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2023/05/19/apple-joins-a-forming-list-of-companies-cracking -down-on-use-of-chatgpt-by-staffers-heres-why/&quot;>;限制在公司自有设备上使用第三方人工智能工具&lt;/a>;，但仍然存在员工可能通过以下途径泄露信息的担忧：在个人设备上使用此类系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了这些风险之外，企业很快将不得不应对新生的、多样化的且有些模糊的法规。 Anyone hiring in New York City, for instance, will have to ensure their AI-powered recruitment and hiring tech doesn&#39;t violate the City&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/new-york-city-s-automated-employment-6844706/&quot;>;automated employment decision tool&lt;/a>;” law. To comply with the new law, employers will need to take various steps such as conducting third-party bias audits of their hiring tools and publicly disclosing the findings. AI regulation is also scaling up nationally with the Biden-Harris administration&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/ostp/ai-bill-of-rights/&quot;>;Blueprint for an AI Bill of Rights&lt;/a>;” and internationally with the EU&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://artificialintelligenceact.eu/&quot;>;AI Act&lt;/a>;, which will mark a new era of regulation for employers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This growing nebulous of evolving regulations and pitfalls is why thought leaders such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/your-7-biggest-chatgpt-questions-answered&quot;>;Gartner&lt;/a>; are strongly suggesting that businesses “proceed but don&#39;t over pivot” and that they “create a task force reporting to the CIO and CEO” to plan a roadmap for a safe AI transformation that mitigates various legal, reputational, and workforce risks. Leaders dealing with this AI dilemma have important decision to make. On the one hand, there is a pressing competitive pressure to fully embrace AI. However, on the other hand, a growing concern is arising as the implementation of irresponsible AI can result in severe penalties, substantial damage to reputation, and significant operational setbacks. The concern is that in their quest to stay ahead, leaders may unknowingly introduce potential time bombs into their organization, which are poised to cause major problems once AI solutions are deployed and regulations take effect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/06/08/1180838096/an-eating-disorders-chatbot-offered-dieting-advice-raising-fears-about-ai-in-hea&quot;>;National Eating Disorder Association&lt;/a>; (NEDA) recently announced it was letting go of its hotline staff and replacing them with their new chatbot, Tessa. However, just days before making the transition, NEDA discovered that their system was promoting harmful advice such as encouraging people with eating disorders to restrict their calories and to lose one to two pounds per week. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/06/13/1074551/an-algorithm-intended-to-reduce-poverty-in-jordan-disqualifies-people-in-need/&quot;>;World Bank&lt;/a>; spent $1 billion to develop and deploy an algorithmic system, called Takaful, to distribute financial assistance that Human Rights Watch now says ironically creates inequity. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-chatgpt-courts-e15023d7e6fdf4f099aa122437dbb59b&quot;>;two lawyers from New York&lt;/a>; are facing possible disciplinary action after using ChatGPT to draft a court filing that was found to have several references to previous cases that did not exist. These instances highlight the need for well-trained and well-supported employees at the center of this digital transformation. While AI can serve as a valuable assistant, it should not assume the leading position.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Principles for Responsible AI at Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To help decision-makers avoid negative outcomes while also remaining competitive in the age of AI, we&#39;ve devised several principles for a sustainable AI-powered workforce. The principles are a blend of ethical frameworks from institutions like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsf.gov/od/recr.jsp&quot;>;National Science Foundation&lt;/a>; as well as legal requirements related to employee monitoring and data privacy such as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bja.ojp.gov/program/it/privacy-civil-liberties/authorities/statutes/1285&quot;>;Electronic Communications Privacy Act&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecpra.org/&quot;>;California Privacy Rights Act&lt;/a>;. The steps for ensuring responsible AI at work include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Informed Consent. &lt;/strong>;Obtain voluntary and informed agreement from employees to participate in any AI-powered intervention &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; the employees are provided with all the relevant information about the initiative. This includes the program&#39;s purpose, procedures, and potential risks and benefits.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Aligned Interests. &lt;/strong>;The goals, risks, and benefits for both the employer and employee are clearly articulated and aligned.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Opt In &amp;amp; Easy Exits. &lt;/strong>;Employees must opt into AI-powered programs without feeling forced or coerced, and they can easily withdraw from the program at any time without any negative consequences and without explanation.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Conversational Transparency. &lt;/strong>;When AI-based conversational agents are used, the agent should formally reveal any persuasive objectives the system aims to achieve through the dialogue with the employee.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Debiased and Explainable AI. &lt;/strong>;Explicitly outline the steps taken to remove, minimize, and mitigate bias in AI-powered employee interventions—especially for disadvantaged and vulnerable groups—and provide transparent explanations into how AI systems arrive at their decisions and actions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;AI Training and Development. &lt;/strong>;Provide continuous employee training and development to ensure the safe and responsible use of AI-powered tools.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Health and Well-Being. &lt;/strong>;Identify types of AI-induced stress, discomfort, or harm and articulate steps to minimize risks (eg, how will the employer minimize stress caused by constant AI-powered monitoring of employee behavior).&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data Collection. &lt;/strong>;Identify what data will be collected, if data collection involves any invasive or intrusive procedures (eg, the use of webcams in work-from-home situations), and what steps will be taken to minimize risk.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data. &lt;/strong>;Disclose any intention to share personal data, with whom, and why.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Privacy and Security. &lt;/strong>;Articulate protocols for maintaining privacy, storing employee data securely, and what steps will be taken in the event of a privacy breach.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Third Party Disclosure. &lt;/strong>;Disclose all third parties used to provide and maintain AI assets, what the third party&#39;s role is, and how the third party will ensure employee privacy.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Communication.&lt;/strong>; Inform employees about changes in data collection, data management, or data sharing as well as any changes in AI assets or third-party relationships.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Laws and Regulations. &lt;/strong>;Express ongoing commitment to comply with all laws and regulations related to employee data and the use of AI.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We encourage leaders to urgently adopt and develop this checklist in their organizations. By applying such principles, leaders can ensure rapid &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; responsible AI deployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make Leadership Positions More Enticing to Primary Care Physicians]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_1293518427.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/The Good Brigade/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the brink of collapse due to historic highs of physician stress, burnout, and exhaustion; mass departures from the profession; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective advocacy to improve primary care on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Healthcare organizations who understand and work to address the issues PCPs face &amp;#8212; and encourage their professional development &amp;#8212; will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://catalyst.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/CAT.23.0029&quot;>;brink of collapse&lt;/a>; due to historic highs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-help-primary-care-physicians-craft-sustainable-careers&quot;>;physician stress&lt;/a>;, burnout, and exhaustion; mass &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostonglobe.com/2023/03/16/metro/months-long-waits-accessing-care-leave-patients-sicker-anguish/&quot;>;departures from the profession&lt;/a>;; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective &lt;a href=&quot;https://nap.nationalacademies.org/catalog/25983/implementing-high-quality-primary-care-rebuilding-the-foundation-of-health&quot;>;advocacy to improve primary care&lt;/a>; on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/why-is-it-so-challenging-to-find-a-primary-care-physician-202209282822&quot;>;shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care&lt;/a>; under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If primary care is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/16/opinion/pandemic-recovery-primary-care.html&quot;>;touted as the foundation of a well-functioning health care system&lt;/a>; — the front line of clinical care and the initial point of contact for most patients — how can it be allowed to deteriorate without unified and passionate intervention? Our research suggests that the answer may be straightforward. While primary care accounts for roughly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aamc.org/data-reports/workforce/data/active-physicians-largest-specialties-major-professional-activity-2021&quot;>;one in three&lt;/a>; practicing physicians and is seen as the bedrock of the health care system, it is also the most overlooked and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jabfm.org/content/primary-care-physician-leadership-top-ranked-us-hospitals&quot;>;underrepresented in the realms of health care leadership&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transformational changes to primary care will require leadership with holistic training, a clear vision, an insider&#39;s perspective, and skin in the game. PCPs are &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/early/2022/05/19/leader-2022-000591.abstract&quot;>;uniquely positioned to lead&lt;/a>; this change. They are the Swiss Army Knives of medicine, offering an increasingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cfp.ca/content/68/11/801&quot;>;rare generalist perspective, requiring strong communication skills, and a community-focused&lt;/a>; approach to care delivery. Not only are they responsible for managing day-to-day concerns for their patients, they also coordinate care across specialties and organizations for those who may have medically complex diagnoses. These clinicians are accustomed to leading teams every day to care for their patients, and must be adaptable, thoughtful, and flexible, given their vast breadth of clinical responsibilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, it is paradoxical that those best poised to lead are often reluctant to do so. In fact, many physicians are not only &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/healthcare-network/2014/sep/01/nhs-leadership-doctors-reluctant-manage-lead&quot;>;reluctant&lt;/a>; but &lt;em>;averse&lt;/em>; to taking on leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We interviewed PCPs in leadership roles to better understand what they believe prevents so many other physicians from pursuing such positions. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.lww.com/jhmonline/Abstract/2022/08000/Engaging_Physicians_in_Leadership__Motivations,.6.aspx&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; highlights three key deterrents:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;PCPs viewed leadership roles as a path to losing autonomy and limiting their ability to develop long-term therapeutic relationships with patients — a key reason many physicians chose careers in medicine in the first place.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs associated leadership roles with major resource constraints, evaporating both time and earnings potential.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs lamented the loss of camaraderie with other physicians when taking on leadership roles, feeling that the roles interrupted collaboration with peers and generated uncomfortable conflict.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Despite these concerns, PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Health care organizations who understand and work to address these deterrents will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1097/HMR.0000000000000173&quot;>;quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three ways that health organizations can counteract these disincentives and support PCPs embracing leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Provide the On-Ramp&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs crave system change and personal growth, but often feel disempowered. They see their experience as valuable and want to leverage it to make a positive impact on the health care system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can tap into this motivation by framing leadership as a constructive opportunity to be a change agent. While organizations may not have the ability to alter a &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/05/creative-job-titles-can-energize-workers&quot;>;position&#39;s specific title&lt;/a>;, the job description can be used to reflect openness to an entrepreneurial mindset and an opportunity for improving perceived system deficits. Instead of drafting a typical (and often dry) administrative job description, frame it to emphasize how the role will enact change or address major obstacles in health care. Postings should speak to a PCP&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicfootprints.org/7-top-tips-on-recruiting-doctors-to-non-clinical-or-leadership-roles/&quot;>;adaptability based on the breadth of their training and diversity of practice experience&lt;/a>;, and PCPs should be encouraged to apply.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By using the frustration PCPs experience with the status quo and their frontline experience, health care organizations can promote vacant or novel leadership roles as opportunities to expand the impact on patients and to garner a broader scope of knowledge and expertise for PCPs identified as having leadership interest or potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Role Design and Definition&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs want to grow and develop professionally, but our study showed that they also identified clear disadvantages in taking on leadership roles. They identified the least attractive aspect of leading, in a word, as “loss.” They feared the loss of autonomy, time, close patient relationships, and camaraderie with peers. This can be due, in part, to their exposure to disappointing experiences observed in peers who have assumed leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can help mitigate this with the use of strategic &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/why-managers-design-jobs-to-be-more-boring-than-they-need-to-be&quot;>;job design&lt;/a>;, where organizations create an optimal job role, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>;, which allows PCPs to define and customize their role themselves. These two complementary pieces of the puzzle yield large gains in employee satisfaction and fulfillment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When organizations realize that fear of loss is a major barrier, they are better positioned to design purposeful and motivating work for PCPs taking on leadership roles. To address the concern for loss of autonomy, the role should be intentionally constructed to allow PCPs the agency to make decisions per their expertise. For those apprehensive about losing time, the role can be devised to encourage a flexible approach in how goals are achieved, including the freedom to decide how they will balance their clinical responsibilities with their new leadership role. In order to address concerns about losing relationships, organizations must provide opportunities for leaders to meet with their colleagues in informal settings and encourage leaders to continue to be actively engaged as a member of their clinical team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Empowering PCPs to engage in job crafting allows them to adjust aspects of the job to suit individual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-job-crafting-how-to-do-it-work-satisfaction-2022-6&quot;>;interests, values, and passions&lt;/a>;, making them more likely to be&lt;a href=&quot;https://positiveorgs.bus.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/What-is-Job-Crafting-and-Why-Does-it-Matter1.pdf&quot;>; engaged and more likely to thrive&lt;/a>; at work, while being successful in their leadership role. PCPs can independently alter the &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/what-job-crafting-looks-like&quot;>;type and scope of tasks; relationships and with whom they work; and how to think&lt;/a>;, communicate about, or conceive of the job. When PCPs have some degree of ownership and authority over how the job is defined, they will have the opportunity to include more of their passion points, while also thoughtfully reducing those aspects of the job that are seen as pain points.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Tools, Training, and Mentorship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs may want system change and growth, but they also need the tools, training, and mentorship to be successful. In most cases, PCPs &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/most-doctors-have-little-or-no-management-training-and-thats-a-problem&quot;>;aren&#39;t taught finance, accounting, management, or leadership skills&lt;/a>; in medical school, nor is there an emphasis on systems operations, despite the fact that, as physicians enter residency, they immediately begin leading medical teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are stark contrasts, both operationally and culturally, between &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/04/turning-doctors-into-leaders&quot;>;business and medicine&lt;/a>;. Executives and health administrators should provide opportunities for PCPs to cross-train with current administrators and to have access to mentors who can help with the transition. Providing resources to support the transition into leadership can help highly qualified and motivated PCPs avoid the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/robertpearl/2016/02/04/five-reasons-why-even-the-best-of-physicians-may-fail-as-leaders/?sh=1c79323bce22&quot;>;common pitfalls than can derail&lt;/a>; their ability to influence others and be successful in their expanded role. This may include offering or supporting continuing medical education (CME) or credentialing opportunities that feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mgma.com/practice-resources/human-resources/the-importance-of-physician-leadership-education&quot;>;management and leadership skills building&lt;/a>;, partnering with institutions of higher education to create pathways into &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.nejmcareercenter.org/article/eyeing-physician-career-boost-via-formal-business-education/&quot;>;graduate business or policy programs&lt;/a>;, or engaging with organizations that specialize in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.physicianleaders.org/about&quot;>;physician leadership training&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having PCPs in leadership roles has never been more important. Without a highly functioning and sustainable primary care system, all health care in the US will suffer. If we want a system that promotes effective and sustainable primary care, PCPs need to be involved in co-designing that system and leading change. Ultimately, this will benefit the entire health care system, and all of us who will, at any stage of our lives, depend on it for our own care and that of our families and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Nail Your Presentation to the Board]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_29_1296672467-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;sturti/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The boardroom is a distinct forum that requires a different type of presentation and preparation. In this article, the author outlines three practices every business leader should embrace to enhance their board presentations: 1) Start with a governing thesis: a big idea or perspective that captures the main point of the discussion. Presentations that start this way leave the audience with a compelling message. 2) Understand that the CEO is not the target audience. A board presentation has to provide some quick refreshers on the operating environment and &amp;#8212; more importantly &amp;#8212; identify the biggest problems that need fixing. 3) Steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback. Instead of concluding remarks that restate key business results, share two or three important ideas that will drive future success and concerns that could benefit from director input. The goal: Get the board&amp;#8217;s validation or critiques of a proposed course of action. The result, invariably, is a mix of candid feedback and intelligent, probing questions that create thoughtful board engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-ways-to-nail-your-presentation-to-the-board?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For most executives, even those at the most senior level, a presentation to the board of directors is the most demanding test of leadership communications. Very few succeed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Conversations with more than 100 public and private boards directors over the last decade reveal that dissatisfaction with presentations is nearly universal. PowerPoint decks are too long, too granular, or simply uninformative, they report.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet the feedback most senior executives receive — “Make it crisper,” “Fewer slides,” “Don&#39;t get caught up in operational details,” or even “More details, fewer headlines” — is often generic and unhelpful. Operators are told they are insufficiently strategic; strategic leaders are criticized for having insufficient operational depth. Both directors and presenter leave frustrated.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, the advice offered by professional speaking coaches is just as likely to lead senior executives astray. “Enhance vocal delivery,” “Use fewer bullet points,” “Tell a story,” or similar well-worn coaching points are rooted in the belief that a board presentation is simply a matter of stagecraft — a variation of a keynote presentation to a customer audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This counsel reveals a misunderstanding about the purpose and value of board meetings. The boardroom is a distinct forum that requires a different type of presentation and preparation. It demands elevated exchanges that leverage both the knowledge of senior leaders and the objectivity of seasoned directors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having coached executives preparing board-level presentations for more than 15 years — including senior leaders auditioning to become the next CEO — I have concluded that the executive&#39;s most important task is to share their thinking about the business they lead. The goal is not just to report the results of the last quarter. (Directors can read that on their own.) Instead, the senior leader should engage the board by discussing the most pressing challenges they face and how they intend to respond.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While each board has unique needs shaped by the company&#39;s operating environment, below I suggest three practices every business leader should embrace to enhance their board presentations — and their own value within the upper levels of the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Bring a compelling message.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The senior executive who arrives in the board room has typically submitted a set of slides well in advance that has been carefully vetted by the CEO and the legal team. In most cases, directors will have already studied the material, or at least flipped through the main points. What, then, is the purpose of the 10 to 30-minute slot that has been allotted to the nervous presenter?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rushing through a slide review might be useful as a quick refresher, but it neither deepens the board&#39;s understanding of the topic nor showcases the leadership skills of the executive. Instead, every presentation should start with a governing thesis: a big idea or perspective that captures the main point of the discussion. Presentations that start this way leave the audience with a compelling message.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Anne Mulcahy, who has served on multiple boards, including J&amp;amp;J, Target, LPL Financial, and Williams-Sonoma, has felt frustrated by the executives who want to convey too much data and information with a series of dense slides. “It almost seems like the objective is to demonstrate how much they know about their business, she says. “It has the opposite outcome. Directors don&#39;t know what the point of the presentation is supposed to be.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By contrast, a “thesis mindset” forces the presenter to confront the future rather than just reciting the facts of the past. The thesis-driven board presentation doesn&#39;t need to be an audacious proposal or a request for more funding. But it ought to frame an issue that requires board attention. At a minimum, the governing thesis tells directors: This is where I see my part of the company going. That idea can&#39;t be slipped into slide 19. It has to be stated unambiguously and boldly at the outset. At the very least, it provides insurance against off-topic interruptions or mid-presentation dozing.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Understand that the CEO is not the target audience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;By the time they are asked to present to the board, a member of a senior leadership team has had plenty of practice leading discussions with the CEO. They may even be very comfortable updating their boss, in an informal way, with little preparation. Unfortunately, bringing the same mindset and habits to the boardroom is a crucial mistake.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“I am always struck by how often business unit leaders come to the boardroom and direct their talk to their boss, rather than the directors assembled around the table,” said Scott Miller, who has been serving on public and private company boards for more than two decades. Miller&#39;s point is not merely a criticism of presentation style, but a recognition that senior officers rarely consider the needs of directors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The board of directors is a unique audience with no comparison to the groups most executives regularly engage. They are not customers who need to be sold. And they are not true business colleagues, where strategy alignment and deep familiarity with the operational details of the business can be assumed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A public company board may be compromised of business leaders, academics, former CEOs, current financial officers, and executives who bring expertise from entirely different industries. As a rule, their range of knowledge about the company and any given topic will vary greatly. Some have been serving on the board for well over a decade; others may be attending their third or fourth meeting. There is also an unspoken (and sometimes unknowable) hierarchy on the board, with its own unstated group of alliances and range of authority.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ron Sugar, the lead director of Uber who also serves on the boards of Apple, Chevron, and Amgen, advises that the job of the presenter “is to fly at the right altitude” in the boardroom: “Dumb it down too much, and you risk insulting the directors. On the other hand, no board wants to be a working group. They want to understand what issues need to be on their radar screen.” He suggests planning to use half the allotted time so that the main point is reached quickly and discussion can follow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sugar&#39;s advice is sound. A board presentation has to provide some quick refreshers on the operating environment and — more importantly — identify the biggest problems that need fixing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These problems will be familiar to the CEO (who should never be taken by surprise in the boardroom). The directors, however, need both a reminder of the core issues in an executive&#39;s portfolio (talent, operations, regulation, or a particular geography) along with looming challenges. Too many executives miss the opportunity to frame problems in the right way — and make their presentations far less engaging than they should be.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The purpose of presenting challenges is not to frighten the board but to enlighten them and engage them in the operational and strategic questions that preoccupy the person presenting the material.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/how-to-increase-the-boards-impact-and-value&quot;>;2022 study&lt;/a>;, EY&#39;s Center for Board Matters found that public company directors felt confident they added value to discussions of capital allocation and succession. But very few felt the top value they delivered came in areas such as revenue growth, innovation, or disruption. Ironically, these latter topics are most frequently what executives are asked to address when they invited into the boardroom.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Effective leaders can help rebalance the value that directors ought to derive from a board meeting by setting up genuine discussions that invite reaction and input. Alas, too many board presentations come to an abrupt conclusion followed by a quick call for “any questions?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Following a presentation, many business unit leaders complain they find themselves falling down a rabbit hole of technical details triggered by an unexpected and mostly irrelevant question from a persistent director. In most instances, the blame is entirely on the presenter. They are ones who failed to set up the right conversation and missed the opportunity to steer the presentation toward getting valuable feedback from the board.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Randy Foutch, the former CEO of Laredo Petroleum, who has sat on many small and large company boards, believes that many executives “miss the opportunity to solicit feedback from the directors with relevant experience.” He has seen so many executives wary of raising questions with directors that they leave directors silent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet driving a sophisticated conversation that promotes “good questions” is the unspoken mandate of robust board presentations. Instead of concluding remarks that restate key business results, a confident executive should share two or three important ideas that will drive future success and concerns that could benefit from director input. In other words, the presenter must sincerely seek out the board&#39;s point of view by posing questions that remain unresolved or business risks that will persist. The goal: Gt the board&#39;s validation or critiques of a proposed course of action. The result, invariably, is a mix of candid feedback and intelligent, probing questions that create thoughtful board engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During an interview, Frank Blake, the former CEO of The Home Depot, described the typical tone of a meeting between an on-the-ground store team and chief executive who has stopped by for a visit. “What the CEO will always hear is some version of: &#39;You&#39;re doing great. We&#39;re doing great. Now leave.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The same tone of forced cordiality — and unproductive feedback — has become the all-too-common standard for board presentations delivered by senior executives. They represent missed opportunities to elevate a company&#39;s board discussions and ensure that both the top team and the directors are getting the greatest intellectual value and leadership insight from every conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Managers Can Make Time for Their Own Development]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_sb10065848cx-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Diamond Sky Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Managers today must balance their day-to-day work with multiple &amp;#8220;ands,&amp;#8221; such as delivering on quarterly objectives &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;thinking strategically. Given these numerous demands, managers tend to deprioritize their own career development. It doesn&amp;#8217;t have to be that way. The more managers take control of their development, the better able they&amp;#8217;ll be to avoid the common career mistakes that will get in the way of their growth. And the more their team members see the positive impact of investing in their career development, the more likely they are to do the same.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-managers-can-make-time-for-their-own-development?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Being a successful manager today is a tough task that requires grappling with multiple “ands”: Supporting team members &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;influencing senior stakeholders; making progress on the day job &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;troubleshooting unexpected problems; delivering on quarterly objectives &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;thinking strategically. In the midst of the “and overload,” it&#39;s not surprising that managers tend to be the least-likely people in an organization to prioritize their own career development.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Through our global work on “squiggly” and nonlinear careers, we support thousands of managers every year who share a sense of frustration that their career development is stalling but struggle to find the time to invest in their own learning. We&#39;ve observed three common career development mistakes managers make and uncovered a few tried-and-tested solutions to help them balance the demands of the day-to-day with investing in their own development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. The Say-Do Development Gap&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our clients often tell us that they find coaching and supporting their team members&#39; career development to be a motivating and enjoyable part of their managerial role — and yet they undervalue the importance of modeling this behavior themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When teams don&#39;t see their manager investing in their own development, it creates a “say-do” development gap, which has a negative ripple effect for both managers and their teams: Team members lose confidence that committing time to their career development is the right thing to do and may even question whether their manager really values continual learning. At the same time, managers miss out on important moments to develop skills and capabilities to improve their performance and support their ambitions for the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Share learning goals&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;One simple and effective way for managers to avoid the say-do development gap is to share their learning goals openly with their teams. Sharing development priorities has multiple benefits. First, it prompts managers to identify what development they want to focus on, and sharing their goals increases accountability. Second, involving team members means that managers are surrounding themselves with more people to support their development and removes the idea that learning from others is linked to levels and hierarchy. Finally, when team members see their managers setting and sticking to development goals, it prompts them to do the same.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a manager who shares a learning goal to increase their internal profile might benefit from a team member spotting an opportunity for them to speak at an event. A manager looking to develop their ability to use data to drive decisions could be supported with feedback from their team members on what they currently do well and what could be better.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When approached in this way, development doesn&#39;t need to be another thing that gets added to a manager&#39;s to-do list; it becomes part of their daily work and is accelerated by the people who work for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. The Bubble Barrier&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;With so many demands on their workdays, it&#39;s understandable that managers rarely spend time on development outside of their organization. The challenge of finding the time and opportunity to learn in different places and with new people often feels insurmountable and falls into the category of “should do” rather than “will do.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Relying on internal-only development results in managers developing a narrow view of the world and limits their learning. And operating in the bubble of internal knowledge and networks means that managers are reenforcing who and what they already know rather than cultivating their curiosity. Managers need to learn beyond the internal bubble so that it doesn&#39;t become a barrier to their growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Knowledge-swap sessions&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;An efficient way to bring the outside in is to approach peers in a non-competing organization to co-host a team development session, where both teams share their expertise with each other. For example, a team with agile expertise could knowledge-swap with a team that has strong communication capabilities. Or an established team in a large organization might spend time with a team from a smaller startup, exchanging insights on innovation in different operating contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-sidebar data-sidebar-alternate=&quot;sidebar&quot;>; &lt;h4>;Example agenda items for knowledge-swap sessions&lt;/h4>; &lt;div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;“What if?” wall:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares an idea or objective they&#39;re working on, and the other organization creates a “what if?” wall of questions to spark new thoughts. For example: What if you were famous for your customer service? What if your product sold twice as much as it does today?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Day in the life:&lt;/strong>; One person from each team describes the reality of a day in their life. This helps create a sense of connection between people, especially when the speaker includes non-work activities. For example: I started my day by taking my five-year-old to the dentist where he decided to scream the place down.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Mistake moments:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares a mistake moment they&#39;ve had and what they learned. This can help teams preempt potential problems and recover quickly when they happen. For example: We were communicating across too many technology platforms and people were getting overwhelmed and missing important information. The team created a communications policy that helps people feel more in control. &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Pride postcards:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares one thing they&#39;re proud from the past few months and how they came together to achieve it. This inspires the other team with the art of the possible and gives them practical insights on how to make it happen. For example: We introduced a new well-being policy for our organization that got featured in the media as an example of best practice. The three things that helped us most were… &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Surprise stories:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares an example of something about their organization or function that might surprise others who aren&#39;t on “the inside.” This gives teams ideas for what they can do differently. For example: In our organization, everyone gets an extra day of holiday on their birthday.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Superpower swaps:&lt;/strong>; Each team shares one of their superpowers and three top tips on how to develop that skill. For example: One of our superpowers is problem-solving, and our three top tips are to use your strengths to solve problems, hold problem-solving hack sessions, and pair people up on problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/article-sidebar>; &lt;p>;These knowledge-swap sessions allow everyone to spend time in a different working world, create new connections, and learn together (which also supports overcoming the say-do gap). The format of a swap session can range from a virtual hour over lunch to a full day in a room. Holding knowledge-swaps gives managers — and their teams — regular opportunities to learn from people outside the organization in a way that&#39;s part of their existing rhythm of work, rather than something extra to squeeze in.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. The Time Trap&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We often hear managers say: “I don&#39;t have time to invest in my development. I&#39;ll get around to it when everything calms down, or when this project has finished, or when I&#39;ve recruited this person, etc.” This way of thinking means keeps many managers stuck in a time trap, which will hold their career back over the long-term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These time traps aren&#39;t a result of managers making excuses — they reflect the reality of the challenges they&#39;re dealing with. The mistake is the hope that one day we&#39;ll magically have more time and fewer things to do. If managers look for the perfect moment to focus on their development, they&#39;re likely to be left waiting and stagnating in their career.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;What to do differently: Manager micro-learning moments&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many people still associate development with formal learning methods like taking a course. But what managers need are small, easy ways to make development part of their day-to-day. Practicing micro-learning moments is a memorable and simple way for managers to kickstart the habit of continual improvement. Effective micro-learning moments usually take less than 10 minutes, and they&#39;re small but significant in their impact, as managers benefit from a compound effect of continual learning over time. Here are a few examples:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Fast feedback:&lt;/strong>; Ask your team members to answer the same fast feedback question: &lt;em>;What three words would you use to describe me at my best? &lt;/em>;This simple question gives managers instant insight into whether their intent is matching their impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;One-minute weekly review:&lt;/strong>; End your week by spending one minute jotting down the answers to these two self-awareness questions: &lt;em>;What has given me the most energy this week? What could have been better this week?&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Strength accelerator: &lt;/strong>;Pick one skill you want to strengthen and identify an action related to either regularity (how could you use that strength more?), range (where else could you use that strength that you don&#39;t today?), or reach (who could you share that strength with?).&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The more managers take control of their development, the better able they&#39;ll be to avoid the career mistakes that will get in the way of their growth. And the more their team members see the positive impact of investing in their career development, the more likely they are to do the same. Helping managers helps everyone succeed in their squiggly careers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Find the Time to Connect with Colleagues When You&rsquo;re Very, Very Busy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_482824941.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HollenderX2/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A consequence of our often never-ending to-do lists at work is the loss of camaraderie among coworkers. While productivity is important, the balance between task completion and taking the time to connect with your team is essential in avoiding burnout and making work more enjoyable. The common misconception is that there simply isn&amp;#8217;t enough hours (or energy) in the day to get your work done and socialize; the reality is that just a quick slack message, coffee run, or group share in the beginning or ending of a meeting are all simple yet impactful acts that require minimal effort and time and thus make the former argument null and void. Studies show that socializing, despite feeling like a daunting task, can be effective in combating mental fatigue by energizing us. Increased energy improves performance and therefore proves socializing to be even more beneficial than the head down work one might prioritize over fostering those connections with colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re feeling behind on tasks and pressed against deadlines, catching up with and connecting with colleagues is about the last thing you feel like doing. You just want to put your head down, check off tasks on your to-do list, and get things done.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are absolutely times when you should put on blinders and focus solely on your tactical objectives. But exclusively interacting in a transactional manner with your coworkers could cause you to lose any sense of personal connection, especially if you work remotely. By taking even a few minutes each day to foster a sense of rapport at work, you could unlock the key to a &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/to-be-happier-at-work-invest-more-in-your-relationships&quot;>;greater sense of purpose and well-being, reduce burnout, and even improve your performance.&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So how do you make time for people without feeling more stressed and overwhelmed? As a time management coach, I&#39;ve seen that with just a little more intention, you can make much more meaningful connections without investing much time.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Chat in One-on-One Meetings&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you already have one-on-one meetings scheduled with your team, take a few minutes at the start of the discussion to find out how they&#39;re doing before jumping to the business agenda. You don&#39;t need to spend the whole time on personal updates, but even reserving five minutes to ask about their recent vacation, find out if their mom is out of the hospital, or to see how they&#39;re recovering from surgery can make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can use the same strategy for one-on-one meetings with colleagues who you regularly work with on projects. Depending on the length of the meeting and how much you need to cover, you may not have time to catch up each time. But if every few meetings you use a few minutes at the beginning or end to talk about more than the projects at hand, you can strengthen those ties. This could include bonding over your excitement about a particular sports team, talking about your families, or discussing anything else that gives you space to connect beyond a one-dimensional, task-oriented level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If remembering details about people&#39;s lives doesn&#39;t come naturally to you, make a private note in your calendar with memory cues, such as asking them about their new puppy, about their kids&#39; latest extracurriculars, or how their side venture is going.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Encourage Group Sharing During Meetings&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a large team meeting, there won&#39;t be much space for personal catchups. But if you have a smaller team, it may be appropriate to take some time on a weekly or monthly basis for updates. This could be as simple as a quick share at the beginning of a meeting about a recent event, such as attending an industry conference. This can also happen organically if you work in person and have a specific forum designated for it: for example, if you bring in coffee and bagels on Monday mornings and have breakfast together, or if there&#39;s a Friday afternoon happy hour. Even 15 to 20 minutes of unstructured talk can lead to a greater sense of team engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re part of a remote or hybrid team, it may be harder to connect organically. Consider hosting a virtual happy hour or have a few people share during a team meeting. Just keep these updates short so that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/irl/highs-lows-weekend-tiktok/&quot;>;the highs and lows don&#39;t turn into a viral meme&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Turn Breaks into Informal Social Time &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Grab a bite to eat with colleagues over your lunch break. Your meeting schedule may not allow a proper lunch break every day, but blocking out at least a couple of days a week where you&#39;re not multi-tasking at your computer can make your lunch more enjoyable and more social. This could be planned out in advance, where you meet up with someone in another department who you don&#39;t get to see often, or it could be more informal with a team member who works right by you. If you&#39;d like to have a relaxed approach, simply ask someone if they want to join you when you&#39;re heading out the door or reheating your leftovers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://creativecloud.adobe.com/discover/article/a-science-backed-guide-to-taking-truly-restful-breaks&quot;>;Social breaks can also effectively combat mental fatigue&lt;/a>; in the mid-afternoon slump and help you feel refreshed for the final work stretch before you&#39;re done for the day. When you notice your eye lids drooping and your head bobbing, stand up and get moving. If you&#39;re in the office, this is an excellent time to walk the halls and connect with a few people or invite someone to grab a cup of coffee. Similar to lunch, you can stop by to chat with members of your own team or drop in on a different department. The movement and conversation will wake you up and serve as a time of connection and potentially internal networking. If you&#39;re working remotely, send a friendly Slack message to a colleague, rather than turning to scroll social media. Even if they&#39;re too busy to respond, they may offer to catch up with you later.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Make Calls During Your Commute &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you commute into the office or travel for business, some of your travel times could offer an ideal opportunity to catch up in an informal manner with colleagues. One of my clients who was an executive with a packed meeting schedule used his drive home to reach out and have informal conversations with his leaders. This helped him get a more personal view on their thoughts and concerns, as the company was going through a major transition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re on the road, you can call from airports, Ubers, or hotels or send messages when you&#39;re waiting in lines or on trains. Even a five- to 10-minute conversation can increase your rapport and, most importantly, show that you care.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Take Advantage of Virtual Messaging &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re working exclusively remotely, the options for informal social connection will be limited. In these cases, you can simply send a quick chat message or text asking how someone is doing or share a quick update with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These conversations can end up taking a lot of time if you&#39;re not conscious of how long they go, so you&#39;ll want to limit how frequently you engage in purely social messaging. But reaching out a few times a week can be fun and help you feel connected. Consider pinging people at natural times when you would have said “Hello!” to coworkers in the past, such as when you first get to your desk, around lunch, or when you&#39;re waiting for a meeting to start.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It can be a challenge to find time to talk with people when you barely feel like you have time for completing tasks and projects. But there are benefits to connecting with your coworkers. Rather than keeping your head down and focusing only on work, find those pockets of time in your schedule where you can thoughtfully connect with colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Prepare Your Culture for AI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_1468369205.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;gremlin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The platform shift to AI is well underway. And while it holds the promise of transforming work and giving organizations a competitive advantage, realizing those benefits isn&amp;#8217;t possible without a culture that embraces curiosity, failure, and learning. Leaders are uniquely positioned to foster this culture within their organizations today in order to set their teams up for success in the future. When paired with the capabilities of AI, this kind of culture will unlock a better future of work for everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As business leaders, today we find ourselves in a place that&#39;s all too familiar: the unfamiliar. Just as we steered our teams through the shift to remote and flexible work, we&#39;re now on the verge of another seismic shift: AI. And like the shift to flexible work, priming an organization to embrace AI will hinge first and foremost on culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The pace and volume of work has increased exponentially, and we&#39;re all struggling under the weight of it. Leaders and employees are eager for AI to lift the burden. That&#39;s the key takeaway from our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/will-ai-fix-work&quot;>;2023 Work Trend Index&lt;/a>;, which surveyed 31,000 people across 31 countries and analyzed trillions of aggregated productivity signals in Microsoft 365, along with labor market trends on LinkedIn.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nearly two-thirds of employees surveyed told us they don&#39;t have enough time or energy to do their job. The cause of this drain is something we identified in the report as digital debt: the influx of data, emails, and chats has outpaced our ability to keep up. Employees today spend nearly 60% of their time communicating, leaving only 40% of their time for creating and innovating. In a world where creativity is the new productivity, digital debt isn&#39;t just an inconvenience — it&#39;s a liability.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI promises to address that liability by allowing employees to focus on the most meaningful work. Increasing productivity, streamlining repetitive tasks, and increasing employee well-being are the top three things leaders want from AI, according to our research. Notably, amid fears that AI will replace jobs, reducing headcount was last on the list.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Becoming an AI-powered organization will require us to work in entirely new ways. As leaders, there are three steps we can take today to get our cultures ready for an AI-powered future:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Choose curiosity over fear&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI marks a new interaction model between humans and computers. Until now, the way we&#39;ve interacted with computers has been similar to how we interact with a calculator: We ask a question or give directions, and the computer provides an answer. But with AI, the computer will be more like a copilot. We&#39;ll need to develop a new kind of chemistry together, learning when and how to ask questions and about the importance of fact-checking responses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fear is a natural reaction to change, so it&#39;s understandable for employees to feel some uncertainty about what AI will mean for their work. Our research found that while 49% of employees are concerned AI will replace their jobs, the promise of AI outweighs the threat: 70% of employees are more than willing to delegate to AI to lighten their workloads.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re rarely served by operating from a place of fear. By fostering a culture of curiosity, we can empower our people to understand how AI works, including its capabilities and its shortcomings. This understanding starts with firsthand experience. Encourage employees to put curiosity into action by experimenting (safely and securely) with new &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.microsoft.com/reinventing-productivity/&quot;>;AI tools&lt;/a>;, such as AI-powered &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bing.com/search?form=MY0291&amp;amp;OCID=MY0291&amp;amp;q=Bing+AI&amp;amp;showconv=1&quot;>;search&lt;/a>;, intelligent writing assistance, or smart calendaring, to name just a few. Since every role and function will have different ways to use and benefit from AI, challenge them to rethink how AI could improve or transform processes as they get familiar with the tools. From there, employees can begin to unlock new ways of working.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Embrace failure&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI will change nearly every job, and nearly every work pattern can benefit from some degree of AI augmentation or automation. As leaders, now is the time to encourage our teams to bring creativity to reimagining work, adopting a test-and-learn strategy to find ways AI can best help meet the needs of the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI won&#39;t get it right every time, but even when it&#39;s wrong, it&#39;s &lt;em>;usefully&lt;/em>; wrong. It moves you at least one step forward from a blank slate, so you can jump right into the critical thinking work of reviewing, editing, or augmenting. It will take time to learn these new patterns of work and identify which processes need to change and how. But if we create a culture where experimentation and learning are viewed as a prerequisite to progress, we&#39;ll get there much faster.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As leaders, we have a responsibility to create the right environment for failure so that our people are empowered to experiment to uncover how AI can fit into their workflows. In my experience, that includes celebrating wins as well as sharing lessons learned in order to help keep each other from wasting time learning the same lesson twice. Both formally and informally, carve out space for people to share knowledge — for example, by crowdsourcing a prompt guidebook within your department or making AI tips a standing agenda item in your monthly all-staff meetings. Operating with agility will be a foundational tenet of AI-powered organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Become a learn-it-all&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I often hear concerns that AI will be a crutch, offering shortcuts and workarounds that ultimately diminish innovation and engagement. In my mind, the potential for AI is so much bigger than that, and it will become a competitive advantage for those who use it thoughtfully. Those will become your most engaged and innovative employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The value you get from AI is only as good as what you put in. Simple questions will result in simple answers. But sophisticated, thought-provoking questions will result in more complex analysis and bigger ideas. The value will shift from employees who have all the right answers to employees who know how to ask the right questions. Organizations of the future will place a premium on analytical thinkers and problem-solvers who can effectively reason over AI-generated content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At Microsoft, we believe a learn-it-all mentality will get us much farther than a know-it-all one. And while the learning curve of using AI can be daunting, it&#39;s a muscle that has to be built over time — and that we should start strengthening today. When I talk to leaders about how to achieve this across their companies and teams, I tell them three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Establish guardrails to help people experiment safely and responsibly. Which tools do you encourage employees to use, and what data is — and isn&#39;t — appropriate to input. What guidelines do they need to follow around fact-checking, reviewing, and editing?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Learning to work with AI will need to be a continuous process, not a one-time training. Infuse learning opportunities into your rhythm of business and keep employees up to date with the latest resources. For example, one team might block off Friday afternoons for learning, while another has monthly “office hours” for AI Q&amp;amp;A and troubleshooting. And think beyond traditional courses or resources. How can peer-to-peer knowledge sharing, such as lunch and learns or a digital hotline, play a role so people can learn from each other?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Embrace the need for change management. Being intentional and programmatic will be crucial for successfully adopting AI. Identify goals and metrics for success, and select AI champions or pilot program leads to help bring the vision to life. Different functions and disciplines will have different needs and challenges when it comes to AI, but one shared need will be for structure and support as we all transition to a new way of working.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The platform shift to AI is well underway. And while it holds the promise of transforming work and giving organizations a competitive advantage, realizing those benefits isn&#39;t possible without a culture that embraces curiosity, failure, and learning. As leaders, we&#39;re uniquely positioned to foster this culture within our organizations today in order to set our teams up for success in the future. When paired with the capabilities of AI, this kind of culture will unlock a better future of work for everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Commit to the LGBTQ+ Community When Hate Is on the Rise]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/commit-to-the-lgbtq-community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_512010335_1421562884_1385767484_109438804_1148780239-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/william87/ MoMo Productions/FG Trade/David Arky/Yifei Fang/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As a dramatic spike in anti-LGBTQ+ sentiment and legislation occurs in the United States and in other countries around the world, there&amp;#8217;sa growing disconnect between well-meaning executives and their constituents. Just as LGBTQ+ employees and communities, civil rights advocates, and socially conscious consumers are looking to employers to take action, many companies are walking back their previous support. However, a majority of consumers continue to expect that corporations maintain their commitment through action, and continue to reward companies that do so with their support and patronage. Amid a hostile social and political environment, companies must root their actions in their organization&amp;#8217;s purpose, value proposition, and values, to embed pro-LGBTQ+ support in their organization&amp;#8217;s identity for the long run. The author recommends three steps to do this: 1) Connect LGBTQ+ inclusion to your customer base, operations, and values; 2) Collaboratively design initiatives that benefit LGBTQ+ communities; and 3) Take a purposeful stand and defend it.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/commit-to-the-lgbtq-community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/commit-to-the-lgbtq-community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“This organization has long been an ally to the LGBTQ+ community,” an executive stated. “But lately, with the political climate the way it is, things that wouldn&#39;t have been controversial to do or say even five years ago are getting a lot more pushback than they used to. How do we show we care?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“This organization says it&#39;s an ally to our community,” an employee said. “But lately, in the face of increasing hostility against LGBTQ+ people, we&#39;re at our breaking point, and our leaders are saying nothing. Why won&#39;t they defend us? Is it because they&#39;ve never cared?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a DEI strategist, I hear these kinds of comments often from people at the organizations I work with. They&#39;re not unusual. These sentiments represent the growing disconnect between well-meaning executives and LGBTQ+ employees, consumers, and communities as corporate involvement in LGBTQ+ causes has evolved. Consumers and workers are increasingly holding corporations to &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/06/were-entering-the-age-of-corporate-social-justice&quot;>;higher standards&lt;/a>;, making their patronage conditional on brands&#39; internal and external treatment of LGBTQ+ people aligning with their glossy marketing, and calling them out for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/life/a43713768/rainbow-washing/&quot;>;rainbow-washing&lt;/a>; when they fail. At the same time, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://acleddata.com/2022/11/23/update-fact-sheet-anti-lgbt-mobilization-in-the-united-states/&quot;>;dramatic spike&lt;/a>; in anti-LGBTQ+ social and political movements, the passage of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.erininthemorning.com/p/may-anti-trans-legislative-risk-map&quot;>;regressive laws&lt;/a>;, hate speech, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/jun/07/lgbtq-violence-protest-glendale-unified-school-district&quot;>;acts of physical violence&lt;/a>; in the US — alongside a related increase in right-wing extremism, authoritarianism, and anti-democratic beliefs around the world — has driven a new wave of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/newshour/nation/online-right-wing-extremists-amp-up-anti-lgbtq-rhetoric-during-pride-month&quot;>;campaigns&lt;/a>; targeting LGBTQ+ communities and the brands and employers that support them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This combination of factors means that now, just as LGBTQ+ employees and communities, civil rights advocates, and socially conscious consumers are looking to employers to take action to support their previous pro-LGBTQ+ commitments, some employers are &lt;a href=&quot;https://nypost.com/2023/05/04/anheuser-busch-ceo-disavows-bud-light-dylan-mulvaney-ads/&quot;>;disavowing their LGBTQ+ partnerships&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2023/05/24/1177963864/target-pride-month-lgbtq-products-threats&quot;>;removing Pride-themed merchandise&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2023/06/23/starbucks-union-workers-are-striking-after-accusing-firm-of-banning-pride-decorations/?sh=371a510a511b&quot;>;forbidding Pride decorations&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders who worry that taking action to support LGBTQ+ communities is now “too risky” can take comfort in knowing that an overwhelming majority of consumers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/01/consumers-say-companies-should-support-lgbtq-community-glaad-survey.html&quot;>;70%, according to a recent survey by GLAAD&lt;/a>; — expect them to take a clear stance on the side of civil rights, equity, and inclusion by supporting LGBTQ+ people. There are well-documented business benefits as well: A large majority of consumers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/13/workers-consumers-prefer-pro-lgbtq-brands-glaad-study.html&quot;>;whether or not they are LGBTQ+ themselves&lt;/a>;, are more likely to purchase from pro-LGBTQ+ companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite these clear benefits, leaders may still feel unsure how to future-proof their commitment to LGBTQ+ inclusion in a hostile social and political environment. The answer lies in rooting their actions in their organization&#39;s purpose, value proposition, and values, to embed pro-LGBTQ+ support in their organization&#39;s identity for the long run.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Connect LGBTQ+ inclusion to your customer base, operations, and values. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While most consumers now expect brands to take stances on social and political issues, it&#39;s not as easy as making a throwaway social media post or a blatantly profit-motivated marketing campaign. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/data/brands-creating-change/&quot;>;study looking into brand communication on social issues&lt;/a>; found that consumers find it most appropriate for brands to take a stance when it relates to the brand&#39;s values, impacts the business, or impacts the brand&#39;s employees or consumers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Future-proofing LGBTQ+ inclusion will require proactive effort to understand the needs of your LGBTQ+ constituents, as well as your non-LGBTQ+ customers and clients&#39; perspective on LGBTQ+ issues. You&#39;ll need to then understand how your operations impact LGBTQ+ communities to find the unique overlaps and opportunities to act. If you have LGBTQ+ customers, you might develop products that meet their needs. If you engage LGBTQ+ content creators or artists, you might tap into their talent for mutual benefit. If you have LGBTQ+ users or clients, you might solicit their feedback to develop a more inclusive product.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To lock these efforts in, you&#39;ll need to reframe them in terms of your organization&#39;s deeply held mission, purpose, and values. If your organization is deeply committed to dignity, you can frame LGBTQ+ inclusion as part and parcel to protecting the dignity of all your customers and employees. If your organization is deeply committed to bravery, you can frame LGBTQ+ inclusion as recognizing bravery against persecution and being brave enough yourselves as an organization to speak.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Put together, this means that organizations able to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deloitte.com/global/en/about/people/social-responsibility/lgbt-inclusion.html&quot;>;articulate&lt;/a>; the place of LGBTQ+ inclusion explicitly as it relates to their core purpose, value proposition, and values will build a strong foundation for their efforts that is less likely to waver when the political winds shift.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Collaboratively design initiatives that benefit LGBTQ+ communities. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As ubiquitous as brands&#39; Pride Month campaigns have become, simply putting a product into the hands of an LGBTQ+ influencer and having them read a script doesn&#39;t particularly resonate with LGBTQ+ people. Done poorly, it can come across as a shallow publicity stunt to profit off the LGBTQ+ community without meaningfully benefiting it. In addition, when these initiatives appear to be disconnected from an organization&#39;s purpose or value proposition, your non-LGBTQ+ constituents can feel like your social stances are arbitrary — opening the door for those who might be prejudiced against LGBTQ+ people to criticize your stance as “telling them what to think.”&lt;span>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The problem you can realistically solve is &lt;em>;not &lt;/em>;the range of beliefs held by consumers, employees, or other constituents, but rather the alignment of social cause, organizational purpose, and constituent needs. When initiatives or partnerships hit all three — say, a Pride Month initiative that was driven by customer demand and designed with customer input to address an unmet need related to the business&#39;s core service — even if constituents don&#39;t belong to the community directly centered, they are likely to support or at worst, feel neutral toward the initiative.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Opportunistic marketing ploys spitballed by a consultant during a 30-minute brainstorm are out. Designing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/lucianapaulise/2022/10/11/how-to-promote-inclusion--virgin-atlantic-removes-gendered-uniforms/?sh=74cb1f3355dd&quot;>;successful initiatives&lt;/a>; in this vein requires deep collaboration with constituents both inside and outside the LGBTQ+ community to ensure that the initiative creates value for the target community, to align it with the organization&#39;s purpose and identity, and to test if it will land in the intended way with audiences. The more constituents can drive and inform this process — whether through advisory boards, focus groups, or other participatory methods — the more likely that the initiatives will successfully meet an unmet need, create value, and resonate.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Take a purposeful stand and defend it. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once you&#39;ve homed in on the needs of the community and the opportunities available for your organization, take decisive and purposeful action with the full weight of your brand behind it. For every initiative and campaign you run, tell a story that illustrates and reinforces the connections between the social cause you&#39;re championing, your organization&#39;s purpose, and your constituent&#39;s needs. The goal is for any person familiar with your brand to say, “Of &lt;em>;course &lt;/em>;they would champion this cause.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What if your pro-LGBTQ+ initiative is targeted by detractors, whether through a boycott, social media campaign, or even in-person intimidation? Running through the steps of aligning your inclusion initiatives with your organization&#39;s purpose, value proposition, core values, and constituent needs isn&#39;t meant to prevent critique, but instead to prepare for it. Preparing in this way gives leaders everything they need to stand strong in the face of critique, and respond: “We designed this initiative in conversation with our global community of customers and employees and are confident that not only does it celebrate Pride Month, but also embodies our deeply held convictions and furthers our core mission. We&#39;re proud to be creating this impact and invite you to learn more about why this initiative matters to us. And while we invite respectful disagreement if you feel like we&#39;ve missed the mark, we won&#39;t tolerate harassment or violence against our team members or other customers.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, it&#39;s possible for organizations to still get things wrong and retract their initiatives with an apology. But if they do, it&#39;s because they made a mistake somewhere along the process of aligning with their purpose, value proposition, and values, understanding their constituents, and meeting their needs — not because they were pressured into it by threats of violence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Use this approach as a litmus test. As the social landscape changes, the expectations facing brands, organizations, and leaders will change as well. Today&#39;s “best practice” may very well be ineffective or even counterproductive 10, five, or even one year from now. Your DEI, ESG, and other social-issue-related initiatives should adapt with the times, but the strength of your commitment should not. To preserve and strengthen the trust your employees, customers, and other constituents place in your organization, use this purpose- and value-driven approach as a litmus test to create, revisit, and revise your initiatives. In action, all it takes is answering these questions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;How does this issue impact our purpose for existing, and the constituents we serve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How might a stance on this issue strengthen our purpose for existing, and benefit our constituents?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How do our constituents want us to act on this issue that centers our purpose and creates value for them?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;One consequence of answering these questions is that your organization &lt;em>;will not &lt;/em>;end up taking stances on every social issue, nor will it engage to the same degree on every cause or current event. It might even receive critique for its inaction in these cases. But when it does take a stance, it will be in strong alignment with its purpose, its value proposition, its values, and its employees, customers, and other constituents. When it acts, it will be with the full weight of its organizational identity and resources, without wavering even in the face of pushback.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This latest wave of anti-LGBTQ+ hostility is alarming, but if your organization holds steady to its purpose, operations, and the people it serves, you&#39;ll hold true to your commitment to LGBTQ+ inclusion every month out of the year.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>