<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/<item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Keep Your Audience Focused During a Presentation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_1029427796.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;AndreyPopov/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;抓住并保持受众的注意力对于沟通成功至关重要。你要说的很重要，所以给自己最好的机会向观众传达你的信息，首先获得关注，但更重要的是维持它。在这篇文章中，作者概述了三种技术——身体、心理和语言——吸引观众。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your- Audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during -a-presentation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;注意力是我们最宝贵的商品。在当今快节奏的世界中，数字设备始终在线，媒体昼夜不停，吸引观众的注意力对于我们的沟通成功至关重要。由于有如此多的干扰因素争夺我们的时间，我们必须首先积极寻求并获得观众的注意力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，仅仅吸引耳朵和眼睛是不够的。获得关注只是第一战；保留它完全是另一个挑战。这就是为什么聪明的沟通者不仅积极采用各种方法来吸引注意力，而且还努力维持注意力。持续关注就是我所说的“参与度”。如果您能够吸引观众，他们就会保持专注并且不会分心。另外，您将能够更好地向他们展示您的主题的相关性和重要性。为此，这里有三种吸引观众的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;吸引观众的三种方法&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;身体参与&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;其中身体走，大脑也会跟着走。任何能让观众用身体做某事的事情都会产生参与感。无论您是进行现场推介或演示，还是进行虚拟会议，请考虑如何在活动中融入实际参与。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，您可以让人们观看视频、阅读文章讲义、点击屏幕上的某些内容、举手或使用虚拟反应。所有这些都要求您的受众成为您沟通的参与者，而不仅仅是观察者。一个简单的邀请“转向你旁边的人并向他们打招呼”或“阅读幻灯片上的内容并分享你的想法”就可以让他们参与进来。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;精神参与&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;通过促进认知参与来对抗观众走神或多任务的倾向。可以通过三种简单的方法来做到这一点： 在整个演示过程中提出问题；纳入挑衅性的陈述、数据和统计数据；并引入巧妙的类比。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你提出问题时，人们几乎会自动开始考虑他们的答案，从而将他们从被动倾听转变为积极参与。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;挑衅性陈述或&lt;a href =&quot;/2020/02/present-your-data-like-a-pro&quot;>;令人信服的数据&lt;/a>;激发好奇心并鼓励观众在内部提出自己的问题。例如，如果您试图证明培训部门的员工人数合理，您可以说：“通过更好地培训用户，可以消除我们 30% 的客户服务单。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;类比是我们比较什么的地方。我们知道我们不知道的事情；换句话说，我们&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/finding-the-right-metaphor-for-your-presentation&quot;>;用熟悉的来解释不熟悉的&lt;/a>;。类比可以让我们积极思考，从而引发参与。需要注意的是：当您使用类比时，请确保它们是人们可以轻松联想到的类比。过度依赖体育隐喻或人们无法理解或理解的复杂比较，将不利于您的参与和加深理解的目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;语言参与&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;语言参与是指使用包容性文字、穿越时空的语言以及对共同观点或经历的引用。包容性措辞意味着邀请人们参与您的沟通。例如，当我们听到自己的名字以及听到“你”这个词时，我们本能地就会振作起来。提及参与者的名字，并使用诸如“正如你所知......”或“你可能想知道......”或“今天，你将学习......”这样的短语&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;时间旅行语言将人们从现在带入现实未来或过去。您可以使用“想象……”或“如果可以……会怎样”或“想象这个……”等短语来带人们进入未来。 “记住何时……”或“回想何时……”会带人们回到过去。通过共同的经历或信念将人们联系起来，创造共同点。例如，突出公司的使命和价值观或引用以前的共同经历可以吸引人们，就像您和您的朋友或家人分享旧故事和笑话一样。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;结合参与技巧&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您不需要一次只依赖一种参与技术。相反，将它们结合起来以增加和增强它们的效果。例如，民意调查是让大脑和身体参与三重活动的好方法。它适用于一个简单的民意调查问题，“通过举手，您认为以下哪一个是 XYZ 中最重要的元素？”在这一问题中部署的身体、心理和语言参与技巧的协同作用使与会者摆脱中立并与您一起流动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;请注意，在投票时，您必须首先告诉观众如何回应（例如，“举手……”或“在聊天中输入……”）。您还必须对收到的答复进行评论（例如，“这就是我所期望的……大约有一半人”或“哇，这是所有人”）。如果您不发表评论，您的听众可能会觉得被欺骗而遵守，或更糟糕的是，您不关心答案，只是将民意调查作为一个噱头。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，这些建议可能并不适用适合您的情况（例如，如果您要对房间里的三名高管进行投票），因此请选择适合场合和小组规模的选项。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然参与技巧可以在沟通中随时使用在这种情况下，它们在开始会议、演示或推介时尤其重要。想想动作片的开头是怎样的。你会被卷入动作之中，演员会立即做出一些令人印象深刻、有趣且激发好奇心的事情。只有当您的注意力被吸引并且兴趣被激发后，标题和制作人员名单才会出现。如果您以传统的“嗨，我的名字是……”开始，您就错过了一个绝佳的机会立即吸引您的观众。同样，在介绍自己之前，通过提出问题、进行民意调查、展示视频或使用类比来吸引观众，可以营造出充满活力的基调。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>; 。 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;抓住并保持受众的注意力对于沟通成功至关重要。如果你想到任何你认为引人注目的沟通和沟通者，他们很可能会利用上面讨论的一些身体、心理或语言参与技巧。您要说的内容很重要，因此请给自己最好的机会向观众传达您的信息，首先获得关注，但更重要的是维持关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div >; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s OK to Fail, but You Have to Do It Right]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6331954317112&quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;加载中... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption= &quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;div>;哈佛商学院教授艾米·埃德蒙森 (Amy Edmondson) 可能因其在工作场所心理安全方面的研究而闻名。她撰写了多本书，包括即将出版的《正确的错误：成功失败的科学》，并且她与《哈佛商业评论》主编阿迪·伊格纳修斯讨论了正确与错误的问题。失败的方法。实验和冒险对于组织的成功至关重要，但以同样的方式失败两次可能是一个错误。&lt;/div>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p >;当您或您的团队尝试新事物时（并非全部成功），这就是所谓的实验。从实验中学习对于公司的成长至关重要。另一方面，当您由于疏忽或缺乏培训而偏离经过验证的实践时，这可能是一个错误。了解其中的差异并创建一个让个人在心理上感到安全并可以明智地冒险的工作空间至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于我们视频系列“工作新世界”的这一集，《哈佛商业评论》主编阿迪·伊格内修斯 (Adi Ignatius) 表示与哈佛商学院教授艾米·埃德蒙森（Amy Edmondson）坐下来，她是心理安全专家，也是即将出版的书的作者 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Right-Kind-Wrong-Science-Failing/dp/1982195061&quot; >;&lt;em>;正确与错误：成功失败的科学&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，讨论：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;高效、明智的失败方法&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;危险没有进行足够的实验&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;平衡员工个人的需求与团队和组织的需求&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;埃德蒙森说，领导者应该在每次失败后进行彻底的事后分析，无论是不管它是否富有成效，以确保它不会重演。 “在新领域、新发现中的失败，即使是明智的失败，第二次发生时就不再是明智的了。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world -of-work&quot;>;工作新世界&lt;/a>;”探讨了高层管理人员如何看待未来以及他们的公司如何努力为成功做好准备。每周，Ignatius 都会在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/harvard-business-review/&quot;>;LinkedIn Live&lt;/a>; 上与一位高层领导交谈 - 之前的采访包括 &lt;a href=&quot; /2021/10/microsofts-satya-nadella-on-flexible-work-the-metaverse-and-the-power-of-empathy&quot;>;微软首席执行官萨蒂亚·纳德拉&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11 /indra-nooyi-前百事可乐首席执行官谈动荡时期的人才培养&quot;>;前百事可乐首席执行官英德拉·努伊&lt;/a>;。他还在专门为《哈佛商业评论》订阅者提供的时事通讯中分享了对这些对话的内部看法，并为未来的讨论征求问题。如果您是订阅者，可以&lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences?movetile=newworldofwork&quot;>;此处&lt;/a>;注册。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS： &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;艾米，欢迎来到新的工作世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;艾米·埃德蒙森：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;很高兴来到这里，阿迪。感谢您邀请我。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New World of Work&quot; dek=&quot;Previous Episodes&quot; cta-text =&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color: black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;新工作世界&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 以前的剧集 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a >; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你的书主要是关于失败的。我的印象是，我们都明白失败是高尚的而不是可耻的，并且提供了有用的学习教训。但你正在写的书似乎在说我们需要认真思考，甚至​​可能以不同的方式思考失败。你想通过这本书实现什么目标？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;艾米·埃德蒙森：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我和你在一起，然后我四处寻找，意识到真相有很多人们仍然对失败感到困惑。外面有很多关于失败的愉快的谈论。硅谷有一句口头禅：快速失败、经常失败、失败是好事、让我们从失败中学习、让我们举办失败派对、让我们拥有失败简历等等。事实是，未来的工作将充满失败。我们不能只是希望它消失，即使我们愿意，我们也必须与之合作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但我认为没有人能真正把关于失败的快乐谈论放在心上，除非他们有一个连贯的框架。你可以将其视为两个阵营：硅谷快速失败阵营和经常失败阵营。然后是另一个阵营，即“我生活在现实世界中，失败不是一种选择。”他们都是对的，或者都是部分正确的，但两者都不是很有帮助，也不是针对具体情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所以我认为，当它没有以连贯的方式来区分不同的观点时，这是愉快的谈话。好的失败和不太好的失败可能更具破坏性而不是有益。它推动了地下的诚实对话。重要的是要讨论哪些失败是我们真正应该张开双臂欢迎的，哪些是我们可能不应该欢迎的。&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;新世界工作&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href =&quot;/resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 订阅我们的每周通讯 &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 工作新世界 &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 关于人才、技术和商业未来的坦诚对话。为订阅者准备的特别电子邮件系列。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>;签名向上&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 感谢您注册，&lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>; &lt;/span>;！ &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 您可以查看我们的&lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;其他新闻通讯&lt;/a>;或通过管理您的&lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;随时选择退出电子邮件首选项&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为你最好的事情关于失败，可以这样说：如果你有一种允许失败、容忍失败的文化，这意味着你正在努力、你正在推动、你正在尝试创新、你正在尝试做困难的事情。这是数字公司定义的一部分。数字化公司经常进行实验、尝试和失败，并且能够容忍失败。我猜如果你和大多数公司交谈，他们会说：“是的，我们就是这样做的。这就是我们的文化。我们以前不这么做，但我们还是这么做了。”所以我想向您提出更多一点：言辞，这是愉快的谈话，但实际上这并不是世界真正的运作方式？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;艾米·埃德蒙森：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;首先，这不是大多数激励措施的设置方式。我并不是说情况一律如此，但大多数时候，组织中的失败不会得到奖励，人们宁愿做任何事，也不愿失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你是对的，也许是更好的方法谈论这不是作为失败，而是作为实验。我们必须非常支持实验。但我们必须支持聪明的实验。我认为聪明的失败是聪明实验的结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;聪明的实验是在新领域发生的实验 - 老实说，如果你能查找答案，找到秘诀，找到蓝图，请这样做，无需进行实验 - 追求与组织价值主张一致的目标的新领域，并假设您已经完成了功课，重要的是，尽可能小。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些是我们必须张开双臂欢迎各种尝试和失败。它们是发现，让我们能够快速弄清楚下一步要尝试什么。但是本书的一部分专门讨论了可以防止失败的最佳实践。贵公司在已知领域内的活动和运营应该进行良好的设置，以使失败极少发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;是否存在不能容忍失败的行业？航空公司飞行员？你真的不希望他们失败。这不是一个反问句。有没有真正不能容忍失败的行业？你能看着它们说：“如果你有这样的政策，你实际上可以获得有趣的结果吗？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们从航空公司开始，因为显然我们都不希望他们接受失败。但我认为航空公司之所以拥有非凡的成功和安全记录，是因为他们愿意并且能够谈论失败。他们确实容忍的故障发生在模拟器中。有培训，非常强调尽早说出来，以防止更糟糕的事情发生。所以他们的安全记录并不是来自不能容忍失败，而是不能容忍重大事故。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，我们必须非常容忍人为错误的现实，以便我们能够发现并纠正，我们可以训练，我们可以允许人们在模拟器等安全环境中承担我们刚才谈到的各种风险和实验，而不是在执行真正的职责时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但我不认为可以按照您的问题所暗示的方式描述行业。我认为不同公司之间存在差异。选择快速消费品等行业。不难发现这些行业内不同公司在文化容错方面的差异。因此，更明智的说法是，一些公司在对智能失败具有健康的容忍度方面比其他公司做得更好。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;富有成效的失败是什么样子的？你确实提到失败有好的和坏的。有什么区别以及如何确保他们的失败是好的？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们有流程的已知领域或者获得我们想要的结果的公式，最好的做法是使用该过程，使用该公式并获得我们想要的结果。因此，当几年前花旗银行的一名员工不小心犯了一个小小的人为错误，意外地将 8 亿美元电汇给他不应该电汇的客户时，这就是一次基本的非生产性失败。结果他们连钱都拿不回来了。因此，不要庆祝这种失败。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;富有成效的失败是指我们获得新的有用的知识，这些新知识可以帮助我们继续创造我们试图在我们的领域创造的价值。市场，为我们的客户。因此，我们发现了一些如果不尝试、不实验就不可能发现的东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您是否建议有一个详细的设计方案？尸检？我认为军方非常注重进行详细的事后分析：发生了什么，出了什么问题，为什么？大概是从中吸取教训，不要再发生同样的事情了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事后尸检并不需要采取过多的措施。时间，但一定要彻底。它应该是分析性的，并仔细观察失败的不同方面，准确理解发生的事情和原因，以防止再次发生同样的失败。因此，在新领域、新发现中的失败，即使是明智的失败，第二次发生时就不再是明智的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想换个话题，更广泛地谈论一下工作场所。真正的问题是：我们还好吗？ &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-reenergize-your-team-when-morale-is-low&quot;>;您最近在《哈佛商业评论》上发表了一篇文章&lt;/a>;，表明事情可能并非如此太好了，但参与度和生产力水平相对较低，倦怠率很高。我们可以推测为什么这是真的，但这准确吗？很难一概而论，但你知道，我们正在受苦吗？如果是这样，作为管理者，我们该如何应对？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;嗯，我没有一种系统的全球数据集从中我可以对人们的行为做出可靠的推断。我的印象来自非正式对话、定性研究、阅读《哈佛商业评论》和许多其他渠道，以了解人们的表现。所以，实际上，在某种程度上，我是在评论《哈佛商业评论》和许多其他商业媒体环境中的对话，也许是 LinkedIn 和其他地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想我可以肯定地说的一件事是，焦虑是现实如此，人们对未来感到担忧。他们在很多方面都对此感到担忧。他们担心气候变化。他们担心人工智能。正如你提到的，他们担心倦怠。我会再次陷入倦怠。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是这种焦虑往往会促使我们退回到自己的角落，人们开始思考，“我会没事吗？”他们变得更加关注自己的福祉，而不是团队的健康或组织的健康。这确实可能导致侵蚀，甚至恶性循环，组织发现自己陷入了孤立地一一响应请求和问题的陷阱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们需要一种更全面的思维方式关于它。我看到有限的证据表明，公司至少被描述为停下来思考更大的前景，他们的价值主张，这意味着他们必须如何构建和领导，以完成必要的工作，以及如何组织这项工作，以一种深思熟虑的方式，考虑各种不同和可变的需求，以及如何激励和激励人们把事情做好。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我简单地谈谈倦怠问题，因为实际上有一些最近的数据一些引起我注意的研究表明，当心理安全感较低时，倦怠感会系统性地升高，对吗？例如，在我看来，倦怠的某些部分与孤独和孤立有关。我认为可以公平地说，当我们真诚地感到我们在一起时，我们与同事保持联系并参与其中，试图应对这些挑战，我们就可以忍受许多挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们不禁会想，“好吧，其中一些与大流行有关吗？”对于我们许多人来说，解散了团队，通过在家工作创造了新的工作环境，这在很多方面对于平衡工作和生活的人们来说都是非常棒的。它可能会对您所写的团队合作的必要性产生影响。这是你的预感吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;艾米·埃德蒙森：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我确实认为这种流行病对我们所有人造成了损失。它造成了如此明显的不确定性。这是一个如此明显的破坏。这不是我们通常习惯的渐进转变。这是一个非常突然的转变，它引发了对不同工作安排的精彩——而且我认为富有成效的——实验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在是时候对什么有效、什么无效进行非常系统的评估了？而且它不能是增量的，对吧？而且它也不能基于人们所说的他们想要的。因为很多时候，我们所说的我们想要的实际上并不是我们从长远来看、更大的视野中真正需要或真正想要的，以到达我们需要和想要去的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/强>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你刚才谈到试图制定一个全面的政策和方法，如果我没听错的话，这并不是总是单独与人打交道，但这就是现在管理的本质。突然之间，除了其他一切之外，管理者还被期望几乎像精神病学家一样，人们愿意分享他们的个人情况、挑战和问题，并且管理者的角色越来越多地参与其中一种明智的方式。因此，最终管理变得高度个性化，但我认为也许您已经面临其中的风险，即失去团队意识和集体努力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY埃德蒙森：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们几乎已经忘记了紧张和权衡。我和我们之间总会存在紧张关系，对吗？我当下的愿望和我的长期愿望之间总是存在着紧张关系。如果你问我想要什么：无限付钱给我，不要求我做任何事情，让我整天吃冰淇淋，对吗？但这并不能让我到达我真正需要去并且想去的地方。我想做出改变。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为我们正处于一个无法帮助人们重视集体的时刻。作为人类，我们是社会生物。这是其中的一部分，但这也是我们想要重视的。我们希望对其他人很重要。我们希望以某种比我们自己和享乐主义欲望更重要的方式发挥作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你可以想到一种老式的公司管理理论，对吧？如果市场自行运作，我们就只需要承包商来完成任务，这将是高效的、明智的、合乎逻辑的。但这不起作用，因为我们要做的很多工作本质上都是协作的，而且是动态的。而且它不是容易划分、分而治之的风格。它要求我们以有意义的方式真正合作。好消息是，这可能是一次非常有吸引力、有益且令人兴奋的体验。坏消息是，这并不容易管理。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但我认为我们可以深入了解每个人的兔子洞，必须以不同的方式进行管理，每个人，你几乎是那个人的精神病学家，让我们退后一步重新思考，我们如何设计我们的活动、我们的运营，以便为我们服务的对象创造最大价值？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;是的，我喜欢这一点，但我不得不说，我认为公司还没有意识到这一点。新冠疫情的破坏让我们看到了一些灵​​活性。但我认为您所关注的问题，我们正在努力解决，而且我认为我们很多人还没有解决，需要继续试验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所以我们在这个焦虑、倦怠的时代。然后，你对生成式人工智能产生了一种恐惧——可能是非理性的，也可能不是——生成式人工智能将能够几乎免费地完成我们所有的工作。我猜你还没有做过定量研究。但从质量上来说，随着生成式人工智能进入工作场所的各个层面，可能性变得越来越清晰，您对人们有什么建议？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为你指出，除了对人和文化的影响之外，这有点超出了我的掌控范围。我从一个在工作和社交聚会的边缘聆听许多对话的人的角度来说话，我认为你是对的。我认为恐惧是主导情绪，当然有些人对即将到来的惊人变化感到兴奋，有些人非常乐观，但我想我偶尔听到的恐惧多于乐观。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实是我们两者都需要。我们需要一些积极的、深思熟虑的、以设计为导向的方法来进行实验并找出行之有效的方法。但我认为它们不会是解决可能出现的戏剧性变化的简单解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是来自来自墨西哥蒙特雷的奥马尔。什么样的指标可以用来衡量智能失败？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的第一反应是制定指标是个好主意。我花最多时间研究的一件事是，有多少失败甚至没有机会被衡量，因为人们没有谈论它们。这就是我最初进入这个主题的方式：发现不同群体之间的巨大差异，即使是在同一组织内，以及他们愿意说出出错的事情，而不仅仅是正确的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个更广泛的挑战，而不仅仅是人们不一定敢于发声：智能失败的类别涵盖了广阔的领域。我认为这些指标必须根据具体情况进行调整——让我来说明一下广阔的领域。当一种新的抗癌药物没有达到我们所希望的功效时，一项运行良好的临床试验就是一次明智的失败。这是在新的领域。除了进行临床试验之外，没有其他方法可以找出答案。它的大小合适，不会比需要的大。这是为了追求目标而由假设驱动的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是一次非常糟糕的相亲也是如此。这就是明智的失败。也许你的朋友认为你们互相喜欢。你愿意出去喝杯咖啡。追求目标时尽可能小的新领域，其余的都是如此。因此，糟糕的相亲和失败的临床试验显然是苹果和橘子，但它们都符合这一类别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为回答衡量问题的最佳方法是，让我们确保遵守标准到。然后，让我们考虑一下，考虑到我们正在尝试做的工作，智能失败的正确频率是多少？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一种说法是：实验的正确频率是多少？我们应该多久尝试一次新事物来挑战极限，发现新的可能性，甚至发现效率？我们经常这样做吗？答案通常是否定的，因为我们大多数人宁愿成功也不愿失败，而且我们大多数人宁愿继续做我们正在做的事情，因为我们很擅长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI伊格纳修斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是穆罕默德在巴基斯坦提出的另一个类似问题。员工可能会犹豫是否提供可能被视为负面的反馈，这可能会阻碍专业发展，阻碍组织进步。如何解决这种情况？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个很好的问题，因为它是真的。我们非常不愿意做事，不愿说出负面或困难的信息，因为坦率地说，不这样做总是更容易。克制总是比坦率地说出你希望做得更好的事情更容易。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让这件非常困难的事情变得更容易的方法是通过指出如何做来做好准备。它确实很有价值。我会定期，甚至经常说，提到这样一个事实：“我们需要做这件困难的事情。 We need to do it well if we want to be as good as we can as a team.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But even individuals who have the ambition to grow and develop in their roles and in their careers have to train themselves to be willing to do this and receive it because of its value. So we&#39;ve got to call attention to its value. We&#39;ve got to call attention to the fact that it&#39;s hard and then do it anyway and support each other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This question is from Don from Calgary in Canada. If it&#39;s true that we learn acutely from mistakes, what are some ways to encourage permission from our leaders who may be risk averse?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re all risk averse, and maybe leaders even more than others, maybe not. But first of all, I make a distinction between mistakes and failures. I&#39;m not anti-mistake because I&#39;m a human being, and I make them, we all do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But a mistake is not the same thing as a failure. A failure is something that went wrong that we wish were otherwise. A mistake is a deviation from a known practice. Now, that could happen because of inattention, because of lack of training, because of exhaustion, you name it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think it&#39;s helpful for leaders, and others for that matter, to talk about the reality that we will make mistakes because we&#39;re human. The very best practice is not to never make a mistake. It&#39;s to catch and correct them quickly, and then also to make that distinction between smart experiments in new territory that we also want to see more of because it&#39;s the secret to future value creation. And we welcome those, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Furthering that, here&#39;s a question from Benny from California. What&#39;s the best way to speak to subordinates after a failure to boost morale and communicate that, “This was a good failure. It&#39;s OK”?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;m going to say “honestly.” You can be honest about, “Wow, this was disappointing for all of us, and let&#39;s get everything we can out of it. Let&#39;s learn as much as possible.” And in fact, given that something substantial that goes wrong nearly always has multifaceted aspects to it, it&#39;s helpful to have a thoughtful and data-driven conversation about what happened. Not “Who did it?”, but, “What happened?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We may go around the team and ask, “What did you see?” And we&#39;re really looking for what happened, what contributed to that, and that&#39;s both commission and omission, things that you did that may have contributed, things that you didn&#39;t do that may have helped. It&#39;s a thoughtful, deliberately learning-oriented conversation designed to help us be better next time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How do you reenergize your team these days? How do we reenergize our team particularly now, in 2023, where it feels like there&#39;s a lot of stuff swirling around?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It starts with personally taking the time to reconnect with your own sense of purpose for doing the job, the role that you are currently doing. And consider why it matters to you and why what you are doing or leading matters to the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having done that, share it. Share it often and then just as quickly invite others in to help navigate the necessarily stormy waters that lie ahead. I think it starts with you and then it&#39;s an honest sharing of why you care, why it&#39;s challenging, why you very much need and are interdependent with others. Because all of us want to be needed. We want to be needed. We want to matter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The last few years, with the pandemic, I&#39;d say certainly in the US, there&#39;s been increased attention to social issues, which on the one hand I think felt right to people in the workplace. On the other, it brought more challenges into the workplace. One imagines there&#39;s a pendulum, and it might swing between leadership needing to be very empathetic to, I don&#39;t know, the backlash if that&#39;s the right word. Leaders need to achieve productivity. That&#39;s what it&#39;s all about. Do you believe in that pendulum or are we in a different place? And if you do, where are we right now on that swing?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I believe in the pendulum. I believe that the pendulum happens and I believe there may be a better way. It&#39;s often thought of as empathy versus productivity. And I looked this up actually: Productivity is defined as the effectiveness of productive effort as measured in terms of the rate of output per unit of input.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first problem is that not all work is easily measured for productivity. The second problem is, often it&#39;s not the right way to measure excellence. Productivity is often a short-term measure, and it has limited predictive value for the future performance of the firm. For example, one way to be really productive is to just push people to their limits. But that has time constraints. Eventually they will burn out, leave, etc. It&#39;s like Buckminster Fuller used to say that it was foolish to burn down the house to keep warm on a cold winter&#39;s night. The excessive pressure can be the equivalent of that error.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And also innovation work in particular, we have case study after case study where the work actually suffers when productivity metrics are brought to bear.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a way, I wish the pendulum were more about excellence than productivity, because I think productivity is really tricky and variable to measure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I see the pendulum existing, but maybe it&#39;s a false dichotomy. Maybe it&#39;s not empathy versus productivity. Maybe we need smart, caring leaders who understand the importance of both. And given that that&#39;s very challenging, they&#39;re open about it being challenging. They&#39;re asking for help. They&#39;re sharing the burden of caring and excellence with their teams and considering, again, the fundamentals of what it is the organization must do well to stay alive in its market, to perform in its market. And talk about it honestly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I sometimes think we don&#39;t talk often enough about the fact that work is work. It&#39;s supposed to be a little bit of work, but that doesn&#39;t mean it can&#39;t be fun, energizing, collaborative, and full of empathy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I love that. Well, that&#39;s a good point to end on. Amy Edmondson, thank you for being on the show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thanks for having me. All the best.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Hybrid Work Can Become Toxic]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_27_1425175448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;阿尔瓦雷斯/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;毒性可能是某些工作环境中的一个不幸的现实。有毒文化有五个共同特征：不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待。尽管这些属性无可否认是负面的，但我们并没有绝对的、统一接受的尺度来衡量它们。使事情变得更加复杂的是，混合环境的定义意味着员工在非常不同的环境中体验他们的工作——不同的环境。有些是面对面的，有些是远程的……这些可能会随着时间的推移而变化。因此，混合工作空间并不统一；有些人可能会经历有毒的混合环境，而另一些人则不会。作者提出了混合性可能导致有毒行为的四种机制，以及在混合环境中预防和解决有毒行为的四种策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-有毒? language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-有毒？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;工作中的毒性——无论我们在哪里或如何工作——都是由一系列因素。重要的是要认识到混合和远程工作的某些方面使毒性更有可能发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，让我们快速概述一下“有毒”的实际含义。它并不是指任何健康组织中自然（且必要）的误解、紧张和冲突。它也不是指一次性事件或偶尔出现的混蛋同事。在大多数情况下，最好将这些类型的刺激视为（工作）生活的正常部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，什么实际上被认为是有毒的？唐纳德·索尔 (Donald Sull) 和他的同事进行的一项研究确定了&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-毒-文化/&quot;>;有毒文化：不尊重、不包容、不道德、残酷和虐待。最近，我与两位该领域的专家同事——哈佛商学院的艾米·埃德蒙森（Amy Edmondson）和奎斯特罗姆商学院的康斯坦斯·哈德利（Constance Hadley）——进行了一次讨论，我们一致认为，毒性也意味着相关行为是普遍存在且持续存在的。我们相信，这就是不良行为上升（或可能下降）到有毒程度的原因。毒性带有一种不可避免的感觉，这也是工作中经历如此痛苦的部分原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管这些属性无可否认是负面的，但没有绝对的、统一接受的尺度来衡量它们——所有五个都是主观的，植根于每个人的经历。让事情变得更加复杂的是，混合环境的定义意味着员工在非常不同的环境中体验他们的工作——有些是面对面的，有些是远程的——而且这些环境可能每天都在变化。因此，混合工作空间并不统一；有些人可能会经历有毒的混合环境，而另一些人则不会。这并不能减轻有毒混合环境对那些经历过这种环境的人的痛苦或损害。然而，这确实意味着某些行为可能是有毒的，即使是善意的——或者至少不是恶意的——行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当与高管谈论毒性时，我鼓励他们这样思考社会科学家，了解混合工作可能导致毒性增加的机制。这是他们应该知道的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;混合工作如何导致毒性&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我的研究和咨询经验使我思考混合性可能导致有毒行为的四种机制.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.远程办公改变动态&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;混合工作意味着，与全职办公室工作相比，更多的沟通将通过电子邮件、短信、电话或视频等技术进行。关于技术介导的沟通影响的研究的早期发现之一是，人们变得更加不拘束，表现出更少的自我监控和自我控制&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/227445694_Reducing_Social_Context_Cues_Electronic_Mail_in_Organizational_Communication&quot; >;通过技术进行交流时&lt;/a>;。换句话说，当我们通过电子方式相互交谈时，我们更有可能脱口而出可能有害的话。想一想您与同事面对面和通过电子方式进行的激烈交流 - 很可能，您更倾向于在电子邮件中插入尖刻的俏皮话，而不是面对面的交流。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这充满活力并不（必然）是成为一个令人讨厌的人。我们都有愤怒、沮丧或激情的时刻，如果处理不当，这些感觉有可能变成有毒的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，在面对面的互动中，另一边的人类这种对话对我们来说更为重要，导致我们大多数人认识到不小心的话可能会付出的代价，并闭口不谈。重点不是我们不应该说出自己的想法（如果我们觉得自己不能说出自己的想法，这对心理安全来说是不利的），而是我们应该好好选择我们的措辞。虽然远程互动带来的自我监控和自我控制的减少并不一定会导致毒性，但它们肯定会更有可能导致&lt;em>;不尊重&lt;/em>;或&lt;em>;辱骂&lt;/em>;（Sull的两种毒性）特征）评论出来。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2。混合性从根本上来说是不平衡的&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;混合性还意味着不同的人在不同的环境中工作。有些人可能在家里，而另一些人可能在办公室——这些地点有着不可否认的差异。办公室里的人有更多的机会获得资源和更高的知名度，通常会因此获得更多的信用和更快的晋升。与此同时，远程工作者常常感到被忽视和回避。尽管这些影响可能是负面的，但如果每个人在某些时候都处于同样的不利地位，那么严格来说它们并不是有毒的。问题在于，有些人（可能是远程/混合员工）&lt;em>;始终&lt;/em>;感到被排除在外——就像我最近共事的一位经理的经历一样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司政策是允许所有员工每周远程工作两天，经理允许她的团队成员选择这些日子。她很快发现她的团队实际上已经根据人们选择上班的日期的不同（但一致）模式进行了分裂。使问题更加复杂的是，团队成员的远程工作选择在很大程度上受到通勤和孩子的学校时间表的影响，这与团队中的人口差异相一致。当一些团队成员觉得自己被排除在另一组在职期间进行的讨论和会议时，问题就出现了。这种分裂导致了人际紧张和冲突，人们感到&lt;em>;被排斥&lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;不受尊重&lt;/em>;（两种毒性特征），并最终导致人员流动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.混合性会降低凝聚力和信任&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/11/a-study-of-1100-employees-found-that-remote-workers-feel-shunned-and-left-out &quot;>;研究表明&lt;/a>;缺乏密切接触会减少联系和信任，而这是健康文化的关键要素。在大流行期间，我与许多远程开始新工作的员工进行了交谈，我一直听说他们不了解同事并感到孤立。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work&quot;>;Microsoft 的研究&lt;/a>;发现远程工作会导致员工的工作规模更小、更少发达的网络。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;远程（以及扩展的混合）工作并不一定意味着组织将具有薄弱或不一致的文化。以Linux为例。它的开源软件开发从第一天起就由一个结构松散的开发人员社区进行，这些开发人员从未见过面，但对该组织的广泛研究发现，它具有强大的社会规范来管理行为。然而，很难否认群体的结构（或缺乏结构）消除或阻碍了我们传统上用来建立、传播和维持文化的许多机制。请注意，Linux &lt;em>;始于&lt;/em>;具有远程、分散的文化。尽管自疫情爆发以来许多公司已经采用远程和混合方式，但他们的文化已经建立，然后进行调整以应对危机。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;文化非常重要，因为它是组织用来避免残酷竞争的指南针&lt;/em>;，在更极端的情况下，&lt;em>;不道德&lt;/em>;行为。需要明确的是，混杂性本身并不会让人们变得更加残酷或不道德（尽管有人可能会认为人与人之间的距离感使他们不太意识到自己行为的负面影响）。然而，在每个社会体系中，我们都会发现一系列行为，而文化通常可以帮助我们控制负面行为。最重要的是，虽然人们不太可能对那些与他们感到亲近和有联系的人表现出不良行为，但远程/混合环境带来的距离使我们更有可能将一些同事视为“我们”，而不是“我们”。他们”——而且更容易对“他们”表现不佳。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4。混合性使得解决问题变得困难&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;远程和混合工作中还有一个更关键的挑战：我们与同事面对面的互动较少，而且研究表明解决争议更加困难（例如那些围绕有毒行为）几乎。想象一下尝试通过 Zoom 与某人讨论敏感话题，并担心从他们正在寻找的位置到他们回复的速度等所有事情。 &lt;em>;他们是否全神贯注于我？我确定我的诚意是通过视频传达的吗？他们的反应缓慢是因为他们不同意还是只是落后了？&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我们面对面时，我们有更多的人际工具可供使用。我们拥有更好的数据，因为我们可以更轻松地读取面部表情并看到镜头外的行为。我们还拥有更好的工具，因为面对面的互动使我们能够同步合作解决分歧。邻近效应（本质上，我们喜欢与我们有更多接触的人）意味着所有这一切都是从更密切的关系开始的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个值得一提的问题是微侵犯，有些人会出现这种情况有人认为，在偏远地区，这种情况发生的频率较低，因为我们彼此相处的时间较少。不过，我要提醒领导者和员工对混合环境中的微侵犯迹象（通常反映在&lt;em>;不包容&lt;/em>;等有毒行为中）保持警惕。虽然这些设置可能发生微侵犯的接触点较少，但它们并不能消除微侵犯发生的基础，也不能阻止微侵犯在其他渠道出现，例如 Slack、消息应用程序或视频会议。实际上，混合工作可能会掩盖问题而不解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;领导者可以做什么&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我建议领导者通过四种方式处理混合工作中的有毒行为：教育、奠定基础，进行持续对话，并快速干预。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;教育员工&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;避免混合团队中有毒行为的第一步是帮助人们了解这种行为是如何产生的。你可能会想，“他们当然知道不要无礼、辱骂或不包容”，但这不是问题所在。与您的员工坐下来讨论这些结果是如何作为混合工作安排和决策的意外后果而发生的。提醒他们，毒性与行为有关——重要的不是你的意图是什么，而是别人如何看待你的行为。一个好的起点是要求员工反思他们可能经历过的有毒混合工作行为（例如，感觉自己经常被排除在社交群体之外，或者在 Slack 上阅读他们认为辱骂或不尊重的评论）。此步骤的目标不是识别特定问题或指责，而是提高员工的自我意识，并增加寻找有毒行为或其前因的眼睛的数量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;奠定基础&lt;/ h3>; &lt;p>;正如本杰明·富兰克林的名言，​​“一盎司的预防胜过一磅的治疗。”您可以采用的最有效的工具之一是具有针对有毒行为的内置抗体的文化。尤其要注重促进同理心和心理安全。以同理心为核心的文化鼓励员工考虑自己的行为对同事的影响，从而增加员工在做出可能令他人不安的行为之前发现自己的可能性。反过来，包含心理安全的文化对于同理心无法阻止的情况至关重要。我们并不总是认识到我们行为的影响，建立心理安全感可以确保员工能够说出他们认为有毒的行为。研究为促进&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/empathy-rules&quot;>;同理心&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;心理安全&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;进行持续的对话&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;因为混合工作的体验在员工之间是不同的，并且随着时间的推移而变化（有人今天可能在办公室，周围都是同事，明天独自在家），毒性是一个不断变化的目标。管理这种活力的唯一真正有效的方法是持续的过程——而基石是重复的、持续的对话。我鼓励混合团队和组织定期进行检查，鼓励每个人提出担忧或标记不良经历。对于频率没有硬性规定，因为它取决于组织的混合环境的动态程度：变化越多、越快，这些对话应该越频繁。作为起点，目标是每月检查一次并根据需要进行调整。如果您希望人们诚实地分享，请确保心理安全基础到位，并且不要将这些对话视为肤浅的打勾练习。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;快速干预&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;即使有对问题的良好理解、积极的文化基础以及持续的讨论，混合工作仍然可能会导致员工认为有害的行为。有毒环境的一个大问题是它们往往会变得更糟：有毒行为要么自我繁殖，滋生更多毒性，要么导致心怀不满的员工脱离工作，由于需要重新分配工作量而造成新的紧张局势。要打破恶性循环，不仅要密切关注不良行为，还要做好发现不良行为的准备，帮助各方开展对话，努力达成双方都能接受的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;假设您注意到类似经理的情况，他的团队在在家办公期间分裂。在这种情况下，召开一次团队会议并分享您对这种情况可能会让人感到排斥的担忧。事实可能是，你的担忧并没有被分享——但你仍然在建立对这个问题的认同和所有权，这样如果它确实成为一个问题，以后就更容易解决。但是，如果您已经认识到某些团队成员正在出现的担忧，那么您可以通过一个论坛来讨论并集体解决该问题，以免问题进一步发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center; ”>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;毒性可能是某些工作环境中的一个不幸的现实。虽然混合工作不一定比面对面工作更容易产生毒性，但重要的是要认识到混合工作引入了一些可能产生毒性的不同机制。 Keeping these in mind can help leaders recognize, guard against, and eliminate toxicity when it occurs — or ideally before.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Why Employees Accept Lower Pay at Mission-Oriented Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_AnChen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;陈安插画&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当今的公司可能会宣传他们的工作如何造福于人类福祉或“让世界变得更美好。” ;最近的研究表明，这可能会给工人带来潜在的经济损失，因为它会阻止他们就更高的工资进行谈判。在五项研究中，求职者一致表示，他们担心向这些公司要求更高的工资会被视为贪婪或不恰当。这表明他们意识到了一种常见的偏见，即动机纯粹性偏见，即管理者认为对工作的物质奖励（如薪酬）感兴趣的员工的积极性低于那些受内在奖励（如工作性质）激励的员工。事实上，研究表明，外在动机和内在动机共同作用，可以预测高绩效。求职者应该投资培养自己的谈判技巧，这样当公司使用社会影响框架时，他们就不会被甩掉。组织应该培训管理者了解动机纯度偏差。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research -why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees- Accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在一个有趣的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com /watch?v=B8C5sjjhsso&quot;>;HBO 情景喜剧《硅谷》的一集&lt;/a>;，一位笨拙的初创公司创始人接连推销他们的公司，宣称公司“让世界变得更美好”。这部讽刺喜剧凸显了公司宣传其工作如何造福人类福利的现象已变得多么普遍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种趋势——学者们称之为&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/ abs/10.1287/orsc.2017.1172?&quot;>;社会影响框架&lt;/a>; — 似乎正在上升。我们在招聘启事、公司网站和消费者广告中都看到了这一点，营利性和非营利性组织都希望雇用“充满热情”和“以使命为导向”的员工，寻求“产生影响”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;如此强调社会影响并非没有道理。其一，它可以反映组织做出积极改变的热切愿望。它还可以通过灌输更大的自我价值感和意义来&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2008-00266-008&quot;>;激励&lt;/a>;员工。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;也就是说，在我们最近在&lt;em>;组织科学&lt;/em>;上发表的&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1287/orsc.2023.1675&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;中，我们发现组织的使用社会影响框架可能会给工人带来潜在的经济损失，因为它会阻止他们就更高的工资进行谈判。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;感知到的规范违规&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们通过五项实验研究探索了这种效应。处于社会影响框架条件下的求职者一致表示，要求更高的工资可能会被招聘组织视为贪婪且不合适。因此，他们没有进行谈判。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的第一项研究中，我们从在线研究平台招募了 392 名参与者，以调查员工对不同类型的组织信息的态度。大约一半的参与者阅读了一家强调社会影响的公司，而其他人则阅读了更通用的公司描述。我们要求参与者就他们是否愿意协商为该公司提供工作机会以及原因进行开放式回答。我们发现，那些收到包含社会影响框架条件的公司描述的人进行谈判的可能性降低了 32%。这种沉默的最常见原因是参与者认为谈判会被视为自私和反规范，并使他们面临被这份工作拒绝的风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的第二项研究涉及 438 名本科生响应校园内的工作机会，他们将招募同学为教育行业的初创公司工作。学生们观看了一段介绍性视频，视频中所谓的公司创始人兼首席执行官（由训练有素的演员扮演）描述了他的招聘组织。大约一半的参与者观看了创始人强调社会影响的视频，而另一半观看了创始人描述了一个专注于高质量工作和成功的更通用组织的视频。观看视频后，参与者有机会要求更高的工资，而不是接受最初提供的工资。与我们的第一项研究一致，处于社会影响状态的学生进行谈判的可能性降低了 43%。同样，这种效应是由于人们认为表现出对高薪的兴趣会违反组织的员工激励规范而产生的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们在其他三项研究中复制了这些结果。我们发现，这种影响在工作场所模拟以及教育、医疗保健、制造和金融等一系列行业中都存在。我们还发现，社会影响框架在很大程度上影响求职者对金钱工作奖励（例如工资和奖金）的要求。这似乎并没有阻止他们要求假期和医疗保健福利等非金钱奖励。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;关于金钱和做好事的假设&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;什么解释了对金钱工作奖励的影响吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;答案在于人们普遍和长期的信念，即金钱会玷污对工作本身的热爱和行善的企图。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，经理有被证明持有“&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2017.0617&quot;>;动机纯度偏见&lt;/a>;”，他们认为员工对材料感兴趣工作奖励（外在奖励）较少受到工作本身性质（内在奖励）的激励，因此不太值得被雇用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种信念是基于错误的前提。研究表明，外在动机和内在动机&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/a0035661&quot;>;&lt;em>;共同&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;共同预测高工作绩效。此外，一种动机的增加并不意味着另一种动机的减少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，在我们的研究中，求职者似乎表现得好像他们意识到管理层对工人物质利益的偏见奖励。因此，在具有社会影响力的背景下——尤其希望员工受到更高尚的动机（例如更高的目标感）的驱动——求职者会对任何表明他们可能也关心金钱的迹象进行自我审查。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;求职者和招聘经理的要点&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;从马克思主义的角度来看，社会影响框架可能被视为另一种文化趋势，它无意中有利于资本所有者，并在工人的费用。然而，鉴于社会影响框架往往植根于组织为社会做出贡献的真正努力，并且也能让员工受益，因此建议组织停止传达其对更大利益的重视就过于简单化了。因此，我们提出了几项建议，以帮助最大限度地减少接触此类消息的工人的财务损失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从工人的角度来看，求职者可以投资&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-to -evaluate-accept-reject-or-negotiate-a-job-offer&quot;>;培养他们的谈判技巧&lt;/a>;，这样他们就可以避免在组织使用社会影响框架时轻易被抛弃。他们还可以调查那些声称关心人类福利的组织&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-tell-if-a-pottial-employer-has-a-burnout-culture&quot;>;如何对待自己的员工&lt;/a>;。如果一家强调社会影响的公司忽视了员工的福祉、财务或其他方面，那将是具有讽刺意味的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织还可以考虑对经理进行培训，让他们了解他们对员工外在动机的偏见，如上所述，可能是毫无根据的。事实上，例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2014.0898&quot;>;供养家人&lt;/a>;的愿望被发现是一种强烈的愿望工作绩效的预测因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过浪漫化内在动机并条件反射地解雇那些对外在工作奖励表现出任何兴趣的求职者，组织可能会拒绝那些同样对工作充满热情并且很可能一直很优秀的优秀候选人。高绩效者。尤其重要的是，努力采取道德方法开展业务的组织可以避免以马基雅维利式的方式部署社会影响框架，将其作为故意压低薪酬的工具。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/分区>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Companies Can &mdash; and Should &mdash; Recommit to DEI in the Wake of the SCOTUS Decision]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_28_1401985.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;露丝·布莱克/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;美国最高法院禁止在学院和大学采取平权行动，州立法将多样性、公平性和包容性努力纳入校园，以及针对 DEI 的更普遍的攻击，企业正在考虑是否需要改变其 DEI 策略。简短的回答是他们不这样做。但这是审查企业价值观、人事政策并与员工就这些问题进行互动的好时机。第一步应该是记住 DEI 的道德和商业案例。他们仍然很强大。&amp;#160;其次，您可能会重新考虑使用 DEI 标签，正如一些人建议的那样。但考虑到员工对此类举措的支持，请谨慎行事。接下来，审查招聘等人力资源实践（包括为候选人撒下更广泛的网络，因为现在大学的渠道将不再那么多样化）；入职（因为有些学生接触 DEI 的机会比其他学生少）；以及绩效评估、薪酬和晋升（以确保不存在种族偏见）。&amp;#160;最后，与肯定是两极分化的员工队伍进行仔细沟通。提出可信的研究，征求意见，努力弥合分歧。最终，您希望您的组织以符合您组织价值观的方式向前发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/ a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;美国最高法院最近禁止平权行动的决定，特别是在学院和大学中禁止具有种族意识的招生，可能不会直接影响美国的工作场所，但毫无疑问，美国企业界需要考虑这一影响——以及未来潜在的司法裁决和州立法 - 将对其 DEI 实践产生影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;至少，我们在高等教育机构中看到的学生群体构成的任何变化也会影响招聘渠道。例如，当加州大学系统于 1995 年取消平权行动时，加州大学洛杉矶分校的黑人学生比例从 7% 下降（相比之下，美国人口为 13.6%，该州为 6.5%）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;短短三年内达到 3.9%&lt;/a>; 和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epi .org/blog/the-supreme-courts-ban-on-affirmative-action-means-colleges-will-struggle-to-meet-goals-of-diversity-and-equal-opportununity/&quot;>;低于 2%到 2006 年&lt;/a>;。同样，当密歇根大学禁止平权行动时，黑人本科生入学率从 2006 年的 7% 下降（相比之下，该州人口的入学率为 13.6%）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10 /31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;2021 年达到 4%&lt;/a>;。这些案例研究表明，当大学取消平权行动时，它们会产生一个不太多样化的候选人库供雇主利用，而这种情况现在很可能在全国范围内发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;加剧了这种情况，现在还有 &lt; a href=&quot;https://www.bestcolleges.com/news/anti-dei-legislation-tracker/&quot;>;超过 30 项州或地方法案&lt;/a>;针对学校的 DEI 资助、实践和推广。例如，德克萨斯州从 2024 年 1 月 1 日起禁止所有 DEI 办公室、公共机构进行多元化培训和“意识形态宣誓和声明”，这可能意味着在校园招聘的公司需要审查其信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;然而，还有比多元化招聘更重要的事情。作为管理思想领袖和工作场所种族问题的专家学者，我们预计会产生许多额外的连锁反应。该裁决已被解读为邀请 DEI 批评者质疑此类努力的有效性、合法性和必要性。例如，右翼倡导组织消费者研究的执行董事威尔希尔德&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-多样性/&quot;>;已经公开表示&lt;/a>;表示，最高法院关于平权行动的决定“将为像我们这样的团体带来风帆，他们希望摆脱基于种族的雇佣和晋升计划美国企业界。”共和党领导的 13 个州的总检察长也发送了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tn.gov/content/dam/tn/attorneygeneral/documents/pr/2023/pr23-27-letter.pdf&quot;>;致财富 100 强公司首席执行官的一封信&lt;/a>;，警告称，根据 SCOTUS，“多元化、公平和包容”的标签现在“非法且错误”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，大学招生受以下法律管辖： 《民权法案》&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crt/fcs/TitleVI&quot;>;第六章&lt;/a>;，禁止任何计划中基于种族、肤色或国籍的歧视或接受联邦财政援助的活动。 Private employment falls under &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;Title VII&lt;/a>; and is enforced by the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), currently led by Charlotte A. Burrows, who has emphasized that the SCOTUS decision has no bearing on its work. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/statement-eeoc-chair-charlotte-burrows-supreme-court-ruling-college-affirmative-action&quot;>;a statement&lt;/a>;, she said, “It does not address employer efforts to foster diverse and inclusive workforces or to engage the talents of all qualified workers, regardless of their background. It remains lawful for employers to implement diversity, equity, inclusion, and accessibility programs that seek to ensure workers of all backgrounds are afforded equal opportunity in the workplace.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That means most corporate DEI efforts are formally safe for now. However, it&#39;s important for organizations to pay attention to the changing landscape.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Taking a Step Back &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s consider whether we still believe race should be considered when making organizational decisions. That depends in part on whether we believe racism still affects our society. If we do, it seems plausible and just to recommend interventions that consider race. If we don&#39;t (or if we are okay with racism), it would seem implausible and unjust to recommend interventions that consider race. So, we ask you, does racism still affect our society? And do we care?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the systematic oppression of Black Americans, who have long been erroneously held up as the face of affirmative action in the United States (while research shows that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-who-benefits-white-women/70371219007/&quot;>;white women&lt;/a>; are instead the biggest beneficiaries of such policies). Even after the abolishment of slavery in 1865, the United States continued to codify the oppression of Black people in legal, political, and social systems. From the post-war &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/brown-v-board-50th-anniversary/southern-black-codes.html&quot;>;Black Codes&lt;/a>; to the 1896 &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.gov/milestone-documents/plessy-v-ferguson&quot;>;Plessy v. Ferguson&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; SCOTUS decision to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/black-history-month/a-brief-history-of-jim-crow&quot;>;Jim Crow laws&lt;/a>; in the US South, white power structures denied Black people full citizenship and equal protection under the law. Counter measures, including Congressional actions such as the landmark 13th, 14th and 15th Amendments, the Supreme Court&#39;s 1954 Brown vs. Board of Education decision, and the Civil Rights Act of 1964, which finally banned racial discrimination from public places, schools and workplaces, represented progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, having been denied the ability to advance professionally and create wealth for more than a century post-slavery, Black people remain disproportionately underrepresented in professional workplaces and leadership roles. As fellow researchers Tony Mayo and Laura Morgan Roberts have &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/toward-a-racially-just-workplace&quot;>;described&lt;/a>;, they are less likely than their white peers to be hired, developed, and promoted. Other racioethnic populations — Latino, Native American, Pacific Islanders — have faced different types of discrimination and are also underrepresented in higher-earning roles and occupations, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/opub/reports/race-and-ethnicity/2020/home.htm&quot;>;data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://extramural-diversity.nih.gov/diversity-matters/underrepresented-groups&quot;>;industry groups&lt;/a>;. This suggests that racism does still affect our society. The United States is not living up to its founding ideals of allowing all citizens to pursue life, liberty, and happiness in equal measure. We should care — and keep working toward those goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A next question to ask is whether we believe diverse teams benefit organizational performance. Ample research shows that they make &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;smarter decisions&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/the-other-diversity-dividend&quot;>;better investments&lt;/a>;, are &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-investing-in-dei-helps-companies-become-more-adaptable&quot;>;more adaptable&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/how-and-where-diversity-drives-financial-performance&quot;>;drive innovation&lt;/a>; when the corporate culture in which they operate is a supportive, &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/research-to-excel-diverse-teams-need-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychologically safe&lt;/a>; one. Diverse and well-trained workforces and leadership teams are also better suited to interact with diverse employees, customers and vendors. Thus, there is still both a moral and a business case for supporting DEI efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some corporate leaders still might be wondering whether they should rethink their whole DEI strategy in light of recent attacks on affirmative action. The short answer is no. Now is not the time to reverse the commitments they made to racial equity in the aftermath of George Floyd&#39;s 2020 murder. Instead, it&#39;s time to clarify organizational values around DEI, clearly communicate them, and ensure that people management processes are aligned with them. Here, we explain how to go about this at this critical moment in US history.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Rethinking L&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;abels&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given the SCOTUS ruling, other pending state legislation, and the warning from those 13 attorneys general, some legal scholars &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;have suggested&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;that companies preemptively protect themselves by moving away from DEI labels to ones clearly protected by law. For example, instead of a chief diversity officer, you would have a Title VII compliance officer. Another option is to use words like “inclusion,” “belonging,” and “engagement” to emphasize that the goal is improving organizational culture not necessarily racial diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We urge caution on this front because DEI remains important to employees. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.bfldr.com/ZZ11QL2O/at/6bpw94vrt588vtc8gr3fgw5/C001_Benevity_TheStateofWorkplaceDEI_Final.pdf?hsCtaTracking=e0c17c58-a6ca-4e73-978b-87718706789f%7C57928514-8a0c-4227-bf1f-498f3e23c304&quot;>;a 2023 Benevity survey&lt;/a>; found that 95% of people weigh a prospective employer&#39;s DEI efforts when choosing between job offers with similar salary and benefits and that 78% would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; consider working for a company that fails to commit significant resources to DEI initiatives. Employees from historically marginalized backgrounds will almost certainly feel disregarded and devalued if their organizations shy away from DEI labels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, any good DEI strategy requires regular evaluation to ensure it is performing against goals set and having the intended impact on employees. And when faced with a big organizational change or new rules and regulations, leaders should have a system in place to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ellavatesolutions.com/the-ellavate-approach&quot;>;tune-up existing DEI&lt;/a>; strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reviewing Processes &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recruitment&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As highlighted earlier, we can expect a smaller percentage of racially marginalized individuals to be admitted to predominantly white institutions (PWI), so companies still seeking diversity in their candidate pool will need to look elsewhere to find as much of it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One solution is to increase recruiting at institutions such as historically Black colleges and universities (HBCUs), Hispanic-serving institutions (HSIs), and tribal colleges and universities (TCUs). Another is to consider non-traditional pathways such as community colleges and building partnerships with community organizations that focus on racially diverse pipelines, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://oneten.org/about/mission/&quot;>;OneTen&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend a shift to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/skills-based-hiring-is-on-the-rise&quot;>;skills-based hiring&lt;/a>;, a well-established DEI best practice that focuses on matching skills between job candidates and roles instead of focusing on only education and experience. Consider partnering with organizations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://opportunityatwork.org/stars/&quot;>;STARS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlt.org/&quot;>;MLT&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://reachingoutmba.org/&quot;>;ROMBA&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://toigofoundation.org/&quot;>;Toigo Foundation&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fortefoundation.org/site/PageServer&quot;>;Forte Foundation&lt;/a>; (full disclosure: the latter two are clients of Tina) that help identify talent employers need.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Onboarding&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many companies now include DEI education as part of their onboarding programs. But they can no longer make assumptions about employee readiness for these conversations. For example, a student educated at a public institution in Florida is now expressly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wbur.org/onpoint/2023/05/23/what-the-desantis-agenda-means-for-higher-education-in-florida&quot;>;prohibited&lt;/a>; from taking a course that “teaches identity politics, or is based on theories that systemic racism, sexism, oppression, and privilege are inherent in the institutions of the United States.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers might therefore need to implement surveys to understand how much new hires know about DEI and take greater care in explaining to new team members why those principles matter to the organization, not just how they&#39;re implemented.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Performance reviews, pay, promotions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As DEI efforts become more highly scrutinized, there is even more reason to make sure your people processes are equitable. Performance evaluations and pay and promotion decisions should be based on standard and objective data — yet a multitude of research indicates that they remain riddled with bias, especially for members of historically marginalized racioethnic groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; found that 90% of people of color but only 72% of white people received notes about their personalities in their reviews. Now is a good time to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;audit these processes&lt;/a>; so no one can argue that you are favoring people of one race over another.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Communicating Carefully &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2023/06/08/more-americans-disapprove-than-approve-of-colleges-considering-race-ethnicity-in-admissions-decisions/&quot;>;public polling&lt;/a>; is any indication employee reaction to the affirmative action ruling will depend on their race and ethnicity, political affiliation, and how they have seen affirmative action framed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Adept managers should be able to surface and address different opinions, show empathy, create employee feedback and support systems, and regularly communicate about these issues. Tools to use include one-on-one meetings (if a few employees are highly concerned); town halls (if many people are worried); emails (if many people have low-intensity interest); or simply monitoring the situation for now (if awareness remains low among most people.) &amp;nbsp;Conversations might be difficult, but it is important for teams to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/dig-bridge-collectively-act&quot;>;dig into sometimes polarizing topics, bridge divides, and agree on collective action&lt;/a>; where possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A cornerstone of successful communication is to include research from credible outlets but, in these polarized times, it can be challenging to find &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/journalism/2020/01/24/us-media-polarization-and-the-2020-election-a-nation-divided/&quot;>;sources&lt;/a>; trusted by all employees. We recommend identifying multiple ones and explaining the vetting process to employees. Organizations will also benefit from conducting surveys to learn about differing views and identifying and seeking input on informal leaders on all sides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With both facts and opinions in hand, leaders will be better equipped to communicate effective messages about their DEI plans. They might, for example, acknowledge that some employees disagree with race-conscious recruiting, or think DEI efforts should be dropped for legal or cost-saving reasons, but explain that the organization prioritizes the increased innovation that comes from having a more diverse team or simply having a workforce that represents the broader society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is important that everyone engages on this issue. While some organizations relegate DEI to HR and HR alone, this is a mistake. Messaging on — and commitment to — DEI should be understood and communicated by everyone from frontline managers to the CEO, especially now when racial tensions remain high and policies like affirmative action are being questioned.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Moving Forward&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that the media furor over &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions v Harvard University and the University of North Carolina&lt;/em>; has slightly abated, organizations have a moment to strategically reflect on how their DEI efforts may be affected. We believe corporate leaders should resist the urge or pressure to backpedal on DEI commitments. Instead, they should enhance DEI in a manner that complies with the law, aligns with their organizational values, and benefits their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Be a Purpose-Driven Leader Without Burning Out]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1298982699.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Grizelj/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The idea of servant leadership &amp;#8212; putting your team&amp;#8217;s needs ahead of your own &amp;#8212; brought us to a more compassionate, human-centered work environment. But in today&amp;#8217;s environment, it&amp;#8217;sa recipe for burnout. Instead, the authors suggest a more impact-driven philosophy called &amp;#8220;noble-purpose leadership,&amp;#8221; that ties leaders and teammates to the pursuit of a shared goal that positively impacts constituents. In servant leadership, the message is: You&amp;#8217;re in your role to serve others, making it tempting to focus on pleasing others and difficult to say no. In noble-purpose leadership, the message is: You&amp;#8217;re in your role to make an impact. This requires more strategic thinking in terms of where to place your efforts. The authors offer three areas where managers can shift their lens to noble-purpose leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When Robert Greenleaf coined the phrase “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenleaf.org/what-is-servant-leadership/&quot;>;servant leadership&lt;/a>;” in a seminal 1970 essay, it was a much-needed improvement over the traditional command-and-control leadership model that had prevailed for centuries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The servant-leader is servant first. It begins with the natural feeling that one wants to serve. Then conscious choice brings one to aspire to lead,” Greenleaf wrote. “That person is sharply different from one who is leader first, perhaps because of the need to assuage an unusual power drive or to acquire material possessions.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Well-documented research tells us that organizations and individuals &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-humble-leadership-really-works&quot;>;perform better&lt;/a>; when leaders focus on the team rather than themselves. On an individual level, servant leadership &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.regent.edu/journal/emerging-leadership-journeys/impact-of-servant-leadership/&quot;>;increases&lt;/a>; followers&#39; trust, loyalty, and satisfaction with the leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet, much has changed in the 50 years since Greenleaf&#39;s original essay, particularly in the last three years. The narrative behind servant leadership is increasingly falling flat, for good reason:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Rampant burnout.&lt;/strong>; In today&#39;s environment, when leaders are tired, overworked, and stressed, serving can feel like pouring from an empty cup. We tell managers, “You&#39;re here to serve your team.” We tell customer-facing teams, “You&#39;re here to serve customers&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;” The sum of it is exhausting.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;People are busier&lt;/strong>;. When Greenleaf originally introduced servant leadership, a typical manager likely supervised a small functional team. They didn&#39;t have their own deliverables, they weren&#39;t on multiple cross-functional initiatives, and they didn&#39;t start their day answering an onslaught of overnight emails. &amp;nbsp;Today, as middle management continues to thin out, leaders typically have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/how-to-identify-the-right-spans-of-control-for-your-organization&quot;>;between 11 to 15 direct reports&lt;/a>; and their own high stakes deliverables. These exhausted managers often feel they don&#39;t have the time to devote to servitude.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Workplaces have become less hierarchical&lt;/strong>;. Today&#39;s org charts often resemble a jungle gym more than they do a &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/stop-offering-career-ladders-start-offering-career-portfolios&quot;>;ladder&lt;/a>;. Leading without formal authority is on the rise and begs the question: Who is the servant and who is served?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Servant leadership was a crucial stepping-stone into a more humane world of work. But the next evolution is upon us. &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/to-retain-employees-give-them-a-sense-of-purpose-and-community&quot;>;The workplace data&lt;/a>; (and our own experiences) tells us that we&#39;re at an inflection point. We&#39;re standing in a moment in time where leaders, both formal and informal, must move forward towards a more purposeful leadership style that focuses on the impact that the organization&#39;s work has on real live human beings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We refer to this impact-driven philosophy as “noble-purpose leadership.” It&#39;s when leaders and teammates alike are in shared pursuit of a cause bigger than themselves (their team, their customers, their community) and their goal is to positively impact their constituents (versus serving them).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a nuanced, yet distinct shift. In servant-driven leadership, the crux of the message is: &lt;em>;You&#39;re in your role to serve others&lt;/em>;. This makes it very hard to say no, and there&#39;s a temptation for leaders (and their teams) to be reactive, trying to please everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In noble-purpose leadership, the core message is: &lt;em>;You&#39;re in your role to make an impact&lt;/em>;. This requires more strategic thinking in terms of where to place your efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When your North Star is a shared purpose, leaders have more choice in the matter; you don&#39;t feel as required to please everyone. In our consulting practice, we&#39;ve seen first-hand evidence that noble-purpose leadership can be an effective evolution toward driving better performance while staying true to a culture of service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three areas where managers can shift their lens towards noble-purpose leadership:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Employee Interactions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managers are often taught to ask their people questions like: What can I do to help you be successful? What kind of support do you need from me? While these are excellent questions (and will certainly get better results than barking orders) well-intended leaders find themselves leaving these interactions with an exhausting list of action items. After a few experiences like that, overworked managers often find it easier not to even ask their team what kind of help they need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rather than giving up on the idea of being supportive, managers can create a subtle, yet powerful shift by calibrating to a higher purpose, and asking questions like: What do &lt;em>;you &lt;/em>;need to be successful in accomplishing our goal? What help will &lt;em>;you&lt;/em>; need to get? This small language change reframes the emotional dynamic. Instead of the leader having to be solely responsible for supporting the employee, asking the employee what they need to be successful creates a shared sense of responsibility. The leader is purposefully positioning themselves to have a positive impact on the employee&#39;s results, yet they&#39;re not taking on sole responsibility for supporting them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s a before and after of how this worked for a client of ours, a vice president who was stretched thin with 12 direct reports and an endless list of their own deliverables. Being a servant leader felt exhausting and impossible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The VP started asking their project managers, “Given our purpose to positively impact our customers, what kind of support will you need to get this done well, and on time?” The project managers quickly determined they needed resources and support from another department to meet the deadline.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Had the VP stuck with the traditional, “What do you need from me?” both parties would have suffered. The VP would have had more on their plate than they could manage, and the project managers wouldn&#39;t have engaged with the other department. With a sightline to the shared purpose (successfully completing a project that improves life for customers), both the leader and their team members become more empowered and effective.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Decision Making &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When your primary focus is to serve, the temptation is to focus on pleasing people&lt;em>; — &lt;/em>;an endless and often fruitless, endeavor. &amp;nbsp;Many elements of work, like tight deadlines and challenging feedback, are inherently displeasing, no matter what the leader does.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When a leader frames their decisions solely through a lens of trying to be as helpful and supportive to their constituents as possible, it&#39;s a recipe for burnout. At worst, it breeds entitlement, where employees think the leader&#39;s job is to do nothing but make them happy. The sum of this emotional turmoil can keep leaders from making tough (but correct) decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, leaders can frame their decisions around purpose. For example, in meetings, rather than asking: How do you feel about this? Does this work for you? Leaders can ask: What impact will this have? How will this affect our people or our customers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Katherine, the head of customer success for a medical device company, used this model to shift her team from complaining to action. Part of the team&#39;s function was to keep customers abreast of delivery times. This included making personal calls to customers when their orders were delayed. After a particularly frustrating day, her team came to Katherine with a request: They no longer want to make these calls. Her team lamented &lt;em>;“Some customers don&#39;t even notice if their order was delayed!”&lt;/em>; Others piled on, &lt;em>;“We can&#39;t speed up the delivery truck! What&#39;s the point of calling? If they&#39;re worried, they call us.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A leader simply trying to please the team would have been tempted to let the team stop making the calls or they might have taken on the calls themselves. &amp;nbsp;Instead, Katherine used questions to recalibrate the team to a higher purpose. She asked: “How will it affect our customers if they are caught off guard, and don&#39;t know the order would be late? How would it impact our reputation if we stop being proactive and are only reactive?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This seemingly simple shift of the lens prompted the team to think about how their work impacts the overarching purpose of the organization. It changed their thought process: Rather than focusing on their own reaction, they began &amp;nbsp;considering the impact on the team and seeing themselves as part of the larger whole. The team decided to keep making the calls, but rotate the responsibility, so everyone wasn&#39;t having to make them every day. Recalibrating the team towards a higher purpose, reduces the pressure on the leader and increases buy-in from the team.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Coaching&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A primary function of any leader is &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;coaching their team&lt;/a>;. However, when coaching is added on top of deliverables, leaders may struggle to invest time in the development of their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recently, during a coaching program we ran for a group of sales managers in the hospitality industry, participants opened up about feeling overwhelmed. The organization has an exceptional culture and managers generally want to do a good job leading their teams. Yet, as travel began to boom, and they added more salespeople, managers found themselves stretched thin.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We asked the managers, “Who do you coach?” Their answer was almost unanimous: the people who are performing the worst. Yet, the sales managers lamented that despite their sizeable coaching investments, the poor performers were showing marginal improvement at best.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We then shifted the lens from servant leadership to noble-purpose leadership. Instead of asking who needs coaching the most, we suggested managers ask themselves: Where will my coaching time have the biggest impact?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The managers started to look at their team through a different lens: Who is the most coachable? Who learns quickly? Who has the most at stake with their customers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After the program ended, these managers began to invest more of their time in their high and mid-performers. They personally coached the high performers on their highest-value opportunities. They gave their mid-performers more attention with group coaching circles and peer-to-peer role plays. They didn&#39;t abandon coaching the bottom tier, but instead of spending hours of their coaching time, they directed lower performers to own more of their learning, via on-demand courses, self-study, etc.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The results followed quickly: High performers got even better, and mid-performers improved too. What&#39;s also interesting is that low performers did one of three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Worked their way to become middle performers&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Stayed the course, making the same marginal improvements as they did when they were taking nearly all of their manager&#39;s coaching time&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Or, when faced with the challenge of taking some ownership in their development, they self-selected out — a process that happened faster and with less frustration than a manager spending hours of time trying to coach a player who doesn&#39;t want to improve.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Overall, the team drove record revenue, and they were more fulfilled doing it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Servant leadership brought us to a more compassionate, human-centered work environment. It&#39;s time for us to make the next leap. In today&#39;s environment, burned-out leaders endlessly trying to serve will struggle to drive the innovation, resilience, and sense of meaning required for future growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Elevating the lens to noble-purpose leadership has the power to unite employees and managers in the pursuit of making a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overcoming Your Fear of Giving Tough Feedback]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1379555.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Juan Moyano/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A lack of constructive feedback is detrimental to your team, depriving them of mentorship and growth opportunities. And workplaces marked by poor communication and unclear expectations are breeding grounds for low trust and disengagement. Giving feedback is essential to being an effective leader. In this article, the author offers five ways to overcome your fear of giving feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“I felt like I was going to throw up,” Filip confessed to me during our coaching session. “Giving feedback is something a leader should be able to do every day without breaking a sweat,” he said. “But for me, it feels like the end of the world.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip was the director of project management at a company that offered translation services for streaming content providers across the globe. Hard working (sometimes to a fault), Filip was an expert at juggling multiple priorities, coordinating translators, quality control experts, and client liaisons across time zones, languages, and cultures. He had a knack for thriving in ambiguity, keeping his eye on strategic goals without getting lost in minutiae.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip also prided himself on always having his team&#39;s back, even if it involved taking the heat from an irate executive. But when it came to delivering feedback to his direct reports, Filip&#39;s resilient exterior crumbled. He would be overcome with worries of damaging the relationships he had worked so hard to build. He&#39;d overthink what to say for hours &lt;/span>;— &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;sometimes days. The mere thought of uttering the words, “I have some feedback for you,” made him nauseous.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;When a high-stakes project spearheaded by Angelique, one of Filip&#39;s brightest team members, failed, it brought his fear of giving feedback into sharp focus. For two weeks Filip had sensed something was amiss. The team&#39;s low spirits and sluggish performance concerned him, but he told himself Angelique would pull everything together in the end. He never voiced his concerns, and the cost was devastating. Their biggest account would now be going to a different provider who could provide better service.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“I could have prevented this. I should have spoken up.” Filip told me. His story echoes a struggle I hear from many of my executive coaching clients: How do I overcome the fear of giving feedback?&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Whether you worry about causing tension, demotivating your people, or handling others&#39; emotional reactions, conflict aversion is a common trait, and managers aren&#39;t immune to it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You&#39;re not doing anyone a favor by avoiding conflict. When problems go unaddressed or are swept under the rug, everyone suffers, including you. A lack of constructive feedback is also detrimental to your team, depriving them of mentorship and growth opportunities. Workplaces marked by poor communication and unclear expectations are breeding grounds for low trust and disengagement.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here&#39;s how to navigate the sense of discomfort and apprehension that comes with difficult conversations, so you can say what needs to be said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Challenge binary thinking.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many leaders who avoid confrontation carry assumptions like, “no one likes a micromanager,” or “bringing up this issue will ruin our working relationship.” While these beliefs may stem from past experiences with rejection and failure, they reflect inaccurate, binary thinking. In actuality, it&#39;s possible to be both assertive and direct without damaging relationships or earning a reputation as the “difficult manager.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Instead, focus on what you could gain by speaking up and the potential rewards of clear communication. Not only will voicing your thoughts help you feel more confident, but:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your input may be exactly what&#39;s needed to drive a challenging assignment to completion&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;That candid comment you make to a coworker about their disruptive behavior could result in a more peaceful, productive work environment.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your constructive criticism could help a team member develop and grow in their role, opening up new career opportunities&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;When you look more closely, you&#39;ll see that expressing your thoughts, feelings, and opinions is far more beneficial than stuffing them down and suffering the consequences.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;See feedback as a tool.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Despite what you may believe, your team craves meaningful, candid feedback. While 72% of employees &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbswk.hbs.edu/item/why-people-crave-feedback-and-why-were-afraid-to-give-it&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;rated&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “managers providing critical feedback” as important for them in career development, only 5% believe managers provide such feedback. Likewise, when team members don&#39;t think their boss is great at giving honest feedback, their engagement scores &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/overcoming-feedback-phobia-take-the-first-step&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;typically&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; take a nosedive. But on the flip side, leaders who rank in the top 10% at giving honest feedback create teams that rank in the top 23% of engagement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;It&#39;s not fair to deprive your team of information they need to grow. When you reframe conflict as a healthy, normative part of leadership, it loosens the anticipatory anxiety you may feel broaching difficult topics with others. Next time you have to give feedback, take a deep breath and remember, you&#39;re not causing a conflict, you&#39;re guiding your people toward growth. You&#39;re not criticizing; you&#39;re nurturing. And you&#39;re certainly not being a villain; you&#39;re being the leader they need.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Anticipate eventualities.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Fear of the unknown or wondering how the recipient will react can hold many leaders back from ever speaking up. What if your direct report becomes defensive and lashes out at you? What if they start crying?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You can calm your anxiety and handle uncertainty using the worst case/best case/most likely tool. Consider the worst that could happen. If your employee cries, for example, how would you handle it? Perhaps you&#39;d take a time out. Then consider the best that could possibly happen to foster more optimism. Finally, consider what is most likely, which is usually somewhere between the two extremes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Start strong.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You can also ease your whirlwind of thoughts by planning your opening. Being in control from the get-go can provide a confidence boost and allows you to set a respectful tone for the conversation. Once Filip realized he needed to tackle the situation with Angelique head on, he approached her and said: “I appreciate your dedication and creativity. Something I wanted to talk about is a pattern of low morale, and I want to understand if there are any obstacles that we can address together.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Using “I” statements whenever possible helps ensure you communicate directly without vacillating or minimizing your concerns simply because you&#39;re scared. Being specific is also important. Rather than saying, “You dropped the ball again,” try saying, “I&#39;m concerned that I didn&#39;t get the documents in time for the client meeting today.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Make feedback part of the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Feedback should be a regular ritual, not an occasional blast. Making feedback a habit ensures the tiny annoyances and frustrations you harbor don&#39;t blow up into major conflicts. Plus, gradually exposing yourself to fearful situations is the best way to overcome them. The more you practice giving feedback in lower-stakes, everyday scenarios as part of your role, the better at it you&#39;ll become.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;A great way to systematize feedback is through regular &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones&quot;>;one-on-ones&lt;/a>; with your team. You can also schedule project debriefs where team members can reflect, or pre-mortems where people can discuss in advance any risks, potential problems, and flesh out how they&#39;ll work with one another.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Creating a positive feedback culture will give you opportunities to flex your newfound assertiveness skills while also strengthening rapport and trust with your team. And that, as a leader, is one of the best things you can hope for.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways Our Brains Undermine Our Ability to Be a Good Leader]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_1464364780.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Orla/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To be successful, researchers at the Neuroleadership Institute have found we must excel across three core domains of great leadership: being future-focused, being good with people, and being able to drive results. And yet, as we develop as leaders, our brains evolve in ways that challenge our ability to excel in these areas. The team analyzed dozens of leadership development programs used by larger organizations and discovered they often fail to equip leaders across all three domains. The good news is that we can be taught to combat these tendencies once we understand why our brains fight us.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Robin, a perennial high achiever, has just been promoted to her first leadership position. But her first few months on the job have been tougher than expected: Her colleagues don&#39;t joke around with her anymore, she&#39;s pulled in different directions, and she&#39;s constantly putting out fires. When one of her top performers suddenly leaves for another opportunity, Robin realizes her team is under-resourced. The pressure takes its toll, and Robin begins to dread Monday mornings. Maybe she just wasn&#39;t cut out to be a leader?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Robin&#39;s story is a familiar one. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90452760/first-time-leaders-need-to-stick-to-these-4-truths-to-succeed&quot;>;Sixty percent&lt;/a>; of new managers fail within the first 24 months. And this isn&#39;t just an issue for new managers: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2020/03/13/why-most-new-executives-fail-and-four-things-companies-can-do-about-it/?sh=6abf27d76730&quot;>;50% to 70%&lt;/a>; of new executives fail in the first 18 months, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be successful, our research at the Neuroleadership Institute has found we must excel across three core domains of great leadership: being future-focused, being good with people, and being able to drive results. And yet, as we develop as leaders, our brains evolve in ways that challenge our ability to excel in these areas. We analyzed dozens of leadership development programs used by larger organizations and discovered they often fail to equip leaders across all three domains. The good news is that we can be taught to combat these tendencies once we understand why our brains fight us.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Focus on the Future &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rather than just doing the work of today, leaders must constantly scan for what&#39;s next and make sure their teams are prepared. This is at odds with how our brains evolved to value the immediate and short-term future. Indeed, in one study, &lt;a href=&quot;https://legacy.iftf.org/americanfuturegap/&quot;>;27%&lt;/a>; of Americans say they rarely or never think about what might happen five years into the future. That&#39;s a concern because anticipating things like industry trends, future skills requirements, and customer needs is central to a leader&#39;s success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to management consultant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/10938&quot;>;Elliott Jaques&lt;/a>;, the higher you go in an organization, the further out you need to think. While a line manager might have to maintain a plan for a quarter, a CEO needs to think about where the business will be in 10 years. Jacques called this concept “time span.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenge, of course, is that thinking about the future is difficult in the best of times. The more people have to think about, the harder it is to notice the quiet signals that can provide insights about possible futures. Our brains also have to battle &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/00345&quot;>;distance bias&lt;/a>;, which causes us to prioritize ideas and decisions closer in time over things further in the future. What&#39;s more, only 16% of the executive leadership programs we studied have outcomes dedicated to thinking about the future, and the numbers are even lower for mid-level and first-time leader programs, at 4% and 6%, respectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, research suggests the habit of thinking about and predicting the future is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;learnable &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;skill&lt;/a>;, and it&#39;s one of many cognitive skills leaders can and should learn as part of leadership training. One way to get started is to block off time each month and map out a “future state” for where you&#39;d like your team to be in three to six months. Using that vision, then work backwards to determine what you&#39;d need to do to get your team to that destination in the next six months.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Your People Are Everything&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders are jugglers — and the things they juggle are often at odds. Take, for example, leaders&#39; overall responsibility: To deliver a business strategy that creates successful outcomes. And yet, they must also be good at connecting with and motivating their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These two tasks are often at odds because people often get promoted to leadership positions &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/transform-your-technical-expertise-into-leadership&quot;>;because of technical competence&lt;/a>;, not personability. Social neuroscientist Matthew Lieberman &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/should-leaders-focus-on-results-or-on-people&quot;>;points out&lt;/a>; that a leader who is both technically competent and highly personable is somewhat of a unicorn. He references one study in which a leader who was seen as focusing on results — which combines strong analytical skills with an intense motivation to move forward and solve problems — only had a 14% chance of being seen as a great leader. If a leader was strong only with social skills — attributes like communication and empathy — they were seen as a great leader even less, only 12%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, for leaders who were strong in both results &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; social skills, the likelihood of being seen as a great leader skyrocketed to 72%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So how many of these unicorns are out there? One of us (David), along with Tricia Naddaff, CEO of Management Research Group, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/your-brain-at-work/201310/find-out-how-many-leaders-are-both-goal-and-people-focused&quot;>;analyzed&lt;/a>; data from thousands of employees in which people rated their bosses on goal focus and people focus. Less than 1% of leaders were rated high on both.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It turns out there&#39;s a neurological reason for this. &lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;Neuroimaging studies&lt;/a>; have shown a seesaw effect exists for the separate brain centers responsible for goal focus and people focus: When one dials up, the other dials down. What&#39;s more, &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0146167207301011&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows that as an individual&#39;s power increases, the brain&#39;s goal-focus network becomes dominant. This process is adaptive because to make effective decisions as a leader, one must often detach from the needs of every individual and view them more as chess pieces than human beings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Getting the right balance between goal and people focus is the key. But according to our research, only 58% of executive leadership programs focus on people outcomes, with 64% and 51% for mid-level and first-time leaders, respectively. Knowing this, leaders can cultivate the right balance by being more intentional about sending the signals to employees that they&#39;re cared for.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Drive Realistic Results &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One of the biggest conundrums of leadership is the way our brains perceive power. As &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ejsp.324&quot;>;individuals perceive themselves&lt;/a>; to be more powerful, they tend to become more optimistic. This often leads to unrealistic targets and inflated expectations, which can cause a disconnect between leaders and their direct reports who are doing the heavy lifting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The result is that leaders become more “&lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;vision-focused&lt;/a>;” and less concerned with detail. Having a sense of power triggers our brain positively and makes us feel good in the same way winning money or getting a reward does. As soon as the brain is triggered this way, it seeks to activate more of those rewards by directing our behavior to power-rewarding activities, like thinking big picture or pursuing goals rather than focusing on details.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news is that by understanding the brain&#39;s tendency to become less detail-oriented and more visionary, you can counteract the urges by seeking other perspectives to stay realistic about the present and set more &lt;a href=&quot;https://neuroleadership.com/your-brain-at-work/putting-people-first&quot;>;people-focused goals&lt;/a>; that are tied to the welfare of others. For example, if you&#39;re embarking on a new project and think it should take three weeks to complete, ask for the perspectives of others who will execute the day-to-day tasks to ensure alignment on how much time it takes to deliver a quality product – and then be open to shifting your timeline, if possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Luckily for Robin, her company invested in a well-designed leadership program that balances all three challenging capabilities. Over the next six months, she gained insights that allowed her to better understand what makes her team tick while learning how to think ahead and balance various aspects of leadership with the tactical demands of the everyday. Although the brain might not be naturally built for leadership, with the right science-based training and habit formation, leaders at all levels can power through that tough Monday — and beyond.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Skills Provide a Development Path for Sub-Saharan Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_996888296.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;wilpunt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa is urbanizing with massive rural-urban migration. But unlike the urbanization of the Western world, Sub-Saharan Africa is missing a critical component: industrialized urban cities. Because of this, these urban areas have become overcrowded with substandard housing and severely inadequate infrastructure to cope with unplanned population growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, a new development playbook to solve this problem is already evolving, and it is anchored on the young people equipped with advanced digital skills in Sub-Saharan Africa. These young workers are digitally savvy, creative, and can lead a massive transformation &amp;#8212; if they&amp;#8217;re equipped and supported to unlock their potential. They can export digital skills to Western Europe, United States, and Asia through the unbounded and unconstrained opportunities the internet has provided through &amp;#8220;digital jobs&amp;#8221; from music to software development to prompt engineering. But to scale this and make it a success, changes must be taken into consideration at both the policy level and in implementation in the areas of quality digital education, tax treaties and harmonization, and outsourcing-focused startups.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa is urbanizing with massive rural-urban migration. But unlike the urbanization of the Western world decades and centuries ago, Sub-Saharan Africa is missing a critical component: industrialized urban cities. In other words, unlike in the Western world where industrialization preceded urbanization, Sub-Saharan Africa&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/documents/africas-urbanisation-dynamics-2022-economic-power-africas-cities&quot;>;urban cities&lt;/a>; are growing with marginal manufacturing output and industrial capacities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The implication is huge, as these urban areas have become overcrowded with substandard housing and severely inadequate infrastructure to cope with unplanned population growth. With limited taxes, urbanizing Sub-Saharan African cities are underfunded and could face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unicef.org/wca/press-releases/unicef-who%E2%80%AFcall-end-historic-underfunding-mental-health-services-africa&quot;>;severe challenges on healthcare delivery&lt;/a>; and overall social welfare. And with climate change affecting major cities like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/pidgin/articles/c97je2gzdlwo&quot;>;Lagos&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.africanews.com/2023/05/07/kenya-residents-on-a-mission-to-reduce-flooding-damage/&quot;>;Nairobi&lt;/a>;, the continent needs urgent solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to Statista, on average, the Sub-Saharan African urbanization rate stood at approximately &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/805657/urbanization-in-sub-saharan-africa/&quot;>;41.83%&lt;/a>; in 2021, even when the continent accounts for just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2016/11/23/figures-of-the-week-africa-industrialization-day/#:~:text=The%20average%20share%20of%20manufacturing,at%20just%20under%202%20percent.&quot;>;2% of the global manufacturing output&lt;/a>;. The implication is that those moving to the urban areas in search of economic opportunity aren&#39;t finding it, and that has resulted in high unemployment rates, especially among young people. The Brookings Institution estimates the youth unemployment rate in Africa to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2021/12/08/the-case-for-job-creation-hubs-to-reduce-youth-unemployment-in-africa/&quot;>;about 60%&lt;/a>;, while the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) puts the &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/press-material/facts-and-figures-7&quot;>;poverty rate at above 50%&lt;/a>; in most of the countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenges posed by this rapid “urbanization before industrialization” have been exacerbated by many factors, including an industrialization policy which has looked more backward than forward. For years, Sub-Saharan African leaders have been architecting a strategy to mimic what worked for China, which relies on an expectation that the Western world would outsource low-level factory jobs to Sub-Saharan Africa to stimulate a dynamic manufacturing sector once wages become relatively more expensive in China.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But, &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/09/why-africas-industrialization-wont-look-like-chinas&quot;>;as I&#39;ve noted before&lt;/a>;, it would be a huge mistake if Africa tries to pursue China&#39;s strategy. What worked for China is already expiring with advances in AI and robotics, making it nearly impossible for Western Europe and the United States to ship some of these low-level jobs outside their shores; robots will do the jobs at home. Instead, Sub-Saharan African policymakers must develop a new developmental playbook that takes into account the realities of the present state of the area.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fortunately, that new development playbook is already evolving, and it is anchored on the teeming young people in Sub-Saharan Africa. Over the last few years, in the process of running Tekedia Capital, an early-stage venture fund, and Tekedia Institute, a business school with thousands of students, I have collected enormous data on sectors, core economic indicators, freelancing, offshore jobs, and other factors. Based on the datasets, the path I see for the development of the continent goes through young people equipped with advanced digital skills. The young people in sub-Saharan Africa are digitally savvy, creative, and can lead a massive transformation if they&#39;re equipped and supported to unlock their potential, not just regionally but globally. These young people can export digital skills to Western Europe, United States, and Asia through the unbounded and unconstrained opportunities the internet has provided. In other words, while the West outsourced factory jobs to China, soon, they will outsource “&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/the-most-and-least-digital-jobs-and-how-well-they-pay&quot;>;digital jobs&lt;/a>;” in multifaceted ways to Sub-Saharan Africa. These digital jobs are diverse, from music to software development to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/the-hottest-job-in-tech-right-now-is-in-prompt-engineering/&quot;>;prompt engineering&lt;/a>;. For nations like Japan and South Korea where birth rates have remained low, Sub-Saharan Africa provides a readily available talent base, to remotely support their economies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some enabling infrastructures are in existence as the Sub-Saharan African region is experiencing deeper broadband penetration. Alongside a growing terrestrial broadband expansion, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/elon-musks-spacex-starlink-arrives-nigeria-meets-ncc-for-permit/&quot;>;arrival&lt;/a>; of SpaceX Starlink satellite broadband brings many promises on connectivity in both urban and rural areas. And with renewal energy startups, which use solar to provide energy services, young techies are overcoming infrastructure challenges, making it easier for them to participate in the global digital economy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These shifts allow young Sub-Saharan workers to earn income where they are, and once that income is imported, they have the capacities to contribute and transform their local economies at scale. Indeed, some digital experts, after they have made money working for international organizations, decide to start their own companies and, in the process, nurture other young talent. The continent has at &lt;a href=&quot;https://guardian.ng/technology/nigeria-produces-five-of-seven-unicorns-in-africa/&quot;>;least seven unicorns&lt;/a>; — startups valued at least $1 billion — and as they become listed in the public stock exchanges, acquired by large multinational firms, or grow to have abilities to pay good dividends, the wealth created would be used to accelerate development. More so, because of the digital nature of their jobs, there is no requirement to remain in even the urban areas; Andela, a digital skill outsourcing startup, for example, hires workers from anywhere in Sub-Saharan Africa, provided they have good internet service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But to scale this and make it a success, the following must be taken into consideration at both the policy level and in implementation:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Quality digital education: &lt;/strong>;The Covid-19 pandemic demonstrated that many Sub-Saharan African countries are still very low on digital readiness. While many universities in China, the US, and Europe were able to transition to remote learning, many Sub-Saharan African universities could not. Building infrastructures to support the future knowledge economy will be essential for Sub-Saharan Africa to unlock the huge potential of the youth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Tax treaties and harmonization:&lt;/strong>; In leading Sub-Saharan African economies like Nigeria, Ghana, and Kenya, most young people work for some of the leading companies in Europe, US, and Canada. Sub-Saharan African policy makers must ensure these workers are compensated fairly, and that they pay local taxes as required by law. A clear policy that makes it easier for global companies to hire and develop these talents should be part of the region&#39;s development priorities. Also important is making sure that burdensome taxation does not dim the young workers&#39; motivations. That calls for effective implementation and harmonization of tax treaties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Outsourcing-focused startups&lt;/strong>;: Regional and national policies should be developed to deepen the capacities of outsourcing-focused digital companies. These companies, like Andela, valued at excess of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/andela-becomes-a-unicorn-raises-200-million-at-1-5-billion-valuation/&quot;>;$1.5 billion&lt;/a>;, train young people and then export their digital skills to the world, while they remain in the continent. African embassies and missions in Europe, Asia, and North America could support them to connect with major clients, providing pipelines to hire the services of African youth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sub-Saharan Africa has young people to fuel the knowledge economy. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.un.org/ohrlls/news/young-people%E2%80%99s-potential-key-africa%E2%80%99s-sustainable-development&quot;>;According&lt;/a>; to the United Nations, “Africa has the youngest population in the world, with 70% of sub-Saharan Africa under the age of 30.” If the continent educates and trains them in the higher-level digital skills, Sub-Saharan Africa will develop within decades, and will experience its unique version of industrialization.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Journey to Cloud Smart: Executives Share Their Perspectives - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM VMWARE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/07/the-journey-to-cloud-smart-executives-share-their-perspectives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-0&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/hero-1024x682.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;In recent years, a growing number of organizations have turned to multiple public cloud providers to run their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some cases, the situation arises unintentionally, as separate teams prefer different platforms. Other times, it&#39;s the result of a strategic decision from organizations eager to gain the competitive and economic advantages of multiple clouds. These can include higher flexibility, lower costs, a greater capacity to monetize data, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet the journey to multi-cloud adoption can be long and painful. Along the way, many enterprises can face spikes in complexity and cost, not to mention and security concerns.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlocking the true potential of a multi-cloud approach—becoming “cloud smart”—requires being intentional and strategic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Struggle with Multi-Cloud Complexity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Multi-cloud challenges can take business leaders by surprise. Public cloud “looked really, really good on paper,” said William Brown, Cloud and Infrastructure Architect at ice Norway.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“After the initial burst of excitement, there&#39;s this phase of disillusionment—that things aren&#39;t going as well as had been expected,” said Tom Eck, SVP and Distinguished Engineer at Fiserv.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For Christoph Rode, senior vice president of Cloud Platforms at T-Systems (part of Deutsche Telekom AG), multi-cloud adoption led to challenges on several fronts. “You realize costs are spiraling even if you do cost control,” he said. “I need to control my costs. I need to control security, compliance, and I need help.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These experiences are not unique. According to a recent survey of nearly 6,000 IT leaders by Vanson Bourne commissioned by VMware, 70% say they struggle with multi-cloud challenges. Few enterprises have reached the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.vmware.com/reaching-multicloud-tipping-point&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;tipping point&lt;/a>; at which the strategic advantages of multi-cloud outweigh its complexities: 70% of companies have not yet achieved an advanced stage on their journey to multi-cloud adoption.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations experiencing these challenges are missing out on key opportunities around multi-cloud revenue, profitability, and data monetization that can deliver competitive advantages. They are also unable to enjoy multi-cloud data sovereignty and data security advantages that keep customers and employees loyal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Advantages of Being “Cloud Smart”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s a better approach to multi-cloud adoption. One in five organizations surveyed in the report could be considered “cloud smart,” or mature in their approach to multi-cloud. They are taking a planned and strategic approach to digital transformation and multi-cloud implementation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The security of your application, the accessibility of your application from various parts of the world, how you utilize these apps, to me, is really what the start of being cloud smart is,” says Joe Van Ert, system architect at Quality Bicycle Products.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These key factors are what separate cloud-smart organizations from those experiencing challenges with multi-cloud adoption:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Application innovation&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Visibility and cloud spend&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Cloud security&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Data management&amp;nbsp;culture and teams&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Regardless of where an enterprise is on the path to cloud adoption, it can adopt a cloud-smart mindset. Organizations that take this approach and draw on the right technology can reduce complexity and mitigate the challenges that come with juggling multiple clouds. Making the most of available cloud platforms allows businesses to maximize revenue and profitability, securely manage data across borders, and monetize the data at their fingertips.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Learn more about &lt;a href=&quot;http://vmware.com/multi-cloud&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;becoming a cloud-smart organization&lt;/a>;.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:55:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Questions Sales Teams Should Ask After Losing (or Winning) a Deal]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Daniel Creel&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When salespeople lose a deal, most prefer to move on rather than linger over the specifics of the loss. Similarly, when they win a deal, most are quick to celebrate. But very few take the time to assess &lt;em>;why&lt;/em>; they won the business. In the authors&amp;#8217; experience leading and coaching sales teams, they see evidence that a brief, well-pointed sales retrospective, where you unpack the reasons behind a win or a loss, can significantly improve a team&amp;#8217;s future win rate. Beyond the obvious benefits for the sales team &amp;#8212; for whom the process can help identify the best messaging and behaviors to use going forward &amp;#8212; unpacking wins and losses also provides valuable insights for product, marketing, and finance teams. Teams should ask three questions: 1) How would the customer articulate the value of their choice? 2) Who was the most influential voice in and out of the room? 3) Beyond price, what were the key deciding factors in the client&amp;#8217;s decision?&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When he read the email, “We&#39;ve decided to go in another direction,” it was like a punch to the stomach. Brent hung his head trying to absorb the loss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Brent, an account executive at a fintech company, had been so sure that this deal was going to go through that he&#39;d put it on his forecast to close the quarter. He had even mentally spent his commission. As he sat with the reality that he&#39;d lost the deal, he recognized there had been a few signs that the client wasn&#39;t fully engaged. Now, they were going to use someone else.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Brent knew he was going to have to tell his boss. But the last thing he wanted to do was spend a meeting unpacking his own failure. Maybe he could get another deal cooking before they talked and avoid what he was sure would be a painful conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When salespeople lose a deal, most prefer to move on rather than linger over the specifics of the loss. Similarly, when they win a deal, most are quick to celebrate. But very few take the time to assess &lt;em>;why&lt;/em>; they won the business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our experience leading and coaching sales teams, we see evidence that a brief, well-pointed sales retrospective, where you unpack the reasons behind a win or a loss, can significantly improve a team&#39;s future win rate. Beyond the obvious benefits for the sales team — for whom the process can help identify the best messaging and behaviors to use going forward — unpacking wins and losses also provides valuable insights for product, marketing, and finance teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The challenge is for leaders and sellers to dig beneath the traditional competitive analysis of pricing and features, to uncover the nuanced factors that played into the customer&#39;s buying decision. While salespeople may groan at the thought of taking a magnifying glass to the rearview mirror, particularly on a loss that may still be stinging, we find that spending even as little as 10 minutes on a retrospective yields big dividends.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Below are three questions organizations and individuals can use in a sales retrospective. The questions work whether the team won or lost the deal. They are designed to help the team understand the real issues driving customers&#39; buying decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How would the customer articulate the value of their choice?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders can pose the questions to the team after a deal closes or falls through. The process starts by challenging the team to go beyond the solution itself. Instead, focus on how the customers would articulate the effects of implementing their chosen solution, be it yours or your competitor&#39;s. For example, the solution may impact other departments at the client beyond the initial user group that sales traditionally talks to, or it may help the customer accomplish additional internal priorities. Looking beyond the obvious product users helps the team understand their larger impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you lost the deal, digging deeper through this lens will help you frame your positioning to create more urgency next time. If you won the deal, this information will help you take actions to ensure a high-value implementation from the client&#39;s perspective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the fintech firm described above, the sales retrospective revealed that the customer had placed a high value on a few product features, which they deemed must-haves for their internal team. The customer believed the competitor&#39;s offering was more robust in these areas. Getting specific during the retrospective prompted the product team at Brent&#39;s company to make some minor tweaks that put them at parity. Marketing also gleaned information about how to adjust their materials to highlight the changes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unpacking a loss typically helps identify opportunities. But there are also benefits to unpacking a win. Asking the salespeople involved how the customer would articulate the value of your solution creates a shared win for the entire team. In a tight economy, playing up the wins, versus exclusively unpacking losses, reminds your sales team that customers find your solution valuable and that many are still buying.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Who was the most influential voice in and out of the room?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Oftentimes, key decision makers, influencers, and subject matter experts aren&#39;t revealed until after the deal has been decided. Knowing who these people are in a deal that you won prepares you for implementation. Knowing whose voices carried strong weight when you lost a deal helps the sales team address these influencers earlier in the sales process during future pursuits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unpacking a loss more holistically by looking at the players and the value story can help a sales team move beyond the sting of rejection. It&#39;s worth noting that an environment of shame and blame rarely produces great insight. Instead focus on what they can do differently next time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When the fintech firm looked more closely at the decision makers, it became clear that the CIO had made the final call. While most of the sales calls had been with the user group, it was the CIO who identified the must-have features that cost the team the deal. Knowing this prompted sales enablement to create additional training to help the sales team become more skilled at calling on CIOs. The marketing team developed a new deck showcasing how their offering addressed typical CIO challenges, and finance developed models to showcase their net-positive impact over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Beyond price, what were the key deciding factors in the client&#39;s decision?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When a team loses a deal, it&#39;s easy to blame it on pricing. Asking the team to think about why a client makes decisions for reasons other than price will allow them to reflect on the full value of the solution. It will also allow them to take a broader look at how their own offering stacks up in a competitive landscape. When you lose a deal, this question will help your team uplevel their skills by being more attuned to the nuances in the future. Conversely, when you win, unpacking why you won beyond pricing strengthens the team&#39;s confidence, which helps you hold margin going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It can also be helpful to ask the buyers themselves what other factors played into the decision. They may not even be aware of the subtle things that drove their thinking until they&#39;re asked to unpack it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After the loss, the fintech team went back to their client to ask why they choose the competitor, allowing the team to get more detailed information about the perceived product differences. Keeping the conversation neutral without trying to re-pitch the sale created an environment where the client was willing to share. The loss still hurt, but the deep insights they gained directly from a client helped the team adjust their offering going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While the benefits of a sales retrospective are clear, the challenge is often in assessing when to use one. Organizations can have hundreds or thousands of deals in a quarter, and not all warrant introspection. The temptation is to limit retrospectives to large deals that didn&#39;t close at the end of the quarter. However, in our experience, emotions are so high at that time that the utility of retrospectives is usually low.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, we find it helpful for sales leaders to have at least one retrospective per account executive per quarter. That enables the team to gather information that is valuable for multiple functions in the company. Perhaps most importantly, this approach will train the sales team to think about why they actually won or lost independent of a retrospective.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regardless of which deals a leader selects to discuss, going from no retrospectives to a few will be a considerable achievement and deliver insights that may change the go-to-market strategy. Through running deeper sales retrospectives, the fintech firm was able to tweak their offering, upskill their sales team, and create a stronger presence with a key set of buyers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For most leaders, it will take time to drive an impact similar to what was achieved in the case study, but along the way, account executives will feel heard, sales will be more effective, and the go-to-market teams will be able to better support sales. Ultimately, this enables leaders to turn small losses into a big win.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>