<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Should You Start a Generative AI Company?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/should-you-start-a-generative-ai-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anja Sušanj 的插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;许多企业家正在考虑创办公司，利用最新的生成式 AI 技术，但他们必须问问自己，他们是否具备在日益商品化的基础上进行竞争的能力模型，或者他们是否应该在利用这些模型的应用程序上进行区分。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06 /should-you-start-a-generative-ai-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/should-you-start-a-generative- ai-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;我正在考虑创办一家采用生成式 AI 的公司，但我不确定是否要这样做。离开地面似乎很容易。但是，如果这对我来说很容易，那么对其他人来说岂不是也很容易吗？&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今年，问我这个问题的企业家比其他任何人都多。生成式 AI 令人兴奋的部分原因在于它的优势似乎是无限的。例如，如果你已经设法创建了一个具有某种通用语言推理能力的人工智能模型，那么你就有了一种智能，可以适应各种新产品，这些新产品也可以利用这种能力——比如屏幕写作、营销材料、教学软件、客户服务等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，软件公司 Luka 构建了一个名为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://replika.com/&quot;>;Replika&lt;/a>; 的 AI 伴侣，它使客户能够与“人工智能朋友”进行开放式对话。由于这项技术非常强大，Luka 的管理人员开始收到入站请求，要求为希望改善聊天机器人客户服务的企业提供白标企业解决方案。最后，Luka 的经理使用相同的底层技术衍生出了企业解决方案和直接面向消费者的 AI 约会应用程序（想想 Tinder，但用于“约会”AI 角色）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在决定无论生成式人工智能公司是否适合你，我建议确定以下两个大问题的答案：1）你的公司会在基础模型上竞争，还是在利用这些基础模型的顶层应用程序上竞争？以及 2) 在高度脚本化的解决方案和高度生成的解决方案之间的连续统一体中，贵公司将位于何处？根据您对这两个问题的回答，这将对您在竞争中保护自己的能力产生长期影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;基础模型还是应用程序？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;科技巨头现在正在租赁出他们最通用的专有模型——即“基础模型”——像 Eluether.ai 和 Stability AI 这样的公司正在以极低的成本提供这些基础模型的开源版本。基础模型正在变得&lt;em>;商品化&lt;/em>;，只有少数初创公司有能力在这个领域竞争。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您可能认为基础模型最有吸引力，因为它们将被广泛使用它们的许多应用将为增长提供有利可图的机会。更重要的是，我们生活在激动人心的时代，一些最复杂的 AI 已经可以“现成”使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;想要将公司建立在基础模型之上的企业家正在不过，这是一个挑战。与任何商品化市场一样，能够生存下来的公司是那些以低价提供非捆绑产品或提供日益增强的能力的公司。例如，Deepgram 和 Assembly AI 等语音转文本 API 不仅相互竞争，而且还通过提供更便宜的非捆绑解决方案与亚马逊和谷歌等公司竞争。即便如此，这些公司仍在价格、速度、模型准确性和其他功能方面展开激烈的竞争。相比之下，亚马逊、Meta 和谷歌等科技巨头进行了大量的研发投资，使他们能够在图像、语言和（越来越多的）音频和视频推理方面不断取得前沿进展。例如，它是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/13/chatgpt-and-generative-ai-are-booming-but-at-a-very-expensive-price。 html&quot;>;估计&lt;/a>; OpenAI 花费了 2 到 1200 万美元来计算训练 ChatGPT——这只是他们提供的几个 API 之一，还有更多 API 正在开发中。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与其竞争在日益商品化的基础模型上，大多数初创公司应该通过提供利用其他公司基础模型的“顶层”软件应用程序来区分自己。为此，他们可以根据客户解决方案独有的高质量专有数据集微调基础模型，为客户提供高价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，营销内容创建者，&lt;em >;Jasper AI，&lt;/em>;主要通过利用 OpenAI 的基础模型成长为独角兽。时至今日，该公司仍在使用 OpenAI 帮助客户为博客、社交媒体帖子、网站副本等生成内容。同时，该应用程序为其营销人员和撰稿人客户量身定制，提供专门的营销内容。该公司还提供其他专业工具，例如多个团队成员可以协同工作的编辑器。既然该公司已经获得了牵引力，那么它可以在未来花费更多的资源来减少对基础模型的依赖，而基础模型正是这些基础模型首先使它能够实现增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于顶层应用程序是这些公司找到竞争优势的地方，他们在保护数据集隐私免受大型技术玩家攻击之间处于微妙的平衡，即使他们依赖这些玩家的基础模型。鉴于此，一些初创公司可能会想要建立自己的内部基础模型。然而，鉴于上述挑战，这不太可能很好地利用宝贵的启动资金。大多数初创公司最好利用基础模型来快速发展，而不是重新发明轮子。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;从脚本化到生成&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您的公司需要从纯脚本化到连续统一体纯生成的解决方案。脚本化解决方案涉及从预定义的脚本化响应数据集中选择适当的响应，而生成式解决方案涉及从头开始生成新的、独特的响应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;脚本化解决方案更安全且受限，但也缺乏创造性和人性化，而生成解决方案风险更大且不受约束，但也更具创造性和人性化。对于某些用例和行业（例如医疗和教育应用程序），需要更多脚本化方法，这些应用程序和行业需要明确限制应用程序的功能。然而，当脚本达到极限时，用户可能会失去参与度，客户保留率可能会受到影响。此外，开发脚本化解决方案更具挑战性，因为您从一开始就限制了自己，限制了您以后的选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一方面，更具生成性的解决方案也面临着自己的挑战。由于基于 AI 的产品包括智能，因此消费者在如何与它们互动方面有更大的自由度，从而增加了风险。例如，一位已婚父亲在与 AI 聊天机器人应用程序 Chai&lt;em>;&lt;/em>; 对话后不幸自杀，该应用程序鼓励他牺牲自己来拯救地球。该应用程序利用了 EluetherAI 的基础语言模型（GPT-4 的定制版本）。 Chai 的创始人后来修改了该应用程序，以便在提及自杀意念时提供有用的文本。有趣的是，Chai 的创始人之一 Thomas Rianlan 承担了责任，他说：“将这个悲惨的故事归咎于 EleutherAI 的模型是不准确的，因为所有朝着更情绪化、有趣和引人入胜的优化都是&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑到底层 AI 的“黑匣子”性质，管理人员很难预测高度生成的应用程序可能出错的所有方式。这样做涉及预测可能非常罕见的风险场景。预测此类情况的一种方法是付钱给人工注释者来筛选可能有害类别的内容，例如性、仇恨言论、暴力、自残和骚扰，然后使用这些标签来训练自动标记此类内容的模型。然而，仍然很难提出详尽的分类法。因此，部署高生成解决方案的管理人员必须准备好主动预测风险，这既困难又昂贵。如果以后您决定将您的解决方案作为服务提供给其他公司，情况也是如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因为完全生成的解决方案更接近自然的、类人智能，所以从保留的角度来看，它更具吸引力和增长，因为它更具吸引力并且可以应用于更多新用例。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;strong>;&lt;br>; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;许多企业家正在考虑创办利用最新生成人工智能技术的公司，但他们必须问自己，他们是否具备在日益商品化的基础模型上竞争的能力，或者他们是否应该在利用这些技术的应用程序上脱颖而出&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他们还必须考虑他们希望在从高度脚本化解决方案到高度生成解决方案的连续统一体中提供什么类型的应用程序，考虑到每种应用程序的不同优缺点。提供更具脚本性的解决方案可能更安全，但会限制他们的保留和增长选择，而提供更具生成性的解决方案充满风险，但更具吸引力和灵活性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们希望企业家会提出这些问题&lt;em >;在 &lt;/em>; 进入他们的第一个生成 AI 企业之前，这样他们就可以就他们想成为什么样的公司做出明智的决定，快速扩大规模，并保持长期的防御能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引文-->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Advance Your Career When Your Company Is Downsizing]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_I6JrdSA3DwE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论员工/Simone Hutsch/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;在公司裁员期间提升你的职业生涯需要转变你的思维方式和行动。在这篇文章中，作者提供了五种策略来将逆境变成你专业成长的垫脚石：1) 重构你的思维。 &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;2) &lt;/span>;填充真空。 3) 寻找速赢。 4) 稍后协商。 5) 横向移动。&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;作为一家制造公司的运营总监，Marlow 走上了发展的快车道。去年，她的团队规模扩大了一倍，这在很大程度上要归功于她带领他们度过动荡的变革并推动一系列重要的供应链计划的能力。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Marlow 的成果和奉献精神使她获得了一个激动人心的机会 - 一个新设立的流程优化副总裁职位。晋升是她设定的目标，代表着在塑造公司未来的同时产生更大影响的机会。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight : 400;&quot;>;不幸的是，就在 Marlow 正处于这一重大职业转变的风口浪尖时，市场开始低迷，公司的利润也随之迅速下滑。面对经济挑战，必须做出艰难的决定。 Marlow 曾经蒸蒸日上的团队被削减了一半，更糟糕的是，她热切期待的副总裁职位也被解散了。她发现自己处于十字路口，质疑当她的愿望是 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/what-to-do-when-youre-passed-over-for-an-internal- 时如何前进position&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;看似出轨&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;许多领导者和专业人士发现自己处于 Marlow 的位置 — 感到沮丧和 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-deal-with-layoff -anxiety&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;不确定&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;随着公司裁员，如何提升他们的职业生涯.难怪什么时候裁员&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/06/layoffs-are-up-nearly-fivefold-so-far-this-year-with -tech-companies-leading-the-way.html&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;2023 年增长近五倍&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight : 400;&quot;>; 金融不稳定看不到尽头。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;组织一直在寻找削减成本的方法，他们的底线。虽然这可能意味着支出冻结和裁员等毁灭性变化，但这不一定会毁掉你的职业前景。事实上，它可以成为增长的跳板。以下是应对成本削减措施带来的干扰并变得更强大的方法。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;重构您的思维。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;经历一系列情绪——悲伤、愤怒、&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/stop-being-so-hard-on-yourself&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;自我怀疑&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; — 在组织动荡时期很自然。但是，关闭、避免这种情况并为自己感到难过会让你无处可去，只会让你感到被困住。相反，将变化和不确定性作为工作描述的一部分。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;无论原因是技术进步、不断变化的市场动态、或不断变化的客户期望，公司正在重组 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jonesday.com/en/insights/2022/01/recent-trends-in-corporate-debt-and-reorganizations-laying -the-groundwork-for-future-large-chapter-11-cases-or-just-more&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;快速发展&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>; span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;.您必须随时为大大小小的转变做好准备。困难时期揭示了您的性格以及最需要您的领导能力的地方。您可以选择采用这样一种观点，将动荡视为一个严峻的时刻，它提供了提供价值的机会，并成为一个有弹性、有影响力的领导者，推动积极变革。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;填补真空。&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;挺身而出填补流沙造成的空白。变化可能令人不安，这就是稳定性变得至关重要的原因。使您的工作与公司的新优先事项保持一致，这些优先事项通常包括关注核心产品、成本控制和运营效率，以及员工和客户保留。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;尽管遇到了挫折，但 Marlow 很快意识到在经济低迷时期降低成本并高度关注关键业务领域的重要性。 Marlow 将她的团队的工作重新调整为仅针对基本操作。列出几个创新项目是一个艰难的决定，但马洛的精明引起了高级管理人员的注意，他们赞赏她展示的战略优先次序。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;寻找快速的胜利。&lt;/ b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;乱世之中，人人都在寻找救世主。从初级员工一直到最高管理层，士气和信心很可能在整个链条上上下波动。通过确定需要改进的领域并迅速采取行动，您可以将自己定位为宝贵的资产，在取得成果的同时将公司的最大利益放在心上。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;寻找在短时间内产生切实影响的方法。例如，您可以：&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;br>; &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;重新谈判供应商合同&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;寻找更便宜的材料采购方式&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;与其他部门合作以节约资源&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;实施自动化以简化流程&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;向未开发的客户群推出您的产品&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;开展活动以促进重复购买&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;谈判&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;副总裁职位被解散后，Marlow 向她的经理解释说她了解公司的财务限制以及原因她一直期待的流程优化角色被解散了。然后她提出了一种平衡组织需求的方法，同时牢记她的长期目标。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“虽然我理解现在可能无法进行重大更改，我想讨论一下重新审视我的范围的可能性，”她说。 “我现在可以承担 X 项职责，但承诺在未来市场改善时探索流程优化领域的机会。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;像马洛一样，你也想看看房间。现在可能不是要求对你的角色、责任或报酬进行重大改变的时候，但你可以尝试在以后获得承诺。例如，“我很乐意现在接受 X，只要承诺在未来重新审视我的范围。”或者“我想帮忙，但我的最终目标是朝 Y 方向走。你认为你什么时候可以做到这一点？”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;横向移动。&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp ;&lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;虽然裁员期间向上和向左的职业发展可能受到限制，但横向移动仍然可以提供机会学习新技能并获得新经验。横向移动可以让您拓宽技能组合，从而增强您的多才多艺，并使您成为组织更有价值的资产。假设您担任销售职务。横向跳槽到产品开发团队可以让你深入了解产品开发流程、市场调研和客户需求分析。提供您的销售见解意味着公司可以更好地使他们的产品与市场需求保持一致。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;横向调动还可以让您接触到新同事并扩展您的专业网络。这可以为未来项目的合作、指导机会和获得更广泛的内部政治知识打开大门。此外，它还能让您接触到新的利益相关者、决策者和高级领导。你认识的人越多 — &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/what-to-do-when-your-hard-work-is-being-overlooked&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;认识你的人越多&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;——你的机会就越多。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;在公司裁员期间提升您的职业生涯需要转变您的思维方式和行动。通过采用这些策略，您可以将逆境变成专业成长的垫脚石。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Will AI Replace the Front Office in Pro Sports?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_516776669.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论员工/Gizelka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;通过对所有活跃玩家的准确玩家可用性预测，人工智能驱动的决策在三个方面得到显着改进：1) 风险管理：例如，如果一名高效的外接手可能受伤，球队可能会在有天赋的替补上投入更多，以尽量减少受伤期间球队表现的下降。 2) 训练和有针对性的干预：如果人工智能表明一名球员容易受伤，球队可以针对该球员进行定制训练、营养或其他方案，以减少受伤的可能性。或者，球队可能会选择减少球员的工作量，同时降低风险。 3) 人事决定：通过确定预测伤病或其他无法上场的因素，球队可以选秀、交易或以其他方式获得他们认为更有可能在整个赛季都上场的球员。此外，球队可能会选择交易可能受伤的球员。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will -ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the- front-office-in-pro-sports?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;2023年3月15日，国足新赛季正式拉开序幕。这也意味着 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcsports.com/boston/patriots/nfl-free-agency-tracker-2023-top-players-signings-start-time-cap-space&quot; 的开始>;自由代理期&lt;/a>;，当球队与不再与前球队签订合同的球员进行交易时；每一份新合同都可能意味着团队预算的数百万美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此正确招聘至关重要。与任何企业一样，NFL 高管和其他职业运动队的领导者必须就如何最好地分配他们有限的预算做出决定，对他们将从资产（在这种情况下为球员）中获得的投资回报率进行明智的押注，包括与预期表现相关的投资回报率（场上和场下）、未来的伤病和其他因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但如果今年，人工智能可以告诉我们一名球员在他们的职业生涯中还剩下多少场比赛，他们接下来会得到多少分呢？赛季，或者他们是否会在不久的将来遭受重大伤病？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然自由球员和其他招募机制已经存在了几十年，&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;关于球员的决定正在发生变化迅速。具体而言，将基于 AI 的技术应用于大量体育数据集正在增强前台部门对球员做出决策的能力——招募、培养、替补或交易谁。它将永久性地改变所有职业运动的运作方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是 AI 会很快取代运动队的前台吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这项新技术肯定会增强人类的决策-我们认为它不会在不久的将来取代体育或其他行业的一般管理团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;改变游戏规则的预测能力&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Amid越来越多的以人工智能为基础的以体育为中心的产品，其中一些旨在帮助团队决策者预测运动员的受伤和寿命。了解在特定时间范围内受伤的可能性对招募有很大影响，因为球队自然会瞄准有望更长时间保持无伤病的球员。对于导致受伤的因素，例如时间和现场“里程”，行业高管总是有一些基于经验的直觉。有时这些预测是正确的，但通常情况下并非如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在的不同之处在于，人工智能可以支持一些传统智慧——例如，在 NFL 中，30 岁以上的外接手比例如，容易受伤和其他挑战——但也可以提供更具体的受伤或表现下降可能性的估计，以及这对给定球员的可用性意味着什么，以及这可能会让球队付出什么代价。一家名为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://probility.ai/&quot;>;Probility AI&lt;/a>; 的公司声称，预测哪些球员下赛季将缺席比赛的准确率为 96%。高管们可以使用这些结果，从“我认为这可能是一个重要因素”转变为“我知道这是一个重要因素，并且可以以前所未有的信心估计其影响和成本。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI 生成的见解远远超过现有的或直觉支持的。例如，Probility AI 根据来自特定 NFL 球队的数据以及其他公共和私人数据源训练其伤害预测模型，以了解特定球员上大学的地点、他们担任的主教练和助理教练的组合等因素的影响根据和随之而来的实践和工作量需求。虽然这些新生的见解值得进一步研究，但它们显示了 AI 在其预测分析中可以深入到什么程度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，与其让总经理试图确保总体上最好的广泛接受者，他们可以找到根据 AI 对未来伤病和表现的预测，&lt;em>;他们团队的最佳接球手&lt;/em>;。由于球员在接受不同的教练、场地条件或队友时通常有不同的预测职业生涯长度和表现结果，这就造成了套利情况，即球员市场价值因球员效力的球队而异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多支 NFL 球队正在部署 Probility AI 和 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/techtank/2021/03/18/how-the-nfl-is-using-ai-to-evaluate-players /&quot;>;其他来源&lt;/a>;，有充分的理由：不这样做会使他们与配备 AI 的同行相比处于劣势。当然，此类模型也被用于其他运动，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/12/22/artificial-intelligence-is-the-new-competitive-edge-in-sports /&quot;>;足球和篮球&lt;/a>;创造价值，并跨业务部门&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2022/11/21/the-top-five- ways-ai-is-transforming-business/?sh=139d9da98e7f&quot;>;增强活动&lt;/a>;，包括告知决策、提高生产力和更好地为客户服务。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;增强，而非替代&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;因此，随着 AI 在运动的关键方面（伤病、交易时机等）获得预测能力，它会取代前台吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;简而言之，不会。现在，将 AI 视为&lt;em>;增强&lt;/em>;人类决策。它不会取代高管，但会帮助他们做出更好的决策，尤其是在更容易出现人为错误和偏见的领域，例如主要根据直觉进行招聘和做“以前行之有效的事情”。过去 20 年的&lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2016/04/02/moneyball-is-dead-long-live-moneyball/&quot;>;点球成金运动&lt;/a>;一直是关于使用以更严格、系统的方式进行球员统计，AI 使用更深入的学习来更好地预测性能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过对所有活跃球员的准确球员可用性预测，决策制定在三个方面得到显着改进：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;风险管理&lt;/strong>;：例如，如果高效的外接手可能受伤，团队可能会在有天赋的替补上投入更多，以尽量减少流失&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;训练和有针对性的干预：&lt;/strong>;如果 AI 表明一名球员容易受伤，球队可以针对该球员进行定制训练、营养或其他方案，以减少受伤的可能性。或者，球队可能会选择减少球员的工作量，同时降低风险。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人事决定&lt;/strong>;：通过确定预测受伤或其他不可用的因素，球队可以选秀、交易、或者以其他方式获得他们认为更有可能在整个赛季可用的球员。此外，球队可能会选择交易可能受伤的球员。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;精明的高管还会将伤病预测纳入财务决策。也就是说，AI 不仅可以生成关于球员可用性的预测，还可以将这些预测输入财务决策引擎，使团队领导能够针对每花费一美元的预期生产率创建精细指标。例如，一名预计在给定年份仅参加 50% 比赛的跑卫在功能上的成本是可以参加每场比赛的类似费用的跑卫的两倍。通过考虑为每个结果支付的价格（获得的码数、完成的铲球、得分等），团队可以以最有效的方式分配他们的资金，优化花费的每一美元的生产率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，该技术由本身是不够的。虽然软件可以分析球员引擎和资源分配，但体育高管的判断力和风险承受能力最终必须在不可避免的权衡中做出选择，并决定所做的决定。我们在上一节中分享了更多相关信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，人工智能绝对是职业运动的游戏规则改变者，并且正在取代非正式甚至基于统计的决策制定，成为由以下因素推动的综合系统的引擎大数据和前所未有的预测能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;很容易看出由 AI 生成的更好的预测将如何对任何企业产生巨大影响。这里的一个类比是预测建筑等劳动密集型行业的工人绩效何时会受到影响，或者为制造厂或炼油厂提供动力的大型设备何时会发生故障或失效，并在发生代价高昂的事件之前采取预防措施。该方法适用于任何资源老化的企业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;更广泛地说，预测从服装到玉米等任何事物的需求将使企业领导者能够就生产做出更好的决策，包括与供应链和其他领域相关的决策。其他基于人工智能的算法可以预测竞争。这样的例子不胜枚举，AI 已经以这些方式和其他方式应用于各个行业，这有助于解释为什么 AI 初创公司获得了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/artificial-intelligence-trends-2023-business -healthcare-2023-1&quot;>;nearly $1.4 billion in funding&lt;/a>; in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Don&#39;t Go Out of Bounds&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Of course there are limitations to using predictive AI, further reinforcing the idea of augmentation versus replacement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With regard to predicting NFL injuries, for example, while new technology can guide decisions about recruiting, trades, and how much to pay a given player, the coaching team has to think strategically about the whole-team dynamic. The AI may tell you it&#39;s time to replace an injury-prone running-back with a player with a given profile, but an executive will have to think about how best to integrate the new recruit into the team. Total risk, after all, is spread out across all the players and their interactions. Here, too, AI is getting better at understanding the big picture of teams and its implications, starting with sports with smaller starting-team sizes, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://uwaterloo.ca/news/media/artificial-intelligence-makes-it-faster-easier-analyze&quot;>;hockey&lt;/a>;, which puts no more than six players on the ice at a given time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moreover, it&#39;s important to understand that AI-based offerings aren&#39;t providing a definitive “answer” but making a prediction with a confidence interval around it. That interval will shrink as the technology improves, but there will always be some looseness related to prediction and that&#39;s, again, where human judgment is critical.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the end, AI is definitely a game-changer for sports, giving front offices and coaches unprecedented predictive power to make an increasing range of decisions with large implications for performance and returns, giving players insights to extend their careers, and keeping more player playing, which is thrilling the fans. But it&#39;s still a story of augmentation, one where leaders, using new technologies to inform their experience-based intuition, must make strategic calls the best they can and maintain accountability for what happens on the field and the balance sheet.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Scale Local Innovations in Big Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_1157569960.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Magnetic-Mcc/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;All too often innovations &amp;#8212; including new products, new HR policies to attract and retain talent, and new production processes &amp;#8212;developed in one part of a business stay there. Other groups that could benefit from them don&amp;#8217;t know they exist. This leads to lost revenues and higher costs, since teams around the world often end up duplicating (or triplicating, or quadruplicating) investments in solving common problems. This article identifies three common obstacles to scaling innovations and describes a way to overcome them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The business advantages of scale and scope are widely recognized, but large, global enterprises often fail to fully realize them when it comes to innovation. Innovations that are developed in one geographic region or business unit — new products to delight customers, new HR policies to attract and retain talent, new production processes that drive efficiency gains — too often stay within them instead of being disseminated across the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the experience of a global consumer packaged goods company, and three of its regional business units. (Innosight was an advisor to the company). Region 1 had developed a new brand targeted at younger consumers, who were increasingly seeking healthier products. Region 2 had changed its production processes in ways that increased profitability. And Region 3 had developed new sustainability focused business models. For reasons we&#39;ve seen time and again, regions that could have imported these innovations dismissed them, or worse, were simply unaware of them, as they innovated in silos.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not everything needs to scale globally. Local innovations for local markets matter. But there are meaningful downsides of not scaling the great many innovations that are born locally but do have significant global potential. These include lost revenues, since a new product originating in one region could be sold to customers in others, and higher costs, since teams around the world often end up duplicating (or triplicating, or quadruplicating) investments in solving common problems. The CEO of McDonald&#39;s, Chris Kempczinski, highlighted this in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/mcdonalds-shutters-us-offices-ahead-of-layoffs-report/448927&quot;>;a recent memo&lt;/a>;, in which he noted that insufficient collaboration across regions meant that “we are trying to solve the same problems multiple times, aren&#39;t always sharing ideas, and can be slow to innovate.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other disadvantages arising from insufficient global scaling are less obvious but also really matter. When regional businesses that started out with similar product portfolios don&#39;t share innovations and instead evolve in isolation of one another, those portfolios become more divergent over time. This leads to a proliferation of product lines, which makes it more difficult for the corporate center to optimally allocate resources, and for shareholders to value the company and understand its growth prospects.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are three common obstacles to scaling innovations from one to many markets. To illustrate both the obstacles and the solutions for overcoming them we&#39;ll use the case of a global retail bank, which Innosight advised.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Fallacies about Local Uniqueness&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Though every region is different, local leaders tend to overestimate the singularity of their markets, their customers, and the conditions under which they operate. But often, new products and other innovations — and the capabilities and learnings that come from their development — are much more transferable than they assume, in particular when they are aligned with innovation priorities that are shared across regions. An innovation priority, or “strategic focus area,” is essentially a broad hunting ground for innovation. At the consumer goods company, for example, one innovation priority was packaging, which led to specific innovations in materials and size and format.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s turn to the bank. One of its regional units had made significant investments in developing a digital mortgage-application platform that further automated its mortgage-application process to make it faster and more consumer friendly. Though mortgages were an important product line across regions, most were reluctant to consider adopting this innovation, contending that the distinct ways that mortgages were regulated within their individual markets made it unfeasible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regulatory frameworks do vary from country to country, of course, but not in ways that precluded this innovation from being widely adopted, since the implementation of the platform could be adapted to address differences in regulatory requirements in each market, much in the same way that existing mortgage-application processes were customized to local markets. What&#39;s more, the platform was consistent with innovation priorities shared across regions, including digitizing and improving customer experiences across existing product journeys and increasing the profitability of mortgage lending.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To overcome this obstacle, the bank&#39;s central corporate strategy team facilitated a process to identify common innovation priorities across regions. First, regions were asked to define their individual innovation priorities in a standard way (for example, “new ecommerce payment and financing solutions”), identify the associated target customer segment, the customer problems to be addressed, and the broad types of technologies and capabilities required. Each of the bank&#39;s four regions defined between five and 10 innovation priorities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The corporate strategy team then facilitated a series of discussions among senior leaders of each region to compare and identify commonalities in their innovation priorities. This surfaced multiple priorities that were shared across all four regions. In addition to those related to the mortgage-application platform, they included the development of new mobile-only products for millennial and Generation Z consumers and reduction of call center use and wait times.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Innovations aligned with those priorities could then be identified as sharable, no matter where they originated. Awareness of common innovation priorities among teams across regions also led &lt;a href=&quot;/2000/01/communities-of-practice-the-organizational-frontier&quot;>;communities of practice&lt;/a>; among designers and product developers to emerge organically. These convened regularly to exchange ideas, disseminate learnings, and co-create new innovations consistent with those shared priorities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Misaligned Incentives and Culture&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Various formal and informal disincentives are another obstacle to scaling innovations. For example, regional leaders&#39; bonuses are typically based on their own unit&#39;s P&amp;amp;L performance, which can make them reluctant to spend time, energy, and resources on exporting an innovation that will benefit another region. Conversely, a “not invented here” mindset can make managers reluctant to import externally generated ideas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank&#39;s bonus plans significantly penalized local leaders who missed ambitious profitability targets. This made them reluctant to dedicate resources to exporting innovations. In addition, a “not invented here” mindset was widespread — from regional leaders who wanted to prove their ability to innovate independently to developers who preferred to write their own code rather than use the software developed by peers in other regions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address these issues, the bank offered P&amp;amp;L relief to regions on a case-by-case basis, allowing them to deviate from profitability targets without risking their bonuses so that they could invest their own resources into scaling innovations for the benefit of other regions. It also established a central fund and team to support global scaling efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regions that were developing innovations that could address shared priorities were invited to submit short “global scaling resource requests” that summarized the additional investments required to scale them to other regions beyond just their own. The request could be to cover the cost of building a product in a way that made it operable across global technology environments, for example, or the team hours required to train and support users in other regions and the potential in-year P&amp;amp;L tradeoffs or broader operational challenges that would result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A global scaling committee, comprised of corporate C-suite leaders and central strategy and finance executives, decided which requests to approve. Most resource requests submitted to scale innovations that addressed shared priorities were approved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank&#39;s corporate leaders also tried to change attitudes by publicly celebrating both managers who shared their region&#39;s innovations and those who adopted those created by others. They spotlighted global scaling initiatives in all-day quarterly business-review sessions attended by top regional executives, where exporting and importing regions jointly discussed the innovations and the process of scaling them. The bank&#39;s leaders also highlighted such innovations and the teams involved in these efforts in company newsletters.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, the bank&#39;s leaders encouraged and frequently reminded regional managers to ask themselves a series of questions before dismissing potential innovations developed by other regions. They included:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Could we better serve the customers we have or seek by adopting this innovation?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;If the innovation isn&#39;t specific to one or more of our local circumstances — for example, if it has been developed in the context of a different technological, regulatory, or competitive environment, or requires a means of production or distribution that we lack — could it be adapted?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;And might we be guilty of having a “not invented here” mindset if our first instinct is to dismiss this innovation?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Lack of Transparency&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As we mentioned, one major reason that business units don&#39;t share innovations and instead often duplicate efforts is a lack of awareness of what one another has developed or is undertaking. One way to address this is by creating a central mechanism that makes it easy for regions to share knowledge of their innovation pursuits from their earliest stages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider one innovation priority shared by all the bank&#39;s regions that we mentioned: developing mobile-only products for millennials. Innovations consistent with this priority across regions included distinct payment, savings, and investment products; new product features like roundup savings and cashback and rewards; innovations to streamline customer journeys within mobile-only apps, and integration with budgeting and bill-splitting tools that appealed to the millennial audience. But regions lacked awareness of each other&#39;s efforts and were in some instances even duplicating spend on development of the same things.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank addressed this issue in two ways: by establishing the process for identifying common innovation priorities across regions that we previously described and by instituting an innovation-portfolio-management system to profile and track innovations. Regions were required to enter into the IT system a description of each innovation project, including the associated innovation priority, the target customer segment, its revenue potential, and anticipated investment requirements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond supporting global scaling, the system helped each region better understand and manage its own innovation pipeline. When it surfaced instances of regions unknowingly duplicating each other&#39;s efforts, they were able to collaborate and pool their insights, development capabilities, and data assets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Too many global enterprises don&#39;t make the most of local innovations. By systematically overcoming the obstacles to scaling them, they can spread them much faster and more effectively and generate a much higher return on their innovation investments.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women in Leadership Face Ageism at Every Age]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_14_1415442562.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/aldomurillo/Imagehit/Hero Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Originally, ageism was understood to be prejudice, stereotypes, and discriminatory behavior targeted at older employees. But with an increasingly diverse and multigenerational workforce, age bias now occurs across the career life cycle &amp;#8212; especially for women. &amp;#8220;Youngism&amp;#8221; refers to ageism toward younger adults, fueled by the conflation of age with maturity and the misperception that tenure is required for competency. Even middle-aged women are feeling the effects of age bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Age diversity in the workplace yields better organizational performance while perceived age discrimination creates lower job satisfaction and engagement. The good news is that there are practical steps for leaders to combat this never-right gendered age bias. First, recognize ageism in your organization; you can fix a problem that isn&amp;#8217;t there. Next, with your employees, address &amp;#8220;lookism,&amp;#8221; and focus on skills, no matter who has them. Finally, cultivate creative collaborations to encourage learning across age groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When a university vice president had an opening for a controller sitting just beneath her in the hierarchy, board members told her to seek an “older man” to complement her. Since she began the vice president role at age 37, board members routinely criticized her age, calling her &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90569439/we-need-to-talk-about-using-pet-names-for-women-at-work&quot;>;diminishing pet names&lt;/a>;, like “kiddo” and “young lady.” But being older wouldn&#39;t necessarily have made a difference, as another woman explained: “I am at the age when I should be getting the higher-level jobs; people in my profession now want to give the jobs to the 30- and younger 40-year-olds with the &#39;fresh, new ideas&#39; as opposed to going with the person with experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Originally, ageism was understood to be prejudice, stereotypes, and discriminatory behavior &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.0021-9029.2006.00062.x&quot;>;targeted at older employees&lt;/a>;. Driven by the misperception that performance worsens and capacity decreases as people age, older employees are expected to just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias-hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;quietly leave&lt;/a>; so that younger talent can take the reins. With an increasingly diverse and multigenerational workforce, age bias now occurs &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1468-0432.2004.00222.x&quot;>;across the career life cycle&lt;/a>;. “&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/xge0001064&quot;>;Youngism&lt;/a>;” refers to ageism toward younger adults and is fueled by the conflation of age with maturity and the misperception that tenure is required for competency.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, research has only just begun to investigate how age is used to justify bias and discrimination specifically against women. Gendered ageism sits at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/bonniemarcus/2021/09/20/gendered-ageism-affects-womens-job-security-and-financial-viability/&quot;>;intersection of age and gender bias&lt;/a>; and is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/fighting-the-double-whammy-of-ageism-sexism.aspx&quot;>;double whammy&lt;/a>; where there is “no right age” for professional women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our recent open-ended survey research of 913 women leaders from four United States industries (higher education, faith-based nonprofits, law, and health care), we discovered that many women suffered from this “never-right” age bias. Conceptions of young, middle, and old age are often based on perceptions and vary between workplaces and contexts. When interpreting our results, we consider “young” to be under 40, middle age to be between 40 and 60, and older women to be over 60.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Oldism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As women age, they are often not seen as valuable or relevant in the way that male counterparts are. Older women in our research expressed that they were deemed unworthy of advancement. “While men become wells of wisdom as they age, older women are seen as outdated, harpy, strident,” one physician noted. “Our voices are discounted.” For example, a 61-year-old deputy chief information officer (CIO) was not considered in CIO succession planning. Instead, the current CIO was grooming a male colleague for the role. Another retirement-aged woman added, “I am largely ignored.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of these women felt discouraged, burnt out, and resigned to not advancing any further. As a 66-year-old faith-based leader said, “At my age and with the mentality of our organization that they need men at the top, there is not a next professional step.” Another woman in the same industry noted that once she turned 60, she was no longer “worth investing in with training or mentoring.” Others felt compelled to find opportunities outside of their organization: “I am tired of proving myself to others and may as well do it in the interests of my own company,” a 60-year-old lawyer indicated.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Youngism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Younger women — and those who looked young — were called pet names or even patted on the head, as one 39-year-old woman reported. Young women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/when-people-assume-youre-not-in-charge-because-youre-a-woman&quot;>;role incredulity&lt;/a>;. They reported being mistaken for students, interns, trainees, support staff, secretaries, paralegals, and court reporters. Such inaccurate assumptions were especially prevalent for non-White women, such as an Asian higher-education executive who appeared young and was presumed to be in a junior position.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many younger women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;https://rowman.com/ISBN/9781538170960/Glass-Walls-Shattering-the-Six-Gender-Bias-Barriers-Still-Holding-Women-Back-at-Work&quot;>;credibility deficit&lt;/a>;, which occurs when women&#39;s statements and expertise are not believed. “I am often told that I don&#39;t have the experience so I can&#39;t know what to do,” one 34-year-old woman explained. In the face of such bias, women (and especially women of color) must expend extra effort to prove themselves. One young-looking Black university chief financial officer noted that she is often “pressed to provide a synopsis of her resume to establish credibility.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other younger women had their appearance scrutinized. One physician noted that between ages 20 and 40, men focused on her looks. After she gave a scientific presentation that she was very proud of, a male colleague told her that she “looked like a Barbie doll up there!”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Middle-ageism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unlike previous notions of a middle-aged “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias-hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;sweet spot&lt;/a>;,” women between ages 40 and 60 in our study fared no better than their younger or older counterparts. One college leader described how some search committees chose not to hire women in their late forties because of “too much family responsibility and impending menopause.” Other search committees declined to hire women in their fifties because they have “menopause-related issues and could be challenging to manage.” And still other committees said that “women in their fifties and sixties may not have &#39;aged well&#39; and do not &#39;look vital.&#39;” Yet the jobs were given to similarly aged men.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lawyer summed up the never-right age bias problem in her field:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we are too young to be responsible or to supervise. This lasts into our mid- to late-thirties but does not for men. (Perhaps they are waiting to make sure we don&#39;t have kids). Then in an instant, we are too old to be hired for anything or anywhere new. Once again, men are still “young enough” at the same age…. Women are young or old, we get no prime time even if we aren&#39;t out for childbearing or rearing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our research we found no age was the right age to be a woman leader. There was always an age-based excuse to not take women seriously, to discount their opinions, or to not hire or promote them. Each individual woman may believe she&#39;s just at the wrong age, but the data make the larger pattern clear. Any age can be stigmatized by supervisors and colleagues to claim that the woman is not valued or is not a fit for a leadership role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Age diversity in the workplace yields better &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/apl0000497&quot;>;organizational performance&lt;/a>; while perceived age discrimination creates &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/josi.12161&quot;>;lower job satisfaction and engagement&lt;/a>;. Similarly, gender diversity also matters. Organizations with diverse leadership teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0148296320303490?via%3Dihub&quot;>;perform better&lt;/a>;, especially in times of crisis; &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2729348&quot;>;earn more&lt;/a>;; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1748-8583.12079&quot;>;have lower turnover.&lt;/a>; The business case is clear — if organizational leaders pay attention. The good news is that there are practical steps for leaders to combat this never-right gendered age bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Combat Gendered Ageism&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recognize age bias&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;You can&#39;t fix a problem you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinessdevelopmentcouncil/2020/09/28/gendered-ageism-is-the-new-sexism/?sh=65b14a2214b1&quot;>;won&#39;t admit is there&lt;/a>;. Whereas sexism and racism are the focus of most workplace diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, ageism has been largely neglected. All employees should be trained on gendered age bias, just as they are on other forms of discrimination. Use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-news/pages/avoiding-age-discrimination-.aspx&quot;>;interactive case studies&lt;/a>; that include “gray areas” in age-related assumptions and address false stereotypes that older age reduces an individual&#39;s commitment, agility, and ability to learn. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/global-campaign-to-combat-ageism-toolkit&quot;>;Company social media can also be leveraged to get the word out&lt;/a>; about ageism using messaging that taps into both emotions and facts. When the problem ceases to be ignored, necessary improvements can be made.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Address “&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;lookism&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;.” &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Much of gendered ageism is hinged on looks or appearance as a function of societal value. The incessant pressure to look young and attractive is something that &lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/lookism-beauty-still-trumps-brains-in-too-many-workplaces-148278&quot;>;typically impacts women more than men.&lt;/a>; Include &lt;a href=&quot;https://fisherpub.sjf.edu/sfd/vol2/iss1/6/&quot;>;lookism&lt;/a>; in DEI training and ensure that it&#39;s not used as a hidden metric for hiring, promotion, or performance evaluation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Focus on &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;skills&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;, no matter who has them&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Younger women are often limited — whether intentionally or not — by the assumption of lack of experience. Middle-aged women may be thought of as difficult to manage or having too many family responsibilities. Women who are older are often constrained by perceptions that they are no longer invested in the organization, are less productive, or cannot be promoted. These falsehoods perpetuate the problem. Rather than focusing on age when hiring, making promotion decisions, or bringing on new team members for a growth opportunity, leaders should focus on each woman&#39;s skills, not their tenure or external demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Cultivate creative collaborations.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Develop intergenerational, mixed-gender teams and professional relationships to encourage &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2018/11/13/what-older-workers-and-younger-workers-can-learn-from-each-other/?sh=5c7f9a9e2117&quot;>;learning from each other and collaborating on solutions&lt;/a>;. Middle-aged and older employees have years of experience, while younger employees have perspectives from growing up in a more recent time. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springtideresearch.org/research/work-life&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>; of Generation Z&#39;s expectations at work showed that one of their highest desires was for mentoring relationships; they long for connection with older workers who take &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/organizational-and-employee-development/pages/generation-z-seeks-guidance-in-the-workplace.aspx&quot;>;an interest in them&lt;/a>;. Too often women lack connections that would help them develop professionally due to exclusion from informal networks and events. Intentionally pairing younger women with older mentors and sponsors will aid their learning and career success and enhance your company&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The research is clear: Any age can be viewed as “the wrong age” for a woman, allowing her capacity to be questioned and her fitness for leadership challenged. But we can stop stigmatizing women&#39;s age — benefitting not just women, but the whole organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Retailers Can Capitalize on the &ldquo;Refund Effect&rdquo;]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_113908305.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Lori Andrews/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In 2022, US consumers returned 16.5% of purchases, costing retailers an estimated $816 billion in lost revenue. Research suggests that cross-selling products during the return process is an effective strategy to reduce this revenue loss. Across a number of experiments, researchers found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so it&amp;#8217;s less painful to spend these funds on another purchase, so long as cross-selling occurs before the money is reissued to the customers&amp;#8217; original payment method and consumers initially expected to keep the goods they were planning to buy. The researchers also found that this &amp;#8220;refund effect&amp;#8221; applies across categories. Creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can reduce revenue loss from product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Product returns pose a major challenge for retailers. In 2022, US consumers returned &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;16.5%&lt;/a>; of merchandise purchases, costing retailers an estimated &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;$816&lt;/a>; billion in lost revenue. Typical strategies to reduce revenue lost to product returns include reducing the likelihood of returns by providing more information about products (eg, reviews and FAQs) and increasing the financial and transaction costs to consumers who do return products (eg, shipping costs and limited return windows). But the former strategy is costly to retailers, and the latter is costly to consumers. Our recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://myscp.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jcpy.1354&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; identifies an effective strategy for reducing this loss of revenue that benefits everyone: cross-selling products during the product-return process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In six experiments we found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so spending these funds on another purchase feels less painful. Research participants were more likely to spend money from a product refund than from a bonus, and even more likely to spend refunded money than unexpected income, like lottery winnings and tax refunds. We call this “the refund effect.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one laboratory experiment, for instance, we gave all participants $4. Some of the participants were asked to use the money to buy a stress ball that they later learned they could return, which most did. Others in a control group made no initial purchase. We then offered everyone the opportunity to keep their $4 or use it to buy a $5 Starbucks gift card at a discount. Only 48% of the control group used their $4 to buy the gift card, whereas 78% of participants who received the refund bought the gift card. We replicated this study with an online sample where the returned product was a gift card from a big-box retailer (ie, Best Buy or Kohls). In this experiment, only 10% of the control group chose to purchase the Starbucks gift card, whereas 25% of participants with refunded money used it to buy the Starbucks gift card.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Retailers who understand the dynamics of the refund effect — when, why, and how it works — stand to mitigate one of the perennial headaches of the industry. Here are three findings retailers should keep in mind to make the most of the refund effect:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cross-selling opportunities occur during the returns process — before money is reissued to the customers&#39; original payment method.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The refund effect is far less likely to boost sales after money has been refunded to a credit card or checking account.为什么？ The refund effect depends on creating and maintaining an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/e/earmarking.asp&quot;>;earmark&lt;/a>;” that reminds consumers the money has been lost. Our research found that if refunded money is pooled with money from other sources the earmark is removed and consumers spend it no differently than money from other sources. For example, research participants were more likely to use a refund from a pair of sneakers to buy a shirt if they had yet to receive their money back. If the money had already been deposited in their checking account, they were no more likely to buy the shirt than participants who simply saw the shirt online.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some retailers already effectively use this cross-selling strategy. By default, Amazon asks customers if they&#39;d like to use their return to buy a gift card. Customers who decline this cross-sell then receive their refund. Clothier Todd Snyder lets customers use their refund to immediately buy other products before they mail their return. The remainder of their refund is issued when the return is received. These cross-selling strategies are likely to work because customers shop out of the refund before getting money back from their returns.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect only works when consumers expect to lose money.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our research showed that consumers have to initially expect to keep the goods and services they buy to create the earmark that makes the refund effect work. “Try before you buy” strategies, where consumers do not expect to pay for returned goods, are unlikely to create a refund effect if those goods are returned.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, research participants who imagined buying two pairs of shoes to try on with the expectation that they would return one pair were no more likely to spend their refund on a jacket than controls who simply imagined seeing the jacket and paying out of pocket. By contrast, participants who did not expect to return a pair of shoes when they bought them were more likely to use the refund from the shoes to buy the jacket&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect applies across categories.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Because refunded money feels as if it has already been lost, the refund effect applies both to cross-sold products in the same category and products in other categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, research participants in a fifth experiment were more likely to spend a refund from a returned bottle of wine on either a gift card from a grocer or from an athleisure brand than buy either kind of gift card with money out of their pocket. This is good news for retailers who offer a range of product categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sale strategies like upselling and exchanges during the product return process should similarly benefit from the refund effect, and they may be better for customer relationship management than increasing the cost of product returns. New companies have stepped into this market. For example, Loop Returns helps 1,500 Shopify merchants, such as Allbirds and Brooklinen, cross-sell, upsell, and exchange products during the product return process, saving &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.loopreturns.com/the-ecommerce-returns-benchmark-report/&quot;>;28% of revenue&lt;/a>; that would otherwise be lost.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The lesson for retailers? Instead of resorting to practices whose harsh transaction costs can &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0008125617741125&quot;>;alienate customers&lt;/a>;, sometimes permanently, creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can be an effective way to reduce the revenue loss incurred by product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Ways Companies Are Addressing Skills Gaps in Their Workforce]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_TylerComrie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Tyler Comrie&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;We&amp;#8217;re in an unusual economic situation, one where recession fears are high but the job market is tight. As training budgets inevitably come under pressure, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The author examines five of the biggest developments in this space: 1) digital apprenticeships that are helping fill jobs in the digital and tech sectors; 2) tuition-assistance programs aimed at frontline workers; 3) learning-experience platforms with features like skills assessments, algorithmic-driven recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking; 4) the democratization of coaching; and 5) the rise of cohort-based courses.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For years, business and HR leaders &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/can-moocs-solve-your-training-problem&quot;>;pinned their hopes&lt;/a>; for better workplace learning on MOOCs, or massive open online courses. Unfortunately, the evidence &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1921417117#ref-3&quot;>;continues to show&lt;/a>; that these are not enough on their own, particularly for those who most need them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies now have more options, thanks to better technology, innovative funding mechanisms, and old approaches reimagined to meet today&#39;s needs. Below, I explain five of the biggest developments in this space.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The New Digital Apprenticeship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a medieval practice is propelling thousands of workers onto the career ladder&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The apprenticeship is perhaps the oldest form of workplace learning, stretching back to ancient times, and boasting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/apprenticeship&quot;>;some illustrious alumni&lt;/a>;, including Benjamin Franklin. There are more than 580,000 active apprentices working in the US right now — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apprenticeship.gov/data-and-statistics&quot;>;up 103% in the past 10 years&lt;/a>;, according to Department of Labor figures.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For companies that consistently struggle to fill important roles, apprenticeships may be an effective solution. While apprenticeships have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/global/2020/feb/04/tanners-tailors-and-candlestick-makers-a-history-of-apprenticeships&quot;>;historically&lt;/a>; been associated with blue-collar jobs, they&#39;re increasingly becoming a way to fill white-collar jobs in the digital and tech sectors. Apprenticeships in the IT and telecommunications sector grew by more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027040416/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/telecommunications#:~:text=In%202020%20there%20were%203%2C654%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20telecommunications%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20300%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years.%20%5B2%5D&quot;>;300%&lt;/a>; between 2011 and 2020, while cybersecurity apprenticeships grew by &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027023746/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/cybersecurity#:~:text=In%202020%2C%20there%20were%202%2C716%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20cybersecurity%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20600%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years%20%5B2%5D.&quot;>;600%&lt;/a>; during the same period, according to the Department of Labor.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend is powered by a growing number of companies, many of which are focused on fast-growing fields like software engineering and data science, that recruit, support, and train apprentices on behalf of large employers. One UK-based provider, Multiverse, was recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://tcrn.ch/3H0ebPR&quot;>;valued&lt;/a>; at $1.7bn and claims to have served &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/multiverse-community-reaches-10-000-apprentices-and-alumni&quot;>;10,000 apprentices&lt;/a>;. “We&#39;ve long been believers in the apprenticeship model, and we&#39;ve found it particularly effective for tech and digital jobs,” said Rashitha Jayasekara, chief of digital manufacturing at Rolls-Royce, which works with Multiverse to&amp;nbsp;upskill existing employees. “The experiential learning that apprentices get through hackathons and project work allows them to combine theory and practice in a way standard training doesn&#39;t, and to continuously develop skills we need within the company.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Verizon, another Multiverse customer, uses the apprenticeship model to fill software engineering jobs and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/creating-software-engineering-jobs-verizon&quot;>;reports&lt;/a>; that 95% of an initial cohort accepted full-time offers at the company after completing an apprenticeship program. The Verizon program was designed to “lower barriers to entry to software jobs while training truly great software developers that we fundamentally believe can propel our business through digital innovation,” said Shankar Arumugavelu, Verizon&#39;s chief information officer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Apprenticeships aren&#39;t right for all training needs. For one thing, they require a significant investment of time — in the US, formal apprenticeships are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2017/article/apprenticeships_occupations-and-outlook.htm#:~:text=Formal%20apprenticeship%20programs%20usually%20last,Department%20of%20Labor%20(DOL).&quot;>;usually four years long&lt;/a>;. In some markets they can also come with restrictive regulation. In the UK, for instance, the government&#39;s apprenticeship funding program &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/news/365530295/Government-urged-to-address-broken-apprenticeship-levy-system&quot;>;has been criticized&lt;/a>; for being too rigid and not in line with employers&#39; needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Fresh Approach to Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a historically elite benefit is becoming accessible for all&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Large companies have long offered to pay for their employees&#39; continuing education. However, these benefits have historically been reserved for a small number of white-collar employees, for example, those pursuing an executive MBA. Or employees were asked to pay for their courses out of pocket and get reimbursed afterwards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the labor market has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/themes/how-to-better-support-and-retain-frontline-workers&quot;>;changed&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/companies-offer-tuition-assistance-so-workers-can-go-back-to-college.html&quot;>;more companies&lt;/a>; are offering tuition benefits as a way to retain their frontline employees — store clerks, baristas, drivers, and hourly workers. In response, a new class of companies has emerged to smooth and synchronize the relationship between training providers, employers, employees, and (in some cases) the government. Employees receive coaching, advice, and support to help them find the training program that&#39;s right for them, and the training programs are paid for by the employer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, in 2021, Target announced a tuition-assistance program called &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.target.com/article/2022/09/dream-to-be-anniversary#:~:text=Our%20%24200%20million%20investment%20in,skills%20and%20build%20their%20careers.&quot;>;“Dream to Be&lt;/a>;” in partnership with Guild, one of the leading players in this growing space. According to Chief Diversity and Inclusion officer Kiera Fernandez, “Target has offered a traditional tuition reimbursement program for more than two decades. Now, through our partnership with Guild to offer Dream to Be, team members can attend classes at more than 40 schools, colleges, and universities … with no out-of-pocket tuition costs.” Fernandez said that as of April 2023, more than 25,000 employees have been approved for the program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If designed effectively, the benefits of tuition assistance programs for employers are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/small-business/human-resources/articles/tuition-reimbursement/&quot;>;clear&lt;/a>;. For example, Jack Hartung, chief financial officer of fast-casual restaurant chain Chipotle, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/video/2021/04/09/chipotle-cfo-says-debt-free-degree-is-a-way-to-invest-in-employees.html&quot;>;told CNBC&lt;/a>; that “employees who take advantage of the company&#39;s free degrees are three and a half times more likely to stay with the company and seven times more likely to move up into management.” However, research suggests that while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180108006550/en/New-Study-Shows-Lasting-Impact-Tuition-Assistance#:~:text=84%25%20say%20access%20to%20a%20tuition%20assistance%20program%20was%20important%20in%20their%20decision%20to%20join%20the%20company&quot;>;84%&lt;/a>; of employees value tuition reimbursement benefits highly, on average, &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholarlycommons.law.northwestern.edu/nulr/vol117/iss6/5/#:~:text=Yet%2C%20despite%20their%20increasing%20availability%2C%20only%202%25%20of%20employees%2C%20as%20a%20percentage%20of%20those%20interested%20in%20pursuing%20further%20education%2C%20are%20utilizing%20these%20reimbursement%20programs&quot;>;only 2%&lt;/a>; of eligible employees use this benefit. This implies employers must do more to take advantage of this powerful tool.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Shift to Learning Experience Platforms&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How employees know what to learn next&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Organizing and tracking what employees are learning can be a cumbersome task. For years, this work has been done by software known as “learning management systems” (LMS), which are relatively simple tools that store learning material, typically in the form of presentations, videos, and text. Most large companies &lt;a href=&quot;https://trainingmag.com/2021-training-industry-report/#:~:text=Some%2098%20percent%20of%20large%20companies%20and%2096%20percent%20of%20midsize%20ones%20currently%20use%20LMSs%20vs.%2080%20percent%20of%20small%20companies.&quot;>;have one&lt;/a>;, but few employees &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinkruse/2021/04/27/usage-of-degreed-is-double-that-of-traditional-learning-platforms/?sh=58ba9a1a2d3d#:~:text=most%20LMS%20and%20online%20content%20companies%20only%20see%205%25%20to%2015%25%20of%20licensed%20seats%20used%20in%20any%20given%20month.&quot;>;spend much time&lt;/a>; on them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the last few years, a new wave of tools has transformed the LMS into “Learning Experience Platforms” (LXP), with features like skills assessments, Netflix-style recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking. LXPs “make learning relevant for individuals, not just managing training programs,” according Todd Tauber senior vice president of strategy at Degreed, one of the leading providers in this space. Industry analyst Josh Bersin estimates the market for LXPs is &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/06/corporate-learning-bombshell-degreed-acquires-learnin-david-blake-returns/&quot;>;$500m,&lt;/a>; up from &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2018/07/edcast-expands-the-lxp-market-with-focus-on-global-upskilling/&quot;>;$200m&lt;/a>; in 2018.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Customers report that the model is working. Chris Harry is the chief learning officer of TEK Systems, a staffing firm that&#39;s been using Degreed. “Since moving our various employee development programs onto Degreed, we&#39;ve seen our highest-ever engagement and satisfaction rates,” he said. According to Harry, 96% of TEK employees have created an account in Degreed, and the company consistently sees 40 to 50% of them actively using the platform each month, which he says is “far higher than anything we&#39;ve seen before.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Results like these require real investment beyond simply buying the technology. For &lt;a href=&quot;https://get.degreed.com/hubfs/Client%20Case%20Studies/Ericsson/Ericsson+Degreed%20Case%20Study_Q2-22_EN-US.pdf?utm_campaign=Ericsson%20Case%20Study%20May%20%2722&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsmi=214005662&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-_8Z515BnP5WAJI5xGCg8ZF2Zi2ftiYmmfHEKikOYkDheoBPQzXBzi5mM6FOcyAZGppjQgdYXltDyoeVeVVC1bEnUM8xfnubGHUldzPilsSLH3Yk90&amp;amp;utm_content=214005662&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_automation&quot;>;example&lt;/a>;, another Degreed customer, Ericsson, said it hired internal champions and developed an extensive internal marketing campaign to roll out its program.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Democratization of Coaching&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How all of us can have a Sherpa for our careers&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Professional coaching is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2009-12395-008&quot;>;well-understood&lt;/a>; way to boost workers&#39; learning, confidence, and effectiveness. However, it has typically been an &lt;a href=&quot;/2009/01/what-can-coaches-do-for-you#:~:text=they%E2%80%99re%20usually%20called%20executive%20coaches%2C%20and%20they%20can%20earn%20up%20to%20%243%2C500%20an%20hour.&quot;>;expensive&lt;/a>; tool, reserved only for senior executives. Moreover, even for those who can afford it, finding a coach can be a challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;New platforms have emerged that use technology to make it easier to find, match, and work with coaches. New companies provide tools to assess what each employee needs from their coach, match them with a coach who has the right experience and expertise, and even conduct coaching sessions via a digital platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The space is growing. According to the International Coaching Federation, there were &lt;a href=&quot;https://coachfederation.org/app/uploads/2020/09/FINAL_ICF_GCS2020_ExecutiveSummary.pdf&quot;>;71,000&lt;/a>; practicing coaches in 2021, up 33% from 2016. Investors expect growth to continue: The leading digital coaching startup, BetterUp, raised $300m in 2021 at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/betterup&quot;>;$5bn valuation&lt;/a>; as part of a wave of &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/01/online-coaching-is-so-hot-its-now-disrupting-leadership-development/&quot;>;investment&lt;/a>; into coaching startups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of this growth is powered by large companies offering coaching services more broadly to their employees. Danone, the France-based food products company, has been working with one provider, CoachHub, to offer this benefit to 250 employees. According to Maxime Hollande, who leads diversity and inclusion for Danone in the Netherlands, “these coaching sessions have been of big added value for employees… One of the metrics we watch closely is the extent to which each employee has progressed toward the personal goals each of them define with their coach. The average score on this metric is 4.9 out of 5.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Chevron, the American global energy company, has made coaching sessions available to 7,000 of its managers around the world via BetterUp. “Prior to BetterUp, we utilized an assortment of internal coaching resources and multiple external coaching vendors,” explained Rhonda Morris, Chevron&#39;s chief human resources officer. “BetterUp&#39;s virtual coaching model … has matured our coaching culture making it more accessible for all who want it.&amp;nbsp; Coaches no longer have to travel to meet our employees. Our employees have been very vocal about their positive experiences with BetterUp.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Because coaching sessions are inherently private experiences, it can be hard for employers to ensure a focus on the topics that are most important to them. At Chevron, they measure the success each quarter by asking employees to rate the effectiveness of leaders who&#39;ve received coaching. “Leadership Effectiveness is consistently one of our highest scoring categories across our organization,” Morris said. “This shows that our BetterUp offerings are having a positive impact on our workforce and culture.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Rise of Cohort-Based Courses &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How to build real skills online&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When it comes to online learning, most participants &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aav7958&quot;>;don&#39;t finish&lt;/a>; the courses they start, mainly because the learning experience is asynchronous. Individuals must be disciplined and diligent enough to complete large amounts of the learning material on their own. This is particularly difficult in today&#39;s workplace, where the number of meetings and distractions has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/great-expectations-making-hybrid-work-work&quot;>;ballooned&lt;/a>; in recent years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now, a new delivery format called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://future.com/cohort-based-courses/&quot;>;cohort-based courses&lt;/a>;” has emerged as a way to improve completion rates. Groups of participants together take a course with defined start and end dates, regular homework assignments, and an instructor to run periodic live online discussion sessions. Within this more structured format, participants still access much of the learning material on their own time, making it easier for them to complete the course and have the chance to apply what they learn over its duration. One of the pioneers of this space, altMBA, says its learners have achieved a &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/behavior-design/how-to-design-an-online-course-with-a-96-completion-rate-180678117a85&quot;>;96% completion rate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boston Consulting Group (BCG) is one leading employer that has embraced cohort-based courses, working in partnership with Emeritus (where I work). Lidia Juszko, BCG&#39;s executive director of global learning and teaming, describes how the format works particularly well for a professional services firm like hers. “We&#39;ve found that cohort-based courses offer a level of structure and support that makes them more engaging than standard online learning,” she said. “Our colleagues report that the combination and cadence of &#39;office hours&#39; with instructors, live discussion sessions with the rest of the cohort, and short videos and exercises to be completed each week are a more accessible way for them to learn. Learning and development opportunities like this allow us to continue to attract and retain the best talent.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;HSBC, the global banking organization, recently began piloting cohort-based online courses as well, and the early results are promising. According to David Morris, global head of people capability, “One of our challenges has been to deliver in-depth learning in an online format, given the range and complexity of our markets. Our early results show that the online cohort-based format is achieving significant improvement across key indicators like completion, confidence, and capability.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The downside of this format is that the live learning elements that make it effective come at a substantial cost. A single license to an open library of standard online courses costs about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.classcentral.com/report/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/comparing-subscription-pricing-2023.png&quot;>;$30 to $60&lt;/a>; per month for access to thousands of courses (most providers also offer significant volume discounts). Meanwhile, cohort-based courses can cost between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/serenitygibbons/2021/12/17/how-cohort-based-learning-is-transforming-online-education/#:~:text=Another%20notable%20difference%20is%20the%20price%3B%20cohort%20based%20courses%20can%20range%20anywhere%20from%20%24500%20up%20to%20more%20than%20%245%2C000.&quot;>;$500 and $5,000&lt;/a>; per course&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>; This means cohort-based learning is unlikely to be an option for all employees, and employers must carefully decide who can benefit the most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We are in an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmoore/2022/12/02/many-indicators-imply-a-2023-recession-the-jobs-market-disagrees/&quot;>;unusual&lt;/a>; economic situation, one where recession fears are up but the job market is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/b1b710a1-6d12-43e5-8508-ae4584a7289a&quot;>;still tight&lt;/a>;. As training budgets inevitably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1812542/half-organisations-looking-cut-ld-costs-amid-economic-difficulty-survey-reveals&quot;>;come under pressure&lt;/a>;, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The five approaches outlined above can help companies move beyond the MOOC to find a learning program that&#39;s right for their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Editor&#39;s Note: Harvard Business Publishing has a content creation and distribution partnership with Emeritus.&amp;nbsp;Neither the author or editor who worked on this article are involved in that partnership.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A More Humane Model for Eldercare in the U.S.]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-u-s]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_200015318-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daly and Newton/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;On the whole, the care for elderly poor people with chronic illnesses leaves a lot to be desired in the United States. PACE, a comprehensive, integrated, community-based care approach that lets older adults continue to live at home as long as possible, can serve as a model for improving the needs of this population. This article examines PACE Southeast Michigan, an outstanding PACE program.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-us?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-us?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The US health care system is not set up to improve the quality of life of the most vulnerable, chronically ill, elderly people, especially those who are poor. Older poor people often face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3016701/&quot;>;loneliness, depression,&lt;/a>; a lost sense of purpose, and an inability to live independently in their homes. They also encounter many health service hurdles, including inadequate care coordination, &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/07/how-to-pay-for-health-care&quot;>;fee-for-service reimbursement&lt;/a>; that often reflexively encourages medical treatment over other forms of care, and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2759755&quot;>;dysfunctional&lt;/a>; nursing home industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help improve services for these patients, we analyzed the design and implementation of a national program called PACE: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/Medicare-Medicaid-Coordination/Medicare-and-Medicaid-Coordination/Medicare-Medicaid-Coordination-Office/PACE/PACE&quot;>;Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly&lt;/a>;. We focused on this program because all PACE participants are vulnerable: They require nursing home–level care, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npaonline.org/sites/default/files/PDFs/Issue%20Brief_Medicaid%20Rate%20Setting%20for%20PACE%202.21.pdf&quot;>;90%&lt;/a>; are eligible for &lt;em>;both&lt;/em>; Medicare and Medicaid. Few integrated-care programs serve this dual-eligible population, which now numbers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kff.org/medicare/issue-brief/a-profile-of-medicare-medicaid-enrollees-dual-eligibles/#:~:text=The%2012.5%20million%20people%20who,from%20their%20state%20Medicaid%20program.&quot;>;12.5 million&lt;/a>; Americans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In-depth interviews with PACE staff and program participants conducted by two of us (Len Berry and Sunjay Letchuman); collaborations with PACE leaders, including two coauthors of this article (Mary Kummer Naber and Peter Fitzgerald); and our collective analysis of the features and daily operations of a PACE model in southeastern Michigan (led by Mary) reveal how PACE successfully delivers individualized, home-centered care to poor older adults while lowering overall costs. Given that PACE currently serves only about 60,000 of these patients, expanding the program has useful management and cost implications for health care systems nationally. Although nursing home and other institutionalized elder care clearly demand improvement, the United States also must invest in reimagining what elder care can be. PACE provides a roadmap.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;More Comprehensive, Less Costly Care&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The PACE program, first developed in San Francisco in 1973, is a comprehensive, integrated, community-based care model that lets older adults continue to live at home as long as possible. There are now 150 PACE programs in 32 states. The basic philosophy is that care should include what matters most to older poor people: all-inclusive care comprising nutrition, social interaction, transportation, and home upkeep, in addition to medical and related services. The goal is to treat patients with dignity as they safely live at home, rather than in an institution, and receive every needed service from one entity — all while lowering costs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All Medicare beneficiaries needing nursing home–level care but wishing to live at home are eligible for PACE. However, Medicare beneficiaries who do not meet their state&#39;s Medicaid income requirement are required to pay an amount equivalent to the monthly Medicaid payment, limiting access to millions of seniors who could benefit from the program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The program offers patients (called “participants”) all their Medicare- and Medicaid-covered benefits, including primary care, adult day care, rehabilitative care, and meals at a local PACE center. PACE provides transportation and various in-home services and is the payer for medical care that it cannot offer internally, such as emergency room visits and hospital stays. PACE organizations are paid on a monthly, risk-adjusted, capitated basis by Medicare and Medicaid, meaning they are paid &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/outreach-and-education/american-indian-alaska-native/aian/ltss-ta-center/info/pace#:~:text=The%20program%20receives%20capitated%20reimbursements,each%20patient%20the%20program%20serves.&quot;>;a set amount per month&lt;/a>; based, in part, on participants&#39; medical complexity. PACE programs bear full financial risk for all care, and participants do not pay anything out of pocket.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Available &lt;a href=&quot;https://agsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jgs.12637&quot;>;evidence&lt;/a>; shows that PACE reduces health care utilization and costs. Compared with similar populations, PACE participants have substantially lower rates of hospitalization (539 vs. 962 admissions per 1,000 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430746/&quot;>;person-years&lt;/a>;). &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/biomedgerontology/article/68/1/47/549686?login=true&quot;>;South Carolina&lt;/a>;, for example, annually saves nearly $9,000 per PACE participant compared with residents in alternative long-term care settings such as nursing homes; &lt;a href=&quot;https://health.wyo.gov/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/SFY-2020-Wyoming-Medicaid-Annual-Report.pdf&quot;>;Wyoming&lt;/a>; saves over $12,000 per PACE participant. However, PACE is about far more than saving money — it is about restoring dignity and joy to people&#39;s lives.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;An Exemplary Model&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One outstanding PACE program is PACE Southeast Michigan (PACE SEMI), which the National PACE Association identified as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npaonline.org/sites/default/files/PDFs/2018%20AC%20PowerPoint.pdf&quot;>;“bright spot”&lt;/a>; for its growth and quality metrics. PACE SEMI is organized as a tax-exempt nonprofit and is owned by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.henryford.com/&quot;>;Henry Ford Health&lt;/a>; (55%) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pvm.org/&quot;>;Presbyterian Villages of Michigan&lt;/a>; (45%). With seven centers serving 1,600 participants and employing 700 people, PACE SEMI increases its net enrollment by an average of 30 participants each month, compared with two participants each month in PACE centers nationally. Approximately 15% of PACE SEMI participants visit an emergency room each year for any reason, compared with &lt;a href=&quot;https://aspe.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/documents/9739cab65ad0221a66ebe45463d10d37/dual-eligible-beneficiaries-integrated-care.pdf&quot;>;25%&lt;/a>; of PACE participants nationally and 31% of Medicare Advantage enrollees. PACE SEMI participants also use inpatient hospital services less frequently: In 2019, PACE SEMI participants had 302 fewer &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.cms.gov/summary-statistics-on-use-and-payments/medicare-service-type-reports/cms-program-statistics-medicare-advantage-inpatient-hospital&quot;>;hospitalizations per 1,000 persons&lt;/a>; compared to Medicare Advantage enrollees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The PACE model is built on interdisciplinary teamwork. All PACE SEMI staff members are expected to see themselves as physical, mental, emotional, and spiritual “healers.” They include the primary care doctor who emphasizes preventing illness and injury as much as ordering treatments, the nurse and social worker who coordinate care, the onsite pharmacist who stays alert for prescribed drugs that may do more harm than good for specific patients, the kitchen chef who customizes meals to participants&#39; tastes and allergies, the participant-care associate who gives supportive care for daily activities (including showers), and the drivers who transport participants to and from PACE centers and other important destinations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike some PACE programs, PACE SEMI has behavioral health and spiritual care specialists at each center who get to know each participant they serve. In one case mentioned by a PACE physician, a spiritual care provider asked clinic staff to immediately check on a patient who seemed “off.” It turned out the patient was having a stroke and quickly received life-saving care. In a less-dramatic case, a social worker took it upon herself to persuade a local Trader Joe&#39;s store to donate flowers for participants to take home each week. Team members hold weekly meetings where everyone has equal input about how to prevent avoidable emergency room visits and advance the quality of life for their participants.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Whole-Person Care&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At its core, the PACE model is relationship-based: Participants and staff members know each other well, which facilitates “whole-person healing” customized to each individual. Indeed, members are called “participants” precisely because of their active role in planning their care, which goes far beyond medical services and addresses head-on the isolation that many older people who live alone endure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A day at a PACE SEMI center includes needed medical and rehabilitative services and is filled with customized activities such as music, painting, games, breakfast and lunch with friends, and regular group sessions where participants share “what I am grateful for,” cultivating a sense of belonging and community. Participants can get their hair shampooed, cut, and styled. They receive instruction on living safely at home and are given iPads (called “GrandPads”), designed for senior use, that let them easily contact family or PACE staff or play games. The kitchen prepares food for participants to take home at the end of the day. Participants can also use the onsite gym staffed with physical and occupational therapists. (“To see a 90-year-old working out is amazing,” one therapist said.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Dancing Kathy” arrived at PACE SEMI in a wheelchair. Aided by the rehabilitation staff, she eventually graduated to a walker and, months later, a cane. In an interview one year after starting at PACE, Kathy said she no longer needed the cane most of the time and could now dance. She then joined several staff members to dance the “Hustle” in front of the cafeteria lunch crowd.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Proactive Investments in Health&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Most of the enormous amount spent on health care in the United States is reactive. Patients get sick, treatment ensues, costs are incurred. PACE shows the potential of investing in health, not just health care, proactively. PACE SEMI and other well-run PACE programs do just about anything to help people continue to live at home safely. For instance, if a participant needs a shower chair at home to prevent a fall, PACE SEMI buys the chair, sets it up, and teaches the participant how to use it. With money generated by community fundraising, PACE SEMI fixes porches and stairs, replaces heaters, improves lighting, and even roots out bedbugs. It partners with an ambulance service whose paramedics often provide in-home care that prevents ER visits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such spending can greatly improve the quality of people&#39;s lives while reducing downstream costs. One of PACE SEMI&#39;s participants, “Mr. B,” had a career as a musician but now lives alone. After leaving the PACE center each week, Mr. B was a frequent visitor to ERs for mental health–related issues and anxiety. After the PACE staff realized Mr. B was missing music in his life, the center bought him a headset and player so he could listen to his favorite music. The ER visits stopped.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Service with a Soul&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PACE SEMI&#39;s secret sauce is its culture. Hiring for caring, not just competence, is as central as intensively training staff to distinguish between nonmedical healing and medical interventions. Some staff members with traditional health care backgrounds must “unlearn” their bias for episodic care. And in working with a vulnerable population, staff must move beyond risk aversion, common in institutional elder care.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Keeping people safe does not require stealing their freedom, as Atul Gawande discussed in &lt;a href=&quot;https://atulgawande.com/book/being-mortal/&quot;>;&lt;em>;Being Mortal&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;: “…our elderly are left with a controlled and supervised institutional existence, a medically designed answer to unfixable problems, a life designed to be safe but empty of anything they care about.” With creativity, compassion, and commitment, a carefully selected, well-trained staff who are themselves treated with dignity can instill dignity, a sense of belonging, and even joy in PACE participants. As Renee, a food service worker at PACE SEMI, puts it, “We add love to the food.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PACE is about investing in people&#39;s well-being, keeping them as well as possible for as long as possible. It offers older adults the chance to live at home with a higher quality of care — and of life. The current model serves primarily low-income seniors; however, the bigger opportunity is to expand it to include all chronically ill older adults. Such models will be useful as Congress &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthaffairs.org/content/forefront/congress-considers-strategies-improve-medicare-and-medicaid-integration-dual-eligible&quot;>;crafts legislation&lt;/a>; to expand PACE, as health care organizations plan how to launch PACE programs efficiently and effectively, and as program leaders and managers seek to develop the nuts and bolts of care that offers healing to patients and energizes staff.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Your Love for Work May Alienate Your Colleagues]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1344042166-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;humanmade/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Research shows that employees who are passionate about their work are more productive, innovative, and collaborative. New research suggests that these employees also see passion for work as a moral imperative, and they&amp;#8217;re more likely to judge colleagues who are motivated by other reasons, such as financial stability, social status, or familial obligations. The research also found that these employees were more likely to offer help to their more passionate colleagues. Leaders must recognize the diverse motivations that drive their workforce and create an inclusive environment that supports and values all forms of motivation, rather than penalizing those who do not fit the passion-centric mold.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0191308522000132?casa_token=fZzxkx3ayVAAAAAA:y_RucibVaoH6Kq9rhrKEOJPv3EKW-Ht94rTqrsXT8ajB4cqEKH_Y3RYdJfDwnqXCDP_i7d774A&quot;>;growing number of companies&lt;/a>; are seeking out employees whose passion for their work is the driving force behind their performance, and they&#39;re investing in strategies to encourage and nurture this motivation. The research on this topic &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/job.2434?casa_token=qK7aO_h5mzMAAAAA:00L4l-RKd7-sc3yfdVz-ToizgtmmobloM6Cvvd4-yWz19BX5JUsGmKTIzANA9GpjMzDpoGdT_LYoiw&quot;>;is clear&lt;/a>; — more passionate employees are more productive, innovative, and collaborative, and they demonstrate higher levels of commitment to their organizations. Fostering passion is a winning strategy for organizations that aspire to achieve sustained growth, innovation, and success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, in the pursuit of nurturing passion, &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2020.1761?af=R&quot;>;our recent research&lt;/a>; reveals that employers may have overlooked and neglected the needs of employees driven by other sources of motivation, such as financial stability, social status, or familial obligations. These employees &lt;a href=&quot;/2003/06/lets-hear-it-for-b-players&quot;>;play a critical role in the success of their companies&lt;/a>;, but may be subject to an invisible penalty due to their perceived lack of passion for their work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Doing What You Love Makes You “Moralize” Loving Your Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our research involving 1,245 full-time employees across several organizations that varied in size and industry revealed a novel phenomenon in the contemporary workplace: The more people love their work, the more they see it as a moral imperative. Employees who were more passionate about their work agreed more strongly with sentences like “Working for personal enjoyment is morally virtuous” and “Being intrinsically motivated is moral.” For these individuals, loving their work had moral significance beyond personal fulfillment, and they were more likely to judge their colleagues&#39; work motivations against their own moral yardstick or ask, “Are my colleagues here for the &lt;em>;right&lt;/em>; reasons?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This emphasis on loving your work as a moral obligation has far-reaching implications. Our research suggests that those who love their work more are also more likely to view working for external rewards less favorably. Those who agreed with sentences like “Being intrinsically motivated is moral” also agreed with sentences like “Those who do their work for money alone are not virtuous employees” and “Employees who are motivated by external rewards tend to be immoral.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Critically, we found consequences to these character judgements. Employees who love their work more also prioritized helping their more passionate colleagues, whom they consider morally superior. In contrast, employees who worked for other reasons received less help from their more passionate colleagues, making it more difficult for them to advance in their organizations and making them more likely to be excluded from important projects. Such treatment can have severe consequences for employee morale, retention, and overall organizational performance. By contrast, employees who worked for external rewards treated their colleagues equally, regardless of why they worked.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Creating an Environment that Values Employees&#39; Diverse Motivations&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managers need to be aware that organizations that valorize passion can create a sense of alienation for some employees. Recognizing and celebrating the unique contributions of all employees, regardless of their underlying motivations, will help create a sense of belonging and purpose among your workforce, leading to increased engagement and productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers should also strive to foster an open and inclusive workplace culture where employees feel comfortable discussing their motivations and goals, even when they are misaligned with a passion-driven ethos. This can both encourage dialogue between employees who vary in their motivations for working and provide opportunities for employees to explore and develop their passion both inside and outside the workplace. For example, mentorship, networking relationships, or job crafting (ie, spending more time on tasks that are more meaningful to them) can expose employees to roles they may be more excited about.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are an employee who loves their work, keep in mind that this could make you more judgmental about your colleagues and affect how much you help them. Not everyone needs to do the work because they are passionate about it. Some employees may have families to take care of, need benefits as a safety net, or have not yet discovered their true passion for work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, organizations should examine whether their benefits and perks appeal to employees with diverse motivations. While some employees may be attracted to work because they are passionate about it, others may be motivated by flexible work arrangements, or access to professional development opportunities. By offering a range of benefits and perks, leaders can create a workplace that appeals to employees with diverse motivations and help retain top talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the prevalent belief that passion is crucial for success, all employees should be appreciated for who they are and how they contribute — regardless of their motivations for working. Leaders should recognize the diverse motivations that drive their workforce and create an inclusive environment that supports and values all forms of motivation, rather than penalizing those who do not fit the passion-centric mold.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Apple&rsquo;s Vision Pro Really For?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1496199364_1363676153.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Justin Sullivan/ Damian Pawlos/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To understand the value of Apple&amp;#8217;s new goggles, it&amp;#8217;s helpful to think about how virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) correspond to two fundamental tasks in decision making. VR presents new information; AR distills information from an existing environment. But previous headsets and internet-enabled glasses haven&amp;#8217;t tapped into the potential for either of these in a decision-making context. Apple is betting that it can build an ecosystem of app developers who can.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Apple announced a new computer last week, to great fanfare. The Vision Pro is a computer that is worn on your face, but the novel aspect is how you use it. Rather than view the computer&#39;s output through a physical screen, that output is projected directly into your eyes with two very small but high-resolution displays a very small distance in front of you. Rather than control the computer through a keyboard, mouse, or touch screen, the primary user interface is through eye tracking and gestures. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Just as they removed the stylus for screens when they launched the iPhone, Apple requires no physical controller to use the computer. The computer senses what you are interested in interacting with by watching your eye movement and then looks at your hands to determine what you want to do. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;There have been antecedents to each of these things — a myriad of worn devices for viewing such as the Google Glass or Meta&#39;s Quest Pro and technologies such as &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/reviews/leap-motion-controller-review/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Leap Motion&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; and the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jVDPrFvBvWw&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Myo Armband&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; for gesture control. But none of these predecessors put it all together as a coherent vision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Apple has termed this new device &lt;/span>;a spatial computer&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;. The name is apt, because the device can use any physical space around you as a canvas to display digital outputs. There is no need for a desk (or lap) to place the device, and there are no limits on the size of the perceived viewing area. That means you could technically sit in a small space, like an airplane seat, and watch a cinema-sized movie. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;What should you be aiming to do with a spatial computer? Right now, Apple has outlined use cases that seem pedestrian. You can use it like a normal computer or iPad but with the current 2D information presented on a much more flexible and unconstrained display. There&#39;s demand for that. It will be of value where you do not have much space. And it will be of value to those who currently use their space with a host of large displays. In that sense, the closest analogue is a very large-screen TV. Would people pay $3,500 for that? They do right now. Even Apple sells a display (the Pro Display XDR) that can cost up to $6,000. From that perspective, it is easily in the cost ballpark for current use cases. This strategy also has the benefit of seeding this new platform with the vast number of applications that already exist for the iPad and the iPhone.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;A better and more convenient display for 2D content, however, does not appear to justify the technological and R&amp;amp;D weight that has gone into the Vision Pro. The real question is whether this device can lead to the augmented and virtual reality applications that would justify strapping a computer to your head. It certainly has the technical capabilities to do so. The Vision Pro can display 3D objects in your current space or even transport you to new spaces. Apple, however, barely mentioned the terms AR and VR during their announcement. In doing so, they drew a line people have not drawn before. This is no AR or VR device or technology. The technology is a spatial computer, and if there is a role for AR and VR, it is in applications that run on a spatial computer.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Let&#39;s review those concepts. Augmented reality (or AR) involves taking the environment around you and changing your perception of it. Google Glass did this by showing you notifications via smart glasses. The Vision Pro does this by placing 2D displays in that environment and fixing them so that when your head moves, the display does not. It appears to be there in your current environment. This is achieved by passing a very accurate video of the real world through the device to you. You don&#39;t see your environment directly, but you think you are doing so. Thus, technically, Apple is augmenting a video capture of your environment, not overlaying things on your direct viewing of it. To a user, there&#39;s no real difference.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Virtual reality (or VR) involves taking the user and immersing them in a virtual environment. The Vision Pro captures the full attention of your eye, and so you are, by definition, immersed in a virtual environment. In one mode, that looks like the environment you are actually in. Turn the dial, and that can change, and you can be transported somewhere else. The video pass-through from your current environment is replaced by a digitally created 3D environment. From that perspective, this is clearly a VR device. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The important thing to note is that despite being capable of AR and VR, these use-cases were not emphasized by Apple. Thus, they have produced a device capable of both but have not found compelling use cases in either domain. This is one of the reasons that they announced it at their annual developer conference. Apple needs apps, and they need other people to imagine them.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In a &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.16872&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;recent paper&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, we outlined what we believed were the ways that AR and VR apps could add unique value. Beyond gaming and entertainment, our focus is on economic uses — specifically, those that would increase users&#39; productivity. In this respect, we ask: Which AR and VR applications can create real value by assisting users in making better decisions? For someone looking to build applications for the platform Apple has created, understanding the possibilities is crucial. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Most decisions involve some degree of uncertainty. Information is the cure for that, allowing you to know more and, therefore, make fewer errors. But there are two aspects to using information in decisions. First, you need to have the right information available. Second, you need to have the cognitive space to distill and parse that information for usefulness.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;As it turns out, AR and VR map into each of these things. VR has the ability to present the user with more relevant information, especially when that information is either not with them or is costly to acquire. By immersing users in new contexts, what it does is bring that information to them. In some cases, it may be a realistic view of what is going on inside a building, say, during a fire. In other cases, it presents a safe, simulated environment, such as a flight simulator that facilitates training without the high stakes.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;By contrast, AR takes information presented in a given context and parses it to yield the information that is relevant. For instance, when you meet someone at a conference, it provides identification of who that person is without you having to search your own memory. Or, it can provide a helpful overlay with exit routes if you are dealing with a fire. In each case, the goal is to distill the quantity of information from the user&#39;s environment and present the information that is needed. The one thing to note is that the Vision Pro is not meant to be a portable computer to be used outside of the home or the workplace, which limits its applicability in navigating external environments (such as while driving).&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This perspective highlights why many previous AR and VR purported use cases have been of low value. VR meetings with avatars in pretty rooms do not provide information that is obviously more useful to those in the meetings that might arise from a Zoom call. AR glasses that provide text notifications as you walk around are increasing your cognitive load rather than decreasing it. Our framework suggests that the best use cases will be in contexts where it is normally expensive or dangerous to get information, highlighting the value of VR, or where the environment is so complex that the value of digital overlays to clarify it via AR is high &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;— &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;or both. Think applications like prototyping the design of a new aircraft or building, or assisting in remote medical procedures. The Vision Pro exhibits capabilities of being able to do each of these things but the job of experimenting and designing for these use cases has been left to others. Developers looking to profit off the platform Apple has created would do well to focus on applications that provide users with hard-to-access contextual information at just the right level of detail.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This is par for the course for Apple when they first introduce a device. The iPod was a digital walkman. The iPhone was a connected iPod. The iPad was a bigger iPhone. The Apple Watch was a better smartwatch. And the Vision Pro is an unconstrained 3D screen. In the previous cases, the device is outgrown and becomes more than that initial use by enabling developer innovation. The Vision Pro is a welcome new&lt;/span>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshuagans.substack.com/p/apples-big-experiment&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;experiment&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; along a well-trodden path in computing.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Proactively Defuse Tension on Your Team]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_691050121.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Unaddressed and unresolved interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior can lead to organizational failure. They can impact team performance, collaboration, and productivity, create operational friction among teams, and cause employees to feel disengaged, distrustful, and unmotivated. While conflict at work is inevitable, we often have our own agency to proactively root out problems and stop them from escalating swiftly with empathy, accountability, self-awareness, and courage. The author, a Chief People Officer, offers five steps to do this: 1) Root out toxic behavior and tensions, 2) seek to understand, not just be understood, 3) assess the right time to intervene, 4) ask for help, and 5) repair harm; repair trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As a chief people officer, I have seen firsthand how unaddressed and unresolved interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior can lead to organizational failure. A subtle racial slight, an argument over a project&#39;s deliverables, or gossip over perceived unfair advantages can negatively impact team performance, collaboration, and productivity, create operational friction among teams, and cause employees to feel disengaged, distrustful, and unmotivated. These issues can arise due to various factors, including differences in personality and perspectives, racial,&amp;nbsp;class&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; and gender privilege, work and communication styles, power imbalances, and/or lack of transparency and clarity over work processes and business goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-navigate-conflict-with-a-coworker&quot;>;interpersonal conflict at work is inevitable&lt;/a>;, we often forget our own agency to root out problems and stop them from escalating swiftly with empathy, accountability, self-awareness, and courage. Doing so can feel scary and dangerous, especially when you&#39;re a junior team member or belong to one or more underrepresented groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recently, a young woman of color, a rising star at my organization, expressed reservations about joining a new team that could significantly advance her career. During a conversation with the team&#39;s manager, she was troubled when he made an insensitive remark about what he perceived as racial segregation of employees at a social event. Concerned about her career and the potential for a racially hostile or uncomfortable work environment where this manager may not respect her identity and experiences, she sought guidance from her HR business partner, who directed her to me.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We discussed her desired outcome of joining the team while holding the manager accountable for the impact of his words and encouraging improvements in his behavior. I offered her the choice of addressing the issue directly or receiving support from me in the conversation, prioritizing her safety and dignity. After careful consideration, she chose to engage directly. I coached her on how to express herself confidently and thoughtfully. Subsequently, she shared a positive outcome—the manager demonstrated empathy, offered a genuine apology, and committed to openly acknowledging the dismissive comments with the entire team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Based on the experience of this employee and many others I&#39;ve coached throughout my career, here are five actions that you&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;can take to reduce or stop interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior if you witness or experience harm in the workplace:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Identify the root cause of the tension.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When dealing with interpersonal friction in the workplace, the first step is to identify the root causes — the true sources of tension. In her book, &lt;em>;The Fearless Organization&lt;/em>;, Amy Edmondson explores the cost of a lack of psychological safety in organizations, including toxic work environments, burnout, and human capital loss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Removing unhealthy behaviors that reduce individuals&#39; and teams&#39; safety, comfort, and performance requires us to face what needs to be changed. Power imbalances and differences of opinion over how to run a project, which partners to engage with, and performance measures are often the root cause of misunderstandings, disagreements, and collaboration collapse. In those situations, junior employees, women of color, and underrepresented employees are often afraid to speak up about conflict for fear of retaliation or being judged negatively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the above example, the root cause of tension was the manager&#39;s racially insensitive comment, leading to concerns about a potentially hostile or uncomfortable work environment, lack of respect, and disregard for the lived experiences of this woman of color and others. By approaching such situations with support, empathy, and courage, we can uncover and address the underlying causes of tensions and prevent them from negatively impacting individuals&#39; well-being and professional development. It&#39;s important to recognize that this approach may not always be feasible or safe. In this case, the employee trusted that I would intervene if the conversation veered off course.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Seek to understand, not just be understood.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Professional relationships are human relationships fraught with shared misunderstandings. A wrongly placed, unintentional word in a stressful moment, especially those fed by gender and racial biases, can drive a deep wedge between coworkers. To build shared understanding, it is important to hold space for others&#39; opinions, empathize with complex and nuanced situations, and take responsibility for nurturing a sense of safety and trust among colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this instance, the manager embraced the opportunity to connect, learn, and grow, seeking to comprehend the impact of their words and actions instead of adopting a defensive stance. This response demonstrated a willingness to acknowledge mistakes and make an effort to change without fearing appearing incompetent or being canceled. Rather than deflecting or bemoaning leadership challenges, the manager prioritized their team&#39;s well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By helping the manager see and understand her concerns, the employee demonstrated a remarkable level of empathy. Though it would have been fair for her to write off this manager, she recognized the opportunity for growth and engaged in a constructive dialogue. This approach allowed her to assert her agency in addressing the manager&#39;s lack of awareness regarding insensitive comments. She chose to model a collaborative approach where others could learn and improve.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their interaction vividly demonstrated the transformative power of open, safe, and trusting communication, highlighting the remarkable potential for positive change when both parties approach tricky, uncomfortable conversations with an authentic intention to understand and be understood.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Assess the right time to intervene.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Saying something and not saying something are both choices that carry profound consequences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sometimes, an intervention can occur in the moment or shortly after that. If you&#39;re alone with someone who has just shared an offensive, denigrating, or derogatory comment and feel at risk of saying something that may be misunderstood or weaponized against you, wait until there are others around that can offer support or report it to HR or an anonymous hotline. Alternatively, if you feel comfortable, you can try saying, “When you said ___, I felt ____” or “I&#39;m sure you didn&#39;t mean it, but that comment didn&#39;t land well on me.” The person receiving the feedback may need to be made aware of the impact of their words and actions. Waiting too long risks negative feelings lingering and growing within yourself and others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Had the employee not shared her concerns, or had the manager responded defensively and retaliated, it would have resulted in a missed opportunity to cultivate a healthy and thriving workplace environment. Moreover, it could have perpetuated a culture of fear and burdened her and other employees who share similar fears, ultimately hindering their growth and well-being throughout their careers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Ask for help.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As I advanced in my career, I yearned for leaders who would use their position of authority to challenge toxic behavior. As I assumed leadership roles myself, I realized the responsibility fell on me to exemplify the behaviors I desired.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you lack guidance from a manager or leader on navigating tricky situations or your organization&#39;s conflict resolution, grievance, and disciplinary procedures, turn to your HR team. I understand the hesitation in reaching out, especially if your relationship with HR isn&#39;t strong. Nevertheless, HR is there to advocate for employee voice, agency, and safety. They can assist you in gathering information, understanding root causes, and determining appropriate actions. An HR partner can facilitate constructive dialogue, coach you and others involved, and find proactive solutions to address behavioral issues. It&#39;s important to approach this option carefully, as it may intensify tensions or discomfort among team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/featured%20insights/diversity%20and%20inclusion/women%20in%20the%20workplace%202022/women-in-the-workplace-2022.pdf&quot;>;Women in the Workplace 2022&lt;/a>;, LeanIn and McKinsey&#39;s annual report about the state of women in corporate America, women overall, and Black women and women with disabilities in particular, frequently experience microaggressions at work, such as having their judgment questioned or receiving criticism for their demeanor. Seeking support from the resources available in the workplace can make a significant difference in fostering a thriving and healthy career. Holding colleagues, managers, and leadership accountable is crucial in addressing and mitigating these harmful experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this example, the employee approached HR for coaching to navigate this complex situation. By utilizing available resources, she empowered herself to address the issue effectively, making a significant difference in her experience and that of others on the team. Her proactive approach, seeking assistance, being open to feedback, and engaging in self-reflection, played a pivotal role in achieving a positive outcome.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Repair harm; repair trust.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Repeated acts of harm, such as subtle &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/research-the-real-time-impact-of-microaggressions&quot;>;microaggressions&lt;/a>;, can weigh heavily on well-being, workplace satisfaction, and productivity. To heal from interpersonal tensions that arise from misunderstandings, misaligned perspectives or expectations, hurtful language, abuses of power, or breaches of trust, the person harmed must feel heard, respected, and valued.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to Kay Pranis, a national leader in restorative justice, assuming accountability and implementing measures to rectify the damage caused and prevent its recurrence requires &lt;a href=&quot;https://irp.cdn-website.com/76b5fa75/files/uploaded/Kay%20Pranis%20Article%20for%20March%20Blog.pdf&quot;>;five elements&lt;/a>;:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Acknowledge that your actions caused harm.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Acknowledge that you had agency in those actions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Understand the full impact of your actions on anyone who was impacted.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Take steps to repair the harm and make amends.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Identify patterns or habits that led to causing harm and take steps to change those habits.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Repairing harm can manifest in various ways: acknowledging the harm, expressing remorse, admitting guilt, and committing to behavioral change through new policies, commitments, or agreements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a woman of color, I&#39;ve heard my fair share of comments that offend, upset, or hurt me, and I have regrettably done the same to others. Whenever I&#39;ve been the target of microaggressions, I try to collect my thoughts and emotions before addressing a coworker, respond assertively with “I” statements, and often reply with kindness and humor to defuse the tension. For example: “When you restated my recommendation in the recap meeting without giving me credit, I felt erased from our conversation. I&#39;d like us to have a healthy working relationship. Can you help me understand why you omitted my contribution?” Or: “When you confused me for the other Latina on the floor, I felt we were both invisible to you. And I think I&#39;m pretty memorable!”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When I unintentionally make an insensitive comment, such as misgendering someone, I immediately approach the impacted individual with humility. I sincerely listen to understand the impact of my words and offer a heartfelt apology while taking complete accountability for my words and actions. I also encourage them to call me in if I repeat such behavior because I am committed to learning from my mistakes and growing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear, it is not the responsibility of women, BIPOC, or members of marginalized communities to educate their colleagues on how to foster healthy interactions. To proactively create more meaningful relationships, ask yourself these questions: How can I focus on what the person is saying, and not solely on how they say it or how they look? What else do I need to know to understand what my colleague is trying to communicate instead of dismissing or avoiding what they say? And before addressing someone&#39;s uncomfortable comment, ask yourself: Am I responding to being shut down, ignored, or offended, or am I trying to be right? If both parties are willing, there are ways of responding that can lead to constructive conversations and shared understanding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Repeated acts of harm in particular must be addressed. MIT&#39;s Sloan School of Management conducted &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/toxic-culture-is-driving-the-great-resignation/&quot;>;a study in 2022&lt;/a>; that found that employee turnover is 10 times more influenced by a toxic corporate culture than compensation. Taking responsibility means understanding the wide range of perspectives and experiences across teams and proactively identifying sources of tension. A good starting point is asking yourself, “What do I need to hear, what do I need to say, and what would I like to see as an outcome?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this example, the manager took essential steps to repair the trust his insensitive comments had initially broken. He demonstrated accountability by acknowledging the harm his words caused and engaged in open dialogue. By actively working to understand the impact of his words and offering to take tangible steps to change his behavior, he successfully began repairing the trust with his new employee and, quite possibly, his relationship with the broader team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of us want to change workplace conditions so everyone can thrive, yet sometimes, we are terrified of messing up, saying the wrong thing, or not being able to do enough. Addressing interpersonal tensions and toxicity requires an ongoing, proactive effort that fosters empathy, intentionality, and courage. By identifying the true source of the tension, seeking understanding, assessing when to intervene, involving neutral third parties if necessary, and repairing harm and trust quickly and often, you can prevent conflict from escalating and build a stronger, more connected, and more effective team.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>