<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[When Your Employee Isn&rsquo;t Reaching Their Full Potential]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potential]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_56660878.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jeanette Martin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; 关闭-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;感觉您的员工没有主动发挥自己的才能，这可能会令人沮丧。作为他们的经理，你甚至可能想知道这是否是知识或意志力的问题：他们是否不明白如何才能发挥最佳表现？或者他们只是没有动力？在本文中，作者探讨了员工可能无法充分发挥潜力的三个主要原因：个人挑战、人际关系问题和领导力问题。考虑到这一点确实令人不快，但请记住，至少 30% 的员工认为自己的工作是有问题的。绩效是管理方式的产物，这意味着您的领导力可以在决定人们是否发挥潜力方面发挥重要作用。尽管你打算支持和培养你的员工，但你可能会通过微观管理、过于宽松的监督或目标沟通不畅等管理罪恶来压制他们的才能。关于这一可能令人震惊的启示的好消息是，它是一个完全在您控制范围内的领域。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potial?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-pottial?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;您已经在您的员工身上看到了真正能力的闪光，甚至可能是偶尔的才华。那么，为什么他们未能发挥这种潜力呢？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一个关心培养员工技能、能力和职业发展轨迹的领导者，如果他们没有主动发挥自己的才能，会感到非常沮丧。有时，您甚至可能想知道这是知识还是意志力的问题：他们是否不明白如何才能发挥最佳表现？还是&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/4-reasons-good-employees-lose-their-motivation&quot;>;他们只是没有动力&lt;/a>;？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;显然，您认为员工的“典型表现”（他们通常做的事情）不如他们的“最大表现”或能力（他们能做到的最好水平）是有原因的 - 因此，作为第一步，重要的是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tand fonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/08959280701333289&quot;>;澄清并量化&lt;/a>;这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许您正在考虑他们巅峰表现的具体示例，例如在高风险情况下发表引人注目的演讲，或者在他们展示宝贵技能的特定时刻，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10. 1111/1467-8721.ep10768746?journalCode=cdpa&quot;>;智力&lt;/a>;（识别重要的隐藏模式，化混乱和复杂为秩序，学习新事物），&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691611421204?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;好奇心&lt;/a >;（提出真正有洞察力的问题），或&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2015.1030293&quot;>;创造力&lt;/a>;（提供意想不到的见解，产生原创且有用的新想法）。如果他们曾经做过一次，那么他们显然有能力达到这个水平，更不用说多次了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，缩小员工可能无法充分发挥潜力的原因至关重要。我们发现了三个主要类别要检查：个人挑战，人际关系问题或您自己的领导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;个人挑战&lt;/strong>; &lt;/strong>; &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;人们无法充分发挥自己的潜力的一个原因是，很少有人知道他们的&lt;a a href =“ “>;实际潜力&lt;/a>;首先。考虑一下，在任何专业知识、才能或绩效领域，人们的优秀程度和他们认为自己的优秀程度之间的重叠度通常小于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2011-29559-001&quot;>;10%&lt;/a>;。作为领导者，您可以向您领导和管理的团队成员赠送一份强大的礼物：了解他们的能力，有时甚至在他们行动之前，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Talk-Three-Powerful-Feedback/dp/1912555093&quot;>;举起一面镜子&lt;/a>;。事实上，反馈是员工绩效的关键催化剂，但&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/buy/1996-02773-003&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，三分之二的情况下，反馈要么不能让别人变得更好，要么甚至让他们&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/the-feedback-fallacy&quot;>;变得更糟&lt;/a>;！&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;确保你特别赞扬了员工在自己的岗位上的表现。最好，这样他们就知道什么是“优秀”，并让他们参与讨论他们在那些时刻为成功所做的事情。他们之所以能成功演讲是因为他们花了时间练习和准备吗？他们是否事先采访了观众以便他们引用相关例子？帮助他们深入挖掘成功背后的原因有助于向他们展示如何复制成功。换句话说，将自己视为&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;作为教练&lt;/a>;，而不是老板。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们未能发挥潜力的另一个主要驱动因素就是&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2010-06019-003&quot;>;动机&lt;/a>;。如果您过去看到您的员工表现出色，那么显然能力不是问题所在，因此他们当前的积极性值得调查。您可以与您的团队成员联系，了解发生了什么情况，尤其是在发生突然变化的情况下。也许他们正在经历&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/how-to-manage-an-employee-whos-having-a-personal-crisis&quot;>;个人生活中的挑战&lt;/a>;，或者正在走向&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/do-you-know-burnout-when-you-see-it&quot;>;倦怠&lt;/a>;，需要休息一下。或者，也许&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-to-lose-your-best-employees&quot;>;他们在自己的角色中感到停滞&lt;/a>;，需要新的挑战，包括延伸目标，您可以&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/02/give-your-employees-specific-goals-and-the-freedom-to-figure-out-how-to-reach-them&quot;>;帮助他们制定&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong >;人际问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;有时，员工的表现不佳来自于他们周围的环境——即其他人。正如鲍里斯·格罗伊斯伯格和他的同事&lt;a href=&quot;/2004/05/the-risky-business-of-hiring-stars&quot;>;所表明的&lt;/a>;，迁移到新公司的明星员工往往无法复制他们的成功，因为帮助推动他们崛起的支持因素（例如公司特定的知识或网络）不再存在。事实上，尽管组织通常为外部聘用的员工支付的费用高于内部晋升的员工，但外部聘用通常无法为内部候选人带来&lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/article/why-external-hires-get-paid-more-and-perform-worse-than-internal-staff/&quot;>;更多价值&lt;/a>;，尤其是因为许多以前使他们成功的条件可能不再存在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，您的员工可能会由于新的团队动态（可能是在同事离开或加入团队后）、角色或职责的改变、或感觉缺乏认可或地位变化（其他人获得晋升或奖金）而陷入停滞状态。您员工的才能可能没有改变，但他们的执行能力却没有改变。如果是这种情况，您需要诚实地讨论动态并找到重新构建或调解冲突的机会，或者将他们转移到更有可能成功的新角色。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;领导力问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;考虑起来令人不愉快，但请记住&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Why-Many-Incompetent-Become-Leaders/dp/163 3696324&quot;>;至少 30% 的员工绩效&lt;/a>;是其管理方式的结果，这意味着您的领导力可以在决定人们是否发挥潜力方面发挥重要作用。尽管您打算支持和培养您的员工，但您可能会通过&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/signs-that-youre-a-micromanager&quot;>;微观管理&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;/2015/06/get-what-you-need-from-your-hands-off-boss&quot;>;过于宽松的监管&lt;/a>;或糟糕的&lt;a href=&quot;/2011/02/making-sure-your -employees-suc&quot;>;传达目标&lt;/a>;，以及其他管理上的过失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关于这一可能令人震惊的揭露的好消息是，这是一个完全在您控制范围内的领域。通过围绕如何与员工沟通、提供反馈、授权他们和管理他们的&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/a-refresher-on-ab-testing&quot;>;A/B 测试&lt;/a>;策略，您可以直接检查您提供的指导的结果，并评估他们表现不佳的主要原因是否确实是 。 。 .&amp;nbsp;你。测试过去对他们有效的策略以及那些已被其他员工证明有效的策略很有用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有人都是独一无二的，没有一种策略适合所有人。话虽如此，通常情况下，当您花更多时间与与您有信任关系的员工相处并给予他们更多反馈（包括建设性批评、值得称赞、认可和资源）时，他们将更有可能发挥自己的潜力，而不是相反。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，请记住，人都是人，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Human-Automation-Quest-Reclaim-Unique-ebook/dp/B099KQ V3ZJ&quot;>;人不是机器&lt;/a>;。这意味着您不应该期望每个人都能始终发挥出最大水平或全部能力。事实上，地球上最有创造力和才华的人——在任何领域——他们的表现可能会非常不一致，因为&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2003-02410-016&quot;>;灵感是结果的强大驱动力&lt;/a>;，也是创新和卓越工作的主要动力。放宽员工的要求，尊重他们的自然周期，当然还要酌情&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/hold-your-team-accountable-with-compassion-not-fear&quot;>;让他们承担责任&lt;/a>;，这就是优秀管理者所做的事情。顺便说一句，支撑工作绩效的不一致或不稳定因素也可能适用于您 - 因此检查您是否正在发挥自己的潜力以及可能阻止您这样做的因素可能会有所帮助。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;了解员工绩效（也许还有您自己）的绩效差距是一种深思熟虑和同理心的练习。通过检查上述可能性，您将能够更好地帮助指导您的团队更频繁地发挥最佳状态。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Effectively &mdash; and Legally &mdash; Use Racial Data for DEI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_24_RacialData.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Ngadi Smart 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption =&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;美国最高法院最近裁决反对高等教育中的平权行动后，领导者可能会担心他们的 DEI 举措和计划将面临更多审查和法律挑战。虽然减少责任是一种负责任的举措，但作者警告不要让这些努力导致因恐惧而放弃有效的 DEI 做法。为了在这段时间内保持 DEI 的进展，企业应重点关注减少法律风险最大的种族数据的使用，同时采取果断行动，继续使用种族数据来消除歧视、消除偏见并创造更公平的工作场所。作者阐述了如何减少这种风险，确定了数据使用的五个目标（识别差异、消除普遍障碍、纠正歧视、设计公平流程以及展示 DEI 进展），并为希望维持 DEI 进展的公司提供了注意事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to- effectively-and-legally-use- race-data-for-dei?language=es&quot;>;西班牙语阅读&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to- effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;继美国最高法院裁定取消高等教育中具有种族意识的招生之后，一些企业领导者可能会担心，除了减少招聘中本已较低的多样性之外，管道，该裁决可能会导致他们的多元化、公平和包容性 (DEI) 举措和计划面临更多审查和法律挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然减少责任是一项负责任的举措，但领导者应注意确保他们防范法律风险的努力不会变成因恐惧而放弃有效的 DEI 实践。在这个动荡的时期保持 DEI 进步和承诺的关键在于有意识地采取行动：减少对最具法律风险的种族数据的使用，同时采取果断行动继续使用种族数据来消除歧视、消除偏见并创造更公平的工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;减少法律风险&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;要了解如何在这个复杂的主题上采取最佳行动，重要的是从法律基础开始。根据&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ftc.gov/policy-notices/no-fear-act/protections-against-discrimination&quot;>;《民权法案》第七章&lt;/a>;，在任何雇佣决策中考虑任何单一候选人或员工的种族都是违法的，即使是为了打造一支更加多元化、公平或包容的劳动力队伍。雇主无法制定事实上的招聘配额（例如，“该部门雇用的员工中 50% 必须是女性”），或为某些群体的员工“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wilmerhale.com/en/insights/blogs/esg-epicenter/20220524-california-court-strikes-down-law-on-board-diversity&quot;>;预留席位&lt;/a>;”，即使是为了多元化。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;根据法律，即使在最高法院最近做出裁决之后，性别意识或种族意识的招聘做法也是允许的&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;，但仅作为有限、临时和高度结构化的一部分&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cov.com/en/news-and-insights/insights/2023/07/considerations-for-employers-following-the-eeocs-response-to-the-supreme-courts -ruling-on-race-thought-college-admissions?utm_source=pardot&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=clientalerts&amp;amp;sc_camp=2D3D522D49CB4CE599B743213715F288&quot;>;自愿平权行动计划&lt;/a>;，仅在雇主发现全公司或全行业招聘歧视的证据时才采取，只是为了纠正最初的不平衡，以及只要不对非目标群体成员造成“不当伤害”（意味着雇主不能解雇白人工人来雇用有色人种工人）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;只要遵循这些指导方针，雇主和 DEI 从业者都不需要惊慌。删除“多元化”这个词，发誓在工作中不提及种族，或者关闭与种族相关的亲和团体，都是有害的过度反应，并不能反映出真正的法律风险。就目前情况而言，绝大多数工作场所 DEI 计划&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/2023/06/29/legal-experts-supremecourt-affirmative-action/&quot;>;受到法律先例的强烈支持&lt;/a>;，并且不太可能受到最高法院裁决的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果做得正确，DEI 计划可以&lt;a href=&quot;https://ajg.com/us/news-and-insights/2021 /sep/diversity-equity-and-inclusion-an-important-loss-prevention-tool/&quot;>;减少&lt;/a>;就业歧视和敌对工作环境索赔的风险，并可以降低整个组织的风险。然而，雇主仍然可以通过审核现有计划来降低风险，以确保它们不会违反现有法律。法律不允许指导招聘经理利用个人种族作为个人候选人的“决胜局”或“加分”的政策。为特定社会群体的成员留出具体数量或百分比的角色或席位也同样存在风险。避免诸如禁止不属于特定种族的员工加入员工资源团体或指示招聘人员由符合特定人口统计标准的人来填补职位之类的硬性规定（例如，“您必须由有色人种女性来担任此职位。”）从本质上讲，如果一项政策、流程或做法需要了解个人的种族特征才能做出影响其就业的决定，您可能需要对其进行审查。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;收集种族数据以识别差异&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一些领导者可能会阅读上一段并假设降低风险的简单方法就是根本不收集任何种族数据。然而，做出这样的结论将是把婴儿和洗澡水一起倒掉，并可能使公司的 DEI 进展面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然使用个人的种族数据来影响招聘决定是非法的，但汇总整个候选人库的种族数据来确定与种族相关的整体差异是完全合理的。结合员工敬业度调查收集人口统计数据可能会揭示会议参与方面的种族差距，值得仔细研究。结合人力资源数据收集人口统计数据可能会揭示值得干预的营业额中的种族差距。换句话说，收集人口数据（包括种族）可以揭示现有做法、先前的歧视性做法或劳动力池的历史限制所造成的不利影响，这些标准均由平等就业机会委员会的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constangy.com/affirmative-action-alert/increase-diversity-without-violating-the-law&quot;>;自愿平权行动指南&lt;/a>;专门列出。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种数据驱动的方法不仅符合规定符合当前雇主指南，但它在确保 DEI 举措产生可衡量的影响方面也非常有效。具有社会意识的投资者、员工和客户希望雇主超越公开的承诺声明，采取具体行动来纠正组织、行业和社会中真正的不平等现象。收集种族数据以获取有关您的组织、行业甚至社会中不平等现象的信息，是您作为领导者可以采取的最有价值的 DEI 相关行动之一，并确保您在采取行动时，心中有明确的目标，有目的地工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据消除普遍障碍&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;对 DEI 举措的一个常见误解是这样的假设：如果发现种族差异，DEI 举措会通过给予边缘化群体来纠正这种差异。群体的优惠待遇——所谓的“反向歧视”。例如，一些管理者可能会认为，如果分析揭示了种族招聘歧视，DEI 举措将寻求以牺牲白人员工为代价来“为边缘化人群提供工作机会”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种粗暴和零和的做法不仅是公然非法的，而且还可能会损害白人员工的利益。这也与 DEI 工作的现实相去甚远。最有效的 DEI 计划使用种族数据来识别在工作场所损害公平和精英管理的歧视性障碍，并制定为每个人消除这些障碍的举措。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，如果使用种族数据的分析发现，由于缺乏标准的晋升流程和候选人的较高准入门槛，黑人、亚洲人、拉丁裔和土著经理候选人面临不成比例的障碍，那么 DEI 举措可能会与所有领导者合作制定标准化的晋升流程，培训领导者如何使用它以及如何消除偏见，并自动考虑所有员工在任职三年后晋升。这些举措还有一个额外的好处，那就是减少经理的偏袒、裙带关系和其他可能对任何背景的员工产生负面影响的不道德行为。大多数 DEI 举措都遵循这种模式：他们收集边缘群体的数据，以设计更适合每个人的工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据纠正歧视&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当雇主寻求&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/how-to-identify-and-fix-pay-inequality-at-your-company&quot;>;薪酬公平审计&lt;/a>;时，他们会了解不同背景的员工是否在同工同酬中得到公平的报酬。如果答案是否定的，那么负责任的雇主可能会主动向受影响的员工提供欠薪，以纠正不平等现象。额外的工资不会像零和游戏那样从未受影响的员工身上“拿走”；雇主提供的信息是为了把事情做对：做大蛋糕，而不是争夺蛋糕。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，如果雇主使用种族数据来确定白人经理正在获得更多的机会来承担具有挑战性的项目、建立人际网络并接受高级领导者的指导，那么除了消除普遍的机会障碍之外，他们可能会主动创造更多的机会，为边缘化群体的成员提供具有挑战性的项目、人际网络和指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以这种方式使用数据的令人惊讶的好处之一是它可以帮助您的员工了解 DEI 计划背后的基本原理。因为大多数人都认为工作场所本质上是公平的，或者是精英管理的，除非事实证明并非如此，所以 DEI 举措（例如，成立一个员工资源小组，主要针对拉丁裔员工进行活动规划）可能会遭到那些对优惠待遇感到焦虑的人的冷漠或强烈反对。通过将 DEI 工作建立在数据基础上（例如，通过分析显示与白人员工相比，拉丁裔员工相对缺乏社区、支持和归属感），您可以帮助您的员工了解 DEI 计划的重要性，并为您支持员工的承诺感到自豪。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据设计公平流程&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您不能使用个人的种族信息来让他们比其他候选人提高 30% 的分数。除了遵循上述指导方针的高度限制的自愿平权行动计划之外，您不能将 30% 的职位分配给边缘化种族群体的成员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;您可以规定招聘流程的每个阶段都由至少 30% 合格的有色人种候选人组成，然后再继续（这种做法称为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.diversitylab.com/pilot-projects/mansfield-overview/&quot;>;曼斯菲尔德规则&lt;/a>;，或&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclusocal.org/en/inclusion-targets-whats-legal&quot;>;包容附加条款&lt;/a>;）。虽然这些做法通常旨在纠正全行业的歧视或有限的劳动力资源，但没有一个候选人的被雇用几率高于或低于下一位候选人。雇主只需在继续之前花额外的时间有意扩大候选人库即可。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;类似的流程可以与其他消除偏见的做法结合起来，以进一步确保公平。例如，您可以明确表示任何自愿共享的种族数据都不会与个人的候选资格相关联。您甚至可能要求处理候选人库多样性种族数据的个人与做出就业决定的人分开工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据来展示 DEI 进展&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一些领导者可能出于值得称赞的最初理由而投资 DEI 举措和计划，因为他们“显然”需要支持劳动力。然而，当这些举措顺利进行时，这些领导者可能会不确定下一步该做什么。当形势好的时候，这些 DEI 举措被视为成功、以人为本的工作场所的标志。但是，当组织面临财务压力、面临业务挑战并且必须兼顾相互竞争的优先事项时，由于缺乏充分的理由，DEI 可能会使其成为&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/protecting-dei-progress-when-budgets-are-tight&quot;>;预算削减的首要目标&lt;/a>;。既无法证明 DEI 计划存在的基于证据的理由，也无法对 DEI 计划的有效性进行基于证据的评估的组织将永远无法将其 DEI 努力与短暂的趋势和时尚脱钩。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;使用显示种族差异或未满足需求的数据启动 DEI 计划的组织来说，种族数据可能是证明其持续存在合理性的最有力工具。如果您的&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/to-understand-whether-your-company-is-inclusive-map-how-your-employees-interact&quot;>;网络分析&lt;/a>;或&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultureamp.com/blog/employee-belonging&quot;>;归属调查&lt;/a>;量化了参与决策过程的种族差距，您可以使用这些发现作为设计新决策过程的基本原理，创建咨询委员会来通知领导者，以及依靠员工资源小组与有色人种员工分享有关他们的意见正在被征求的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过再次运行相同的分析并比较您收到的数据，您将能够对您的计划的成功或失败做出强有力的推论，并利用这些发现进一步改进您的 DEI 计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;要记住的原则&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;不要：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;恐慌，放弃您的 DEI努力，或出于毫无根据的恐惧而损害有效的举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;根据了解个人的种族或民族做出就业决定或为个人提供资源，而无需事先分析显示差异，也无需首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;向种族群体成员分配或保留一定比例的理想资源（例如，晋升、职位、任务），而无需事先分析显示差异，也无需首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;利用人们的种族数据来提高或降低他们的绩效在没有事先分析显示差异的情况下，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈的情况下，在任何决定中表达种族偏好、标准或限制。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;在没有事先分析显示差异的情况下，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈的情况下，表达对任何角色或职位的种族偏好、标准或限制。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;要做：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;使用种族数据为招聘工作提供信息并实现候选人库多样化（例如，通过使用曼斯菲尔德规则）。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;汇总种族数据以保留匿名性在不失去群体层面洞察力的情况下，利用种族数据来识别组织中的种族不平等和差异。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;引用种族数据来设计消除障碍和纠正歧视的 DEI 工作和举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;参考纵向种族数据来显示 DEI 进展，交流 DEI 计划的有效性，并庆祝您的胜利。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/to-drive-diversity-efforts-don t-tiptoe-around-your-legal-risk&quot;>;尽早与律师和法律专家合作&lt;/a>;，设计和沟通合法且有效的 DEI 计划。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;DEI 工作不会有任何进展，领导者也知道这一点：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bain.com/about/media-center/press-releases/2023/bain--company-study-shows-85-of-business-leaders-view-social-最近的一项调查显示，85% 的公司将社会问题视为“紧急”问题。员工和消费者仍然期望组织不仅承诺做得更好，而且&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/to-make-having-progress-on-dei-measure-outcomes&quot;>;实现可衡量的成果&lt;/a>;，以证明他们的言论并非空话。这样做需要基于证据的 DEI 工作——需要合法有效地收集和使用种族数据以及其他人口统计数据——成为这项工作的新标准。如果做得好，您将能够同时支撑您的法律风险，并加速您的组织过渡到您的选民期望从其 DEI 计划中获得更高的透明度、问责制和有效性标准。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这只是 DEI 的下一步发展，它以 1964 年《民权法案》为基础，在工作中争取更大的多样性、公平性和包容性，并得到了数十年的广泛支持。您的组织如何满足当前的需求将决定您如何适应 DEI 旅程的下一阶段。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: A Little Nature in the Office Boosts Morale and Productivity]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-a-little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_MaryHaasdykVooys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Mary Haasdyk Vooys 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more -caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;综述。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;“微观自然”研究&amp;#8212;将小型、经济实惠的自然元素融入工作场所——展示了其对员工绩效和福祉的积极影响。研究表明，在工作中接触大自然可以提高生产力、乐于助人和创造力，而且没有证据表明存在负面影响。建议包括真实的和人造的自然，延伸到办公环境之外，利用未充分利用的空间，并鼓励工作时间之外接触自然。工作场所融入自然可以提高整体业务绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a-little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=es&quot;>;学习西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a-little-nature- in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在金丝雀码头这个繁华的地区，许多全球企业的伦敦基地，开发商正在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.architectsjournal.co.uk/news/glenn-howells-and-eden-project-to-give-canary-wharf-a-green-revamp&quot;>;建设一个“绿色脊柱”&lt;/a>;很快就会蜿蜒穿过摩天大楼，让工人们在工作日可以随时进入绿色空间。在城镇另一边，正在建设中的 Google 英国总部，一座&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/6/1/15723642/google-london-office-pictures-headquarters-kings-cross&quot;>;300 米长的屋顶公园&lt;/a>;拥有 250 多棵树，为员工提供了远离办公室和城市环境的自然场所。 On the other side of the Atlantic, retailer LL Bean cut out the middle of one of their warehouses and turned the space into a courtyard, so that everyone &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90908239/ll-bean-new-headquarters&quot;>;at their new home office&lt;/a>; would have views of nature while working. These real-world examples of incorporating nature into commercial spaces are part of a growing trend to design places where employees can be immersed in nature during their workdays.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Increasing nature in the work environment certainly aligns with many companies&#39; sustainability initiatives. However, the motive also stems from nature&#39;s effect on humans — it is well established that nature makes us feel better. Our emotions, our thinking, our connection to others, and our physical well-being &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2017.0177&quot;>;are all enhanced by being in and around nature&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the connection between contact with nature and our well-being, large investments in bringing nature into the workplace raise some thorny issues. First, in a time of economic headwinds and cost-cutting, is there a business case for incorporating nature into employees&#39; surroundings? Second, what about those workplaces where it is not feasible or sensible to incorporate a green spine or a rooftop garden?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Answering these questions requires first understanding whether nature has effects on metrics that matter to organizations&#39; bottom lines (eg, employee satisfaction and performance) and if so whether less-extreme doses of nature are meaningful enough to elicit these gains. Thus, we set out to test the effects (if any) of what we call &lt;em>;micro-nature &lt;/em>;— small, affordable, seemingly innocuous ways of incorporating nature into the workplace — on how employees feel at work, and how they perform.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Research&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We measured or manipulated contact with nature at work in different ways across multiple studies, with workers in the US, Canada, China, New Zealand, and Indonesia. In experiments, working adults were simply shown images of workplaces suffused with natural elements or matching images without nature. We then asked them to imagine they worked in these spaces and report how it would make them feel and perform. We also conducted more complex studies in real-world work settings. For instance, we assessed employees&#39; actual contact with nature during a week at work (eg, working near plants, natural views, or the sound of running water), and then measured their feelings and objective job performance. Finally, in a field experiment in an accounting firm, we went into the offices at night and placed potted plants at some employees&#39; desks and similar pots, only filled with office supplies, at other desks. We then measured the attitudes and job performance of the two groups and compared them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The results were largely consistent across these studies: Experiencing even small doses of nature at work improved the way employees felt in ways that fueled &lt;a href=&quot;https://discovery.ucl.ac.uk/id/eprint/10166977/1/Tang%20et%20al%20final%20prepublished.pdf&quot;>;higher task performance, increased helping&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063231172182&quot;>;enhanced creativity&lt;/a>;. These findings indicate that incorporating micro-nature into work settings can contribute to worker well-being and performance in a meaningful way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also looked into whether there were differences between employees that shaped how nature affected them at work — factors such as how much individuals appreciate nature in general, and the extent to which they are drawn to novel experiences. Our findings showed that some people are especially prone to experiencing the benefits of nature. However, we found no evidence that any employees were negatively impacted by nature exposure at work; thus, micro-nature seems to hold considerable promise for employees with little downsides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bearing these findings in mind, we believe that nature should be accessible to as many employees as possible, not just those lucky enough to work below a green roof or alongside a park. Companies should provide employees with micro-nature experiences. Below, we offer suggestions for incorporating micro-nature into the workplace, while also encouraging managers to take liberties and get creative in their specific organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Capitalizing on Micro-Nature&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;Real is best, but artificial works too.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Giving employees opportunities to access “the real thing” is ideal when it comes to nature: indoor water features, windows with views of nature or that open to let in natural sounds like birdsong. But just because it&#39;s not the real thing does not mean that employees will not benefit from nature. Research shows that even depictions of nature, such as murals and artificial flowers, can give employees a natural boost.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Think beyond the office…&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It goes without saying that it is not just office workers who benefit from nature. Employees in settings where the work environment feels especially removed from nature — think warehousing or manufacturing — are especially likely to notice a dash of the outdoors brought inside and be positively impacted by it because of how different it is from their status quo.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;…and beyond the workplace.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The benefits of nature extend beyond employees&#39; work lives. Some of our research looked at the work-related benefits of spending time outdoors in the evening, after the workday. We found that employees &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063221106430&quot;>;were more productive the next day&lt;/a>; when they spent time outdoors the prior evening. Especially for hybrid and remote workers, the implications are clear: The benefits of being around nature at home carry over into work. So even incentivizing employees to take an evening walk can help them be more productive the next day.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Utilize unused or underused spaces.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;By definition, micro-nature is small, and can be as simple as painting a wall with natural tones, adding flowers to the break room, or landscaping the area outside employees&#39; windows. We encourage managers to keep an eye out for the unused or underused spaces around their workplace that can be easily and cheaply turned into natural features. For instance, adding more landscaping to an overly industrial parking lot may boost employees&#39; morale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Overall, our findings indicate that the benefits of connecting employees to nature at work extend beyond sustainability, and include positive effects on employees&#39; well-being and how they perform their jobs. As such, we view contact with nature as a valuable supplement to well-designed jobs that already include meaningful work, fair compensation, and respectful treatment. For firms that provide these things and are looking for more ways to enhance the environment in which their employees work, micro-nature offers considerable promise.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies Need to Prove They Can Be Trusted with Technology]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1282056839.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Hiroshi Watanabe/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Trust in technology &amp;#8212; and the companies that use it &amp;#8212; has taken a hit over the past few years. Transgressions against individuals&amp;#8217; privacy, calcification of corporate or individual biases into life-altering algorithms, constant threats that new tech erodes their ability to make a living, and beta testing unsecured or faulty connected devices or vehicles on an unsuspecting populace have encouraged healthy skepticism. To rebuild digital trust, companies need to pursue three broad goals: security and reliability, accountability and oversight, and inclusive, responsible, ethical use. Practically, this requires three steps: 1) define a vision for digital trust, 2) plan to act in more trustworthy ways, and 3) recruit people who will help earn trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Technological solutionism — the idea that tech developers can be trusted to innovate or code our way out of problems, and into prosperity — is on its way out. Individuals&#39; trust in tech and the companies who develop it has been eroded by innumerable failures. For businesses, it&#39;s no longer acceptable to use technology without taking steps to ensure it&#39;s trustworthy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regular people — and, increasingly, legislators and regulators — have reasonably been made skeptical by recent transgressions against individuals&#39; privacy, calcification of corporate or individual biases into life-altering algorithms, constant threats that new tech erodes their ability to make a living, and beta testing unsecured or faulty connected devices or vehicles on an unsuspecting populace. Looking at the near future, with generative AI and virtual worlds being implemented faster than we can track, the trust problem is only getting worse.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More tech isn&#39;t going to solve this problem. Customers are looking at the choices that company leaders make and assessing whether those choices match individual consumers and citizens&#39; values — and whether they put people first. And because every company uses some form of digital technology in its operations and relationships with customers and partners, every company needs to worry about digital trust. “Digital trust programs are a necessity, and when done right, can be both a differentiator and enabler for a business. As demands rise for companies to show they are trustworthy, organizations should strive to build a digital trust strategy that meets or exceeds their customers&#39; expectations, not just what&#39;s legally required,” according to Vikram Rao, Salesforce&#39;s Chief Trust Officer and a member of the World Economic Forum Digital Trust Steering Committee.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some companies may look at the problem and hope they can buy or hire their way out of it. In some cases, a new role, like a Chief Trust Officer or Chief Digital Trust Officer may help. But before CEOs and boards rush into creating a c-suite role as a panacea, they need to take a hard look at what exactly trustworthy technology looks like in the 21st century, how companies earn digital trust, and what changes and investments they need to make to do that.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What makes technology trustworthy?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;No technology is inherently trustworthy or untrustworthy. After all, technologies have no agency in themselves; instead, as a character in the Afrofuturist film &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://greatergood.berkeley.edu/article/item/twelve_new_films_that_highlight_the_best_in_humanity&quot;>;Neptune Frost&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; puts it, “technology is only a reflection of us.” Trust in technology is a reflection of the decisions people make when they develop the tech, use it, and implement it. While there are many ways to think about trust, when the World Economic Forum convened business, government, and civil society leaders in the field of trustworthy tech, the assembled group &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;reached this consensus&lt;/a>;: “Digital trust is individuals&#39; expectation that digital technologies and services — and the organizations providing them — will protect all stakeholders&#39; interests and uphold societal expectations and values.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this work, the Forum&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/community&quot;>;Digital Trust Community&lt;/a>; realized that the most important question to ask with regard to technology is not “how do you get people to trust technology?” Rather it&#39;s “what do we need to do — as technology developers, owners, and users — to respect people&#39;s values and expectations?” With the right mindset and the right goals, it&#39;s possible to develop an effective and trustworthy strategy for the use of digital technology. At its heart, such a trustworthy tech strategy comes from consideration for the individuals subjected to new technologies (regardless of the technology in question).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With respect for individual rights and expectations in mind, a trustworthy digital technology strategy should identify the right goals. The World Economic Forum&#39;s digital trust community offered three broad sets of goals:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Security and Reliability&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Accountability and Oversight, and&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Inclusive, Ethical, and Responsible Use&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As Julie Brill, Microsoft&#39;s Chief Privacy Officer and a member of the Forum&#39;s Digital Trust Steering Committee said at the time, “the goals of any developer of AI or other technologies should mirror the goals of the organizations and individuals who use or encounter that technology. Shared goals of inclusivity and responsible use, strong privacy and security protections, and effective oversight are the foundational elements to building a trustworthy relationship between developers, their customers, and individuals who use the technology.” Users and consumers can better rely on technologies that protect them, that include their needs and match their values, and that have good governance practices baked in, to remediate any inadvertent harms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do you invest in digital trust?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Earning digital trust isn&#39;t simple, and it can&#39;t be automated. Rather it requires a series of judgment calls, investments, and organizational changes that reflect the totality of a technology&#39;s likely impact on individuals. These shifts, encompassing the whole business, can only be orchestrated by company leaders. As Keith Enright, Chief Privacy Officer at Google and Digital Trust Steering Committee member, said, “decisions companies are making now about preparedness determine where they will be down the line in terms of trust.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Becoming prepared to start earning back trust requires CEOs and Boards of Directors to do at least three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Define a vision for digital trust&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Plan to act in more trustworthy ways&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Recruit people who will help earn trust&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The first investment leaders need to make is to take the time and energy to truly understand the impact of the technologies they create or deploy. Developing a realistic and comprehensive vision for how an organization uses technology in service of its goals and those of the people who rely on it determines how an organization will invest in digital trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders should approach decisions involving technology with a clear sense of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_World_Economic_Forum_Digital_Trust_Initiative_2023.pdf&quot;>;how those technologies reflect and impact core organizational values&lt;/a>; and the values of the society in which the business operates. Their vision for creating or adopting new technologies must consider both the benefits to the business and society alongside a clear and responsible assessment of the potential harms new technologies might impose on potential customers or other stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a business adopting generative AI must assess how the technology might increase efficiencies (a benefit to the business), unlock new solutions to pressing challenges (a benefit to society) while also developing a plan to prevent &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-the-risks-of-generative-ai&quot;>;expected harms&lt;/a>;, for example, to democratic processes from AI “hallucinations” or misinformation and to workers displaced by these advanced technologies. Only a vision that responsibly considers both the benefits and the risk of new technology can truly be considered trustworthy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After deciding on a vision that includes trustworthy goals, organizations need a plan to act for digital trust. This plan requires leaders to invest in the internal structures and teams that best support digital trust. For all applications of digital technology, the Forum&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/framework&quot;>;work&lt;/a>; identified eight dimensions where positive action can help achieve an organization&#39;s goals — both trust goals and overall financial or strategic goals. Those dimensions are cybersecurity, safety, transparency, interoperability, auditability, redressability, fairness and privacy. (As with the Digital Trust Goals, these dimensions are defined and explored in the Forum&#39;s Insight Report, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;&lt;em>;Earning Digital Trust: Decision-making for Trustworthy Technologies&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In most organizations, these areas likely fall to different departments and leaders, which means optimizing them requires an interdisciplinary approach — and possibly some structural change — in order to support the careful decision-making required to earn trust from users and other stakeholders. However, the realities of a given industry or company may mean it&#39;s not possible to maximize every one of the dimensions described. For example, greater transparency may not be possible for companies who work in highly-sensitive industries (eg, national security), so their accountability and security would have to supplement. Similarly, some dimensions of trustworthiness (perhaps most noticeably privacy) vary between jurisdictions and geographies. People&#39;s expectations and values are the litmus test for what makes technology trustworthy. Trust, itself, may be highly region and industry specific.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The third big initial investment is in the people who can help the business earn digital trust. Making technology trustworthy is a multi-faceted effort conducted on an organizational (or societal) scale — which means that ultimate responsibility for trustworthiness falls to the CEO. This general duty of trustworthy technology decision-making doesn&#39;t mean, however, that the business shouldn&#39;t invest in recruiting experts (maybe even on the c-suite), who can help establish the right strategy, and the right structures, to support digital trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This leader, possibly a Chief Trust Officer — but just as likely to be the Chief Privacy Officer, General Counsel, CISO, or another executive — must be both an expert in stakeholder management and a trusted counselor to the CEO and the board. Stakeholder management comes into play where companies already have cybersecurity, privacy, compliance, and even ethics functions. The leads for each of those roles has a stake in the overall trustworthiness of the digital strategy of a company — in both building it and benefiting from it. In order to be a counselor on digital trust, this individual must also be able to think systemically — bridging between these disciplines in order to help leaders make the best judgement call on how, where, and toward what ends new technologies should be applied.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In order to be most effective, an officer responsible for digital trust can&#39;t be an expert on every technology and every facet of trust, rather they have to be able to understand the strategy for the company and the values of affected individuals, workers, and customers. They support development of a trustworthy vision by conveying a system-wide picture of what the technology landscape looks like to CEOs and boards and helping build a strategy that supports trust rather than erodes it. They also help oversee the myriad and interdepending actions that, taken together, earn trust from users, partners, and other stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CEOs must understand that trust in the technology that underlies and enables virtually every business can&#39;t be bought, but by investing in the time it takes to make the right decisions, establish a trustworthy vision, and recruit effective supporters, it can be earned.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens After the U.S. Economy&rsquo;s Soft Landing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-u-s-economys-soft-landing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1427804800.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;baona/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A year ago, a recession was seen as a foregone conclusion &amp;#8212; and yet the Fed appears to have successfully lowered inflation without triggering a recession. Many of the negative forecasts followed a pattern of underestimating the US economy&amp;#8217;s resilience, typically because they were based on historical models and precedent, not situational and idiosyncratic context. While the soft landing may be progressing with promise, it won&amp;#8217;t be an end state &amp;#8212; a new disequilibrium will emerge. Leaders can&amp;#8217;t wait for macroeconomic certainty or stability. Instead, they must recognize that the macroeconomy will remain untamed by models &amp;#8212; and that what matters is judgment.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The US economy has defied the doomsayers once again. More than a year has passed since a recession was seen as a foregone conclusion and a “soft landing” pronounced near impossible. But today, the soft landing is well advanced, even if not complete: The Fed has found success in lowering inflation without triggering a recession. The labor market, the only reliable evidence that the economy is in recession, has cooled without pushing up the unemployment rate.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though this is welcome news, the protracted uncertainty surrounding the economy has confounded many leaders — and came at a cost for those who hunkered down prematurely in anticipation of recession. This uncertainty will persist. What comes after the soft landing (if in fact it can be completed)? To answer this question, we look at why the recession calls were wrong and what lies ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Recession Prophecies, Unfulfilled&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As in the pandemic, when doomsayers predicted a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.project-syndicate.org/commentary/coronavirus-greater-great-depression-by-nouriel-roubini-2020-03&quot;>;Greater Depression&lt;/a>;,” much negativity dominated public discourse of the last year and a half. Some leaders predicted a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/01/jamie-dimon-says-brace-yourself-for-an-economic-hurricane-caused-by-the-fed-and-ukraine-war.html&quot;>;hurricane&lt;/a>;” would hit the economy shortly; others &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@alex.domash/can-job-vacancies-fall-without-an-increase-in-unemployment-1031fe19c635&quot;>;dismissed even the possibility&lt;/a>; of a soft landing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But as the below graphic illustrates, that is exactly what has played out over the last 16 months. Job openings have come off their highs as firms feel under less strain, and quit rates have fallen as workers feel less enticed to jump ship — all while hiring (“payrolls”) continues at a robust pace. As the unemployment rate remains near its 60-year low there is no sign of recession.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360940&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230719_SZLEZAK_SOFT_LANDING_360.png&quot; >; &quot; title=&quot;US Labor Market&#39;s Progress Toward a Soft Landing.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1592&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;What went wrong, or, more appropriately, what went right?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of the negative forecasts followed a pattern of underestimating the US economy&#39;s resilience, typically because they were based on historical models and precedent – not situational and idiosyncratic context. Consider the following four displays of resilience:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Labor market resilience.&lt;/strong>; The widespread assumption was that monetary policy would push labor demand collectively under water. Instead we have seen pockets of weakness, covered by aggregate strength. Significant layoffs happened where hiring had overshot (eg, tech) but in other sectors (eg, services) hiring was still catching up and remained strong. Laid-off workers found new jobs. Resilience was found in the unusual economic diversification of recessionary sectors with booming ones.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Consumer resilience.&lt;/strong>; Growing layoffs, inflation eating away at household budgets, and falling portfolios weakening balance sheets led to predictions of a collapse in spending. But the context mattered. Balance sheets had buffers, including cash. And while individual budgets were squeezed, the total number of incomes continued to grow rapidly as hiring persisted, providing consumer strength. The aggregate downdraft has not happened.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Housing resilience.&lt;/strong>; A common fear has been that rising interest rates would kneecap the housing market — delaying construction activity, pushing down prices, or even, as some doomsayers predicted, causing another housing-centered recession. But these narratives overlooked the fact that activity remains precisely because &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/08/09/real-estate-housing-market-falling-prices-economic-risk/&quot;>;housing inventory is low&lt;/a>;. As a result, higher rates have tamped down — rather than choked — housing activity. Housing starts and prices dipped, and transactions fell, but they have stabilized and are rising again.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Financial system resilience.&lt;/strong>; Another common fear was that the Fed will hike until something breaks. The idea that the financial system would be the collateral damage of higher rates is not unreasonable as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/03/15/svb-collapse-financial-instability-fed-inflation-recession-finance-banks-economy-carlsson-szlezak-swartz/&quot;>;collapse of SVB demonstrated&lt;/a>;. But the risk of contagion was overestimated, while the ability of policy-makers to avert it was underestimated.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The better-than-expected outcomes share a pattern. Each concern had merit but was considered too narrowly. The idiosyncratic, contextual, and situational drivers mattered more than what historical relationships — and the models that are based on them — said about these sectors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lesson that cannot be learned often enough, it seems, is that trust in macroeconomic models remains too strong. The idiosyncrasies of the cycle call for judgment rather than precise forecasts. Meanwhile, the doomsaying is routinely amplified as the microphone is reliably passed to the gloomiest voices.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Path Ahead&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Economics often unhelpfully frames the economic cycle as “moving to equilibrium.” (The aviation analogy of a “soft landing” is similarly guilty.) In reality, we are always moving from one idiosyncratic disequilibrium to another, meaning &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/business-forecasts-are-reliably-wrong-yet-still-valuable&quot;>;executives cannot rely on forecasts&lt;/a>;. New idiosyncratic drivers will always deliver new situations that models won&#39;t readily pick up on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, what could the new disequilibrium be?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though the first stages of the soft landing are a success, ruling out a recession would be a mistake. It remains a possible, even plausible, outcome (and over time an inevitability). Monetary policy still has a foot on the brake. Real shocks can always end a cycle, particularly when growth is already slow and the economy thus more vulnerable, and financial stressors, such as bank failures, can pop up unexpectedly. Considering the &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/assessing-the-current-risks-to-the-us-economy&quot;>;three types of recession&lt;/a>; risk remains indispensable, but we still view recession risk in the near term as much lower than consensus.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A re-acceleration is more likely, as a resilient economy successfully weathers this period of weak (but non-recessionary) growth. Yet, such a re-acceleration could play out in different ways – some are welcome, others are not.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 1: A Re-run of the Overshooting Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If demand picks up strongly and outstrips the economy&#39;s capacity (think available labor, capital, and known processes), another bout of inflation is likely. This would necessitate a fresh round of monetary tightening with all the risks we discussed above.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even so, it would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; immediately point to an “inflation regime break” — the mistaken narrative of the last two years that the US economy was seeing a structural return of inflation. It would mean another bout of cyclical inflation that comes (and goes) with a mismatch of demand and supply.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 2: A Just-Right Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If demand grows in line with the economy&#39;s capacity, the expansion can plod along at acceptable growth rates without renewed inflation pressures. Monetary policy could ease from its very tight stance toward a more neutral stance — until a shift toward a new disequilibrium arises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 3: A Better-Than-Good Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We know this has arrived when the economy&#39;s capacity grows considerably faster than demand, facilitating rapid growth without concomitant cyclical inflation. While strong capital formation and strong labor participation can help facilitate this scenario to a degree, it&#39;s crux would be an acceleration of productivity growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Can this happen and is it likely?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many are eager to pencil in much higher growth courtesy of ChatGPT and other applications of AI — but not so fast. The mere availability of labor does not guarantee faster productivity growth; think of tech as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/08/the-secret-of-productivity-growth-is-not-technology/&quot;>;just the fuel&lt;/a>;. The &lt;em>;spark&lt;/em>; typically comes in the form of tight labor markets. When firms are forced to substitute capital for labor, they tend to do more of it. When they can&#39;t hire the next worker, they transform their processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such sustained labor market tightness and its benefits are a realistic prospect. Still, leaders should remain prudent about size and speed of such gains. Big productivity gains at the macroeconomic level come gradually, not abruptly, and their size is often overestimated — as we saw in the pandemic, when analysts rushed to pencil in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/10/how-to-be-realistic-about-covids-impact-on-productivity-growth/&quot;>;an extra 1 percentage point of growth&lt;/a>; that did not materialize.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The benefits of such a scenario would be broader than just somewhat higher growth. Tight labor markets create real wage growth across the income distribution, and the biggest winners tend to be at the bottom of the distribution. This creates opportunities for career advancement and job creation for those who have had fewer opportunities or struggled to get on the job ladder, and it pulls into the labor market those who may have otherwise exited.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While the soft landing may be progressing with promise, it won&#39;t be an end state — a new disequilibrium will emerge. Leaders can&#39;t wait for macroeconomic certainty or stability. Instead, they must recognize that the macroeconomy will remain untamed by models — and that what matters is judgment. Gloomy headlines will persist, and economic models will offer a flat view of the world that misses out on critical context. Leaders must apply the same skills they employ each day to lead their firms through uncertainty to navigating the macroeconomy. They must avoid both overreacting to the latest piece of data and preparing for only one unchanging view the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For firms, the &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/why-firms-are-struggling-with-the-us-economys-soft-landing&quot;>;challenges of a tight economy&lt;/a>;, including margin pressure, as well as higher, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/06/07/inflation-interest-rates-higher-but-healthy-bcg/&quot;>;healthy interest rates&lt;/a>;, are likely here to stay — but they are preferable to the alternative of recession. Meeting these challenges head on means more capital for labor substitution, more reinvention, and more technological absorption. Each of these form the foundation of the better-than-good economic scenario.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Using Sprints to Boost Your Sales Team&rsquo;s Performance]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_20_stk149282rke.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;George Doyle/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Over the last two decades, technology developers have utilized the agile methodology to work more effectively. As sales teams are stretched thin and face change initiatives and strategy shifts, using the sprints made popular by agile can help them focus on priorities that will drive results. At the heart of this is a cadence of structured, weekly meetings between the manager and the salesperson.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/using-sprints-to-boost-your-sales-teams-performance?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Fueled by a rapidly changing digital world, sales organizations are spending significant amounts of resources and energy on strategic initiatives. Whether these involve wholesale changes (eg, reorganizing the sales team or shifting to hybrid field-digital customer engagement) or less disruptive ones (eg, introducing new sales quotas or adopting new sales technologies), the primary roadblock to intended impact is the failure to achieve execution excellence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For sales teams, executing on new strategies can be quite difficult. Sales is a multifaceted job, with many choices of what to do at any moment. Demanding customers, sales managers, marketing managers, and digital nudges can push salespeople in inconsistent directions. They may choose to do tasks that are easier, such as calling on friendly accounts with modest upside, or focusing on small short-term wins rather than advancing larger longer-term opportunities. Further, salespeople can be reluctant to adopt new approaches that disrupt how they have engaged customers in the past. Results, especially with large deals, follow weeks and months after the actions salespeople take to drive those results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A solution that has helped many sales teams close execution gaps is sales sprints – time-boxed periods of one to two weeks bookended by a one-on-one meeting between the sales manager and salesperson (or account team). The idea is to break down strategies and goals into small, more manageable tasks to help sales teams stay focused and be accountable. Sales sprints have some obvious parallels to &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/05/embracing-agile&quot;>;agile sprints for technology development&lt;/a>; – both break down work into small segments and those involved meet frequently to monitor progress and adjust. But unlike agile sprints (which are used for projects with a beginning and an end), sales sprints are part of a regular management cadence for continually improving the processes of growing value for customers and driving sales.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales sprints sound straightforward, and they are. However, successful implementation takes work. To be effective, sales sprints must be embedded into the operating rhythm of an organization; they can&#39;t pile on more administrative duties for sales teams. Sprints work best when the effort is supported by a centralized digital platform that connects the approach to sales management programs including pipeline management, goal setting, coaching, and rewards.&amp;nbsp;Further, sales managers must collaborate with their peers across the organization to bring insights and experiences to each sprint conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Sales Sprints in Action&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The global steel and wire manufacturer Deacero has a vast product portfolio and longstanding customer relationships. To achieve aggressive growth targets, the company wanted to move beyond a transactional “inside-out” sales process in which its sales teams focused on getting orders for what was in inventory. Leaders recognized the need for a new market-focused “outside-in” sales strategy that would rely on anticipating market trends, and proactively prioritizing accounts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deacero launched “Win the Week,” a program of sales sprints to gradually introduce new capabilities (eg, key account management, solution selling) and activities (eg, account prioritization and planning). The goal was to ensure salesperson focus on individual customer opportunities and needs. After a short training session, sales managers started using sprints to guide their salespeople to define and complete a set of customer advances to increase pipeline value.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In each weekly 50-minute 1:1 meeting, usually on a Friday, the manager and salesperson discussed three questions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What happened?&lt;/strong>; For example, how did the planned actions play out last week? How did we do on pipeline progress and key result areas? What did we learn about customers and the market?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What&#39;s next? &lt;/strong>;For example, which prospects and customers should we focus on next week? What actions should we take? What offers and value do we need to communicate? What customer advances or progress should we seek?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How can the manager help?&lt;/strong>; For example, what could the manager do to support next week&#39;s planned efforts? What support is needed from the rest of the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Sales managers used sprint conversations to help their salespeople break down larger, more complex sales strategies (eg, increase product portfolio sales) into smaller, more manageable, opportunity-specific customer activities (eg, in vertical market A, sell solution B, to account C, by meeting with decision maker D, and leveraging value proposition E). Managers ensured that weekly schedules centered around spending a greater portion of time with accounts that demonstrated the highest growth potential. Planning conversations focused on how Deacero&#39;s full suite of products could best meet the needs of key accounts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The success of sprints with the sales team encouraged Deacero to use sprints with more teams and across organizational levels. Sales, marketing, and manufacturing executive teams began working together in bi-monthly sprint meetings to align the business towards specific market opportunities. Sales executives then worked with sales managers to break down quarterly forecasts into salesperson-based key performance indicators.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deacero supported the sprints with a leading CRM platform. The mindset and processes of the organization transformed to produce what the market needed, rather than to sell what was produced.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Results were stellar – with increased focus on customer advances, sales reps sold an average of 8% more product categories to each account. Within the first six months in the new organization, sales reps exceeded sales goals previously thought unachievable, resulting in a 16% revenue increase.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why Sales Sprints Are Effective&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Here is what salespeople and sales managers say about how sales sprints drive results.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Move from strategy to execution:&lt;/strong>; “Our quarterly plans before were like checking the box. I never looked at them after I had developed them … Sprints make the plans dynamic and actionable.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Collaborate across the business:&lt;/strong>; “I&#39;ve never had this type of conversation. Marketing and sales brainstorm together to generate ideas that move the needle.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Link insights to actions:&lt;/strong>; “The past approach was too general and not relevant. Sprints help us stay informed on the market and focused on priority actions that help us achieve our sales goals.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Focus on the customer:&lt;/strong>; “The weekly game planning for specific customer decision makers helps me focus on what is important in each conversation. Things don&#39;t fall through the cracks.”&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As companies across industries such as manufacturing, technology, health care, and professional services seek to drive growth in a fast-changing digital world, they are leveraging sales sprints to connect their ever-changing strategies to execution. Further, these organizations are accelerating the success of their sprints by supporting them with cross-functional collaboration, incentive compensation plans aligned with growth strategies, and CRM dashboards that help identify sales pipeline gaps. Sales sprints are helping organizations keep strategy and execution in synch, and in turn, drive value for customers to “win&#39;” each week, quarter, and year.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make Generative AI Greener]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_AlexWilliam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Alex William&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Generative AI is impressive, but the hidden environmental costs and impact of these models are often overlooked. Companies can take eight steps to make these systems greener: Use existing large generative models, don&amp;#8217;t generate your own; fine-tune train existing models; use energy-conserving computational methods; use a large model only when it offers significant value; be discerning about when you use generative AI; evaluate the energy sources of your cloud provider or data center; re-use models and resources; include AI activity in your carbon monitoring.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-make-generative-ai-greener?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While observers have marveled at the abilities of new generative AI tools such as ChatGPT, BERT, LaMDA, GPT-3, DALL-E-2, MidJourney, and Stable Diffusion, the hidden environmental costs and impact of these models are often overlooked. The development and use of these systems have been hugely energy intensive and maintaining their physical infrastructure entails power consumption. Right now, these tools are just beginning to gain mainstream traction, but it&#39;s reasonable to think that these costs are poised to grow — and dramatically so — in the near future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The data center industry, which refers to a physical facility designed to store and manage information and communications technology systems, is responsible for 2–3% of global greenhouse gas (GHG) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;emissions&lt;/a>;. The volume of data across the world doubles in size &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivery.io/blog/big-data-statistics-how-much-data-is-there-in-the-world/&quot;>;every two years&lt;/a>;. The data center servers that store this ever-expanding sea of information require huge amounts of energy and water (directly for cooling, and indirectly for generating non-renewable electricity) to operate computer servers, equipment, and cooling systems. These systems account for around &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;7% of Denmark&#39;s&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www1.villanova.edu/university/engineering/faculty-research/Energy-Smart-Electronic-Systems/Datacenter-efficiency-challenges.html&quot;>;2.8% of the United States&#39;&lt;/a>; electricity use.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Almost all of the best-known generative AI models are generated by “hyperscale” (very large) cloud providers with thousands of servers that produce major carbon footprints; in particular, these models run on graphics processing unit (GPU) chips. These require 10–15 times the energy a traditional CPU needs because a GPU uses more transistors in the arithmetic logic units. Currently, the three main hyperscale cloud providers are Amazon AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If we try to understand the environmental impact of ChatGPT through the lens of carbon footprint, we should understand the carbon footprint lifecycle of machine learning (ML) models first. That&#39;s the key to beginning to make generative AI greener through lower energy consumption.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Determines the Carbon Footprint of Generative AI Models?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;All large generative models are not alike in terms of their energy use and carbon emissions. When determining the carbon footprint of an ML model, there are three distinct values to consider:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint from training the model&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint from running inference (inferring or predicting outcomes using new input data, such as a prompt) with the ML model once it has been deployed, and&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;the carbon footprint required to produce all of the needed computing hardware and cloud data center capabilities.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Models with more parameters and training data generally consume more energy and generate more carbon. GPT-3, the “parent” model of ChatGPT, is at or near the top of the generative models in size. It has 175 billion model parameters and was trained on over 500 billion words of text. According to one &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.blog/2023-04-07-what-developers-need-to-know-about-generative-ai/&quot;>;research article&lt;/a>;, the recent class of generative AI models requires a ten to a hundred-fold increase in computing power to train models over the previous generation, depending on which model is involved. Thus overall demand is doubling about every six months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Training models are the most energy-intensive components of generative AI. &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3442188.3445922&quot;>;Researchers&lt;/a>; have argued that training a “single&amp;nbsp;large&amp;nbsp;language deep learning model” such as OpenAI&#39;s GPT-4 or Google&#39;s PaLM is estimated to use&amp;nbsp;around 300&amp;nbsp;tons&amp;nbsp;of CO2 — for comparison, the average person is responsible for creating &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/the-world-s-top-1-of-emitters-produce-over-1000-times-more-co2-than-the-bottom-1&quot;>;around 5 tons&lt;/a>; of CO2 a year, though the average North American generates &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/the-world-s-top-1-of-emitters-produce-over-1000-times-more-co2-than-the-bottom-1&quot;>;several times that amount&lt;/a>;. Other &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1906.02243&quot;>;researchers&lt;/a>; calculated that training a medium-sized generative AI model using a technique called “neural architecture search” used electricity and energy consumption equivalent to 626,000 tons of CO2 emissions — or the same as CO2 emissions as driving five average American cars through their lifetimes. Training a single BERT model (a large language model developed by Google) from scratch would require the same energy and carbon footprint as a commercial trans-Atlantic flight.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Inference, or using the models to get responses to user prompts, uses less energy each session, but eventually involves many more sessions. Sometimes these models are only trained once, and then deployed to the cloud and used by millions of users for inference. In that case, deploying large deep-learning models to the cloud for inference purposes also consumes a lot of energy.&amp;nbsp;Analysts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2019/05/09/google-cloud-doubles-down-on-nvidia-gpus-for-inference/?sh=7aa7fce46792&quot;>;report&lt;/a>; that NVIDIA estimates that 80–90% of the energy cost of neural networks lies in ongoing inference processing after a model has been trained.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to initial training and inference usage of energy by large generative models, users and resellers of these models are increasingly employing &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data&quot;>;fine-tuning or prompt-based training&lt;/a>;. When combined with the original generative model trained on large volumes of data, fine-tuning allows prompts and answers that are tailored to an organization&#39;s specific content. Some &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2205.01541.pdf&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; suggests that fine-tuning training consumes considerably less energy and computing power than initial training. However, if many organizations adopt fine-tune approaches and do it often, the overall energy consumption could be quite high.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although it is difficult to calculate the cost of manufacturing the computers needed to run all this AI software, there is reason to believe that it is very high. One &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.networkworld.com/article/2229029/computer-factories-eat-way-more-energy-than-running-the-devices-they-build.html&quot;>;2011 study&lt;/a>; estimated that 70% of the energy used by a typical laptop computer is incurred during its manufacture, and that desktop computers are even higher. It is likely that the complex and powerful GPU chips and servers used to run AI models are much higher than laptops and desktops.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Make AI Greener&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given all that, there is a movement to make AI modelling, deployment, and usage more environmentally sustainable. Its goal is to replace power-hungry approaches with more suitable and environmentally-conscious replacements. Change is needed from both vendors and users to make AI algorithms green so that their utility can be widely deployed without harm to the environment. Generative models in particular, given their high energy consumption, need to become greener before they become more pervasive. We know of several different ways in which AI and generative AI can move in this direction, which we describe below.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use existing large generative models, don&#39;t generate your own. &lt;/strong>;There are already many providers of large language and image models, and there will be more. Creating and training them requires enormous amounts of energy. There is little need for companies other than large vendors or cloud providers to generate their own large models from scratch. They already have access to the needed training data and massive volumes of computing capability in the cloud, so they don&#39;t need to acquire it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Fine-tune train existing models. &lt;/strong>;If a company wants a generative model trained on its own content, it shouldn&#39;t start from scratch to train a model but rather refine an existing model. Fine-tuning and prompt training on specific content domains consume much less energy than training new large models from scratch. It can also provide more value to many businesses than generically-trained models. This should be the primary focus for companies wishing to adopt generative models for their own content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use energy-conserving computational methods.&lt;/strong>; Another approach to reducing generative AI energy consumption is to use less computationally expensive approaches such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tinyml.org/&quot;>;TinyML&lt;/a>; to process the data. The TinyML framework allows users to run ML models on small, low-powered edge devices like microcontrollers with low bandwidth requirements (no need to send the data to the server for processing). While general CPUs consume an average of 70 watts of power and GPUs consume 400 watts of power, a tiny microcontroller consumes just a few hundred microwatts — a thousand times less power — to process the data locally without sending it to data servers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Use a large model only when it offers significant value.&lt;/strong>; It is important for data scientists and developers to know where the model provides value. If the usage of a 3x more power-hungry system increases the accuracy of a model by just 1–3% then it is not worth the extra energy consumption. More broadly, machine learning and artificial intelligence are not always required to solve a problem. Developers need to first do research and analysis of multiple alternative solutions and select an approach according to the findings. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://montrealethics.ai/publications/&quot;>;Montreal AI Ethics Institute&lt;/a>;, for example, is actively working on this problem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Be discerning about when you use generative AI. &lt;/strong>;Machine learning and NLP tools are revolutionary for medical-related health problems and prediction. They are great for predicting natural hazards such as tsunamis, earthquakes, etc. These are useful applications, but tools just for generating blog posts or creating amusing stories may not be the best use for these computation-heavy tools. They may be depleting the earth&#39;s health more than they are helping its people. If a company is employing generative AI for content creation, it should try to ensure that the models are used only when necessary or to reduce other computing costs, which should also reduce their overall computing budgets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate the energy sources of your cloud provider or data center. &lt;/strong>;AI (and software in general) carbon intensity can be minimized by deploying models in regions that are able to use environmentally friendly power resources and are carbon friendly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlco2.github.io/impact/#publish&quot;>;This practice&lt;/a>; has shown a 75% reduction in operational emissions. For example, a model trained and operating in the US may use energy from fossil fuels, but the same model can be run in Quebec where the primary energy source is hydroelectric. &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/sustainability/clean-energy-projects-begin-to-power-google-data-centers&quot;>;Google&lt;/a>; has recently started to build a $735 million clean energy data center in Quebec and plans to shift to 24/7 carbon-free energy by 2030. It also offers a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://services.google.com/fh/files/misc/active_assist_sustainability_spotlight.pdf&quot;>;Carbon Sense Suite&lt;/a>;” to help companies reduce energy consumption in their cloud workloads. Users of cloud providers can monitor the companies&#39; announcements about when and how they have deployed carbon-neutral or zero-carbon energy sources.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Re-use models and resources&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;.&lt;/strong>; Just like other materials, tech can be reused. Open-source models can be used rather than training new ones. Recycling can lower the impact of carbon-producing AI practices. Raw materials can be extracted to make newer generations of the latest laptops, processors, hard drives, and much more.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; Include AI activity in your carbon monitoring.&lt;/strong>; Carbon monitoring practices need to be adopted by all research labs, AI vendors, and AI-using firms to know what is their carbon footprint. They also need to publicize their footprint numbers in order for their customers to make intelligent decisions about doing AI-related business with them. The calculation of GHG emissions is dependent on the data sets of the data suppliers and processing firms such as research labs and AI-based service providers such as OpenAI. From the inception of the ideas to the infrastructure that will be utilized to gain research results, all need to be following green AI approaches. There are several packages and online tools available like &lt;a href=&quot;https://codecarbon.io/&quot;>;CodeCarbon&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.green-algorithms.org/&quot;>;Green algorithms&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlco2.github.io/impact/#compute&quot;>;ML CO2 Impact&lt;/a>;, which can be included in your code at runtime to estimate your emissions and we should encourage the developer community to consider these performance metrics to establish benchmarks and to evaluate ML models.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there are many considerations involved with the use of generative AI models by organizations and individuals: ethical, legal, and even philosophical and psychological. Ecological concerns, however, are worthy of being added to the mix. We can debate the long-term future implications of these technologies for humanity, but such considerations will be moot if we don&#39;t have a habitable planet to debate them on.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Protecting Your Workforce from Extreme Heat]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_20_1484622360.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies have more than one reason to be worried about soaring global temperatures and heat waves. The health risks to employees range from exhaustion, cramps, worsening mental health, diabetic complications, and even stroke. In addition, extreme heat is projected to cause the loss of more than $4 trillion annually in productivity by 2030. The author, a physician who advises corporate leaders, recommends six best practices to help employers safeguard their people and their business.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/protecting-your-workforce-from-extreme-heat?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Temperatures are soaring, records are being &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/whats-causing-this-record-breaking-heat/&quot;>;shattered&lt;/a>; and it can feel as if there is no relief in sight. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2023/07/13/heatwave-california-arizona-florida-texas-records/&quot;>;coast-to-coast heat domes&lt;/a>; to eponymous heatwaves like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-66183069&quot;>;Cerberus&lt;/a>;, extreme heat events may be the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/10/climate/climate-change-extreme-weather.html&quot;>;new norm&lt;/a>;. And companies have more than one reason to be worried.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://assets.website-files.com/5df9172583d7eec04960799a/618872a58d35f2643cbcaef2_BX9770_ESG_Critical%20industries%20have%20substantial%20exposure_7Nov2021.pdf&quot;>;2021 Moody&#39;s report&lt;/a>; identified heat stress as a physical risk that impacts almost every sector. Beyond rising &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/heat-waves-can-create-stormy-economic-weather-n894311&quot;>;cooling costs&lt;/a>; and shifting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/13/business/disney-world-universal-orlando-attendance-down/index.html&quot;>;consumer demand&lt;/a>;, heat stress represents a major threat to companies because of its effects on human health. Heat waves can cause exhaustion, cramps, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/news-room/news-releases/extreme-heat-contributes-to-worsening-mental-healt#:~:text=Extreme%20heat%20has%20been%20associated,with%20an%20increase%20in%20suicide.&quot;>;worsening mental health&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/diabetes/library/features/manage-diabetes-heat.html&quot;>;diabetic complications&lt;/a>;, and even stroke. There is considerable risk in any population, and this includes your company&#39;s workforce.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to direct health costs of heat waves, the World Health Organization cites one of the most important economic impacts as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789240057906&quot;>;lost productivity&lt;/a>;. Two percent of total working hours are projected to be lost each year due to heat stress at work, representing more than $&lt;a href=&quot;https://futureearth.org/publications/issue-briefs-2/heatwaves/&quot;>;4 trillion annually&lt;/a>; by 2030. So when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/weather/2023/07/13/heatwave-california-arizona-florida-texas-records/&quot;>;100 million Americans&lt;/a>; are under a heat alert, that could mean up to one in three employees – or more, depending on your company&#39;s geography — are at risk at a given time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Keeping your cool when extreme heat hits your workforce isn&#39;t easy, but insights from health care can help. As a physician working for an international organization advising corporate leaders, I&#39;m seeing employers looking to deepen their understanding of heat stress to adopt new best practices that safeguard their people &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; their business. Here are six actions to consider in navigating this challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Take a preventative approach.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Employers should start by educating employees on what heat stress is, how it affects their health and safety, and how it can be prevented.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In any warm environment, the human body relies on its ability to get rid of excess heat to maintain a healthy internal body temperature. This happens naturally through sweating and increased blood flow to the skin. If this doesn&#39;t happen quickly enough, body temperature rises and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ehs.research.uiowa.edu/occupational/heat-stress&quot;>;heat stress&lt;/a>; can occur.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Workers may experience symptoms including thirst, irritability, &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22440-heat-rashprickly-heat#:~:text=A%20heat%20rash%20is%20an,in%20hot%20and%20humid%20climates.&quot;>;heat rash&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21480-heat-exhaustion#:~:text=Heat%20exhaustion%20happens%20when%20your,resting%20in%20a%20cool%20place.&quot;>;heat exhaustion&lt;/a>;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21812-heatstroke#:~:text=A%20note%20from%20Cleveland%20Clinic,loss%20of%20consciousness%2C%20among%20others.&quot;>;heat stroke&lt;/a>; which includes brain dysfunction such as slurred speech, confusion, disorientation or even coma. Heat stress can also impair &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facilities.udel.edu/safety/5224/&quot;>;fine motor s&lt;/a>;kills, such as typing, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1518/001872007X230226&quot;>;reduces capacity&lt;/a>; to process task-relevant information.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During heat waves, workers may experience a combination of two kinds of heat-related illness: “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC164365/&quot;>;exertional heat illness&lt;/a>;” due to physical activity and “&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/582911&quot;>;environmental heat illness&lt;/a>;” due to ambient conditions like heat and humidity. The latter is especially common in &lt;a href=&quot;https://climatekids.nasa.gov/heat-islands/#:~:text=An%20urban%20heat%20island%20occurs,environment%20absorb%20and%20hold%20heat.&quot;>;urban heat islands&lt;/a>; where temperatures in a city are much warmer than nearby rural areas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ultimately, heat stress can lead to illness, hospitalization, and even death. Given the potential severity, upstream solutions are critical. An effective heat-related illness prevention program should be incorporated in your organization&#39;s broader health and safety program and align with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/safety-management&quot;>;Occupational Safety and Health Administration&#39;s&lt;/a>; (OSHA) recommended practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During the first few days in a heat wave, employers should encourage workers to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/UserFiles/works/pdfs/2017-126.pdf&quot;>;hydrate&lt;/a>;, take frequent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/UserFiles/works/pdfs/2017-127.pdf&quot;>;breaks&lt;/a>;, and quickly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/osha3154.pdf&quot;>;identify&lt;/a>; any heat-related symptoms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Know how hot is too hot — and for whom.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Workplace heat exposure involves a combination of factors. To determine if heat stress is too high, employers need to assess the:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Environment (including conditions such as humidity, sunlight, and airflow)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Job (for example, whether it involves physical activity or protective gear)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Worker (assessing common individual risk factors, such as age, pre-existing health conditions, and lifestyle)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The most accurate way to measure environmental heat impact on body temperature is with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.popsci.com/environment/wet-bulb-globe-temperature/&quot;>;wet bulb globe temperature&lt;/a>; (WBGT) meter, which incorporates temperature, humidity, sunlight, and air movement into a single measurement. OSHA provides &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/hazards#environmentalheat&quot;>;guidance&lt;/a>; for use and interpretation of results. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weather.gov/ama/heatindex#:~:text=The%20heat%20index%2C%20also%20known,combined%20with%20the%20air%20temperature.&quot;>;heat index&lt;/a>; focused on temperature and humidity alone can provide &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25616731/&quot;>;helpful surrogate data&lt;/a>; in certain circumstances.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Job-related physical activity can be estimated using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/hazards#metabolicheat&quot;>;metabolic heat and workload tables&lt;/a>; with workload classified from light (eg, sitting or standing) to very heavy (eg, intense activity). Employers should also be aware of whether workers&#39; clothing increases risk and recognize jobs in hot environments such as firefighting, farming, construction work, mining, and factory work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Individual worker factors can also indicate unique risks whereby different employees react to heat in different ways. This includes vulnerable populations, such as those who are 65 years of age or older, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/repro/heat.html&quot;>;pregnant&lt;/a>;, have certain types of heart disease, high blood pressure, obesity, diabetes or use certain &lt;a href=&quot;https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-heat-and-how-it-affects-medication/&quot;>;medications&lt;/a>;. Gender differences are important to consider as well. The National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) reports &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccohs.ca/oshanswers/phys_agents/heat/heat_health.html#:~:text=The%20National%20Institute%20for%20Occupational,less%20heat%20tolerant%20than%20men.&quot;>;several studies&lt;/a>; showing women are less heat tolerant than men.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Maximize indoor thermal comfort.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccohs.ca/oshanswers/phys_agents/thermal_comfort.html&quot;>;Thermal comfort&lt;/a>; for office work is important for well-being and productivity. Too warm, and employees feel &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/288297978_Effects_of_thermal_discomfort_on_performance_of_office_work_and_physiological_behaviours&quot;>;fatigue or experience mood disturbance&lt;/a>;. Too cold, and attention can &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23443576/&quot;>;drift&lt;/a>; with employees feeling restless or distracted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Maintain consistent thermal conditions in the office environment. Even minor deviation may cause stress and affect performance and safety. Workers already under stress are less tolerant of uncomfortable conditions, so temperature becomes particularly important for high-demand jobs and during periods of high-stress crisis response.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Optimize temperature to match recommended guidelines. The American Society of Heating, Refrigerating, and Air Conditioning Engineers (ASHRAE) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/indoorenv/hvac.html&quot;>;Standard&lt;/a>; recommends temperature ranges of 68.5°F to 75°F in the winter, and 75°F to 80.5°F in the summer. The difference in seasonal temperature ranges is largely due to clothing selection.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some situations, legislation may have specific requirements and it is important for employers to meet these. Beyond federal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/heat-exposure/standards&quot;>;OSHA standards&lt;/a>;, some states have adopted OSHA-approved &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/stateplans/&quot;>;state plans&lt;/a>; that cover hazards not otherwise addressed. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mn.gov/admin/assets/heat_stress_guide_tcm36-207189.pdf&quot;>;Minnesota&lt;/a>; regulates indoor air temperatures in places of employment and varies requirements based on intensity level of work. Similarly, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.opb.org/article/2022/05/11/oregon-heat-wildfire-smoke-farmwork-laborer-rules/&quot;>;Oregon&lt;/a>; recently adopted some of America&#39;s most protective heat rules for workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recommended temperature ranges meet the needs of at least &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ashrae.org/File%20Library/Conferences/Specialty%20Conferences/2018%20Building%20Performance%20Analysis%20Conference%20and%20SimBuild/Papers/C036.pdf&quot;>;80% of individuals&lt;/a>; but some employees may feel uncomfortable even if these values are met. Temperature needs and preferences vary greatly, and there is no one temperature that can satisfy everyone. Additional measures may be required.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Difference in thermal comfort may be due to indoor climate regulations being based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://cris.maastrichtuniversity.nl/en/publications/energy-consumption-in-buildings-and-female-thermal-demand&quot;>;standard values in men&lt;/a>; and can impact women&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2019/05/26/727108363/how-office-temperature-affects-cognitive-performance&quot;>;cognitive performance&lt;/a>;. In general, women prefer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0360132306000242&quot;>;higher ambient temperature&lt;/a>; at home and in the workplace. That being said, when it comes to heat waves, women are generally &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935122013135&quot;>;more vulnerable&lt;/a>; to high temperatures. And this vulnerability increases after menopause when &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26674572/&quot;>;lack of estrogen production&lt;/a>; makes it more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935122013135&quot;>;difficult to adapt&lt;/a>; to sudden temperature increases.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given thermal comfort is determined by a number of factors beyond temperature, such as activity levels, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/engineering/solar-gain#:~:text=Solar%20gain%20(or%20solar%20heat,results%20from%20absorbed%20solar%20radiation.&quot;>;solar gain&lt;/a>;, and air flow, optimizing for those can help. For example, enhance access to desk fans or working areas of greater air flow for menopausal women experiencing hot flashes. Other options to make the workplace more comfortable include changes to workload and schedules. For example, scheduling work during off-peak temperature hours or shorter shifts with frequent rest breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Tailor training and safety for outdoor workers.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Provide a heat stress training program before hot outdoor work begins. Training may include proper use of heat-protective clothing and equipment, effects of drugs and alcohol on heat stress tolerance, immediate reporting of signs or symptoms of heat-related illness (in oneself or coworkers), and procedures for responding to these symptoms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Supervisors should be provided with additional training. This may include monitoring alert reports, responding to hot weather advisories, procedures to follow when a worker has signs or symptoms of heat-related illness (including contacting emergency medical services where appropriate), encouraging hydration, and reinforcing rest breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond training, employers should reduce workplace heat stress using engineering and administrative controls. Engineering controls include changes to work-setting design that reduce exposure to heat, such as the use of reflective or heat-absorbing shielding. Administrative controls are changes to tasks or schedules that reduce heat stress, for example, limiting time in the heat, increasing recovery time in cool shaded areas, increasing the number of workers per task, or providing adequate cool, potable water. It is also important to limit heat burden while wearing personal protective equipment (PPE) and to explore auxiliary cooling systems, like water-cooled garments or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6997718/&quot;>;cooling vests&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Additional strategies include creating a multi-disciplinary working group (eg, cohort of workers, qualified health care provider, safety manager), instituting medical and self-monitoring programs, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7374462/&quot;>;wearable monitors&lt;/a>; to estimate workload (eg, heart rate sensors), and a buddy system where workers observe each other for signs of heat-related illness.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Practice acclimatization.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Individuals can adapt to higher temperatures through repeated exposures, for example, via increased sweating efficiency. This is particularly relevant for outdoor workers during rapid onset heat waves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers should develop acclimatization schedules in hot conditions that gradually increase worker exposure time and physical demands. This is typically done in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/mining/userfiles/works/pdfs/2017-124.pdf&quot;>;step-wise process&lt;/a>; over a seven to 14 day period. New workers will need more time to acclimatize than those with pre-existing exposure, and absence for a week or more may require re-acclimatization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The level of adaptation for each worker is relative to physical fitness and heat stress experienced. It is also important to consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33205218/&quot;>;gender differences&lt;/a>;, as women require greater intensity, frequency, and duration of heat exposure for adaptation. Given related literature primarily focuses on males, current guidelines may not account for physiological differences and may require employers to explore &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10289939/&quot;>;new frameworks&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6. Adopt a long-term heat-health action plan&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As extreme heat continues to worsen, employers must adopt a long-term approach. The World Health Organization&#39;s guidance for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789289071918&quot;>;heat-health action plans&lt;/a>; offers particularly useful principles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similar to how airlines track weather for flight planning, employers should tap into accurate and timely temperature alert systems that trigger weather-related warnings, determine thresholds for action, and communicate risks. &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalnews.ca/news/8738567/summer-air-travel-heat-wave-impact/&quot;>;Establishing links&lt;/a>; with local public health systems and emergency response services also helps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You should also have a communication plan that includes what to communicate, to whom, and when. Recognize that you may be managing multiple environmental health issues simultaneously — for example, extreme heat and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires&quot;>;air quality issues&lt;/a>; related to wildfires — and be sure to streamline messaging. Avoid overwhelming employees with multiple non-synchronized communications. Also tailor your messaging for local areas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your heat-health action plan should also include short and medium-term heat relief approaches, such as reduction in indoor heat exposure, enhanced outdoor worker protections, and a care strategy for vulnerable populations. Your long-term approach should include strategic urban planning to address &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90653389/how-an-ancient-design-technique-could-help-us-survive-extreme-heat-no-ac-needed&quot;>;building design&lt;/a>;, location, and transit access points that can reduce heat exposure for employees in their end-to-end journey from home to work and back.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Track efficacy of your heat-health strategy over time. Implement real-time surveillance and evaluation particularly for outdoor workers, and don&#39;t forget oversight of indoor environment controls. Monitor for quality and consistency to make sure you are meeting ASHRAE recommendations and local legislation requirements. Engaging safety checklists and standard best practices found in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://airlines.iata.org/2014/12/08/severe-weather-warning&quot;>;airline industry&lt;/a>; can be especially helpful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Extreme heat can greatly impair the performance and health of your greatest assets — your people. As these high temperatures become more commonplace, employers must seize the opportunity to protect their employees today and into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: How to Effectively Market Green Products]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1173369992.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Richard Drury/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A study, involving Edelman and nine major brands, finds that despite corporate hesitations, sustainable products are growing twice as fast as conventional ones, appealing across all demographics. Brands should ensure that product quality is not compromised while promoting sustainability. Combining sustainability claims with core brand attributes can broaden consumer appeal. Effective sustainability messages prioritize the personal and community benefits, while technical or scientific claims are less compelling unless tied to consumer benefits. Sustainably-marketed goods are consistently growing across demographics, indicating that compelling sustainability claims can boost customer engagement and business growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-how-to-effectively-market-green-products?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In these polarized times, corporate leaders are growing skittish about promoting sustainability in their products. Yet &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/csb-sustainable-market-share-index&quot;>;our research&lt;/a>; on actual consumer purchases demonstrates that sustainable products are growing two times faster than conventional, at a 28% premium in average, across most demographics.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help brand managers and marketing leads capitalize on this growing market, we partnered with Edelman and nine leading brands across different industries (tech, apparel, beverage, food) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/research-initiatives/effective-sustainability-communications-best-practice-guide-brands-marketers&quot;>;to research which sustainability messages work best with consumers.&lt;/a>; In contrast to current hyperbole about polarized consumers, we found that the most resonant sustainability claims are highly compelling for &lt;em>;all&lt;/em>; demographics — old/young, blue state/ red state, high income/low income, men/women, etc.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We conducted a custom online study of a sample of the US general population in end 2022/early 2023 for the nine iconic brands. Respondents for each brand were asked to evaluate 30–35 different claims (including a mix of category and environmental sustainability claims) to gauge their overall appeal. Rather than using a traditional rating scale, we utilized a user-friendly and robust analytical approach called MaxDiff. It forces a top and bottom pick from a short list of claims in each choice set, making the respondent task easier, and providing better discrimination in responses across the claims. Each respondent evaluated multiple choice sets, allowing for claims to be randomized based on an experimental design. The MaxDiff results yielded an appeal score for each claim — in aggregate and among key sub-groups of interest. Most importantly we added a TURF component to identify the optimal combination of claims to maximize overall appeal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Following are the insights and lessons learned.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Core category claims are paramount — the product must work, be tasty, clean properly, etc. This makes sense. Who wants sustainable chocolate that does not taste good or a sustainable cleaning product that does not clean? Yet, occasionally, marketing materials focus solely on sustainability which can limit a brand&#39;s potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Compelling sustainability claims anchored in the core brand attributes significantly expand brand reach by bringing in new consumers. As seen in Figure 1, the core attribute claim may resonate with 44 of every 100 people (average among nine brands tested), but when you add compelling sustainability claims you can increase customer appeal to 74 in every 100 people. An example of a high-performing, laddered claim is: “Formulated with sustainable ingredients that are good for your skin.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;High-resonance sustainability claims focus on what is in it for the consumer, starting with themselves and their families and then moving to their communities. For instance:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Healthy for you and your family: “&lt;em>;Grown without harmful ingredients synthetic pesticides, herbicides, or fungicides” &lt;/em>;for food, and “&lt;em>;Formulated without harmful ingredients parabens, phthalates, dyes and aluminum” &lt;/em>;for skincare&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Saves you money: &lt;em>;“Lower energy for lower monthly energy bills,” &lt;/em>;or&lt;em>; “Helps reduce waste and save money.&lt;/em>;” For non-CPG items, messaging can stress durability and access to repair services.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Protects our children: “&lt;em>;For future generations.&lt;/em>;”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Helps local farmers: “&lt;em>;Working with local farmers to use regenerative farming practices to help conserve nature, encourage biodiversity, and improve soil health.&lt;/em>;” Claims that only talked about regenerative practices without connecting the claims to local farmers did not resonate.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Protects animals: &lt;em>;“Not tested on animals.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Sustainably sourced: “&lt;em>;Sourced from 100% sustainable ingredients/materials.&lt;/em>;”&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Lower performing claims included science-based claims, traceability, packaging-based claims, and certifications. In other words, the consumer is less interested in technical topics than in personal concerns. However, if the reason for the consumer to care was added to science-based claims they performed better (eg, carbon neutral for cleaner air to breath vs. carbon neutral). Certifications, while not highly resonate by themselves, are important to ensure the brand protects against green-washing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In summary, effective sustainability marketing, though to a certain degree category specific, has a top 10 set of components that are compelling for all demographics. Marketing leaders can use the following guidance to develop messaging (and also review the full report). It should be stressed that sustainability marketing needs to be tied to real and effective sustainable sourcing and production practices. To move forward:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Prioritize the communication of your brand benefit first and foremost.&lt;/strong>; Leverage the relevant sustainability messaging to strengthen the brand positioning.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Link the sustainability claim to the category reason-for-being.&lt;/strong>; “100% sustainably farmed for a great tasting product.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Focus the claim on the benefit to the consumer and their families.&lt;/strong>; Consider sustainability claims that ensure the products are safe for human consumption or contact such as “made without chemicals harmful to human health.” Articulate the claim with an emotional component, particularly as it relates to the long term health of the planet or their children, such as “good for your children/future generations,” or “good for the planet.” To the extent possible, provide a personal monetary benefit to the claim, such as “longer life,” “less waste,” “lower energy bills.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;The term sustainable, as it relates to “sustainable sourcing and production” is compelling&lt;/strong>; and does not need further explanation. Eg, “100% sustainably sourced,” “100% sustainably produced.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Consumers are concerned about animal welfare&lt;/strong>;. If appropriate, include communication to ensure that no harm is done to animals in the testing of the product, such as “no animal testing” or “cruelty-free.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;For food and personal care categories, if possible&lt;strong>;, tie the claims to farmers and local sourcing,&lt;/strong>; such as “sourced from local farmers.” Regenerative agriculture claims are compelling, for example, when focused on local farmers and their farms. Eg, “Partnering with local farmers to ensure the long-term health of the farm for the future of our food systems.” or “Partnering with local farmers to ensure the farms stay climate resilient, nutrient dense.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Provide a reason to care when communicating the more scientific aspects of sustainability&lt;/strong>;. “Carbon neutral to reduce the impact of climate change” vs. “carbon neutral” by itself.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Quantify sustainability claims for greater resonance&lt;/strong>;, such as&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; “Using 1 million tons of ocean-recovered plastic bottles.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Use certifications to guard against greenwashing, but don&#39;t rely on them as the sole point of information.&lt;/strong>; For example, “100% sustainably sourced and certified by the Rainforest Alliance” works better than just putting the label on pack.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Deliver the product with fully recyclable packaging&lt;/strong>;. While consumers generally were less responsive to sustainable packaging claims, “made from 100% recycled plastic/cardboard” was the most compelling.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We are convinced that compelling sustainability claims will help businesses grow consumer loyalty and market share. In another research initiative with Circana (which collects consumer purchasing data), we have reviewed purchases of consumer packaged goods in the US on an annual basis since 2019 (when we looked back to 2014). In reviewing 36 categories annually (several hundred thousand products), we have observed consistent conversion of conventional products into sustainable ones. For example, in 2019, nine out of 36 categories were over 20% market share in terms of sustainability-marketed products and 14 categories were under 5%. Today 13 categories are over 20% and 9 categories are under 5%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And, while purchasing skews younger, wealthier, urban, and more educated, in fact we see significant purchasing across all demographics. Sustainability-marketed milk and yogurt, for example, which have more than 60% market share, are purchased by virtually every demographic at that rate, including rural, high school education or less, seniors and lower-income (despite an approximate 30% premium).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sustainable production of goods is beneficial for the planet, for consumers and for business. Corporate leaders can take heart from this research and invest in authentic and compelling messaging to engage customers, grow market share and make a positive contribution to society.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[20 Questions to Ask When Your Team&rsquo;s Vibe Is Off]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1347421073.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Has your team lost sight of its purpose and the goals you&amp;#8217;re working toward together? If so, it might be time for a team reset that focuses on realignment. Or, maybe your team just doesn&amp;#8217;t feel like a team anymore? Maybe team members feel disconnected, invalidated, or frustrated, and even minor issues are creating friction? In that case, your reset must focus on revitalizing your team dynamic. This article focuses on some approaches that managers can use to address alignment gaps to jump-start a new, healthier, happier team dynamic.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/20-questions-to-ask-when-your-teams-vibe-is-off?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Is your team feeling stuck, stymied, or just a bit stale? Have you fallen into routines that are no longer serving you? It&#39;s okay; teams need occasional course corrections, even in calm waters. And in today&#39;s stormy seas, you might need to chart a whole new course as we navigate return-to-office and hybrid work arrangements. The good news is that resetting your team can be easier than you think.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your first step is to reflect on what feels off. You can think about it in two broad categories. First, is the problem that your team has lost sight of your purpose and the goals you&#39;re working toward? If so, your reset will need to focus on realignment. The other possibility (and it could be both) is that you don&#39;t feel like a team anymore. Maybe team members feel disconnected, invalidated, or frustrated — so much so that even minor issues are creating friction. In that case, your reset must focus on revitalizing your team dynamic. Here&#39;s how to navigate both of these approaches:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Realignment&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You&#39;ll want to prioritize realignment over revitalization for two reasons. First, many team dysfunctions manifest as trust issues when, in fact, they stem from discrepancies in goals, priorities, or expectations. Clearing up those misunderstandings often resolves what you thought were interpersonal issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another reason to start with realignment is that it allows you to tie your reset to external shifts rather than individual behavior problems, making it less likely to trigger defensiveness. When you realign, you&#39;re not judging anyone; instead, you&#39;re asking how you need to evolve to capitalize on opportunities and mitigate emerging risks. Here are some anchor points for realignment. Choose the ones that best match your situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team&#39;s mandate.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The first possibility is that your team&#39;s purpose needs to evolve. You can explore that possibility with these questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What external trends require us to adapt?&lt;/strong>; What are the most salient changes in the external environment, and how do they change the context for your team? For example, if you&#39;re a content marketing team, how does ChatGPT change your team&#39;s value?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How does a shift in company strategy affect your role?&lt;/strong>; Does your organization have a new vision, strategy, or KPI that alters what your team needs to deliver? For example, if you&#39;re an HR team, does opening European offices require new capabilities or activities?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How is your value within the organization evolving?&lt;/strong>; As organizations grow and change, the role of teams can evolve. How will changes in your organization structure require you to refocus? For example, how will you tailor your offerings if you&#39;re an R&amp;amp;D team now supporting two units instead of one?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team&#39;s goals.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If your mandate has changed, you&#39;ll certainly need to revisit your goals, but even if your purpose is unchanged, your goals might need a refresh. So, consider these as reasons to move the target.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How will you build on prior results?&lt;/strong>; What did you accomplish in the last quarter, and how does that change the trajectory you want for the next few quarters? If you&#39;ve been achieving your goals, are they ambitious enough? On the other hand, if you&#39;ve been missing consistently, do you need to lower your goals or risk demoralizing everyone?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How will external factors affect your goals? &lt;/strong>;Is there anything external that might suggest a goal change? For example, do you need to temper expectations in light of an economic downturn, supply chain backlogs, or labor shortages? On the other hand, if your team benefits from new technological advances, could you accomplish more than planned?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What can you do to improve your measures?&lt;/strong>; Are your goals fuzzy, or are your metrics nebulous? Your fastest way to improve alignment might be to tighten your definitions or tweak your metrics, making it more evident whether you&#39;re getting traction.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your strategies and tactics.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Any changes based on your mandate or goals will necessitate reexamining your strategies. But don&#39;t limit a strategy refresh to situations where the targets have moved; considering new possibilities can be a good reset anytime.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Are your strategies aligned with your mandate?&lt;/strong>; If your mandate or goals have shifted, how must your strategy change in response? For example, if your team has been tasked with adding professional services to your software offering, what will it take to make that business model successful?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Where do you need revised tactics?&lt;/strong>; If you&#39;re still working toward existing goals, what&#39;s been working, and where could you change your tack? Conversely, what do you need to abandon? Where could you double down?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What contingencies might emerge?&lt;/strong>; Even if you&#39;re sticking with your existing mandate, goals, strategies, and tactics, you can reset by considering new scenarios and preparing your contingency plans. What assumptions are embedded in your current plan? What would negate those assumptions? What would be the leading indicators that something is changing?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your roles.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s possible that your team is on the right track but that you&#39;re not optimizing the energy and talents of team members. In that case, consider these questions about individuals&#39; accountabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Do people need a change in role?&lt;/strong>; Are there any changes in roles or responsibilities that would make the people in your team more effective? Do you need to change someone&#39;s portfolio? Could you shake up who&#39;s in what role for multi-skilling, development, or succession advantages? Who might be reinvigorated by a new challenge?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you make accountabilities more straightforward?&lt;/strong>; Are there opportunities to fine-tune people&#39;s responsibilities to make them more compelling? Are there spots where shared accountabilities are diluting people&#39;s sense of obligation? How could you increase alignment, efficiency, and effectiveness by clarifying who owns which decisions?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;One of the most constructive ways to reset your team is to refocus on what your organization, colleagues, and customers are counting on you to do. Rekindling your team&#39;s passion and reminding them what you&#39;re fighting for is the best place to start.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Revitalization&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second type of reset is to revitalize your team dynamic. Does it feel like you&#39;ve devolved from being a true team into a loose collection of people where the whole is no more than the sum of the parts? Or worse, is mistrust or unhealthy conflict making it feel like teamwork is a net negative? In that case, your reset might need to focus less on &lt;em>;what&lt;/em>; your team needs to do and more on &lt;em>;how&lt;/em>; you do it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your communication habits.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Over time, teams can become lazy and fall into communication patterns that dilute connection. Revisiting your communication habits can help you reconnect.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Can you reset your communication channels?&lt;/strong>; Do you default to certain modes of communication that aren&#39;t optimized for the content? For example, if you&#39;re using Zoom to inform and email to debate, you&#39;ve got it backward. Can you use richer communication vehicles for more novel content, contentious discussions, and unfamiliar participants? Can you shunt informational items to email?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What warrants synchronous communication?&lt;/strong>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/hybrid-tanked-work-life-balance-heres-how-microsoft-is-trying-to-fix-it&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that the average person has more than double the hours of meetings than before the pandemic. Which types of information could you share asynchronously instead to allow people more control over their schedules?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you implement blackout periods?&lt;/strong>; In addition to the deluge of meetings, most people are also inundated by a torrent of emails. How could your team enforce blackout periods where people can turn off notifications and work without communication obligations? How can you increase the opportunities for people to work &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/to-control-your-life-control-what-you-pay-attention-to&quot;>;without distractions&lt;/a>;?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your meetings.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you optimize your standing meetings?&lt;/strong>; Meetings tend to be more effective when they have homogeneous content. Could you clean up your &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/04/a-step-by-step-guide-to-structuring-better-meetings&quot;>;meeting structure&lt;/a>; to separate content that requires different mindsets and behaviors?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Does the participant list need to change?&lt;/strong>; One way to reset the conversation is to change who&#39;s party to it. Is it time to step out of some meetings and let your team take the reins? Would new voices and new perspectives bring some &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/01/if-your-team-agrees-on-everything-working-together-is-pointless&quot;>;productive conflict&lt;/a>;?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Do you need to prepare better?&lt;/strong>; Inefficient meetings are infuriating meetings. How could you use &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/how-to-create-the-perfect-meeting-agenda&quot;>;better primer documents&lt;/a>; to prepare team members to contribute in evidence-based and thoughtful ways?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Reset your team dynamics.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What would be your new ground rules?&lt;/strong>; Maybe you&#39;ve had &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/write-down-your-teams-unwritten-rules&quot;>;ground rules&lt;/a>; and stopped respecting them, or you never had any. What behaviors have you been tolerating that need to stop? What would be a welcome addition? Revisiting the principles for how team members behave can be an excellent way to reset.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;How could you resolve conflict debts?&lt;/strong>; If your team has been avoiding difficult conversations about priorities and trade-offs or trust and disrespect, you need to get the issues out in the open to move beyond them.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;What activities would foster insight into each other?&lt;/strong>; If your team dynamics are suffering, you might want to enlist outside help with formal team development activities. For example, psychometric tools or group coaching could foster trust and promote candor.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;If your team is accomplishing plenty but finding it&#39;s harder than necessary, these different approaches will jump-start a new, healthier, happier team dynamic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And finally, a personal note. While you ponder your team reset, it&#39;s an excellent time to consider whether you need to reset your own approach. For example, has work started consuming more time and energy than is healthy? Are you taking on too much and delegating too little? This is also the perfect opportunity to consider &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;what reset you need as the team&#39;s leader&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Taking a Vacation Improves Your Well-Being]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_1393555725.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Javier Zayas Photography/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Making sure your employees regularly take time off is key to creating a more sustainable workplace. Research shows that taking time off benefits employees in three ways: 1) Mentally. Taking a vacation provides greater opportunity for rest and better sleep (both quantity and quality), which can help unclutter your mind to boost creativity. 2) Body. Relaxing on vacation can reduce the levels of your stress hormones and allow your immune system to recover, making you less prone to get sick. 3) Soul. While it sounds hokey, answers to life&amp;#8217;s big questions &amp;#8212; like &amp;#8220;What do I really want?&amp;#8221; or &amp;#8220;What&amp;#8217;s most important to me?&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; are more likely to come to us when there is some space and stillness.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;fJZdvvhLBXBnM0awCRi2N9HHNyNCvzzf/ZLTeqiPe9l6izIl1hjxZtNoQ9yiC+8U&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5iAHwuINYiqwQMPfwPWVfV9MxEM9MBqao9YfMEZCzGrw==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;07&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; >; &lt;p>;We all know that taking vacation is good for you, but it&#39;s less clear that both employers and employees understand exactly just &lt;em>;how good&lt;/em>; it is for you, given that every year more than half of Americans give up paid time off. According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ustravel.org/toolkit/time-and-vacation-usage&quot;>;US Travel Association&lt;/a>;, in 2018, this amounted to 768 million days of unused vacation time, with more than 30% of it forfeited completely. Add to this, the fact that over &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;50% of managers&lt;/a>; feel burned out, taking vacation (and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/set-these-5-boundaries-before-you-go-on-vacation?ab=HP-latest-text-3&quot;>;actually unplugging&lt;/a>;) has never been more important.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>