<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Why Customers Leave Platforms &mdash; and How to Retain Them]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/why-customers-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Aug23_30_663665217.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司经常误解用户离开平台的问题。去中介化表明您的客户认为您没有像您想象的那样增加价值。陷入去中介化困境的公司可以采取简单的措施来止血，以免为时已晚——如果他们了解到底发生了什么。他们应该考虑六个因素：紧迫性、佣金、风险、技能、频率和模块化。去中介化的解决方案非常简单：创造比你获取的更多的价值。停止扮演收费看门人的角色，开始扮演增值合作伙伴的角色。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/08/why-customers-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why- customer-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;平台公司（支持两方之间交易的企业）不断努力阻止这些合作伙伴不得将交易移出平台。这种情况的技术术语是“脱中介化”，其例子包括读者在网上而不是从书店购买、Upwork 和 ZBJ（中国的猪八戒）程序员直接与客户签订合同，以及 Airbnb 不仅与房客直接与房东签订合同，而且还与房客直接签订合同。还与一些最大的专业主机&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-stock-falls-after-short-report-says-hosts-directly-compete-with-platform-173546532 .html&quot;>;据报道在新平台上与之竞争&lt;/a>;。去中介化——以及未能理解和解决它——扼杀了博德斯图书、百视达电影和塔尔唱片等曾经繁荣的企业。很容易理解为什么平台公司如此担心被排除在循环之外。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但事情是这样的：真正的脱媒很少见。大多数买家和卖家不会完全消除中间商，而是寻找新的提供商来降低交易成本或增加更多价值，因此转换是一个自然的选择。读者从亚马逊购买，而不是直接从作者那里购买。电影观众和歌曲听众不会从好莱坞工作室或音乐家那里购买音乐，而是从 Netflix 和 Spotify 购买音乐。简而言之，这些不是多对多交互的原子市场。新的吸引力中心（亚马逊、Netflix 和 Spotify）已经重新中介化了旧的吸引力中心（Borders、Blockbuster 和 Tower）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;问题在于公司经常误解这个问题：去中介化是一个迹象：您的客户认为您没有像您想象的那样增加价值。仅仅因为您启用了第一笔交易，并不意味着您有权从第二笔、第三笔以及后续交易中获取所有价值。然而，好消息是，那些似乎正在与脱媒作斗争的公司可以在为时已晚之前采取简单的措施来止血——如果他们了解到底发生了什么。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;预测脱媒&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;公司如何知道交易何时具有粘性以及何时会转移到其他地方？至少有六个因素会导致合作伙伴从您的平台上取消交易。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，紧迫性反映了现在解决问题的需要，这有助于保留交易。与高质量但不可用的单一平台外资源相比，在紧急情况下能够快速满足需求的大型平台更有价值。例如，配送应用 Drizzly 为聚会提供按需酒精饮料。去酒类商店可能花费较少，但需要提前计划或有人在聚会中退出。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;佣金&lt;/em>;是平台为促成交易而收取的费用。该费用越高，合作伙伴就越想避免这种情况。 Groupon 的佣金接近 50% &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholars.cityu.edu.hk/en/publications/how-users-drive-value-in-twoside-markets(94885ed2-0e38-40e4-9388-35008ffcc834 ).html&quot;>;导致其股票价值暴跌和稳定&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;风险&lt;/em>;是交易失败的危险。如果一个项目有风险，那么买家和供应商都更愿意受益于平台提供的声誉系统、保险和调解服务。 Uber 承担司机费用，并让乘客在车内呕吐时承担责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;技能&lt;/em>;是执行任务所需的专业知识水平。对于低技能工作，主要问题通常是价格，大量供应商可以帮助客户获得最好的交易。这意味着平台可以为首次交易和后续交易提供最佳价值，例如电子贸易。但当一项工作需要高技能时，平台通常只会为第一笔交易增加价值，而声誉系统的好处才真正重要。之后，买家一旦找到可靠的供应商，就可以省去把关人的麻烦。例如，Rocket Lawyer 将人们与专家律师联系起来，帮助解决法律问题。但一旦有人找到了可靠的律师，他们就不再需要这个平台了。而且，他们不想再次解释自己的情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;后续交易会强调相关因素，&lt;em>;互动频率&lt;/em>;，或者合作伙伴必须多久沟通一次才能完成任务，以及&lt;em>;项目模块化&lt;/em>;，或者将任务划分为更小、独立组件的程度。如果一项任务需要重复沟通或者可以轻松分解为单独的部分，则买家和卖家有多种机会&lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4150094&quot;>;建立独立于平台的关系&lt;/a>;。例如，在 Upwork 上，通过网站部署的各个阶段（规范、设计、编码、后端、测试等），各方有机会减少每个阶段的佣金。然后后面的阶段可以在平台外进行。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-363193&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230728_VAN_ALSTYNE_DISINTERMEDIATION_FACTORS_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和数据中的更多 HBR 图表。视觉效果&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;从广义上讲，这六个因素告诉公司如何降低&lt;em>;搜索&lt;/em>;成本，与达成交易相关的&lt;em>;谈判&lt;/em>;、&lt;em>;风险&lt;/em>;或&lt;em>;交付&lt;/em>;与制作作品本身不同。从经济学角度来说，这些被称为“交易成本”。该平台的作用是与下一个最佳替代方案相比降低它们。了解这一原则可以让高管控制结果，即使表面属性发生变化。平台帮助协调交易，但供应商实际上产生结果，如果买方和供应商能够在没有平台的情况下更有效地处理交易成本，那么他们将使交易脱媒。有趣的是，阿里巴巴首席战略官甚至将成功平台的测试定义为实现“最低交易成本的联系”。以这种方式理解非中介化，就会为您提供防止非中介化的工具。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;防止非中介化&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;非中介化的解决方案非常简单：创造比您获取的更多的价值。停止扮演收费看门人的角色，开始扮演增值合作伙伴的角色。要么降低交易成本，要么增加买家或供应商的价值，或者两者兼而有之。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;每个平台交互都有生产者方和消费者方。无论活动是一次骑行、一条推文、一次停留、一项产品、一项服务还是一件艺术品，都是如此。诀窍是为双方设计适当的胡萝卜加大棒，并重点强调胡萝卜。为什么胡萝卜比大棒更好？胡萝卜&lt;em>;增加价值&lt;/em>;，以保持平台内的互动，而大棒&lt;em>;增加成本&lt;/em>;，以实现平台外的互动。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-desiredby =&quot;caption-attachment-363192&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230728_VAN_ALSTYNE_DISINTERMEDIATION_CARROTS_STICKS_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr. org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;在 Data &amp;amp; 中查看更多 HBR 图表。视觉效果&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;许多平台选择大棒是因为它们更容易实施，或者因为他们觉得有权获得一定水平的利润。然而，大棒不会在客户、服务提供商、自由职业者或开发人员之间产生善意。它们包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;隐藏供应商联系信息以防止直接沟通。多年来，Angies List（现为 Angi）隐藏了家庭服务提供商的联系信息，这限制了互动和发展。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;向提出脱媒建议的买家和供应商支付奖金。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>; li>;提出此类建议以测试合作伙伴忠诚度的秘密购物者和秘密卖家。当自由职业者不想与大额佣金分享时，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=53948&quot;>;ZBJ&lt;/a>;同时使用赏金和秘密购物者平台。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;去平台化、公开羞辱，并最终采取法律行动，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/24/business/apple-epic-games-appeal .html&quot;>;当《堡垒之夜》试图使用自己的系统来促进支付时，苹果就尝试过&lt;/a>;，而不是使用苹果的系统，并征收 30% 的过高税款。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;胡萝卜要好得多，因为它们表现出对创造价值的承诺，这是获取价值的唯一真正基础。它们包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;为用户提供软件工具来增强产品或服务的生产、交付、质量或消费。 Instagram 和 Vimeo 提供的滤镜和图像编辑工具不仅可以降低生产者的成本，还可以帮助他们为消费者创造价值。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;此策略的一个变体是提供增值服务。自由平台Upwork将通过划分大型合同并将组件外包给不同的分包商来为大型合同提供项目管理。 99Designs 是一个设计竞赛平台，可帮助设计师自动化计费、跟踪进度并缴纳税款。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;频繁买家或频繁卖家奖励。 OpenTable 为买家提供用餐积分，他们可以在餐厅用餐，而 CoachUp 则为专业教练提供批量折扣。 Etsy 通过展示艺术家的作品来奖励艺术家的忠诚度。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将货币化转变为平台能够增加最大价值的点。 ZBJ引入了一种可选的定价模式，从交易费转变为订阅费。一旦支付了第一笔交易的费用，供应商每笔新交易的成本就为零。当平台的进一步使用是免费的时，卖家更喜欢平台上自动跟踪和计费的好处。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;保险，这对卖家和买家来说都是最成功的好处之一。在卖方方面，爱彼迎为房东提供火灾、盗窃和财产损失保险。在买家方面，亚马逊提供免费退货和退款保证。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;基本安全。优步推出了大多数出租车不提供的乘客紧急帮助按钮。当自由职业合同基于小时费率时，Upwork 提供了监控软件，以便客户知道程序员正在编码而不是仔细阅读 Facebook。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;引入买家和卖家评级系统。几乎每个主要平台现在都使用某种形式的审查来减少寻找不良提供商的逆向选择以及即使支付了费用但他们可能无法交付的道德风险。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;具有讽刺意味的是，这些策略确实伴随着挑战——“脱媒困境”。旨在增加价值的策略可能会无意中导致泄漏。当策略&lt;em>;确实&lt;/em>;增加价值但仅对第一次交互而不是第二次交互时，就会发生这种情况。考虑对家庭清洁工或园艺师进行五星级评级。一旦建立了联系并建立了信任，一个不再增加任何价值的平台将被取消中介。这个问题&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/01/why-some-platforms-thrive-and-others-dont&quot;>;注定了 Homejoy 在推出后的几年内&lt;/a>;。同样，Groupon 通过为买家提供团购折扣和为商家提供发现来增加首次销售的价值。但随后交易在商家的平台外完成，其“漏桶”对后续交易几乎没有增加任何价值。买家只需拜访商家即可。相比之下，Groupon 的中国继任者美团通过该平台处理配送，频繁产生买家奖励，并帮助商家设计新产品和选址新店。增加交易量会增加收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;去中介化是一个信号。它真正告诉你的是，你在初次比赛后没有提供足够的价值。你拿的比你应得的多。去中介化仅仅意味着其他人提供的价值比你多。相反，如果您创造的价值多于您获取的价值，您就会吸引而不是排斥交易。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Arrange Your Meeting Schedule to Boost Your Energy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_29_1464685906.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/iStock/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;大多数会议建议都集中在如何提高会议效率或如何减少会议数量。但是如何将会议与其他工作任务一起安排以最好地管理您的生产力呢？新的研究探讨了这个问题，发现许多人在安排日程时犯了两个关键错误：在同一天堆放太多会议，或者将紧张的会议与其他紧张的任务配对。这两种策略实际上都会削弱你白天充电和补充能量的能力，这可能不利于你的工作。相反，本文提供了如何平衡工作和会议的新技巧，并建议您在计划一天时可以问自己的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;会议仍然是大多数知识工作者面临的常见挑战。虽然常见的建议和先前的研究通常侧重于提高会议效率或减少我们在会议上花费的时间，但还有一个很少被考虑到的关键方面：我们每天安排和安排会议的方式。然而，日程安排可以帮助或阻碍我们在工作中的精力和生产力，因此需要仔细研究。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2023-61289 -001&quot;>;我们的研究&lt;/a>;，我们调查了知识工作者日常会议安排的影响，包括某些策略如何看似聪明，但实际上可能会无意中耗尽我们自己的精力。让我们考虑两个例子。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taylor 是一位领导初级分析师团队的高级数据专家，他注意到周四的日历上有两次会议 - 一次与供应商联络，另一次与其他部门的高级专家举行。然后他意识到他还需要安排一些与初级分析师的会面。他应该在周四与现有的两次会议一起挤出这些额外的会议，还是应该将它们安排在周五？他很想把会议安排在周四，这样他就可以节省时间并保持周五的日程安排“干净”，以便专注于项目报告中自己的部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在另一种情况下，敏利是一位经验丰富的人软件工程师兼开发团队经理本周将面临两次即将召开的会议。周二，她计划向战略委员会召开一次重要会议，该会议可能会影响预算。第二天，她的任务是为新实习生进行入职培训——这是一项熟悉且相对容易的职责。除了这些会议之外，敏莉还必须解决她自己在两个项目上的技术工作：一个遇到了一些严峻的挑战，另一个几乎完成了，只需要一些最后的润色。她应该在周二处理困难的项目并在周三处理较容易的项目，还是扭转计划？敏莉倾向于第一种选择。通过在周二解决会议和个人工作中最艰巨的挑战，她预计本周剩余时间的压力会减轻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taylor 和 Minli 的方法很常见：压缩会议日程以节省时间，或者在同一天将重要会议与紧张的个人任务配对，以尽快完成它们。然而，我们的研究结果表明，这些策略有其自身的缺点，特别是考虑到它们对工作日精力的影响时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们进行了两项研究，跟踪了 400 多名全职知识分子的日常工作活动工人，一些来自科技公司，另一些来自涉及脑力工作的不同行业。在整个工作周中，我们在每个工作日的中间和结束时对员工进行调查，了解他们上午和下午的会议、个人任务和其他活动，以及每个半天结束时的精力水平。此外，我们还从他们的主管那里了解了他们的工作绩效，包括任务绩效和创造力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们有两个重要发现。首先，影响知识员工精力的并不是他们花在会议上的时间总量，而是会议时间与他们花在个人任务上的时间的相对比例。我们发现，在某一天，知识工作者花在与个人任务相关的会议上的时间越多，他们用于恢复精力的小型休息活动（例如短途散步、随意交谈、简短有趣的阅读）就越少在那一天。这种对于定期补充能量至关重要的休息活动的缺乏，会损害他们工作日的精力。精力受损反过来会对知识型员工的任务绩效、创造力和工作满意度产生负面影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，我们发现，如果结构合理，会议和个人任务可以创造出我们想要的东西。称之为工作日的“压力互补效应”。两种互补的配置——高压个人任务伴随低压会议，或者相反，低压个人任务伴随高压会议——可以有益于一个人的能量。例如，有一天，当一位数据专家轻松完成日常文书工作时，她可能会发现一场高风险的会议，会上她提出了一项充满活力的新举措；相反，当她忙于处理一份高压报告的时候，一场有关公司IT系统的低压更新会议可以为她的精力提供必要的喘息机会。我们发现，当知识工作者尚未被当天的需求消耗殆尽时，尤其是在上午而不是下午，这种互补效应最为明显。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些研究结果揭示了泰勒和敏利的日程安排方式这些方法可能会无意中削弱他们工作日的精力，但它们也揭示了潜在改进的途径。泰勒决定将会议安排在一天内，导致当天的会议和个人工作之间的时间严重不平衡，这可能会减少他对补充能量至关重要的短暂休息活动的参与。尽管旨在优化他的日程安排，但这种方法可能反而会导致能量耗尽和性能下降。在这两天中更加平衡地分配会议和个人任务可能会增强他的精力和效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;就敏莉的情况而言，她计划在周二处理一个困难的项目和一个重要的会议，这可能会造成过度的压力，而不会造成不必要的压力。足够的救济和恢复机会。相反，她的周三充满了低压会议和更轻松的项目，可能缺乏刺激。相反，如果敏丽可以在某一天将要求较高的个人任务与负担较轻的会议结合起来，另一天则相反，那么她就更有可能在这两天中保持精力充沛。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，当面临安排工作日的挑战时，尤其是在安排个人任务的同时安排会议时，请考虑以下事项：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;关注特定日期会议时间与个人工作时间的相对比例，而不仅仅是总时间会议和个人任务之间的合理平衡可以在整个工作日提供必要的休息和能量补充。这种方法不需要在一天中召开过多的会议，即使它有时看起来是一种节省时间的策略。管理每天的会议时间相对于个人工作的比例可以增强工作中的精力水平，从而有助于提高绩效、创造力和工作满意度。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;设计您的工作日，以在会议和个人之间创造互补&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;认识到将高压会议与低压个人任务配对的好处，反之亦然。不要将相同压力水平的活动集中到一个时期内，而是将具有挑战性的任务和会议分布在不同的日子或一天中的不同时间段。这种方法可以促进适当的压力互补，从而增强工作日的精力，从而实现更好的绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;采用更全面的方法来安排工作日。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;而不是简单地将会议或个人任务融入到工作中。为了方便使用日历，请考虑对您的工作日结构的更广泛影响。请注意日程安排决策可能会如何改变您工作日的安排模式，从而可能影响您的精力和生产力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下问题可能对您的计划过程有用：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li >;此安排决策将如何影响我在这一特定日期的会议和个人工作时间之间的平衡？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将此会议添加到一天中的此特定时段是否会过多压缩我的个人工作时间，从而牺牲必要的休息时间和补货？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;这样的日程安排会导致一天内连续召开高压会议和任务吗？如何避免这种情况？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我的日程安排中是否有更好的时间来安排此会议或任务，以便更有效地混合全天的高压和低压工作？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;对于知识工作者来说，管理会议不仅仅是为了提高效率和时间效率；更是为了提高效率。它还要求对日常日程安排采取战略方法。这意味着考虑每日会议和个人任务，无论是时间分配还是它们会给你带来多少压力。注意这些方面可以帮助您避开微妙的日程安排陷阱，并防止您的精力和生产力意外消耗。事实上，通过采用更全面的会议安排方法，您可以改变您处理工作日的方式，从而对日常职责进行更加平衡和富有成果的安排。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[No, SCOTUS Did Not Make Your Company&rsquo;s DEI Programs Illegal]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_30hero.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p >;最有效的 DEI 方法也是控制法律风险的最佳方法：将 DEI 计划的重点放在消除通过基本业务系统不断传播的偏见上。这就是大多数企业 DEI 计划的运作方式，这些计划通常侧重于培训和调整组织系统以创造公平的竞争环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;喧嚣正在进行中围绕最高法院最近推翻平权行动的决定，&lt;em>;学生公平招生诉哈佛&lt;/em>;。在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://aflegal.org/america-first-legal-puts-woke-corporations-law-firms-and-hospitals-on-notice-all-dei-programs-and-workplace-balancing -based-on-race-national-origin-and-sex-violate-the-law/&quot;>;博客文章&lt;/a>;，题为“美国第一法律将唤醒公司......置于通知”，美国第一法律是一个由以下人士领导的组织特朗普前顾问史蒂芬·米勒 (Stephen Miller) 断言，“所有 DEI 项目”现在都是“非法的”。米勒提供无偿法律帮助，反对“那些对我们同胞延续法西斯主义偏见的机构。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是政治，朋友们；这就是政治。不要将其误认为是法律。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在最基本的层面上，最高法院的判决解释了美国宪法的平等保护条款，该条款通常不适用于私人雇主。同样基本的是：基于种族的就业决定&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;根据联邦法规第七章已经是非法的&lt;/一个>;。这排除了为有色人种保留招聘或晋升名额以及利用种族作为决胜局等做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/ us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;九个州&lt;/a>;已经禁止基于种族的平权行动，通常是根据其州宪法。在我居住的加利福尼亚州，近 30 年前，209 号提案禁止在州立大学招生、州招聘和州合同方面基于种族采取平权行动。我从未听说过 209 号提案将私营公司的 DEI 计划定为非法的传闻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此评论认为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-06 -22/supreme-court-affirmative-action-ruling-jeopardizes-corporate-diversity-too#xj4y7vzkg&quot;>;“公司……[将]关闭所有 DEI 工作&lt;/a>;”和&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-07-06/yes-the-supreme-court-s-affirmative-action-ruling-really-does-affect-employers#xj4y7vzkg&quot;>;“企业多元化努力[ ] 陷入法律麻烦”&lt;/a>; 似乎有点歇斯底里。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司 DEI 计划受到牵连的唯一原因是尼尔·戈萨奇法官的同意意见中的几句话，只有克拉伦斯法官加入了该意见托马斯.戈萨奇的同意远远超出了本案所涉及的问题。它简要讨论了禁止就业中种族和性别歧视的联邦法规，向未来的原告表明他欢迎未来针对雇主的诉讼。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，我们开始讨论戈萨奇法官是否可能会这样做能够在未来组建最高法院多数派——特别是因为美国第一法律公司等资金雄厚的保守派非营利组织已承诺未来提起诉讼。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实上，人力资源咨询公司 Workforce 21C 的辛西娅·托马斯·卡尔弗特 (Cynthia Thomas Calvert)指出，“在最高法院做出裁决之前，白人雇员提出的‘反向歧视’诉讼已经在增加。”一名员工获得了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://casetext.com/case/duvall-v-novant-health-inc-5&quot;>;380 万美元&lt;/a>;；在第二起诉讼中，陪审团判决&lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/starbucks-racism-philadelphia-manager-lawsuit-bfa9cd9a897dff402f8547f167455d10&quot;>;2560万美元&lt;/a>;。这些金额虽大，但诉讼数量却很少。这些裁决可能无法继续存在：第一个裁决已被上诉，第二个裁决可能会被上诉。请继续关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;原告质疑公司多元化声明，或质疑其员工中一定比例是有色人种的目标，需要证明该目标导致了损害其职业生涯的“不利就业行动”。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/diversity-equity-dei-companies-blum-2040b173&quot;>;雇主会辩称事实并非如此&lt;/a>;，并会指出法院给予公司广泛的保护自行决定以他们认为合适的方式经营业务。所有这些都会使这些诉讼难以胜诉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最有效的 DEI 方法也是控制法律风险的最佳方法：将 DEI 计划的重点放在中断通过基本业务系统不断传播的偏见上。这就是大多数企业 DEI 计划的运作方式，这些计划通常侧重于培训和调整组织系统以创造公平的竞争环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如何？让我们举一个招聘偏见的例子，该实验是我的团队目前在该领域进行的 25 个偏见中断实验之一中发现的。我们发现，一家科技初创公司雇用的白人男性的评分远低于其他任何群体。我们还发现，白人通常只有在评分非常低的情况下才会被拒绝。来自其他群体的候选人即使评分高得多，也会被拒绝。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们正在合作的科技初创公司从不愿意收集和分析数据，到要求所有参与招聘的员工接受我们举办了关于消除招聘偏见的研讨会。将您的 DEI 计划建立在此类数据的基础上可以帮助改变公司的氛围。指标可以移山。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;收集这些数据还可以降低法律风险，因为第七章禁止基于种族或性别产生不同影响的政策。没有公司愿意在原告提起歧视诉讼后才了解此类问题。凡事有预谋。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦获得数据，您就需要解决发现的任何问题。不要让有偏见的系统留在原地，然后试图解决你在最后一刻明确考虑种族而造成的问题。相反，通过增加结构来遵循工业组织心理学的基本规则。例如，应通过使用标题和标准化量表根据预先确定的能力对每个候选人进行排名来审查简历。然后添加旨在防止实验社会心理学家记录的各种偏见的程序。例如，跟踪需求何时被放弃，并寻找模式。 (Research shows that requirements typically are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/10.7758/9781610443913&quot;>;applied&lt;/a>; rigorously to out groups but leniently to in groups.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you do this, you will not fall afoul of the &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions&lt;/em>; ruling, because you are avoiding precisely what the majority opinion found so offensive: explicit racial preferences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As Chief Justice Roberts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/22pdf/20-1199_hgdj.pdf&quot;>;noted in his opinion&lt;/a>;, Harvard&#39;s racial preferences led to a situation where a Black student in the fourth lowest academic decile had a higher chance of admission than an Asian American in the top decile. We have never, ever found anything like this at a company, and we have worked with scores of companies for over a decade.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The typical problem is epitomized by one telling statistic: In our database of nearly 20,000 people, 80% to 88% of white men report fair access to career-enhancing assignments while the percentage among women of color sinks as low as 50%. This is a recipe for a lawsuit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Two final parts of the majority opinion hold messages for the corporate world. If you do want to hire a qualified person of color in a context where a reverse discrimination suit might ensue, the majority opinion tells you exactly what to say. &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions&lt;/em>; says that while one cannot give someone an automatic boost based on race, one can consider how a candidate overcame various life obstacles, including racial discrimination. Heads up that this is how to talk.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The final important part of the majority opinion is its discussion of stereotyping. Harvard&#39;s “admissions process rests on the pernicious stereotype that &#39;a black student can usually bring something that a white student cannot offer,&#39;” Justice Roberts wrote. “UNC is much the same. It argues that race in itself &#39;says [something] about who you are.&#39;” In the court&#39;s view, “it demeans the dignity and worth of a person to be judged by ancestry instead of by his or her own merit and essential qualities.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This language has implications for another common DEI practice: employee resource groups (ERGs), or voluntary groups of employees who align around a shared identity. These groups reflect on the evidence-based-but-now-illegal assumption that (for example) Black employees tend to have a different experience than white employees at your company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The simple fix, according to Laura Maechtlen, a partner at Seyfarth Shaw LLP, to open up ERGs to anyone who supports the mission of the group. You should also make sure your ERGs have a mission statement, business goals, and rules that prevent people from joining the group simply to disrupt it. This is best practice anyway, because this approach can help reduce backlash and develop allies. If your ERG includes capacity building (such as leadership training), make sure that the training also offered in other contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s the bottom line: Far-right advocates like American First Legal are pretending that &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions&lt;/em>; stands for a lot that it doesn&#39;t stand for. No harm, no foul: that&#39;s what advocates do. But don&#39;t mistake it for a serious assessment of legal risk. It isn&#39;t.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How a Hybrid Platform Can Help Enable Trusted Generative AI - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM CLOUDERA, AMD & DELL]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/08/how-a-hybrid-platform-can-help-enable-trusted-generative-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;LJH82erDHQp3AvTAeo0Mt+iTzxaGx7qrjFjwWkGV8zlYqv6/tcfKxr2toAHeF+Bc&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLe1ccDR72ijPS6FDnxIL/8g==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;true&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-a-hybrid-platform-can-help-enable-trusted-generative-ai&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3,DFP_IC_pos4&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;sponsored&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;true&quot; >; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-0&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Clouderahero-1024x536.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;Generative artificial intelligence (AI) is still in its infancy, but it already brings irresistible promise to help businesses serve their customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations can use generative AI to quickly and economically sift through large volumes of their own data to help create relevant and high-quality text, audio, images, and other content in response to prompts based on legions of training data. And hosted open-source large language models (LLMs) can help organizations add enterprise data context to their outputs, producing more reliable responses while reducing false information (“hallucinations”).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But the dilemma is that, to get more accurate outputs from a generative AI model, organizations need to give third-party AI tools access to enterprise-specific knowledge and proprietary data. And companies that don&#39;t take the proper precautions could expose their confidential data to the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That makes optimal hybrid data management critical to any organization with a strategy that entails using third-party software-as-a-service (SaaS) AI solutions with its proprietary data.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Harnessing the Power of Hybrid Cloud&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The public cloud offers scalable environments ideal for experimenting with LLMs. However, full-scale LLM deployment can be prohibitively expensive in the cloud. And while LLMs are only as good as their data, sending sensitive or regulated data to cloud-based LLMs presents significant privacy and compliance risks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The private cloud offers an optimal environment for hosting LLMs with proprietary enterprise data and a more cost-effective solution for long-running LLM deployments than is offered by public clouds. Housing LLMs in a private cloud also ensures enhanced data security, safeguarding sensitive information from external threats and compliance issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Organizations that adopt a hybrid workflow can get the best of both worlds, making the most of generative AI without sacrificing privacy and security. They can benefit from the flexibility of the public cloud for initial experimentation while keeping their most sensitive data safe on on-premises platforms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One organization&#39;s experience demonstrates how hybrid cloud-based data management can incorporate public customer data in real time while protecting confidential company and customer information.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;A More Personalized Experience&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the largest financial institutions in Southeast Asia, Singapore-based, wanted to use AI and machine learning (ML) to enhance the digital customer experience and improve its decision making. It used a hybrid cloud platform to do so.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;OCBC built a single entry point for all its LLM use cases: a hybrid framework that could seamlessly integrate multiple data sources, including inputs from thousands of customers and a private-cloud data lake that would keep customer data safe, to get real-time insights customized to its own company standards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank built prompt&amp;nbsp;microservices for accessing LLMs stored on its on-premises servers as well as LLMs available in the public cloud: a cost-effective model that allowed it both to use public cloud LLMs and to host open-source LLMs, depending on the functionality and customization it needed. By deploying and hosting its own code assistant, scaled for 2,000 users, OCBC saved 80% of the cost of using SaaS solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Combining the vast capabilities available on the public cloud with the portability of its private platform helped the bank securely train its AI models and derive more accurate inferences from its outputs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The platform integrates with the bank&#39;s ML operations pipelines and fits into its larger ML engineering ecosystem. This cloud-based ML-powered platform lets OCBC build its own applications and use the tools and frameworks its data scientists choose.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The initiative has led to a more personalized customer experience, higher campaign conversion rates, faster transactions, reduced downtime for data centers, and an additional SGD100 million (US$75 million) in revenue a year.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Innovating with Generative AI, Securely&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations are racing to adopt generative AI to streamline their operations and turbocharge innovation. They need AI tools that have enterprise-specific context and draw on knowledge from proprietary data sources.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But while the technology is still maturing, there&#39;s no need to sacrifice privacy, security, and compliance. By using hosted open-source LLMs, businesses can access the latest capabilities and fine-tune models with their own data while maintaining control and avoiding privacy concerns—and limiting expenses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Going with a hybrid platform allows organizations to use the advantages of the public cloud while keeping proprietary AI-based insights out of public view. By allowing businesses to store and use their data wherever, whenever, and however they need while offering a significant cost advantage, hybrid workflows incorporating vendor-agnostic and open and flexible solutions are truly democratizing AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Learn more about how you can &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudera.com/why-cloudera/enterprise-ai.html?internal_keyplay=data-lakehouse&amp;amp;internal_campaign=FY24-Q3_SC_Globl_HBR_ContentArticle_2023-08-11&amp;amp;cid=701Hr0000029gooIAA&amp;amp;internal_link=on-page-body&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;use open-source LLMs with your own data in a secure environment&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why We Glorify Overwork and Refuse to Rest]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_28_590177686.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Orbon Alija/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;None of us want to admit that we would rather feel overwhelmed than underwhelmed. In fact, we often experience a greater sense of our own value when we&amp;#8217;re working than we do when we&amp;#8217;re not. Working is not just a way to stay busy, but also to prove our worthiness &amp;#8211; to others and to ourselves. The result is that without the right guardrails in place, we silently collude with employers who encourage us to overwork through intense pressure to perform. The authors outline strategies for intervening if you find yourself compulsively overworking, including honestly recognizing your tendency to work long and continuous hours, prioritizing sleep and movement, and choosing one activity outside of work that brings you true enjoyment.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;hlFJa4rIESdsHeLrhl0cVa4L0Vs5z6ZL2rREMbIQOaFEaCWWLMGJ9vbjJlQTRUNv&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLkkr4KLIudCcZ656s9EHxHQ==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;Nearly half of all US workers fail to use all their allotted vacation days, according to a recent survey from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/03/30/how-americans-view-their-jobs/&quot;>;Pew Research Center&lt;/a>;.&amp;nbsp; The reasons they cite include having too much to do, concern about falling behind at work, and a reluctance to ask coworkers to cover their responsibilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 21:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Survey: Remote Work Isn&rsquo;t Going Away &mdash; and Executives Know It]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/survey-remote-work-isnt-going-away-and-executives-know-it]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_26_74011380.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;ER Productions Limited/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Many CEOs are publicly gearing up for yet another return-to-office push. Privately, though, executives expect remote work to keep on growing, according to a new survey. That makes sense: Employees like it, the technology is improving, and &amp;#8212; at least for hybrid work &amp;#8212; there seems to be no loss of productivity. Despite the headlines, executives expect both hybrid and fully remote work to keep increasing over the next five years.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;MqyPx+iZb/LrP/bWQAMVolJjHZn+BSPk7KUnJpgKbrEQEnM/8piwvtFVwfUL2eF/&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLMsuUTRBYWbwIuLdaIgIerQ==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;survey-remote-work-isnt-going-away-and-executives-know-it&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;Remote work &lt;a href=&quot;https://wfhresearch.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SIEPR1.pdf&quot;>;spiked&lt;/a>; during the pandemic, from about 6% of full workdays in the US to more than 50% in the spring of 2020. Since then, it&#39;s steadily decreased and since early 2023 has hovered around 28%.&amp;nbsp;Many executives believe it&#39;s time to come back to the office: Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan, has declared himself a &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-chides-184750015.html&quot;>;remote-work skeptic&lt;/a>;; Mark Zuckerberg has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/12/tech-ceos-fall-out-of-love-with-wfh&quot;>;declared&lt;/a>; that engineers “get more done” in the office; and Google&#39;s chief people officer recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/2023/06/13/companies-aggressive-return-to-office&quot;>;told employees&lt;/a>; that office attendance would factor into performance reviews. Even &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/08/07/business/zoom-return-to-office/index.html&quot;>;Zoom&#39;s leadership&lt;/a>; wants employees back in person two days a week.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Reskill Your Workforce in the Age of AI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-to-reskill-your-workforce-in-the-age-of-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;6335553519112&amp;quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;Loading... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;>;By now, it&amp;#8217;s probably clear to most of us that the Age of AI has arrived. Artificial intelligence applications promise to transform nearly every aspect of business, from analytics to product development to customer experience to pretty much everything else.&amp;#160;What&amp;#8217;s less clear is how we can best manage this potential. In particular, how do we organize and reskill our workforces to take advantage of both the automated and human skills that will be necessary to drive future success. To try to answer these questions, we invited Raffaella Sadun, a professor at Harvard Business School, to be our guest&amp;#160; on &amp;#8220;The New World of Work&amp;#8221;. Raffaella&amp;#8217;s research focuses on the managerial and organizational drivers of productivity and growth, and she is the co-author of the cover story in the latest issue of Harvard Business Review: &amp;#8220;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/reskilling-in-the-age-of-ai&quot;>;Reskilling in the Age of AI&lt;/a>;.&amp;#8221; The conversation mainly focused on the reskilling challenge. Her underlying message is that companies need to adapt properly to the technology at hand. Do it right, and you can unlock opportunities for innovation and growth. Do it wrong, and you might stagnate.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;L4GZzHexvVAsKmt7OArzg3hz9esHSLLBhlfZcTgQRJaeWUQiCdXtRQKsP/ABeOqo&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5xQDQXkk0ocDzwDYTbUpB3qyxQ7MDzNB7O9n9zb1LYYg==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-to-reskill-your-workforce-in-the-age-of-ai&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;How will AI affect businesses and employees? It&#39;s the million-dollar question, and according to Harvard Business School&#39;s Raffaella Sadun, the answer will depend on how well an organization connects the new technologies to both a broad corporate vision and individual employee growth. One without the other is a recipe for job elimination and fewer new opportunities for all.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 26 Aug 2023 01:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When a Coworker Undermines You in a Meeting]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/when-a-coworker-undermines-you-in-a-meeting]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_25_1364036821.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Feeling undermined, unappreciated, or unsupported by a colleague when you&amp;#8217;re both in the same meeting can lead to loss of trust, along with feelings of self-doubt and lack of confidence. But looking to see what you can do to help the situation, rather than dwelling on what someone is doing to you, can begin to ease tension and repair a dysfunctional working relationship. In this article, the author offers strategies to try when a coworker doesn&amp;#8217;t have your back.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;MAGYSGa/GTuwpkSqFNBb8nDuNsvhR9I3rA/AQwoNIPY12N6m4LdKCYuu37jnbISb&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhL+qa8f0pm9nVvHKNYNg/+gA==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;when-a-coworker-undermines-you-in-a-meeting&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;In my coaching conversations with Anna, she remarked that she felt unsupported by a colleague who she thought tried to sabotage her during team meetings rather than having her back. According to Anna, this coworker (we&#39;ll call Dina) seemed to relish the opportunity to find something critical to say, shoot down Anna&#39;s ideas, and rally others to an opposing viewpoint. The situation understandably caused Anna to feel vulnerable, doubt herself, and lose trust in a relationship she valued. As her executive coach, she turned to me for strategies to counter this negativity.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Speak Confidently to Your Team During Chaotic Times]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-to-speak-confidently-to-your-team-during-chaotic-times]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_25_1269876214.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Grizelj/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;These days, many employees feel like they&amp;#8217;re constantly receiving a stream of bad or confusing news that affects their work in unpredictable ways. When they only hear simple summaries from their leaders about issues they know aren&amp;#8217;t so simple, teams can feel frustrated and even angry. Next time you feel you need to say something, but you&amp;#8217;re not sure what to say, try these three strategies: 1) Recognize the power of &amp;#8220;and&amp;#8221; &amp;#8212; it allows you to align two seemingly separate thoughts, such as &amp;#8220;things are difficult and things will be okay.&amp;#8221; 2) Teach the past to arm the future. Unpacking the past and connecting it to the present can help you create more certainty. 3) Adopt a more experimental mindset. This can help change feel less risky.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;7NlsZsLfQn7CftqS35l5Ltyqm0rPiMHHVggJBhnoXNAxc/ZTCuUGjKV0bU1vH29C&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5xQDQXkk0ocDzwDYTbUpB3LHDHuEgIMO7LzepkuVj/lg==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-to-speak-confidently-to-your-team-during-chaotic-times&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;“The chaos right now in our organization is overwhelming,” Lara revealed during our executive coaching session. At the time, her company had just hired a new CEO, and the ripple effects of change were traveling throughout the organization. “I need to keep my team focused and encouraged, but anything I say feels fake and distracting. Should I just stay quiet until things calm down?”&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 25 Aug 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Science of Choice Can Boost Innovation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-the-science-of-choice-can-boost-innovation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_24_1306871683-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;golero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Ever since the late 1990s, social psychologists have known a surprising truth: If you want to maximize someone&amp;#8217;s satisfaction with a choice, don&amp;#8217;t give them unlimited options. Instead, you should give them&amp;#160;&lt;em>;some&lt;/em>; choice but with clear constraints. This added structure is crucial for picking a desired option with confidence. This research also translates to innovation, which often results from 1) identifying a big problem to solve; 2) breaking it down into sub-problems; 3) identifying how those subproblems had been previously solved; and 4) combining the subproblem solutions in a unique and novel way. This process, which the author calls &amp;#8220;choice mapping,&amp;#8221; adds helpful constraints to your process.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;GRBHc/zoa/3fqYxHsZKVyG3V1+KHrwbVTe86jV2oxn0gPwVOxTi/XBGKIqwPRP65&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW5iAHwuINYiqwQMPfwPWVfV7GGOj4tTcbxCGJgmmdQPLg==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;how-the-science-of-choice-can-boost-innovation&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;While history would like you to believe breakthroughs are the result of genius inspiration, or divine intervention, the truth is far more prosaic. Whether it&#39;s the invention of basketball or an organization-wide system for learning and innovation, our greatest minds have arrived at their&amp;nbsp;&lt;em>;Eureka!&lt;/em>;&amp;nbsp;moments by way of clever choosing. That is, they identified their big problem, broke it down into several subproblems, searched to find options for how each subproblem had been previously solved, and combined those options in unique ways to arrive at a novel solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Using ChatGPT to Make Better Decisions]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/using-chatgpt-to-make-better-decisions]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_24_1468320081.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jorg Greuel/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A successful decision-making process has three steps: Framing the decision, generating alternatives, and deciding between them. Large language models can help at each stage of the process. But while it may be tempting to merely ask ChatGPT for answers, the real power of LLMs is how they can assist at each stage. Ask for help thinking of considerations you might be missing, or alternatives you might not have considered. LLMs can be a de-biasing tool, helping you frame and make the decision yourself.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;mPWLrM8C84VMIAUOGhmUS+O+7wL1EYaLmwfEqV1JMhPeeAK1F0JgPcrwqidBSbAS&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLKdg5Vzjfs/EE6uTNh+VtYA==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;using-chatgpt-to-make-better-decisions&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;Can &lt;a href=&quot;https://chat.openai.com/auth/login&quot;>;ChatGPT&lt;/a>; help executives make better decisions? The large language model everyone has been talking about for months also has an eloquent answer to this question: “Yes, I can support you in management decisions by providing information, facts, analysis, and perspectives that can help you make an informed decision.” ChatGPT immediately follows up with a limitation of its own competence. “However, it is important to note that my advice and recommendations are based on an algorithmic analysis of data and information, and you, as a human being, still have to make the final decision based on your experience, knowledge, and assessment of the situation.”&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 24 Aug 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>