<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How a Federal Ban on Ransomware Payments Could Help CISOs]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-a-federal-ban-on-ransomware-payments-could-help-cisos]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_04_163514653.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;杰弗里·柯立芝/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;白宫正在考虑禁止支付勒索软件，这可能会改变首席信息和安全官 (CISO) 的职位。该禁令将把网络安全对话提升至首席执行官、首席财务官和董事会，并有可能结束在发生漏洞时将首席信息安全官当作替罪羊的做法。这是一个重大转变：在 Uber 前首席安全官因掩盖 2016 年网络攻击而被定罪后，CISO 有更多理由担心这份工作带来的个人责任。企业现在应该如何为这种新形势做好准备：为最坏的情况做好准备，让高级领导层负责网络安全对话，测试他们的安全态势，定期审核内部流程和员工安全培训，以找出网络准备方面的差距。 &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;3WJ7G5QfvpEALLck/S+S+3A5ygX2pLrqm4MYuf401Bcgss7LlSvQg55fqPyZ3/Up&quot; data-索引=“BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW63kSqFbbABFP5qz3keUVTgAQ2bH00R3gGJXcZ9ZRfeag==”数据豁免=“假”数据页年=“2023”数据页月=“08”数据页-seo-title=“how-a-feeder”阿尔-ban-on-ransomware- payments-could-help-cisos&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;首席信息安全对于大部分人来说，高管（CISO）倦怠一直是行业中的一个&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2010/06/01/health/01mind.html&quot;>;health/01mind.html&quot;>;问题&lt;/a>;过去十年，似乎只是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sdxcentral.com/articles/analysis/the-great-ciso-resignation-why-security-leaders-are-quitting-in-droves/ 2023/05/&quot;>;变得更糟&lt;/a>;。随着网络攻击的增加、管理更广泛、更复杂的攻击面，以及在预算紧张的情况下做更多事情的压力越来越大，难怪美国有四分之三的 CISO &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles /cybersecurity-leaders-suffer-burnout-as-Presses-of-the-job-intensify-b0609ef1&quot;>;报告&lt;/a>;感觉精疲力尽。今天的首席信息安全官不仅仅是在处理资源——他们在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/security-chiefs-take-on-it-roles-as-more-infrastruct-moves- online-edb3ccf8?mod=djemCyber​​secruityPro&amp;amp;tpl=cy&quot;>;双重 CIO/CISO 角色&lt;/a>;，旨在简化战略并进一步削减成本。当发生安全漏洞和勒索软件攻击时，CISO 通常会自动承担责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Mastering the Art of the Request]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/mastering-the-art-of-the-request]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt; /span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;即使是最高效的领导者也认识到有多少事情是他们无法控制的，但我们所有人都有代理权的一件事是我们如何与他人沟通。对于我们大多数人来说，清晰表达的请求、能够引起真正回应的请求并不是自然而然的。事实证明，提出请求是一门艺术——无论是针对交付成果不合格的员工，还是针对来自不同部门、在协作项目上没有尽全力的同事。这就是提出请求如此困难的原因、许多领导者仍然犯错的原因，以及发出请求以引发具体、可操作的响应的一些策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;文章内容&quot; data-key=&quot;HMGN7jgz9xcPyiC/cCCdvRUVY+JUx3pKw37OyPtBvRIaeZ0YbvCxBeymLAhKA6QI&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6 3kSqFbbABFP5qz3keUVTgvIfdCZQW9kY5QAdPhYcp9g==”数据豁免=“假” “ data-page-year =“2023”data-page-month =“08”data-page-seo-title =“mastering-the-art-of-the-request”data-page-adUnit-locations =“” data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;如果曾经有一个时候，领导者可以简单地发出命令并认为它们已经完成，那么现在肯定不是那个时候。我们生活在一个扁平化组织结构、跨职能团队和重视协作、自主和敏感性的工作场所文化的世界。在过去 20 年对公司和非营利组织高管进行培训的过程中，我发现领导者越​​来越多地发现自己必须提出要求才能完成工作。通常，他们不知道该怎么做。&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Don&rsquo;t Let Your Company&rsquo;s Culture Stifle Leadership Development]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/dont-let-your-companys-culture-stifle-leadership-development]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_03_200570342-003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Tom Fowlks/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;领导力发展计划常常没有充分考虑领导者工作所在的文化、规范和系统。领导者可能会被要求在注重即时结果的文化中进行长期思考，或者当他们在自己的团队中因工作而获得奖励时，他们可能会被教导要跨组织边界进行协作。当领导者和领导力发展实践者未能认识到 1) 公司文化和组织环境以及 2) 最高层领导者的关键作用时，他们在塑造这种环境方面的作用过于简单化，并可能损害他们的领导力发展努力。作者分享了 Intuit 用来建立一种加强而不是抑制领导者积极成长的文化的四种策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/08/dont-let-your-companys-culture-stifle-leadership-development?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/ dont-let-your-companys-culture-stifle-leadership-development?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;泰勒是一家中型科技公司的经验丰富的经理，最近完成了培训关于如何进行困难的对话。泰勒发现培训很有价值。她学习了一种新模型，练习了与同伴进行的困难对话，并从其他参与者那里得到了反馈。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但泰勒从未进行过对话。这感觉很冒险，她担心这个人会如何反应。虽然泰勒知道这次谈话很重要，但她自己的经理很少如此直接地沟通，她公司的大多数经常得到认可和晋升的领导者也没有这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“泰勒”是我认为许多积极进取的领导者的综合体。多年来一直与我们合作，他们受到鼓励和培养，以他们在公司中看不到的榜样或奖励方式进行领导。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我已经 &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/two -techniques-for-helping-employees-change-ingrained-habits&quot;>;之前写过&lt;/a>;关于使用行为科学来提高员工发展计划有效性的力量。当完成培训后，个人准确定义何时采取行动并计划他们将遇到的不可避免的障碍时，他们更有可能实现目标并做出有意义的行为改变。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，这种关注点对个人发展的关注并不能解释任何行为改变努力中的另一个关键变量：个人工作的背景或环境。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://cancercontrol.cancer.gov/brp/research/constructs/environments&quot;>;在几乎所有领域&lt;/a>;，一个人的环境在塑造其行为方面发挥着重要作用。我们环境的设计会影响我们的选择和随之而来的习惯。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们也受到环境中其他人的规范和期望的强烈影响。当我们看到周围的人&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-07712-9&quot;>;无私&lt;/a>;或&lt;a href=&quot;https://ijbnpa. biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/1479-5868-7-86&quot;>;锻炼&lt;/a>;，我们更有可能采取同样的行为方式。斯坦福大学行为设计实验室的创始人兼主任 BJ Fogg 甚至表示，“只有一种方法可以从根本上改变你的行为：从根本上改变你的环境。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在组织环境中，高级人员领导者在创造环境方面发挥着重要作用。 Edgar Schein，被认为是组织文化“之父”，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Organizational-Leadership-Jossey-Bass-Business-Management-dp-1119212049/dp/1119212049/ref =dp_ob_title_bk&quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;领导者关注的内容、榜样、教导和强化的内容将对组织文化产生重大影响。如果一个领导者把所有时间都花在与上级领导在一起而忽视了自己的团队，那么他就会发出一个信号，表明他们认为什么是重要的。当领导者拒绝承认错误或弱点时，他们就在含蓄地告诉团队，这样做也不安全。在泰勒的案例中，她的经理避免了困难的、直接的对话，并定下了这样的基调：此类对话没有重要到优先考虑的程度，可以避免。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，领导力发展计划常常不会“不能充分考虑领导者工作所在的文化、规范和系统。领导者可能会被要求在注重即时结果的文化中进行长期思考，或者当他们在自己的团队中因工作而获得奖励时，他们可能会被教导要跨组织边界进行协作。当领导者和领导力发展从业者未能认识到 1) 公司文化和组织环境以及 2) 最高层领导者在塑造这种环境中的关键作用时，他们就会过于简单化，并可能会破坏他们的领导力发展工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;在 Intuit，我们过去五年一直致力于建立一种能够加强而不是抑制领导者积极成长的文化。一路走来，我们学到了很多东西，包括需要使我们的学习技术现代化，这需要我们的人力资源和技术团队的大量支持和投资。我们还被提醒，我们的领导人在有限的时间和许多相互竞争的优先事项中始终如一地优先考虑他们的发展是多么困难。虽然我们还有很长的路要走，但我们已经看到了积极的反馈、参与度和行为变化，这表明我们正走在正确的轨道上。希望我们的经历可以为经历类似旅程的其他人提供启发。以下是我们为确保我们的文化支持和加强领导力发展而采取的四项行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;定义领导力。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;首先，高层领导者需要明确阐明贵公司的优秀领导力是什么样子，并围绕您的领导力期望创建一种共享语言。为此，请考虑以下问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;我们最好的领导者真正擅长什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我们的领导者未来需要擅长什么？&lt;/li>; >; &lt;li>;我们期望领导者塑造和强化的文化有何独特之处？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;在 Intuit，我们围绕领导力的共同语言与以下方面相关且适用，这对我们来说非常重要：各级领导者——不仅仅是我们的高管。我们还希望确保它“易于记忆和背诵”，因此我们避免使其过于规范或复杂。最终，我们将定义集中在三个核心能力上：1）以清晰的愿景领导； 2）建立高绩效文化； 3) 推动取得胜利。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下一步是建立领导框架。我们将其称为“领导力手册”，它包括针对每项核心能力的三种支持行为。我们纳入的许多行为，例如“培养人才以提高绩效”，都是最佳实践，可能与许多其他公司和行业的期望行为类似。其他的，例如“专注于客户问题”，反映了我们独特的公司优先事项和价值观。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们不断收到领导者的反馈，认为将这些行为编入法典有助于明确他们的期望和提供一个框架来应对真正的领导力挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;树立领导力典范。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您是高级领导者，您可以做的最有影响力的事情是确保要让你的公司文化与你的领导力期望保持一致，你需要亲自塑造公司的领导行为。正如 Schein 所说，你的行为将对塑造文化产生不成比例的巨大影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了在 Intuit 鼓励这一点，我们从最高层开始，由我们的最高层领导者启动我们的许多领导力发展工作。当我们最初在年度领导力会议上推出《领导力手册》时，我们的首席执行官萨桑·古达齐 (Sasan Goodarzi) 和他的员工，以及我们的前首席执行官、时任执行主席布拉德·史密斯 (Brad Smith) 分享了他们实践手册行为的经验以及行为表现的方式根据他们独特的领导风格而有所不同。我们的最高层领导者为组织的其他成员定下了基调，他们的行动（比他们的言论更重要）表明了他们认为重要的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们还努力帮助领导者建立自我意识，了解他们是否他们正在模仿我们的领导行为。作为我们多个高管发展计划的一部分，领导者会收到来自其团队和/或经理的反馈，了解他们实践我们的领导力手册的程度。然后，领导者根据这些输入制定发展目标，以确保他们不断强化和实践这些行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;教授领导力。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在书中 &lt;em >;高产出管理，英特尔前首席执行官安迪·格罗夫讨论了“管理杠杆”的概念——领导者可以采取的行动来增加组织的产出。他将培训视为“经理可以采取的最有效的行动之一。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为我们建立领导力发展文化的努力的一部分，我们正在培训我们的领导者抓住可传授的领导力时刻。这些可以是正式的机会——例如，我们设计的几乎所有培训项目至少部分是由领导老师主导的。我们尝试构建这些机会，以便领导者能够教授他们感兴趣的主题，并分享他们自己的经验和观察中的教训。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;教学也可以在领导者日常对话中出现的非正式时刻进行。 、1:1 和团队会议。我们鼓励我们的领导者发展一种领导哲学——教授兼领导力专家诺埃尔·蒂奇（Noel Tichy）称之为“可传授的观点”。我们建议他们问自己以下问题，以形成自己的可传授观点：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;哪些经历或观察影响了我对领导力的看法？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我学到了哪些重要的教训？从我的经验中学到了什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我如何将我的经验教训整理或简化为原则或切实的建议？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;在我们上一财年，我们 100% 的执行副总裁和 88我们 % 的高级副总裁促进了学习体验。也许并不奇怪，参与者的出席率、参与度和对领导力发展项目的承诺相对较强。在推出《领导力手册》后的第一年，95% 的副总裁自愿参加我们的第一个高管计划，即副总裁领导力实验室。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;认识并加强领导力。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;为了让你的领导行为持续下去，必须通过你的人才和绩效系统和流程来系统地强化它们。当您的绩效系统与您所提倡的行为不一致时，&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.mit.edu/curhan/www/docs/Articles/15341_Readings/Motivation/Kerr_Folly_of_rewarding_A_while_hoping_for_B.pdf&quot;>;领导者持续实践这些行为的可能性要小得多。考虑您雇用、奖励和认可领导者的所有正式和非正式方式。每个流程都提供了一个机会来强化您的组织对卓越领导力的定义。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们将领导力手册嵌入到我们的招聘、入职和绩效管理流程中。我们将行为面试问题映射到我们的剧本中，以便在招聘领导者时使用。例如，为了了解我们的“定义成功并激励团队围绕它”的领导行为，我们纳入了面试问题：描述一次你必须影响他人朝着他们最初抵制的方向前进的经历。您做到了吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在员工入职培训期间，每位员工都会了解该手册，并且所有新高管都会参加为期一年的深入学习，作为我们高管入职培训的一部分。领导力手册是我们用于绩效和晋升决策的准则，也是我们公司领导力奖项和年度领导力会议的基础。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多组织都有像“泰勒”一样的领导者 - 好奇、积极、渴望为他们的公司和团队做正确的事情，但要克服组织的阻力。采取措施创造一种环境和文化，支持和增强而不是削弱他们作为领导者的成长和发展，将会产生巨大的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt; /a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make a Pivot in the Latter Half of Your Career]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-to-make-a-pivot-in-the-latter-half-of-your-career]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_03_1319676725-2-scaled.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption =&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;作为一名老年工人，改变职业可能会令人畏惧，尤其是在当今无情的不确定性的情况下。但你已经具备了让自己成为候选人所需的条件——你只需要做一些额外的准备，以确保招聘经理和面试官能够看到你独特的技能、经验和观点将如何推动他们的团队和组织向前发展。如果您考虑在职业生涯后期转向不同类型的角色或行业，作者提出了五个面试技巧，供您尝试。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-to-make-a-pivot-in-the-latter-half-of-your-career?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-to-make-a-pivot-in-the-latter-half-of-your-career?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/ a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;改变职业可能具有挑战性，尤其是当您从事单一职业或行业时。当你处于职业生涯的最后一两年时，这样做可能会更加困难，因为你需要保持一定的薪酬、水平或头衔，而你的竞争对手更年轻并且“经验足够”来完成工作。&lt;/我记得 33 岁时，当我想从电视新闻记者转行到娱乐律师时，我担心招聘经理不会重视我十年的工作经验。当我在 48 岁时决定再次将职业生涯从娱乐律师转向科技这一新行业的人力资源业务合作伙伴时，这种恐惧成倍增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您正在考虑跳槽到不同类型的角色或行业在您职业生涯的后期，这里有一些方法可以让您在面试过程中从初级竞争对手中脱颖而出。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;突出显示需要多年工作才能掌握的经验。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在工作场所更加成熟意味着您不仅了解工作的“内容”，而且还了解“如何”表现出色。强调对您的职业成就和进步做出贡献的个人技能、人际交往技能和软技能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可靠、准时和承诺等个人技能显示了您完成工作的整体职业道德和精力。软技能也很重要，例如独立执行工作、能够在组织的各个级别工作以及了解您的工作如何为公司的更大目标做出贡献的能力。例如，如果您有机会向首席执行官或其他高管展示或与他们一起工作，请突出显示这一经历，以表明您具有高管风范、有效沟通的能力，并且您不会被更高级的领导者吓倒。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，人际交往能力在企业工作场所中至关重要。知道如何与跨职能团队成员合作，与他人解决问题，通过变革协调和管理利益相关者，以及如何在没有权力的情况下施加影响，是每项工作都重视的技能。但你的目标是展示这些技能以及更高水平的商业头脑——也许可以通过举一个例子来展示你理解决策的广泛影响的能力，或者在回答问题时表现出盈利能力的方向。提供复杂工作环境的示例来展示您对人际交往能力的掌握，将使您与那些没有太多接触或时间来获得这种经验的初级员工区分开来。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;展示您将如何带来价值.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;即使您从未在您所追求的特定职业领域工作过，作为一名经验丰富的工人，您也可能已经掌握了大量适用于该领域的技能和经验。在此期间，当许多公司通过合并角色来削减成本并期望员工事半功倍时，展示您的技能组合将有助于招聘经理将您视为最佳候选人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，说您的整个职业生涯都在金融领域工作，现在想进入商业运营领域。您对金融、平衡损益、摊销等细微差别的深刻理解，可能会让您成为比没有直接金融经验的资历较浅的人更有吸引力的候选人。当被问到一个以“告诉我一次……”开头的行为问题时，不要只从运营角度谈论你做了什么——还要解释你的金融背景如何成为你成功解决问题的主要原因。问题、影响某人的观点或获得利益相关者的一致。将这些点联系起来，以便面试官了解您广泛的技能如何使您比仅具有职位描述中列出的所需技能或工作经验更有限的人更有价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;展示您如何不断提高技能。 &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;不断地&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/5-ways-to-acquire-new-skills-without-going-back-to-school&quot;>;培养你的技能&lt;/a>;向你展示有精力继续学习，您就不会轻松退休。为了将自己与初级候选人区分开来，请解释一下您如何以与新职业相关的特定方式发展自己的技能和知识。通过查看最低和最高级别角色的职位描述，熟悉行业中常用的数字工具和应用程序。在那里，您会找到诸如“必须精通 X”或“必须具有利用 Y 等多种技术的经验......”之类的语言，然后研究这些应用程序在特定领域的使用方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，花时间了解人工智能和机器学习可能如何影响新的职业——即使你计划相对较快退休。通过简单搜索“人工智能对营销的影响”或“人工智能对金融的影响”，研究人工智能在您想要的领域中如何被使用或将来可能被使用。能够讨论新兴技术以及它们将如何改变工作方式，将使您的候选资格高于那些不具备分析能力的初级候选人，无法将这些知识应用到面向未来的战略对话中。&lt;/p>; &lt; h2>;准备回答：“但你以前没有真正这样做过？”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;永远不要承认！在所有面试中，您的工作是使用职位描述中的关键字将您的技能与您正在面试的职位联系起来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我从娱乐律师转变为人力资源业务合作伙伴和执行教练时，我在每次采访中都被问到这个确切的问题。以下是我为了说服招聘经理我拥有在新职业中取得成功的技能和能力所说的话（职位描述中的关键字以粗体显示）：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;人力资源业务合作伙伴&lt;strong>;调整员工&#39; 实现公司目标的技能和能力&lt;/strong>;。这就是我在真人秀节目中所做的事情：&lt;strong>;战略性地帮助&lt;/strong>;创意主管和制作人打造强大的演员阵容，拥有&lt;strong>;适当的技能&lt;/strong>;，以确保成功的节目&lt;strong>;推动&lt;/strong>;我还负责&lt;strong>;指导&lt;/strong>;制片人&lt;strong>;处理那些没有剧本&lt;/strong>;且&lt;strong>;需要特殊判断力的与人相关的问题&lt;/strong>;强>;。这正是&lt;strong>;人力资源业务合作伙伴&lt;/strong>;在办公室所做的事情 - 我只是在现场。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;我会与我的客户一起准备回答这个问题。也重新转变职业。例如，英语老师珍妮特被问到：“那么你是老师还是项目经理？”珍妮特回复：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;两者都是。我是一名英语老师，但要完成这项工作，我需要成为一名&lt;strong>;出色的项目经理&lt;/strong>;，&lt;strong>;准备项目以实现我们的业务目标&lt;/strong>;，在我的世界里，这就是提高两者整个学区的学生和教师&lt;strong>;表现&lt;/strong>;。由于我更像是一名项目经理而不是教育家，因此我获得了&lt;strong>;项目管理认证&lt;/strong>;，这样我就可以在&lt;strong>;长期规划&lt;/strong>;等领域获得更多工具和最佳实践， &lt;strong>;协调多个项目之间的相互依赖性&lt;/strong>;，&lt;strong>;并促进学区内多所学校和领导之间的项目沟通&lt;/strong>;。我相信，作为一名&lt;strong>;项目经理&lt;/strong>;，我可以为公司带来最大的&lt;strong>;价值&lt;/strong>;，这就是为什么我将这些&lt;strong>;技能和能力&lt;/strong>;运用到更多的公司环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h2>;依靠并突出您庞大的网络。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您已经工作了 20 到 30 年，您可能已经与现在是高管、董事会成员或经理的人，因此有能力为您提供担保。利用这些关系来了解工作（其中一些可能尚未公开发布），并看看这些关系是否可以将您介绍给招聘人员或招聘经理。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，对于某些工作，需要庞大的网络，经验不足的候选人不太可能拥有哪些经验，可能会让您成为特别有吸引力的候选人。例如，您在销售或业务开发工作中的客户或联系人可以扩大您的影响力、影响力或使下一家公司受益的机会，并帮助您被认为比没有书的不太成熟的候选人更有价值业务或深厚的行业关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为一名老年员工，改变职业可能会令人畏惧，尤其是在当今充满不确定性的情况下。但你已经具备了让自己脱颖而出的候选人所需的一切——你只需要做一些额外的准备，以确保招聘经理和面试官能够看到你独特的技能、经验和观点将如何推动他们的团队和组织&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx. net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; 目标=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managers Are Burned Out. Here&rsquo;s How to Help Them Recharge.]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_02_1501196141.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;作为领导者中的领导者，您“创造天气”；为您的团队。你的工作不仅是支持精疲力尽的领导者，还要防止他们继续精疲力尽。在本文中，作者提供了六种策略来帮助团队中精疲力竭的经理重新充电：1）认识并承认他们的倦怠； 2）创造面对面和虚拟的个人联系机会； 3）重新评估、重新确定优先顺序并重新分配工作； 4) 修改关于如何协同工作的团队协议； 5）定期与领导进行一对一的接触； 6) 与团队成员设定期望，让他们利用所有假期时间——当有很多事情要做时，很容易推迟或跳过假期。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href= &quot;/2023/08/managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08 /managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;您组织中的经理很可能&lt;a href =&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;感觉精疲力尽&lt;/a>;。中层管理人员感到必须从上层执行战略，同时指导和发展其下属的团队，从而感到压力——通常无法从更高级的管理人员那里获得相同类型的发展或授权。他们往往资源不足，经常卷起袖子与团队一起工作，特别是考虑到过去几年的人员流动率较高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/podcast/2023/07/麦肯锡的研究&lt;/a>;显示，除了管理职责外，一些中层管理人员每周最多花两天时间进行个人贡献者工作，每周花一天时间进行行政任务。太多的工作，再加上太少的时间和资源，导致许多经理精疲力竭，他们几乎&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;两倍根据微软的研究，&lt;/a>; 他们更有可能离开雇主。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;职业倦怠不仅仅只是因为疲劳或压力——因此，从中恢复并不是一个快速的解决办法。不仅需要时间、意图和组织支持才能重新获得平衡感，而且还要再次感到精力充沛、投入和积极主动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可以肯定的是，每个人的倦怠经历都会&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/your-burnout-is-unique-your-recovery-will-be-too&quot;>;不同&lt;/a>;，因此解决这个问题的各种方法会对它们产生不同的影响。同样，也没有灵丹妙药。采用包括以下策略在内的多管齐下的方法将有助于您的经理完成职业倦怠恢复之旅。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;认识&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;此策略有两个方面。首先，认识到并关心一个人正在经历倦怠，可以帮助他们感到被关注、被理解，甚至被关心。承认倦怠也可以将其摆到桌面上，以便解决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二个方面是认可经理的持续努力以及对业务的积极贡献或影响。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.work human.com/resources/reports-guides/from-thank-you-to-thriving-work human-gallup-report?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023q2_wh_sem_nb_awareness_secondary_na_phr_pros&amp;amp ;utm_content=workers_burnout&amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwv8qkBhAnEiwAkY-ahmQoboWxnUHCOMtoK16gZ4GmZrzXKVd2RIKjn2OYTEAWhGeyBUPOBBoC3ZgQAvD_BwE&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;超过 12,0 00 员工、Workman 和盖洛普显示员工认可度和幸福感之间存在很强的正相关关系，这也带来了更好的结果业务成果。此外，这种认可可以向个人表明他们正在做出改变，特别是当他们的影响可能对他们来说不那么明显时。这可以帮助他们克服工作效率下降的感觉，减少他们的愤世嫉俗或与工作的心理距离，并从他们的工作中获得更多的意义。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“当我们花时间去认识别人时，它不仅具有对他们和我们自己都有积极的影响。”员工赞赏和工作场所文化专家克里斯托弗·利特菲尔德 (Christopher Littlefield) 分享道。 “关注进展顺利、庆祝进步以及分享工作影响的行为有助于我们产生意义、希望和归属感——所有这些都可以促进幸福。这可以很简单，只需花五分钟写一封&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/how-to-write-a-meaningful-thank-you-note&quot;>;有意义的感谢信&lt;/a>;，给快速&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/how-to-give-and-receive-compliments-at-work&quot;>;赞美&lt;/a>;，甚至使用反思性识别。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;重新联系&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在管理者之间创造个人联系（无论是面对面还是虚拟）的机会，可以消除倦怠中常见的孤立感，特别是对于那些远程工作的人来说。创造一种社区意识，让管理者可以与同事分享他们的挑战（和成功），不仅可以促进支持，还可以减少倦怠带来的孤立感，并创造一种“在一起”的感觉。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;同样，在手头的工作之外进行一对一的联系也很有效，并且对某些人来说可能更有意义。 “拿起电话向同事汇报情况可以帮助提醒别人，你在他们身边，”工作场所归属感主题演讲者亚当·斯迈利·波斯沃尔斯基 (Adam Smiley Poswolsky) 分享道。 “与一段时间没有联系的同事重新联系可以为他们提供能量和灵感，尤其是当他们在压力或倦怠中挣扎时。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Poswolsky 补充道：“一个简单的善举 —就像记住同事的生日，或者给同事买他们最喜欢的咖啡一样，会让人们有归属感。当我们在工作中&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/01/the-little-things-that-make-employees-feel-appreciated&quot;>;为人际关系提供更多的时间和空间&lt;/a>;时，我们就会正常化谈论完整的员工关系。人类情绪的范围很广，其中倦怠是最常见的一种。当我们正常谈论倦怠、压力或孤独时，我们可以帮助人们减少孤独感，从而帮助他们感觉更好。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;重新评估、重新确定优先顺序和重新-分配工作&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当管理者感到精疲力尽时，很可能在很大程度上是由于工作量过多、持续不断，并且随着新的优先事项出现，现有项目的优先级并没有降低。一切都变得很重要，并且都留在他们的盘子里，使工作量变得不可持续。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对您的经理每个人的工作内容以及占用他们大部分时间的内容进行审核。确定对实现组织目标最有影响的三个领域。管理者将精力集中在这些方面，而不是其他方面。在此过程中，确定哪些内容可以暂时搁置，哪些截止日期可以延长，或者哪些内容可以完全取消。同样，&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/managers-adjust-your-expectations-without-lowering-the-bar&quot;>;重新评估&lt;/a>;某些工作产品或指标所需的细节或质量水平&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为重新评估的一部分，请花时间了解每个人的工作量和能力以及&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/08/help-your-team-achieve-work-life-balance -even-when-you-cant&quot;>;根据需要重新分配工作&lt;/a>;。此外，将此作为一种常规做法，以帮助您的经理持续重新评估和管理优先事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然您无法在一天中创造更多时间，但您可以调整范围工作量与可用资源（即人员、时间和预算）相称，或主张提供更多资源，例如雇用更多人员的预算或聘请外部承包商分担工作量，即使只是暂时管理高峰&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;修改团队协议&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;授权团队中的经理通过修改有关大家如何合作的协议来帮助解决倦怠问题。您和您团队的经理可以同意尊重哪些界限？这可能包括不发送晚上或周末电子邮件或避免其他&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/dont-let-micro-stresses-burn-you-out?autocomplete=true&quot;>;微压力&lt;/a>; 。通过制定新规范来寻找更好的共同前进之路，有助于建立一种在精疲力竭的情况下经常缺失的代理感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一个团队，您可以决定如何让彼此负责等事情遵守各自的承诺，允许对方推迟或拒绝，并确定特定的非会议日来开展重点工作。达成此类协议可以减少浪费的时间、精力和挫败感，并为他们的未来体验创造一种授权感和主人翁感。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;定期签到&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h2>; &lt;p>;定期与您的经理进行一对一的接触，尤其是那些表现出倦怠迹象的经理。查看他们的表现以及您如何才能最好地支持他们。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/ask-your-team-what-are-you-stuck-on&quot;>;询问他们遇到的困难&lt;/a>;。让他们在感到&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/how-to-deal-with-constantly-feeling-overwhelmed&quot;>;不知所措&lt;/a>;时可以安全地大声说出并告诉您，以便你们可以讨论如何通过适当地清除障碍或把事情从他们的盘子上移开来减轻他们的工作负担。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;放松并重置&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;虽然单独不足以从倦怠中恢复过来，从工作中进行一次有意义的休息来减压是恢复经理能量水平并帮助他们在精神和身体上重新调整的必要步骤。设定期望，让他们&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-take-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot;>;利用所有假期时间&lt;/a>;——这很容易被推迟或者当有很多事情要做时&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/thinking-of-skipping-vacation-dont&quot;>;跳过假期&lt;/a>;。现实是，总会有更多事情要做，所以试着等到你感觉&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/youre-never-going-to-be-caught-up- at-work-stop-feeling-guilty-about-it&quot;>;忙于工作&lt;/a>;就像跑一场没有终点线的马拉松。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，通过休假&lt;a href= “/2017/08/what-one-company-learned-from-forcing-employees-to-use-ir-vacation-time&quot;>;强制&lt;/a>;，您可以帮助抵制组织文化中可能存在的任何战士心态是导致倦怠的一个因素。这可以在团队成员之间以交错的方式完成，以避免业务中断，或者某些组织选择在一年中的特定几周内完全关闭。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论您采取哪种方法，都要允许您的员工完全拔掉电源。当他们不在的时候，为你的团队树立榜样。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/dont-work-on-vacation-seriously&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，在休息时间工作（遗憾的是，三分之二的美国人这样做）会降低内在动力，从而如果一个人一开始就精疲力尽，他的人生就已经处于低谷了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;治疗倦怠的方法不是一劳永逸的单一解决方案，也不是万能的。随着时间的推移，结合使用上述策略不仅可以为精疲力尽的领导者提供支持和充电，还可以防止他们继续精疲力尽。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A More Ethical Approach to Employing Contractors]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/a-more-ethical-approach-to-employing-contractors]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_02_645973167.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;对于公司来说，将劳动力外包给第三方的做法变得很有吸引力：他们可以获得经过预先筛选的灵活劳动力，并且能够卸载合法就业对其他人的责任。这一引人注目的机会已远远超出科技领域，扩展到医疗保健和物流等行业。不幸的是，这种劳动力模式对工人和公司来说都是有代价的。雇主有一种方法可以在不让工人受到伤害的情况下将责任外包出去——以及他们自己增加的责任&amp;#8212;采取六大支柱：1) 所有工人都应获得足以维持家庭生活的工资和福利，2) 同工同酬，3) 提供工作场所安全协议并给予工人发言权，4) 要求公平采购，5) 提供途径全职就业，6) 透明。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/a-more-ethical -approach-to-employing-contractors?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/a-more-ethical-approach-to-employing-contractors?language= pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;2022 年 11 月 3 日星期四，成千上万的 Twitter 员工不知道他们早上是否能找到工作。那些被推特直接聘用的人醒来时会收到一封电子邮件，里面要么是新的任务，要么是遣散费。但像梅丽莎·英格尔这样的合同工却一无所获。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;英格尔受雇在 Twitter 处理政治错误信息，努力确保中期选举不会受到机器人和恶作剧的影响。她和她的合同工同事赶紧检查收件箱中是否有决定电子邮件，但他们从未收到过。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;梅丽莎随后试图在接下来的一周专注于她的工作，在接下来的几天里解决错误信息到了 2022 年中期选举，她一直在想那一天是否会是她在公司的最后一天。 11 月 12 日星期六，当 Ingle 与女儿和朋友在商场时，她收到一条通知，上面写着“您的一个或多个访问令牌已被撤销”。她尝试打开工作电子邮件和 Slack，却收到一条通知：“不存在这样的用户”。梅丽莎就是这样被解雇的。没有开会讨论这个问题，甚至没有一封电子邮件——她就被删除了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/07/05/tech-layoffs- Contract-temp-workers/&quot;>;梅丽莎的经历并非独一无二&lt;/a>;。据估计，仅在加利福尼亚州，&lt;a href=&quot;https://americanstaffing.net/research/fact-sheets-analysis-staffing-industry-trends/staffing-statistics-by-state/&quot;>;每年就有近 200 万人&lt;/a >;&lt;a href=&quot;https://americanstaffing.net/research/fact-sheets-analysis-staffing-industry-trends/staffing-statistics-by-state/&quot;>;人们&lt;/a>;通常是合同工与直接雇用的同行做同样的工作，但工资更低，福利更差，保护也更少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于公司来说，将劳动力外包给第三方的做法变得有吸引力：他们获得预先筛选的、灵活的劳动力劳动力以及将合法就业的责任转移给其他人的能力。这一引人注目的机会已远远超出科技领域，扩展到医疗保健和物流等行业。人力资源服务公司 Gusto 发现，其平台上使用合同工的雇主数量&lt;a href=&quot;https://gusto.com/company-news/us-contract-work-2022-survey&quot;>;已自疫情爆发以来增加了 28%&lt;/a>;，平均公司的合同工与普通员工的比例接近 1 比 5。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，这种劳动力模式的对工人和公司来说都是成本。我们的研究表明，合同工——&lt;a href=&quot;https://contractwork.techequitycollaborative.org/&quot;>;更有可能是黑人、原住民、拉丁裔、女性和非二元性别&lt;/a>;——经常做同样的事情与直接受雇的同事一样工作，但赚的钱更少，领取的福利更少，而且工作不稳定。这种动态不仅让合同工受到伤害，也让公司面临一些巨大的风险。最初被认为是减少公司持续财务责任的系统，外包已成为一种法律、财务和声誉责任。法院和监管机构越来越多地发现，当工人受到伤害时，雇主应对这种伤害承担责任——无论他们是否是直接雇主。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;雇主有一种方法可以在不暴露工人的情况下承担责任。伤害——以及他们自己增加的责任。通过实施负责任的合同标准，确保工人享有基本保护和获得机会的途径，雇主可以降低他们的风险。实施这些标准还可以通过释放合格的多元化人才库来实现多样性、公平和包容性承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为我们在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techequitycollaborative.org 的研究的一部分/&quot;>;TechEquity Collaborative&lt;/a>;，我们创建了负责任的合同标准，作为公司实施明确、高标准合同实践的蓝图，使工人和公司都受益。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;危害和风险合同工&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;1996 年，长期服务的“临时”合同工起诉微软，要求其获得如果被归类为直接雇员的话可以获得的福利。工人们辩称，与直接雇员履行相同的工作职能并为相同的经理工作，他们有权获得相同的报酬。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/archive/business/2000/12/13/microsoft-to-settle-with-temp-workers/6f59576a-0725-4bea-93cc-3e2d759bda45/&quot;>;微软2000 年，该诉讼达成和解&lt;/a>;，此案为科技公司提供了从那时起如何处理合同工与直接雇佣之间的分离的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司已建立（通常很脆弱）防火墙和流程来避免分类合同工作为雇员——要求他们使用不同颜色的徽章进入大楼，禁止他们使用内部系统，禁止他们参加年度假日聚会等全员活动。同时，许多合同工的绩效管理和日常职责都由科技公司直接控制。与此同时，在微软诉讼之后，许多公司将他们的合同设计成不断旋转的门：员工从一份初始合同开始，通常为期六个月，而他们的经理则以重复的、较短的增量延长他们的工作时间。这些合同可以随时取消或不续签，使工人始终处于不稳定状态。这些工人中的许多人都处于这种短期无保障合同延期的模式长达两年，期间他们被迫休息，以免公司违反微软和解协议中规定的直接雇员资格标准。一旦他们离开公司长达六个月，他们中的许多人就会被重新雇佣，重新开始这个过程，暴露了他们是“临时”员工的闹剧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不仅是合同他们自己脱节了，但他们所从事的工作也是脱节的。合同工常常陷入双重管理结构的中间：他们的日常工作由母公司的经理监督，而他们的雇佣运作方面——处理工资、管理福利和处理工作场所投诉——则由母公司的经理监督。雇用他们的人事代理机构的职权范围。与合同工保持一定距离——无论是因为无法接触公司人力资源、内部工具和信息，还是职业发展——都会造成沟通渠道漏洞、权力失衡以及潜在的工人伤害。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;不幸的是，种族和性别不平等加剧了合同工作的不稳定（及其给公司带来的风险）。在科技行业，我们发现&lt;a href=&quot;https://contractwork.techequitycollaborative.org/&quot;>;合同工和临时工更有可能是黑人、原住民、拉丁裔、女性和非二元性别&lt;/a>;在直接就业的劳动力中。对伊利诺伊州蓝领工作临时工作的研究发现&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-temporary-staffing-agcies-racial-discrimination-20210223-34sof3i56rhjxhzu42xtcshx44-story。 html&quot;>;黑人和拉丁裔工人占芝加哥蓝领临时工作的 85%&lt;/a>;，但只占人口的 40%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有这些潜在危害，因种族和性别而更加复杂不平等，造成潜在的法律责任。如果一名工人遭受伤害——无论是工资和工时违规、骚扰、歧视还是充满敌意的工作环境——并决定针对这种伤害寻求补救措施，公司不一定能摆脱困境，即使他们辩称自己没有受到伤害。工人的合法雇主。法院和监管机构越来越多地发现这些公司与人才中介机构是共同雇主，因此应对合同工遭受的任何违法行为或伤害承担责任。过去五年来，科技行业发生了多起引人注目的此类动态实例。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;2021 年，Meta 同意&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.saverilawfirm. com/our-cases/facebook-content-moderators-safe-workplace-litigation/#:~:text=viewing%20objectionable%20conduct.-,The%20award%20also%20builtes%20a%20%2452%20million%20fund% 20for%20ongoing,financial%20compensation%20for%20content%20moderators.&quot;>;向内容版主支付 5200 万美元&lt;/a>;，这些内容版主是通过第三方人才中介机构聘用的，负责审查从儿童色情到自杀和兽交等令人不安的内容，而无需支付任何费用采取适当的健康和安全措施。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;在针对 Riot Games 的集体诉讼中，法官裁定合同工应纳入 2021 年&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost. com/video-games/2021/12/27/riot-discrimination-100-million-settlement/&quot;>;针对遭遇工作场所性别歧视和骚扰的 1 亿美元和解金&lt;/a>;。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;动视暴雪 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2022/03/29/1089577389/judge-activision-blizzard-settlement- Sex-harassment&quot;>;支付了 1800 万美元的和解金&lt;/a>;，以惩罚女性工人，包括直接员工和合同工，以及性骚扰和怀孕歧视。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;不采用高端合同做法的公司会造成逐底竞争，降低工作质量和职业流动性。制定高标准做法，并要求与您公司合作的任何供应商采取这些做法，有助于首先减轻工人受到伤害的可能性，从而有助于减少未来的责任和风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;前进之路：负责任的合同标准&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;简单地说，避免工人伤害责任的最佳方法是首先减少伤害的可能性。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techequitycollaborative.org/download-responsible-contracting-standard/&quot;>;责任承包标准&lt;/a>;提供了公司可以采取的六种明确途径，以减少工人伤害、降低企业风险并关闭工作场所合同工的股权差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;维持家庭的工资&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这一点非常简单 - 所有工人都应该获得维持家庭的工资和福利。通过明确您期望承包机构向合同工支付多少工资，您​​可以确保合同工获得足以维持家庭生活的工资——通常根本不需要提高您的合同预算。其他最佳实践包括要求人事代理机构提供维持家庭的福利、可预测的时间表、合同续签时的清晰沟通等等。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;同工同酬&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;所有现有研究表明与全职雇员从事相同工作的合同工的工资往往较低。您可以通过以下方式确保同工同酬：提供透明且响应迅速的加薪和晋升系统、要求职介机构报告薪资数据、将薪资与全职员工进行比较以及实施公平的招聘做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 >;工作场所安全协议和工人的声音&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;合同工经常面临选择，是大声说出工作场所的问题还是取消合同。建立清晰的报告问题渠道以及让合同工参与全公司的沟通流程，可以对直接员工和合同工等员工的工作场所士气做出积极贡献。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;公平采购&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一次性合同与全职劳动力相比，工人可能会遇到薪资差距，因为人事代理机构从合同中抽取的费用比您讨价还价的要高。通常，公司认为他们雇用合同工的速度与团队中其他员工相同，却没有意识到人才中介机构会大幅削减工资。要求人才中介机构披露他们的“加价”费用或工人的工资率可以帮助提高流程透明度，并帮助您的公司避免不公平的薪酬结构，而不必增加您的总体成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;直接就业的途径&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;有色人种合同工，尤其是黑人工人，更有可能经历过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.americanprogress.org/article/elimination-black-white-wealth-gap- Generational -挑战/&quot;>;积累财富的结构性障碍&lt;/a>;。解决职业隔离的一种方法是提供从合同职位到公司全职职位的有意义的途径。一些最佳实践包括允许员工在简历中分享他们为贵公司工作的经验、授予进入内部招聘委员会的权限、终止合同工的竞业禁止协议以及提供专业发展培训。通过打造真正的职业流动机会，您的公司可以利用经过资格预审的多元化人才库，这不仅可以提高公平性，还可以降低招聘成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;透明度&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;展示您的人才通过负责任的合同透明，体现公司对股东、员工和公众的价值观和承诺。衡量供应商对这些实践的采用情况、审核标准的实施情况以及直接与员工进行核对以了解更多有关他们的经验 - 所有这些都有助于确保您雇用的人才中介机构正确应用您的书面政策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•••&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;负责任的承包不仅仅涉及风险缓解。除了作为固有商业价值的“做正确的事”之外，负责任的承包是一项吸引和培养人才、提高员工士气、产生回报和提升品牌的投资。前期投资将帮助您的公司实现包容性承诺并获得收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Pandemic Changed Marketing Channels]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Adrià Voltà 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;疫情无疑改变了营销人员实施渠道策略的方式，并且没有单一的成功途径。由于渠道比以往任何时候都多，营销人员需要确定哪些渠道可以增加明显的价值，而忘记其他渠道。进入某个渠道可能很诱人，因为那里有你的竞争对手。但由于客户时间和注意力有限，营销人员必须战略性地确定他们可以在哪些渠道中产生最大的影响。作者研究了从 CMO 调查中收集到的五种大流行后渠道策略，并分析了营销人员如何运用这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how- the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 大流行促使公司快速适应和响应新的客户需求。这种动态最明显的方式之一是公司为与客户互动并向客户销售产品而采用的营销渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，发生了什么变化？最新版本的&lt;a href=&quot;https://cmosurvey.org/results/&quot;>;CMO 调查&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;从 314 位美国营销领导者那里收集到了五个主要趋势。我们还提供分析和建议，帮助营销人员落实这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;渠道正在扩大。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近三分之二 (61%) 的公司表示增加了他们使用的渠道数量。虽然 B2B 和 B2C 公司都如此，但 B2C 服务领先，77% 的公司表示有所增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;渠道扩张的一个好处是，消费者现在可以选择自己喜欢的与公司互动的方式。然而，拓展渠道需要大量的努力和投资。在介入之前，营销团队应该问：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;新渠道是否会吸引新客户进入该类别，从竞争对手那里抢走现有客户，还是增加现有客户的钱包份额？&lt;/li>; &lt; li>;从品牌和客户体验的角度来看，更多的渠道是否一致？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;接触点是否指向相同的利益和品牌形象？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;渠道是否无缝连接？&lt; /li>; &lt;li>;客户是否了解他们通过使用不同渠道获得的价值以及如何在这些渠道之间轻松移动？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;面对面 (F2F) 渠道仍然存在好吧。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;只有 6.7% 的公司表示他们的 F2F 渠道已完全数字化，这意味着大多数公司仍保持 F2F。此外，28% 的公司正在开设新的 F2F 渠道。&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;鉴于公司和市场的数字化转型，我们预计 F2F 渠道将大幅减少。我们认为渠道持续存在的原因有三个。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，消费者&lt;a href=&quot;https://siteefy.com/how-many-ads-do-we-see-a-day/ &quot;>;每天&lt;/a>;接触 5,000 到 10,000 个广告。这种数字混乱很难渗透，因此保持面对面的方式可能会为营销人员提供不同的方式来接触消费者并实现突破。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，消费者表示，由于使用的应用程序数量和屏幕交互次数过多，他们感到数字疲劳。平均一天 — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lxahub.com/stories/what-is-digital-event-fatigue-and-how-can-marketers-avoid-it&quot;>;级别&lt;/a>;疫情期间增幅超过100%。因此，我们怀疑许多人在他们忙碌的数字生活中渴望人际互动。消费者还&lt;a href=&quot;https://escp.eu/news/why-consumers-seek-refuge-products-branded-authentic-pandemic-and-post-pandemic-era&quot;>;想要更多的真实性&lt;/a>;，这是对过去三年的风险和不确定性的自然反应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三，许多公司将实体店等 F2F 渠道视为了解消费者行为的实验室。他们正在利用先进技术，例如物联网连接的商品和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-footfall-analysis-why-important-geoiq-io/&quot;>;客流量分析&lt; /a>;，更多地了解客户的需求以及他们在旅程中的行为方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，我们确实观察到样本中的一些差异，这些差异可能有助于诊断您的 F2F 渠道的需求行业。与服务公司 (22%) 相比，产品公司不太可能完全数字化，并且更有可能开设新的 F2F 渠道 (31%)。只有纯粹的互联网公司才不会开通F2F渠道。新的面对面渠道在房地产、零售和通信/媒体领域最为普遍，而在医疗保健、制药/生物技术和技术领域则最不常见。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;品牌社交媒体的使用正在扩大。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近一半 (45%) 的公司现在使用社交渠道来销售产品和服务，其中 (61.5%) 的 B2C 服务公司正在使用社交渠道。在这一领域，房地产公司 (100%)、通信/媒体公司 (82%) 和零售商/批发商 (70%) 处于领先地位。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;社交媒体公司，例如 Snapchat、Facebook 和Instagram 在疫情大流行的第一年就实现了创纪录的电子商务销售额。 Instagram 在 2020 年推出的应用内结账功能可能会加速这一过程，为覆盖更多&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/183585/instagram-number-of-global-users /&quot;>;12 亿&lt;/a>; 用户滚动他们的社交信息流。 Furthermore, the ease of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.hootsuite.com/how-social-commerce-is-reshaping-customer-experience/#Social_channels_are_the_new_storefronts&quot;>;social messaging&lt;/a>; allows marketers to engage in real time with customers to answer questions. In 2022, more than half of US adults &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.insiderintelligence.com/insights/social-commerce-brand-trends-marketing-strategies/&quot;>;purchased&lt;/a>; something through a social media channel, and a Sprout Social &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/data/social-shopping-2022/&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; found 98% expected to use this channel to make a purchase in the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take the example of Scrub Daddy, which has established a cheeky TikTok personality and collaborated with up-and-coming social media influencers, resulting in billions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foodandwine.com/scrub-daddy-review-trend-7483598#:~:text=Designed%20to%20make%20the%20often,3%20billion%20views%20on%20TikTok.&quot;>;views&lt;/a>; and millions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90756764/how-to-find-tiktok-influencers-scrub-daddy&quot;>;followers&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals.com/philadelphia/news/2022/02/21/how-viral-tiktok-fame-propelling-scrub-daddy-100m.html&quot;>;online sales&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When we think about brands on social media, we tend to envision B2C brands. Indeed, those companies are more likely to sell their products and services on social channels (58%) compared to B2B brands (37%). However, there is a place for B2B companies in this world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take the case of &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1525/cmr.2014.56.3.142?casa_token=cu8dtuoZwScAAAAA:dv3SkiOmyT4Vr0cgFpqQlEI8v_hFu0w9ij_uacVoe61fl5egMUdQnKhWj3py-wCL1w2d1ioAWetWakc&quot;>;Maersk&lt;/a>;, the Danish shipping company, which launched a social media campaign more than a decade ago to build its brand reputation. Managers were surprised to find that 22% of its 850,000 Facebook followers were actual customers (even though Maersk was not yet selling shipping services online). Leveraging this channel for feedback and follow-up sales was a natural next step for the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, it has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/linkedin-statistics/&quot;>;reported&lt;/a>; that 89% of B2B marketers turn to LinkedIn to generate leads. These numbers are encouraging and we expect they will only increase as younger, social media-savvy consumers move into management positions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The D2C revolution has begun. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Almost a quarter (24%) of companies added a direct-to-customer (D2C) channel in 2023. B2C product companies led the charge with 41% of brands adopting this channel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Why are brands moving into D2C channels? First and most importantly, D2C allows companies to gather valuable firsthand insights into customer online behavior and needs — an opportunity companies in certain sectors, such as consumer packaged goods (CPG), have historically lacked. This first-party data is more important than ever given growing privacy restrictions on access to third-party data around the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, D2C lets companies test new strategies and collect valuable feedback. If used wisely, this type of experimentation should yield more effective and efficient strategies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, D2C means companies can control the customer experience with the brand. This is especially important for premium and unique brands that deliver their benefits, in part, through the channels experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given these reasons, we weren&#39;t surprised to find that 55% of CPG companies report adding D2C. B2C services made the biggest leap — up from 15% in 2022 to 45% in 2023.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tesla has fully embraced the D2C revolution. The company sells its vehicles directly to customers through its online platform and national network of retail stores in major urban centers in US By bypassing traditional car dealerships, Tesla is able to control the sales experience (and markups), which most consumers find unpleasant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies should consider two important factors before entering this space. First, does the company have a robust &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adroll.com/blog/what-is-d2c-and-why-does-it-matter#:~:text=A%20Better%20Connection%20With%20Customers&amp;amp;text=By%20offering%20a%20more%20streamlined,loyalty%20and%20encourage%20repeat%20business.&quot;>;digital&lt;/a>; footprint in place to analyze and execute D2C strategies? This is important considering D2C models&#39; reliance on digital marketing, social media, and data analytics skills to deliver positive returns. Also, does the brand have customer-service structures ready to handle the likely increase in customer interactions from this direct channel?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To prevent partners from moving direct to consumers, we recommend distributors and other intermediaries provide value-added services in marketing, inventory, or logistics. Sharing customer data and analytics can also foster long-lasting and mutually beneficial partnerships between organizations. Another powerful partnership strategy is to leverage cross-category perspectives to share recommendations with key partners for new products, in-store advertising and promotion strategies, and even potential acquisition targets. The point is: provide value!&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gamification is underutilized. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gamifying shopping and other customer interactions via rewards, points, competitions, or other similar fun interactions is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/PressReleases/gamification.asp&quot;>;expected&lt;/a>; to grow from $9.1B in 2020 to $30.7B in 2025 — a 237% increase.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite this, only 4.8% of marketers integrated gamification into digital channels to sell. B2C product companies (13%) and companies with sales of $10 billion or higher (23%) are outpacing other sectors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large-scale research of the effect of gamification on brand outcomes has not been performed. However, practitioner &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/growth-marketing-and-sales/our-insights/coping-with-the-big-switch-how-paid-loyalty-programs-can-help-bring-consumers-back-to-your-brand&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; has shown that loyalty programs do increase the likelihood that customers will choose the brand over competitors, pay higher prices, and increase their spending levels. Gamification, we suspect, is only likely to heighten these effects. Given this, we think this low percentage is a missed opportunity for many companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The key to making gamification work is brand fit – the game has to make sense given the brand&#39;s position and associations. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webpronews.com/business-leveraging-gamification/&quot;>;Fitbit&lt;/a>;&#39;s exercise milestones and friendly competitions help consumers gain more benefits from their devices and increase the likelihood they&#39;ll buy more products and recommend them to their friends. The game also needs to be engaging, but low-cost or free. If either of these elements are missing, current and potential customers will not play. Therefore, marketers must understand what motivates and delights their customers and use small-scale experiments to test different approaches to assess these costs and benefits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Gamification is more daunting for B2B companies. Our findings show only 1% of B2B companies are using this strategy, compared to 13% of B2C companies. Using gamification with employees who serve B2B customers, including your salesforce, is perhaps the easiest way to begin the process. Another option is to introduce gamification during webinars that are generally somewhat boring. This may provide a way to keep attending prospects paying closer attention to sales pitches.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate and Deploy New Channels Strategically &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The pandemic undoubtedly changed how marketers approach channel strategy, and there is no single route to success. With more channels than ever, marketers need to map which channels add clear value and forget the rest. It can be tempting to enter a channel because your competitors are there. But with limited customer time and attention, marketers must strategically determine in which channels they can have the greatest impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:55:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Using AI to Build Stronger Connections with Customers]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_1500238081.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As companies learn to use generative AI to create value, there&amp;#8217;sa risk that they take the wrong approach when applying the technology to the customer experience. In fact, research shows AI can help boost customer satisfaction when it&amp;#8217;s used to offer customers more personalized solutions or to help human employees provide better service than they would without the technological assist. Some examples of companies experiencing early success with this are in the financial services industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The surge of generative artificial intelligence (AI) applications is spurring exciting innovations and consumer experiments, but it also worries many people who are concerned about data privacy or only being able to communicate with a company through a bot. These concerns are especially acute in industries where customer interactions and data privacy are critical, such as banking or healthcare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some level of anxiety typically accompanies breakthrough technologies, and it&#39;s natural to worry about a technology that mimics human intelligence. As this new class of large language models has emerged, however, most companies have put model risk, accuracy of the model&#39;s output, and ethical use of data at the heart of their risk frameworks. They aim to ensure responsible uses of new AI technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Less appreciated is the risk that companies will cede the customer experience to models and bots designed to extract value in the short term, not to foster long-term customer loyalty. Companies might increasingly pair traditional AI and machine learning models with generative AI to deliver messages and offers to customers in more human-like ways. If we are not careful, profit-seeking bots, algorithms, and predictive models could indeed lead to dystopian experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even in the world of AI, customer love should lead the way. Traditional metrics of customer sentiment, such as Net Promoter Score (NPS), may start to look different, but one premise will endure: Every interaction enhances or diminishes a customer&#39;s perception the company involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Informing each decision with the goal of enriching customers&#39; lives will lay down a reliable route to an AI-enabled future that creates more value for customers, employees, and shareholders. In fact, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w31161/w31161.pdf&quot;>;early published results&lt;/a>; from researchers at Stanford University and Massachusetts Institute of Technology show favorable effects from the rollout of an AI-based conversational assistant tool to 5,200 customer support agents in several countries. Not only did the tool raise agent productivity by 14% on average, but the AI-assisted interactions had higher average NPS, and monthly agent attrition dropped by 9%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Make It Personal&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Orienting AI around customer love requires a fundamental rethink of objective functions. Most existing algorithms optimize around ROI for a particular moment rather than around an entire experience. AI-enabled customer engagement holds the promise of a company learning more from each interaction and finding more ways to create value for customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s a good sign because customers increasingly expect more personalized, relevant experiences and are open to sharing their data in return. Bain &amp;amp; Company&#39;s latest survey of almost 30,000 banking customers in 11 countries found that the respondents who agreed that their bank personalizes the experience are more likely to reward it with a higher NPS. There&#39;s a 123-point difference in NPS between respondents who strongly agree that their bank interacts based on knowing who they are and those who strongly disagree.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One way AI refines personalization is through digital assistants for customers, as shown by emerging efforts in banking and payments. Royal Bank of Canada uses an AI-enabled assistant called NOMI to personalize digital money management for customers. Features include timely tips pushed to clients, personalized budgets, and savings recommendations based on spending behavior and cash flow. In the year following its launch, the results were promising, with 50% more&amp;nbsp;digital interactions for NOMI customers relative to the entire customer base, 93% more time spent on financial accounts, and 2% attrition of NOMI customers vs. 8% for their peers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Generative AI digital assistants are also helping employees to strengthen their customer connections, reinforcing the places where a human touch may be a source of differentiation. Morgan Stanley Wealth Management, for instance, is rolling out an AI assistant to help its thousands of financial advisers better support their clients in a personalized way. The assistant combines search and content creation so that financial advisers can quickly find and tailor the right information for each client at any moment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large language models will enable a new era of personalization. Machine learning techniques already turn each customer&#39;s pattern of digital interactions into a unique behavioral “fingerprint,” and recent AI advances will now enable these fingerprints to include speech and text interactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Help employees help their customers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Companies should start with a few no-regrets cases to get the organization comfortable with generative AI technology. These typically use AI to help employees who deliver aspects of the customer experience so that humans can vet the model&#39;s output. Examples include suggestions to relationship managers for the next conversation with a customer based on recent engagement or providing specific actions for handling collections with customers facing financial hardship.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next wave of cases would feature AI embedded in standard operating procedures for employees. Promising cases include predictive routing of a customer&#39;s inquiry to the agent best equipped to handle a particular issue or real-time script recommendations for relationship managers. The technology will listen to a customer call in real time and help agents know whether their interactions are creating a promoter or a detractor Other employee-supporting features in the near future could include devising a personalized offer with images and text that evoke a customer&#39;s favorite hobby or reminding a relationship manager to call on a customer during key life stages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a few industries such as retail, a fully AI-enabled front line is starting to support automated engagement directly with customers. Over time, this digital front line could deliver service with the same thoughtful empathy as traditional human front lines. Bots will engage with customers and learn to serve up relevant products and information just as the best employees have always done. The best uses of AI may even completely reimagine the overall experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a time of high inflation and tight economics, some managers may be tempted to use generative AI technology only to cut costs and improve efficiency. That would be misguided. While generative AI has the potential to bend the cost curve in many industries, the greatest value will come to those companies that focus on enriching the lives of their customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Secure Support for Your ERG&rsquo;s Initiatives]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_1058899848.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Maren Caruso/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Employee resource groups are essential in fostering belonging and advancing potential, and they need support to be able to continue to do that. But given cost cutting, lack of cultural awareness, and increasing pressure&amp;#160;to slash DEI budgets,&amp;#160;the challenges many identity groups or social causes face can slip through the cracks.&amp;#160;In such challenging circumstances, how can ERG members galvanize and get the attention their networks need to influence and have impact? The author presents several strategies based on her work with people facing similar challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Employee resource groups, more commonly known as staff networks in the UK, have served as important vehicles for promoting inclusion and advocating for traditionally underestimated segments of workers with shared identities and interests. Unfortunately, many ERGs aren&#39;t given the resources, budget, and attention they need to fulfill that promise. Here are some concerns I&#39;ve seen in my work coaching individuals and delivering talks to ERGs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;How can I secure more budget allocation to support my faith-based ERG?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Why is my organization not running charity campaigns for floods in Pakistan or earthquakes in Turkey and Syria?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;My organization has an active women&#39;s network but lacks focus on intersectionality. How do I get them to prioritize this?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Given cost cutting, lack of cultural awareness, and increasing pressure&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mo-house-passes-budget-that-slashes-diversity-initiatives-defunds-libraries/ar-AA19jWvC&quot;>;to slash DEI budgets&lt;/a>;,&amp;nbsp;the challenges many identity groups or social causes face can slip through the cracks.&amp;nbsp;In such challenging circumstances, how can ERG members galvanize and get the attention their networks need to influence and have impact? Here are a few strategies based on how I&#39;ve supported people with similar challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Know Your Why&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, get clarity on what exactly you want to achieve and what the added support would mean for you and your fellow ERG members. For example, Nadia* sought my advice on how to request a dedicated Wudu area for &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;Muslim colleagues&lt;/a>;, while Hamza wanted to host an annual Iftar party during Ramadan. Despite the existence of faith networks at their companies, both faced obstacles due to their organizations&#39; reluctance to make “&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy&quot;>;special religious arrangements&lt;/a>;.” Meanwhile, Akua, who was member of a women&#39;s network at her company, wanted to organize a conference for women of color that would focus solely on the challenges faced by women from Black, Asian, and multiethnic backgrounds. However, she was told that the organization would only fund the women&#39;s network initiatives that championed “all women.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As disappointing as this was and despite the resistance from their respective organizations, I encouraged all three to take time to reflect on why these initiatives were essential to them. My goal was to help them solidify their ask and improve their chances of achieving their outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To get others on board with your ideas, start affirming your outcomes based on what you want to happen, not what you want to avoid. Additionally, take the time to consider the resources required, potential obstacles, and how your desired outcome will impact the system as a whole. By staying focused on your purpose, you can increase your sense of ownership and strengthen your conviction when presenting your idea to others. Here are some of the questions I asked Nadia, Hamza, and Akua to answer:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Why do you want this? What purpose does it serve and value does it provide?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What, where, when, and with whom will you achieve this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What are the internal and external resources required to realize this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What will you gain or lose by achieving this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is your action plan?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What changes would your desired outcome bring about in the larger system, and what will happen if you don&#39;t get to that outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will you monitor progress or overcome any challenges?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will you measure the impact of this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once these questions have been answered, it&#39;s time to move on to preparing the business case. It may be helpful to keep revisiting the above as priorities evolve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Prepare Your Business Case&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that you&#39;ve identified your why, it&#39;s time to get ready to make your case to leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most organizations operate on a “what&#39;s in it for me?” basis.&amp;nbsp;Cherron Inko Tariah MBE, author of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em>;The Incredible Power of Staff Networks&lt;/em>;, encourages asking yourself the following questions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Are you aware of what&#39;s happening in the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Do you know the workplace culture and the issues facing the business? What&#39;s at the top of your CEO&#39;s inbox?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What was discussed at the last board meeting?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What are the HR leader&#39;s priorities?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s important to ensure that any new initiative aligns with the company&#39;s overall goals and strategies. This is exactly what Nadia did when she presented her case for a &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;Wudu sink&lt;/a>;. She was able to clearly show how this provision would support the company&#39;s goal of becoming one of the top inclusive employers within three years. By linking her proposal to that larger goal, she was able to gain the support needed to move forward and make it a reality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Measuring and regularly tracking progress can significantly impact how an ERG and its activities are seen and valued. To make a compelling business case, ERG leaders must gauge their work&#39;s effectiveness and calculate the&amp;nbsp;return on investment&amp;nbsp;for their efforts. Metrics such as membership numbers and participation, satisfaction, and retention rates are excellent tools to leverage. To help you substantiate the need for and interest in your initiative, use pulse surveys to capture sentiment and solicit feedback from your members. Equally important is making adjustments as necessary to ensure that your ERG is meeting its goals and adding value to your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, you can also help build your case by evaluating the global and intercultural benefits of your ERG&#39;s activity. Help leaders consider a macro perspective: How will the initiative affect individuals, work groups, customers, and the global organization? For example, Salman, a member of the Black Asian multiethnic network at his company&#39;s London office, wanted to initiate a campaign to collect funds for victims of floods in Pakistan during South Asian Heritage Month last year. However, he received little support from colleagues and managers, as they had recently donated to refugees of the war in Ukraine. Additionally, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2022/mar/02/civilised-european-look-like-us-racist-coverage-ukraine&quot;>;people tend to support those they can relate to&lt;/a>; or champion causes that get more international attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salman reached out to his colleagues in the company&#39;s South Asia location and used their help and experience to garner interest at the London office through storytelling. After learning how the floods had affected families of employees working in the Pakistan region, the London office was more inclined to take action.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s also valuable to collect information and share examples of how best-in-class companies (including competitors) are addressing your cause and encouraging others to join the alliance. To help get support at her company, Hamza gathered information on similar organizations that had successfully led Ramadan campaigns at their respective organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At this stage, it&#39;s understandable that you&#39;re keen to press forward, but making your case tactfully is crucial; engaging in the conversation with humility while avoiding comparisons and “&lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/whataboutism-what-it-is-and-why-its-such-a-popular-tactic-in-arguments-182911&quot;>;whataboutism&lt;/a>;” is more likely to yield a successful result. Attempts to minimize other groups or initiate a competing narrative when fighting for your right to be heard or seen will backfire and make you lose support from different identity groups. When we draw comparisons, we neither heal nor drive positive change. It shouldn&#39;t be a case of “this or that” but rather “this &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; that.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider starting your conversation with leadership like this: “I appreciate the organization&#39;s focus on inclusion. I have thoroughly enjoyed being part of XYZ network and can see the positive impact it has created. Encouraged by the influence, I propose an initiative for XYX.” Then you can elaborate on why what you&#39;re asking for is essential, including the data you&#39;ve gathered.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Gather Support&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The company will only consider your case if there&#39;s sufficient interest, so once your “why” is clear and you&#39;ve prepared a business case, it&#39;s time to rally support.&amp;nbsp;When I asked Nadia if there were other employees she could rely on, she affirmed there were quite a few. She then created an internal Google form survey and gathered responses from colleagues who shared the benefits of a separate a Wudu sink for their Muslim and non-Muslim colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, it was necessary to get senior leaders involved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at-work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;McKinsey research found&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;that ERG leaders who have strong ties to executives are better able to obtain resources and funding than those with weak ties. Speaking to allies and sponsors you can count on for&amp;nbsp;support is vital. Hamza did exactly this and was able to bring many on board for her Iftar celebration — in fact, some were even eager to participate in a Ramadan Challenge before partaking in the Iftar celebration. Taking advantage of solid connections and visible supporters higher up within the ranks can be a significant bolster for the initiative to be taken seriously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even if you don&#39;t have sufficient numbers from your identity group to advocate for your initiative, you can look to other ERGs to support you. Here&#39;s one possible way to approach the conversation with ERG leaders:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I loved being part of your network&#39;s initiative; my participation has helped me recognize why your network is important and why it&#39;s essential to have our needs seen and acknowledged. Inspired by you, I&#39;ve asked management to allocate resources to XYZ. Can I count on the support of your network as I prepare to approach them?&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;The advantage of this is twofold: Not only will you have their backing, but because it&#39;s not uncommon for ERGs to combine resources and jointly advocate for social impact initiatives, they may even organize or run programs for you if you&#39;re unsuccessful securing what you need. But remember that such mutually beneficial associations rely on reciprocity — if you expect them to help, you must also be a visible ally for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Be Specific and Prepare to Pivot&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the earlier example, when Salman wanted to organize a charity drive for flood victims in Pakistan, he took charge of the initiative. He asked for specific things he needed: using the office&#39;s hall to hold a bake sale, mentioning the campaign in the company newsletter and a company-wide email, and using the office kitchen to store goods.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be prepared to pivot when you don&#39;t get what you ask for. Prepare a sliding scale of asks and try to secure minimum commitment to start the conversation. If the company doesn&#39;t grant the budget for an event, perhaps ask them to at least send a company-wide email showing support and solidarity. Also, see if you can tie in with other networks and share resources or budgets. Remember, a “no” doesn&#39;t mean a “no” forever — revisit the ask in a few weeks or months as circumstances change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ERGs are essential in fostering belonging and advancing potential, and they need support to be able to continue to do that. Organizations need to include all identity groups and champion all social causes equally, but it&#39;s naïve to expect that to happen without a substantial push. Systemic inequities and organizational bias permeate most organizations, and leaders will remain complacent if they aren&#39;t actively challenged. Navigating a system where some voices are often trivialized or go unheard altogether requires ERG leaders and members to be resourceful and project their asks more strategically. Waiting for organizations to take that initiative may translate into a very long wait — better to push and be heard than not be heard at all.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* Names have been changed throughout to protect privacy.&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Value of Digital Transformation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_NiyiAdeogun.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Niyi Adeogun&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort. Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate. To see where digital transformation creates value, the authors used McKinsey&amp;#8217;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. They found that digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards, often by creating value that&amp;#8217;s hard to copy.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“Show me the money!” Cuba Gooding Jr., playing Rod Tidwell, made those words a cultural touchstone in the movie &lt;em>;&lt;i>;Jerry McGuire&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;. He was not just voicing his concerns about committing to a sports agent, played by Tom Cruise in this case; he was also questioning Cruise&#39;s commitment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Business leaders, shareholders, and board members have increasingly been saying the same thing — albeit using different words — when it comes to their company&#39;s digital and AI transformations. While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/three-new-mandates-for-capturing-a-digital-transformations-full-value&quot;>;only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift&lt;/a>; and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That track record begs some tough questions: Is all this digital effort worth it? Do I really need to lead my industry or is being a fast-follower a smarter strategy? Can I create digital and AI capabilities that give me a lasting competitive advantage or is this just the price of doing business in the modern age?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate, as we argue in our book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/rewired&quot;>;&lt;em>;&lt;i>;Rewired: How to Outcompete in the Age of Digital and AI&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;. But using proprietary data, we&#39;ve found just how and where digital transformations create value — and what businesses can do to beat the competition.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Hard Evidence, Real Value&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Hard evidence that directly ties digital and AI transformation to improvements in operational KPIs and financial performance is scant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To redress this issue, we turned to banking, a sector that has enough of a history with digital transformations to produce meaningful findings and where we own a unique longitudinal dataset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we used McKinsey&#39;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. We then isolated performance in two metrics — the percentage of mobile adoption by their customer base and the percentage of sales originated in digital channels — to define 20 digital leaders and 20 digital laggards. These two metrics are broadly recognized in the industry as core indicators of a digital retail banking model.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, we combined this data with McKinsey&#39;s Corporate Performance Analytics to see how banks ultimately perform against financial metrics (eg, total shareholder return, growth, expenses). We then ran a blind assessment (ie, the identity of the banks was hidden) of the maturity of digital and AI capabilities of the leading and lagging banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The findings have been striking: Digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders achieved average annual total shareholder returns of 8.1% vs. 4.9% for laggards. Leaders also had significantly better return on pre-tax tangible equity (ROTE), growing it from 15.5% in 2018 to 19.3% in 2022, vs. a more modest growth from 13.6% to 15.3% for laggards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This financial outperformance is a result of leaders&#39; success in growing revenue and better containing expense growth. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders have grown their active customer base at 0.5% and their retail revenues at 0.8% annually, while digital laggards saw zero growth in their active customer base and a decline of 1.4% per year on retail revenues. During the same period, leaders&#39; operating expenses grew at 1.3% per year, while laggards grew at almost twice that (2.3% per year). So, how are leaders able to outcompete so demonstrably?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Creating Value That&#39;s Hard to Copy&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Where does value come from? Let&#39;s look under the “digital hood.” Both digital leaders and laggards are growing adoption of their mobile app at the same rate, with a gap of 14 to 15 percentage points between them staying constant over time. (See below chart.) This is not surprising. As soon as a bank introduces a new mobile app feature, others see it and follow suit relatively quickly. The mobile app is table stakes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Turning to digital sales provides a much more insightful answer. Here, the gap between leaders and laggards is growing fast, with leaders almost doubling their advantage over laggards over the five-year period. In fact, digital leaders grew digital sales from 40% to 70%, while digital laggards grew from 8% to 17%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reason for this large differential is that to drive digital sales, leading banks go well beyond the mobile app to digitally transform what&#39;s hard to see and hard to copy: the end-to-end process from origination to fulfillment to servicing. To do this, they must orchestrate hundreds of teams capable of developing digital and AI innovations, day-in, day-out, across all their customer journeys and core business processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the front end of this process, for example, leading digital banks deploy personalization analytics and digital marketing campaigns to bring relevant offers to (potential) customers. In the middle of this process, they create an omnichannel experience where branch and contact center professionals have the tools and data to support customers at any stage of the sales journey, even if that journey was started online. These leading banks also provide customer approvals in real time, thanks to automated credit-risk decisioning. At the back end of the process, they drive customer self-servicing through well-designed digital workflows enabled by a modern data architecture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The value of this approach to transformation is also revealed in contact center staffing. Laggards saw an increase of 20% over the past five years, as they were unable to contain inbound calls from customers that enter digital channels. In contrast, digital leaders were able to decrease contact center staffing by 11% as they benefited from their ability to fully fulfill customer demand online and provide effective self-servicing capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361201&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Knowing what to do is important, but executing on the “how” is what makes the difference. Let&#39;s see how a US bank did it for its secured lending business. Traditionally, the bank took about 45 days for a customer to secure a loan, on average. The process involved multiple documentation requests to customers (eg, pay stubs, W2s, letters of explanation), and back-end processes (eg, initial file review, file assignment, ad hoc reports) were highly manual.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To transform this journey, the bank&#39;s leadership team reinvented the entire process. To speed pre-approvals, they developed a database of tens of millions of US households combining credit, property and income attributes using internal and external data sources. This data allowed them to generate personalized pre-approved offers that customers could accept with one click. They built a mobile-first customer experience, where customers could personalize their offers based on real-time data and finalize a pre-filled application, either on mobile or with the assistance of a bank employee. They redesigned key processes (eg, specialized loan “assembly lines”), automated key tasks (eg, initial file scrub), and developed digital tools for operators to drive productivity (eg, daily workflow management). And they modernized credit policy execution to enable greater use of data in underwriting (eg, using direct deposit data for income), while maintaining or increasing risk controls for the bank.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To enable all these innovations, they implemented key technology and data capabilities, including a customer data platform, AI/ML models (eg, propensity models), data products (eg, income), a digital app for customers and a workflow tool for the fulfillment center, all deployed on a cloud-based platform-as-a-service infrastructure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, this transformation required more than a dozen use-cases across the entire journey and massive change management programs (eg, training, retooling) for agents in branches, contact centers, and operations. But, only 18 months after the initial launch, the approval process was shortened from 28 to 7 days. This leap allowed the bank to become a leading secured lending originator and increase originations by 35%, while reducing origination cost by 20%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Capabilities Needed to Outcompete&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A company that aspires to outperform needs to do the kind of end-to-end changes the bank above did across dozens of customer journeys and core business processes. That&#39;s only possible when it is rewired with differentiated capabilities. Our study of more than 200 large-scale digital and AI transformations isolated the six core capabilities rewired companies develop:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Creating ambitious and focused transformation roadmaps&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. This requires business leaders to align their efforts on specific domains (eg, journeys or processes) that matter to customers and generate significant value.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Building a quality digital talent bench&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. Leaders prioritize creating an environment that attracts top-notch engineers and allows them to thrive (eg, tailored career tracks, autonomy).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;An operating model &lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;where hundreds of small cross-functional “pods” made up of business, engineering, and resources from control functions are mobilized against priority solutions. A single journey (or product) owner responsible for the end-to-end experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;A distributed technology environment and modern software engineering practices&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; to allow the entire organization&amp;nbsp;— not just IT&amp;nbsp;— to develop digital and AI-based solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Data products and modern data architecture&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; that make it easy for different parts of the organization to consume data for their own applications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Change management to ensures digital solutions are adopted and can scale&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; by making them easy to use and reuse across the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our blind assessment of these capabilities for the leaders and laggards, we found that leaders stand out across the board on these capabilities. No single one explains their success. All are needed. With that baseline, the most differentiated capabilities are talent and operating model, not technology. Over time, these capabilities create ever-improving customer experiences and drive lower unit cost. Financial rewards follow.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361204&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_CAPABILITIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While our research has focused on banking, our experience reflects similar lessons and patterns in every industry, whether B2B or B2C, products, or services. A digital and AI transformation, however, cannot be done in “special project” mode. To pull this off, the entire organization must be able to deliver constant digital innovation, which requires a holistic set of capabilities. The effort is significant, but so is the reward.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:55:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Keep Your Audience Focused During a Presentation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_1029427796.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;AndreyPopov/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&amp;#8217;s focus is critical to communication success. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it. In this piece, the author outlines three techniques &amp;#8212; physical, mental, and linguistic &amp;#8212; to engage your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Attention is our most precious commodity. In today&#39;s fast-paced world of always-on digital devices and round-the-clock media cycles, getting our audience&#39;s attention is critical to our communication success. With so many distractions vying for our time, we must actively seek and gain our audience&#39;s attention first.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, capturing ears and eyes isn&#39;t enough. Getting attention is only the first battle; keeping it is another challenge entirely. That&#39;s why smart communicators not only actively deploy ways to capture attention, but they work to sustain it. Sustained attention is what I call &lt;em>;engagement&lt;/em>;. If you can engage your audience, they will stay focused and be less distracted. Plus, you will have a better shot at demonstrating the relevance and significance of your topic to them. To that end, here are three approaches to engaging your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Three Ways to Engage Your Audience&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Physical Engagement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Where the body goes, the brain will follow. Anything that gets your audience doing something with their bodies will create engagement. Whether you are giving an in-person pitch or presentation, or conducting a virtual meeting, think about how you can include physical engagement in your activities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, you can have people watch a video, read a handout, click on something on their screens, raise their hands, or use virtual reactions. All of these require your audience to become participants in your communication, not just observers. A simple invitation to “Turn to the person next to you and greet them” or “Read what is on the slide and share your thoughts” can get them involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Mental Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Fight back against your audience&#39;s tendency to zone out or multitask by fostering cognitive engagement. There are three simple ways to do this: ask questions throughout your presentation; incorporate provocative statements, data, and stats; and introduce smart analogies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you ask a question, people almost automatically start to consider their answer, thereby moving them from passive listening to active participation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Provocative statements or &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/present-your-data-like-a-pro&quot;>;compelling data&lt;/a>; ignite curiosity and encourage your audience to internally ask their own questions. For example, if you&#39;re trying to justify headcount for your training department, you could say: “30% of our customer service tickets could be eliminated by training users better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Analogies are where we compare what we know to what we don&#39;t know; in other words, we &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/finding-the-right-metaphor-for-your-presentation&quot;>;use the familiar to explain the unfamiliar&lt;/a>;. Invoking analogies invites involvement by making us actively think. One caveat: When you use analogies, make sure they&#39;re ones people can readily relate to. Over-reliance on sports metaphors or on complex comparisons people cannot follow or understand will work against your goal of engagement and greater understanding.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Linguistic Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Linguistic engagement refers to the use of inclusive words, time-traveling language, and references to shared perspectives or experiences. Inclusive wording means inviting people into your communication. For instance, we&#39;re hardwired to perk up when we hear our own name, as well as when we hear the word “you.” Mention participants&#39; names, and use phrases like “As you know…” or “You may be wondering…” or “Today, you will learn…”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Time-traveling language takes people from the present into the future or the past. You can use phrases like “Imagine…” or “What if you could…” or “Picture this…” to take people into the future. “Remember when…” or “Think back to when…” will take people into the past. Connect people through shared experiences or beliefs to create common ground. For instance, highlighting your company&#39;s mission and values or referencing a previous shared experience can draw people in, much like when you and your friends or family share old stories and jokes.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Combining Engagement Techniques&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You don&#39;t need to rely on only one engagement technique at a time. Instead, combine them to increase and enhance their effect. For example, polling is a great way to get both brains and bodies involved with a triple-whammy of activity. It works with a poll question as simple as, “By show of hands, which of the following do&lt;em>; you&lt;/em>; believe is the most important element of XYZ?” The synergy of the physical, mental, and linguistic engagement techniques deployed in this one question get attendees out of neutral and in the flow with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Note that when polling, you must first tell your audience how to respond (eg, “By show of hands…” or “Type into the chat…”). It&#39;s also imperative that you comment on the response you get (eg, “That&#39;s what I expected…about half of you,” or “Wow, that is everyone”). If you fail to comment, your audience might feel tricked into complying, or worse, that you did not care about the answer and were just using the poll as a gimmick.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, these suggestions might not be appropriate for your situation (for example, if you&#39;re polling the three executives in the room), so choose options that fit the occasion and group size.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While engagement techniques can be used any time in a communication situation, they&#39;re especially critical when starting meetings, presentations, or pitches. Think about how an action movie opens. You&#39;re thrown into the midst of action with the actor doing something impressive, interesting, and curiosity provoking right away. Only after your attention is engaged and your interest piqued do the title and credits appear. If you start out with the traditional “Hi, my name is..,” you&#39;ve missed a prime opportunity to&amp;nbsp; engage your audience immediately. Similarly, engaging your audience by asking a question, taking a poll, showing a video, or using an analogy before introducing yourself sets an energetic tone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;. 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&#39;s focus is critical to communication success. If you think about any communication and communicator that you find compelling, they&#39;re likely leveraging some of the physical, mental, or linguistic engagement techniques discussed above. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>