<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How Large Language Models Reflect Human Judgment]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_10_1448510799.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;人工智能基于预测。但决策既需要预测，也需要判断。这就为人类留下了一个角色，可以判断哪些类型的结果更好，哪些更差。但是大型语言模型代表了一个关键的进步：OpenAI 已经找到了一种方法，通过聊天使用一种简单的人类反馈形式来教授其 AI 人类判断。这为人类使用 AI 的新方式打开了大门，本质上是与他们讨论对于任何给定类型的决策，哪些结果更好或更差。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/06/how-large-language-models-reflect-human-judgment?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;人工智能是预测机器。他们可以告诉你今天下雨的概率，但他们不能告诉你是否应该带把伞。那是因为带伞的决定需要的不仅仅是预测——如果下雨的概率是 10%，有些人会选择带伞，而其他人则不会。为什么不同的人面对同样的信息会有不同的表现呢？因为他们有不同的偏好。在这种情况下，有些人比其他人更关心弄湿。只有您或熟悉您的人才能判断带伞的成本和收益。为您做出该决定需要根据您的偏好进行预测和判断。&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;: 6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;AI 擅长预测，但不具备判断力。可以肯定的是，有许多我们知道回报或可以轻松解决的决定。从根本上说，我们知道驾驶员在大多数情况下应该做什么——加速、刹车、转弯——因为我们知道不做正确事情的后果。但是要求谷歌给你关于新洗碗机的建议，它能做的最好的事情就是预测哪些页面可能提供你正在寻找的信息。告诉你该做什么是不够幸运的。同样，虽然你可能担心你的雇主会使用人工智能来决定你是否应该被解雇，但机器并不是最终的负责人。 AI 可能会预测您的表现，但是由您的雇主进行判断并决定解雇谁。&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6 ,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;正是出于这个原因，在我们的 2018 年书 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Prediction-Machines-Economics-Artificial-Intelligence/dp/1633695670&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;预测机&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;，我们看到了奖励函数工程师的角色，他们的工作是“根据人工智能的预测，确定各种行动的奖励”使。人工智能预测可以改进如此多的决策，以至于了解这些预测和相关决策的奖励函数工程师将在人工智能采用持续快速发展的过程中提供熟练的补充。但奖励函数工程的创新进展缓慢。在开发工具以在大规模部署之前将适当的人类判断编入机器方面进展甚微。 &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;直到最近。大型语言模型 (LLM)，尽管看起来很智能，但仍然只是预测机器。但它们正在改变人工智能协助决策的方式，因为它们正在改变人类提供判断的方式。 &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;要求 ChatGPT 为特定受众更清楚地重写一段，它不会给你选择或语法和修辞讲座。它给你一个段落。令人印象深刻，但这里真正的奇迹是 ChatGPT 可以编写段落 &lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;you wanted&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;自动”>;。写一段话会涉及到大量的回报和风险问题。写作是否诚实（与事实一致）、无害（不包括可能冒犯的词语）和有帮助（实现段落的目标）？想想最后一个。这些模型是根据人们现有的文字进行训练的。所产生的段落的核心是一遍又一遍地使用一种“自动完成”来编写。当我们的手机自动完成时，它们会做得很好但并不完美。那么，ChatGPT 是如何产生比普通人更好的书面结果的呢？ ChatGPT 如何能够从所有内容（无论好坏）中判断质量？更一般地说，为什么它没有发展成 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;Microsoft 的 Tay 聊天机器人变成的有毒污水池在推特上度过一天后&lt;/a>;?&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;; :276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;有些人，比如&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://writings.stephenwolfram。 com/2023/02/what-is-chatgpt-doing-and-why-does-it-work/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Stephen Wolfram&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data- contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;，相信法学硕士正在揭示一些基本的语法规则。是的，这可以使文字可读，但肯定不能使文字清晰和引人注目。&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot ;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;A &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https: //arxiv.org/abs/2203.02155&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;来自 OpenAI 研究人员的 2022 年论文&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;提供了一条重要线索。该论文描述了如何采用原始的、未修改的 LLM，并将其用于向真实的人提供输出。在大多数情况下，人们被要求&lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;使用他们的判断来对几个备选结果进行排名&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot; auto&quot;>; 到相同的提示。仔细指定了排名标准（即，优先考虑乐于助人、诚实和无害）。事实证明，通过明确的指示和一些人对人的培训，不同的人很容易就这些事情达成一致。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot; ;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;然后使用这些排名调整或“微调”算法。该模型学习了人类的判断，并根据正负强化进行了调整。排名靠前的作品获得了积极的提升。那些没有受到负面影响的人。有趣的是，即使对于在数十亿页上训练的模型，只有几千个以排名响应形式出现的人类判断示例，人工智能也开始为所有排名靠前的查询生成结果。即使对于那些看起来与评估者排名相去甚远的查询，也会发生这种情况。不知何故，人类对书写质量的判断在整个模型中传播得相当远。&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot; ;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;评估人员实际上是奖励函数工程师。但与统计模型不同，其输出可能会让很多人反感，LLM 以通俗易懂的语言进行交互——任何人都可以帮助教授模型判断。换句话说，任何会说话或打字的人都可以成为奖励功能工程师。 ChatGPT 背后的惊人发现是，通过相对较少的努力，奖励函数工程师能够训练 LLM 变得有用和安全。这就是 OpenAI 能够推出面向消费者的模型的方式，该模型在发布到野外时没有受到其前辈缺陷的影响。这种将人类判断转化为机器的简单方法增强了人工智能的性能。这台机器现在不仅能够预测可能的单词序列，还能将奖励函数工程师的判断应用于这些序列，以增加它们对读者的吸引力。机器应用人类判断的一种简单方法的发现——在各种情况下指定风险和回报的任何 AI 预测机器的补充——带来了所有的不同。&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props= &quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span 数据对比=&quot;auto&quot;>;对于许多决策，需要专门的奖励函数工程师来大规模部署 AI 预测机器。这种将人类判断转化为机器的直观方法的发现——通过强化学习从人类反馈中进行微调——可能会开启人工智能的许多有价值的应用，在这些应用中，人类的判断很难事先转化为代码，但当你看到它时很容易实施。&lt;/ span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&quot;201341983&quot;:0,&quot;335551550&quot;:6,&quot;335551620&quot;:6,&quot;335559740&quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;/ p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Will Accelerate the Circular Economy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_12_1295939564.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Almost Green Studio/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;尽管生活在一个资源有限的星球上，但我们的经济在很大程度上仍然是线性的，并且充满了一次性产品。向公司回收或回收资源的循环经济的转变遇到了障碍，包括使用过的产品价值低和回收成本高。哈佛 D^3 研究所最近强调了数字工具和人工智能如何帮助克服这些障碍。他们讨论了三个关键策略：延长产品的使用寿命、在生产中使用更少的材料以及使用更多的回收材料。这些技术支持的策略有望带来可观的财务回报，但要充分发挥其潜力，则需要大量投资。简而言之，现在是企业认识到变废为宝潜力的时候了。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/06/how-ai-will-accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-will- accelerate-the-circular-economy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;全球经济仍然以线性方式运行，其特点是提取、生产、消费和处置材料。这是一个问题，因为我们生活在一个资源有限的星球上。然而，尽管提供了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.summaequity.com/assets/Reports/PDF/230417- Investing-in-a-circular-and-waste-free-Europe.pdf&quot;>;数万亿美元的价值创造&lt;/a>;。障碍包括使用过的产品残值低、无法收集材料、分离和加工材料的成本高昂，以及缺乏对回收产品和材料的可追溯性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;加快创新步伐和学习方面，哈佛商学院数字、数据和设计 (D^3) 研究所最近举办了一场 &lt;a href=&quot;https://environment.harvard.edu/event/d3-catalyst-circular-economy-conference&quot; >;以循环经济为主题的活动&lt;/a>;，企业家和商业领袖分享了他们如何使用数字工具和人工智能来消除这些障碍并创造全新的市场和商业模式。具体来说，这次会议帮助确定了实现循环经济的三个主要途径：提高产品利用率、材料效率和回收材料的使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;产品利用率&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt; p>;产品利用旨在延长产品的使用寿命，例如通过共享经济平台、产品翻新计划或延长产品使用寿命。公司延长产品寿命的一种新方法是通过无线软件更新来增加产品的剩余价值。以 iPhone 为例。今天，iPhone 占 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/the-used-smartphone-market-is-booming-surprisingly-thats-good-news-for-apple/&quot;>;80%二手市场中约 3 亿部手机的市场份额&lt;/a>;。 Sprint 和 Softbank International 的前首席执行官马塞洛·克劳雷 (Marcelo Claure) 在活动中解释说，取得这一成功的主要原因是 iOS 操作系统的向前兼容性，这确保用户可以访问应用程序生态系统和 Apple 发布的所有新功能，保持 iPhone 在二手市场上作为优质产品的吸引力。软件无线更新正成为更多产品的常态——甚至是汽车。因此，我们预计使用过的产品的剩余价值会增加，产品利用率也会提高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与延长产品寿命可能会阻碍销售增长的信念相反，因此公司应该实施计划淘汰策略，领先的公司将提高产品利用率视为接触新消费者、提高客户满意度和建立商业模式的机制，通过服务创造更耐用的产品。在其服务部门&lt;a href=&quot;https://investor.apple.com/sec-filings/sec-filings-details/default.aspx?FilingId=16157374&quot;>;已增长&lt;/a>;至近 800 亿美元与硬件业务相比，收入和毛利率几乎翻了一番。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;延长产品使用寿命的另一个机会是通过产品即服务模式，公司保留对硬件的所有权产品，而消费者为其使用付费。数据和追踪技术的进步使信息流更好，从而促进了这种商业模式。例如，SuperCircle 开发了一种数字基础设施，通过将客户购买数据与仓库和配送系统集成以追踪服装的生命周期，从而实现时尚行业的循环。 SuperCircle 的联合创始人、企业家 Chloe Songer 解释了他们如何与 Reformation 等服装品牌合作，创造一种客户体验，允许退货以获得信用或折扣，同时还促进物流基础设施将这些衣服聚集并出售给回收站部门。将消费者确定为长期资产的临时所有者，为继续吸引客户开辟了一个充满机遇的世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;材料效率&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;材料效率，这指的是用更少的材料制造产品，对于许多长期追求精益运营模式的公司来说并不是一个新概念，其特点是最大限度地减少生产过程中的浪费。然而，随着最近人工智能和创新技术的突破，材料效率正在见证更多机会的出现。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，我们的会议听取了企业家 Shelly Xu 的 SXD Zero Waste 如何应用人工智能重新设计服装模型减少服装生产过程中边角料产生的消费前废物。结果是毛衣、连衣裙或裤子的面料浪费接近零，成本降低了约 55%，而传统设计的浪费为 10-30%。成功的创业解决方案将是那些投入时间对 B2B 客户进行教育以了解节省成本的潜力以及修改传统上会导致更多浪费的传统流程（例如时装设计）的必要性的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“强硬技术” ”部门利用突破性的科学、工程和技术，也有可能创造出既能减少现有供应链的物质影响，又能创造出可以融入现有供应链的“直接”解决方案的解决方案。这个领域的企业家的一个例子是 Luciano Bueno，他创立了 GALY，这是一家在实验室用细胞种植棉花的公司，与传统农业相比，它使用的资源减少了 80%。高难度技术创新之旅的一个重要部分是让投资者了解更长的创新周期以及在可扩展性道路上迭代的必要性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;再生材料&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt; p>;也许循环商业模式中最广为人知的要素是将原始材料的使用量降至最低，占产品总材料的百分比。例如，Apple 的产品现在包含 20% 的回收材料。除了减少碳排放外，更多回收材料的使用还有助于公司提高“材料安全”，这对于依赖锂和钴等稀有矿物的行业尤其重要。增加回收材料也是降低水泥和钢铁等难以减排行业碳强度的关键解决方案。然而，来自麦肯锡的 Joy Chen 和 Per Anders Enkvist 强调，回收材料的可用性目前有限，有时甚至比原始材料更贵。因此，提高高质量回收材料的可用性并降低成本的技术改进是巨大的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;特别是，扩大材料回收和分离是使回收材料更容易获得和负担得起的关键。北欧最大的废物管理公司 Norsk Gjenvinning 的首席执行官 Bjørn Arve Ofstad 解释说，该行业需要上游原料、分类和处理废物以供下游使用的技术，以及下游接收者。这个过程需要在行业规模上完成，在正确的时间、价格和质量上获取材料。机器人技术可以以较低的成本促进这种分拣过程。例如，Apple 开发了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/iphone-terminator-apples-daisy-teardown-robot-can-rip-your-phone-apart-in-18-secs/ &quot;>;Daisy&lt;/a>;，一种最先进的机器人，可以在 18 秒内将 iPhone 分解成可重复使用的组件，包括钴、金和铂等稀有矿物。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不透明供应链代表了理解报废材料分解以进行回收和分类的重大障碍。来自谷歌的 Maria McClay 解释了谷歌如何在 2019 年试行一项解决方案，以使用机器学习和分析来提供更全面的纺织品价值链影响视图，并在 2021 年能够将该产品扩展到其他品牌。 Procter &amp;amp; 的 Hari Nair 描述的另一种解决方案Gamble 是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pg.co.uk/blogs/HolyGrail/&quot;>;HolyGrail 项目&lt;/a>;，它在产品中使用数字水印，以便在生命周期结束时更轻松地对可回收物品进行分类.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;投资万亿美元的机会&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了支持采用和扩展这些支持数字化的解决方案，我们需要投资来资助万亿美元美元的机会。然而，循环中的资产配置者面临着“模式识别”的挑战，其中识别有前途机会的能力仍在不断发展。风险投资基金一直对投资有大量资本支出需求的早期公司犹豫不决，这在循环解决方案中很常见。另一方面，私募股权基金一直不愿投资早期创业公司。 Generate Capital 的安德鲁·梅里诺 (Andrew Merino) 描述的一种解决方案是出现多部门、以可持续发展为重点的基金，弥合传统风险投资和私募股权之间的差距。为挖掘循环经济的全部投资潜力，投资者需要在投资结构方面发展深入的行业专业知识和创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Video Quick Take &ndash; Google&rsquo;s Gautam Ramdurai on Emerging Consumer Behavior - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM GOOGLE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/video-quick-take-googles-gautam-ramdurai-on-emerging-consumer-behavior]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;p>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6328969026112&quot;}&quot; js- target=&quot;video-player-page&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;正在加载.. . &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt; p>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Harvard Business Review 研究和特殊项目高级编辑 Todd Pruzan 最近采访了谷歌亚太区广告营销集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai，采访了新一期的 HBR Video Quick Take。由于当今的每个企业都需要驾驭一系列复杂的因素来推动可持续和盈利增长，同时牢记这样做的核心仍然是了解客户以及他们如何做出决策，Pruzan 与 Ramdurai 谈到了对新兴消费者行为的新见解&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;很多关于消费者行为的事情似乎都在持续发生变化。您现在看到亚太地区的消费者行为发生了哪些变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span >;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;我们现在发现的东西很吸引人。尤其需要注意的是，2023 年与 2020 年甚至 2022 年的真正不同之处在于。我们知道这场大流行病从根本上改变了很多事情，但我认为随着我们走出大流行病，其他危机正在介入：政治动荡、气候变化和生活成本危机。当所有这些类型的公共危机同时发生时，我们需要开始考虑它们所产生的总体影响。答案是：我们正在进入一个真正的混合世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;想想在大流行期间每个人是如何上网的。但是，随着我们从大流行中走出来，当你想到你的杂货店购物时，你是如何决定哪些物品是在商店购买的，哪些是在网上购买的？即使是最简单的决策，每个人的头脑中都会进行这种复杂的计算，这仅仅是因为决策本身的因素数量以及您从中获取信息的渠道数量。例如，考虑与您交互的设备数量，然后将其乘以您使用的渠道数量，从 Google 搜索到 YouTube 再到任何其他视频平台再到报纸。您可以进出在线和离线世界。甚至在网络世界中，也有如此多的多样性，你试图找到摆脱它的方法。到 2023 年，这将变得非常棘手。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，在整个亚太地区，我们的研究告诉我们，想知道和知道之间的差距——一直存在——从未如此之大。这就是我们所说的置信度差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push (function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt ;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;好吧，信任和信心如今比以往任何时候都更重要，但消费者如何驾驭这种格局？企业如何驾驭它？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;集团营销经理 Gautam Ramdurai&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;让我们从消费者开始。消费者是聪明的。他们总是比企业更善于与时俱进。因此，消费者所做的是相当快地找到他们的内部微积分。换句话说，每个人都有他们通过的这些决策因素以及他们在做出决策时要寻求的这些信息源。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们举一个想要做某事的人的例子：我有一个三- 岁，所以我一直在想我三岁的孩子什么时候应该骑自行车。那是一个重要的时刻，对吧？因此，当消费者想到“哦，我需要为我的女儿买一辆自行车”时，第一个问题永远不会是“我在哪里买自行车？”相反，它是“孩子骑自行车的合适年龄是多少？”这是一个更基本的生活问题，也是一个好奇心驱动的问题。你从一个关于孩子骑自行车的正确时间的问题开始，然后慢慢过渡到研究有哪些类型的自行车。您最终会被孩子们第一次尝试学习如何骑自行车的视频所吸引。您很快意识到您还需要购买头盔。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种好奇心路径扩展了消费者寻找正确信息的过程。当消费者浏览所有这些内容时，我们发现他们真正寻找的是六个特定的信心线索。这些线索是噪音中的信号；它们会告诉他们需要知道什么，以便更接近于对自己的决定充满信心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，想象一下您处于信心差距中。你被困在那里，不知道下一步该去哪里。你让好奇心引导你回答下一个问题。我们发现在这个过程中有一些关键信息将所有内容汇集在一起​​。例如，其中一个信心线索是评论。这家生产这种自行车的公司是否经过了良好的审查？这家公司是否以制造安全自行车或整体安全公司而享有盛誉？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他重要因素，例如社会认同。可持续性正变得越来越重要，因此一家公司的可持续性实践正成为越来越重要的购买考虑因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;令人惊讶的是，我们发现了一个额外的隐含线索。这第七个提示实际上是关于平台的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天有大量的数字信息，当我告诉你数字世界正在扩展时，我知道我是在向合唱团宣讲。人们拥有的信息源数量比以往任何时候都多，随之而来的是大量虚假信息和错误信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type= &quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;简而言之，平台本身在 2023 年发挥的作用比我们以前看到的要大得多。它们成为关于您对获取信息的平台本身有多信任的第七个线索。这就像查看两个不同的新闻站点并决定您更信任哪个。同样的逻辑现在也适用于平台世界：您查看所有信息或查找信息的平台实际上与品牌或企业本身可能传达给客户的任何其他信心线索一样重要。 &lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;所以平台必须成为一部分你的日常生活。它必须是安全的。它必须是一个你信任的平台，几乎就像你会根据他们过去告诉你的那样相信一个人的话而不是另一个人的话。平台是这里的关键？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p >;是的，这就是我们在多个平台上看到的，尤其是谷歌和 YouTube。对于像 Google 这样的网站，人们在不确定的时候会去寻找一些东西，它几乎就像一个人类意图的图书馆。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，虽然品牌本身可以查看六个线索，但它不是就是你在这六个信心提示中所说的话。相反，它是您展示同样重要的自信线索的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b >;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;那么媒介真的是信息还是信息的重要组成部分？&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;正确。我会说这是其中很大一部分，因为媒体永远不可能是完整的信息。您拥有自己的品牌。你知道它想对世界说话的真相。但我认为现在的复杂性——这可以追溯到我们关于 2023 年与以往相比的独特之处的研究——涉及需要考虑消费者必须经历的微积分。然后我们需要将其与企业必须经历的演算配对。因此，如果消费者没有在正确的时间、正确的地点和正确的媒介中找到正确的信息，他们将退出购买之旅。&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan，哈佛商业评论&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;哇，听起来这是一个非常脆弱的交易。&lt;/p>; &lt; h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai，集团营销经理&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;当然可以。一切都回到了桌面上。凭直觉——这是我昨天与某人进行的讨论的一部分——你会想，“哦，在不确定的时候，我们会回到我们所知道的事情上。”但我们看到的是，人们实际上会花更多的时间进行研究，即使他们拥有已经使用了很长时间的品牌。因此，几乎就像是大流行病加剧了这种对信任和信心的需求，以至于人们正在将他们久经考验的品牌转移到餐桌的后面。这意味着您不能认为信任是理所当然的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;再次回到交易信任，它不是在人们购买产品时建立的。 It&#39;s built when the person is thinking of using a product; it&#39;s built when the consumer doesn&#39;t even know they have the need for the product. So if you go through the entire consumer journey, you need to be able to establish those confidence cues across the whole board.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And it doesn&#39;t end when they&#39;ve bought your product. The more important part of the journey is when they&#39;re actually using your product or your service. That customer experience doesn&#39;t end at the buy button. It almost starts there in many ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;If trust is important to consumers, how does this start translating to business outcomes?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;In 2023, it has a pretty direct impact. If consumers are looking for information to build up their confidence about buying your product or your service, how you show up is super important. If you don&#39;t show up the right way, it has direct implications on your bottom line. For example, in both India and Southeast Asia, one in three consumers decided not to buy a brand they were considering already because they felt a little anxious. They were not assured of their choice.¹ So that&#39;s an abandoned cart right there.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And we&#39;re seeing the positive side of trust show up in a big way as well. If you&#39;ve done the job of being with your customers/consumers throughout their buying journey and their overall purchase experience, and you&#39;ve built and fed into that trust account, highly trusted brands are seven times more likely to be purchased² — and it doesn&#39;t end at purchase. Consumers who are confident in their product choices before purchasing are almost 20% more likely to repurchase that brand.³&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Plus, the consumer journey is cyclical, so the trust and confidence you&#39;ve built with your consumers don&#39;t end when they hit “Buy.” It almost starts there. And if you want to continue building that virtuous loop of trust and confidence, you need to step up everywhere, even when they&#39;ve already bought your products. We&#39;re seeing this come through very clearly in the data. So for the confidence-seeking consumer in 2023, all brands are back on the table, and it&#39;s up to you as the seller to choose whether you want to be part of that transaction or journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;What can businesses do to keep up with what their customers need? And how do you see that changing over the next few years?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Once someone has gotten all the signals they need to make their choice, that&#39;s when we think they&#39;ve made a confidence shift: You&#39;ve helped them find the answer to that life question, and your product or service is a part of that. We think businesses that are smart and able to power this confidence shift are the ones that are going to thrive in this very messy future — and present, for that matter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But when you start thinking about how your business can help them make the confidence shift, you need to know which cue to show, when to show it, and whom is it for, because all your consumers are probably not built the same, and all of them are not in the same part of the journey. These are all moving targets: the right cues, right consumers, right formats, right messages, right devices, and right points in the decision journey. The only way to start making sense of this — and these are all predictive decisions in a lot of ways — and to do it at scale, and for large companies, especially, in milliseconds, is by harnessing the power of data and AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Again, this brings us back to whether you want to be a transactional business or a business that builds trust and confidence over time. This is an investment that you need to make across the entire customer experience. The gold standard of campaigns used to be that you&#39;d have and meet just one KPI a quarter, but we&#39;re moving away from that. Now the gold standard is whether you can drive new customers who also have high lifetime value. Those used to be two different meetings in the marketing rooms, but now they&#39;re being mushed together. The way to unpack this complexity is with data and AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Gautam, thank you for your insights. Do you have any parting words today, especially about how you are going to find that bike for your daughter?&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;What a complex question! There are many life questions that exist when it comes to buying that bike. I need to keep the following in mind as I navigate that path: We know that life is a lot more complicated and complex than it has been before, and we don&#39;t know what the next set of uncertainties will be. We also know that they will come; there will be more uncertainty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regarding the confidence gap that has always been there, consumers will still find themselves in it, and maybe it will widen. Maybe the confidence cues will evolve. But I think we have to keep our ear to the ground to understand our consumers&#39; decision making if we want to know which cues they need. Our job is to help them make that confidence shift, and that will only become more and more important as we move into the future. The world of complex decision making is here to stay, and the businesses that invest in their ability to make that confidence shift with the power of data and AI are probably the ones that are going to thrive in this environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Thank you so much for a great conversation and for all of your insights today.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Gautam Ramdurai, Group Marketing Manager&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Thank you, Todd, for having me.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Todd Pruzan, HBR&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;To learn more, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkwithgoogle.com/intl/en-apac/marketing-strategies/automation/build-brand-confidence-ai-marketing/?utm_source=twg_partnership_external&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023-APAC-GML-EVOS-HBR-VQT-HL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Think With Google&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Return to the “&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/multiply-your-marketing-with-ai&quot;>;Multiply Your Marketing With AI&lt;/a>;” Sponsor Content Hub from Google APAC on HBR.org&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;¹Source: Google/Kantar/Quantum, “Emotional Value of Search”, IN, ID, VN, MY, PH, TH, PK, 2021, n=5006 P18M category buyers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;² Source: Edelman, “Trust, The New Brand Equity”, 2022, n=14,000 consumers across 14 countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;³ Source: Google/ Ipsos, Decoding Repurchase, AU, IN, ID, JP, KR, VN, 2023, n=1500 per market, Buyers of Home appliances, Personal care, Health and wellbeing products.&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Three Ways To Use The Customer Perspective As A Measure Of Success - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/three-ways-to-use-the-customer-perspective-as-a-measure-of-success]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358516&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_KPI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;In business, you can&#39;t improve what you&#39;re not measuring—and today&#39;s organizations typically measure progress and success with key performance indicators (KPIs).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A successful business is synonymous with higher customer satisfaction, retention, and overall brand reputation. So it&#39;s no surprise that most companies rank customer experience as their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.superoffice.com/blog/customer-experience-statistics/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;top business priority&lt;/a>;. But all too often, in their mission to track and quantify progress, business leaders end up prioritizing processes that directly oppose customer-centric behaviors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Traditional KPIs include measures of profitability, productivity, and process efficiency—all of which are internal metrics. Analyzing these metrics can undoubtedly give indications of overall performance. But when prioritized above all else, they risk missing the bigger picture of how a business can provide the most value to customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumers are increasingly deriving value from their interactions and experiences with a brand. Eighty-three percent of consumers pay as much attention to &lt;a href=&quot;https://khoros.com/resources&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;how brands treat them&lt;/a>; as they do to the products, and 89% report &lt;a href=&quot;https://harris-interactive.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;switching to a competitor&lt;/a>; following a poor experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So as experience becomes a more important measure of performance, the most successful companies are creating emotional connections at every touchpoint. With today&#39;s consumers firmly in the driver&#39;s seat, business leaders need to have the right tools, processes, and overall customer-centric culture to stay in the game.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Customer Value as a KPI&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Although efficiency, productivity, and profitability will continue to be important, customer value is rapidly becoming the real star of the analytics show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, measuring customer value is more complex than tracking traditional KPIs. Factors such as social value, brand cachet, and the emotional experience a service or product provides come into play—all of which are harder to quantify with standard methods.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s how to shift your KPI scorecard toward customer value to set yourself up for success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Establish which KPIs will give you rich, customer-centric data.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Customer engagement metrics are useful at this stage, helping you allocate your resources better and establish standards to monitor and assess—and, crucially, understand—how your customer views you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A good range of customer engagement metrics include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Customer satisfaction score &lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Measuring your customer satisfaction score tells you how happy a customer was with their last interaction with your company and gives you a chance to improve based on their feedback. Net promoter score is a similar metric you can use to measure the customer experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Churn rate&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Your churn rate reflects the percentage of customers who stop doing business with you during a specific period. Although customers leave for a variety of reasons, you need to know whether there is a consistent theme so you can address the cause.&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Customer lifetime value&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This KPI ties nicely into churn. Your customer lifetime value score will give you the expected revenue your company can generate from a customer, helping you estimate the future return from marketing initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Let customer value take center stage with customer performance indicators.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;KPIs are a great place to start, but it can be too easy to get lost in the numbers and distracted from what matters to customers. Another approach to measuring success is to supplement these metrics with customer performance indicators (CPIs).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many companies confuse KPIs with CPIs. Although KPIs can be an effective measure of sentiment, there&#39;s still a risk that KPIs overlook what&#39;s relevant to customers. KPIs are intrinsically linked to a company&#39;s goals, but CPIs focus on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-performace-indicators-surbhit-suman-banga&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;what customers care about the most&lt;/a>;, such as value and satisfaction, which lead to loyalty and retention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ongoing dialogue with your customers is the best way to get the most out of your CPIs. Ask them what value they derive from your business, what keeps them coming back, and what influences their purchases. Ask, listen, design, implement—and then ask again.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;Bring together the right metrics, the right tools, and the right mindset.&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;This continuous loop of monitoring and adjusting requires a more sophisticated approach than isolated measurement tools collecting data from single touchpoints. Unlocking value from customer-centric data requires an analytics platform that can integrate, extract, and synthesize data from across the software stack.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Customer-relationship management (CRM) technology with agile, intuitive analytics features can yield results far beyond what managers see in their organization-wide tableau setup. A 360-degree view of your business empowers you to make bigger decisions based on granular detail.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Judging your measurement of success from traditional KPIs risks creating a situation in which teams are motivated to perform aggressive sales tactics to achieve their targets, which can be destructive to good customer relationships. Complementing these metrics with CPIs cultivates a different type of accountability, encouraging teams to achieve customer satisfaction above all else—which can lead to better retention and more revenue.&lt;/p>; &lt;h5>;&lt;b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 11.0pt;&quot;>;The Experience of Customer Experience&lt;/span>;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h5>; &lt;p>;Always remember that customer experience is just that: an experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumers are less interested in your brand than you are. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2019/11/21/consumers-are-hungry-for-an-experience-based-connection-with-your-brand/?sh=2974384358fe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;They&#39;re focused on their own experience&lt;/a>;. To truly measure your brand&#39;s impact on their lives, you need to look past individual touchpoints and evaluate their holistic experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although this is about more than just the numbers, the only way to know whether you&#39;re hitting the mark is with data. Your analytical tools and processes need to be flexible enough to help you measure and deliver authentic experiences that will cultivate lasting customer relationships.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm.com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;Discover&lt;/a>; how Zoho CRM&#39;s intuitive analytics can help you deliver lasting customer value.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovering Where ChatGPT Can Create Value for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_4896946.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Although the speed, scale, and scope of ChatGPT&amp;#8217;s impact may be unique, the underlying phenomenon &amp;#8212; an emerging technology transforming vast parts of business and society &amp;#8212; is not. But harnessing the power of emerging technology requires a new approach. Unlike traditional methods for innovation, such as design thinking, ChatGPT poses a fundamentally different challenge because there are no clear problems to address, user pain points to alleviate, or KPIs to achieve. In fact, ChatGPT can seemingly solve problems in almost any industry, domain, or context. Using it, therefore, requires a different skill: emergent thinking, which involves generating ideas for innovation without fully understanding the problem that needs to be solved.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/discovering-where-chatgpt-can-create-value-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When OpenAI released its flagship product ChatGPT last November, it reached 1 million users in only four days and 100 million users in two months, achieving this milestone more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/chatgpt-sets-record-fastest-growing-user-base-analyst-note-2023-02-01/&quot;>;75% faster than any other tech giant&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has continued to evolve quickly, beginning as an AI chatbot that only responded to user prompts. Now it includes features such as analyzing data and interpreting images, leaving everyone from high school students to C-suite executives scrambling to learn ChatGPT so they can use it in new and productive ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Although the speed, scale, and scope of ChatGPT&#39;s impact may be unique, the underlying phenomenon — an emerging technology transforming vast parts of business and society — is not. But harnessing the power of emerging technology requires a new approach. Unlike traditional methods for innovation, such as &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/why-design-thinking-works&quot;>;design thinking&lt;/a>;, ChatGPT poses a fundamentally different challenge because there are no clear problems to address, user pain points to alleviate, or KPIs to achieve. In fact, ChatGPT can seemingly solve problems in almost any industry, domain, or context. Using it, therefore, requires a different skill: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/326964001_An_Integrated_Model_of_Dynamic_Problem_Solving_Within_Organizational_Constraints&quot;>;emergent thinking&lt;/a>;, which involves generating ideas for innovation without fully understanding the problem that needs to be solved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Two of us (Johnathan and Jennifer) recently conducted &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886923001289&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; showing that the main thought process for this style of innovation is to start by understanding the core functions of a technology, &lt;em>;then&lt;/em>; explore how it can be used to solve problems across different domains. Other hallmarks of emergent thinking include evaluating ideas without understanding the criteria for success, improvising ideas with little preparation or planning, and changing a project&#39;s target outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These activities tend to run counter to good business practices promoting efficiency and reliability, and they may even violate some of the core tenets of design thinking — namely the need to identify a clear user problem to address &lt;em>;before&lt;/em>; generating ideas for a solution. Yet, they&#39;re also critical when trying to leverage ChatGPT (or any other emerging technology, for that matter) for innovation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many companies have already started integrating ChatGPT into their products, processes, and services. By analyzing this burgeoning landscape of innovation, we&#39;ve identified three emergent-thinking pathways for leaders that can help increase the chances of implementing ChatGPT successfully while also avoiding potential pitfalls.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 1: Exploiting a Current Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first pathway involves using ChatGPT to further exploit a value proposition a company already provides to customers. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/instacart-could-do-worse-than-incinerating-32-bln-2023-03-01/&quot;>;Instacart has grown to $2.5 billion in annual revenue&lt;/a>; by focusing on the core value proposition of providing fast, reliable, and affordable grocery delivery to customers at home. Recently, they &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instacart.com/company/updates/instacart-chatgpt/&quot;>;launched a plugin for ChatGPT&lt;/a>; that aims to strengthen this value proposition by increasing the speed and efficiency of ordering groceries online. With this plugin, customers can receive recommendations for meals to prepare, and once they find something they like, ChatGPT will create a new Instacart order that automatically adds all the necessary ingredients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To pursue this pathway for innovation, start by using ChatGPT without directing it toward any specific customer problems. This thought process can be challenging because most business training teaches us to be strategic thinkers and verify the importance of customer problems before spending any time developing solutions. However, starting with strategic goals like this can actually blind us to seeing ChatGPT&#39;s potential for new and valuable applications. Instead, start with an open mind and deeply engage with the tool to understand its core functions. Once you have that understanding, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048733320301463&quot;>;natural human cognition will take over&lt;/a>; and start making connections to any relevant problems you might be aware of.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, one of the core functions of ChatGPT is to interpret and generate natural language text that provides human-like responses to a wide variety of questions, prompts, and requests. Companies can use this function to enhance existing features of products or services that focus specifically on text-based interactions with customers. For instance, the product-management tool Notion now provides customers with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.notion.so/product/ai&quot;>;immediate access to ChatGPT&lt;/a>; at the tap of the spacebar, which activates a prompt to receive an AI response that can be immediately integrated into existing tasks and workflows. As the functions of ChatGPT continue to grow, new possibilities will emerge for how it can be used to further enhance value propositions across a wider range of companies and contexts.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 2: Expanding the Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A second pathway uses ChatGPT to expand a company&#39;s value proposition by solving new problems for customers in a way that complements their current offering. For example, Khan Academy was created in 2006 with the mission of providing all students with a free, world-class education. They&#39;ve since grown to nearly 20 million users per month, primarily by offering short online videos that start with a blank canvas and get filled with colorful, hand-written text. Recently, they integrated ChatGPT into their platform &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.khanacademy.org/sal-khans-2023-ted-talk-ai-in-the-classroom-can-transform-education/&quot;>;by creating a personalized AI tutor called Khanmigo&lt;/a>;. This tool not only helps students by guiding them through online videos and practice questions more effectively, but it can also help teachers by explaining teaching methods and designing lesson plans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can follow the same pathway by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/335242871_Matthew_A_Cronin_and_Jeffrey_Loewenstein_The_Craft_of_Creativity&quot;>;clearly defining your perspective and learning how to change it&lt;/a>;. For emergent thinking, this first involves breaking down a value proposition into three core elements:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;The goals customers are trying to accomplish&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The context in which customers are trying to accomplish those goals&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The specific target demographic of the customers&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once defined, the next step is to assess how ChatGPT&#39;s core functions (see Pathway 1) can help expand each element in new directions. For example, Khan Academy originally focused on &lt;em>;helping&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;K–12 students&lt;/em>; (target demographic) &lt;em>;learn topics at a self-guided pace&lt;/em>; (goal), &lt;em>;done&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;completely online &lt;/em>;(context). Using ChatGPT, they expanded this goal for students by facilitating online learning either through self-guided practice or via an AI tutor, and they also expanded the target demographic to include teachers, helping them accomplish new goals that were not previously possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This two-step definition and expansion process offers a complementary skillset to design thinking, which typically encourages people to think of many different solutions before converging on one to implement. With emergent thinking, however, you apply those same &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/03/better-brainstorming&quot;>;brainstorming techniques&lt;/a>; to the problem, rather than the solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During this process, it&#39;s key to maintain an open mind and avoid settling on a problem too quickly, which may be particularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/228198146_Performance_Pressure_as_a_Double-Edged_Sword_Enhancing_Team_Motivation_While_Undermining_the_Use_of_Team_Knowledge&quot;>;challenging to do in conditions of uncertainty&lt;/a>;. ChatGPT has unleashed an unprecedented level of pressure on companies to act quickly, or else suffer dramatic consequences for their future survival. However, research shows it&#39;s also possible to &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/jpo/article-abstract/7/1/2/5707381&quot;>;withstand these pressures and explore a wider range of innovation options&lt;/a>;. To do that, work with trusted collaborators so you can navigate ambiguity more effectively and take greater risks together.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Pathway 3: Exploring a New Value Proposition&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The final pathway is based on using ChatGPT to explore a completely new value proposition that customers may not even know they need yet. Although this may run counter to traditional methods for innovation, it also aligns with common advice for creating breakthroughs. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/1998-05-25/steve-jobs-theres-sanity-returning&quot;>;when Steve Jobs was asked&lt;/a>; whether Apple did any market research when developing the iMac, he responded: “It&#39;s really hard to design products by focus groups. A lot of times, people don&#39;t know what they want until you show it to them.” This wisdom seems to have been fully embraced by OpenAI, which released ChatGPT to the public and is now discovering countless ways it can be used in various contexts to accomplish new and unforeseen goals. This pathway for innovation represents the purest form of emergent thinking, which has the greatest uncertainty and therefore must also be pursued with the greatest caution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The main challenge comes when trying to converge on a single problem to focus on out of the many dozens identified when brainstorming different goals, contexts, and target demographics (see Pathway 2). When organizations have relatively clearer value propositions — such as increasing the speed of online ordering at Instacart or improving the quality of online education at Khan Academy — it can be easier to filter out problems that seem far-fetched or unlikely to reflect valuable customer needs. However, when customer needs are still unknown and emerging along with the technology, it becomes difficult for teams to agree on a shared direction to pursue. This becomes especially challenging when trying to include the diverse perspectives that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/smarter-collaboration-a-new-approach-to-breaking-down-barriers-and-transforming-work/10535&quot;>;fundamental to innovation&lt;/a>;, because team members can pull the project in different directions &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Extreme-Teaming-Lessons-Cross-Sector-Leadership/dp/1786354500&quot;>;despite their best intentions to collaborate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help overcome these challenges, &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2343944&quot;>;identify a clear and coherent analogy&lt;/a>; that summarizes the core value proposition. For example, Tome is a startup that&#39;s using ChatGPT to help customers create better presentations out of online documents, videos, and digital content. However, instead of highlighting all the specific benefits they can provide, they&#39;ve described their product as an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20230427180425/https:/beta.tome.app/&quot;>;AI storytelling partner&lt;/a>;.” This simple concept helps integrate many different features into a coherent product experience so that both developers and customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/234021855_When_Is_a_New_Thing_a_Good_Thing_Technological_Change_Product_Form_Design_and_Perceptions_of_Value_for_Product_Innovations&quot;>;easily understand its value&lt;/a>;. By creating an analogy for your product, you can avoid wasting valuable resources creating features that might not support the core value proposition, and you can help customers develop a clear mental model of the various features and why they can be useful.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ChatGPT is an unprecedented technology that has potential to unlock value for millions of customers across many industries. However, pursuing these rewards also comes with considerable risks, as we&#39;re all entering uncharted territory with AI, and we must learn how to use it effectively so it can be leveraged for positive rather than negative outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Build Upon the Legacy of Your Family Business &mdash; and Make It Your Own]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_1009603322.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Sean Murphy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Family companies often have a strong sense of history and tradition. Although these legacies can create advantages, they sometimes leave next-generation leaders feeling handcuffed or constrained by the way their ancestors ran things. To overcome that, they should seek to reformulate the company&amp;#8217;s story in a way that creates advantages for the present.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-build-upon-the-legacy-of-your-family-business-and-make-it-your-own?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Founded by Henry Ford &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/about/history.html&quot;>;in 1903&lt;/a>;, the Ford Motor Company rocketed to success by mass-producing reliable, low-priced automobiles. When Henry&#39;s son, &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.ford.com/articles/history/edsel-ford-biography.html&quot;>;Edsel&lt;/a>;, took the helm in 1918, he championed a different strategy for a new era. He sought to replace the Model T — iconic but outdated — with a more modern design geared to high-end and foreign markets, and later embraced compromise with labor amid the suffering of the Great Depression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But Henry could not let go of Ford&#39;s origin story, undermining his son at every turn. The result was declining sales and years of labor strife that left the company on the brink of collapse by the 1940s. It was only the efforts of Edsel&#39;s son, the more forceful &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.automotivehalloffame.org/honoree/henry-ford-ii/&quot;>;Henry Ford II&lt;/a>;, that saved the auto giant from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In family enterprise, generational transitions often pit one narrative against another: tradition versus innovation, continuity versus change. Indeed, when older generations craft painstaking succession plans or build elaborate constraints into trusts or shareholder agreements, they are really constructing a story: about the values and life lessons that helped them succeed, and that they hope will do the same for their children. Younger generations, however, must often adapt this narrative to their own goals and values, along with the changing world around them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to reconcile conflicting narratives can spell ruin for a family business or the waste of a financial legacy, as it nearly did for the Fords. To avoid this fate, families need to think differently about the stories they tell.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The value of critical distance&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Conventional wisdom holds that family heritage, like wealth and reputation, “belongs” to the older generation. In this telling, succeeding generations are merely stewards or caretakers. They are given an inheritance or entrusted with the family business — and then charged with not frittering it away or screwing it up. Framed this way, a legacy can feel more like a burden than a gift.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, it&#39;s not as simple as that. Research suggests that younger generations &lt;em>;do&lt;/em>; value their family heritage, especially as a source of traditions more motivating than money alone, and are motivated to preserve it. According to a 2021 &lt;a href=&quot;https://home.kpmg/content/dam/kpmg/ca/pdf/2022/02/who-are-the-guardians-of-family-legacy-report-en.pdf&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; of 300 Canadian business owners by the Family Enterprise Foundation, nearly 90% of next-generation family business leaders believe it is important to preserve a legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But younger generations also want something more from that heritage: a sense of purpose, a collective identity for the family, the seeds of new entrepreneurial gambits, permission to go their own way. And as our own &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0894486520941944?journalCode=fbra&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows, next-generation leaders are uniquely positioned to find what they are looking for in the family story.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Older generations often identify closely with the family or the family business, which can actually obstruct key learnings from the past. Eager to protect the family&#39;s reputation, they may downplay scandal or setback rather than learn from it. By contrast, our analysis of 94 family businesses shows that younger generations tend to have more critical distance from the family story. This lets them grapple with its difficult chapters and respond appropriately, whether by making amends for past misdeeds or by reforming business practices going forward. It also frees them to draw insights from their story that can fuel innovation and sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Legacy as a source of purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How, then, can the next generation build on their family legacy while recasting it as their own? Our research and experience suggest four strategies for next-generation leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;1. Seek out role models in the family story.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Some next-generation leaders hesitate to embark on risky new ventures outside the traditional scope of the family business. Locating exemplars in the family story can legitimize a new way forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One third-generation CEO used this approach to advance his vision for a more sustainable enterprise. Fredo Arias-King, head of Mexican pine resin producer Pinosa Group, had lamented the disappearance of Mexico&#39;s ancient pine forests that threatened both the industry and the communities that depend on it. Then he stumbled onto the published speeches of his grandfather, company founder José Antonio Arias Álvarez, who had preached environmental stewardship. “I don&#39;t think he could have known just how devastated the forest would eventually become,” said Arias-King, “but somehow my grandfather knew that planting trees would become extremely important.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Affirmed by his grandfather&#39;s words, Arias-King helped found &lt;a href=&quot;https://ejidoverde.com/about-us/&quot;>;Ejido Verde&lt;/a>;, a nonprofit that would later become an independent, for-profit enterprise. By making no-interest loans to farmers and communities, with pine resin as the means of repayment, the organization promotes reforesting through new pine plantations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;2. Forge an identity beyond the founder-entrepreneur.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to revere the family&#39;s wealth creator. For the two adult grandchildren of one founder-entrepreneur — a private equity pioneer who rose from poverty to become one of America&#39;s richest people — that was the problem. They wanted their own children, beneficiaries of a generation-skipping trust, to know the person behind the legacy that would pass to them. So they engaged one of us (John Seaman) to probe beyond the classic rags-to-riches tale they had heard growing up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The founder, they learned, was a gifted yet deeply troubled man. This more nuanced understanding enabled the two generations to have a frank conversation about the issues raised by their ancestor&#39;s life: the obligations of a business to its workers and communities; the consequences of untreated mental illness; and the unfair burden often shouldered by women in wealthy families.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This conversation, in turn, led members of the fourth generation, all in their twenties, to rethink their roles in the family enterprise. One set aside her qualms about joining the family business and put herself on a path to succeed her father as president, but with a determination to nudge the company&#39;s private equity portfolio toward impact investing. Another resolved to pursue her own entrepreneurial dreams outside of the business, rooted in progressive values that were in stark contrast with her great-grandfather&#39;s. Still another joined the board of the family foundation, where she helped steer its grant-making toward her generation&#39;s individual passions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By seeing their founder-entrepreneur in human terms, the family&#39;s younger generation was able to move beyond hero worship to forge their own identities — which promised to make them responsible owners &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;stewards of their ancestor&#39;s wealth and the business that created it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3. Reckon with past wrongs to find a new path forward.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many families have skeletons in the closet —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/how-companies-can-address-their-historical-transgressions&quot;>;scandal or wrongdoing&lt;/a>; they have long concealed or downplayed. (Henry Ford&#39;s history of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/americanexperience/features/henryford-antisemitism/&quot;>;antisemitism&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/how-the-ford-motor-company-won-a-battle-and-lost-ground-45814533/&quot;>;violent confrontations&lt;/a>; with unions are examples of this.) The willingness to confront these darker chapters, it turns out, can be a powerful motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That was the case for the Reimann family, owners of consumer goods conglomerate JAB Holding Company and one of Germany&#39;s richest families. The three adult children of Albert Reimann Jr., who ran the company in the 1930s and 1940s, knew they had been born of their father&#39;s affair with an employee, Emilie Landecker. They also knew that Emilie&#39;s Jewish father, Alfred, had been murdered by the Nazis. But it was not until 2019, when they commissioned research on the company, that a more sinister secret emerged: their father and paternal grandfather were themselves ardent believers in Nazi race theory who abused forced laborers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It was the younger generation — Albert Jr.&#39;s grandchildren — who were most adamant about reckoning with this secret. “When I read of the atrocities…sanctioned by my grandfather, I felt like throwing up,” recalled Martin Reimann. “I cannot claim that I was very interested in politics before…But after what happened, I changed my mind.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the insistence of Martin&#39;s generation, the Reimanns paid compensation to former forced laborers and their families. But they did not stop there. They refocused their family foundation on combating antisemitism and strengthening democratic institutions. They also renamed the foundation in honor of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alfredlandecker.org/en&quot;>;Alfred Landecker&lt;/a>;, making him the narrative driver behind the more fundamental change they sought. Far from an isolated act of corporate atonement, then, this was an attempt by the next generation to use lessons from their family heritage to build a more just future.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;4. Leverage the family story as a source of competitive advantage.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;For some family business entrepreneurs, the next venture can begin with a step back. So it was for British restaurateurs (and sisters) Helen and Lisa Tse, whose family heritage empowered their rise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their grandmother, Lily Kwok, had emigrated from Hong Kong in 1956 and settled in Manchester, where she and her daughter Mabel built one of Britain&#39;s first Chinese restaurants. But the business eventually went bankrupt, the victim of racism and Chinese gangs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The story might have ended there. Instead, Helen and Lisa picked up the threads of their family narrative and carried it forward. Abandoning successful professional careers, they established their own Manchester restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sweetmandarin.com/&quot;>;Sweet Mandarin&lt;/a>;, in 2004. But the restaurant only took off when Helen published a best-selling memoir about her grandmother. With this narrative platform, the sisters branched out into other endeavors, like cookbooks and cookery classes, tied to their own life stories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For the Tse sisters, family heritage proved to be a source of competitive advantage. By recovering an immigrant&#39;s tale with universal appeal, they gained acceptance outside of their own ethnic communities. And by situating themselves in an entrepreneurial tradition spanning three generations, they created a sense of longevity that evoked quality and trustworthiness, even as they also innovated new products alongside recipes inherited from their grandmother.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Family legacy is not a monologue; it&#39;s a dialogue, a collective story that belongs to the whole family. When families think of legacy in these terms, they empower younger generations to harness that story to their own purposes, drawing strength from their elders. Legacy, in short, becomes not a burden but a blessing — one that can help families sustain wealth and purpose long into the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Identify the Right Strategic Goals for Your Company]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_09_670123874.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;cyano66/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In setting strategic objectives, companies usually end up with a list of worthy but vague aspirations. The secret to getting a list of clearly defined and measurable objectives is to anchor them in what you, as a company&amp;#8217;s leaders, want to get from your stakeholders. This leads you to defining desired behavioral outcomes, even fairly obvious ones like buying more. The debate can then move to thinking about how to trigger that behavior, and progress toward these outcomes can be described in measures that are in dollars, like revenue; quantities, like units sold; or percentages, like market share. Thinking in this way sounds prosaic, even obvious, but it is an effective way of getting a management team to think clearly about what they need to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-identify-the-right-strategic-goals-for-your-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann is the CEO of my country&#39;s largest independent, not-for-profit aged-care provider, offering residential aged care, retirement living, and at-home support. It was established well over a hundred years ago and is set in many of its ways. One of these is how strategic objective-setting is conducted. But Ann&#39;s not happy with the process. I asked her, “Why not?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;She explained. “When we get together to discuss our future direction as a business, we invariably get to the point where we need to write down our objectives. If we&#39;re using a facilitator, and we usually do, that person will walk over to a flipchart or whiteboard and write &#39;Objectives&#39; at the top. Then everyone piles in brainstorming to produce a list that&#39;s far too long.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“And you whittle that list down?” I asked.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Yes,” Ann continued. “The discussion and arm-wrestling then start with the aim of reducing the items to about half a dozen. After some considerable time, my exhausted and frustrated colleagues are only too happy to move on to the next agenda item.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Ann explained how her team was usually not content with the result. “Nor am I,” she added, “because invariably the &#39;Objectives&#39; list contains a hodgepodge of activities, nice-to-haves, and vague statements of intent.” Ann showed me her latest result:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;To become an employer of choice.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To grow the business by opening additional centers.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To maintain stability in resident and client care.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To manage risks and crises effectively.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To secure compliance with regulatory authorities.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To transform operations by adopting additional technology.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Maybe your own endeavors have produced a similar list. You might be wondering: What&#39;s wrong with this? The answer is: Plenty.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Any strategy she comes up with will have to specify what the company can do to meet the needs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;each key stakeholder group&lt;/a>;: residents, clients, employees, suppliers, shareholders, and the community. This means that her business will have to take a &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the-volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;position on the factors important to each of those groups&lt;/a>;. For instance, Ann&#39;s management team must set policy on working conditions, pay, organization culture, and so on for employees. What should guide these decisions? And how will Ann know if the decisions are progressing the organization? How will she measure this?&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The answers should be her list of strategic objectives. But Ann&#39;s hodgepodge doesn&#39;t deliver a clear line of sight between the business&#39;s competitive stance for each key stakeholder group and the results. How can you tell if a strategy is working? It&#39;s as though the list of objectives exists in a black hole.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Shift Your Thinking About Objective-Setting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The trick to breaking away is to flip your perspective and ask what your organization wants &lt;em>;from&lt;/em>; its key stakeholders. (This comes as an “aha” moment for most managers.) These will be your strategic objectives. For example, consider revenue from customers, innovation from employees, and support from the community. Your thinking must shift to be outside-in if you are to produce successful strategic objectives. If you picture organization objective-setting this way, you can see how it can be broken into a stakeholder-by-stakeholder exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 1: Identify a behavioral outcome for each stakeholder group.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;To illustrate, let me share a story. One CEO I advise, Stuart, heads up a mutual bank with “members.” I ran a workshop for him and his managers. We identified the credit union&#39;s key stakeholders, one of which was, naturally, members. To break through the traditional brainstorming hodgepodge, I asked the group a seemingly simple question: “What do you want your members to do?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This came as a surprisingly fresh approach to the group and required them to think more deeply. After some discussion, we got this: “To get members to borrow more and to get potential members to become members.” I explained how I call this a &lt;em>;behavioral outcome&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 2: Convert behavioral outcomes into organization objectives.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I then led Stuart&#39;s group to the second step, which is to convert this behavioral outcome to an &lt;em>;organization objective.&lt;/em>; This usually starts with “to increase” or “to decrease.” After careful consideration and debate, the group agreed to: “To increase revenue from current and future members.” Notice “future.” This will be driven by positioning on the strategic factors relevant to members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Why didn&#39;t I just start there at the second step? The reason is that invariably the process falls back into becoming a hodgepodge. Identifying a behavioral outcome for each key stakeholder group first anchors organization objectives, which then become clear and measurable&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Step 3: Identify measures.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This brings me to the third step: identifying &lt;em>;measures&lt;/em>;, a short list of which is usually referred to as key performance indicators or KPIs. This can be tricky, as all sorts of things become labeled as KPIs in exercises like this. In the past, Stuart&#39;s organization had labeled actions by individuals and program descriptions as KPIs. So, I needed to point out that a key performance indicator is a key performance &lt;em>;measure.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The clincher for Stuart and his group came when I demonstrated that there are only three ways to measure results in business and that they can be neatly summarized by three symbols: $ (or the local currency), # (number of), and % (percentage). No one had condensed results for them in that way before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The advantage of this is that Stuart and his team now have a stakeholder-oriented objective for members that can be measured. Stuart can measure the total revenue generated by new and existing members; the number of new and existing members; and the bank&#39;s percentage of market share. Any strategies aimed at creating competitive advantage — around, for example, product range, customer service, and pricing — can be evaluated using these hard results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I do this for each of an organization&#39;s key stakeholders: customers, employees, suppliers, and so on. It always gets a management group to probe what the organization is really trying to achieve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;Your Objective-Setting Journey&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;If you want to produce clearly targeted strategy, you simply must avoid the standard practice of brainstorming to yield a list of strategic objectives. It leads to a hodgepodge of difficult-to-measure items, as Ann&#39;s experience demonstrates. Instead, rethink your journey by identifying who your key stakeholders are&amp;nbsp;— and what you want from them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This will provide you with clear and measurable outcomes that will help focus your organization&#39;s strategic positions for each of your key stakeholders. Strategic clarity will be your result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Will Working with AI Really Require?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_EdmonDeHaro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Edmon de Haro; filonmar/Getty Images (chip); JulieAlexK/Getty Images (glasses)&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities, and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent. To do this effectively, they need to think about where and how this technology will be used to assist people in their work &amp;#8212; where people and machines will collaborate &amp;#8212; and where either people or AI have skills that give them a clear advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-will-working-with-ai-really-require?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Despite concerns about machines replacing human workers, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/projects/expanding-ais-impact-with-organizational-learning/&quot;>;research &lt;/a>;challenges the overhyped claims of ascendant AI. In most knowledge-intensive tasks, workers will more likely find themselves augmented &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0007681318300387&quot;>;in partnership with machines&lt;/a>; than automated out of a job. Humans and machines will simultaneously collaborate and compete with one another, like a track team competing in various events. In some events, like the 100-yard dash, teammates compete against each other, but in others, such as the relay race, they work together towards a common goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In such a relationship, humans and AI systems both need distinct competitive and cooperative skills. Competitive skills refer to the unique advantages that either humans or AI possess over the other, while cooperative skills enhance the ability of humans and AI to work together effectively. To foster a symbiotic relationship between humans and AI, organizations must find the appropriate balance between investing in human skills and technological capabilities — and think strategically about how they attract and retain talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Humans&#39; competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;AI may not replace workers in a human-centered workplace, but it could fundamentally transform their work. In order to remain relevant and indispensable, humans need to work &lt;em>;with &lt;/em>;and &lt;em>;against &lt;/em>;the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effectively collaborating with AI systems — working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; them — requires data-driven analytical abilities, but also understanding about the capabilities and limitations of the machines (areas where human intervention is most required), how to interpret and contextualize AI-generated insights, and the ethical considerations of AI-powered decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Data-centric skills:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the results generated by algorithms to inform and support decision-making. A &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/boost-your-teams-data-literacy&quot;>;recent survey&lt;/a>; highlighted (1) the ability to distinguish relevant data and evaluate its credibility, (2) capability to validate results by testing hypotheses through A/B testing, and (3) skill in creating and tailoring clear and comprehensible visualizations to communicate results to multiple stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AI literacy:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how algorithms work, how they can support and augment human decision-making as well as the limitations and biases that may be present in their decision-making processes. Area experts will likely take on the responsibility of developing fairness criteria for algorithmic outcomes that promote equity, especially for vulnerable populations, and continuously auditing algorithmic results against these criteria.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Algorithmic communication:&lt;/strong>; Understanding how to articulate human needs and objectives to algorithms, as well as how to interpret and explain the results generated by algorithms to others is important and &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-digital-mindset-what-it-really-takes-to-thrive-in-the-age-of-data-algorithms-and-ai/10413&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that we often err by talking to machines – even advanced AI tools – as though they were human. We do better when we recognize that we should talk to machines in specific ways that build on their strengths. For example, through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/prompt-engineering-ai-chatgpt-jobs-explained-2023-3&quot;>;“prompt engineering,”&lt;/a>; or crafting prompts to elicit most effective responses from AI systems, humans can teach AI models to produce the desired results for specific tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Humans&#39; competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;People also need to hone the human-centered skills and abilities that cannot be replicated by machines — that help them work &lt;em>;against&lt;/em>; AI partners — such as those rooted in emotional intelligence (eg, communication skills for interacting with other human stakeholders), a strategic and holistic perspective, critical thinking and intuitive decision making. These include:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Emotional intelligence:&lt;/strong>; The ability to recognize one&#39;s own emotions and reflect on them in the context of interacting with algorithms, as well as understanding and communicating the emotional implications of algorithm-generated results. For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-chatgpt-chatbot-workplace-call-centers-5cd2142a?st=6fma808gi52qayz&amp;amp;reflink=article_email_share&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR0oBB-2wT03uN-8OV3kaJGNXqDPKW-ZJ_7hc8KdYMYlHPK3dCrqxJr-GcA&quot;>;human customer service agents&lt;/a>; may not solely rely on scripts or real-time advice provided by the AI agents, but instead personalize solutions by empathetically comprehending the customers&#39; requirements or feelings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Holistic and strategic thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to consider the big picture and understand how algorithmic results fit into the larger context of a problem or decision. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2153353922007507&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, algorithmic inference can inform pathologists, but they still need to consider factors such as patients&#39; medical history, lifestyle, and overall health to arrive at an informed and comprehensive diagnosis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Creativity and outside-the-box thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to think creatively and use algorithms in novel and innovative ways. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/si/en/pages/strategy-operations/articles/AI-in-marketing.html&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, AI systems are used to analyze massive consumer data and identify patterns in the interests and behavior of a target audience, but it is the creative thinking of marketers that will craft a message that resonates with the audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Critical and ethical thinking:&lt;/strong>; The ability to critically assess machine inferences, and to understand the ethical implications and responsibilities associated with using algorithms, including privacy and accountability. As generative AI such as ChatGPT are increasingly integrated into various products, experts in different business domains are needed to work alongside these systems to continuously address &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/chatbots-got-big-and-their-ethical-red-flags-got-bigger/&quot;>;potential false or biased information &lt;/a>;to which these systems are prone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI&#39;s competitive and cooperative skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It is not only humans that must acquire new capabilities. While AI systems are rapidly expanding their competitive abilities over humans, they still need to improve their cooperative skills in order to be widely adopted by organizations. In particular, the lack of explainability remains a challenge in high-stakes decisions, hindering accountability and compliance with legal requirements. For example, if the AI&#39;s decision-making process remains opaque to medical professionals, it will impede the adoption of these systems in healthcare, even if these systems deliver near-optimal decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s cooperative skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To work effectively with human partners, AI systems need skills such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;NLP (Natural Language Processing):&lt;/strong>; The ability to process, analyze, understand and mimic human language. Systems like ChatGPT excel at interacting with humans because they make it easy for people to ask questions and express themselves in a natural way, including expressing emotions like excitement, frustration, or surprise. The reality, however, is that these systems are far from &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4213593&quot;>;sentient&lt;/a>;. Situations that go beyond a function are best done by a human or with human supervision. For example, AI can analyze and reveal patterns in healthcare data, but it should not replace a physician&#39;s role in providing individualized care to patients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Explainability:&lt;/strong>; The ability to provide humans with clear and understandable explanations of its decision-making process and results. The inherent inscrutability of deep-learning AI is an ongoing challenge that requires multiple solutions, including building an &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/when-and-why-you-should-explain-how-your-ai-works&quot;>;“explainability framework”&lt;/a>; that addresses the risks of AI black boxes to specific industries and organizations. Technological solutions may also involve adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7768142/&quot;>;explainability engines&lt;/a>;, which offer human-readable explanations for AI &#39;systems&#39; decisions and predictions, particularly for critical areas like healthcare and finance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Adaptability and personalization:&lt;/strong>; The ability to learn from previous interactions and personalize responses based on individual users. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3252218/cortana-explained-why-microsofts-virtual-assistant-is-wired-for-business.html&quot;>;personal intelligent assistants&lt;/a>; are growing in importance in helping people tackle information and communication overload. By analyzing a user&#39;s activities, these assistants work collaboratively with workers in an individualized manner, enhancing their productivity in areas such as time management, meeting organization, and communication assistance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Context awareness:&lt;/strong>; The ability to understand the context in which an interaction is taking place and respond accordingly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2021/03/30/how-chat-commerce-is-changing-e-commerce/?sh=570d87f1142c&quot;>;For instance&lt;/a>;, in e-commerce websites, chatbots that present context awareness can analyze a user&#39;s previous inquiries and purchase history to offer solutions or recommendations that are more pertinent to the customer&#39;s needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;AI&#39;s competitive skills&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;AI systems continue to present unique competitive advantages, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Analytical capacities:&lt;/strong>; The ability to perform complex calculations, process large amounts of data, and identify patterns and relationships within the data. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/louiscolumbus/2019/08/01/ai-is-predicting-the-future-of-online-fraud-detection/?sh=6cdf5e3174f5&quot;>;For example&lt;/a>;, AI systems are becoming more competent at detecting fraudulent transactions in massive datasets of credit card transactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Generativity:&lt;/strong>; The ability to generate novel and unique outputs that are not simply reproductions of existing data. Using large models and neural networks to analyze patterns, generative AI is transforming the creation of image, text, and even music that resembles those created by human experts. These systems automated content generation, improve content quality, increase content variety, and offer personalized content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Performance at scale:&lt;/strong>; The ability to scale operations efficiently, handle a large number of real-time transactions and support large-scale applications without sacrificing performance. For example, AI systems have demonstrated superior ability to process &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/industries/financial%20services/our%20insights/ai%20powered%20decision%20making%20for%20the%20bank%20of%20the%20future/ai-powered-decision-making-for-the-bank-of-the-future.pdf&quot;>;thousands of credit card applications&lt;/a>; real-time or offer “&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/algorithmic-management-the-role-of-ai-in-managing-workforces/&quot;>;algorithmic management&lt;/a>;” of thousands of Uber drivers and riders simultaneously, creating a structured and consistent operational framework at an unprecedented scale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Racing with and against the machines&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The challenge for organizations trying to build a strategy for using new and more AI tools lies in designing organizational systems that effectively balance the competitive and cooperative skills of humans and AI. Organizations that seek to strike this balance should consider the following:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Democratize data to foster the continuous development of competitive human and machine skills. &lt;/strong>;AI systems can generate data insights at scale and detect patterns often missed by the human eye, but translating that competitiveness into business growth and agility requires the very human skills of strategic thinking and creativity. To enable this type of collaboration, companies should democratize access to data throughout all levels of their organization. Nearly every role within your organization should be working alongside data analytics to inform how to make the workflows more efficient, make data-driven decisions and ultimately inform a better understanding of how to service the end customer. The more data visibility AI can give your workforce, the greater ability for humans to apply and develop their uniquely competitive skills.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Look outside your own organization&#39;s walls for cooperative human skills. &lt;/strong>;A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/operations/articles/future-of-gig-economy-shared-services-delivery-model.html&quot;>;Deloitte study&lt;/a>; found that nearly half (49%) of traditional workers — full-time employees — updated their skills more than a year ago or have never engaged in skills development, whereas 60% of the alternative workforce — defined as gig workers, freelancers, independent workers, and crowd workers — updated their skills within the past six months. In fact, 44% of alternative workers at large organizations hold a postgraduate degree according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upwork.com/resources/enterprise-companies-need-to-know-freelancers&quot;>;new research by Upwork&lt;/a>;. This is likely due to the fact that most technical skill sets, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/EPYMNBJA&quot;>;research by IBM&lt;/a>;, experience a half-life of 2.5 years. And, according to Upwork&#39;s database, the top in-demand skills are technical and related to web, mobile and software development. If your organization is struggling to keep up with cooperative human skills to work alongside machines, it may be time to engage a broader ecosystem of skills outside your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Don&#39;t let geography limit the skills your company is hiring for.&lt;/strong>; The pandemic ushered in a new era of work as many organizations learned work could be done remotely. Technical work can be done almost anywhere in the world as machines have largely made geography irrelevant to finding the skills you need to cooperate with machines. Enabling remote work strategies will ensure your organization is equipped to capture the ever-changing talent landscape and help you win in the race with and against the machines.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By focusing on the balance of these skills, organizations can reap the benefits of an infinity loop between AI and human competitive skills. In this balance, humans may work toward “coopetition” as an arrangement where parties engage in both cooperative and competitive behavior. In such a relationship with AI systems, humans may leverage both the partnership with machines and their own competitive edge against the machine. This relationship helps to maintain their relevance and indispensability as algorithms are increasingly working as team members or even managers (ie, algorithmic management).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This formulation offered here helps shape the future of education and skill development, by emphasizing the importance of focusing on skills that give humans a competitive advantage over machines, rather than those that we have already lost to machines. For example, the use of calculators and spell checkers no longer serve as our advantage as we surrendered these tasks to technology long ago.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Global Information Sharing Can Help Stop Cybercrime]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_3858085.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The Cybercrime Atlas is an initiative hosted by the World Economic Forum&amp;#8217;s (WEF) Partnership Against Cybercrime. While it&amp;#8217;s still in prototype stages, it&amp;#8217;s being designed to provide a platform for academic analysts, cybersecurity companies, national and international law enforcement agencies, and global businesses to share knowledge about the cybercriminal ecosystem. At its core, the Atlas project is a database about cybercrime. Information could come from government alerts, cryptocurrency analysis companies, platform providers, court records, and publicly available materials &amp;#8212; anything the analysts can identify that might be relevant to understanding the entirety of the criminal ecosystem. Analysts could then use this database to generate multiple different views or maps of various parts of the cybercriminal ecosystem. For example, one analyst might be interested in ransom payments and could use Atlas to help understand how illicit funds are moving. Another might be interested in identifying the platforms that appear to host a large number of criminal actors. Another &amp;#8220;map&amp;#8221; or view might focus on the relationships between different criminal groups. By creating an international information repository based on public data and voluntarily shared information, cybersecurity practitioners can create a tool that will enable them to fight cybercrime more effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-global-information-sharing-can-help-stop-cybercrime?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Cybercrime is big business. While reliable statistics are difficult to come by, estimates of the global cost of cybercrimes range from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/chart/28878/expected-cost-of-cybercrime-until-2027/&quot;>;trillions to tens of trillions of dollars annually&lt;/a>;. Regardless of the precise figure, cybercrime clearly drains significant resources from the global economy and poses a substantial threat to global security and prosperity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Why has the problem grown so large? Cybercrime has some characteristics that make it difficult for governments to fight:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;It has an inherently transnational structure, while law enforcement operates within national borders.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Some nation-states harbor and protect cybercriminals, while others turn a blind eye, and still others lack the capacity to combat the problem.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Defenders lack systemic knowledge and insights regarding the full extent of cybercriminal activities, which in turn inhibits effective targeting.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Cybercrime groups have evolved from two or three people working together into large, distributed organizations with extensive, complex, and sophisticated infrastructures that are difficult for any single entity to understand.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The global internet&#39;s staggeringly large data volume makes it difficult to separate the malicious activity from the “noise.”&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;The internet allows criminals to scale in the same way that legitimate businesses do, but it also allows them to obfuscate their true numbers, locations, and identities.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Overcoming these challenges will require innovation and adaptation in many areas, such as updating international legal regimes and making operational collaboration between the public and private sectors a regular occurrence. Another key area for innovation includes understanding the nature of the criminal ecosystem.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Understanding the Cybercrime Ecosystem&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While it may seem strange to apply the term “ecosystem” to crime, it aptly describes the way that cyber criminals operate. Cybercriminals are no longer just disaffected individuals wearing hoodies and living in their parents&#39; basements. Instead, they tend to operate in loose, distributed groups and exist within a large network of suppliers, coders, buyers, financiers, and partners. Few criminals conduct an entire operation from beginning to end without any support from someone else. While this complexity provides substantial benefits in terms of efficiency and effectiveness, it also creates an opportunity for law enforcement and defenders, if we can take advantage of it. By relying on an extensive ecosystem to carry out their activities, cybercriminals have made themselves more vulnerable to disruption.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;Managing Cyber Risk&quot; dek=&quot;Exploring the challenges and the solutions.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/managing-cyber-risk&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;Managing Cyber Risk&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Exploring the challenges and the solutions. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s where the Cybercrime Atlas project comes in. The Atlas is an initiative hosted by the World Economic Forum&#39;s (WEF) Partnership Against Cybercrime, designed to mitigate some of the characteristics that make cybercrime difficult to combat. Specifically, the Atlas initiative will provide a platform for academic analysts, cybersecurity companies, national and international law enforcement agencies, and global businesses to share knowledge about the cybercriminal ecosystem. During its initial standup, the WEF will host the secretariat for the project, supported by Fortinet, Microsoft, Paypal, and Santander. Other organizations, such as the Cyber Threat Alliance, will also support the initiative through in-kind donations of time and capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Mapping the Cybercrime Ecosystem &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At its core, the Atlas project is a database about cybercrime. While a database may seem somewhat pedestrian or anticlimactic compared to the size of the task, the power of correlating and combining information should not be underestimated. Further, the information in this database will not just be random bits of data, nor will it be limited to the technical indicators of compromise that cybersecurity companies usually share. Instead, it will bring in a wide range of data types from many different types of sources. Information could come from government alerts, cryptocurrency analysis companies, platform providers, court records, and publicly available materials — anything the analysts can identify that might be relevant to understanding the entirety of the criminal ecosystem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, analysts can use this database to generate multiple different views or maps of various parts of the cybercriminal ecosystem, hence the name “Atlas.” For example, one analyst might be interested in ransom payments and could use Atlas to help understand how illicit funds are moving. Another might be interested in identifying the platforms that appear to host a large number of criminal actors. Another “map” or view might focus on the relationships between different criminal groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These different views will support a wide array of activities, from the private, non-profit, and public sectors. A platform like Microsoft could use Atlas information to support legal action against actors abusing their services, while banks could use a payment map to try to recover stolen money. Law enforcement agencies could use an infrastructure map to identify targets for disruption or seizure. The list goes on. Given past experience, the Atlas project will likely support analysis we cannot yet anticipate.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These maps will have several benefits. First, they will identify the places where the criminals are most vulnerable to disruption by highlighting single points of failure. Second, since they will be based primarily on open-source information and private sector information, they will help governments target intelligence and law enforcement resources against the gaps that the private sector can&#39;t fill while avoiding areas where the private sector already has a lot of insight. Such focus would make law enforcement and intelligence collection more efficient and effective. It could even illuminate the makeup of criminal groups, making it harder for a group to seem like 1,000 people when it&#39;s really only 10. It will also provide a Rosetta Stone for understanding the various names attached to a given group by different companies, making it easier to correlate research and findings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By creating an international information repository based on public data and voluntarily shared information, cybersecurity practitioners can create a tool that will enable them to fight cybercrime more effectively. But regular businesses stand to benefit greatly from a project like the Cybercrime Atlas too. Reining in cybercrime would reduce not only the current economic burden of malicious activity like ransomware, but it would also enable businesses to continue expanding the services they offer online. Absent a change in its trajectory, the rampant criminality in cyberspace will inevitably drive some, possibly many, consumers and organizations to pull back from the digital ecosystem. It is not a law of nature that more and more activity will occur in cyberspace, and such a retrenchment is possible if we cannot make cyberspace safer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As of mid-2023, the Cybercrime Atlas is still in the prototype stage. As a leader of an information sharing organization, I have no illusions about the challenges associated with making a project like the Cybercrime Atlas successful. Yet, its foundation is strong and its promise as a tool to help defenders, law enforcement, and other analysts navigate the criminal landscape is large. Given what&#39;s at stake, we have an obligation to use every tool at our disposal to combat the pernicious threat posed by cybercrime.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[To Build a Top Performing Team, Ask for 85% Effort]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_08_1434391518.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anchiy/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;An outdated way of thinking about peak performance is: &amp;#8220;maximum effort = maximum results.&amp;#8221; But research shows that it doesn&amp;#8217;t actually work that way in reality. Here&amp;#8217;s what actually works: The 85% rule, which counterintuitively suggests that to reach maximum output, you need to refrain from giving maximum effort. Operating at 100% effort all of the time will result in burnout and ultimately less-optimal results. While the precise number 85% may just be a rule of thumb, it&amp;#8217;sa helpful one for managers who want to create high-performance teams without burning people out.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Despite some companies&#39; attempts, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/beyond-burned-out&quot;>;we can&#39;t fix today&#39;s burnout culture with a wellness app&lt;/a>;. What it takes, instead, is a mindset and culture shift among managers and organizations everywhere.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The old management mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;An outdated way of thinking about peak performance is “maximum effort = maximum results.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/cne.920180503&quot;>;It doesn&#39;t actually work that way in reality&lt;/a>;, but many managers still believe that it does. They might talk a good game about “practicing self-care,” but their core assumptions are often more akin to a bad 1980s motivational speaker. (Think: “No pain, no gain,” “No guts, no glory,” and “Give it 110%!”)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When managers expect 80+ hours a week from people while offering Friday yoga to combat stress, they unintentionally create a toxic contradiction. It&#39;s a classic example of what we call in psychology a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://dictionary.apa.org/double-bind&quot;>;double bind&lt;/a>;”: Employees can&#39;t talk about the contradiction, and they can&#39;t talk about not being able to talk about it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, many well-intended efforts to end the burnout epidemic don&#39;t actually work. If you think individual overachievers are solely to blame for exhaustion, then you&#39;ll only end up addressing the wrong problem. Consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/mhi/our-insights/addressing-employee-burnout-are-you-solving-the-right-problem&quot;>;McKinsey&#39;s research on burnout&lt;/a>;, which showed that “in all 15 countries and across all dimensions assessed, toxic workplace behavior was the biggest predictor of burnout symptoms and intent to leave by a large margin.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only does this old mindset &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; produce high performance, it also creates a downward spiral of toxicity begetting burnout begetting toxicity. What we need instead is a new management mindset, supported by data, for how to really get the best out of our people. Instead of “maximum effort = maximum results,” a better formula is: “optimal effort = maximum results.” Less effort can actually lead to more success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The new management mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s what actually works: the 85% rule. The 85% rule counterintuitively suggests that to reach maximum output, you need to refrain from giving maximum effort. Operating at 100% effort all of the time will result in burnout and ultimately less-optimal results.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, when sprinters are told to accelerate to their 100% level too soon, they end up &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1260/1747-9541.6.3.479&quot;>;running a slower race overall&lt;/a>;. As Carl Lewis, who won nine Olympic gold medals, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elitetrack.com/forums/topic/carl-lewis-interview-with-info-on-tellez-training-methods/&quot;>;explains&lt;/a>;, the notion of “no pain, no gain” is ridiculous. He says, “Your training should be sensible. In many cases it is more important to rest than it is to drive yourself to the point of pain.” Lewis&#39;s coach, Tom Tellez, suggests that the peak performer in sprinting relax their jaw, face, and eyes. “Don&#39;t grit your teeth,” he advises. “If you do, that tension will run all the way down your neck and trunk to your legs.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to build a high-performing team — without burning people out&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;Create a “done for the day” time&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Where possible, managers should establish a “done for the day” time. When managers are ambiguous about the length of workdays, they risk introducing decision fatigue, diminishing returns, or even getting negative returns from their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Toxic managers see setting a reasonable hard stop for the day as impossible. A colleague told me that their boss said in no uncertain terms: “You can&#39;t get ahead here if you want to be home for dinner with your family.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transactional managers see employees having a done-for-the-day time as a necessary evil: “I suppose you need to do what you need to do.” They let people keep to the schedule begrudgingly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transformational managers insist upon a reasonable time for employees to leave work. For example, when a new employee at a private equity firm was eager to make a good impression, he stayed late. After all, he had been trained at previous companies to expect kudos for the extra effort. But this company and manager were different. When his manager saw him still sitting at his desk after everyone else had gone home, he said, “Why are you still here? We don&#39;t stay late here unless there is an absolute emergency. We want you to be fresh tomorrow morning. Please go home.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask for a little less than maximum capacity&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effort and fatigue can create confusion for people regarding the quality of their performance. People can mistake the perception of maximum effort with what actually produces maximum results. However, &lt;a href=&quot;https://coachesinsider.com/track-x-country/highest-effort-doesnt-always-equal-highest-performance-article/&quot;>;the highest effort doesn&#39;t always equal the highest performance&lt;/a>;. Managers can take advantage of this by inviting team members to work a little below what they perceive to be their maximum capacity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help coach employees to get to and stay in this sweet spot, managers can ask, “What does it feel like to be at 100% intensity?” and then follow up with: “How can you keep this closer to the 85% level?” This type of&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/ptj/article-abstract/64/3/343/2727707&quot;>; perceived level of exertion&lt;/a>; is a concept used in physical rehab to prevent latent — or hidden — fatigue, but it can also be used by managers to help their employees stay in their sweet spot (see the following figure).&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357760&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/04/W230417_MCKEOWN_PERFORMANCE_85_PERCENT_RULE_EFFORT_PERFORMANCE_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask “how am I making your work more stressful than it needs to be?”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Top performers are typically already self-motivated, so managing them like everyone else will only exhaust them, leading them to become a flight risk. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://osf.io/h6qnf/&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; at the&lt;a href=&quot;https://medicine.yale.edu/childstudy/services/community-and-schools-programs/center-for-emotional-intelligence/&quot;>; Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence and the Faas Foundation&lt;/a>; of over 1,000 US employees found that 20% of employees reported being both highly engaged and having high burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This “engaged-exhausted group” were passionate about their work, but also had a high level of stress and frustration. These were the employees with the highest risk of quitting their jobs — higher even than unengaged employees. This suggests that companies may lose their most capable employees not due to a lack of engagement, but rather because of their high stress and burnout levels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To avoid this, managers can ask their top performers a simple but powerful question — “How am I making your work more stressful than it needs to be?” — and then take the necessary actions to improve upon the situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Encourage 85%-right decisions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When making decisions as a team, don&#39;t push for “100% perfect.” Let people know when an 85%-right decision is acceptable.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0191886901002021&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; has uncovered two distinct types of perfectionists. The first is “&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/12/the-pros-and-cons-of-perfectionism-according-to-research&quot;>;excellence-seeking&lt;/a>;” perfectionists: people who hold high standards for themselves and others. The second type is “failure-avoiding” perfectionists: people who are consistently anxious that their work is not sufficient or adequate, who fear losing the esteem of others if they fail to attain perfection.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Asking for 85%-right decisions takes unnecessary pressure off your highest-performing employees — and it keeps your team moving forward, rather than waiting for the 100%-right decision before they take action.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Watch out for high-pressure language&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As a manager, it is vital to be mindful of the language you use when communicating with your team. The use of high-pressure terms such as “ASAP,” “NEED,” or “URGENT” in emails or meetings can create excessive stress and pressure for your team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To avoid this, it&#39;s essential to foster open communication about genuine deadlines, the reasons behind them, and the potential trade-offs. Instead of expecting employees to always agree to every request, consider asking them, “What do you need to say no to in order to say yes to this?” By granting autonomy in choosing their projects, you can ensure that your &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/06/how-are-you-protecting-your-high-performers-from-burnout&quot;>;star employees maintain high performance levels while also avoiding burnout&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;End meetings 10 minutes early&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A manager shared this with me recently: “If you can be any kind of manager, be the kind who ends the meeting early.” It struck me as both funny and true.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many employees still feel like they live the “Zoom, eat, sleep, repeat” life that was so common during the pandemic. Certainly, far more meetings are now held on video than ever before. And we know that video “exhaust(s) the human mind and body” &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.stanford.edu/2021/02/23/four-causes-zoom-fatigue-solutions/&quot;>;faster than in-person meetings or just being on the phone&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/brain-research&quot;>;Research from Microsoft&#39;s Human Factors Lab&lt;/a>; found that our brains work differently when we take 10-minute breaks between meetings. That small break stops stress from building up, while back-to-back meetings decrease people&#39;s ability to focus and engage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The researchers asked 14 people to take part in video meetings while wearing electroencephalogram (EEG) equipment to monitor their brain activity. Each person participated in two different types of meeting sessions. On day one, they attended four back-to-back meetings with no breaks in between. On another day, the meetings had 10-minute breaks in between. Here&#39;s what the EEGs showed:&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-357852&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/04/W230417_MCKEOWN_PERFORMANCE_85_PERCENT_RULE_BREAKS_360-2.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The cooler colors in the visual representation indicate lower stress levels from having breaks between the meetings. However, those who were deprived of breaks experienced a gradual rise in beta wave activity, indicating a buildup of stress over time, as shown by a shift in colors from cool to hot in the visual. The chart represents the relative difference in beta activity between break and no-break conditions at the beginning of each meeting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By ending meetings 10 minutes early, managers can help keep their employees out of “red brain” and keep them in “blue brain,” where they can do their best thinking.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Set your own intensity level to 85%&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s important that managers also set their &lt;em>;own&lt;/em>; minds to 85% intensity to model to their team that it&#39;s okay not to be stressed out of their minds all the time. When managers say that employees should not work late nights or on weekends, but then send emails at 2 am on Sunday morning, their actions speak louder than their words.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/07/your-bosss-work-life-balance-matters-as-much-as-your-own&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that employees look to their bosses for cues far more than many managers realize. In a curious finding, researchers found that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/intl/blog/work-matters/201005/how-often-do-you-look-at-your-boss-baboons-do-it-every-20-or-30-seconds&quot;>;baboons look to their alpha male “boss” every 20 to 30 seconds&lt;/a>;, and humans may not be so different. So, if you&#39;re going to write emails late and on weekends, at least schedule them to be sent at 9 am Monday morning.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The 85% rule may seem counterintuitive. However, in this time of ongoing, persistent burnout, it has the power of relevancy. As Dr. Stephen Ilardi, a psychologist at the University of Kansas, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Depression-Cure-6-Step-Program-without/dp/0738213888&quot;>;written&lt;/a>;, “Human beings were never designed for the poorly nourished, sedentary, indoor, sleep-deprived, socially-isolated, frenzied pace of 21st-century life.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Certainly, we can do better. Managers who adopt the 85% rule as their new mindset can help to reduce this frenzy while actually improving their team&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-Powered Automation As A Route To Boosting Productivity - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM ZOHO]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/ai-powered-automation-as-a-route-to-boosting-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-358514&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/HBR_AI-image.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;How AI-powered CRMs are changing the game and solving the customer relationship challenge&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For sales and marketing teams, the residual peaks and troughs of pandemic-era business suggest a challenging future of independent buyers and mounting consumer expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The B2B buyer group is increasingly self-starting. Virtually 100% of tech buyers now want &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.trustradius.com/vendor-blog/2022-b2b-buying-disconnect-the-age-of-the-self-serve-buyer?utm_source=cision&amp;amp;utm_medium=content_syndication&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2022_06_b2bdisconnect&amp;amp;utm_term=v&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;a self-serve experience&lt;/a>;. The demand for digital sales and marketing is growing in tandem, with younger buyers most likely to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitalcommerce360.com/2023/02/20/the-stark-digital-gap-between-b2bs-older-and-younger-buyers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;digital channels to engage and to make purchases&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consumer expectations for self-servicing are higher than ever, led by the standouts of customer experience in each industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales and marketing priorities have shifted, no longer going all out on growth but instead juggling &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescommunicationscouncil/2022/12/09/navigating-economic-uncertainty-three-ways-marketing-can-help-sales-in-2023/?sh=4c7845476af3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;customer retention and sustained growth&lt;/a>;. And that puts more pressure on already taxed teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this climate, sales and marketing teams need to be hyperflexible—to interact when, where, and how their customers want. And they need to prioritize personalization, tailoring experiences to meet rising expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By automating tasks and providing real-time data, with artificial intelligence (AI)–powered automation supporting a customer relationship management (CRM) platform, these teams can perform at once-unattainable levels of efficiency and growth.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Doing More with Less&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At many organizations, the customer relationship challenge is to meet new needs while legacy operations and the costs of changing those operations stand in the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But investing in a CRM with AI-enabled automation can shift an organization&#39;s repetitive tasks—composing follow-up emails, scheduling, managing socials—to clear time-sapping jobs from the schedules of employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-enabled CRMs can eliminate silos by collating data from multiple sources to offer sales and marketing teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.infoworld.com/article/3624010/3-ways-ai-improves-crm.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;actionable, data-driven guidance&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When teams can offload menial tasks, they can regain the autonomy to work on value-adding, satisfying responsibilities, such as building relationships with customers and closing deals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And this level of intelligent automation can significantly cut costs. With increased efficiency and productivity, growing businesses can hire staff who can think big and spend on automatable tasks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Real Relationships, Not Robots &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-powered CRM isn&#39;t all chatbots and no employees. The optimal AI- and automation-powered CRM gives its human workforce the right insights to apply as they believe best suit their customers so sales and marketing teams can offer more engaging, more satisfying experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;An AI CRM platform can strengthen relationship management in three ways:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Automation removes internal friction and accelerates processes among teams and systems, with a customer-facing payoff: connected data and reduced human error help processes go faster.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;By automatically tracking any behavioral changes in customers and prospects, sales and marketing teams can easily understand where each account is along its buyer or customer journey and support it accordingly. AI automation can take that even further, predicting sale probabilities and triggering alerts to notify teams of customers&#39; needs based on their behavior.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;It can serve the workforce with the optimal combination of insights and time. Beyond consolidating customer information into one database, an AI automation–enriched CRM can take on repetitive tasks like scheduling content or following up on low-priority prospects.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Revolutionary Relationship Management&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CRM platforms empowered by AI automation transform the way we work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A sales and marketing team that can easily access actionable insights can just as easily create custom reports and dashboards and measure operations in real time to drive sustainable growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.zoho.com/portal/en/kb/crm/zia-artificial-intelligence/zia/zia/articles/zia-overview&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;conversational AI assistant&lt;/a>; can fetch information and take dictation, providing immediate answers over voice or text chat. Beyond that, AI-powered data mining and machine learning capabilities can yield powerful insights and personalized recommendations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-augmented data can quickly reveal conversion predictions and alert teams to anomalies that might otherwise be harder or take longer to detect, such as drops in new leads or an increase in calls. These capabilities can make a significant impact: a sales and marketing team that once had to wait for reports so it could analyze them to change strategy can instead receive these updates and identify anomalies—and act on them—in real time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;New Efficiencies Without New Disruptions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sales and marketing teams are under increasing pressure to achieve both great customer retention and sustained growth. Productivity is key to those efforts. But many organizations are already working as productively as they can in their current modes of operation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To serve customers and prospects better than your competitors can, it&#39;s time to change the game. With AI automation integrated into a CRM platform to connect sales and marketing, data and customers, your organization can gain the bandwidth it needs to accomplish levels of productivity and growth that were until recently unattainable—delighting your customers, leading your sector, and growing your business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;To find out how Zoho CRM can boost your teams&#39; productivity with intelligent automation, &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zohocrm.com/request-callback.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;talk to us today&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:55:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>