<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How the Pandemic Changed Marketing Channels]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Adrià Voltà 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;疫情无疑改变了营销人员实施渠道策略的方式，并且没有单一的成功途径。由于渠道比以往任何时候都多，营销人员需要确定哪些渠道可以增加明显的价值，而忘记其他渠道。进入某个渠道可能很诱人，因为那里有你的竞争对手。但由于客户时间和注意力有限，营销人员必须战略性地确定他们可以在哪些渠道中产生最大的影响。作者研究了从 CMO 调查中收集到的五种大流行后渠道策略，并分析了营销人员如何运用这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how- the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 大流行促使公司快速适应和响应新的客户需求。这种动态最明显的方式之一是公司为与客户互动并向客户销售产品而采用的营销渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，发生了什么变化？最新版本的&lt;a href=&quot;https://cmosurvey.org/results/&quot;>;CMO 调查&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;从 314 位美国营销领导者那里收集到了五个主要趋势。我们还提供分析和建议，帮助营销人员落实这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;渠道正在扩大。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近三分之二 (61%) 的公司表示增加了他们使用的渠道数量。虽然 B2B 和 B2C 公司都如此，但 B2C 服务领先，77% 的公司表示有所增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;渠道扩张的一个好处是，消费者现在可以选择自己喜欢的与公司互动的方式。然而，拓展渠道需要大量的努力和投资。在介入之前，营销团队应该问：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;新渠道是否会吸引新客户进入该类别，从竞争对手那里抢走现有客户，还是增加现有客户的钱包份额？&lt;/li>; &lt; li>;从品牌和客户体验的角度来看，更多的渠道是否一致？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;接触点是否指向相同的利益和品牌形象？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;渠道是否无缝连接？&lt; /li>; &lt;li>;客户是否了解他们通过使用不同渠道获得的价值以及如何在这些渠道之间轻松移动？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;面对面 (F2F) 渠道仍然存在好吧。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;只有 6.7% 的公司表示他们的 F2F 渠道已完全数字化，这意味着大多数公司仍保持 F2F。此外，28% 的公司正在开设新的 F2F 渠道。&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;鉴于公司和市场的数字化转型，我们预计 F2F 渠道将大幅减少。我们认为渠道持续存在的原因有三个。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，消费者&lt;a href=&quot;https://siteefy.com/how-many-ads-do-we-see-a-day/ &quot;>;每天&lt;/a>;接触 5,000 到 10,000 个广告。这种数字混乱很难渗透，因此保持面对面的方式可能会为营销人员提供不同的方式来接触消费者并实现突破。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，消费者表示，由于使用的应用程序数量和屏幕交互次数过多，他们感到数字疲劳。平均一天 — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lxahub.com/stories/what-is-digital-event-fatigue-and-how-can-marketers-avoid-it&quot;>;级别&lt;/a>;疫情期间增幅超过100%。因此，我们怀疑许多人在他们忙碌的数字生活中渴望人际互动。消费者还&lt;a href=&quot;https://escp.eu/news/why-consumers-seek-refuge-products-branded-authentic-pandemic-and-post-pandemic-era&quot;>;想要更多的真实性&lt;/a>;，这是对过去三年的风险和不确定性的自然反应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三，许多公司将实体店等 F2F 渠道视为了解消费者行为的实验室。他们正在利用先进技术，例如物联网连接的商品和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-footfall-analysis-why-important-geoiq-io/&quot;>;客流量分析&lt; /a>;，更多地了解客户的需求以及他们在旅程中的行为方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，我们确实观察到样本中的一些差异，这些差异可能有助于诊断您的 F2F 渠道的需求行业。与服务公司 (22%) 相比，产品公司不太可能完全数字化，并且更有可能开设新的 F2F 渠道 (31%)。只有纯粹的互联网公司才不会开通F2F渠道。新的面对面渠道在房地产、零售和通信/媒体领域最为普遍，而在医疗保健、制药/生物技术和技术领域则最不常见。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;品牌社交媒体的使用正在扩大。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近一半 (45%) 的公司现在使用社交渠道来销售产品和服务，其中 (61.5%) 的 B2C 服务公司正在使用社交渠道。在这一领域，房地产公司 (100%)、通信/媒体公司 (82%) 和零售商/批发商 (70%) 处于领先地位。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;社交媒体公司，例如 Snapchat、Facebook 和Instagram 在疫情大流行的第一年就实现了创纪录的电子商务销售额。 Instagram 在 2020 年推出的应用内结账功能可能会加速这一过程，为覆盖更多&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/183585/instagram-number-of-global-users /&quot;>;12 亿&lt;/a>; 用户滚动他们的社交信息流。此外，&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.hootsuite.com/how-social-commerce-is-reshaping-customer-experience/#Social_channels_are_the_new_storefronts&quot;>;社交消息传递&lt;/a>;的便捷性使营销人员能够参与真实的活动与客户一起回答问题的时间。 2022 年，超过一半的美国成年人&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.insiderintelligence.com/insights/social-commerce-brand-trends-marketing-strategies/&quot;>;通过社交媒体购买&lt;/a>;商品Sprout Social &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/data/social-shopping-2022/&quot;>;调查&lt;/a>;发现 98% 的人预计会使用此渠道在&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以 Scrub Daddy 为例，该公司在 TikTok 上树立了厚脸皮的形象，并与崭露头角的社交媒体影响者合作，带来了数十亿的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www. foodandwine.com/scrub-daddy-review-trend-7483598#:~:text=Designed%20to%20make%20the%20often,3%20billion%20views%20on%20TikTok。&quot;>;观看次数&lt;/a>;和数百万&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90756764/how-to-find-tiktok-influencers-scrub-daddy&quot;>;关注者&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals。 com/philadelphia/news/2022/02/21/how-viral-tiktok-fame-propelling-scrub-daddy-100m.html&quot;>;在线销售&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我们考虑品牌时在社交媒体上，我们倾向于设想 B2C 品牌。事实上，与 B2B 品牌 (37%) 相比，这些公司更有可能在社交渠道 (58%) 上销售其产品和服务。然而，B2B 公司在这个世界上有一席之地。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以 &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1525/cmr.2014.56.3.142 为例?casa_token=cu8dtuoZwScAAAAA:dv3SkiOmyT4Vr0cgFpqQlEI8v_hFu0w9ij_uacVoe61fl5egMUdQnKhWj3py-wCL1w2d1ioAWetWakc&quot;>;Maersk&lt;/a>;，丹麦航运公司，十多年前发起了一场社交媒体活动，以建立其品牌声誉。经理们惊讶地发现，在 Facebook 的 85 万粉丝中，有 22% 是实际客户（尽管马士基尚未在线销售运输服务）。利用此渠道获取反馈和后续销售是公司自然而然的下一步。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，&lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/linkedin-statistics/ &quot;>;报告&lt;/a>;称，89% 的 B2B 营销人员通过 LinkedIn 寻找潜在客户。这些数字令人鼓舞，我们预计，随着精通社交媒体的年轻消费者进入管理职位，这些数字只会增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;D2C 革命已经开始。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近四分之一 (24%) 的公司在 2023 年增加了直接面向客户 (D2C) 渠道。B2C 产品公司一马当先，有 41% 的品牌采用了此渠道。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;为什么品牌进入 D2C 渠道？首先也是最重要的是，D2C 使公司能够收集有关客户在线行为和需求的宝贵的第一手见解——这是消费品 (CPG) 等某些行业的公司历来缺乏的机会。鉴于全球范围内对访问第三方数据的隐私限制日益严格，第一方数据比以往任何时候都更加重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，D2C 可以让公司测试新策略并收集有价值的反馈。如果使用得当，这种类型的实验应该会产生更有效和高效的策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三，D2C 意味着公司可以控制客户的品牌体验。这对于优质且独特的品牌尤其重要，这些品牌在一定程度上通过渠道体验来提供其优势。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;鉴于这些原因，我们毫不惊讶地发现 55% 的 CPG 公司报告添加了 D2C。 B2C 服务实现了最大的飞跃——从 2022 年的 15% 增长到 2023 年的 45%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;特斯拉已全面拥抱 D2C 革命。该公司通过其在线平台和美国主要城市中心的全国零售店网络直接向客户销售车辆。通过绕过传统汽车经销商，特斯拉能够控制大多数消费者感到不愉快的销售体验（和加价）。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;公司在进入这个领域之前应该考虑两个重要因素。首先，该公司是否拥有强大的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adroll.com/blog/what-is-d2c-and-why-does-it-matter#:~:text=A%20Better% 20Connection%20With%20Customers&amp;amp;text=By%20offering%20a%20more%20streamlined,loyalty%20and%20encourage%20repeat%20business.&quot;>;数字化&lt;/a>;足迹是否已到位以分析和执行 D2C 策略？考虑到 D2C 模式依赖数字营销、社交媒体和数据分析技能来提供积极回报，这一点非常重要。此外，该品牌是否已准备好客户服务结构来应对这一直接渠道可能增加的客户互动？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了防止合作伙伴直接面向消费者，我们建议分销商和其他中介机构提供增值服务营销、库存或物流服务。共享客户数据和分析还可以促进组织之间持久和互利的合作伙伴关系。另一个强大的合作策略是利用跨品类的视角，与主要合作伙伴分享新产品、店内广告和促销策略，甚至潜在收购目标的建议。重点是：提供价值！&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;游戏化未得到充分利用。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;通过奖励、积分、竞赛或其他类似的有趣互动来游戏化购物和其他客户互动是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/PressReleases/gamification.asp &quot;>;预计&lt;/a>;将从 2020 年的 $9.1B 增长到 2025 年的 $30.7B，增长 237%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，只有 4.8% 的营销人员将游戏化整合到数字渠道中进行销售。 B2C 产品公司 (13%) 和销售额达到或超过 100 亿美元的公司 (23%) 正在超越其他行业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尚未对游戏化对品牌成果的影响进行大规模研究。然而，从业者&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/growth-marketing-and-sales/our-insights/coping-with-the-big-switch-how-paid-loyalty-programs- can-help-bring-consumers-back-to-your-brand&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，忠诚度计划确实增加了客户选择该品牌而不是竞争对手的可能性，支付更高的价格，并增加他们的支出水平。我们怀疑，游戏化只会加剧这些影响。鉴于此，我们认为如此低的百分比对许多公司来说是错失的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让游戏化发挥作用的关键是品牌契合度——考虑到品牌的地位和关联，游戏必须有意义。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webpronews.com/business-leveraging-gamification/&quot;>;Fitbit&lt;/a>; 的锻炼里程碑和友好竞赛可帮助消费者从其设备中获得更多益处，并提高锻炼的可能性他们会购买更多产品并将其推荐给朋友。游戏还需要具有吸引力，但成本低廉或免费。如果缺少其中任何一个元素，当前和潜在的客户就不会玩游戏。因此，营销人员必须了解什么能够激励和取悦客户，并使用小规模实验来测试不同的方法来评估这些成本和收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;游戏化对于 B2B 公司来说更加令人畏惧。我们的调查结果显示，只有 1% 的 B2B 公司采用这种策略，而 B2C 公司的这一比例为 13%。与为 B2B 客户提供服务的员工（包括您的销售人员）一起使用游戏化也许是开始该流程的最简单方法。另一种选择是在通常有些无聊的网络研讨会期间引入游戏化。这可能提供一种让潜在客户更加关注销售宣传的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;战略性地评估和部署新渠道&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;疫情无疑改变了营销人员的方式渠道策略，并没有单一的成功途径。由于渠道比以往任何时候都多，营销人员需要确定哪些渠道可以增加明显的价值，而忘记其他渠道。进入某个渠道可能很诱人，因为那里有你的竞争对手。但由于客户时间和注意力有限，营销人员必须战略性地确定他们可以在哪些渠道中产生最大影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:55:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Using AI to Build Stronger Connections with Customers]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_1500238081.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;随着公司学习使用生成式人工智能来创造价值，他们在将该技术应用于客户时存在采取错误方法的风险经验。事实上，研究表明，当人工智能被用来为客户提供更个性化的解决方案或帮助人类员工提供比没有技术帮助时更好的服务时，可以帮助提高客户满意度。金融服务行业是一些公司在这方面取得早期成功的例子。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08 /using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-与客户建立更强的联系？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;生成式人工智能 (AI) 应用的激增正在刺激令人兴奋的创新和消费者实验，但也让许多人感到担忧担心数据隐私或只能通过机器人与公司沟通的人。在银行或医疗保健等客户互动和数据隐私至关重要的行业中，这些担忧尤其严重。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;突破性技术通常会带来一定程度的焦虑，人们很自然地担心模仿人类智能的技术。然而，随着这类新型大型语言模型的出现，大多数公司已将模型风险、模型输出的准确性以及数据的道德使用置于其风险框架的核心。他们的目标是确保负责任地使用新的人工智能技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不太受重视的是，公司将客户体验拱手让给旨在短期内获取价值的模型和机器人，而不是培养长期客户。忠诚。公司可能会越来越多地将传统人工智能和机器学习模型与生成式人工智能结合起来，以更人性化的方式向客户传递消息和优惠。如果我们不小心，逐利的机器人、算法和预测模型确实可能会导致反乌托邦的体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;即使在人工智能的世界里，客户的热爱也应该引领潮流。传统的客户情绪指标，例如净推荐值 (NPS)，可能开始看起来有所不同，但有一个前提将持续存在：每一次互动都会增强或减弱客户对所涉及公司的看法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过以下方式告知每个决策丰富客户生活的目标将为人工智能驱动的未来奠定可靠的道路，为客户、员工和股东创造更多价值。事实上，斯坦福大学和麻省理工学院的研究人员&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w31161/w31161.pdf&quot;>;早期发表的结果&lt;/a>;显示出良好的效果向多个国家的 5,200 名客户支持代理推出基于人工智能的对话助理工具所产生的影响。该工具不仅将座席工作效率平均提高了 14%，而且人工智能辅助交互的平均 NPS 更高，座席每月流失率下降了 9%。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;个性化&lt;/h2>; &lt;p >;以客户喜爱为导向的人工智能需要对目标函数进行根本性的重新思考。大多数现有算法围绕特定时刻的投资回报率而不是整个体验进行优化。支持人工智能的客户参与有望让公司从每次互动中学到更多知识，并找到更多为客户创造价值的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个好兆头，因为客户越来越期望获得更个性化、相关的体验，并且愿意接受作为回报分享他们的数据。贝恩咨询公司该公司对 11 个国家近 30,000 名银行客户进行的最新调查发现，同意银行提供个性化体验的受访者更有可能获得更高的 NPS 奖励。强烈同意银行基于了解自己身份进行互动的受访者与强烈反对的受访者之间的 NPS 存在 123 点差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能完善个性化的一种方式是通过客户数字助理，如图所示通过银行和支付领域的新兴努力。加拿大皇家银行使用名为 NOMI 的人工智能助手为客户提供个性化数字货币管理。功能包括及时向客户推送提示、个性化预算以及基于消费行为和现金流的储蓄建议。在推出后的一年里，结果令人鼓舞，相对于整个客户群，NOMI 客户的数字互动增加了 50%，花在金融账户上的时间增加了 93%，NOMI 客户流失了 2%，而 NOMI 客户流失了 8%。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生成式人工智能数字助理还可以帮助员工加强与客户的联系，加强人性化可能成为差异化来源的地方。例如，摩根士丹利财富管理公司正在推出人工智能助手，以帮助其数千名财务顾问以个性化的方式更好地支持客户。该助手将搜索和内容创建结合在一起，以便财务顾问可以随时快速找到并为每个客户量身定制正确的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大型语言模型将开启个性化的新时代。机器学习技术已经将每个客户的数字交互模式转变为独特的行为“指纹”，而最近的人工智能进步现在将使这些指纹能够包括语音和文本交互。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;帮助员工帮助他们的客户&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;公司应该从一些无悔案例开始，让组织适应生成式人工智能技术。这些通常使用人工智能来帮助员工提供客户体验的各个方面，以便人类可以审查模型的输出。例如，根据最近的参与度，向客户关系经理提出与客户进行下一次对话的建议，或提供处理面临财务困难的客户收款的具体行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下一波案例将在标准操作程序中嵌入人工智能。对于员工。有希望的案例包括将客户的询问预测路由给最有能力处理特定问题的代理，或为关系经理提供实时脚本建议。该技术将实时监听客户的电话，并帮助客服人员了解他们的互动是否会产生积极的影响。在不久的将来，其他员工支持功能可能包括设计个性化的报价，其中包含唤起客户最喜欢的爱好的图像和文本或提醒客户关系经理在关键生命阶段拜访客户。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在零售等少数行业，完全支持人工智能的前线开始支持直接与客户进行自动化互动。随着时间的推移，这个数字化前线可以像传统的人类前线一样提供周到的同理心服务。机器人将与客户互动，并学习提供相关产品和信息，就像最优秀的员工一直所做的那样。人工智能的最佳用途甚至可能完全重新构想整体体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在高通胀和经济紧缩的时代，一些管理者可能会倾向于使用生成式人工智能技术，只是为了削减成本和提高效率。那会被误导。虽然生成式人工智能有潜力改变许多行业的成本曲线，但最大的价值将来自那些专注于丰富客户生活的公司。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Secure Support for Your ERG&rsquo;s Initiatives]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_1058899848.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;马伦·卡鲁索/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;员工资源小组对于培养归属感和提升潜力至关重要，他们需要支持才能继续做到这一点。但考虑到成本削减、缺乏文化意识以及削减 DEI 预算的压力越来越大，“许多身份群体或社会事业面临的挑战可能会被忽视。”在如此充满挑战的情况下，如何ERG 成员能否激励并获得其网络所需的关注以产生影响力？作者根据她与面临类似挑战的人们的合作，提出了几种策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/ how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for -your-ergs-initiatives?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;员工资源团体，在英国通常被称为员工网络，是促进包容性和倡导的重要工具对于传统上被低估的具有共同身份和利益的工人群体。不幸的是，许多 ERG 没有获得履行这一承诺所需的资源、预算和关注。以下是我在辅导个人和向 ERG 进行演讲的工作中看到的一些担忧：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;我如何才能获得更多预算分配来支持我基于信仰的 ERG？&lt;/li>; &lt;li >;为什么我的组织没有针对巴基斯坦的洪水或土耳其和叙利亚的地震开展慈善活动？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我的组织拥有活跃的妇女网络，但缺乏对交叉性的关注。我如何让他们优先考虑这一点？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;鉴于成本削减、缺乏文化意识和不断增加的压力&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.msn.com/en- us/news/politics/mo-house-passes-budget-that-slashes-diversity-initiatives-defunds-libraries/ar-AA19jWvC&quot;>;削减 DEI 预算&lt;/a>;，许多身份群体或社会事业面临的挑战面子可能会从裂缝中溜走。在如此充满挑战的情况下，ERG 成员如何激发并获得其网络所需的关注，以产生影响力？以下是基于我如何支持面临类似挑战的人的一些策略。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;了解您的原因&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;首先，明确您到底想要实现什么以及增加的支持是什么对您和您的 ERG 成员来说都意味着。例如，Nadia* 向我寻求建议，询问如何为&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;穆斯林同事申请一个专门的小巫区&lt;/ a>;，而哈姆扎则想在斋月期间举办一年一度的开斋派对。尽管他们的公司存在信仰网络，但由于他们的组织不愿让“&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy&quot;>;特殊”，两人都面临着障碍宗教安排&lt;/a>;。”与此同时，Akua 是公司女性网络的成员，她希望为有色人种女性组织一次会议，重点关注黑人、亚洲人和多种族背景的女性所面临的挑战。然而，她被告知该组织只会资助支持“所有女性”的女性网络倡议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管这令人失望，尽管来自各自组织的抵制，但我鼓励这三个人花点时间反思为什么这些举措对他们来说至关重要。我的目标是帮助他们巩固他们的要求并提高他们实现成果的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了让其他人接受你的想法，开始根据你想要发生的事情而不是你想要的来确认你的结果避免。此外，花时间考虑所需的资源、潜在的障碍以及您期望的结果将如何影响整个系统。通过专注于你的目标，你可以在向他人展示你的想法时增强你的主人翁意识并增强你的信念。以下是我请 Nadia、Hamza 和 Akua 回答的一些问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;你为什么想要这个？它的目的和价值是什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您将在什么、何处、何时以及与谁一起实现这一成果？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;实现这一目标需要哪些内部和外部资源？这个结果？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;实现这个结果你会得到什么或失去什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;你的行动计划是什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;你期望的结果会带来什么变化？更大的系统，如果没有达到这个结果会发生什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您将如何监控进展或克服任何挑战？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您将如何衡量这一影响结果？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;回答了这些问题后，就可以开始准备业务案例了。随着优先事项的发展，不断重新审视上述内容可能会有所帮助。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;准备您的业务案例&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;现在您已经确定了原因，是时候准备好提出您的案例了领导力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大多数组织的运营理念都是“这对我有什么好处？” Cherron Inko Tariah MBE，&lt;em>;员工网络的不可思议的力量&lt;/em>;一书的作者，鼓励问自己以下问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;您是否意识到正在发生的事情组织？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您了解工作场所文化和企业面临的问题吗？您的首席执行官收件箱顶部的内容是什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;上次董事会会议讨论了什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;人力资源主管的优先事项是什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;确保任何新举措都符合公司的总体目标和战略非常重要。这正是 Nadia 在介绍 &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;Wudu 水槽&lt;/a>; 的案例时所做的。她能够清楚地展示这一条款将如何支持公司在三年内成为最具包容性雇主之一的目标。通过将她的提案与更大的目标联系起来，她能够获得前进所需的支持并将其变为现实。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;衡量和定期跟踪进度可以显着影响 ERG 及其活动的看法和影响。有价值的。为了打造令人信服的商业案例，ERG 领导者必须衡量其工作的有效性并计算其努力的投资回报。会员数量、参与度、满意度和保留率等指标是很好的利用工具。为了帮助您证实您的计划的需求和兴趣，请使用脉搏调查来捕获情绪并征求会员的反馈。同样重要的是进行必要的调整，以确保您的 ERG 实现其目标并为您的组织增加价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，您还可以通过评估 ERG 活动的全球和跨文化效益来帮助构建您的案例。帮助领导者从宏观角度考虑：该计划将如何影响个人、工作团队、客户和全球组织？例如，萨尔曼是其公司伦敦办事处黑人亚裔多民族网络的成员，他希望发起一项活动，为去年南亚传统月期间巴基斯坦洪水灾民筹集资金。然而，他几乎没有得到同事和经理的支持，因为他们最近向乌克兰战争难民捐款。此外，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2022/mar/02/civilized-european-look-like-us-racist-coverage-ukraine&quot;>;人们倾向于支持那些与他们相关的人&lt;/a>; 或支持获得更多国际关注的事业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salman 联系了公司南亚办事处的同事，并利用他们的帮助和经验，通过讲故事吸引了伦敦办事处的兴趣。在了解洪水对巴基斯坦地区工作的员工家庭的影响后，伦敦办事处更倾向于采取行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;收集信息并分享一流公司如何应对的示例也很有价值（包括竞争对手）正在致力于您的事业并鼓励其他人加入联盟。为了帮助获得公司的支持，哈姆扎收集了在各自组织中成功领导斋月活动的类似组织的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个阶段，您渴望继续前进是可以理解的，但要让您的巧妙地处理案件至关重要；谦虚地参与对话，同时避免比较和“&lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/whataboutism-what-it-is-and-why-its-such-a-popular-tropic-in-arguments- 182911&quot;>;Whataboutism&lt;/a>;”更有可能产生成功的结果。 Attempts to minimize other groups or initiate a competing narrative when fighting for your right to be heard or seen will backfire and make you lose support from different identity groups. When we draw comparisons, we neither heal nor drive positive change. It shouldn&#39;t be a case of “this or that” but rather “this &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; that.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider starting your conversation with leadership like this: “I appreciate the organization&#39;s focus on inclusion. I have thoroughly enjoyed being part of XYZ network and can see the positive impact it has created. Encouraged by the influence, I propose an initiative for XYX.” Then you can elaborate on why what you&#39;re asking for is essential, including the data you&#39;ve gathered.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Gather Support&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The company will only consider your case if there&#39;s sufficient interest, so once your “why” is clear and you&#39;ve prepared a business case, it&#39;s time to rally support.&amp;nbsp;When I asked Nadia if there were other employees she could rely on, she affirmed there were quite a few. She then created an internal Google form survey and gathered responses from colleagues who shared the benefits of a separate a Wudu sink for their Muslim and non-Muslim colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, it was necessary to get senior leaders involved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at-work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;McKinsey research found&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;that ERG leaders who have strong ties to executives are better able to obtain resources and funding than those with weak ties. Speaking to allies and sponsors you can count on for&amp;nbsp;support is vital. Hamza did exactly this and was able to bring many on board for her Iftar celebration — in fact, some were even eager to participate in a Ramadan Challenge before partaking in the Iftar celebration. Taking advantage of solid connections and visible supporters higher up within the ranks can be a significant bolster for the initiative to be taken seriously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even if you don&#39;t have sufficient numbers from your identity group to advocate for your initiative, you can look to other ERGs to support you. Here&#39;s one possible way to approach the conversation with ERG leaders:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I loved being part of your network&#39;s initiative; my participation has helped me recognize why your network is important and why it&#39;s essential to have our needs seen and acknowledged. Inspired by you, I&#39;ve asked management to allocate resources to XYZ. Can I count on the support of your network as I prepare to approach them?&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;The advantage of this is twofold: Not only will you have their backing, but because it&#39;s not uncommon for ERGs to combine resources and jointly advocate for social impact initiatives, they may even organize or run programs for you if you&#39;re unsuccessful securing what you need. But remember that such mutually beneficial associations rely on reciprocity — if you expect them to help, you must also be a visible ally for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Be Specific and Prepare to Pivot&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the earlier example, when Salman wanted to organize a charity drive for flood victims in Pakistan, he took charge of the initiative. He asked for specific things he needed: using the office&#39;s hall to hold a bake sale, mentioning the campaign in the company newsletter and a company-wide email, and using the office kitchen to store goods.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be prepared to pivot when you don&#39;t get what you ask for. Prepare a sliding scale of asks and try to secure minimum commitment to start the conversation. If the company doesn&#39;t grant the budget for an event, perhaps ask them to at least send a company-wide email showing support and solidarity. Also, see if you can tie in with other networks and share resources or budgets. Remember, a “no” doesn&#39;t mean a “no” forever — revisit the ask in a few weeks or months as circumstances change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ERGs are essential in fostering belonging and advancing potential, and they need support to be able to continue to do that. Organizations need to include all identity groups and champion all social causes equally, but it&#39;s naïve to expect that to happen without a substantial push. Systemic inequities and organizational bias permeate most organizations, and leaders will remain complacent if they aren&#39;t actively challenged. Navigating a system where some voices are often trivialized or go unheard altogether requires ERG leaders and members to be resourceful and project their asks more strategically. Waiting for organizations to take that initiative may translate into a very long wait — better to push and be heard than not be heard at all.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* Names have been changed throughout to protect privacy.&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Value of Digital Transformation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_NiyiAdeogun.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Niyi Adeogun&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort. Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate. To see where digital transformation creates value, the authors used McKinsey&amp;#8217;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. They found that digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards, often by creating value that&amp;#8217;s hard to copy.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“Show me the money!” Cuba Gooding Jr., playing Rod Tidwell, made those words a cultural touchstone in the movie &lt;em>;&lt;i>;Jerry McGuire&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;. He was not just voicing his concerns about committing to a sports agent, played by Tom Cruise in this case; he was also questioning Cruise&#39;s commitment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Business leaders, shareholders, and board members have increasingly been saying the same thing — albeit using different words — when it comes to their company&#39;s digital and AI transformations. While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/three-new-mandates-for-capturing-a-digital-transformations-full-value&quot;>;only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift&lt;/a>; and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That track record begs some tough questions: Is all this digital effort worth it? Do I really need to lead my industry or is being a fast-follower a smarter strategy? Can I create digital and AI capabilities that give me a lasting competitive advantage or is this just the price of doing business in the modern age?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate, as we argue in our book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/rewired&quot;>;&lt;em>;&lt;i>;Rewired: How to Outcompete in the Age of Digital and AI&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;. But using proprietary data, we&#39;ve found just how and where digital transformations create value — and what businesses can do to beat the competition.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Hard Evidence, Real Value&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Hard evidence that directly ties digital and AI transformation to improvements in operational KPIs and financial performance is scant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To redress this issue, we turned to banking, a sector that has enough of a history with digital transformations to produce meaningful findings and where we own a unique longitudinal dataset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we used McKinsey&#39;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. We then isolated performance in two metrics — the percentage of mobile adoption by their customer base and the percentage of sales originated in digital channels — to define 20 digital leaders and 20 digital laggards. These two metrics are broadly recognized in the industry as core indicators of a digital retail banking model.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, we combined this data with McKinsey&#39;s Corporate Performance Analytics to see how banks ultimately perform against financial metrics (eg, total shareholder return, growth, expenses). We then ran a blind assessment (ie, the identity of the banks was hidden) of the maturity of digital and AI capabilities of the leading and lagging banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The findings have been striking: Digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders achieved average annual total shareholder returns of 8.1% vs. 4.9% for laggards. Leaders also had significantly better return on pre-tax tangible equity (ROTE), growing it from 15.5% in 2018 to 19.3% in 2022, vs. a more modest growth from 13.6% to 15.3% for laggards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This financial outperformance is a result of leaders&#39; success in growing revenue and better containing expense growth. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders have grown their active customer base at 0.5% and their retail revenues at 0.8% annually, while digital laggards saw zero growth in their active customer base and a decline of 1.4% per year on retail revenues. During the same period, leaders&#39; operating expenses grew at 1.3% per year, while laggards grew at almost twice that (2.3% per year). So, how are leaders able to outcompete so demonstrably?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Creating Value That&#39;s Hard to Copy&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Where does value come from? Let&#39;s look under the “digital hood.” Both digital leaders and laggards are growing adoption of their mobile app at the same rate, with a gap of 14 to 15 percentage points between them staying constant over time. (See below chart.) This is not surprising. As soon as a bank introduces a new mobile app feature, others see it and follow suit relatively quickly. The mobile app is table stakes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Turning to digital sales provides a much more insightful answer. Here, the gap between leaders and laggards is growing fast, with leaders almost doubling their advantage over laggards over the five-year period. In fact, digital leaders grew digital sales from 40% to 70%, while digital laggards grew from 8% to 17%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reason for this large differential is that to drive digital sales, leading banks go well beyond the mobile app to digitally transform what&#39;s hard to see and hard to copy: the end-to-end process from origination to fulfillment to servicing. To do this, they must orchestrate hundreds of teams capable of developing digital and AI innovations, day-in, day-out, across all their customer journeys and core business processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the front end of this process, for example, leading digital banks deploy personalization analytics and digital marketing campaigns to bring relevant offers to (potential) customers. In the middle of this process, they create an omnichannel experience where branch and contact center professionals have the tools and data to support customers at any stage of the sales journey, even if that journey was started online. These leading banks also provide customer approvals in real time, thanks to automated credit-risk decisioning. At the back end of the process, they drive customer self-servicing through well-designed digital workflows enabled by a modern data architecture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The value of this approach to transformation is also revealed in contact center staffing. Laggards saw an increase of 20% over the past five years, as they were unable to contain inbound calls from customers that enter digital channels. In contrast, digital leaders were able to decrease contact center staffing by 11% as they benefited from their ability to fully fulfill customer demand online and provide effective self-servicing capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361201&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Knowing what to do is important, but executing on the “how” is what makes the difference. Let&#39;s see how a US bank did it for its secured lending business. Traditionally, the bank took about 45 days for a customer to secure a loan, on average. The process involved multiple documentation requests to customers (eg, pay stubs, W2s, letters of explanation), and back-end processes (eg, initial file review, file assignment, ad hoc reports) were highly manual.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To transform this journey, the bank&#39;s leadership team reinvented the entire process. To speed pre-approvals, they developed a database of tens of millions of US households combining credit, property and income attributes using internal and external data sources. This data allowed them to generate personalized pre-approved offers that customers could accept with one click. They built a mobile-first customer experience, where customers could personalize their offers based on real-time data and finalize a pre-filled application, either on mobile or with the assistance of a bank employee. They redesigned key processes (eg, specialized loan “assembly lines”), automated key tasks (eg, initial file scrub), and developed digital tools for operators to drive productivity (eg, daily workflow management). And they modernized credit policy execution to enable greater use of data in underwriting (eg, using direct deposit data for income), while maintaining or increasing risk controls for the bank.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To enable all these innovations, they implemented key technology and data capabilities, including a customer data platform, AI/ML models (eg, propensity models), data products (eg, income), a digital app for customers and a workflow tool for the fulfillment center, all deployed on a cloud-based platform-as-a-service infrastructure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, this transformation required more than a dozen use-cases across the entire journey and massive change management programs (eg, training, retooling) for agents in branches, contact centers, and operations. But, only 18 months after the initial launch, the approval process was shortened from 28 to 7 days. This leap allowed the bank to become a leading secured lending originator and increase originations by 35%, while reducing origination cost by 20%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Capabilities Needed to Outcompete&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A company that aspires to outperform needs to do the kind of end-to-end changes the bank above did across dozens of customer journeys and core business processes. That&#39;s only possible when it is rewired with differentiated capabilities. Our study of more than 200 large-scale digital and AI transformations isolated the six core capabilities rewired companies develop:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Creating ambitious and focused transformation roadmaps&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. This requires business leaders to align their efforts on specific domains (eg, journeys or processes) that matter to customers and generate significant value.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Building a quality digital talent bench&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. Leaders prioritize creating an environment that attracts top-notch engineers and allows them to thrive (eg, tailored career tracks, autonomy).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;An operating model &lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;where hundreds of small cross-functional “pods” made up of business, engineering, and resources from control functions are mobilized against priority solutions. A single journey (or product) owner responsible for the end-to-end experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;A distributed technology environment and modern software engineering practices&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; to allow the entire organization&amp;nbsp;— not just IT&amp;nbsp;— to develop digital and AI-based solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Data products and modern data architecture&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; that make it easy for different parts of the organization to consume data for their own applications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Change management to ensures digital solutions are adopted and can scale&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; by making them easy to use and reuse across the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our blind assessment of these capabilities for the leaders and laggards, we found that leaders stand out across the board on these capabilities. No single one explains their success. All are needed. With that baseline, the most differentiated capabilities are talent and operating model, not technology. Over time, these capabilities create ever-improving customer experiences and drive lower unit cost. Financial rewards follow.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361204&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_CAPABILITIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While our research has focused on banking, our experience reflects similar lessons and patterns in every industry, whether B2B or B2C, products, or services. A digital and AI transformation, however, cannot be done in “special project” mode. To pull this off, the entire organization must be able to deliver constant digital innovation, which requires a holistic set of capabilities. The effort is significant, but so is the reward.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:55:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Keep Your Audience Focused During a Presentation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_1029427796.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;AndreyPopov/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&amp;#8217;s focus is critical to communication success. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it. In this piece, the author outlines three techniques &amp;#8212; physical, mental, and linguistic &amp;#8212; to engage your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Attention is our most precious commodity. In today&#39;s fast-paced world of always-on digital devices and round-the-clock media cycles, getting our audience&#39;s attention is critical to our communication success. With so many distractions vying for our time, we must actively seek and gain our audience&#39;s attention first.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, capturing ears and eyes isn&#39;t enough. Getting attention is only the first battle; keeping it is another challenge entirely. That&#39;s why smart communicators not only actively deploy ways to capture attention, but they work to sustain it. Sustained attention is what I call &lt;em>;engagement&lt;/em>;. If you can engage your audience, they will stay focused and be less distracted. Plus, you will have a better shot at demonstrating the relevance and significance of your topic to them. To that end, here are three approaches to engaging your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Three Ways to Engage Your Audience&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Physical Engagement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Where the body goes, the brain will follow. Anything that gets your audience doing something with their bodies will create engagement. Whether you are giving an in-person pitch or presentation, or conducting a virtual meeting, think about how you can include physical engagement in your activities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, you can have people watch a video, read a handout, click on something on their screens, raise their hands, or use virtual reactions. All of these require your audience to become participants in your communication, not just observers. A simple invitation to “Turn to the person next to you and greet them” or “Read what is on the slide and share your thoughts” can get them involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Mental Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Fight back against your audience&#39;s tendency to zone out or multitask by fostering cognitive engagement. There are three simple ways to do this: ask questions throughout your presentation; incorporate provocative statements, data, and stats; and introduce smart analogies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you ask a question, people almost automatically start to consider their answer, thereby moving them from passive listening to active participation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Provocative statements or &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/present-your-data-like-a-pro&quot;>;compelling data&lt;/a>; ignite curiosity and encourage your audience to internally ask their own questions. For example, if you&#39;re trying to justify headcount for your training department, you could say: “30% of our customer service tickets could be eliminated by training users better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Analogies are where we compare what we know to what we don&#39;t know; in other words, we &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/finding-the-right-metaphor-for-your-presentation&quot;>;use the familiar to explain the unfamiliar&lt;/a>;. Invoking analogies invites involvement by making us actively think. One caveat: When you use analogies, make sure they&#39;re ones people can readily relate to. Over-reliance on sports metaphors or on complex comparisons people cannot follow or understand will work against your goal of engagement and greater understanding.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Linguistic Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Linguistic engagement refers to the use of inclusive words, time-traveling language, and references to shared perspectives or experiences. Inclusive wording means inviting people into your communication. For instance, we&#39;re hardwired to perk up when we hear our own name, as well as when we hear the word “you.” Mention participants&#39; names, and use phrases like “As you know…” or “You may be wondering…” or “Today, you will learn…”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Time-traveling language takes people from the present into the future or the past. You can use phrases like “Imagine…” or “What if you could…” or “Picture this…” to take people into the future. “Remember when…” or “Think back to when…” will take people into the past. Connect people through shared experiences or beliefs to create common ground. For instance, highlighting your company&#39;s mission and values or referencing a previous shared experience can draw people in, much like when you and your friends or family share old stories and jokes.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Combining Engagement Techniques&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You don&#39;t need to rely on only one engagement technique at a time. Instead, combine them to increase and enhance their effect. For example, polling is a great way to get both brains and bodies involved with a triple-whammy of activity. It works with a poll question as simple as, “By show of hands, which of the following do&lt;em>; you&lt;/em>; believe is the most important element of XYZ?” The synergy of the physical, mental, and linguistic engagement techniques deployed in this one question get attendees out of neutral and in the flow with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Note that when polling, you must first tell your audience how to respond (eg, “By show of hands…” or “Type into the chat…”). It&#39;s also imperative that you comment on the response you get (eg, “That&#39;s what I expected…about half of you,” or “Wow, that is everyone”). If you fail to comment, your audience might feel tricked into complying, or worse, that you did not care about the answer and were just using the poll as a gimmick.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, these suggestions might not be appropriate for your situation (for example, if you&#39;re polling the three executives in the room), so choose options that fit the occasion and group size.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While engagement techniques can be used any time in a communication situation, they&#39;re especially critical when starting meetings, presentations, or pitches. Think about how an action movie opens. You&#39;re thrown into the midst of action with the actor doing something impressive, interesting, and curiosity provoking right away. Only after your attention is engaged and your interest piqued do the title and credits appear. If you start out with the traditional “Hi, my name is..,” you&#39;ve missed a prime opportunity to&amp;nbsp; engage your audience immediately. Similarly, engaging your audience by asking a question, taking a poll, showing a video, or using an analogy before introducing yourself sets an energetic tone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;. 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&#39;s focus is critical to communication success. If you think about any communication and communicator that you find compelling, they&#39;re likely leveraging some of the physical, mental, or linguistic engagement techniques discussed above. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s OK to Fail, but You Have to Do It Right]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;6331954317112&amp;quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;Loading... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;div>;Harvard Business School professor Amy Edmondson is probably best known for her work on psychological safety in the workplace. She has authored a number of books, including the forthcoming &lt;em>;Right Kind of Wrong: The Science of Failing Well&lt;/em>;, and she spoke with HBR editor in chief Adi Ignatius about the right&amp;#8211;and wrong&amp;#8211;ways to fail. Experimentation and risk-taking are crucial for an organization&amp;#8217;s success, but failing twice in the same way is probably a mistake.&lt;/div>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When you or your team try new things — and not all of them succeed — that&#39;s called experimentation. Learning from experiments is essential for your company&#39;s growth. On the other hand, when you deviate from proven practice because of inattention or lack of training, that&#39;s probably a mistake. It&#39;s critical to know the difference, and to create a workspace where individuals feel psychologically safe to take smart risks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For this episode of our video series “The New World of Work”, HBR editor in chief Adi Ignatius sat down with Harvard Business School professor Amy Edmondson, an expert in psychological safety and author of the upcoming book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Right-Kind-Wrong-Science-Failing/dp/1982195061&quot;>;&lt;em>;Right Kind of Wrong: The Science of Failing Well&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, to discuss:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Productive, intelligent ways to fail&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Dangers of not experimenting enough&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Balancing individual employees&#39; needs with those of the team and organization&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Edmondson says that leaders should do a thorough post-mortem after every failure, whether it was productive or not, to ensure that it does not repeat itself. “A failure, even an intelligent failure, in new territory, new discovery, is no longer intelligent the second time it happens.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;The New World of Work&lt;/a>;” explores how top-tier executives see the future and how their companies are trying to set themselves up for success. Each week, Ignatius talks to a top leader on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/harvard-business-review/&quot;>;LinkedIn Live&lt;/a>; — previous interviews included &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/microsofts-satya-nadella-on-flexible-work-the-metaverse-and-the-power-of-empathy&quot;>;Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/indra-nooyi-former-ceo-of-pepsico-on-nurturing-talent-in-turbulent-times&quot;>;former PepsiCo CEO Indra Nooyi&lt;/a>;. He also shares an inside look at these conversations —and solicits questions for future discussions — in a newsletter just for HBR subscribers. If you&#39;re a subscriber, you can sign up &lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences?movetile=newworldofwork&quot;>;here&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Amy, welcome to The New World of Work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Great to be here, Adi. Thanks for having me.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New World of Work&quot; dek=&quot;Previous episodes&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New World of Work&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Previous episodes &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your book is primarily about failure. I was under the impression that we all understood that failure is noble and not shameful, and provides useful learning lessons. But you&#39;re writing a book that seems to be saying that we need to think hard and maybe differently about failure. What are you trying to accomplish with this book?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I was with you and then I poked around and realized that the truth is many people were still confused about failure. There is a lot of happy talk about failure out there. There&#39;s the virtual mantra of Silicon Valley to fail fast, fail often, failure&#39;s good, let&#39;s learn from failure, let&#39;s have failure parties, let&#39;s have failure resumes and so forth. And the truth is, the future of work will be riddled with failure. We can&#39;t just wish it away, even if we wanted to, we have to work with it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think no one can really take to heart the happy talk about failure unless they have a coherent framework. You could think of it as two camps: the Silicon Valley fail fast, fail often camp. And then the other camp, which is, “I live in the real world, failure&#39;s not an option.” And they&#39;re both right or they&#39;re both partially right, but neither is terribly helpful nor context specific.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So I think the happy talk, when it&#39;s not qualified with a coherent way of making distinctions between the good kind of failure and the not-so-good kind, is possibly more destructive than helpful. It drives the honest conversation underground. It&#39;s important to talk about the kinds of failure for which we really should be welcoming it with open arms and the kinds where we maybe shouldn&#39;t.&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;The New World of Work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href=&quot;/resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Subscribe to our Weekly Newsletter &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; The New World of Work &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; Candid conversations on talent, tech, and the future of business. A special email series for subscribers. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>; Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Thanks for signing up, &lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>;&lt;/span>;! &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; You can view our &lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;other newsletters&lt;/a>; or opt out at any time by managing your &lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;email preferences&lt;/a>;. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think the best thing you can say about failure is if you have a culture that permits failure, that tolerates failure, it means you&#39;re stretching, you&#39;re pushing, you&#39;re trying to innovate, you&#39;re trying to do things that are difficult. That&#39;s part of the definition of what a digital company is. A digital company experiments frequently and tries and fails, and is able to tolerate failure. I would guess if you talk to most companies, they&#39;d say, “Yeah, we do that. That&#39;s the culture we have. We didn&#39;t used to, but we do that.” So I want to push you a little bit more: the rhetoric, that&#39;s the happy talk, but in reality that&#39;s not really how the world works?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First of all, it&#39;s not how most incentives are set up. I&#39;m not saying uniformly that&#39;s the case, but most of the time, failure is not rewarded in organizations, and people would rather do anything but fail.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And you&#39;re right, maybe a better way to talk about this is not as failure, but as experimentation. We have to be very pro-experimentation. But we have to be pro-&lt;em>;smart&lt;/em>;-experiments. And I think smart failures are the result of smart experiments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Smart experiments are ones that happen in new territory — honestly, if you can look up the answer, find the recipe, find the blueprint, please do, no need to experiment — new territory in pursuit of a goal that&#39;s consistent with the value proposition of the organization, with a hypothesis you&#39;ve done your homework on and importantly, as small as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Those are the kinds of both experiments and failures we must welcome with open arms. They are discoveries and they allow us to figure out quickly what to try next. But a portion of the book is devoted to best practices for failure-proofing that which can be failure-proofed. The activities, the operations in your company that are in known territory, are ones that should be well set up to make failure extremely rare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Are there industries that do not tolerate failure? Airline pilots? You don&#39;t really want them to fail. This isn&#39;t a rhetorical question. Are there industries that really don&#39;t tolerate failure? And can you look at them and say, “You actually can get interesting results if you have that kind of policy?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s start with airlines because clearly none of us want them to be comfortable with failure. Yet I think the reason why airlines have an extraordinary record of success and safety is because they&#39;re willing and able to talk about failure. The failures that they do tolerate happen in the simulator. There&#39;s training, there&#39;s a lot of emphasis on speaking up early to prevent something worse from happening. So their safety record does not come from being intolerant of failure, but rather being intolerant of major accidents.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Therefore, we have to be very tolerant of the reality of human error so that we can catch and correct, we can train, we can allow people to take the kinds of risks and experiments we were just talking about in safe settings like the simulator, not in the execution of the real duties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I don&#39;t think it&#39;s possible to describe industries in the way your question implies. I think there&#39;s variation across companies. Pick an industry like fast-moving consumer goods. It&#39;s going to be not that hard to find differences in cultural failure tolerance within those industries across companies. So a more sensible way to put that is that some companies are doing better than others in having a healthy tolerance of intelligent failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What does a productive failure look like? You did mention that there are good and bad failures. What&#39;s the difference and how does one try to make sure their failures are the good kind?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In known territory where we have a process or a formula for getting the result we want, it&#39;s best practice to use that process, use that formula and get the result we want. So when a Citibank employee a number of years ago accidentally made a small human error and accidentally wired $800 million to a client that he shouldn&#39;t have, that was a basic unproductive failure. Turns out they were not even able to get the money back. So, not celebrating that kind of failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A productive failure is one where we get new and useful knowledge, new knowledge that helps us go forward in creating the kind of value we&#39;re trying to create in our market, for our customers. So we discovered something that we could not have discovered without trying it, without the experiment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Would you recommend that there be an elaborate postmortem? I think the military is very focused on doing detailed postmortems: what happened, what went wrong, why? Presumably to learn from that and not have it happen again.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is not the case that a postmortem has to take inordinate amounts of time, but it should be thorough. It should be analytical, and look carefully at the different facets of the failure, to understand accurately what happened and why, for the express purpose of preventing that exact failure from happening ever again. So a failure, even an intelligent failure, in new territory, new discovery, is no longer intelligent the second time it happens.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I want to shift gears a little bit to talk more generally about the workplace. The question really is: Are we OK? &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-reenergize-your-team-when-morale-is-low&quot;>;You wrote a recent piece in Harvard Business Review&lt;/a>; that suggested maybe things are not so great, with relatively low levels of engagement and productivity, high rates of burnout. We can speculate as to why that&#39;s true, but is that accurate? It&#39;s hard to generalize, but you know, are we suffering? And if so, how do we respond to that as managers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Well, I don&#39;t have a kind of systematic worldwide dataset from which I can make solid inferences about how people are doing. My impression comes from informal conversations, qualitative research, reading HBR and so many other outlets, to see how people are doing. So really, in a way, I&#39;m commenting on the conversation in HBR and so many other business media contexts, maybe LinkedIn and elsewhere.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One thing I think I can say for sure is that the anxiety is real, and people are worried about the future. They&#39;re worried about it on so many fronts. They&#39;re worried about climate change. They&#39;re worried about AI. They&#39;re worried about burnout, as you mentioned. I&#39;ll come back to burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But that anxiety tends to push us toward a retreat to our individual corner, and people start to think, “Am I going to be OK?” They become more focused on their own wellbeing than on the health of the team or health of the organization. And that gives rise to a real potential for erosion, even vicious cycles, where organizations find themselves in the trap of responding to requests and issues in isolation, one by one.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We need a more holistic way of thinking about it. And I see limited evidence of companies being at least described as pausing to think about the larger picture, their value proposition, what it implies for how they must be structured and led, to get the necessary work done, and how to organize that work, with all its variety and variable needs, in a thoughtful way, and how to inspire and motivate people to do it well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let me just briefly go to the burnout issue, because there actually has been some recent data, some studies that have caught my eye, showing that burnout is systematically higher when psychological safety is lower, right? For instance, it seems to me that some portion of the burnout is associated with loneliness and isolation. I think it&#39;s fair to say that we can endure many challenges when we feel genuinely that we&#39;re in it together, that we&#39;re connected and engaged with our colleagues in trying to sort of navigate these challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One can&#39;t help but think, “Okay, is some of this related to the pandemic?” Which for many of us, broke up teams, created new work environments with work from home, that in many ways is fantastic for people who are balancing their work and life. It must take a toll on maybe the teaming imperative that you&#39;ve written about. Is that your hunch?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I do think the pandemic took a toll on us, on all of us. It created such an obvious uncertainty. It was such an obvious disruption. It wasn&#39;t the gradual shifts that we&#39;re normally used to. It was a very abrupt shift, and it gave rise to wonderful—and I think productive—experiments on different work arrangements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now it&#39;s time for a very systematic assessment of what&#39;s working and what isn&#39;t? And it can&#39;t be incremental, right? And it also can&#39;t be based on what people say they want. Because oftentimes, what we say we want is not actually what we need or truly want in the longer term, bigger picture, to get where we need and want to go.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You talked a second ago about trying to have a comprehensive policy and approach that, if I heard you right, is not dealing with people always individually, but that&#39;s sort of the nature of management now. Suddenly, managers are expected to be, in addition to everything else, almost like psychiatrists, that there&#39;s an openness for people to share their personal situations, challenges, problems, and that it&#39;s the role of the manager, increasingly, to engage with that in an intelligent way. So you end up where management becomes hyper-personalized, but I think maybe you&#39;re already on to the risks in that, which is losing the sense of the teaming and the collective effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s almost as if we&#39;ve lost sight of tensions and trade-offs. There will always be a tension between me and we, right? There will always be a tension between my desires in the moment and my aspirations over the long term. If you ask me what I want: pay me infinitely and don&#39;t ask me to do anything, and let me eat ice cream all day, right? But that&#39;s not going to get me where I really, really need to go, and want to go. I want to make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think we&#39;re in a moment of not helping people value the collective. As human beings, we&#39;re social creatures. That&#39;s part of it, but it&#39;s also that we want to matter. We want to matter to others. We want to matter in some way that&#39;s larger than ourselves and our hedonistic desires.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can think of an old-fashioned management theory of the firm, right? If markets worked by themselves, we would just have only contractors doing tasks, and it would be efficient, it would be sensible, it would be logical. But it doesn&#39;t work, because a lot of the work we have to do is inherently collaborative, and dynamically so. And it isn&#39;t easily parceled out, dividing-and-conquering style. It requires us to really work together in meaningful ways. The good news is, that can be a very engaging, rewarding, exciting experience. The bad news is, it&#39;s not easy to manage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think we can go down that rabbit hole of each person has to be managed differently, each person, you&#39;re almost a psychiatrist to that person, versus let&#39;s step back and rethink, how do we design our activities, our operations, so that we create the most value for those we serve?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yeah, I love that, and I have to say that I don&#39;t think companies have figured that out yet. The disruption of Covid opened our eyes to some flexibility. But I think the things you&#39;re putting your finger on, we&#39;re trying to solve for that, and I think a lot of us haven&#39;t yet and need to keep experimenting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So we&#39;re in this age of anxiety, where there&#39;s burnout. And then, you throw on top of that generative AI, and a fear—possibly irrational, possibly not—that generative AI will be able to do all of our jobs at almost no cost. I assume you haven&#39;t done quantitative research. But qualitatively, what&#39;s your advice for people as generative AI enters the workplace at every level and the possibilities become clearer and clearer?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you indicated, it&#39;s a little outside my wheelhouse, except for the effects on people and culture. I speak from the perspective of someone listening at the margins to the many conversations in work and social gatherings alike, and I think you&#39;re right. I think fear is the dominant emotion, that certainly some are excited, some are super optimistic about the amazing changes to come, but I think casually I hear more fear than optimism.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The truth is we need both. We need some positive, thoughtful, design-oriented approaches to experiment and figure out what&#39;s going to work. But I don&#39;t think they&#39;re going to be simple solutions to the dramatic shakeup of what&#39;s possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s a question from Omar from Monterrey, Mexico. What kind of metrics can be used to measure smart failures?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My first response is that it&#39;s a good idea to have metrics. One of the things that I&#39;ve spent the most time studying is how many failures just don&#39;t even get the chance to be measured, because people don&#39;t speak up about them. This was how I got into this topic in the first place: the discovery of dramatic differences across groups, even within the same organization, and their willingness to speak up about things that go wrong rather than just things that go right.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s the challenge more broadly than just people not necessarily speaking up: the category of intelligent failure covers vast territory. I think the metrics have to be tailored to the context — and let me illustrate vast territory. A well-run clinical trial on a new cancer drug is an intelligent failure when it turns out it doesn&#39;t have the efficacy that we hoped. It was in new territory. There was no other way to find out but to do a clinical trial. It&#39;s the right size, it&#39;s no bigger than it has to be. It&#39;s hypothesis-driven in pursuit of a goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But so is a really bad blind date. That&#39;s intelligent failure. Maybe your friend thought you&#39;d like each other. You are willing to go out and have a coffee. Smallest possible new territory in pursuit of a goal, all the rest. So a bad blind date and a failed clinical trial are clearly apples and oranges, yet they both qualify under the category.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think the best way to answer the measurement question is, let&#39;s make sure the criteria are adhered to. And then, let&#39;s think about what the right frequency is, given the work we&#39;re trying to do, of intelligent failures?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another way to say that is: What&#39;s the right frequency of experimentation? How often should we be trying new things to push the envelope, to discover new possibilities, even to discover efficiencies? And are we doing that often enough? The answer is usually no, because most of us would rather succeed than fail, and most of us would rather keep doing what we&#39;re doing because we&#39;re kind of good at it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So here&#39;s another question along those lines from Mohammed in Pakistan. Employees may be hesitant to offer feedback that could be perceived as negative, which can impede professional development, hinder organizational progress. How does one tackle this situation?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such a good question because it&#39;s true. We are very reluctant to do things, to speak up with negative or difficult information, because frankly it will always be easier not to. It will always be easier to hold back than to speak up candidly and forthrightly about something that you hope could be made better.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The way to make this very difficult thing easier is to set the stage by pointing out how valuable it is. Periodically, I would say even frequently, refer to the fact that “We need to do this hard thing. We need to do it well if we want to be as good as we can as a team.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But even individuals who have the ambition to grow and develop in their roles and in their careers have to train themselves to be willing to do this and receive it because of its value. So we&#39;ve got to call attention to its value. We&#39;ve got to call attention to the fact that it&#39;s hard and then do it anyway and support each other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This question is from Don from Calgary in Canada. If it&#39;s true that we learn acutely from mistakes, what are some ways to encourage permission from our leaders who may be risk averse?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re all risk averse, and maybe leaders even more than others, maybe not. But first of all, I make a distinction between mistakes and failures. I&#39;m not anti-mistake because I&#39;m a human being, and I make them, we all do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But a mistake is not the same thing as a failure. A failure is something that went wrong that we wish were otherwise. A mistake is a deviation from a known practice. Now, that could happen because of inattention, because of lack of training, because of exhaustion, you name it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think it&#39;s helpful for leaders, and others for that matter, to talk about the reality that we will make mistakes because we&#39;re human. The very best practice is not to never make a mistake. It&#39;s to catch and correct them quickly, and then also to make that distinction between smart experiments in new territory that we also want to see more of because it&#39;s the secret to future value creation. And we welcome those, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Furthering that, here&#39;s a question from Benny from California. What&#39;s the best way to speak to subordinates after a failure to boost morale and communicate that, “This was a good failure. It&#39;s OK”?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;m going to say “honestly.” You can be honest about, “Wow, this was disappointing for all of us, and let&#39;s get everything we can out of it. Let&#39;s learn as much as possible.” And in fact, given that something substantial that goes wrong nearly always has multifaceted aspects to it, it&#39;s helpful to have a thoughtful and data-driven conversation about what happened. Not “Who did it?”, but, “What happened?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We may go around the team and ask, “What did you see?” And we&#39;re really looking for what happened, what contributed to that, and that&#39;s both commission and omission, things that you did that may have contributed, things that you didn&#39;t do that may have helped. It&#39;s a thoughtful, deliberately learning-oriented conversation designed to help us be better next time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How do you reenergize your team these days? How do we reenergize our team particularly now, in 2023, where it feels like there&#39;s a lot of stuff swirling around?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It starts with personally taking the time to reconnect with your own sense of purpose for doing the job, the role that you are currently doing. And consider why it matters to you and why what you are doing or leading matters to the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having done that, share it. Share it often and then just as quickly invite others in to help navigate the necessarily stormy waters that lie ahead. I think it starts with you and then it&#39;s an honest sharing of why you care, why it&#39;s challenging, why you very much need and are interdependent with others. Because all of us want to be needed. We want to be needed. We want to matter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The last few years, with the pandemic, I&#39;d say certainly in the US, there&#39;s been increased attention to social issues, which on the one hand I think felt right to people in the workplace. On the other, it brought more challenges into the workplace. One imagines there&#39;s a pendulum, and it might swing between leadership needing to be very empathetic to, I don&#39;t know, the backlash if that&#39;s the right word. Leaders need to achieve productivity. That&#39;s what it&#39;s all about. Do you believe in that pendulum or are we in a different place? And if you do, where are we right now on that swing?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I believe in the pendulum. I believe that the pendulum happens and I believe there may be a better way. It&#39;s often thought of as empathy versus productivity. And I looked this up actually: Productivity is defined as the effectiveness of productive effort as measured in terms of the rate of output per unit of input.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first problem is that not all work is easily measured for productivity. The second problem is, often it&#39;s not the right way to measure excellence. Productivity is often a short-term measure, and it has limited predictive value for the future performance of the firm. For example, one way to be really productive is to just push people to their limits. But that has time constraints. Eventually they will burn out, leave, etc. It&#39;s like Buckminster Fuller used to say that it was foolish to burn down the house to keep warm on a cold winter&#39;s night. The excessive pressure can be the equivalent of that error.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And also innovation work in particular, we have case study after case study where the work actually suffers when productivity metrics are brought to bear.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a way, I wish the pendulum were more about excellence than productivity, because I think productivity is really tricky and variable to measure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I see the pendulum existing, but maybe it&#39;s a false dichotomy. Maybe it&#39;s not empathy versus productivity. Maybe we need smart, caring leaders who understand the importance of both. And given that that&#39;s very challenging, they&#39;re open about it being challenging. They&#39;re asking for help. They&#39;re sharing the burden of caring and excellence with their teams and considering, again, the fundamentals of what it is the organization must do well to stay alive in its market, to perform in its market. And talk about it honestly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I sometimes think we don&#39;t talk often enough about the fact that work is work. It&#39;s supposed to be a little bit of work, but that doesn&#39;t mean it can&#39;t be fun, energizing, collaborative, and full of empathy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I love that. Well, that&#39;s a good point to end on. Amy Edmondson, thank you for being on the show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thanks for having me. All the best.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Hybrid Work Can Become Toxic]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_27_1425175448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Toxicity can be an unfortunate reality of some work environments. Toxic cultures share five attributes: they&amp;#8217;re disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive. Undeniably negative as these attributes are, there is no absolute, uniformly accepted scale against which we can measure any of them. Making matters more complicated, a hybrid environment by definition means that employees are experiencing their work in very different contexts &amp;#8212; some face-to-face, others remote &amp;#8212; and those may vary by the day. As a result, hybrid workspaces aren&amp;#8217;t uniform; some people may experience a hybrid environment as toxic while others do not. The author presents four mechanisms through which hybridity can lead to toxic behaviors, as well as four strategies for preventing and addressing toxic behavior in a hybrid environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Toxicity at work — no matter where or how we do our jobs — is caused by a range of factors. It is important to recognize that some aspects of hybrid and remote work make toxicity more likely to occur.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, though, let&#39;s quickly outline what “toxic” actually means. It doesn&#39;t refer to the misunderstandings, tensions, and conflicts that are a natural (and needed) part of any healthy organization. Nor does it refer to a one-off incident or a coworker who is a jerk every now and again. These kinds of irritations, for the most part, are best thought of as normal parts of (working) life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, what actually is considered toxic? A study by Donald Sull and his colleagues identified &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/&quot;>;five attributes of a toxic culture&lt;/a>;: disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive. In a recent discussion I had with two colleagues who are experts on the subject, Amy Edmondson of Harvard Business School and Constance Hadley of the Questrom School of Business, we agreed that toxicity also implies the behavior in question is both pervasive and ongoing. And that, we believe, is what makes bad behavior rise — or perhaps fall — to the level of toxic. Toxicity carries a sense of inescapability, which is part of what makes it so painful to experience at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Undeniably negative as these attributes are, there is no absolute, uniformly accepted scale against which we can measure any of them — all five are subjective, anchored in each person&#39;s experience. Making matters more complicated, a hybrid environment by definition means that employees are experiencing their work in very different contexts — some face-to-face, others remote — and those may vary by the day. As a result, hybrid workspaces aren&#39;t uniform; some people may experience a hybrid environment as toxic while others do not. That does not make a toxic hybrid environment any less painful or damaging to those who experience it as such. However, it does mean that some behaviors may be toxic even as a result of well-meaning — or at least not ill-meaning — actions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When talking with executives about toxicity, I encourage them to think like social scientists, to understand the mechanisms through which hybrid working can lead to increased toxicity. Here&#39;s what they should know.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How Hybrid Work Can Lead to Toxicity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;My research and consulting experience has led me to think in terms of four mechanisms through which hybridity can lead to toxic behaviors.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Remoteness changes dynamics&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Working hybrid means that, compared with full-time in-office work, more communication will take place via technologies like email, text, phone, or video. One of the early findings in research on the effects of technology-mediated communication was that people become more disinhibited and exhibit less self-monitoring and self-control &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/227445694_Reducing_Social_Context_Cues_Electronic_Mail_in_Organizational_Communication&quot;>;when communicating through technology&lt;/a>;. In other words, when we talk to one another electronically, we are more likely to blurt out things that might be hurtful. Think about heated exchanges you&#39;ve had with colleagues both in person and electronically — chances are, you were much more tempted to try to slip in a sharp quip in an email than face-to-face.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This dynamic is not (necessarily) about being a nasty person. We all have moments of anger, frustration, or passion, and if handled badly, those feelings have the potential to turn toxic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In face-to-face interactions, though, the human on the other side of the conversation is far more salient to us, leading most of us to recognize the potential costs of a less-careful word and bite our tongues. The point isn&#39;t that we shouldn&#39;t speak our minds (if we feel that we can&#39;t, that&#39;s bad for psychological safety), but that we should choose our words well. While the reduced self-monitoring and self-control that come with remote interactions do not necessarily cause toxicity, they certainly make it more likely for &lt;em>;disrespectful&lt;/em>; or &lt;em>;abusive&lt;/em>; (two of Sull&#39;s toxicity characteristics) comments to come out.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Hybridity is fundamentally imbalanced&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Hybrid also means different people are working in different contexts. Some may be at home, while others are in the office — and those locations have undeniable differences. People in the office have greater access to resources and higher visibility, often leading to more credit and quicker promotion as a result. Remote workers, meanwhile, often feel left out and shunned. Negative as these effects may be, they are not strictly toxic if everyone is equally disadvantaged at some point. The problem is when some people (likely remote/hybrid workers) feel &lt;em>;consistently&lt;/em>; excluded — as was the experience of one manager I recently worked with.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Company policy was to allow all employees to work remotely two days a week, and the manager had allowed her team members to choose those days. She quickly discovered her team had effectively split on the basis of different (but consistent) patterns of which days people chose to come into the office. Compounding the issue, team members&#39; remote-work choices were heavily driven by commutes and children&#39;s school schedules, which aligned them with demographic differences in the team. Problems arose when some team members felt they were being excluded from the discussions and meetings that occurred on the in-office days of the other group. The split led to interpersonal tensions and conflict, people feeling &lt;em>;excluded&lt;/em>; and &lt;em>;disrespected&lt;/em>; (two toxicity characteristics), and it ultimately resulted in turnover.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Hybridity can reduce cohesion and trust&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/11/a-study-of-1100-employees-found-that-remote-workers-feel-shunned-and-left-out&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; that lack of close contact reduces connection and trust, which are key elements of a healthy culture. During the pandemic, I spoke to many employees who had started new jobs remotely, and I consistently heard that they hadn&#39;t gotten to know their colleagues and felt disconnected. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work&quot;>;Research from Microsoft&lt;/a>; found remote working leads employees to have smaller, less-well-developed networks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Remote (and by extension hybrid) working does not necessarily mean organizations will have a weak or inconsistent culture. Take Linux as an example. Its open-source software development from day one has been carried out by a loosely structured community of developers who have never met in person, yet extensive research on the group has found it has strong social norms governing behavior. However, it is hard to deny that the group&#39;s structure (or lack thereof) removes or impedes many of the mechanisms we traditionally use to establish, transmit, and maintain culture. Note that Linux &lt;em>;started &lt;/em>;with a remote, dispersed culture. While many companies have embraced remote and hybrid since the pandemic started, their cultures were already established and then adjusted to handle the crisis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Culture is so important because it is the compass organizations use to eschew &lt;em>;cutthroat&lt;/em>; and, in more extreme cases, &lt;em>;unethical&lt;/em>; behavior. To be clear, hybridity does not inherently lead people to be more cutthroat or unethical (though one might argue the sense of distance between people makes them less aware of the negative ramifications of their actions). However, in every social system we find a range of behaviors, and culture typically helps us rein in the negative ones. On top of that, while people are less likely to exhibit toxic behaviors toward those they feel close and connected to, the distance that a remote/hybrid environment brings makes us more likely to view some of our colleagues not as “us” but as “them” — and it&#39;s much easier to act poorly toward “them.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Hybridity makes it hard to resolve issues&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s one more key challenge in remote and hybrid work: We have fewer face-to-face interactions with colleagues, and research shows that it is harder to resolve disputes (like those around toxic behaviors) virtually. Think about trying to address a sensitive topic over Zoom with someone and worrying about everything from where they&#39;re looking to how fast they reply. &lt;em>;Are they giving me their full attention? Am I sure my sincerity is coming through over video? Was their slow response because they disagreed or are just lagging?&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When we&#39;re face-to-face, we have more interpersonal tools at our disposal. We have better data, as we can more easily read facial expressions and can see off-camera behaviors. We also have better tools, as face-to-face interactions allow us to synchronously work together to resolve differences. And the propinquity effect (essentially, we like people we have more exposure to) means all of this happens from a starting point of a closer relationship.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One other issue it&#39;s important to mention is microaggressions, which some people have argued happen less often in remote settings because we&#39;re around one another less. However, I would caution leaders and employees alike to stay vigilant for signs of microaggressions (often reflected in toxic behaviors like &lt;em>;noninclusion&lt;/em>;) in hybrid settings. While these settings may have fewer touchpoints where microaggressions can occur, they do not remove the underpinnings of why microaggressions happen — nor do they prevent them from coming out in other outlets, such as Slack, messaging apps, or videoconferencing. In effect, hybrid work can obscure the problem without resolving it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Leaders Can Do&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I advise leaders to approach toxic behaviors in hybrid work in four ways: educate, lay a foundation, have ongoing conversations, and intervene quickly.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Educate employees&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The first step toward avoiding toxic behavior in hybrid teams is to help people learn how it can arise. You may think, “Of course they know not to be disrespectful, abusive, or noninclusive,” but that&#39;s not the issue. Sit down with your employees and have a conversation about how these outcomes can happen as unintended consequences of hybrid work arrangements and decisions. Remind them that toxicity is about behavior — and that what matters isn&#39;t what your intention was but how others perceive your actions. A good starting point is to ask employees to reflect on hybrid work behaviors they may have experienced as toxic (for example, feeling routinely excluded from a social group or reading comments on Slack that they found abusive or disrespectful). The goal of this step is not to identify particular issues or point fingers but rather to increase employees&#39; self-awareness and the number of eyes out there looking for toxic behaviors or their antecedents.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Lay a foundation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As Benjamin Franklin famously said, “An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure.” One of the most effective tools you can put in place is a culture with built-in antibodies against toxic behaviors. In particular, focus on promoting empathy and psychological safety. A culture with a core of empathy encourages employees to consider the impact of their actions on their colleagues, increasing the likelihood that employees catch themselves before behaving in a way another might find troubling. In turn, a culture that includes psychological safety is critical for those cases that empathy doesn&#39;t prevent. We don&#39;t always recognize the impact of our actions, and building psychological safety ensures that employees can speak up about the behaviors they perceive as toxic. Research has provided excellent practical advice for promoting both &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/empathy-rules&quot;>;empathy&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychological safety&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Have ongoing conversations&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Because the experience of hybrid work is different among employees and dynamic over time (someone may be in the office today, surrounded by colleagues, and at home alone tomorrow), toxicity is a moving target. The only truly effective way to manage such dynamism is with an ongoing process — and the cornerstone is repeated, ongoing conversations. I encourage hybrid teams and organizations to have periodic check-ins where everyone is encouraged to raise concerns or flag toxic experiences. There is no hard-and-fast rule for frequency, as it depends on how dynamic the organization&#39;s hybrid environment is: The more and faster it changes, the more frequent those conversations should be. As a starting point, aim for a monthly check-in and adjust as needed. Make sure the psychological safety foundation is in place if you want people to share honestly, and treat these conversations as more than a superficial box-ticking exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Intervene quickly&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Even with a good understanding of the issues, a positive cultural foundation in place, and ongoing discussions, hybrid working may still lead to behaviors that your employees find toxic. A big problem with toxic environments is that they tend to get worse: Toxic behaviors either feed on themselves, breeding more toxicity, or cause disgruntled employees to disengage, creating new tensions due to workloads needing to be redistributed. To break the cycle, you need to not only keep an eye out for toxic behaviors but also be ready to move fast when you see them, help all parties engage in a dialogue, and work to reach a mutually acceptable solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s say you notice a situation like that of the manager whose team was split over their WFH days. In a case like that, call a team meeting and share your concerns of how the situation might feel exclusionary. It may turn out your concerns aren&#39;t shared — but you&#39;re still creating buy-in and ownership of the issue, making it easier to address later if it does become a problem. If, however, you&#39;ve recognized a budding concern for some of your team members, you have a forum to discuss and collectively resolve it before it gets too far along.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Toxicity can be an unfortunate reality of some work environments. While hybrid work does not necessarily cause toxicity any more than in-person work does, it is important to recognize that hybrid introduces some different mechanisms through which toxicity may arise. Keeping these in mind can help leaders recognize, guard against, and eliminate toxicity when it occurs — or ideally before.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Why Employees Accept Lower Pay at Mission-Oriented Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_AnChen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by An Chen&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Today&amp;#8217;s companies are likely to tout how their work benefits human welfare or &amp;#8220;makes the world a better place.&amp;#8221; Recent research suggests that this may come with a potential financial drawback for workers, as it can inhibit them from negotiating for higher pay. Over five studies, job candidates consistently reported that they worried asking for higher pay from these companies would be seen as greedy or inappropriate. This suggests they are aware of a common bias, known as motivation purity bias, where managers believe employees interested in material rewards of work (such as pay) are less motivated than those motivated by intrinsic rewards, such as the nature of the work. In reality, research has shown that extrinsic and intrinsic motivations operate jointly to predict high performance. Job candidates should invest in building their negotiation skills so they are less thrown off when companies use social impact framing. And organizations should train managers to be aware of the motivation purity bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In an amusing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B8C5sjjhsso&quot;>;episode&lt;/a>; of the HBO sitcom &lt;em>;Silicon Valley&lt;/em>;, one awkward startup founder after the other pitches their company by proclaiming that it “makes the world a better place.” The satirical comedy highlights how common it has become for companies to tout how their work benefits human welfare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend — which academics call &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2017.1172?&quot;>;social impact framing&lt;/a>; — appears to be on the rise. We see it across job postings, company websites, and consumer advertisements, with for-profits and non-profits alike looking to hire “passionate” and “mission-oriented” workers seeking to “make an impact.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such emphasis on social impact isn&#39;t without merit. For one, it can reflect organizations&#39; earnest desires to make a positive difference. It can also &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2008-00266-008&quot;>;motivate&lt;/a>; employees by instilling a greater sense of self-worth and meaningfulness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, in our recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1287/orsc.2023.1675&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; published in &lt;em>;Organization Science&lt;/em>;, we uncover that organizations&#39; use of social impact framing can come with a potential financial drawback for workers, as it can inhibit them from negotiating for higher pay.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Perceived Norm Violation&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We explored this effect over five experimental studies. Consistently, job candidates in the social impact framing condition reported that asking for higher pay would likely be viewed as greedy and inappropriate by the hiring organization. As a result, they refrained from negotiating.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our first study, we recruited 392 participants from an online research platform to examine workers&#39; attitudes in response to different types of organizational messaging. Approximately half of the participants read about a company that emphasizes social impact, while the others read a more generic company description. We asked participants to write open-ended responses about whether or not they would negotiate a job offer to work for the company, and why. We found that those who received the company descriptions that included social impact framing condition were 32% less likely to negotiate. The most common reason for this reticence was participants&#39; belief that negotiating would be seen as selfish and counter-normative, and put them at risk of being passed up for the job.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our second study involved 438 undergraduate students responding to an on-campus job opportunity in which they would be recruiting fellow students to work for a startup in the educational industry. The students watched an introductory video where the purported company founder and CEO — played by a trained actor — described his hiring organization. Approximately half of participants watched a video in which the founder emphasized social impact, while the other half watched a video in which the founder described a more generic organization focused on high-quality work and success. After viewing the video, participants were given the opportunity to ask for a higher wage for the job versus accept the initially offered wage. Consistent with our first study, students in the social impact condition were 43% less likely to negotiate. Again, this effect was driven by the perception that showing interest in higher pay would violate the organization&#39;s norms for employee motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We replicated these results in three other studies. We found that the effects held true in a workplace simulation and across a range of industries, including education, health care, manufacturing, and finance. We also found that social impact framing largely affects job candidate requests for monetary job rewards, such as salary and bonuses. It does not seem to deter them from asking for non-monetary rewards like vacation time and health care benefits.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assumptions About Money and Doing Good&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;What explains the effects on monetary job rewards?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The answer lies in widespread and longstanding beliefs that money taints love of the work itself and attempts to do good.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers, for instance, have been shown to hold a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2017.0617&quot;>;motivation purity bias&lt;/a>;,” where they believe that employees interested in the material rewards of work (extrinsic rewards) are less motivated by the nature of the job itself (intrinsic rewards), and are thus less worthy of being hired.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This belief is based on a false premise. Research has shown that extrinsic and intrinsic motivations operate &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/a0035661&quot;>;&lt;em>;jointly&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>; to predict high work performance. Furthermore, more of one type of motivation doesn&#39;t mean less of the other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nonetheless, in our research, job candidates seem to act as if they are aware of this managerial bias against workers&#39; interests in material rewards. Consequently, in social impact contexts — where workers are especially expected to be driven by loftier motivations such as a sense of higher purpose — job candidates self-censor on any indications that they might also care about the money.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Takeaways for Job Candidates and Hiring Managers&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;From a Marxist perspective, social impact framing might be viewed as yet another cultural trend that inadvertently operates in favor of the owners of capital and at the expense of workers. Yet, given that social impact framing is often rooted in organizations&#39; genuine efforts to contribute to society and can benefit employees as well, it would be overly simplistic to suggest that organizations stop communicating their emphasis on the greater good. We thus offer several suggestions to help minimize the financial downside for workers of exposure to such messaging.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From the perspective of workers, job candidates can invest in &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-to-evaluate-accept-reject-or-negotiate-a-job-offer&quot;>;building their negotiation skills&lt;/a>;, so that they can avoid being easily thrown off in their approach when organizations use social impact framing. They can also investigate how organizations that claim to care about human welfare &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-tell-if-a-potential-employer-has-a-burnout-culture&quot;>;treat their own employees&lt;/a>;. It would be ironic if a company that emphasizes social impact neglects its own workers&#39; well-being, financial or otherwise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations might also consider training managers about their biases against employee extrinsic motivation which, as described above, can be unfounded. Indeed, the desire to &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2014.0898&quot;>;provide&lt;/a>; for one&#39;s family, for instance, has been found to be a robust predictor of work performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By romanticizing intrinsic motivation and reflexively dismissing job candidates who express any interest in extrinsic job rewards, organizations might be turning away perfectly good candidates who are also passionate about the work and might well have been high performers. Not least, organizations that strive to take an ethical approach to business can avoid deploying social impact framing in a Machiavellian manner, as a tool to intentionally suppress pay.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Companies Can &mdash; and Should &mdash; Recommit to DEI in the Wake of the SCOTUS Decision]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_28_1401985.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Ruth Black/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In the wake of the US Supreme Court ban on affirmative action at colleges and universities, state legislation attaching diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts on campus, and more general attacks on DEI, companies are considering whether they need to change their DEI strategies. The short answer is they don&amp;#8217;t. But it is a good time to review corporate values, personnel policies, and engage with employees on these issues. The first step should be to remember the moral and business cases for DEI. They remain strong.&amp;#160; Second, you might reconsider using DEI labels, as some have suggested. But given employee support for such initiatives, proceed cautiously. Next, review HR practices like recruiting (including casting a wider net for candidates since the college pipeline will now be less diverse); onboarding (since some students will have less exposure to DEI than others); and performance reviews, pay, and promotion (to ensure there is no racial bias).&amp;#160; Finally, communicate carefully with what is sure to be a polarized workforce. Present credible research, solicit opinions, work to bridge divides. Ultimately, you want your organization to move forward in a way that is aligned with your organizational values.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The recent US Supreme Court decision banning affirmative action, specifically race-conscious admissions in colleges and universities, may not directly impact US workplaces, but there&#39;s no question that corporate America needs to consider the effect this — and potential future judicial rulings and state legislation — will have on their DEI practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At a minimum, any changes we see in student body composition at institutions of higher education will also affect hiring pipelines. For example, when the University of California&#39;s system eliminated affirmative action in 1995, Black student representation at UCLA dropped from 7% (compared with 13.6% for the US population and 6.5% for the state&#39;s) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;to 3.9% in just three years&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epi.org/blog/the-supreme-courts-ban-on-affirmative-action-means-colleges-will-struggle-to-meet-goals-of-diversity-and-equal-opportunity/&quot;>;to less than 2% by 2006&lt;/a>;. Likewise, when affirmative action was banned at the University of Michigan, Black undergraduate enrollment declined from 7% in 2006 (compared with 13.6% for the state population) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;to 4% in 2021&lt;/a>;. These case studies suggest that when universities eliminate affirmative action, they produce a less diverse candidate pool for employers to tap, and this is now likely to happen across the country.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Exacerbating the situation, there are also now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bestcolleges.com/news/anti-dei-legislation-tracker/&quot;>;more than 30 state or local bills&lt;/a>; targeting DEI funding, practices, and promotion at schools. For example, Texas has a ban beginning January 1, 2024, on all DEI offices, diversity training and “ideological oaths and statements” at public institutions, which could mean that companies recruiting on campus need to review their messaging.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There is much more at stake than diversity recruitment, however. As management thought leaders and expert scholars on race in the workplace, we anticipate many additional ripple effects. The ruling has already been interpreted as an invitation for DEI critics to challenge the validity, legality, and necessity of such efforts. For example, Will Hild, the executive director of Consumers&#39; Research, a right-wing advocacy group, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;has already gone on record&lt;/a>; to say that the SCOTUS decision on affirmative action “will put the wind in the sails of groups like ours, who want to get the woke, racially based hiring and promotion schemes out of corporate America.” The attorneys general of 13 Republican-led states have also sent&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tn.gov/content/dam/tn/attorneygeneral/documents/pr/2023/pr23-27-letter.pdf&quot;>; a letter&lt;/a>; to the CEOs of Fortune 100 companies warning that labels of “diversity, equity, and inclusion” are now “unlawful and wrong, per SCOTUS.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, college admissions are governed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crt/fcs/TitleVI&quot;>;Title VI&lt;/a>; of the Civil Rights Act, which prohibits discrimination on the basis of race, color or national origin under any program or activity receiving federal financial assistance. Private employment falls under &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;Title VII&lt;/a>; and is enforced by the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), currently led by Charlotte A. Burrows, who has emphasized that the SCOTUS decision has no bearing on its work. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/statement-eeoc-chair-charlotte-burrows-supreme-court-ruling-college-affirmative-action&quot;>;a statement&lt;/a>;, she said, “It does not address employer efforts to foster diverse and inclusive workforces or to engage the talents of all qualified workers, regardless of their background. It remains lawful for employers to implement diversity, equity, inclusion, and accessibility programs that seek to ensure workers of all backgrounds are afforded equal opportunity in the workplace.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That means most corporate DEI efforts are formally safe for now. However, it&#39;s important for organizations to pay attention to the changing landscape.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Taking a Step Back &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s consider whether we still believe race should be considered when making organizational decisions. That depends in part on whether we believe racism still affects our society. If we do, it seems plausible and just to recommend interventions that consider race. If we don&#39;t (or if we are okay with racism), it would seem implausible and unjust to recommend interventions that consider race. So, we ask you, does racism still affect our society? And do we care?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the systematic oppression of Black Americans, who have long been erroneously held up as the face of affirmative action in the United States (while research shows that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-who-benefits-white-women/70371219007/&quot;>;white women&lt;/a>; are instead the biggest beneficiaries of such policies). Even after the abolishment of slavery in 1865, the United States continued to codify the oppression of Black people in legal, political, and social systems. From the post-war &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/brown-v-board-50th-anniversary/southern-black-codes.html&quot;>;Black Codes&lt;/a>; to the 1896 &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.gov/milestone-documents/plessy-v-ferguson&quot;>;Plessy v. Ferguson&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; SCOTUS decision to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/black-history-month/a-brief-history-of-jim-crow&quot;>;Jim Crow laws&lt;/a>; in the US South, white power structures denied Black people full citizenship and equal protection under the law. Counter measures, including Congressional actions such as the landmark 13th, 14th and 15th Amendments, the Supreme Court&#39;s 1954 Brown vs. Board of Education decision, and the Civil Rights Act of 1964, which finally banned racial discrimination from public places, schools and workplaces, represented progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, having been denied the ability to advance professionally and create wealth for more than a century post-slavery, Black people remain disproportionately underrepresented in professional workplaces and leadership roles. As fellow researchers Tony Mayo and Laura Morgan Roberts have &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/toward-a-racially-just-workplace&quot;>;described&lt;/a>;, they are less likely than their white peers to be hired, developed, and promoted. Other racioethnic populations — Latino, Native American, Pacific Islanders — have faced different types of discrimination and are also underrepresented in higher-earning roles and occupations, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/opub/reports/race-and-ethnicity/2020/home.htm&quot;>;data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://extramural-diversity.nih.gov/diversity-matters/underrepresented-groups&quot;>;industry groups&lt;/a>;. This suggests that racism does still affect our society. The United States is not living up to its founding ideals of allowing all citizens to pursue life, liberty, and happiness in equal measure. We should care — and keep working toward those goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A next question to ask is whether we believe diverse teams benefit organizational performance. Ample research shows that they make &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;smarter decisions&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/the-other-diversity-dividend&quot;>;better investments&lt;/a>;, are &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-investing-in-dei-helps-companies-become-more-adaptable&quot;>;more adaptable&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/how-and-where-diversity-drives-financial-performance&quot;>;drive innovation&lt;/a>; when the corporate culture in which they operate is a supportive, &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/research-to-excel-diverse-teams-need-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychologically safe&lt;/a>; one. Diverse and well-trained workforces and leadership teams are also better suited to interact with diverse employees, customers and vendors. Thus, there is still both a moral and a business case for supporting DEI efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some corporate leaders still might be wondering whether they should rethink their whole DEI strategy in light of recent attacks on affirmative action. The short answer is no. Now is not the time to reverse the commitments they made to racial equity in the aftermath of George Floyd&#39;s 2020 murder. Instead, it&#39;s time to clarify organizational values around DEI, clearly communicate them, and ensure that people management processes are aligned with them. Here, we explain how to go about this at this critical moment in US history.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Rethinking L&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;abels&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given the SCOTUS ruling, other pending state legislation, and the warning from those 13 attorneys general, some legal scholars &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;have suggested&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;that companies preemptively protect themselves by moving away from DEI labels to ones clearly protected by law. For example, instead of a chief diversity officer, you would have a Title VII compliance officer. Another option is to use words like “inclusion,” “belonging,” and “engagement” to emphasize that the goal is improving organizational culture not necessarily racial diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We urge caution on this front because DEI remains important to employees. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.bfldr.com/ZZ11QL2O/at/6bpw94vrt588vtc8gr3fgw5/C001_Benevity_TheStateofWorkplaceDEI_Final.pdf?hsCtaTracking=e0c17c58-a6ca-4e73-978b-87718706789f%7C57928514-8a0c-4227-bf1f-498f3e23c304&quot;>;a 2023 Benevity survey&lt;/a>; found that 95% of people weigh a prospective employer&#39;s DEI efforts when choosing between job offers with similar salary and benefits and that 78% would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; consider working for a company that fails to commit significant resources to DEI initiatives. Employees from historically marginalized backgrounds will almost certainly feel disregarded and devalued if their organizations shy away from DEI labels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, any good DEI strategy requires regular evaluation to ensure it is performing against goals set and having the intended impact on employees. And when faced with a big organizational change or new rules and regulations, leaders should have a system in place to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ellavatesolutions.com/the-ellavate-approach&quot;>;tune-up existing DEI&lt;/a>; strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reviewing Processes &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recruitment&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As highlighted earlier, we can expect a smaller percentage of racially marginalized individuals to be admitted to predominantly white institutions (PWI), so companies still seeking diversity in their candidate pool will need to look elsewhere to find as much of it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One solution is to increase recruiting at institutions such as historically Black colleges and universities (HBCUs), Hispanic-serving institutions (HSIs), and tribal colleges and universities (TCUs). Another is to consider non-traditional pathways such as community colleges and building partnerships with community organizations that focus on racially diverse pipelines, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://oneten.org/about/mission/&quot;>;OneTen&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend a shift to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/skills-based-hiring-is-on-the-rise&quot;>;skills-based hiring&lt;/a>;, a well-established DEI best practice that focuses on matching skills between job candidates and roles instead of focusing on only education and experience. Consider partnering with organizations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://opportunityatwork.org/stars/&quot;>;STARS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlt.org/&quot;>;MLT&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://reachingoutmba.org/&quot;>;ROMBA&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://toigofoundation.org/&quot;>;Toigo Foundation&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fortefoundation.org/site/PageServer&quot;>;Forte Foundation&lt;/a>; (full disclosure: the latter two are clients of Tina) that help identify talent employers need.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Onboarding&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many companies now include DEI education as part of their onboarding programs. But they can no longer make assumptions about employee readiness for these conversations. For example, a student educated at a public institution in Florida is now expressly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wbur.org/onpoint/2023/05/23/what-the-desantis-agenda-means-for-higher-education-in-florida&quot;>;prohibited&lt;/a>; from taking a course that “teaches identity politics, or is based on theories that systemic racism, sexism, oppression, and privilege are inherent in the institutions of the United States.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers might therefore need to implement surveys to understand how much new hires know about DEI and take greater care in explaining to new team members why those principles matter to the organization, not just how they&#39;re implemented.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Performance reviews, pay, promotions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As DEI efforts become more highly scrutinized, there is even more reason to make sure your people processes are equitable. Performance evaluations and pay and promotion decisions should be based on standard and objective data — yet a multitude of research indicates that they remain riddled with bias, especially for members of historically marginalized racioethnic groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; found that 90% of people of color but only 72% of white people received notes about their personalities in their reviews. Now is a good time to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;audit these processes&lt;/a>; so no one can argue that you are favoring people of one race over another.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Communicating Carefully &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2023/06/08/more-americans-disapprove-than-approve-of-colleges-considering-race-ethnicity-in-admissions-decisions/&quot;>;public polling&lt;/a>; is any indication employee reaction to the affirmative action ruling will depend on their race and ethnicity, political affiliation, and how they have seen affirmative action framed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Adept managers should be able to surface and address different opinions, show empathy, create employee feedback and support systems, and regularly communicate about these issues. Tools to use include one-on-one meetings (if a few employees are highly concerned); town halls (if many people are worried); emails (if many people have low-intensity interest); or simply monitoring the situation for now (if awareness remains low among most people.) &amp;nbsp;Conversations might be difficult, but it is important for teams to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/dig-bridge-collectively-act&quot;>;dig into sometimes polarizing topics, bridge divides, and agree on collective action&lt;/a>; where possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A cornerstone of successful communication is to include research from credible outlets but, in these polarized times, it can be challenging to find &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/journalism/2020/01/24/us-media-polarization-and-the-2020-election-a-nation-divided/&quot;>;sources&lt;/a>; trusted by all employees. We recommend identifying multiple ones and explaining the vetting process to employees. Organizations will also benefit from conducting surveys to learn about differing views and identifying and seeking input on informal leaders on all sides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With both facts and opinions in hand, leaders will be better equipped to communicate effective messages about their DEI plans. They might, for example, acknowledge that some employees disagree with race-conscious recruiting, or think DEI efforts should be dropped for legal or cost-saving reasons, but explain that the organization prioritizes the increased innovation that comes from having a more diverse team or simply having a workforce that represents the broader society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is important that everyone engages on this issue. While some organizations relegate DEI to HR and HR alone, this is a mistake. Messaging on — and commitment to — DEI should be understood and communicated by everyone from frontline managers to the CEO, especially now when racial tensions remain high and policies like affirmative action are being questioned.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Moving Forward&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that the media furor over &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions v Harvard University and the University of North Carolina&lt;/em>; has slightly abated, organizations have a moment to strategically reflect on how their DEI efforts may be affected. We believe corporate leaders should resist the urge or pressure to backpedal on DEI commitments. Instead, they should enhance DEI in a manner that complies with the law, aligns with their organizational values, and benefits their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Be a Purpose-Driven Leader Without Burning Out]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1298982699.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Grizelj/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The idea of servant leadership &amp;#8212; putting your team&amp;#8217;s needs ahead of your own &amp;#8212; brought us to a more compassionate, human-centered work environment. But in today&amp;#8217;s environment, it&amp;#8217;sa recipe for burnout. Instead, the authors suggest a more impact-driven philosophy called &amp;#8220;noble-purpose leadership,&amp;#8221; that ties leaders and teammates to the pursuit of a shared goal that positively impacts constituents. In servant leadership, the message is: You&amp;#8217;re in your role to serve others, making it tempting to focus on pleasing others and difficult to say no. In noble-purpose leadership, the message is: You&amp;#8217;re in your role to make an impact. This requires more strategic thinking in terms of where to place your efforts. The authors offer three areas where managers can shift their lens to noble-purpose leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When Robert Greenleaf coined the phrase “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenleaf.org/what-is-servant-leadership/&quot;>;servant leadership&lt;/a>;” in a seminal 1970 essay, it was a much-needed improvement over the traditional command-and-control leadership model that had prevailed for centuries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“The servant-leader is servant first. It begins with the natural feeling that one wants to serve. Then conscious choice brings one to aspire to lead,” Greenleaf wrote. “That person is sharply different from one who is leader first, perhaps because of the need to assuage an unusual power drive or to acquire material possessions.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Well-documented research tells us that organizations and individuals &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-humble-leadership-really-works&quot;>;perform better&lt;/a>; when leaders focus on the team rather than themselves. On an individual level, servant leadership &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.regent.edu/journal/emerging-leadership-journeys/impact-of-servant-leadership/&quot;>;increases&lt;/a>; followers&#39; trust, loyalty, and satisfaction with the leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet, much has changed in the 50 years since Greenleaf&#39;s original essay, particularly in the last three years. The narrative behind servant leadership is increasingly falling flat, for good reason:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Rampant burnout.&lt;/strong>; In today&#39;s environment, when leaders are tired, overworked, and stressed, serving can feel like pouring from an empty cup. We tell managers, “You&#39;re here to serve your team.” We tell customer-facing teams, “You&#39;re here to serve customers&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>;” The sum of it is exhausting.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;People are busier&lt;/strong>;. When Greenleaf originally introduced servant leadership, a typical manager likely supervised a small functional team. They didn&#39;t have their own deliverables, they weren&#39;t on multiple cross-functional initiatives, and they didn&#39;t start their day answering an onslaught of overnight emails. &amp;nbsp;Today, as middle management continues to thin out, leaders typically have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/how-to-identify-the-right-spans-of-control-for-your-organization&quot;>;between 11 to 15 direct reports&lt;/a>; and their own high stakes deliverables. These exhausted managers often feel they don&#39;t have the time to devote to servitude.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Workplaces have become less hierarchical&lt;/strong>;. Today&#39;s org charts often resemble a jungle gym more than they do a &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/stop-offering-career-ladders-start-offering-career-portfolios&quot;>;ladder&lt;/a>;. Leading without formal authority is on the rise and begs the question: Who is the servant and who is served?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Servant leadership was a crucial stepping-stone into a more humane world of work. But the next evolution is upon us. &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/to-retain-employees-give-them-a-sense-of-purpose-and-community&quot;>;The workplace data&lt;/a>; (and our own experiences) tells us that we&#39;re at an inflection point. We&#39;re standing in a moment in time where leaders, both formal and informal, must move forward towards a more purposeful leadership style that focuses on the impact that the organization&#39;s work has on real live human beings.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We refer to this impact-driven philosophy as “noble-purpose leadership.” It&#39;s when leaders and teammates alike are in shared pursuit of a cause bigger than themselves (their team, their customers, their community) and their goal is to positively impact their constituents (versus serving them).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a nuanced, yet distinct shift. In servant-driven leadership, the crux of the message is: &lt;em>;You&#39;re in your role to serve others&lt;/em>;. This makes it very hard to say no, and there&#39;s a temptation for leaders (and their teams) to be reactive, trying to please everyone.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In noble-purpose leadership, the core message is: &lt;em>;You&#39;re in your role to make an impact&lt;/em>;. This requires more strategic thinking in terms of where to place your efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When your North Star is a shared purpose, leaders have more choice in the matter; you don&#39;t feel as required to please everyone. In our consulting practice, we&#39;ve seen first-hand evidence that noble-purpose leadership can be an effective evolution toward driving better performance while staying true to a culture of service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three areas where managers can shift their lens towards noble-purpose leadership:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Employee Interactions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managers are often taught to ask their people questions like: What can I do to help you be successful? What kind of support do you need from me? While these are excellent questions (and will certainly get better results than barking orders) well-intended leaders find themselves leaving these interactions with an exhausting list of action items. After a few experiences like that, overworked managers often find it easier not to even ask their team what kind of help they need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rather than giving up on the idea of being supportive, managers can create a subtle, yet powerful shift by calibrating to a higher purpose, and asking questions like: What do &lt;em>;you &lt;/em>;need to be successful in accomplishing our goal? What help will &lt;em>;you&lt;/em>; need to get? This small language change reframes the emotional dynamic. Instead of the leader having to be solely responsible for supporting the employee, asking the employee what they need to be successful creates a shared sense of responsibility. The leader is purposefully positioning themselves to have a positive impact on the employee&#39;s results, yet they&#39;re not taking on sole responsibility for supporting them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s a before and after of how this worked for a client of ours, a vice president who was stretched thin with 12 direct reports and an endless list of their own deliverables. Being a servant leader felt exhausting and impossible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The VP started asking their project managers, “Given our purpose to positively impact our customers, what kind of support will you need to get this done well, and on time?” The project managers quickly determined they needed resources and support from another department to meet the deadline.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Had the VP stuck with the traditional, “What do you need from me?” both parties would have suffered. The VP would have had more on their plate than they could manage, and the project managers wouldn&#39;t have engaged with the other department. With a sightline to the shared purpose (successfully completing a project that improves life for customers), both the leader and their team members become more empowered and effective.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Decision Making &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When your primary focus is to serve, the temptation is to focus on pleasing people&lt;em>; — &lt;/em>;an endless and often fruitless, endeavor. &amp;nbsp;Many elements of work, like tight deadlines and challenging feedback, are inherently displeasing, no matter what the leader does.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When a leader frames their decisions solely through a lens of trying to be as helpful and supportive to their constituents as possible, it&#39;s a recipe for burnout. At worst, it breeds entitlement, where employees think the leader&#39;s job is to do nothing but make them happy. The sum of this emotional turmoil can keep leaders from making tough (but correct) decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, leaders can frame their decisions around purpose. For example, in meetings, rather than asking: How do you feel about this? Does this work for you? Leaders can ask: What impact will this have? How will this affect our people or our customers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Katherine, the head of customer success for a medical device company, used this model to shift her team from complaining to action. Part of the team&#39;s function was to keep customers abreast of delivery times. This included making personal calls to customers when their orders were delayed. After a particularly frustrating day, her team came to Katherine with a request: They no longer want to make these calls. Her team lamented &lt;em>;“Some customers don&#39;t even notice if their order was delayed!”&lt;/em>; Others piled on, &lt;em>;“We can&#39;t speed up the delivery truck! What&#39;s the point of calling? If they&#39;re worried, they call us.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A leader simply trying to please the team would have been tempted to let the team stop making the calls or they might have taken on the calls themselves. &amp;nbsp;Instead, Katherine used questions to recalibrate the team to a higher purpose. She asked: “How will it affect our customers if they are caught off guard, and don&#39;t know the order would be late? How would it impact our reputation if we stop being proactive and are only reactive?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This seemingly simple shift of the lens prompted the team to think about how their work impacts the overarching purpose of the organization. It changed their thought process: Rather than focusing on their own reaction, they began &amp;nbsp;considering the impact on the team and seeing themselves as part of the larger whole. The team decided to keep making the calls, but rotate the responsibility, so everyone wasn&#39;t having to make them every day. Recalibrating the team towards a higher purpose, reduces the pressure on the leader and increases buy-in from the team.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Coaching&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A primary function of any leader is &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;coaching their team&lt;/a>;. However, when coaching is added on top of deliverables, leaders may struggle to invest time in the development of their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recently, during a coaching program we ran for a group of sales managers in the hospitality industry, participants opened up about feeling overwhelmed. The organization has an exceptional culture and managers generally want to do a good job leading their teams. Yet, as travel began to boom, and they added more salespeople, managers found themselves stretched thin.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We asked the managers, “Who do you coach?” Their answer was almost unanimous: the people who are performing the worst. Yet, the sales managers lamented that despite their sizeable coaching investments, the poor performers were showing marginal improvement at best.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We then shifted the lens from servant leadership to noble-purpose leadership. Instead of asking who needs coaching the most, we suggested managers ask themselves: Where will my coaching time have the biggest impact?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The managers started to look at their team through a different lens: Who is the most coachable? Who learns quickly? Who has the most at stake with their customers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After the program ended, these managers began to invest more of their time in their high and mid-performers. They personally coached the high performers on their highest-value opportunities. They gave their mid-performers more attention with group coaching circles and peer-to-peer role plays. They didn&#39;t abandon coaching the bottom tier, but instead of spending hours of their coaching time, they directed lower performers to own more of their learning, via on-demand courses, self-study, etc.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The results followed quickly: High performers got even better, and mid-performers improved too. What&#39;s also interesting is that low performers did one of three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Worked their way to become middle performers&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Stayed the course, making the same marginal improvements as they did when they were taking nearly all of their manager&#39;s coaching time&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Or, when faced with the challenge of taking some ownership in their development, they self-selected out — a process that happened faster and with less frustration than a manager spending hours of time trying to coach a player who doesn&#39;t want to improve.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Overall, the team drove record revenue, and they were more fulfilled doing it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Servant leadership brought us to a more compassionate, human-centered work environment. It&#39;s time for us to make the next leap. In today&#39;s environment, burned-out leaders endlessly trying to serve will struggle to drive the innovation, resilience, and sense of meaning required for future growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Elevating the lens to noble-purpose leadership has the power to unite employees and managers in the pursuit of making a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overcoming Your Fear of Giving Tough Feedback]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1379555.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Juan Moyano/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A lack of constructive feedback is detrimental to your team, depriving them of mentorship and growth opportunities. And workplaces marked by poor communication and unclear expectations are breeding grounds for low trust and disengagement. Giving feedback is essential to being an effective leader. In this article, the author offers five ways to overcome your fear of giving feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“I felt like I was going to throw up,” Filip confessed to me during our coaching session. “Giving feedback is something a leader should be able to do every day without breaking a sweat,” he said. “But for me, it feels like the end of the world.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip was the director of project management at a company that offered translation services for streaming content providers across the globe. Hard working (sometimes to a fault), Filip was an expert at juggling multiple priorities, coordinating translators, quality control experts, and client liaisons across time zones, languages, and cultures. He had a knack for thriving in ambiguity, keeping his eye on strategic goals without getting lost in minutiae.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip also prided himself on always having his team&#39;s back, even if it involved taking the heat from an irate executive. But when it came to delivering feedback to his direct reports, Filip&#39;s resilient exterior crumbled. He would be overcome with worries of damaging the relationships he had worked so hard to build. He&#39;d overthink what to say for hours &lt;/span>;— &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;sometimes days. The mere thought of uttering the words, “I have some feedback for you,” made him nauseous.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;When a high-stakes project spearheaded by Angelique, one of Filip&#39;s brightest team members, failed, it brought his fear of giving feedback into sharp focus. For two weeks Filip had sensed something was amiss. The team&#39;s low spirits and sluggish performance concerned him, but he told himself Angelique would pull everything together in the end. He never voiced his concerns, and the cost was devastating. Their biggest account would now be going to a different provider who could provide better service.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“I could have prevented this. I should have spoken up.” Filip told me. His story echoes a struggle I hear from many of my executive coaching clients: How do I overcome the fear of giving feedback?&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Whether you worry about causing tension, demotivating your people, or handling others&#39; emotional reactions, conflict aversion is a common trait, and managers aren&#39;t immune to it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You&#39;re not doing anyone a favor by avoiding conflict. When problems go unaddressed or are swept under the rug, everyone suffers, including you. A lack of constructive feedback is also detrimental to your team, depriving them of mentorship and growth opportunities. Workplaces marked by poor communication and unclear expectations are breeding grounds for low trust and disengagement.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here&#39;s how to navigate the sense of discomfort and apprehension that comes with difficult conversations, so you can say what needs to be said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Challenge binary thinking.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many leaders who avoid confrontation carry assumptions like, “no one likes a micromanager,” or “bringing up this issue will ruin our working relationship.” While these beliefs may stem from past experiences with rejection and failure, they reflect inaccurate, binary thinking. In actuality, it&#39;s possible to be both assertive and direct without damaging relationships or earning a reputation as the “difficult manager.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Instead, focus on what you could gain by speaking up and the potential rewards of clear communication. Not only will voicing your thoughts help you feel more confident, but:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your input may be exactly what&#39;s needed to drive a challenging assignment to completion&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;That candid comment you make to a coworker about their disruptive behavior could result in a more peaceful, productive work environment.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your constructive criticism could help a team member develop and grow in their role, opening up new career opportunities&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;When you look more closely, you&#39;ll see that expressing your thoughts, feelings, and opinions is far more beneficial than stuffing them down and suffering the consequences.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;See feedback as a tool.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Despite what you may believe, your team craves meaningful, candid feedback. While 72% of employees &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbswk.hbs.edu/item/why-people-crave-feedback-and-why-were-afraid-to-give-it&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;rated&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “managers providing critical feedback” as important for them in career development, only 5% believe managers provide such feedback. Likewise, when team members don&#39;t think their boss is great at giving honest feedback, their engagement scores &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/overcoming-feedback-phobia-take-the-first-step&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;typically&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; take a nosedive. But on the flip side, leaders who rank in the top 10% at giving honest feedback create teams that rank in the top 23% of engagement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;It&#39;s not fair to deprive your team of information they need to grow. When you reframe conflict as a healthy, normative part of leadership, it loosens the anticipatory anxiety you may feel broaching difficult topics with others. Next time you have to give feedback, take a deep breath and remember, you&#39;re not causing a conflict, you&#39;re guiding your people toward growth. You&#39;re not criticizing; you&#39;re nurturing. And you&#39;re certainly not being a villain; you&#39;re being the leader they need.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Anticipate eventualities.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Fear of the unknown or wondering how the recipient will react can hold many leaders back from ever speaking up. What if your direct report becomes defensive and lashes out at you? What if they start crying?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You can calm your anxiety and handle uncertainty using the worst case/best case/most likely tool. Consider the worst that could happen. If your employee cries, for example, how would you handle it? Perhaps you&#39;d take a time out. Then consider the best that could possibly happen to foster more optimism. Finally, consider what is most likely, which is usually somewhere between the two extremes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Start strong.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;You can also ease your whirlwind of thoughts by planning your opening. Being in control from the get-go can provide a confidence boost and allows you to set a respectful tone for the conversation. Once Filip realized he needed to tackle the situation with Angelique head on, he approached her and said: “I appreciate your dedication and creativity. Something I wanted to talk about is a pattern of low morale, and I want to understand if there are any obstacles that we can address together.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Using “I” statements whenever possible helps ensure you communicate directly without vacillating or minimizing your concerns simply because you&#39;re scared. Being specific is also important. Rather than saying, “You dropped the ball again,” try saying, “I&#39;m concerned that I didn&#39;t get the documents in time for the client meeting today.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Make feedback part of the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Feedback should be a regular ritual, not an occasional blast. Making feedback a habit ensures the tiny annoyances and frustrations you harbor don&#39;t blow up into major conflicts. Plus, gradually exposing yourself to fearful situations is the best way to overcome them. The more you practice giving feedback in lower-stakes, everyday scenarios as part of your role, the better at it you&#39;ll become.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;A great way to systematize feedback is through regular &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones&quot;>;one-on-ones&lt;/a>; with your team. You can also schedule project debriefs where team members can reflect, or pre-mortems where people can discuss in advance any risks, potential problems, and flesh out how they&#39;ll work with one another.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Creating a positive feedback culture will give you opportunities to flex your newfound assertiveness skills while also strengthening rapport and trust with your team. And that, as a leader, is one of the best things you can hope for.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:55:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>