<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Harvard&rsquo;s Arthur C. Brooks on the Secrets to Happiness at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/harvards-arthur-c-brooks-on-the-secrets-to-happiness-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6336299890112&quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;加载中... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption= &quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Arthur C. Brooks 是畅销书作家、哈佛大学教授，也是《大西洋月刊》的一位广受读者欢迎的专栏作家，他的文章取材于科学和哲学，旨在为我们如何过上最好的生活提供见解和策略。他与奥普拉·温弗瑞 (Oprah Winfrey) 合着了即将出版的新书《构建你想要的生活：获得幸福的艺术与科学》，并与《哈佛商业评论》编辑阿迪·伊格内修斯 (Adi Ignatius) 共同创作了本集新工作世界分享如何在工作和生活中获得快乐的见解。事实证明，幸福是会传染的。但痛苦也是如此。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/harvards-arthur-c- brooks-on-the-secrets-to-happiness-at-work?language=es&quot;>;西班牙语阅读&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/harvards-arthur-c-brooks-on -the-secrets-to-happiness-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;对于那里的奋斗者和工作狂，畅销书作家、哈佛大学教授阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯 (Arthur C. Brooks) 说：给你的信息：在为时已晚之前改变你的行为。布鲁克斯就是你们中的一员：一位设定节奏的老板，他希望其他人像他一样每周工作 80 小时，几乎没有时间陪伴朋友和家人。他说他不是对工作上瘾，而是对成功上瘾。他怀念看着自己的孩子长大。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天，他将像他这样的行为归类为一种可能导致痛苦的病态。他还提供了具体、可行的建议来增加您的生活幸福感。事实上，他&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/projects/how-build-life/&quot;>;在&lt;em>;大西洋月刊&lt;/em>;的常规专栏&lt;/a>;中撰写了相关文章.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的视频系列“工作新世界”的这一集中，《哈佛商业评论》主编阿迪·伊格纳修斯与布鲁克斯（与奥普拉·温弗瑞）共同撰写了即将出版的新书《&lt;a href =&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Build-Life-You-Want-Science/dp/0593545400&quot;>;&lt;em>;打造你想要的生活：变得更幸福的艺术与科学&lt;/em>;&lt;/a >;、讨论：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;是什么导致过去几年总体幸福感严重下降？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;在工作中找到真正快乐的人的两个特质&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; “交易朋友”和“真正的朋友”之间的区别。真正的人“非常无用”，你比交易朋友更需要他们&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;布鲁克斯说，幸福是会传染的，只要和一个快乐的人在一起就能让你更快乐。 “但是，”他说，“痛苦更具传染性。”&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;亚瑟，欢迎。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作新世界&quot; dek=&quot;前几集&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight- center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心精选 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;新工作世界&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 往期剧集 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-组件>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;嗨，阿迪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong >;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我不想从巡回售书中抢走任何风头，但我想谈谈您的研究和见解的各个方面，特别是与工作世界相关的方面。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然。事实上，这本书是基于我在哈佛商学院教授的很多内容，我教授的课程名为“领导力与幸福”，这是一个非常超额认购的课程。它有 180 个座位，400 个等候名单，甚至还有一个他们认为我不知道的秘密 Zoom 链接。我很高兴与我的学生以及我们精彩的观众谈论我所谈论的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我希望有一些学生们听到你知道 Zoom 链接时感到震惊。但让我们设置一些背景。从一些数据开始。数据显示，尽管幸福产业蓬勃发展，但像您这样思考这个问题的人却认为我们变得越来越不幸福。&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;The New World of Work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href=&quot;/ resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 订阅我们的每周通讯 &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; 工作新世界 &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 关于人才、技术和商业未来的坦诚对话。为订阅者准备的特别电子邮件系列。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>;登录向上&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 感谢您注册，&lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>; &lt;/span>;！ &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 您可以查看我们的&lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;其他新闻通讯&lt;/a>;或通过管理您的&lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;随时选择退出电子邮件首选项&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;确实如此。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;至少在美国，抑郁症病例数量有所增加，自我报告自己快乐的人数也有所增加已下降。我知道不可能确切地说出原因，但你的预感是什么？这是怎么回事？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们确实很清楚发生了什么。你会发现，在 80 年代末、90 年代初，幸福感开始变得有点萎靡，有点下降，但随着社交媒体的出现，幸福感出现了真正的大幅下降。&lt;/p>; &lt;社交媒体对幸福感来说是灾难性的。部分原因是，当我们感到孤独时，我们会用一些类似于社交生活中的汉堡和薯条的东西来分散自己的注意力。它们给你提供大量卡路里，但营养不多。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这背后有很多神经科学，但每个人都知道，当你感到无聊或孤独时，你就会开始查看你的设备，然后你的手机，你实际上会变得更无聊，你会变得更孤独。这是一个巨大的问题，特别是对于年轻人来说。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后冠状病毒出现了，这是我们长期以来在全球范围内看到的对公众幸福最灾难性的事件。通常，大约 30% 的人会说他们对自己的生活非常幸福，15% 的人会说他们不幸福。其余的都在中间。这些都被翻转了。现在大约有 30% 的人不快乐，15% 的人非常快乐。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些趋势实际上并没有扭转。我们知道它与社会生活息息相关。它与我们的爱情关系息息相关。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们知道带来最幸福生活的习惯——你的哲学或信仰生活、你的家庭生活、你真正的友谊，以及亲自为他人服务的工作——这些已经在下降。当这些事情衰退时，没有任何技术可以解决问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你确实掌握了它。我想专注于工作世界。我认为这是从书中的统计数据得出的，我想你说只有 16% 的员工自我报告说他们对自己的工作非常满意。我想问这个问题是因为我们醒着的时间有一半是在办公室度过的，但我们却没有得到应有的成就感和满足感。那么这里发生了什么以及我们如何考虑改变现状？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C.布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我一直在研究什么能给人们带来工作满意度。时间最长，当我刚开始时，我还是一名新博士。我想，好吧，让我们看看营利性工作、非营利性工作和政府工作：哪个能带来最大的幸福？事实证明，这微不足道。所以我说，好吧，高薪与低薪。超过一定的生存水平，那就是洗钱了。受过大学教育，没有受过大学教育，白领，蓝领，这些都不重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最幸福的工人，即从工作中获得最大幸福感的人，会表现出两件事。他们觉得自己正在赢得成功，也就是说，他们正在用自己的生活和工作生活创造价值，他们的成就正在推动发展，他们因这些成就而受到认可。第二，他们觉得自己在为人们服务，所以他们是被需要的。这是两件大事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在很多人都在关注我们，他们都是雇主，我也曾担任过首席执行官。为了招聘、留住人才，你能做的第一件事就是确保你有一个系统，让人们通过自己的优点和个人成就来获得成功，而最终的回报远远超出了金钱的范围。他们知道这一点，他们看到了这一点，他们的朋友也是如此。他们实际上感觉自己正在为其他人服务，并且他们可以看到他们正在为之创造价值的人们的面孔。这些都是大事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有一件事要记住，当我们面对面时，这些事情是最容易做的。就是这样。你说我们一生的一半时间都是在工作中与同事度过的。好吧，我不知道，伙计，不再了。很多人一生的一半时间都在 Zoom 屏幕前度过，在那里你很难获得成功，很难感觉自己在为别人服务，甚至看不到你的工作伙伴。这是很难的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你是对的，那么这里一定有一些自欺欺人。如果你问人们，他们喜欢混合动力。他们喜欢在家工作。他们谈论这让他们更好地平衡工作与生活，我们认为所有这些都会转化为满足感和幸福感。但你认为我们在欺骗自己吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在某种程度上，存在一系列偏见在起作用这里。例如，我们发现的一件事是，当你真的感到孤独时，它会损害你大脑的执行中枢。我们知道这一点。这就是为什么当你真的感到悲伤和孤独时，你会窝在沙发上，盖上舒适的毯子，看 Netflix 视频，吃哈根达斯。你应该做的是起床，到外面去获取一些维生素 D，骑自行车，给你的朋友打电话，但你在那个特定时刻受到了损害。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在大流行期间，人们开始变得更加孤立。我不得不说，他们充分利用了这种隔离，创造了非常非常方便的生活。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也就是说，有些人确实有更好的工作与生活平衡，因为他们想把这一切都花掉与家人共度时光。问题在于，所有与家人和朋友分离的人实际上都看不到工作中的人，这对幸福来说确实是灾难性的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>; &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这本书在很多方面都是关于代理的：幸福和满足感不是基于外部变量或发生在我们身上的事情，而是完全在我们的控制范围内。问题是很难采取戏剧性的行动来重新安排一个人的生活。如何让人们明白他们应该这样做，但谁不这样做呢？你如何实现这一飞跃？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;部分问题在于，很多人注意到他们可以管理自己的资金他们可以管理自己的公司，但无法管理自己的感情。或者他们可以管理自己的家，可以管理自己的家庭生活，但他们无法管理自己的情绪。原因是情感生活是一个不同种类的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们工作中周围的事情，这些都是复杂的问题，这意味着它们很难弄清楚。但是一旦你这样做了，你就可以掌握它们并一遍又一遍地重复解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生活和你的情绪，内心的事情和你所得到的感受，无论是积极的还是消极的，它们都会”一点也不复杂。它们就是数学家所说的复杂问题。这是一个非常容易理解的问题，没有任何计算能力可以为您解决它。你只能进入其中、体验它并实时处理它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;猫是一个复杂的问题。烤面包机是一个复杂的问题。你的工作更像是烤面包机，而你的人际关系则更像是一只猫。你的感受非常复杂。结果是，我可以掌握所有这些高度复杂的事情，但我无法专注于自己的感受。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;解决方案始于理解人类情感科学。这就是我在很多工作中所做的事情。这就是我的哈佛商学院学生来找我的时候，这些才华横溢、成功的 MBA 学生，确实是在世界上最好的商学院。他们会说，“我最大的问题是我无法控制自己的感受，我觉得我真的失控了。”因此，我们获得的首要技能是像对待您要管理的其他任何东西一样对待您的情感系统、大脑边缘系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将其视为您正在参与的复杂系统并使用我们在课堂上讨论的技术，这些技术基本上是从学习如何体验你的情绪开始的，不是当它们传递给你时，而是在你大脑的前额叶皮层中，这样你就可以决定如何反应，替代情绪，甚至无视情绪，而是故意的。这是一套称为元认知的特定技术，我基于尖端神经科学来介绍它。任何人都可以做到。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;问题是，我们不教孩子们这样做。我们不教小学生这样做。我们不教商人这样做。如果按照我的方式，每个商学院、每个高中都会有这个课程，当你来到大公司工作时，他们会开设元认知和情绪自我管理课程，你必须首先学习这些课程。一周的迎新活动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为，正如您所说，无论以何种标准衡量，这些商科学生都取得了令人难以置信的成功。可能存在分歧，但您是否发现他们渴望您所教的内容，或者他们对您所教的内容持怀疑态度？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C.布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/他们真的很渴望它。我的意思是，最持怀疑态度的人可能没有参加这门课。毕竟这是选修课。真正持怀疑态度的人来自供应链管理之类的领域。但事实是，他们真的渴望它，因为他们想要它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的方法基本上是这样的：你可以更快乐，但你必须了解科学。你需要利用科学来改变你的习惯和生活方式，然后你需要将其传授给其他人，使其永久存在于你的生活中。这门课被称为“领导力与幸福”，因为我希望每个领导者都成为一名幸福老师。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我每年在哈佛以外的地方进行 175 场演讲，主要是与商业观众交谈。我说，“听着，我要给你看一堆关于幸福科学的幻灯片，我想让你做的就是拿着这些幻灯片，把我的名字去掉，写上你的名字，然后我想要你把它教给别人，这样你就能永久地理解这项技术，并且在自己的生活中也不会忘记它。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是完成它的方法。这就是我们在哈佛教授的方式，而且它确实非常有效。我告诉你，阿迪，坦率地说，我是这项工作中我自己的第一个病人。因为我想变得更快乐。作为一名社会科学家，我将自己的工具包应用于自己。我想成为一个更快乐的人。因为我一直在写关于幸福的科学，所以我在自己身上进行了实验，我在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/projects/how-build-life/&quot;>; 中建议的一切我在&lt;em>;大西洋月刊&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;上的专栏以及我的学生，我首先要确保我确实相信它有效。我不仅仅是阅读学术期刊文章，然后将其传授给其他人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在过去四年中，我的幸福感提高了 60%。短短四年时间。可以肯定的是，它一开始的基线较低，但 60% 很大程度上是基于幸福感的最佳测量技术。所以我知道它是有效的，而且我每天也在我的学生中看到它的结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们继续关注沙发多一点。你给人的印象是一个积极的、大概是快乐的人。我知道第一印象可能会有所偏差，但即使是“我的幸福感提高了 60%”这句话，我也无法想象你到底在衡量什么才能得出这样一个具体的数字。有哪些测量值？您的数字为何发生变化以及如何变化？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们可以参加一些一般幸福感调查。它们遍布互联网。如果他们的心理测量能力强，他们就能做得很好。然而，我喜欢看的是我将情感中的消极和积极强度水平分开。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;情感意味着情绪。我们发现，如果你有一点不适，如果你是一个忧郁的人，要么你的快乐水平太低，要么你的不快乐水平太高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在，它似乎我在这里吹毛求疵，但我没有。很多人认为幸福和不幸福是相反的：如果你不幸福，就意味着你缺乏幸福。这是完全错误的。快乐和不快乐，或者积极和消极的情绪，它们很大程度上存在于大脑的不同半球。它们的产生有不同的原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;恐惧、愤怒、厌恶和悲伤等负面情绪，这些情绪是为了让你活下去而进化出来的。你应该非常非常感谢你的负面情绪。但如果它们太强烈，就会损害您的生活质量。你的快乐、爱和对事物的兴趣等积极情绪，这些都是进化而来的，它们确实是值得拥有的好东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;问题是有些人的幸福水平太低。其他人，他们的不快乐程度太高了。我有一个对我的学生进行的测试。我没有开发它。它是由心理测量学家在大约 20 年前开发的。但这被称为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://psytests.org/emo/panasen.html&quot;>;PANAS 测试&lt;/a>;，即积极情绪消极情绪系列，它可以区分积极情绪和消极情绪的强度.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;实际上，你有四种不同的特征。你可以高度积极，也可以高度消极。你可以是低积极的，也可以是低消极的。你可以是高积极和低消极，当然你也可以是高消极和低积极。他们各占人口的四分之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;高，高，这是一个高情感的人，它被称为疯狂科学家。这就是我。我的幸福问题不是我不快乐或者我不够快乐。相反，这只是意味着我需要管理我的高水平负面情绪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他人有不同的问题。每个人都希望自己的积极性高，消极性低。这就是所谓的啦啦队长。事实证明啦啦队也有问题。例如，如果两个拉拉队队员相遇并结婚，他们将无法承受任何威胁或听到任何坏消息或认为将来可能会发生任何不好的事情。他们会花光所有的钱并破产。拉拉队长，他们往往是相当不稳定的首席执行官，因为他们不会听坏消息，而且他们往往会被威胁消灭。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;高消极，低积极，这些都是诗人。他们往往非常有创造力，但他们经常遭受悲伤和这些负面情绪的困扰。他们必须处理好这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，低，低，这些人并不是非常不快乐或生活质量低下。他们的影响强度较低。这些是法官。这些人都是清醒的人。他们是伟大的外科医生，他们是伟大的诉讼律师和法官。他们是青少年、高压力职业等的优秀父母。但他们往往看起来有点不热情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我给我的学生做这些测试，这样他们就可以知道该嫁给谁，如何管理自己，如何管理自己。围绕他们建立一个与他们互补的管理团队。这真的非常非常有启发性，这是我衡量自己幸福感的方法之一，也是我需要的管理技巧，将神经科学应用于我的生活，并且我可以将其应用到其他人的生活中。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们需要在多大程度上快乐地工作？我的意思是，一种工作方式可以是我这样做，我希望赚到体面的钱来养活自己，并且我专注于我的个人发展，关注工作之外的幸福。显然，在一个理想的世界里，我们到处都是快乐和满足的，但我们需要在工作中快乐吗？这有多重要？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C.布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是一个关于生活质量高的人是否倾向于工作快乐或者没关系。事实上，如果你在工作中不快乐，你的生活也可能会不快乐。这很简单。我的意思是，就像没有人每天工作一个小时一样。也许您是每周工作四小时的幸运者之一。我的朋友 Tim Ferriss 写了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/4-Hour-Workweek-Escape-Live-Anywhere/dp/0307465357&quot;>;那本著名的书&lt;/a>;，事实是，很多人可以在比他们少得多的时间内完成工作。但我们大多数人都没有这样的奢侈。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我的整个职业生涯中，我每周工作 80 个小时，其中一部分是一种病态。我不会骗你，我在研究中谈论了很多关于自我客体化、工作狂的话题，这些都是基于成功成瘾和对失败的恐惧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有人都在观看，你们知道我也在谈论你。所以要小心这些病症，因为它们和其他任何事情一样都是成瘾的，其中有很多大脑化学反应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但关键是，你将花费大量时间来做这件事。如果这是苦差事，那就糟糕了。你不想做苦差事。至少它应该是令人愉快的事情，并且有时它完全超出了我们的掌控范围，并且使其变得令人愉快。如果你有一份你真正讨厌的工作和一个最糟糕的老板，那么，那就不好了。但很多事情都掌握在我们手中，这就是我正在做的很多事情，也是我试图帮助人们了解他们实际上可以管理的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS： &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你刚才提到了工作狂。我想我们中的许多人都怀疑自己患有这种疾病，但也许不愿意太仔细地审视这是否属实。但工作狂是一种高度，我们得到了一种自我意识，一种成就感等等。但这肯定不完全是一件好事。对于那些可能没有意识到自己就是这样的工作狂，您有什么建议？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，工作狂实际上是对你的生活质量来说太糟糕了。问题是，当你是工作狂时，人们会祝贺你。没有人说：“伙计，你喝杜松子酒真是太棒了。”从来没有人说过，“伙计，你对你能消耗多少甲基苯丙胺感到难以置信。”这些并不是赞美。当你沉迷于其他物质、赌博、色情或任何其他有害、危险、令人上瘾的东西时，人们会为你感到难过，这些东西会占据你的大脑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是工作狂，伙计，你整夜工作，当你每周工作 100 小时时，人们会说：“伙计，你真是太累了。”你会说，“是的，我对自己感觉很好，但为什么我不能维持适当的关系？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事情的真相是，确实有四个人的投资组合拥有真正幸福生活的事物，它们需要既丰富又平衡。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第一是信仰和哲学，无论它是宗教的还是非宗教的，它都必须是让你看不到生命的伟大，让你变得渺小，这样你就能正确看待自己。你会得到平安。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，你必须认真关注你的家庭关系。不是开玩笑，家庭关系是最神秘的一种爱，你无法替代任何东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你的友谊，现在，对于工作狂来说，这是非常糟糕的。工作狂有很多生意上的朋友，但真正的朋友却很少。每个观看我们节目的人都知道真实与交易之间的区别。如果你不这样做，那就带上那些工作狂同事，带上你最常见到、花最多时间相处的 10 个人，在每个人之后写下真实的内容或交易，然后亲眼看看你是否需要对此进行调整。交易的朋友很有用，真正的朋友对你来说毫无用处。无用之人够多吗？这就是问题所在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后但并非最不重要的是工作。工作中真正重要的两部分不是头衔、金钱、钦佩、权力，而是赢得成功和为他人服务。工作狂会损害我们生活中的这些成就感来源。它使人贫穷。它使我们变得更加贫穷，以至于我们实际上无法追求这些其他支柱。结果是我们没有一个平衡的投资组合。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;看，如果你为幸福所做的一切都是工作，那就相当于把你的全部养老金都投入了希腊债券。也许可行，但我是一名经济学家。我不推荐它。这不是多元化战略。你很可能不会按照你想要的方式退休。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是沙特阿拉伯提出的一个问题，很简单，有趣的问题。幸福会传染吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;是的，幸福绝对具有传染性，因为社会传染是真实存在的。阿迪，我们附近有一项非常伟大的研究，他们被称为来自马萨诸塞州弗雷明汉的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.framinghamheartstudy.org/&quot;>;弗雷明汉心脏研究&lt;/a>;。看起来有50多年了。它的成立是为了观察人们的生活，生活的不同社会方面如何影响身体物质，肥胖是否具有社会传染性等等。但他们开始关注其他事物，比如幸福感，他们发现，仅仅处于和一个快乐的人在一起会让你更快乐。让你的配偶变得更快乐会让你更快乐。让你最好的朋友变得更快乐会让你更快乐。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但更具传染性的是痛苦。这就是为什么你不希望你十几岁的孩子和一个穿着一身黑、总是看起来闷闷不乐的孩子一起出去玩。那是因为它就像，“哦，那太糟糕了。一切都很糟糕。”你不希望这样，因为这在社会上具有传染性，你的孩子会变得令人难以置信的消极和悲伤。没有人希望自己的孩子受到这种影响，因为他们有一种社会传染的感觉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我在家庭动态中看到的第一个问题是消极情绪的社会传染。这就是我们每个人都必须扭转的局面，就是尝试将幸福病毒注入我们的家庭，并且基本上是有目的地这样做的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;这是一个来自尼泊尔的问题，与您的主题相关。您谈到了人们在自己的生活以及自己的成就感和幸福感中发挥作用。但是，我们应该如何对待那些不相信这些东西、不相信工作与生活平衡的领导者呢？你可以自己努力，但正如你所说，痛苦和所有这些东西是会传染的。如果领导层不重视这些，你怎么能推动领导力的发展呢？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;阿瑟·C·布鲁克斯：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当谈到领导力时，领导者领导你自己。你的第一名员工就是你自己。不要成为引领者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还记得 Daniel Goleman 写那本著名的书时&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Leadership-Results-Harvard-Business-Classics/ dp/1633692620&quot;>;&lt;em>;取得成果的领导力&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;？这是关于六种类型的领导者，每个人都认为很棒但实际上很糟糕的第一个领导特征是工作狂领导者，他们一直在办公室里说：“看，如果我是要要求别人努力工作，我就必须更加努力。”这对其他人来说是非常令人沮丧的。这降低了他们的生活质量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我担任首席执行官时，我告诉你，我的执行团队中的某个人说，“Arthur，你必须停止在凌晨 5:00 和 11:00 发送电子邮件：晚上 00 点，因为人们会熬夜想知道是否需要回复您的电子邮件。”我说，“我不希望任何人……”这不是重点。因此，我在电子邮件上设置了计时器来做到这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但更好的是，当我的妻子开始限制并说：“你需要多睡觉。你需要多去健身房。你需要有更多的生活。”所以第一，如果你是一名领导者，你需要抓住这个问题，因为你会伤害自己，破坏你的人际关系，并使你周围的所有人都感到沮丧。这是一个大问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二，不要为工作狂工作。如果可以的话，不要为他们工作。再说一遍，并不是每个人都拥有所有这些程度的自由，但我们大多数人在工作方面都有一些选择。顺便说一句，如果你的老板虐待你并且无可救药地沉迷于毒品，你就必须改变环境。这是一种虐待关系。我建议远离工作狂。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在，工作狂的背后是什么？工作狂朋友们？这就是成功瘾。工作狂是成功成瘾的次要成瘾，其中很多都是基于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/podcasts/archive/2021/10/howto-arthurbrooks-happiness-identity- drshefali-mindativity-meaning-2021/620282/&quot;>;客观化自己&lt;/a>;，这是一件坏事，而且对失败有深深的恐惧。这些才是真正需要开始做的事情。你不能只是说：“少工作，有什么问题吗？”这几乎总是自我客体化和对失败的恐惧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是你会想到新加入劳动力队伍的人，其中一些人are your HBS students who are working for investment banks, who are working for law firms, and there is this expectation of exploitation where, yes, I&#39;m working around the clock. It is killing me, but it is getting me to where I will be rich, fulfilled, happy. How can people who are ambitious in those fields do otherwise?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ARTHUR C. BROOKS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the things that I tell my students is you&#39;ve got to have a balanced happiness portfolio, and killing all of your relationships to spend 110 hours in an investment bank is the worst, most unbalanced happiness portfolio you can possibly get. Plus, you&#39;re losing your best years to establish the relationships that you&#39;re going to want to cultivate for the rest of your life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;People say, “Okay, I&#39;m 28. I&#39;m going to go get an investment bank job, they&#39;re going to expect me to work a hundred hours a week. That&#39;s fine. I&#39;ll look for a spouse when I&#39;m 35.” Probably not. I got the data, and the data don&#39;t lie. You&#39;re more and more likely to actually not have the thing that&#39;s going to give you the most happiness in your life, which is your marriage. We actually have to think in a balanced-portfolio approach to the happiness that we&#39;re trying to get, and making those sacrifices are really bad sacrifices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Adi, guys like you and me, our age, in our fifties, you notice that we don&#39;t make those sacrifices anymore. And the reason is because our time parameters are shorter. But also we&#39;ve had bitter experience with these types of things. It&#39;s funny, it&#39;s like I&#39;m a grandfather now and my grandson was born and suddenly I was a lot less interested in working. But part of it was the bitter experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;ll tell you a story actually that will motivate this. When I was interviewing this woman for my last book, which is called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Strength-Finding-Success-Happiness-Purpose-ebook/dp/B08WCKY8MB&quot;>;&lt;em>;From Strength to Strength&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, about how to get happier as you get older, a titan of Wall Street. This woman was just famous and rich, a billionaire, and she was horribly unhappy. She was my age, late fifties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And I said, “What&#39;s wrong?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;She said, “Well, my husband and I were roommates. I&#39;m kind of cordial with my adult kids, but it&#39;s not close. I&#39;m getting bad reports from the doctor. I think I drink too much. I need to go to the gym. My employees are starting to doubt the wisdom of my decision-making. And I don&#39;t know, what do I do?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And I said, “What do you mean? You don&#39;t need a Harvard professor to tell you what to do. You&#39;re prescribing to yourself, stepping back, going away with your husband. You&#39;re already rich. Why don&#39;t you do that?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;She said, “It&#39;s true, but I guess I&#39;ve always chosen to be special rather than happy.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boom, man. It was like a knife to my heart, Adi. All these years when I was running a company and the 14th hour at the office before the first hour with my kids, well, news flash man, they grew up. They grew up and I missed a lot of it. And I really, really regret that. Now I&#39;m not going to miss it with my grandkids, I get a do-over. I&#39;m not going to screw that up twice. That&#39;s a really important thing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If I could have had a little bit more perspective, I would not have been less successful. The data don&#39;t lie on this either. The 14th hour is not productive. It&#39;s just compulsive. Just like any other addiction, the 14th drink doesn&#39;t give you more joy. Stop at two, is the bottom line, because you need the balance in this part of your life as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At HBR we try to be super practical, so before you go, can you leave the audience shortcuts to happiness, or just things that viewers can think about or do today that can be a meaningful step in that direction?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ARTHUR C. BROOKS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Every week in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/projects/how-build-life/&quot;>;my column in the Atlantic&lt;/a>;, every Thursday morning, I have a big topic and I do talk about the science, but then I always give three ways to live this thing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Just in general, since we&#39;re on the meta topic of happiness, the way to think about happiness is that it&#39;s not a feeling. If happiness were a feeling, that would be very disappointing. It would depend on how you slept last night and what you ate for breakfast and no good. If your spouse yelled at you this morning, no good. Don&#39;t chase the feeling. Feelings are evidence of happiness, like the smell of the turkey is evidence of your Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Happiness is three things that we need to be thinking about and managing in our lives. Enjoyment, satisfaction, and purpose. Those are the three big things that we need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Enjoyment is not pleasure, pleasure is an animal thing. Enjoyment is the pleasure you get plus the people that you enjoy it with and the memories that you&#39;re making. That&#39;s why beer commercials don&#39;t have a guy alone in his apartment pounding a 12 pack. They have people enjoying a few beers together because it&#39;s pleasure plus people plus memory. Don&#39;t do the stuff that makes you feel good alone. That&#39;s the rule of thumb.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second is satisfaction. Satisfaction is the joy you get when you struggle for something and you get that. Now fellow strivers, the striver&#39;s curse is you get on something called the hedonic treadmill where you struggle and struggle and achieve it, but then it doesn&#39;t give you very much satisfaction for very long and so you keep trying and trying and trying again.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The solution to that is not to have more, it&#39;s to want less. Your satisfaction is your haves divided by your wants. Manage your denominator with a wants-management strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And last but not least, it&#39;s meaning, it&#39;s purpose in your life. The way to figure out if you have a purpose crisis is asking yourself two simple questions. There&#39;s no right answers, but you have to have answers. “Why am I alive, and for what am I willing to die today?” And if you don&#39;t have answers, go looking for the answers with introspection. When you see somebody that finds those answers, it&#39;s like an actual miracle.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These are the three things practically to think about. “Do I have enjoyment or just pleasure? Am I managing my wants or my haves, so I can have satisfaction? And do I have enough meaning in my life by answering those two questions?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s great. I hope people took notes, I hope people try to act on that. Arthur, I want to thank you for being on the show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ARTHUR C. BROOKS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thank you, Adi. And thanks to everybody watching.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Incorporating DEI into Decision-Making]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/incorporating-dei-into-decision-making]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_01_aJTiW00qqtI_5989933_B3UFXwcVbc4_3neSwyntbQ8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash/Pexels&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Most people believe in promoting DEI in the workplace. But implicit and unconscious biases &amp;#8212; not to mention the constant juggling of priorities required at work &amp;#8212; can lead to inequitable decision-making. In this article, drawing on recent research, the authors suggest that this problem can be addressed by making DEI more immediately obvious, or &lt;em>;salient&lt;/em>;, to managers immediately before they need to make consequential decisions about such matters as hiring, promotions, and performance evaluation. The authors discuss three particularly effective ways of doing so.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/incorporating-dei-into-decision-making?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/incorporating-dei-into-decision-making?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Most people don&#39;t think of themselves as biased or prejudiced, and people often explicitly endorse diversity as something companies should strive for. But many organizations struggle with DEI. Why?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Implicit or unconscious biases can lead to inequitable decision-making. More mundanely, people are just busy. They have lots of competing priorities and lots to occupy their brains. Even if they care about DEI, they might not have it top of mind as they go about their work. As a result, they might not see how their decisions are relevant for DEI and so might inadvertently make inequitable decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To fix this, managers and organizations should make DEI more immediately obvious, or &lt;em>;salient&lt;/em>;, when it matters most — that is, when consequential decisions about such matters as hiring, promotions, and performance evaluation are being made. Our academic research and experiences partnering with companies suggest that to make real progress on DEI, managers and organizations need to make DEI salient in those moments of consequential decision-making. We&#39;ve identified three particularly effective ways of doing so.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Ask managers to hire for more than one job at a time. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many hiring decisions are made in isolation, with only one person being hired at a time. When this is the case, diversity simply just isn&#39;t that salient to decision-makers, who are often thinking not about diversity but instead about technical skills, cultural fit, or how quickly a candidate can start. This shouldn&#39;t be surprising, because diversity is a property of groups, not individuals. You can describe a group of people as “diverse” or “homogeneous,” after all, but not an individual person.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the other hand, when people make collective hiring decisions — when they hire multiple people at a time — our &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2019.3533&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; shows that people select more diversity. They start thinking about the candidates they&#39;re selecting as a group, which makes diversity more salient and leads to hiring decisions that improve it. For example, rather than hiring one person every month, a company might benefit from grouping these decisions together and hiring three people very quarter. The total number of people hired will be the same, but making collective decisions every quarter should lead to more diversity. Relatedly, it might also be beneficial to give one person oversight over hiring decisions across teams or departments, enabling that person to make collective hiring decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Ask managers to make diversity more salient in the promotion process. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This recommendation comes from work that we&#39;ve done at our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.morethannow.co.uk/single-post/2022/8/22/the-inclusion-lab&quot;>;Inclusion Lab at MoreThanNow&lt;/a>;, a collaboration of academics and consultants focused on generating empirical evidence about what actually works at improving DEI in the workplace. Specifically, it grows out of a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/why-you-should-start-ab-testing-your-dei-initiatives&quot;>;field experiment&lt;/a>; we conducted with a global management, engineering, and development consultancy that wanted to know if we could help it increase equity in its promotions process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At this company, promotions are made by a group of high-level senior managers in a bi-annual promotions process, during which managers can nominate their employees for promotion. Managers justify their nominations in a statement of 50 words or less in an online form. In our experiment, 116 of these senior managers were randomly assigned to receive one of two messages in advance of submitting their nominations. The control group was asked to consider promoting people who had displayed excellent performance and competence beyond their current grade. The treatment group was asked to consider the same criteria — but also to consider the diversity of their nominees as a whole, and whether their choices would help to close representation gaps. In other words, we made DEI more salient for this group of managers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What happened when we did this? Although the sample for this experiment was small (which means some caution should be exercised in interpreting the findings), we found that making diversity salient increased the number of employees promoted from underrepresented ethnic backgrounds. The effects seem to be driven by male senior managers, who at baseline may have been less likely to think spontaneously about diversity. We did not find any statistically significant positive or negative treatment effects on the promotion rates of female employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Ask managers to view a short diversity training video right before formal people decisions. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This suggestion uses salience to help organizations dramatically rethink how they implement diversity training. Prior research suggests that training is &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/does-diversity-training-work-the-way-its-supposed-to&quot;>;largely ineffective at actually changing behavior&lt;/a>;. However, we think this may be because it doesn&#39;t make DEI salient in the moment of consequential decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In most organizations, people are given diversity training when they get onboarded, or perhaps on an annual basis. That&#39;s often months or years before they actually make consequential hiring, promotion, or performance-evaluation decisions for the company, which means they&#39;re extremely unlikely to have the messages of the training in mind when they make those decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Imagine instead if an organization had managers take a short training immediately prior to making a consequential HR decision. Because the training happens just before the decision, it has a much higher likelihood of ensuring that DEI remains salient and encourage managers to make more equitable choices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have evidence of exactly this finding from a field experiment that we at the Inclusion Lab have been conducting with Ericsson, a multinational telecommunications company headquartered in Sweden. We delivered an automated 5-minute DEI training to some managers before they screened resumes and found that the managers who got this training were significantly more likely to hire people from underrepresented groups at Ericsson.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The experiment suggests that the significant amount of time and cost we invest into DEI training can indeed pay off — but only when organizations choose the right moment for it. One-off “blanket” training may well not be the way forward. Instead, organizations may want to consider how to use repeated smaller training modules in advance of key decision points to make DEI salient and therefore effective. We see this as fertile ground for further experimentation in the months and years ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Most people really do want to do the right thing when it comes to DEI, but they often just need a nudge or prompt to keep DEI top of mind at the right time. Our research strongly suggests that managers and organizations can do this by making DEI more salient at moments of consequential decision-making.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 01 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are Collaboration Tools Overwhelming Your Team?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/are-collaboration-tools-overwhelming-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_31_1494319608-2-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当今的员工对碎片化、不可预测且势不可挡的协作工具集合感到麻木。广告上说的那些东西正是为了提高他们的生产力。他们知道自己超负荷了，感到精疲力竭，但相信自己几乎无法采取任何措施来减缓沟通的冲击。作者探讨了协作技术膨胀如何影响员工，并试图帮助人们掌控自己的工作。他们将自己的干预措施称为“合作清理”。以下是他们的研究结果，以及领导者简化员工流程的策略。协作工具的使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/are-collaboration-tools-overwhelming-your-team ?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/are-collaboration-tools-overwhelming-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;阅读葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;典型员工会检查电子邮件 &lt;a href=&quot;https://ppm.express/blog/how-much-time-your-employees-spend-on-checking-emails/&quot;>;77 次&lt;/a>; 并收到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/technology/shortcuts/2019/apr/08/how-many-work-emails-is-too-many&quot;>;121 封新电子邮件&lt; /a>; 每天。在这样做的同时，许多人还&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/how-much-time-and-energy-do-we-waste-toggling- Between-applications&quot;>;在应用程序之间来回切换&lt;/a>; 、在 Slack 和 Teams 等应用程序上的 ping、对共享文档的评论以及来自一系列公司门户网站的通知之间来回切换。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，当今的员工因支离破碎、不可预测且难以承受的工作而感到麻木，也就不足为奇了。协作工具的集合——被广告上宣传的可以提高生产力的东西所困。他们知道自己负担过重，感到精疲力尽，但相信自己几乎无法采取任何措施来减缓沟通的冲击。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们探讨了协作技术的膨胀如何影响员工，并试图帮助人们掌控自己的工作工作。我们将我们的干预措施称为“协作净化”。在这里，我们将探讨我们的发现（剧透：有好消息也有坏消息），并概述领导者应该采取哪些措施来简化员工协作工具的使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;协作清理&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这种“清理” ” 由 Asana 的工作创新实验室与 Amazon Web Services 合作实施。我们将 58 名志愿者（其中包括 Asana 和 Amazon 员工）随机分配到两组中的一组。我们要求所有参与者每周至少报告一次他们用于与同事互动的协作技术（例如 Slack、Figma 和 Zoom）。我们还要求他们评估每种工具如何帮助他们实现当前的工作目标，以及使用每种工具需要付出多少努力。最后，我们要求他们选择特定的技术，并在两周内不要使用。我们要求第一组的人在两周内停止使用一半的协作工具。第二组的人可以选择取消哪些协作工具以及取消多少协作工具。所有参与者都告诉我们他们计划搁置哪些技术，并每天记日记，记录他们偏离“批准”列表的任何情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种清理的灵感来自于对 &lt;a href=&quot;https&quot; 的研究://static.macmillan.com/static/smp/the-friction-project/&quot;>;减法思维&lt;/a>;，包括我们之前在工作创新实验室的干预&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/meeting- Overload-is-a-fixable-problem&quot;>;帮助人们消除并重新设计糟糕的会议&lt;/a>;。这项研究表明，人们倾向于通过给自己和他人增加&lt;em>;更多&lt;/em>;的复杂性和负担来解决问题——即使减法是一种更有效的策略。但促使他们放慢速度，思考他们可以和应该从工作中删除什么，可以帮助他们克服添加而不是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/when-subtraction-adds-value&quot;>;减去&lt;/a的本能>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;好消息：参与者更加意识到他们的数字负担&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当他们开始进行清理时，两组参与者都更加意识到他们生活中充斥着的数字混乱 —他们没有考虑太多或根本没有考虑过，也没有尝试过减少或消除这些杂乱。百分之四十一的人报告（没有提示）他们变得更加注意使用太多协作工具对他们的注意力和生产力的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一位研究科学家这样向我们介绍：“[净化] 让我更加了解我正在使用的不同工具以及它们对我的生产力和专注感的影响。切换工具会产生微妙的成本，而且额外的摩擦会损害我的注意力和生产力。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了更深入地反思他们如何使用工具之外，参与者还朝着使用更少的协作工具迈出了小步全面的。超过一半 (53%) 的参与者告诉我们，由于清洁，他们至少会减少使用一种工具的频率。他们希望有意识地剔除自己的技术堆栈，从而腾出时间和认知带宽来进行更专注的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一位客户洞察分析师告诉我们，这种清理教会她在使用某些特别分散注意力的内容时更加谨慎。协作技术（例如消息传递平台）可减少干扰。她做出的一项改变是计划时间间隔，在早上 10 分钟、午餐后 10 分钟和一天结束时 10 分钟集中使用协作技术，否则根本不会使用它们。&lt;/p >; &lt;h2>;坏消息：参与者在净化后感到更加无助和疲惫&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;干预似乎还产生了一些令我们惊讶的负面后果。在我们促使参与者更加注意他们的工具使用后，他们报告说他们的无助感增加了。当他们停下来寻找要进行减法的数字工具时，许多人意识到这样做将是一项耗时的考验，或者根本不可能。这是因为团队内部和外部的许多其他人期望（或要求）他们使用特定的协作工具，因此摆脱这些共享工具的决定不是他们一个人（或根本不是）。协作清理引发的意识让他们想要反击并彻底改革他们的工具。但许多人感到受到不可避免的规则、传统和权力动态的阻碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，一位项目风险经理表示，她会尽量减少协作工具的使用，但认为自己不会成功。由于不同的团队因自己的喜好或公司要求而使用不同的工具，她和她的同事经常对应该使用哪种消息传递工具与不同业务部门的人员进行沟通感到困惑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两组参与者均表示一种无助感和由此产生的疲惫感，但第一组的情况似乎更为严重，我们要求参与者在两周内不要使用一半的工具——事实证明，这项任务不仅艰巨，而且往往是不可能的。许多参与者意识到他们无法按照自己的意愿减少工具的使用，这让他们感到沮丧和疲惫。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二组的参与者可以灵活地削减协作工具列表他们认为有必要，也报告了无用和数字疲惫的感觉，尽管他们的痛苦似乎不那么激烈。我们发现，减少工具的任务是复杂而艰巨的，并且留意实现这一目标的斗争可能会无意中加剧无助感。 ://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/AMPROC.2023.11120abstract&quot;>;相关研究&lt;/a>;，我们采访了来自各个行业的 63 名知识工作者。我们发现，数字疲惫感取决于员工是否觉得自己有自主权来决定使用哪些工具。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的结论是什么？当人们意识到他们无法做太多或任何事情来减少他们使用的协作工具的数量（或者他们使用这些工具的时间和频率）时，他们会感到更加无助和疲惫。正如一位软件工程师所说，“这在个人层面上确实很难改变。”他接着解释说，如果他决定不使用其他同事使用的工具，他和他的合作者就会更难完成他们的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;变革需要来自高层&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;变革需要来自高层&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; h2>; &lt;p>;许多研究表明，组织中有效且持久的变革是从底层冒出来的，管理层的强烈格言&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/youre-going-digital -now-what/&quot;>;会给员工制造障碍&lt;/a>;。我们&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.macmillan.com/books/9781250284426/thefrictionproject&quot;>;引用了&lt;/a>;大部分研究&lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product /the-digital-mindset-what-it-it-it-real-takes-to-thrive-thrive-in-the-age-of-data-algorithms-and-ai/10413&quot;>;在我们自己的工作中&lt;/a>;，以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/youre-going-digital-now-what/&quot;>;甚至也产生了相当多的内容&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是当谈到技术过载和数字枯竭，减少问题的最佳方法（有时是唯一方法）是强有力的、持久的、甚至完全不灵活的自上而下的干预。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的合作清理结果表明，协作技术的交互性和相互依存性使得员工个人几乎不可能自行有意义地减少在工作场所使用工具。正如我们研究的参与者所明确的那样，尝试或未能改变他们使用数字工具的方式和时间可能比根本不尝试更糟糕。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;较低级别的员工通常拥有有关哪些工具的最佳信息保留哪些，消除哪些。但那些处于最高地位的人最有能力利用自己的权力在整个组织中进行变革，并帮助员工在数字洪流中生存。以下是领导者如何帮助员工更好地掌握协作工具的方法：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;提供有目的的约束。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;为员工何时应使用特定技术制定明确的指导方针。这将有助于防止他们花费时间和精力来事后猜测使用哪种技术来完成什么类型​​的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建立不容谈判的条件。例如，与我们合作的一个组织的领导者明确指出，Slack 应该用于时间敏感且需要快速响应的沟通，而不是用于不太紧迫的事务。其他组织的领导者已完全禁止电子邮件，或决定仅使用一种项目管理工具。这里的关键是具体和严格：不要让太多工具扰乱人们的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;解决根本原因和连锁反应。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为领导者，至关重要的是面对技术过载的明显症状和根本原因。开始对组织的工具堆栈进行自上而下的修剪，消除冗余和低效的技术。一位参与清理工作的数据科学家描述了他的公司领导如何取消了冗余文件共享平台的员工许可证，这帮助他和其他人在处理文档时坚持使用单一平台，而不是被迫在不同平台之间不断切换。每个都需要不同的步骤和命令。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您还有责任帮助您的团队减轻工具过载的连锁反应。鼓励员工使用“请勿打扰”等功能并关闭不必要的通知，以重新控制自己的注意力。但如果您不以身作则，您的员工也不太可能这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;正面解决摩擦。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;鼓励、支持甚至要求员工定期评估他们的技术习惯。我们的清理表明，这种有意识的反思可以让您的员工更加意识到技术过载的代价。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://us.macmillan.com/books/9781250249869/subtract&quot;>;减法思维&lt;/a>;可以成为变革的强大催化剂，促使员工停下来并批判性地评估其技术对企业的影响。他们的生产力和幸福感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，我们的干预还表明，如果员工感到无力做出改变，这种意识的增强可能会导致数字疲惫感加剧。作为领导者，您的工作不仅是促进这种有意识的反思，而且还提供支持和资源，以便员工能够改变他们的技术使用。这可能涉及促进团队内关于技术习惯的讨论，提供有关如何更有效地使用协作工具的培训，或者利用您的权力根据员工反馈改进组织的技术堆栈。准备好坚持到底并让自己承担责任，以确保提高对工具过载的认识会带来积极的变化，而不是增加绝望。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;小心信用卡方法。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这对于经理们只需向公司信用卡收取少量月费，即可为其团队购买数字平台订阅服务，而无需通知 IT 部门。许多科技公司设计了定价策略，以便管理人员可以进行这些采购，而无需经过漫长的公司审批流程。尽管许多经理采用这种方法是因为他们认为这有助于他们的团队快速采用最好的技术，但缺乏摩擦会导致每个成员自己的技术堆栈膨胀，并可能导致更多的数字疲惫感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;经理需要更加意识到他们向员工介绍了多少工具，以及他们一旦开始使用工具就很难停止使用。在我们合作的一家中型公司中，首席技术官指示会计团队在公司卡上标记所有向软件供应商进行的购买。每个未经 IT 授权的订阅均被取消。如果经理想要恢复它，他们必须以书面形式向 CTO 提出正式请求。当然，这是一种艰难的自上而下的方法。但在要求管理者不要用工具压垮团队一年之后，首席技术官最终迫使人们解决问题，而不仅仅是做出空洞的承诺。大规模取消后六个月，该公司使用的工具减少了近 30 个。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;协作技术超载会使员工陷入选择之中，让他们感到无助。具有讽刺意味的是，通过限制这些选择，为采用另一种协作技术增加令人沮丧的障碍，并从个人手中夺走控制权，员工会感觉更好地控制自己的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>;分区>; &lt;/分区>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Prepare for a GenAI Future You Can&rsquo;t Predict]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-to-prepare-for-a-genai-future-you-cant-predict]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_31_1500235907.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;鉴于生成式 AI 发展的惊人速度，难怪如此多的高管被 AI 的可能性所吸引，担心寻找并留住合格的员工，并因最近的市场调整或未达到分析师预期而感到沮丧。他们设想未来的工作方式将不再像今天一样多。但这是一个误判。领导者担心错过下一波技术浪潮，这是可以理解的，他们在不知不觉中对公司的业务进行了冒险的押注。期货。以下是每个领导者应该采取的步骤，为一个不确定的世界做好准备，在这个世界中，生成型人工智能和人类劳动力共存，但将以不可知的方式演变。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div >; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-to-prepare-for-a-genai-future-you-cant-predict?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-to-prepare-for-a-genai-future-you-cant-predict?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;最近，一家知名银行的首席执行官打电话给我，讨论生成式人工智能的前景。我们最初通过各种场景来改善欺诈检测和客户服务，但随着最近不断发布的公告，很明显他心中有更宏伟的抱负。与许多行业一样，银行业也存在劳动力问题：对技术人员的需求与愿意返回办公室并遵守新冠疫情前规则的工人的供给之间存在差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生成式人工智能他想，这可能是一种灵丹妙药。它可以通过自动化节省成本并提高效率，但这些新工具是否也能解决人才短缺问题？简单地说：人工智能多久才能取代人类工人？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的对话与我自去年 11 月以来与一系列企业的高管进行的对话相呼应，包括保险、制造、制药，甚至是领导层的高管好莱坞电影公司的编剧和演员目前正在罢工。他们都想知道他们的公司如何利用更少的人力资源创造更多的价值。那是因为去年秋天，OpenAI 开发的聊天机器人 ChatGPT&lt;a href=&quot;https://openai.com/blog/chatgpt&quot;>;突然走红&lt;/a>;，展示了 AI 生成自己电子邮件的能力，论文、食谱、财务报告、文章和想法。高盛&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/generative-ai-could-raise-global-gdp-by-7-percent.html&quot;>;估计&lt;/a>;十年内，3 亿个工作岗位将被生成型人工智能消除或大幅减少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们已经开始看到动荡。 “即时工程师”（要求 ChatGPT 等系统生成内容的人员）的招聘信息是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-prompt-engineer-jobs-pay-salary-requirements-no- tech-background-2023-3&quot;>;提供 30 万美元或以上的年薪&lt;/a>;。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4389233&quot;>;OpenAI 的 GPT-4 通过了统一律师考试&lt;/a>;并暗示在不久的将来，我们可能不会需要律师进行交易工作。事实上，沃尔玛&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230111005148/en/Pactum%E2%80%99s-Autonomous-Negotiation-Technology-on-Display-at-the-National -Retail-Federation%E2%80%99s-2023-Retail-Big-Show&quot;>;对生成式 AI 系统（与 OpenAI 无关）进行原型设计&lt;/a>;，以协商其部分供应商合同； &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pymnts.com/news/artificial-intelligence/2023/walmart-finds-75-percent-vendors-prefer-negotiating-with-chatbot/&quot;>;75% 的合同律师和采购另一方的官员表示，他们现在更喜欢与人工智能谈判，而不是与有血有肉的对手谈判。 Google 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/healthcare-life-sciences/sharing-google-med-palm-2-medical-large-language-model&quot;>;Med-PaLM 2&lt; /a>; 是一个经过医学知识训练的专门模型，现在可以以医生的专家水平回答医学考试问题。今年夏天，合作伙伴将开始测试可以查看 X 射线并自动编写乳房 X 光检查报告的应用程序，而无需人类医生参与。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着发展速度惊人，难怪如此许多高管都得出了同样的结论：在短短几年内，强大的人工智能系统将执行与人类劳动力相​​同（甚至更高）水平的认知工作。受到人工智能的可能性的诱惑，担心寻找和留住合格的员工，并因最近的市场调整或未达到分析师预期而感到沮丧，企业领导者设想了一个没有像今天那么多人的未来工作方式。从我的角度来看，这是一个巨大的误判。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，现在预测人工智能的确切未来还为时过早 - 特别是考虑到生成式人工智能只是一个具有许多相互依赖关系的领域中的一个很小的领域，每个领域都具有不同的相互依赖关系。发展阶段。人工智能到底会消除哪些工作以及何时消除，目前还只是猜测。人工智能系统仅仅执行任务是不够的；输出必须被证明是值得信赖的，集成到现有的工作流程中，并针对合规性、风险和监管问题进行管理。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，在技术带来的快速颠覆时期，领导者过于狭隘地关注眼前的问题收益，而不是其价值网络未来如何转变。随着人工智能的发展，它将需要对整个业务领域进行实时重新构想，但在我们充分了解未来会是什么样子之前。还记得公共互联网和网络浏览器的早期被视为娱乐吗？没有人计划过两者都会引发的根本性转变。那时不可能预测它有一天会如何影响总统选举或创建世界上第一家价值数万亿美元的公司。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可以肯定的是，今天的高管必须在我所见过的最复杂的运营环境中做出决策。从早期的互联网时代就可以看到。领导者担心错过下一波技术浪潮，这是可以理解的，他们在不知不觉中对公司的未来做出了冒险的赌注。以下是每个领导者应该采取的步骤，为一个不确定的世界做好准备，在这个世界中，生成式人工智能和人类劳动力共存，但将以不可知的方式发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;为无法预测的未来做好准备&lt;/h2>; &lt;这是一个悖论：我们需要认为劳动力是随着生成人工智能而发展的，而不是被生成人工智能所取代。劳动力需要不断发展，工人们必须在几年内迭代地学习新技能。领导者必须采用一种新方法来最大限度地发挥组织中人工智能的潜力，这需要以不同的方式跟踪人工智能的关键发展，使用迭代过程来培养准备好的劳动力，最重要的是，创建有证据支持的未来场景，挑战内部的传统思维组织。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;领导者现在可以做些什么来度过这个时期？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;首先，调整对生成式人工智能可以和将为您的业务带来什么的期望。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;从历史上看，人工智能会经历一些阶段，包括突破、资金激增和主流兴趣转瞬即逝，然后是未达到预期和资金收回。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;1970 年，马文·明斯基 (Marvin Minsky)，一位有影响力的计算机科学家，也是创始人之一AI 的父母，&lt;a href=&quot;https://aiws.net/the-history-of-ai/this-week-in-the-history-of-ai-at-aiws-net-marvin-minsky-was -引用《生活杂志》中的话，“三到八年内我们将拥有一台具有普通人类一般智力的机器b/” >;告诉&lt;/a>;《生活》杂志，通用人工智能——一种具有与人类无法区分的认知能力的人工智能——距离我们只有三年的时间了。请记住，在 20 世纪 70 年代，这种人工智能所需的计算能力还不存在。超级计算机大多是理论上的。个人电脑也是如此。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://r5.ieee.org/houston/ieee-stepping-stone-award-datapoint-2200-the-first-personal-computer/&quot;>;Datapoint 2200&lt;/a>; 及其处理器最终成为我们后来所知的 PC 的基础架构。明斯基和他的同事许诺的宏伟抱负从未实现，因此资金和兴趣枯竭。这种情况在 1987 年再次发生，当时计算机科学家和企业再次对人工智能的时间表做出了大胆的承诺，但这是不可能实现的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然功能强大，但当今主流的生成式人工智能工具 — ChatGPT、Midjourney、DALL-E 2 — 不是成品。很快，人们就会对自己的新鲜感感到厌烦，并意识到虽然人工智能可以创造内容，但它还不足以实际使用。同样，对于医学、气候和生命科学领域特定的人工智能工具来说，现在还处于早期阶段。为了让生成式人工智能以大规模且具有成本效益的方式创造我们所承诺的奇迹，我们还需要做更多的工作。请记住，直到最近，这些工具大多只是理论上的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;高管们需要清楚生成式人工智能将在当今的组织中执行的实际功能。他们还应该务实地对待生成式人工智能最终将带来的机遇和风险。人工智能并不是一个庞然大物，我们正处于一个漫长发展轨迹的开端。这听起来可能很直观，但根据我的观察，很少有领导者能够制定切实可行的战略，将今天的运营与明天的愿景联系起来，在管理团队中进行交流，并相应地修改他们的绩效指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最近，我遇到了一家跨国消费品 (CPG) 公司的高管领导层渴望与一家生成式人工智能公司合作。我向他们介绍了一个高概率的场景，其中客户使用聊天工具回答了一些有关他们的偏好和目标的问题，然后在线购物车自动填充了他们本周需要的物品。但 CPG 的品牌都没有出现在购物车中，或者即使出现了，也没有出现在列表中的第一位。正如谷歌和亚马逊等搜索引擎发明了搜索引擎优化的新机制和规则一样，未来，跨零售商和购物车应用程序等平台的生成式人工智能集成将为消费品公司带来新的挑战，这些公司可能会发现自己在价值链的下游更加深入。做出关键决策的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;其次，评估您的公司正在生成哪些数据以及生成式人工智能在今天和将来如何使用这些数据。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;业务数据非常宝贵因为一旦模型经过训练，将这些数据移植到另一个系统可能成本高昂，技术上也很麻烦。目前，新兴的人工智能平台不易实现互操作，这是设计使然。生成式人工智能平台正在演变成围墙花园，创造技术的公司控制着其生态系统的各个方面。最大的人工智能公司正在争夺市场份额，以及他们需要的大量数据，以使他们的模型最具竞争力。通过向公司推销他们的平台，他们希望锁定这些平台（及其数据）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当今的人工智能系统是使用一种称为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://huggingface.co/ 的技术创建的blog/rlhf&quot;>;&lt;em>;利用人类反馈进行强化学习&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，或 RHLF。从本质上讲，人工智能系统需要持续的人类反馈，否则它们就会面临学习和记住错误信息的风险。获取的数据越多，需要的注释、标签和培训就越多。如今，肯尼亚和巴基斯坦等新兴经济体的零工工人的这项工作已经自动化。随着人工智能的成熟，将需要具有专家级知识的专家。我见过的许多企业领导者并没有规划一个包含内部 RHLF 部门的未来，该部门的任务是持续监控、审计和调整人工智能系统和工具。 （任何领导者最不希望看到的就是一个无人监督的人工智能系统做出关于如何改进自身的决策。）&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;即使有训练有素的人员参与其中，企业也必须不断设计场景，以暴露与生成式人工智能一起工作的风险系统，尤其是由第三方运营的系统。这是因为人工智能系统不是静态的；随着时间的推移，他们正在逐步改进。每一个新的发展都会带来新的潜在风险和机遇。如果这些预测不会很快过时，就不可能提前排除所有潜在的负面结果。 （目前，还没有办法建立一个完全准确的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techtarget.com/searchcloudcomputing/definition/Monte-Carlo-simulation&quot;>;蒙特卡洛模拟&lt;/a>;预测未来。）相反，一个专门的团队应该负责监控正在学习的生成式人工智能系统以及相关的网络安全挑战，并且他们应该开发简短的“假设”场景，想象事情可能出错的方式。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;同样，随着人工智能的发展，释放新增长的机会也会随之发展。这意味着企业还应该拥有一支专门的内部业务开发团队，为新兴工具提高生产力和效率、促进产品开发、刺激创新等的多种方式开发近期和长期场景。&lt;/ p>; &lt;h3>;第三，在人工智能方面，领导者必须将注意力从底线转移到顶线。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这似乎违反直觉，因为许多人将生成式人工智能视为降低运营成本的一种手段。今天的智能聊天机器人很快就会被多模式系统所取代，多模式系统是能够同时解决不同问题并实现不同目标的人工智能。想象一下一家财产和意外伤害保险公司，每个承保人都与人工智能合作。最初，承保人可能会要求人工智能评估与财产保险相关的风险；在对文本进行初步分析后，她可能会要求使用检查报告中的图像或对潜在保单持有人的音频采访来完善结果。她可能会使用不同的数据源来回几次，直到收到保险公司和客户的最佳报价。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;高效利用多模式人工智能的关键是了解如何以及如何使用将什么委托给机器，以便人类和人工智能都可以通过协作而不是独立工作来完成更多工作。然而，授权是专业人士经常遇到的问题：他们要么分配太多，要么分配不够，要么分配不正确的任务。与多模式人工智能一起工作需要员工掌握授权的艺术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦员工了解如何正确授权，它将成为组织内的力量倍增器。各个团队可以更加雄心勃勃地通过构思和模拟新的收入来源、寻找和获取新客户以及寻求对公司整体运营的各种改进来增加公司的营收。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这预示着一个需要的未来一种不同的技能提升方法。大多数员工不需要学习如何编码，或如何编写基本提示，正如我们在会议上经常听到的那样。相反，他们需要学习如何利用多模式人工智能来做更多、更好的工作。只需看看 Excel，每天就有 7.5 亿知识工作者&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/10/10-excel-functions-everyone-should-know&quot;>;使用&lt;/a>;它。该软件包含 500 多个功能，但绝大多数人只使用几十个功能，因为他们不完全了解如何将 Excel 提供的大量功能与他们的日常认知任务相匹配。现在，想象一下人工智能——一种更复杂、更复杂的软件——无处不在的未来。仅仅因为企业领导者对技能提升的关注范围太窄，将会留下多少效用？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;引导不断发展的人工智能劳动力的框架&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;劳动力变化是技术发展不可避免的副作用，领导者需要一种系统化的方式来了解随着生成式人工智能的发展，他们的组织的未来会是什么样子。为此，这个简单的框架将帮助任何组织的领导者预测他们的员工队伍需要如何以及何时改变才能利用人工智能。目标不是做出长期预测，甚至不是为一切做好准备 - 而是让组织为人工智能的不断改进做好准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-desiredby =&quot;caption-attachment-363183&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230728_WEBB_IDEA_FRAMEWORK_360.png&quot;>;&quot; title=&quot;IDEA 框架。&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;620&quot;>; &lt;/figure >; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和视觉中的更多 HBR 图表&lt;i>;&lt; /i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;该框架应用于开发企业未来的场景。它旨在帮助您尽早发现风险和机遇，定期使用该框架，使领导者能够更清楚地了解情况，评估组织内的差距，并将新兴技术与现有战略联系起来，使他们能够自信地做出决策。重要的是，它要求领导者以指数方式思考人工智能，但逐步采取行动以应对新的发展。虽然它无法预测您的公司的独特未来（没有任何场景可以做到这一点），但它将帮助领导者做好准备，领先于竞争对手做出决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织现在可以做的最好的事情——在这个充满巨大变化和不确定性的时期——有条不紊地规划未来。这需要了解生成式人工智能的局限性和优势，并采取持续评估和改进的文化。它还意味着从巧妙的产品演示转向更平凡、更务实的对话，讨论开发轨迹、数据如何使用以及公司使用新兴工具的实际方式。抵制住裁员的诱惑，而是利用战略远见来创造一个未来，让高技能的劳动力充分利用人工智能，并且人类与人工智能团队一起工作比单独工作更有生产力、创造力和效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Global Companies Can Create a Consistent Customer Experience]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-global-companies-can-create-a-consistent-customer-experience]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_30_3850269.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yaroslav Danylchenko/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Building a global company is easier, but also more nuanced and complex, than ever before. In the past, companies could limit expansion in a more controlled fashion to just one market at a time. In the digital age, global growth is far more continuous and incremental in nature. But with this new approach comes risk: If your customers in one market receive less value than those in another, they perceive your offering differently. This is not only unfair to them, but it can also hurt your business in the long run. To truly create an equitable experience for your customers, you will need to focus as early as possible on driving a GLOBE mindset, one that&amp;#8217;s geography-agnostic, linguistically inclusive, operationalized, balanced, and empathetic.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-global-companies-can-create-a-consistent-customer-experience?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-global-companies-can-create-a-consistent-customer-experience?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;On the surface, international business expansion seems easier than ever. Today, any company can reach multiple markets in a matter of seconds: Publish a blog post, launch a mobile app, buy digital ads, and target customers in as many countries as you wish. The rise of online global marketplaces has made it even easier for companies to launch into multiple countries simultaneously, often from their earliest days. This has given rise to a wave of “global native” companies that have an international presence from day one.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When Ian Harkin founded Lottie, a toy company based in Donegal, Ireland that manufactures Barbie doll alternatives with a child&#39;s dimensions instead of an adult&#39;s, he began with international markets in mind from the very start. “In the toy industry, with very high up-front development costs, it&#39;s difficult to justify the expense to launch in just one country,” he explains. Harkin, the company&#39;s CEO, integrated their storefront into Amazon, and immediately reached customers in the United States, Canada, Mexico, Germany, France, Italy, Spain, Holland, Sweden, and Poland. Nearly 100% of the company&#39;s revenue today comes from outside of Ireland. Harkin points out, “For us, going global early helped our product and brand reach more potential customers, much faster, than if we would have expanded one country at a time.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This growing phenomenon of going global as early as possible in the life of a business isn&#39;t only happening with physical products that can launch via global platforms like Amazon or Etsy. Partners at Andreessen Horowitz have written about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://a16z.com/2022/07/20/the-company-of-the-future-is-default-global/&quot;>;new wave of “default global” companies&lt;/a>;, which radically compress the timeframe it takes to go global. They contrast these with “default local” firms, which often take five years before operating in just a few foreign markets. The default global companies are often in double the number of markets as default local companies are by year three. In addition, &lt;a href=&quot;https://stripe.com/newsroom/stories/global-natives&quot;>;research from Stripe&lt;/a>; shows that 89% of successful tech companies had expanded internationally prior to achieving “unicorn” status, a valuation of $1 billion or higher.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But building a global company is also more nuanced and complex than ever before. In the past, companies could limit expansion in a more controlled fashion to just one market at a time. In the digital age, global growth is far more continuous and incremental in nature. But with this new approach comes risk: If your customers in one market receive less value than those in another, they perceive your offering differently. This is not only unfair to them, but it can also hurt your business in the long run.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For this reason, even if you&#39;re already having success as a global company, it&#39;s time to raise the bar. To sustain your success for the long term, you&#39;ll need to build not just a company that has customers or revenue streams from many different countries, but one that operates as a globally equitable organization (GEO for shorthand).&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Rise of the Globally Equitable Organization &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When I ran international expansion efforts for HubSpot, a large public tech company, over the space of nearly eight years, I noticed this pronounced shift toward continuous expansion happening before my eyes. But I also observed another important trend at play in the broader market. In the past, companies that sought to expand internationally measured their success strictly using qualitative measures, usually in the form of revenue or customer count from new markets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today, with global becoming the new default, the goal is no longer as simple as just increasing revenue share from between different parts of the world. Instead, the new measure is more customer-oriented in nature. Companies have realized that it&#39;s not enough to initially acquire new customers in other geographies — retaining them is critical, as this ensures that revenue can be sustained. The best global companies ask themselves: How successful can our local customers be with our business in each market, without geography getting in the way?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take Teamwork, a project management software company headquartered in Cork, Ireland. “You can sell software from anywhere in the world from the get-go. There are no boundaries,” explains Peter Coppinger, Teamwork CEO and co-founder. “One of the biggest lessons we learned with Teamwork&#39;s international expansion is that once you reach a certain scale, you need to get more deliberate about targeting the regions with the most potential.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the company deepened its presence in specific markets, Coppinger and team found that they needed to ramp up sales and customer talent in order to support customers in new time zones. “There is no substitute for having staff in the same time zone speaking the same language as your target customer,” he points out. When Teamwork recognized some customers were feeling this pain, they were proactive about creating a more equitable experience for all customers. Today, the company has 20,000 customers in 170 countries, and a global workforce of 350 employees in 15 countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Make Local Customer Experiences Equitable, Not Identical &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the digital age, it&#39;s easy to go global without adapting the customer experience. But if companies fail to make sufficient adaptations, they miss the chance to build true connections of value with their customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Making local experiences equitable doesn&#39;t mean they have to be identical. In fact, where many companies go wrong is that they try to enforce a cookie-cutter approach onto all markets, in the name of “global leverage.” But in doing so, they miss out on the importance of local adaptations that ensure their customers across markets are equally happy with the value they&#39;re receiving, even if they define and derive that value in different ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a shining example, look no further than Starbucks. At the product level, customers can order many of the same standard menu items in every location globally. But to appeal to local tastes, a customer in Peru, where the Lúcuma fruit grows, can order a Lúcuma Crème Frappuccino from their local barista. Starbucks adapts not only their physical products, but their digital outreach to customers too. They achieve global consistency offline as well as online, but the company customizes their digital marketing campaigns in each country tied to the seasons, holidays, and local traditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The table below offers some examples of adaptations a company might make in order to ensure it is providing an equitable experience to customers in a new market:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- table start -- Ensuring a Globally Equitable Experience -- -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;h4>;Ensuring a Globally Equitable Experience&lt;/h4>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;The table below offers some examples of adaptations a company might make in order to ensure it&#39;s providing an equitable customer experience as it enters new markets around the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot;>; &lt;thead>; &lt;tr>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;Customer experience area&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;Current home market approach&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;Initial local market approach&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;Why it&#39;s globally equitable&lt;/th>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;/thead>; &lt;tbody>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Customer experience area&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;MARKETING&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Current home market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A large website that has built up over the years with large amounts of content&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Initial local market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A microsite with just the core content that enables customers to understand the parts of your offering that matter most to them&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Why it&#39;s globally equitable&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;You didn&#39;t create such a large website for your home market overnight, so you don&#39;t need to localize all of it. Start small in your local market and focus on their unique needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Customer experience area&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;SALES&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Current home market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A large inside-sales team that sells directly to customers&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Initial local market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A local partner that resells and implements your products&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Why it&#39;s globally equitable&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;In a local market you can&#39;t recreate the trust you&#39;ve built up in your home market over many years. Going in with an already-trusted brand makes more sense.&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Customer experience area&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PRODUCT&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Current home market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A fully featured product offering with numerous tiers, bundling options, and pricing add-ons&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Initial local market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A lightweight version of your product without features that won&#39;t work in the local market, offered for a single, lower price point&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Why it&#39;s globally equitable&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;Your business mix is more complex in your home market than in a new local one. It&#39;s often better to customize than to sell things that they don&#39;t need or can&#39;t use.&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Customer experience area&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;SUPPORT&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Current home market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;An in-app support tool that offers automated support via a chatbot with the option to reach a human 24/7&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Initial local market approach&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;A local phone number that routes to a local human rep, only during local business hours&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;Why it&#39;s globally equitable&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;It might be logistically easier to launch in the local market with human support reps than to localize your chatbot, and you can build greater brand trust with humans initially. The cost of human talent is typically lower in the new market anyway.&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;/tbody>; &lt;/table>; &lt;div>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>; &lt;!-- Source: goes here -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- table end -- Ensuring a Globally Equitable Experience -- -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The temptation at most global companies, especially ones with digital and software products, is to always do the same thing, all at once, in every market. While this is a natural inclination, it actually can have the opposite effect and require investments that are disproportional for each local market. Instead of doing “all things in all markets,” be selective and show a true willingness to adapt. Encourage your employees to flex their creative muscles when thinking about what strategy will work best for a new local market so that they can derive equal value, even if the approaches vary.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Ensure Your Organization Has a Globally Equitable Mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To truly create an equitable experience for your customers, you will need to focus as early as possible on driving what I call a GLOBE mindset, one that&#39;s geography-agnostic, linguistically inclusive, operationalized, balanced, and empathetic. This will ensure that all of your employees — not just those with “international” in their titles — keep the global equity momentum going in perpetuity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re launching a new global initiative at your company, I recommend asking these five questions to ensure your approach is equitable:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Geography-agnostic:&lt;/strong>; Is this project designed around the needs of customers in one market, or is it inclusive of multiple geographies?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Linguistically inclusive:&lt;/strong>; Have we considered the language and literacy needs of customers in the local markets we serve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Operationalized: &lt;/strong>;Have we accounted for local differences with our plans, so we can prevent friction for local teams when it&#39;s time to execute?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Balanced:&lt;/strong>; Are our resources, especially funding and headcount, aligned to support our priority markets?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Empathetic:&lt;/strong>; Have we talked with customers and/or leaders of our local markets to ensure we are truly taking their needs into consideration?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;If you get into the habit of putting these five simple principles at the center of your leadership team&#39;s mindset, you&#39;ll naturally be driving equitable experiences for your customers around the globe.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today, international expansion is more ongoing in nature, with a constant pace of change. The more you focus on driving up value across all markets in an equitable way, the greater the financial success that will follow — but only as a consequence of taking a new approach, one that places value on delivering equitable experiences to your local customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:55:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Customers Leave Platforms &mdash; and How to Retain Them]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/why-customers-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Aug23_30_663665217.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies often misunderstand the problem of users leaving their platforms. Disintermediation is a sign that your customers don&amp;#8217;t think you are adding as much value as you think you are. Firms struggling with disintermediation can take simple steps to stop the bleeding before it&amp;#8217;s too late &amp;#8212; if they understand what&amp;#8217;s really taking place. They should consider six factors: urgency, rake, risk, skill, frequency, and modularity. The solution for disintermediation is quite simple: Create more value than you take. Stop playing the role of toll-taking gatekeeper and start playing the role of value-adding partner.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why-customers-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why-customers-leave-platforms-and-how-to-retain-them?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Platform firms — businesses that enable transactions between two parties — constantly struggle to prevent those partners from taking their deals off-platform. The technical term for this is “disintermediation,” and examples of it include readers buying online rather than from bookstores, Upwork and ZBJ (China&#39;s Zhu Bajie) programmers contracting directly with clients, and Airbnb struggling not only with guests contracting directly with hosts, but also with some of its biggest professional hosts &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airbnb-stock-falls-after-short-report-says-hosts-directly-compete-with-platform-173546532.html&quot;>;reportedly competing against it on new platforms&lt;/a>;. Disintermediation — and the failure to understand and address it — killed once thriving businesses like Borders books, Blockbuster movies, and Tower records. It&#39;s easy to understand why platform companies worry so much about being cut out of the loop.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s the thing, though: True disintermediation is rare. Most buyers and sellers don&#39;t cut out the middleman entirely, but rather find a new provider that cuts transaction costs or adds more value so that switching is a natural choice. Readers buy from Amazon, not authors directly. Movie watchers and song listeners don&#39;t buy from Hollywood studios or musicians but from Netflix and Spotify. Simply put, these are not atomic markets of many-to-many interactions. New centers of attraction (Amazon, Netflix, and Spotify) have re-intermediated the old ones (Borders, Blockbuster, and Tower).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The issue is that companies often misunderstand the problem: Disintermediation is a sign that your customers don&#39;t think you are adding as much value as you think you are. Just because you enabled the first transaction doesn&#39;t mean you&#39;re entitled to take all the value from the second, the third, and subsequent transactions. The good news, however, is that firms that appear to be struggling with disintermediation can take simple steps to stop the bleeding before it&#39;s too late — if they understand what&#39;s really taking place.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Predicting disintermediation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;How can a firm know when deals are sticky and when they will go somewhere else? At least six factors contribute to partners taking deals off your platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, &lt;em>;urgency&lt;/em>; reflects the need to solve a problem now, which helps keep the deal. A large platform that can address a need quickly is more valuable when urgency is high, in contrast to a single off-platform source that is high-quality but unavailable. For instance, the delivery app Drizzly provides on-demand alcohol for parties. A trip to the liquor store might cost less, but it requires advance planning or someone stepping out mid-party.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Rake&lt;/em>; is what a platform charges for facilitating a deal. The higher this fee, the more partners want to avoid it. Groupon&#39;s rake of nearly 50% &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholars.cityu.edu.hk/en/publications/how-users-drive-value-in-twosided-markets(94885ed2-0e38-40e4-9388-35008ffcc834).html&quot;>;contributed to its plunge and plateau in stock value&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Risk&lt;/em>; is the danger that a deal goes badly. If a project is risky, then both buyers and suppliers prefer having the benefit of reputation systems, insurance, and mediation services the platform provides. Uber covers driver costs and holds riders accountable if riders throw up in the car.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Skill&lt;/em>; is the level of expertise required to perform the task. For low-skill jobs, the main issue is usually price, and a large pool of suppliers helps customers secure the best deal. That means platforms offer the best value for both the first and subsequent deals, as with E-Trade for example. But when a job requires high skill, platforms often only add value to the first deal, where the benefits of reputation systems truly matter. After that, buyers can cut out gatekeepers once they find a reliable supplier. For instance, Rocket Lawyer connects people with expert attorneys to help with legal issues. But once someone has found a reliable attorney, they no longer need the platform. And, they don&#39;t want to explain their situation all over again.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Subsequent deals highlight related factors, &lt;em>;interaction frequency&lt;/em>;, or how often partners must communicate to complete the task, and &lt;em>;project modularity&lt;/em>;, or the degree to which a task can be divided into smaller, independent components. If a task requires repeated communication or it can be broken easily into separate parts, then buyers and sellers have multiple opportunities to &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4150094&quot;>;establish a relationship independent of the platform&lt;/a>;. On Upwork, for example, working through stages of website deployment — specification, design, coding, backend, test, etc. — gives parties a chance to reduce the rake on each stage. Then later stages can happen off-platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-363193&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230728_VAN_ALSTYNE_DISINTERMEDIATION_FACTORS_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Broadly speaking, these six factors tell companies how to reduce the costs of &lt;em>;search&lt;/em>;, &lt;em>;negotiation&lt;/em>;, &lt;em>;risk&lt;/em>;, or &lt;em>;delivery&lt;/em>; associated with getting the deal to happen as distinct from producing the work itself. In economic terms, these are known as “transaction costs.” The platform&#39;s role is to lower them compared to the next best alternative. Understanding this principle gives executives control over the outcome even if the superficial attributes change. The platform helps orchestrate the deal, but the supplier actually produces the result, and if the buyer and supplier can handle the transaction costs more efficiently without the platform, then they will disintermediate the deal. Interestingly, the Chief Strategy Officer for Alibaba even defined a test for successful platforms as achieving “the nexus of lowest transaction costs.” Understanding disintermediation in this way then gives you the tools to prevent it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Preventing disintermediation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The solution for disintermediation is quite simple: Create more value than you take. Stop playing the role of toll-taking gatekeeper and start playing the role of value-adding partner. Either decrease transaction costs or increase value for buyers or suppliers, or both.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Every platform interaction has a producer side and a consumer side. This is true regardless of whether the activity is a ride, a tweet, a stay, a product, a service, or a piece of art. The trick is to design appropriate carrots and sticks for both sides, with a heavy emphasis on carrots. Why are carrots better than sticks? Carrots &lt;em>;add value&lt;/em>; for keeping interactions on-platform, while sticks &lt;em>;add costs&lt;/em>; for taking interactions off-platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-363192&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230728_VAN_ALSTYNE_DISINTERMEDIATION_CARROTS_STICKS_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Many platforms choose sticks because they are easier to implement or because they feel entitled to a certain level of profit. Sticks, however, do not engender goodwill among customers, service providers, freelancers, or developers. They include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Hiding supplier contact information to prevent direct communication. For years, Angies List (now Angi) hid home service provider contact information, which limited interactions and growth.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Bounties paid to buyers and suppliers who rat on the other side for proposing disintermediation.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Secret shoppers and secret sellers who make such proposals to test partner loyalty. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbs.edu/faculty/Pages/item.aspx?num=53948&quot;>;ZBJ&lt;/a>; used both bounties and secret shoppers when freelancers did not want to share large commissions with the platform.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Deplatforming, public shaming, and eventually legal action, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/24/business/apple-epic-games-appeal.html&quot;>;Apple tried&lt;/a>; when Fortnite tried to use its own system to facilitate payments rather than use Apple&#39;s system with its exorbitant 30% tax.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Carrots are far better because they show a commitment to creating value, which is the only real basis for capturing value. They include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Giving users software tools to enhance the production, delivery, quality, or consumption of the product or service. Instagram and Vimeo offer filters and image editing tools that not only reduce costs for producers but also help them create value for consumers.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;A variant of this strategy is to offer value-adding services. The freelance platform Upwork will provide project management for large contracts by partitioning it and farming out components to different subcontractors. 99Designs, a design contest platform, helps designers automate their billing, track their progress, and pay their taxes.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Frequent buyer or frequent seller rewards. OpenTable gives buyers dining points that they can spend on restaurant meals, while CoachUp gives professional coaches volume discounts. Etsy rewards artists&#39; loyalty by showcasing their work.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Shifting monetization to the point where the platform adds the most value. ZBJ introduced an optional pricing model that shifts from a transaction fee to a subscription fee. Once the fee is paid for the first deal, suppliers&#39; costs for each new deal are zero. When further use of the platform is free, sellers prefer the benefits of automated tracking and billing that happens on-platform.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Insurance, which is one of the most successful benefits to both sellers and buyers. On the seller side, Airbnb insures hosts against fire, theft, and property damage. On the buyer side, Amazon offers free returns and money back guarantees.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Basic safety. Uber introduced a rider emergency help button that most taxis do not offer. When a freelance contract is based on an hourly rate, Upwork has provided monitoring software so that a client knows a programmer is coding and not perusing Facebook.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Introducing buyer and seller rating systems. Almost every major platform now uses some form of review to reduce the adverse selection of finding bad providers and the moral hazard that, having been paid, they might not deliver.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Ironically, these strategies do come with a challenge — a “disintermediation dilemma.” Strategies intended to add value can inadvertently lead to leakage. This occurs when tactics &lt;em>;do&lt;/em>; add value but only to the first interaction and not the second. Consider a five-star rating on a home cleaner or landscaper. Once contact is made and trust established, a platform that adds no further value will be disintermediated. This problem &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/01/why-some-platforms-thrive-and-others-dont&quot;>;doomed Homejoy&lt;/a>; within a few years of launch. Groupon, likewise, adds value to a first sale by providing group buying discounts for buyers and discovery for merchants. But then deals conclude off-platform at the merchant and its “leaky bucket” adds little value to later deals. Buyers just visit the merchants. By contrast, Meituan, a Chinese successor to Groupon, handles delivery through the platform, generates frequent buyer rewards, and helps merchants design new products and situate new stores. Increased volume increases benefits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Disintermediation is a signal. What it really tells you is that you don&#39;t provide enough value after an initial match. You&#39;re taking more than your fair share. Disintermediation simply means someone else provides more value than you do. Instead, if you create more value than you take, you will attract deals rather than repel them.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Arrange Your Meeting Schedule to Boost Your Energy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_29_1464685906.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/iStock/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Most meeting advice focuses on how to make meetings more effective or how to cut down on the number of meetings you have altogether. But what about how to schedule your meetings alongside other work tasks to best manage your productivity? New research explores this question and finds that many people commit two key errors in organizing their schedules: stacking too many meetings together on the same day or pairing intense meetings with other intense tasks. Both strategies can actually diminish your ability to recharge and replenish during the day, which can be a detriment to your work. Instead, this article offers new tips for how to balance work and meetings and suggests questions you can ask yourself when planning your day.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/arrange-your-meeting-schedule-to-boost-your-energy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Meetings remain a frequent challenge for most knowledge workers. While common advice and prior research often focuses on making meetings more effective or reducing the time we spend in them, there is another critical aspect rarely taken into account: the way we schedule and arrange our meetings on a daily basis. Scheduling can, however, aid or impede our energy and productivity at work, and thus warrants a closer look.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2023-61289-001&quot;>;our research&lt;/a>;, we investigate the impact of knowledge workers&#39; daily meeting scheduling, including how certain strategies may seem smart but can, in fact, unintentionally drain our own energy. Let&#39;s consider two examples.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taylor, a senior data specialist who leads a team of junior analysts, notices two meetings on his Thursday calendar — one with a vendor liaison and another with senior specialists from other departments. Then he realizes that he also needs to arrange some check-ins with his junior analysts. Should he squeeze in those extra meetings on Thursday alongside the existing two, or should he schedule them for Friday instead? He is tempted to stack the meetings on Thursday, so that he can save time and keep his Friday schedule “clean” to focus on his own portion of a project report.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In another context, Minli, a seasoned software engineer and manager of a development team, faces two upcoming meetings this week. On Tuesday, she is scheduled to present to the strategic committee, a critical meeting with potential budget implications. The next day, she is tasked with an orientation session for new interns — a familiar and relatively easy duty.除了这些会议之外，敏莉还必须解决她自己在两个项目上的技术工作：一个遇到了一些严峻的挑战，另一个几乎完成了，只需要一些最后的润色。她应该在周二处理困难的项目并在周三处理较容易的项目，还是扭转计划？敏莉倾向于第一种选择。通过在周二解决会议和个人工作中最艰巨的挑战，她预计本周剩余时间的压力会减轻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taylor 和 Minli 的方法很常见：压缩会议日程以节省时间，或者在同一天将重要会议与紧张的个人任务配对，以尽快完成它们。然而，我们的研究结果表明，这些策略有其自身的缺点，特别是考虑到它们对工作日精力的影响时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们进行了两项研究，跟踪了 400 多名全职知识分子的日常工作活动工人，一些来自科技公司，另一些来自涉及脑力工作的不同行业。在整个工作周中，我们在每个工作日的中间和结束时对员工进行调查，了解他们上午和下午的会议、个人任务和其他活动，以及每个半天结束时的精力水平。此外，我们还从他们的主管那里了解了他们的工作绩效，包括任务绩效和创造力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们有两个重要发现。首先，影响知识员工精力的并不是他们花在会议上的时间总量，而是会议时间与他们花在个人任务上的时间的相对比例。我们发现，在某一天，知识工作者花在与个人任务相关的会议上的时间越多，他们用于恢复精力的小型休息活动（例如短途散步、随意交谈、简短有趣的阅读）就越少在那一天。这种对于定期补充能量至关重要的休息活动的缺乏，会损害他们工作日的精力。精力受损反过来会对知识型员工的任务绩效、创造力和工作满意度产生负面影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，我们发现，如果结构合理，会议和个人任务可以创造出我们想要的东西。称之为工作日的“压力互补效应”。两种互补的配置——高压个人任务伴随低压会议，或者相反，低压个人任务伴随高压会议——可以有益于一个人的能量。例如，有一天，当一位数据专家轻松完成日常文书工作时，她可能会发现一场高风险的会议，会上她提出了一项充满活力的新举措；相反，当她忙于处理一份高压报告的时候，一场有关公司IT系统的低压更新会议可以为她的精力提供必要的喘息机会。我们发现，当知识工作者尚未被当天的需求消耗殆尽时，尤其是在上午而不是下午，这种互补效应最为明显。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些研究结果揭示了泰勒和敏利的日程安排方式这些方法可能会无意中削弱他们工作日的精力，但它们也揭示了潜在改进的途径。泰勒决定将会议安排在一天内，导致当天的会议和个人工作之间的时间严重不平衡，这可能会减少他对补充能量至关重要的短暂休息活动的参与。尽管旨在优化他的日程安排，但这种方法可能反而会导致能量耗尽和性能下降。在这两天中更加平衡地分配会议和个人任务可能会增强他的精力和效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;就敏莉的情况而言，她计划在周二处理一个困难的项目和一个重要的会议，这可能会造成过度的压力，而不会造成不必要的压力。足够的救济和恢复机会。相反，她的周三充满了低压会议和更轻松的项目，可能缺乏刺激。相反，如果敏丽可以在某一天将要求较高的个人任务与负担较轻的会议结合起来，另一天则相反，那么她就更有可能在这两天中保持精力充沛。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，当面临安排工作日的挑战时，尤其是在安排个人任务的同时安排会议时，请考虑以下事项：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;关注特定日期会议时间与个人工作时间的相对比例，而不仅仅是总时间会议和个人任务之间的合理平衡可以在整个工作日提供必要的休息和能量补充。这种方法不需要在一天中召开过多的会议，即使它有时看起来是一种节省时间的策略。管理每天的会议时间相对于个人工作的比例可以增强工作中的精力水平，从而有助于提高绩效、创造力和工作满意度。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;设计您的工作日，以在会议和个人之间创造互补&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;认识到将高压会议与低压个人任务配对的好处，反之亦然。不要将相同压力水平的活动集中到一个时期内，而是将具有挑战性的任务和会议分布在不同的日子或一天中的不同时间段。这种方法可以促进适当的压力互补，从而增强工作日的精力，从而实现更好的绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;采用更全面的方法来安排工作日。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;而不是简单地将会议或个人任务融入到工作中。为了方便使用日历，请考虑对您的工作日结构的更广泛影响。请注意日程安排决策可能会如何改变您工作日的安排模式，从而可能影响您的精力和生产力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下问题可能对您的计划过程有用：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li >;此安排决策将如何影响我在这一特定日期的会议和个人工作时间之间的平衡？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将此会议添加到一天中的此特定时段是否会过多压缩我的个人工作时间，从而牺牲必要的休息时间和补货？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;这样的日程安排会导致一天内连续召开高压会议和任务吗？如何避免这种情况？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;我的日程安排中是否有更好的时间来安排此会议或任务，以便更有效地混合全天的高压和低压工作？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;对于知识工作者来说，管理会议不仅仅是为了提高效率和时间效率；更是为了提高效率。它还要求对日常日程安排采取战略方法。这意味着考虑每日会议和个人任务，无论是时间分配还是它们会给你带来多少压力。注意这些方面可以帮助您避开微妙的日程安排陷阱，并防止您的精力和生产力意外消耗。事实上，通过采用更全面的会议安排方法，您可以改变您处理工作日的方式，从而对日常职责进行更加平衡和富有成效的安排。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[No, SCOTUS Did Not Make Your Company&rsquo;s DEI Programs Illegal]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_30hero.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p >;最有效的 DEI 方法也是控制法律风险的最佳方法：将 DEI 计划的重点放在消除通过基本业务系统不断传播的偏见上。这就是大多数企业 DEI 计划的运作方式，这些计划通常侧重于培训和调整组织系统以创造公平的竞争环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/08/no-scotus-did-not-make-your-companys-dei-programs-illegal?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;喧嚣正在进行中围绕最高法院最近推翻平权行动的决定，&lt;em>;学生公平招生诉哈佛&lt;/em>;。在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://aflegal.org/america-first-legal-puts-woke-corporations-law-firms-and-hospitals-on-notice-all-dei-programs-and-workplace-balancing -based-on-race-national-origin-and-sex-violate-the-law/&quot;>;博客文章&lt;/a>;，标题为“美国第一法律将唤醒公司......置于通知”，美国第一法律，一个由以下人领导的组织特朗普前顾问史蒂芬·米勒 (Stephen Miller) 断言，“所有 DEI 项目”现在都是“非法的”。米勒提供无偿法律帮助，反对“那些对我们同胞延续法西斯主义偏见的机构。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是政治，朋友们；这就是政治。不要将其误认为是法律。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在最基本的层面上，最高法院的判决解释了美国宪法的平等保护条款，该条款通常不适用于私人雇主。同样基本的是：基于种族的就业决定&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;根据联邦法规第七章已经是非法的&lt;/一个>;。这排除了为有色人种保留招聘或晋升名额以及利用种族作为决胜局等做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/ us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;九个州&lt;/a>;已经禁止基于种族的平权行动，通常是根据其州宪法。在我居住的加利福尼亚州，近 30 年前，209 号提案禁止在州立大学招生、州招聘和州合同方面基于种族采取平权行动。我从未听说过 209 号提案将私营公司的 DEI 计划定为非法的传闻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此评论认为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-06 -22/supreme-court-affirmative-action-ruling-jeopardizes-corporate-diversity-too#xj4y7vzkg&quot;>;“公司……[将]关闭所有 DEI 工作&lt;/a>;”和 &lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-07-06/yes-the-supreme-court-s-affirmative-action-ruling-really-does-affect-employers#xj4y7vzkg&quot;>;“企业多元化努力[ ] 陷入法律麻烦”&lt;/a>; 似乎有点歇斯底里。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司 DEI 计划受到牵连的唯一原因是尼尔·戈萨奇法官的同意意见中的几句话，只有克拉伦斯法官加入了该意见托马斯.戈萨奇的同意远远超出了本案所涉及的问题。它简要讨论了禁止就业中种族和性别歧视的联邦法规，向未来的原告表明他欢迎未来针对雇主的诉讼。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，我们开始讨论戈萨奇法官是否可能会这样做能够在未来组建最高法院多数派——特别是因为美国第一法律公司等资金雄厚的保守派非营利组织已承诺未来提起诉讼。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实上，人力资源咨询公司 Workforce 21C 的辛西娅·托马斯·卡尔弗特 (Cynthia Thomas Calvert)指出，“在最高法院做出裁决之前，白人雇员提出的‘反向歧视’诉讼已经在增加。”一名员工获得了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://casetext.com/case/duvall-v-novant-health-inc-5&quot;>;380 万美元&lt;/a>;；在第二起诉讼中，陪审团判决&lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/starbucks-racism-philadelphia-manager-lawsuit-bfa9cd9a897dff402f8547f167455d10&quot;>;2560万美元&lt;/a>;。这些金额虽大，但诉讼数量却很少。这些裁决可能无法继续存在：第一个裁决已被上诉，第二个裁决可能会被上诉。请继续关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;原告质疑公司多元化声明，或质疑其员工中一定比例是有色人种的目标，需要证明该目标导致了损害其职业生涯的“不利就业行动”。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/diversity-equity-dei-companies-blum-2040b173&quot;>;雇主会辩称事实并非如此&lt;/a>;，并会指出法院给予公司广泛的保护自行决定以他们认为合适的方式经营业务。所有这些都会使这些诉讼难以胜诉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最有效的 DEI 方法也是控制法律风险的最佳方法：将 DEI 计划的重点放在中断通过基本业务系统不断传播的偏见上。这就是大多数企业 DEI 计划的运作方式，这些计划通常侧重于培训和调整组织系统以创造公平的竞争环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如何？让我们举一个招聘偏见的例子，该实验是我的团队目前在该领域进行的 25 个偏见中断实验之一中发现的。我们发现，一家科技初创公司雇用的白人男性的评分远低于其他任何群体。我们还发现，白人通常只有在评分非常低的情况下才会被拒绝。来自其他群体的候选人即使评分高得多，也会被拒绝。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们正在合作的科技初创公司从不愿意收集和分析数据，到要求所有参与招聘的员工接受我们举办了关于消除招聘偏见的研讨会。将您的 DEI 计划建立在此类数据的基础上可以帮助改变公司的氛围。指标可以移山。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;收集这些数据还可以降低法律风险，因为第七章禁止基于种族或性别产生不同影响的政策。没有公司愿意在原告提起歧视诉讼后才了解此类问题。凡事有预谋。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦获得数据，您就需要解决发现的任何问题。不要让有偏见的系统留在原地，然后试图解决你在最后一刻明确考虑种族而造成的问题。相反，通过增加结构来遵循工业组织心理学的基本规则。例如，应通过使用标题和标准化量表根据预先确定的能力对每个候选人进行排名来审查简历。然后添加旨在防止实验社会心理学家记录的各种偏见的程序。例如，跟踪需求何时被放弃，并寻找模式。 （研究表明，要求通常&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/10.7758/9781610443913&quot;>;严格应用于&lt;/a>;组外，但对组内宽松。）&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;如果你这样做，你就不会违反&lt;em>;学生公平招生&lt;/em>;的裁决，因为你恰恰避免了大多数人认为令人反感的事情：明确的种族偏好。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;正如首席大法官罗伯茨&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/22pdf/20-1199_hgdj.pdf&quot;>;在他的意见中指出的&lt;/a>;，哈佛大学的种族偏好导致了黑人学术排名第四低的学生比排名前十分之一的亚裔美国人有更高的录取机会。我们从来没有在一家公司发现过这样的事情，而且我们已经与数十家公司合作了十多年。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个有说服力的统计数据概括了典型的问题：在我们包含近 20,000 人的数据库中80% 至 88% 的白人男性表示能够公平地获得促进职业发展的任务，而有色人种女性的比例则低至 50%。这是引发诉讼的秘诀。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多数意见的最后两个部分向企业界传达了信息。如果您确实想在可能引发反向歧视诉讼的情况下雇用一名合格的有色人种，那么大多数人的意见都会准确地告诉您该说什么。 &lt;em>;学生公平招生组织&lt;/em>;表示，虽然不能根据种族自动提升某人的地位，但可以考虑候选人如何克服各种生活障碍，包括种族歧视。注意，这就是说话的方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多数意见的最后一个重要部分是对刻板印象的讨论。哈佛的“录取过程建立在一种有害的刻板印象之上，即‘黑人学生通常可以带来白人学生无法提供的东西’，”罗伯茨法官写道。 “北卡罗来纳大学的情况大致相同。它认为，种族本身“说明了你是谁。”在法院看来，“根据血统而不是根据他或她自己的优点和基本品质来评判一个人，贬低了他或她的尊严和价值。 ”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种语言对另一种常见的 DEI 实践有影响：员工资源团体 (ERG)，或围绕共同身份结盟的自愿员工团体。这些团体反思了基于证据但现在非法的假设，即（例如）黑人员工在贵公司的经历往往与白人员工不同。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据 Laura Maechtlen 的说法，简单的解决办法Seyfarth Shaw LLP 的合伙人，向任何支持该集团使命的人开放 ERG。您还应该确保您的 ERG 有使命宣言、业务目标和规则，以防止人们加入该组织只是为了破坏该组织。无论如何，这都是最佳实践，因为这种方法可以帮助减少强烈反对并发展盟友。如果您的 ERG 包括能力建设（例如领导力培训），请确保在其他环境中也提供培训。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;底线是：像美国第一法律这样的极右倡导者假装&lt;em>;学生公平招生代表了很多它不代表的东西。没有伤害，没有犯规：这就是倡导者所做的。但不要误认为这是对法律风险的认真评估。事实并非如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How a Hybrid Platform Can Help Enable Trusted Generative AI - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM CLOUDERA, AMD & DELL]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/08/how-a-hybrid-platform-can-help-enable-trusted-generative-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/英雄图像>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;LJH82erDHQp3AvTAeo0Mt+iTzxaGx7qrjFjwWkGV8zlYqv6 /tcfKxr2toAHeF+Bc&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLe1ccDR72ijPS6FDnxIL/8g==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;true&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;08 “ 数据页-seo-title =“how-a-hybrid-platform-can-help-enable-trusted-generative-ai”data-page-adUnit-locations =“DFP_IC_pos3，DFP_IC_pos4”data-page-slug =“赞助”数据- Piano-verified=&quot;true&quot; >; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-0&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08 /Clouderahero-1024x536.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;生成式人工智能 (AI) 仍处于起步阶段，但它已经为帮助企业服务客户带来了不可抗拒的承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织可以使用生成式人工智能可以快速、经济地筛选大量自己的数据，帮助创建相关且高质量的文本、音频、图像和其他内容，以响应基于大量训练数据的提示。托管的开源大语言模型 (LLM) 可以帮助组织将企业数据上下文添加到其输出中，产生更可靠的响应，同时减少虚假信息（“幻觉”）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但困境在于，为了从生成式人工智能模型中获得更准确的输出，组织需要让第三方人工智能工具访问企业特定的知识和专有数据。不采取适当预防措施的公司可能会将其机密数据暴露给全世界。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这使得最佳混合数据管理对于任何采用第三方软件作为策略的组织都至关重要。 -服务（SaaS）人工智能解决方案及其专有数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;利用混合云的力量&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公共云提供了可扩展的环境，非常适合试验法学硕士。然而，在云中全面部署 LLM 的成本可能会非常昂贵。虽然法学硕士的质量取决于其数据，但向基于云的法学硕士发送敏感或受监管的数据会带来重大的隐私和合规风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;私有云为托管拥有专有企业数据和数据的法学硕士提供了最佳环境。对于长期运行的 LLM 部署来说，这是比公共云提供的更具成本效益的解决方案。将法学硕士安置在私有云中还可以确保增强的数据安全性，保护敏感信息免受外部威胁和合规问题的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>; if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;采用的组织混合工作流程可以两全其美，在不牺牲隐私和安全的情况下充分利用生成式人工智能。他们可以受益于公共云的灵活性来进行初始实验，同时在本地平台上保证最敏感数据的安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个组织的经验展示了基于混合云的数据管理如何将公共客户数据纳入其中。实时，同时保护公司和客户的机密信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;更加个性化的体验&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;总部位于新加坡的东南亚最大的金融机构之一使用人工智能和机器学习 (ML) 来增强数字客户体验并改进其决策。它使用混合云平台来做到这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;OCBC 为其所有 LLM 用例构建了一个单一入口点：一个混合框架，可以无缝集成多个数据源，包括来自数千名客户和私人数据源的输入。 -云数据湖，可确保客户数据安全，以获得根据其自己的公司标准定制的实时见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该银行构建了即时微服务，用于访问存储在其本地服务器上的法学硕士以及公共云中可用的法学硕士：一种经济高效的模型，允许使用公共云法学硕士并托管开源法学硕士，具体取决于所需的功能和定制。通过部署和托管自己的代码助手（可容纳 2,000 名用户），OCBC 节省了 80% 的 SaaS 解决方案使用成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将公共云上可用的大量功能与其私有平台的可移植性相结合，有助于减少成本。该银行安全地训练其人工智能模型，并从其输出中得出更准确的推论。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该平台与银行的机器学习操作管道集成，并融入其更大的机器学习工程生态系统。这个基于云的机器学习驱动平台让 OCBC 可以构建自己的应用程序并使用其数据科学家选择的工具和框架。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/ javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;该举措带来了更加个性化的客户体验、更高的营销活动转化率、更快的交易速度、减少了数据中心的停机时间，并且每年额外增加了 1 亿新元（7500 万美元）的收入。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;利用生成式 AI 安全地进行创新&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织正在竞相采用生成式 AI 来简化运营并推动创新。他们需要具有企业特定背景并利用专有数据源知识的人工智能工具。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，尽管技术仍处于成熟阶段，但无需牺牲隐私、安全性和合规性。通过使用托管的开源法学硕士，企业可以访问最新的功能并使用自己的数据微调模型，同时保持控制并避免隐私问题并限制费用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;使用混合平台使组织能够利用公共云的优势，同时将基于人工智能的专有见解排除在公众视野之外。通过允许企业随时随地以所需方式存储和使用数据，同时提供显着的成本优势，结合供应商无关的开放灵活解决方案的混合工作流程真正实现了人工智能的民主化。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>; &lt;strong>;&lt;em>;详细了解如何操作&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudera.com/why-cloudera/enterprise-ai.html?internal_keyplay=data-lakehouse&amp;amp ;internal_campaign=FY24-Q3_SC_Globl_HBR_ContentArticle_2023-08-11&amp;amp;cid=701Hr0000029gooIAA&amp;amp;internal_link=on-page-body&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;使用开源 LLM 以及您自己的数据安全的环境&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!--引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why We Glorify Overwork and Refuse to Rest]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_28_590177686.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Orbon Alija/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;我们都不想承认自己宁愿感到不知所措，也不愿感到不知所措。事实上，我们在工作时常常比不工作时更能体会到自己的价值。工作不仅仅是保持忙碌的一种方式，更是为了证明自己的价值——对他人和我们自己。结果是，如果没有适当的护栏，我们就会默默地与雇主勾结，雇主通过巨大的工作压力鼓励我们过度工作。作者概述了如果您发现自己强迫性过度工作的干预策略，包括诚实地认识到您长时间连续工作的倾向，优先考虑睡眠和运动，以及选择工作之外的一项能给您带来真正乐趣的活动。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span >; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;文章内容&quot; data-key=&quot;hlFJa4rIESdsHeLrhl0cVa4L0Vs5z6ZL2rREMbIQOaFEaCWWLMGJ9vbjJlQTRUNv&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8 lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7LhLkkr4KLIudCcZ656s9EHxHQ==”数据- waiver =“假”data-page-year =“2023”data-page-month =“08”data-page-seo-title =“为什么我们-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest”data- page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;根据最近的一项调查，近一半的美国工人未能使用所有分配的假期来自&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/03/30/how-americans-view-their-jobs/&quot;>;皮尤研究中心&lt;/a>;。他们列举的原因包括有太多事情要做、担心在工作中落后以及不愿意要求同事承担自己的责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 21:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Survey: Remote Work Isn&rsquo;t Going Away &mdash; and Executives Know It]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/survey-remote-work-isnt-going-away-and-executives-know-it]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_26_74011380.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;ER Productions Limited/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;许多首席执行官公开准备再次重返办公室。不过，一项新调查显示，高管们私下预计远程工作将继续增长。这是有道理的：员工喜欢它，技术正在进步，而且“”至少对于混合工作来说是这样的——生产力似乎没有损失。尽管有这些头条新闻，但高管们预计混合工作和完全远程工作在未来五年内将继​​续增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;文章内容”数据键=”MqyPx+iZb/LrP/bWQAMVolJjHZn+BSPk7KUnJpgKbrEQEnM/8piwvtFVwfUL2eF/”数据索引=”BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW6/Kbq5iPmmJvF9sjdH7 LhLMsuUTRBYWbwIuLdaIgIerQ==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year= “2023”data-page-month=“08”data-page-seo-title=“survey-remote-work-isnt-going-away-and-executives-know-it”data-page-adUnit-locations=“ &quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;远程工作 &lt;a href=&quot;https://wfhresearch.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SIEPR1. pdf&quot;>;在大流行期间激增&lt;/a>;，从美国全工作日的约 6% 上升到 2020 年春季的 50% 以上。此后，这一比例稳步下降，自 2023 年初以来一直徘徊在 28% 左右。 ；许多高管认为是时候回到办公室了：摩根大通首席执行官杰米·戴蒙 (Jamie Dimon) 宣布自己为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-chides -184750015.html&quot;>;远程工作怀疑论者&lt;/a>;；马克·扎克伯格&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/12/tech-ceos-fall-out-of-love-with-wfh&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>;让工程师在办公室“完成更多工作”； Google 首席人力官最近&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/2023/06/13/companies-aggressive-return-to-office&quot;>;告诉员工&lt;/a>;，办公室出勤率将影响绩效评估。就连 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/08/07/business/zoom-return-to-office/index.html&quot;>;Zoom 领导层&lt;/a>;也希望员工两天后亲自回来一周。&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>