<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Let the Urgency of Your Customers&rsquo; Needs Guide Your Sales Strategy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Adrià Voltà 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当公司创建可能目标客户的档案时，他们经常忽略一个维度：产品需求的紧迫性。本文提供了以这种方式细分潜在客户并制定销售策略的流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023 /07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/让您的客户需求的紧迫性指导您的销售策略？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;许多企业领导者认为，他们完全了解自己的业务最佳目标客户。他们开发了清晰的个人资料（又名人物角色），其中包含经过充分研究的参数，例如标准特征（例如，年龄、教育水平、在公司工作的年限、职位）或公司统计（例如，年收入、员工人数）。 、行业、地理、从业年限）。虽然这些特征很重要，但它们忽略了另一个关键特征：需求的紧迫性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为中小型私人牙科诊所提供软件即服务计费解决方案的公司可能会专注于经典的人口统计数据，例如诊所的规模（员工人数或牙医人数）、诊所的年龄（因为较旧的诊所更有可能拥有过时的系统）或诊所每年的保险账单金额。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;这些变量有助于生成潜在客户列表，但它们并不能确定销售团队应首先联系哪些牙科诊所。然而，如果该公司添加的数据反映了这些实践中哪些需求是最紧迫的，那么那些在过去一年中为计费和索赔管理做广告的人提供的帮助超过两倍（表明他们正在努力跟上计费的步伐） ）——销售人员将能够优先关注这些潜在客户。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;四个细分市场&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这种基于需求的方法需要将潜在客户分为四个细分市场：&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;紧急&lt;/strong>;。客户认识到自己有迫切的需求。 &lt;em>;（我们刚刚有另一位计费人员辞职了！）&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;非紧急。&lt;/strong>;客户认识到这一需求，但在这次。 &lt;em>;（我们意识到我们的计费需求正在发生变化，我们当前的系统需要进行改造。我们计划在明年开始研究这个问题。）&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;目前遇见了。客户认为它已经有了足够的解决方案来满足目前的需求，但认识到这可能不是一个长期的解决方案。 &lt;em>;（我们有一个较旧的计费系统，目前仍然有效。）&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;无&lt;/strong>;。客户根本没有需要，也不期望很快有这样的需要。 &lt;em>;（我们的小型诊所自付费用的患者数量有限。由于所有付款都是在服务时支付，因此我们根本不需要复杂的新计费系统。）&lt;/em>;&lt;/li >; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;关注目标客户需求的紧迫性听起来像是常识，但我们在与 B2B 公司（从中型企业到财富 50 强企业）的合作中发现，这些公司涉及一系列行业，例如例如金融服务、企业信息技术、公用事业、工业解决方案和医疗保健技术——他们往往无法考虑这个维度。以下是公司可以采用的流程来应用此方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;识别新客户。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;要识别现有客户群之外的潜在客户，您可以使用可用的信息。其中一个来源是我们提到的：反映特定需求的招聘广告。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但还有很多其他来源。例如，如果一家公司销售库存管理解决方案，有价值的数据来源可能是制造业并购数据，这可以揭示公司是否迫切需要更改或合并系统（例如库存管理系统）。如果一家公司销售质量管理解决方案，那么有价值的数据来源可能是因质量差而在社交媒体上受到打击的公司。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;收集必要的信息。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;要识别客户真正的需求紧迫性，需要超越典型的人口统计和公司概况分析。首先是与客户和潜在客户交谈的外展活动。目的是提出问题，以确定可能影响客户需求紧迫性的新目标客户参数：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;挫败感。 &lt;/strong>;解决这些挫折的需要有多紧迫？如果解决哪些挫折，最能加速成功？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;目标。 &lt;/strong>;你的目标是否清晰、一致、合理且可衡量？您的目标最近有变化吗？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;障碍。 &lt;/strong>;是什么阻碍你实现目标？ （即，是什么让您彻夜难眠？）这些障碍的影响有多大？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;环境和情境因素。 &lt;/strong>;您是否正在经历任何行业整合、组织或执行管理变化或不稳定、竞争变化、监管变化等？这些因素的影响有多大？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;技术因素。是否有新的或不断变化的技术会影响您实现目标的能力？您是否因技术报废问题或不兼容性而面临风险？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;评估您公司服务较低级别细分市场的能力。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;一旦公司完成了基于需求的细分工作，它应该寻求回答有关四个级别中每个级别的以下问题。调查结果将决定销售和营销策略、投资水平和资源分配。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;第 1 级。紧急需求&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们能够多快满足他们的需求？我们怎样才能最好地为他们服务？市场机会是否足够大，足以只关注这些潜在客户？考虑到客户的紧迫性，我们如何为产品定价以优化利润，而又不会因显得剥削而损害关系？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;第 2 级。非紧急需求&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们能否说服他们，他们的需求是比他们目前认为的更紧迫？我们如何有效地与他们保持联系，以便当他们意识到自己的需求变得紧急时，我们仍然是首要考虑的？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;第 3 级。目前的需求已得到满足&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们是否应该放弃这些前景？如果是这样，我们何时以及如何与他们联系以了解他们的需求是否发生了变化？或者是否有机会继续努力让他们相信，他们的需求比他们意识到的更重要，或者可以更好地得到满足？如果是这样，让他们重新考虑当前状况并认识到他们的真正需求及其紧迫性的最佳方法是什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4 级。不需要&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我们应该完全删除这些联系人吗？有什么潜在的前景吗？我们是否可以通过其他产品来满足他们的其他需求？我们是否应该有计划地联系他们，看看他们的情况是否有变化？我们如何最好地做到这一点？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;理想的客户是那些清楚地了解并认识到他们对您的产品有迫切需求的客户。但是，如果该机会不足以满足公司的销售量目标，则可能有必要将努力扩展到 1 级以上。吸引这些额外目标客户的注意力，挑战他们对需求的看法，并教育他们如何提供您的产品使他们受益将需要资源。因此，需要进行严格的评估，以确定机会是否超过满足其他级别客户所需的投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;测试您的新目标。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在彻底改变销售人员优先考虑机会的方式之前，请选择一到两名经验丰富的销售人员来帮助您测试新的目标客户参数。确定一些符合您修改后的目标概况的潜在客户，并了解所选销售人员如何能够渗透到他们中。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;改进您的销售信息和培训。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt; p>;在销售信息中包含潜在客户的需求级别——销售团队在与客户互动时使用的语言。改进您的销售工具（销售过程中使用的宣传册、技术论文和客户评价等材料），以体现需​​求的紧迫性。并教销售人员如何阅读和应对潜在客户的需求水平，并适当地调整他们的语言。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过增加目标客户资料的需求紧迫性，公司可以做的不仅仅是更有效地差异化他们的产品。他们还可以发现新的增长机会，并成功摆脱放缓或紧缩的市场。他们可以加速新产品的销售。最后但并非最不重要的一点是，他们可以将表现不佳的销售团队转变为表现出色的团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt; br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https:// /feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Help Your Team Grow, Give Them Space to Struggle]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/to-help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_1198521996.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;凯瑟琳瀑布商业/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;当您看到一名员工在一项您可以轻松完成的任务上苦苦挣扎时，它&amp;#8217想要介入并提供帮助是很自然的。但从另一方面来看，这更像是微观管理而不是支持。当领导者因给自己保留太多工作而过度运作时，他们就会让周围的人无法发挥作用。我们都知道委派是多么重要既可以帮助员工成长，又可以创建一个更具协作性、授权性和生产力的团队。您如何才能更好地掌握这项关键的领导技能？&amp;#160;首先，从实干者心态转变为领导者心态。其次，拥抱学习过程中的不适。第三，确定委托风险较小的低风险任务。最后，保持好奇心和促进性，而不是规定性。&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023 /07/to-help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to- help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “你如何证明销售和费用估算的合理性？”首席执行官问道。我的脸红得结结巴巴。我的心跳加快，喉咙发紧。我看着我的老板瓦莱丽。她进行了眼神交流，温柔地注视着，什么也没说。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;她本可以缓解我的一些热情。她插话救了我，但她没有。那是因为我请求瓦莱丽给我一个向我们组织的领导团队展示的机会。在会议之前，她通知我们银行部门的负责人和首席执行官，我将承担这项延伸任务，而她将担任观察员。因此，当我面临棘手的问题时，她并没有接管我的工作，而是让我自己想办法摆脱不适。&lt;/span>;这让我为下次与他的会面做好了更好的准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;我记得瓦莱丽是一位好老板，因为她经常给我这样的发展机会。风险通常很低，就像小型内部会议一样，每个人都知道我仍然是新手并且会提供支持。瓦莱丽在场，但在幕后，让我成功或失败，但无论哪种方式都可以从经验中学习。后来，她再也没有给我一长串如何改进的建议。相反，她提出了很好的问题，促使我思考我可以采取哪些不同的做法。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;理论上，大多数领导者知道将具有挑战性的任务委派给员工是多么重要，这不仅可以帮助他们成长，还可以创建一个协作、授权、高效的团队。但是，面对真实的工作场所需求，将其付诸实践可能很困难。 &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;我的许多客户都会说“我是唯一能胜任这项工作的人”或“如果这个项目进展不顺利，整个项目就会失败”。团队将会受苦。”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;同理心可以&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/connect-with -empathy-but-lead-with-compassion&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;妨碍&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; ， 也。当您看到员工陷入困境时，您很自然地想要介入并提供帮助。但从另一方面来看，这更像是微观管理而不是支持。当领导者因承担太多任务而过度运作时，他们就会导致团队运作不足。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;这里有一些您可以用来简化授权的策略。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;从实干者心态转变为领导者心态&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400 ;&quot;>;在我的公司工作中，我们将最优秀的实干家提拔为领导者。这是基于这样一种假设，即他们会神奇地从擅长并受卓越绩效和奖励激励转变为擅长并深切关心开发他人的潜力。 &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;心态转变可能是最困难的部分。那么，你如何才能自己促进这一点呢？&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;注意您所做的事情的回报。&lt;em>;&lt;/em>; &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;成就的快感提供了快速&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.noesislearning.com/2019/11/19/the -neuroscience-of-achievement/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;多巴胺命中&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;。但你需要抵制这种情绪，才能获得帮助他人进步的更大成就感。&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;通过明确价值观来彰显您的领导身份。问问自己：我希望人们用哪三个词来描述我的领导风格？例如：我想要以控制力、紧迫感和专业知识来领导吗？或者，有耐心、好奇心和授权？&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;有意识地回应，而不是反应。当您被触发介入的时刻，问问自己：这符合我的价值观以及我想成为的领导者吗？&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;接受学习过程中的不适&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;许多领导告诉我，在目睹员工犹豫不决后，收回工作感觉是最支持的事情。我也感受到了这种紧张。但瓦莱丽教会了我保持斗争空间的力量。是的，这会给领导者和员工带来不适，因为这对每个人来说都是一种新的工作方式。但是，如 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/389807/top-things-employees-next-job.aspx&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400; &quot;>;盖洛普提醒我们&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;，工作投入的关键之一是提供刺激挑战的机会。当你完成斗争时，结果就是各方的成长。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;如何才能拥抱而不是抵制，学习的不适？&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;说出您的情绪&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/3-ways-to-better-understand- your-emotions&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;根据&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;心理学家 Susan David，提供了清晰度和弹性，可以让您有意识地做出回应，并符合您的价值观。&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;将不舒服正常化。 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.edutopia.org/article/neuroscience-behind-productive-struggle/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;神经科学家知道&lt;/span>; &lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;这是学习和培养毅力的时期。&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400；” aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;重新构建情况。一个潜在的重构是：“我被允许去奋斗，这就是我对自己的技能充满信心的地方。因此，我将给予我的员工同样的时间来自己解决问题。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;区分高风险任务和低风险任务&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;领导者经常告诉我，他们仍然被困在实干家的行列中，因为员工犯了太多需要干预的高影响力错误。但这种情况通常发生在老板自己把所有工作都抓了太久，然后被迫在错误的时间委派出去的时候。关键是在风险较低且可以容忍甚至预期出现失误时转交任务。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;是什么让环境低风险？失败对学习的支持大于对声誉的损害。错误不会影响团队或公司的成功。环境对于停留和重来是安全的。相关人员对学习曲线上经验不足的同事表示支持和同情。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;要了解哪些任务适合委派，请考虑哪些任务现在你觉得很容易或死记硬背，但对你团队中的人来说是很好的发展机会吗？还要考虑一下那些会耗尽您精力、与您的技能、才能和优势不相符，但可能会令人兴奋并感觉非常适合其他人的工作。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;例如，如果您的员工的目标是培养更好的演讲技巧，请尝试先进行低风险活动，例如要求他们主持下一次员工会议，然后再进行高风险活动，例如主持客户会议会议。或者，如果他们想更好地影响他人，请挑战他们在使用新工具或工作流程方面获得小团队的支持，然后再要求他们说服整个部门实施它。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp ;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;保持好奇心并提供帮助&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;在我的企业职业生涯的早期，作为一名培训师，人们告诉我，我在主持的课程中明显感到紧张。我向老板解释说，我担心无法回答参与者的问题。她的回答是：“如果你的角色不是获得所有答案而是促进房间里的专业知识怎么办？”这改变了我的观点。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;像培训师一样，领导者不能指望拥有所有答案。但他们确实需要有耐心和好奇心，并提出有洞察力的问题来促进学习。例如：您目前的做法是什么？你能应用过去的经验来解决这个问题吗？这种情况教会了你什么？&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;最后，练习慈悲和恩典。这并不意味着要容忍不努力或粗心的错误。相反，它意味着当某人没有完全按照您的方式做事时提供理解和通融。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Valerie&#39;s那天与我们首席执行官的接触当时感觉不太好。但如果她介入，我就不会学会如何回答意想不到的问题，也不会在事后反思如何更好地准备高管演讲。如果她遵循建议，我就不会发现自己真正的改进方法。直到今天，我仍然相信她帮助我培养了在高风险情况下冷静表达的能力。她也是我有勇气将工作委托给同事和团队成员的原因，即使这意味着看着他们挣扎。这是我们所有人（领导者和员工）成长的唯一途径。 &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Train Generative AI Using Your Company&rsquo;s Data]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_1488880093.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;利用公司的专有知识对其竞争和创新能力至关重要，尤其是在当今动荡的环境中。组织创新是通过知识资产和专有技术的有效和敏捷的创建、管理、应用、重组和部署来推动的。然而，组织内的知识通常是通过各种来源和形式生成和捕获的，包括个人思想、流程、政策、报告、运营交易、讨论区以及在线聊天和会议。因此，公司的综合知识往往不被考虑，并且难以以有效或高效的方式组织和部署在需要的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;许多公司正在尝试ChatGPT 和其他大型语言或图像模型。他们普遍发现他们用清晰的语言表达复杂想法的能力令人震惊。然而，大多数用户意识到这些系统主要接受基于互联网的信息的培训，无法响应有关专有内容或知识的提示或问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;利用公司的专有知识对其竞争能力至关重要并创新，尤其是在当今动荡的环境中。组织创新是通过知识资产和专有技术的有效和敏捷的创建、管理、应用、重组和部署来推动的。然而，组织内的知识通常是通过各种来源和形式生成和捕获的，包括个人思想、流程、政策、报告、运营交易、讨论区以及在线聊天和会议。因此，公司的综合知识往往下落不明，并且难以以有效或高效的方式组织和部署在需要的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以大型语言和图像生成人工智能模型形式出现的新兴技术为以下领域提供了新的机遇：知识管理，从而提高公司绩效、学习和创新能力。例如，在财富 500 强业务流程软件提供商进行的一项&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w31161&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;中，基于生成式 AI 的客户支持系统提高了客户支持代理的工作效率并提高了保留率，同时也为客户带来了更高的积极反馈。该系统还加快了新手代理的学习和技能发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;像该公司一样，越来越多的组织正在尝试利用大型语言模型 (LLM) 的语言处理技能和一般推理能力来捕获并为内部（或客户）提供广泛的获取其自身智力资本的途径。他们将其用于向面向客户的员工通报公司政策和产品/服务建议、解决客户服务问题或在员工离开组织之前获取知识等目的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些目标也是在 20 世纪 90 年代和 2000 年代初“知识管理”运动的鼎盛时期，大多数公司发现当时的技术不足以完成这项任务。然而，如今，生成式人工智能正在重新点燃在整个组织及其外部获取和传播重要知识的可能性。正如一位为此目的使用生成式人工智能的经理所说，“我感觉喷气背包刚刚进入我的生活。”尽管目前取得了进步，但过去导致知识管理困难的一些因素仍然存在。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;基于人工智能的生成式知识管理技术&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p >;将组织的特定领域知识纳入法学硕士的技术正在迅速发展。目前，将专有内容合并到生成模型中的方法主要有三种。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;从头开始训练法学硕士&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一种方法是从头开始创建和训练自己的特定领域模型划痕。这不是一种常见的方法，因为它需要大量高质量的数据来训练大型语言模型，而大多数公司根本不具备这种能力。它还需要获得相当大的计算能力和训练有素的数据科学人才。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;彭博社是采用这种方法的公司之一，该公司最近宣布，它已经为特定于金融的内容和自然的内容创建了 BloombergGPT。与其数据终端的语言接口。彭博社拥有 40 多年的财务数据、新闻和文件，并结合了来自财务备案和互联网数据的大量文本。彭博社的数据科学家总共使用了 700 个令牌，即约 3500 亿个单词、500 亿个参数和 130 万小时的图形处理单位时间。很少有公司拥有这些资源。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;微调现有的法学硕士&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;第二种方法是“微调”培训现有的法学硕士，将特定领域的内容添加到系统中，已经接受过一般知识和基于语言的互动方面的培训。这种方法涉及调整基本模型的一些参数，通常需要更少的数据（通常只需要数百或数千个文档，而不是数百万或数十亿），并且比从头开始创建新模型所需的计算时间更少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;例如，Google 在其 &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/healthcare-life-sciences/sharing-google-med-palm-2-medical- Large-language-model&quot;>;Med-PaLM2&lt;/a>;（第二版）医学知识模型。该研究项目从 Google 的通用 PaLM2 LLM 开始，并根据来自各种公共医疗数据集的精心策划的医学知识对其进行了重新培训。该模型能够回答 85% 的美国医疗执照考试问题，比系统的第一个版本提高了近 20%。尽管进展如此之快，但当根据科学事实、精确性、医学共识、推理、偏见和伤害等标准进行测试，并由来自多个国家的人类专家进行评估时，开发团队认为该系统在应用于临床之前仍需要大幅改进。实践。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，微调方法有一些限制。尽管比培训法学硕士所需的计算能力和时间要少得多，但培训成本仍然很高，这对谷歌来说不是问题，但对许多其他公司来说却是问题。它需要大量的数据科学专业知识；例如，Google 项目的&lt;a href=&quot;chrome-extension://bdfcnmeidppjeaggnmidamkiddifkdib/viewer.html?file=https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.09617.pdf&quot;>;科学论文&lt;/a>; 31 位共同作者。一些数据科学家认为，最适合的不是添加新内容，而是添加新的内容格式和风格（例如像威廉·莎士比亚那样聊天或写作）。此外，一些 LLM 供应商（例如 OpenAI）不允许对其最新的 LLM（例如 GPT-4）进行微调。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;提示调整现有的 LLM&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;也许为非云供应商公司定制 LLM 内容的最常见方法是通过提示进行调整。通过这种方法，原始模型保持冻结状态，并通过包含特定领域知识的上下文窗口中的提示进行修改。经过及时调整后，模型可以回答与该知识相关的问题。这种方法是三种方法中计算效率最高的，并且不需要在新内容域上训练大量数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，摩根士丹利使用即时调优来训练 OpenAI 的 GPT -4 模型使用精心策划的 100,000 个文档集，其中包含重要的投资、一般业务和投资流程知识。目标是为公司的财务顾问提供关于他们在为客户提供建议时遇到的关键问题的准确且易于获取的知识。经过及时培训的系统在私有云中运行，只有摩根士丹利员工才能访问。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这可能是组织采用的三种方法中最简单的一种，但它并非没有技术挑战。当使用文本等非结构化数据作为 LLM 的输入时，数据可能太大且包含太多重要属性，无法直接在 LLM 的上下文窗口中输入。另一种方法是创建向量嵌入——由另一个预先训练的机器学习模型从文本生成的数值数组（摩根士丹利使用 OpenAI 中的一个称为 Ada 的模型）。向量嵌入是该数据的更紧凑的表示，它保留了文本中的上下文关系。当用户在系统中输入提示时，相似性算法会确定哪些向量应提交给 GPT-4 模型。尽管一些供应商正在提供工具来简化这一快速调整过程，但它仍然足够复杂，以至于大多数采用该方法的公司都需要拥有大量的数据科学人才。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，这种方法不需要如果所需的内容已经存在，这将非常耗时或昂贵。例如，投资研究公司晨星 (Morningstar) 在其基于生成人工智能的 Mo 研究工具中使用了即时调整和向量嵌入。它包含了超过 10,000 项晨星研究成果。经过大约一个月的系统工作后，晨星就向其财务顾问和独立投资者客户开放了 Mo 的使用。它甚至将莫附加到一个可以说出答案的数字化身上。这种技术方法并不昂贵；在使用的第一个月，Mo 回答了 25,000 个问题，每个问题的平均成本为 0.002 美元，总成本为 3,000 美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;内容管理和治理&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与传统知识管理（其中文档被加载到 Microsoft Sharepoint 等讨论数据库中）一样，使用生成式 AI，在以任何方式定制法学硕士之前，内容需要是高质量的。在某些情况下，就像 Google Med-PaLM2 系统一样，已经有广泛可用的医学知识数据库。否则，公司需要依靠人工管理来确保知识内容准确、及时且不重复。例如，摩根士丹利在菲律宾有一个由 20 名左右的知识经理组成的团队，他们不断地根据多种标准对文档进行评分；这些决定了是否适合纳入 GPT-4 系统。大多数没有精心策划内容的公司会发现仅出于此目的而这样做具有挑战性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;摩根士丹利还发现，如果内容作者意识到，保持高质量的知识会容易得多如何创建有效的文档。他们需要参加两门课程，一门是关于文档管理工具的课程，另一门是关于如何编写和标记这些文档的课程。这是该公司内容治理方法的一个组成部分，内容治理方法是一种捕获和管理重要数字内容的系统方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在晨星，内容创建者正在学习什么类型的内容适合 Mo 系统，以及什么不。他们将内容提交到内容管理系统中，内容会直接进入提供 OpenAI 模型的矢量数据库。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;质量保证和评估&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一个重要的内容管理生成式人工智能内容的一个方面是确保质量。众所周知，生成式人工智能有时会产生“幻觉”，自信地陈述不正确或不存在的事实。此类错误可能会给企业带来问题，但在医疗保健应用程序中可能是致命的。好消息是，根据特定领域信息调整法学硕士的公司发现，幻觉比开箱即用的法学硕士问题要小，至少在没有扩展对话或非业务提示的情况下是这样。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;采用这些方法进行生成式人工智能知识管理的公司应制定评估策略。例如，对于旨在回答金融和投资问题的 BloombergGPT，该系统在公共数据集金融任务、命名实体识别、情感分析能力以及一组推理和通用自然语言处理任务上进行了评估。 Google Med-PaLM2 系统最终旨在回答患者和医生的医疗问题，具有更广泛的评估策略，反映了医疗领域准确性和安全性的重要性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;生死攸关。这是摩根士丹利的一个问题，但对金融和投资问题做出高度准确的回答对于公司、其客户和监管机构来说非常重要。系统提供的答案在发布给任何用户之前都经过了人工审核员的仔细评估。然后由 300 名财务顾问进行了几个月的试点。作为持续评估的主要方法，摩根士丹利制定了一组 400 个已知问题的“黄金问题”。每次对系统进行任何更改时，员工都会用黄金问题进行测试，看看是否存在任何“回归”或不太准确的答案。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;法律和治理问题&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与 LLM 部署相关的法律和治理问题非常复杂且不断变化，导致涉及知识产权、数据隐私和安全、偏见和道德以及虚假/不准确输出的风险因素。目前，LLM输出的法律地位仍不清楚。由于法学硕士不会生成用于训练模型的任何文本的精确副本，因此许多法律观察家认为版权法的“合理使用”条款将适用于他们，尽管这尚未在法庭上得到测试（并且没有经过法庭测试）。所有国家的版权法中都有此类规定）。无论如何，对于任何广泛使用生成式人工智能来管理知识（或大多数其他目的）的公司来说，让法律代表参与调整后的法学硕士的创建和治理过程是一个好主意。例如，在晨星公司，该公司的律师帮助创建了一系列“预先提示”，告诉​​生成人工智能系统应该回答哪些类型的问题以及应该礼貌地避免哪些类型的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;用户提示公开- 可用的LLM用于训练系统的未来版本，因此一些公司（&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-ai-like-例如，chatgpt-for-staff-after-misuse-of-chatbot.html&quot;>;三星&lt;/a>;）担心机密和私人信息的传播，并禁止员工使用法学硕士。然而，大多数公司用特定领域内容调整法学硕士的努力都是在公共用户无法访问的模型的私有实例上进行的，因此这应该不是问题。此外，一些生成式人工智能系统（例如ChatGPT）允许用户关闭聊天记录的收集，这即使在公共系统上也可以解决机密性问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了解决机密性和隐私问题，一些供应商为法学硕士提供先进和改进的安全功能，包括删除用户提示、限制某些主题以及防止将源代码和专有数据输入到可公开访问的法学硕士中。此外，企业软件系统供应商正在其产品和服务中纳入“信任层”。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/salesforce-aims-to-plug-ai-trust-gap-with-new-tech-tools-19e11750?mod=djemCIO&quot;>;Salesforce&lt;/a >; 例如，将 Einstein GPT 功能纳入其 AI Cloud 套件中，以解决希望快速部署 LLM 功能的公司与这些系统在业务环境中带来的上述风险之间的“AI 信任差距”。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2 >;&lt;strong>;塑造用户行为&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;易于使用、广泛的公众可用性以及跨越各个知识领域的有用答案，导致了基于人工智能的生成知识的快速、无指导和有机采用由员工管理。例如，最近的一项调查表明，超过三分之一的受访员工在工作中使用生成式人工智能，但 68% 的受访者没有告知主管他们正在使用该工具。为了抓住生成式人工智能应用知识管理的机遇并管理潜在风险，公司需要培养一种透明和问责的文化，使基于生成式人工智能的知识管理系统取得成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了政策的实施之外和指南，用户需要了解如何安全有效地将生成式人工智能功能融入到他们的任务中，以提高性能和生产力。生成式人工智能能力，包括对背景和历史的感知、通过聚合或组合各种来源的知识生成新内容以及数据驱动的预测，可以为知识工作提供强大的支持。基于生成式人工智能的知识管理系统可以自动化信息密集型搜索过程（例如法律案例研究）以及大容量和低复杂性的认知任务，例如回复常规客户电子邮件。这种方法提高了员工的效率，使他们能够将更多的精力投入到工作中复杂的决策和解决问题方面。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些可能需要通过培训或政策灌输的具体行为— 包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;了解系统可以提供哪些类型的内容；&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如何创建有效的提示；&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;提示的类型以及允许对话，哪些不允许对话；&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如何请求将额外的知识内容添加到系统中；&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如何使用系统的响应来与客户和合作伙伴打交道； &lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如何以有用且有效的方式创建新内容。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;摩根士丹利和晨星都对内容创建者进行了培训，特别是如何最好地创建和标记内容，以及哪些类型的内容非常适合生成式人工智能的使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;“一切都进展得非常快”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们采访的一位高管表示，“我可以告诉你今天的情况。但这个领域的一切都进展得非常快。”新的法学硕士和调整其内容的新方法每天都会宣布，供应商提供的具有特定内容或任务重点的新产品也是如此。任何致力于将自己的知识嵌入生成式人工智能系统的公司都应该准备好在未来几年内经常修改其解决该问题的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然构建和使用生成式人工智能系统涉及许多具有挑战性的问题人工智能系统是根据公司自己的知识内容进行训练的，我们相信，为了公司的整体利益，值得努力应对这些挑战。让任何员工以及客户能够轻松获取公司内外的重要知识以提高生产力和创新的长期愿景具有强大的吸引力。生成式人工智能似乎是最终使其成为可能的技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Making the Air in the Office Cleaner]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/making-the-air-in-the-office-cleaner]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_04_1400864430.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/fizkes/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;雇主确保其设施内空气清洁的压力越来越大。 CDC 设定了居住空间换气的目标，以降低 Covid-19 等空气传播感染的风险。联邦怀孕工人公平法案于 2023 年 6 月 27 日生效，要求雇主为怀孕工人提供“合理的便利”。对于怀孕的工人。最近加拿大野火造成的严重空气污染蔓延到美国大部分地区，凸显了另一个原因：森林火灾。本文介绍了组织可以采取的三个步骤，以经济高效的方式改善空气质量。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/making-the-air-in-the-office-cleaner?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/making-the-air- in-the-office-cleaner?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;五月份，疾病控制与预防中心将每小时换气五次 (ACH) 设置为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/community/ventilation.html&quot;>;办公室和商店等占用的室内空间所需的目标通风量，以更好地减少Covid-19 等空气传播感染的风险。这一水平将更好地保护每个人，对于免疫功能低下和其他无法通过疫苗充分保护的高危人群尤其重要。 （疾病预防控制中心仍然建议&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/need-extra-precautions/people-who-are-immunocompromished.html&quot;>;免疫功能低下&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/need-extra-precautions/pregnant-people.html&quot;>;怀孕&lt;/a>;人群避免前往拥挤或通风不良的室内空间。） &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了此建议之外，组织应认真对待此目标还有其他原因。其中之一是联邦《怀孕工人公平法案》，该法案于 6 月 27 日生效。类似于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/wysk/what-you-should-know-about-covid-19-and-ada-rehabilitation-act-and- other-eeo-laws&quot;>;美国残疾人法案&lt;/a>;要求保护免疫功能低下者，它要求雇主为怀孕工人提供“合理的便利”。 （与免疫功能低下的人一样，孕妇及其发育中的婴儿也面临更大的风险 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/cases-updates/special-populations/pregnancy- data-on-covid-19/what-c​​dc-is-doing.html&quot;>;Covid-19 带来的严重并发症&lt;/a>;。）另一种现象似乎发生得更加频繁：森林火灾。近期严重的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/opinion/story/2023-06-16/air-quality-new-york-pollution-wildfires-climate-change&quot;>;空气污染&lt;/a >; 蔓延到美国大部分地区的加拿大野火就是一个明显的例子。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于许多建筑物来说，升级中央空调系统以实现五个 ACH 需要进行大规模且昂贵的翻修。即使完成后，这些系统也会产生高昂的&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CathNoakes/status/1586299281752920064&quot;>;能源成本&lt;/a>;来循环大量空气。或者，企业可以采取三个步骤，通过使用经济高效的室内便携式空气净化器来轻松实现 5 个 ACH。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.安装便携式空气净化器（净化器）。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048969722029813&quot;>;便携式低噪音空气净化器&lt;/a>; 例如 HEPA 净化器和自制 (DIY) 空气净化器&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.patentknowhow.com/safe.html&quot;>;组装&lt;/a>;由箱式风扇、过滤器、和其他现成的材料是通过回收每个房间的空气来实现 CDC 目标的一种经济有效的方法。基于我们的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/san-francisco/san-francisco-unified-seeks-nearly-3-million-to-buy-air-purifiers-for- every-classroom/2639904/&quot;>;在旧金山学校的经验&lt;/a>;，三个DIY净化器可以&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2022.11.05.22281734v1&quot;>;超过&lt;/a>; a>; 对于典型的 900 平方英尺&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EYtmnUc8cBE&quot;，CDC 的目标是低至 250 至 400 美元（约每平方英尺 0.25 至 0.50 美元） >;教室&lt;/a>;天花板高 10 英尺，每月电费不到 10 美元。由于 HEPA 可以在商店购买并&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EN3kYm7bXJs&quot;>;快速&lt;/a>;自行构建，因此它们可以在短时间内作为有效的清洁空气解决方案实施天 — 结果已由 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0360132322011507&quot;>;CDC&lt;/a>; 和 &lt;a href=&quot;https:// onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/ina.13163&quot;>;美国环境保护署&lt;/a>;。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.projectn95.org/free-air-purifiers/&quot;>;免费&lt;/a>;向为弱势群体服务的组织提供 DIY 空气净化器。最近，市场上出现了使用&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cleanairkits.com/&quot;>;个人电脑冷却风扇&lt;/a>;的更加节能的DIY型号。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;总的来说，所需净化器的数量及其总成本与房间体积和空气交换目标成比例增加。许多净化器都具有可变速度。它们需要设置为以达到 CDC 目标 5 个 ACH 所需的速度运行；否则，其效果将会降低，并且可能达不到预期目标。安装并运行后，可以使用手持式&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2022.08.09.22278555v10&quot;>;粒子计数器&lt;/a>;检查空气交换率，以测量空气交换率的变化房间内存在空气颗粒。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.在拥挤的情况下超过 12 ACH 的新 CDC 目标。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了限制细菌生长，鱼缸通常使用过滤系统每小时至少清洁水四次（每 15 分钟），类似到四个空气 ACH 来获取房间内的空气。直到最近，对于有效减少建筑物内病毒传播所需的空气净化程度还缺乏明确的认识。所以2022年我们在《美国医学会杂志》上&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2799161&quot;>;写信给CDC&lt;/a>;，要求它说清楚需要多少 ACH 才能阻止 Covid。 CDC 研究人员&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799159&quot;>;回复&lt;/a>;表示，虽然他们不知道有 5 到 6 个 ACH 的空间中爆发了 Covid-19，但 12 个 ACH在某些情况下，可能需要或更多（例如飞行中的飞机或医院的空中隔离室）。随着空间内人数的增加，传播的可能性也会增加，这可能需要更多的 ACH 和距离来降低风险。例如，加州公共卫生部&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdph.ca.gov/Programs/CCDPHP/DEODC/EHLB/IAQ/CDPH%20Document%20Library/School_ventilation_and_filtration_ADA.pdf&quot;>;建议&lt;/ a>; 学校中至少有 6 个 ACH，最好是 12 个 ACH。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.在工作时间内运行空气净化器，以降低成本并定期更换过滤器。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;过滤器和风扇可以按照制造商建议的定期时间表进行更换，或者，如果组织想要保守的话，经过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048969722029813&quot;>;测试&lt;/a>;后显示他们的表现已降至可接受的水平以下。测试可以揭示过滤器或风扇的使用寿命何时比预期更长，或者其性能下降是否比预期更快（例如，过滤器被颗粒堵塞或在强烈的野火烟雾事件后失去了过滤颗粒的能力）。在某些地方，例如医院，它们可能需要 24×7 运行，但对于许多企业来说，如果仅在有人在场的典型营业时间（例如上午 9 点至下午 5 点）开启，它们可以持续长达时间延长四倍，功耗减少四倍。它们可以由房间里的人手动打开和关闭，也可以通过低成本的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B009KSECO8&quot;>;运动传感器&lt;/a>;（可以设置） 20 分钟不活动后自动关闭。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;企业可以实施这三个步骤，以经济有效地支持新的 CDC 标准和 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/ Wellness/air-purifier-smoke-covid-best/2021/08/29/28ea4176-0740-11ec-a266-7c7fe02fa374_story.html&quot;>;保护&lt;/a>;人们免受新冠病毒感染，&lt;a href=&quot;https://aaqr .org/articles/aaqr-21-03-tn-0046&quot;>;野火烟雾&lt;/a>;、过敏原和任何其他可能出现的空气传播危险。这些清洁空气的简单步骤最终将使每个人受益，并为高危人群创造一个更具包容性的环境，包括免疫功能低下的人、孕妇、老年人、儿童以及患有慢性心肺疾病的人。&lt;/ p>; &lt;!-- 引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Your Company Have a Culture of Quiet Retaliation?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_05_1423429755.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;无声的报复形式非常常见，并且在工作场所可能会传染。接受这种形式的报复作为标准做法的组织很难雇用和留住优秀人才。报复&amp;#8212;各种形式的不仅会伤害当前的团队成员，而且容忍报复的文化也会损害使命和组织向客户和利益相关者提供服务的能力。为了创造一种心理安全成为常态、创新蓬勃发展、团队效率高的文化，解决暗中发生的报复问题至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我们大多数人都熟悉教科书或人力资源政策中对报复的定义。公开、大声的报复时刻确实会发生，比如有人在大声疾呼或正式表达担忧后被解雇。然而，在我们与团队的合作中，我们经常目睹更微妙的报复形式，这些报复经常发生，但通常被忽视或忽视。微妙的、通常是无声的报复会毁掉职业生涯，侵蚀目标个人的价值感，并损害团队的效率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们尚未遇到任何自称具有报复性的领导者，但我们经常看到报复的发生在团队上。当领导者只通过公开和大胆的行动来看待报复时，他们就会忽视其更微妙的表现，而其后果同样严重。如果领导者无法识别自己和他人的这些行为，他们就有可能对个人、团队和他们所服务的组织造成短期和长期伤害。为了创造一种心理安全为常态、创新蓬勃发展、团队效率高的文化，我们必须了解暗中发生的报复行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;报复的现实&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在在美国，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/eeoc-releases-fiscal-year-2020-enforcement-and-litigation-data&quot;>;55.8% 的索赔中提到了员工报复&lt; /a>; 于 20 财年向美国平等就业机会委员会 (EEOC) 提交了申请 - 这正是所报道的内容。举报报复行为可能会给个人的财务稳定性、未来职业发展和声誉带来重大风险。举报所需的时间和精力对许多人来说是一种威慑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一些最常见的报复行为涉及经理&lt;em>;不&lt;/em>;采取的行动。这种悄悄的——有时是隐蔽的——报复行为极其有害，因为它可能会持续多年而不被发现、不被提及或不被报道。它不仅会影响目标个人，还会降低目睹这一事件的团队成员的信任水平、创造力和生产力，并使虐待文化永久化。维拉诺瓦教授 Manuela Priesemuth 在她的文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/06/times-up-for-有毒-workplaces&quot;>;有毒工作场所的时代到了&lt;/a>;”中分享了虐待和报复文化如何“蔓延到整个组织，形成了整个虐待氛围。因为员工向经理寻求并向经理学习，他们逐渐明白这种人际虐待在公司是可以接受的行为。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是我们在工作辅导中观察到的五个隐蔽报复的具体例子领导者及其服务的团队：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;拒绝提供指导、反馈或专业发展机会&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;拒绝为项目或部门提供资源&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;故意给予在几乎没有支持的情况下完成具有挑战性的任务，或者给出注定会失败的具有挑战性的任务&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;阻止其他人倾听或重视团队成员的声音、专业知识或贡献&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;将团队成员排除在必要的之外马克*以报复性着称，在退休前曾担任一家大型零售公司的首席执行官十多年。当我们与新任首席执行官领导下的剩余领导团队合作时，我们很快发现，仅靠马克的离职不足以平息员工的恐惧。尽管马克已经不在了，但公司里仍然存在着明显的恐惧情绪。我们从几位领导那里听说，与马克的任何分歧都意味着你在公司内成长的终结。 “当他对某个敢于发声的人感到失望时，他会露出一种表情，”我们从几位领导人那里听到了这样的说法。 “他会在你的名字上画一条线，而不是在名字下面。每个人都知道，比赛基本上就结束了。你被困住了。”对于马克来说，报复采取了社会破坏和排斥的隐蔽形式。这对组织的影响是巨大的：创新停滞、文化受损、业务停滞。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Julia 是一家中型科技公司的首席财务官。当她收到部门内部有关敌对工作环境投诉的通知时，她表示自己已经意识到这些问题，因为这些问题已经发生多年，但一直避免解决。朱莉娅一直直言不希望她的团队成员与人力资源部讨论任何问题。 “为什么人们不能低下头完成工作呢？为什么我的工作就是处理他们幼稚的行为？”她问她的同龄人。朱莉娅随后剥夺了投诉团队成员获取执行工作所必需的信息和文件的权限。朱莉娅还不再及时回复她的电子邮件，并希望缺乏通信会导致项目按时完成的延误，进一步让团队成员在同事面前丢脸。当被问及这些行为时，朱莉娅回答说：“这不可能是报复，因为我没有解雇他们。”我们经常看到领导者进行悄悄的报复行为，从而产生巨大的影响，但他们并不认为这是报复，因为他们将报复狭隘地定义为解雇员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;罗恩曾在一家医院担任护士长。医院急诊科连续15年获青睐，年内大幅晋升。虽然医院内的正式领导赞赏罗恩严格、传统的管理风格，但其他急诊室工作人员的经历却截然不同。 “如果你做了一些让他烦恼的事情——也许表达了担忧或指出某些供应不足——你可以预期你将来所说或所做的一切都会受到审查。他无法接受任何反馈，即使是关于口罩或手套库存等简单的事情，”我们从一位值班领导那里听到。在这种特殊情况下，持续的负面审查对文化和僵局造成的负面影响不仅影响了部门，还危及公共安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;领导者应如何自我评估其影响&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;领导者经常将自己视为部门或组织中正确行为的看门人。在我们刚才描述的每种情况下，领导者都相信这就是他们正在做的事情。危险并不在于看不到你的意图和影响之间的脱节。领导人报复的连锁反应是巨大的。当领导者缺乏加深对其行为及其影响的自我认识所需的工具时，对所有利益相关者来说后果可能是可怕的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们倾向于根据我们的良好意图来判断自己，并根据他们的影响来判断他人。我们的领导指导原则之一是：你无法决定你的影响力；你可以决定你的影响力。其他人也这么做。那么，您如何才能更好地评估您的行为的影响并了解您行为的根本原因呢？从这三个实践开始：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;进行勇敢的审核。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;检查自己的行为并深入挖掘行为背后的动机。我们强烈建议基于&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gse.harvard.edu/hgse100/story/changing-better&quot;>;免疫变化&lt;/a>;的工作进行“勇敢的审计”实践罗伯特·基根和丽莎·莱希。变革免疫模型在这种情况下特别有效，因为它挑战我们思考我们的行为（或缺乏行为）如何妨碍创建心理安全的工作环境。想想团队成员中最让你沮丧的情况，并寻找你的行为方式是否没有效率或可能具有报复性。挑战自己，好奇地提问并勇敢地回答：我在做什么或不做什么会妨碍安全文化？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;意识到适得其反的行为是改变它们的第一步。我们经常听到领导者说，以这种方式反思自己在同事面前显得太脆弱，因此与经验丰富的教练合作是增强您在工作场所中的思想和行为的自我意识的有效方法。&lt;/p>; &lt; h3>;识别你的影子意图。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;影子意图是指我们（有意识或无意识）出于自我和自我保护的立场而行动。拒绝你自己声称的“提供帮助”或“保护你的部门”的愿望。您的想法或行为以何种方式意图通过隐蔽或被动的方式伤害团队成员？你什么时候被自我保护驱使而不受控制？您什么时候可能会允许您的第一次压力驱动反应对您对他人产生的影响产生负面影响？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;伊丽莎白是一家不断发展的 IT 公司的一员，而且从各方面来看，她都是领导团队的重要成员。当发生合并时，“必须为即将上任的领导者腾出空间”，她也多次被忽略晋升。虽然她希望继续证明自己的价值并领导好团队，但她需要支持来积极摆脱自己希望新领导者失败的阴影意图，这样她就可以因其卓越和持续的承诺而得到奖励。通过努力放松她的影子意图对她的控制，她能够将更多的注意力带回自己的部门并更好地支持创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;探索你的内群体/外群体。&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;评估您对周围人的想法和假设。谁能对你诚实，甚至不同意你的观点？你看重谁的意见？为什么？你和谁一起奋斗？ What commonalities exist between the people in your in-group versus your out-group?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Identifying your own patterns is the pivotal first step of working toward a team where everyone is included and can contribute fully. Dan, the CEO of a midsize firm, wanted to think differently about several leadership changes that were occurring due to retirements. He wanted to bring the new executives in and build a cohesive team with the remaining members. In an audit of his own in- and out-groups, he discovered that two leaders of the executive team were in his out-group. Both had started during the pandemic, and Dan hadn&#39;t had the one-on-one time with them he usually invests in new executives on his team. Dan decided to start building connections with them more intentionally by scheduling individual lunches once a month and initiating a 15-minute one-on-one with each of them once a week.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are many strategies help leaders in connect with their out-group, but the most important point thing to keep in mind is that the person with the most power must initiate the connection.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Quiet forms of retaliation are incredibly common and can be contagious in the workplace. The organizations we serve that accept this form of retaliation as a standard practice have difficulty hiring and retaining great people. Retaliation — in all its forms — not only harms current team members, but a culture that tolerates retaliation results in harm to the mission and the organization&#39;s ability to deliver to its customers and stakeholders. Organizations are defined by what they celebrate and what they tolerate. Leaders who engage in or tolerate retaliation can create lasting scars on individuals and organizations alike. The humans we serve deserve better.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* Names have been changed throughout to protect privacy.&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Removing the Roadblocks That First-Generation Americans Face at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_03_1369183308.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Many first-generation Americans face a cultural seesaw effect when trying to be successful in Western workplaces. For example, members of the Asian American and Pacific Islander (AAPI) community can find it challenging to self-promote, as it goes against their values. They&amp;#8217;re taught from a very young age to be humble, to stay under the radar, and to never correct authority figures, as a sign of respect. They hope their hard work will simply speak for itself. But self-promotion and voicing opinions have become key elements needed to thrive in Western workplaces, which clearly advantages some and disadvantages others. Further, first-generation Americans and other marginalized communities endure numerous generational, societal, and workplace traumas that create mental health disparities, which can result in an apprehension to advocate for themselves in work environments. While leaders cannot control how their employees will cope with societal and generational trauma, it is their responsibility to foster environments where all employees can feel secure in raising their hands for support. In order for this to successfully occur, organizations should closely look at whether current employee behaviors are in fact promoting inclusivity, or if processes and norms need to be modified to provide an equitable landscape for all workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When my family immigrated from India to the US nearly four decades ago, they had no indication of what a new world would bring. They were filled with hope that this relocation would provide a surplus of opportunities unavailable before. With that hope came a justified reservation about acceptance in a new community, so they applied a strategy many immigrant families deploy: assimilate and prosper.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The goal was not to suppress our identities. In contrast, it was to engage in a new environment with foreigners in a non-burdensome way. Rather than demanding a promotion at their jobs, my parents patiently waited until their hard work was finally rewarded — years after their American peers. Instead of asking for support in their daily duties, they silently took on additional responsibilities to prove their worth. Both of my parents wore their sense of altruism, undying commitment, and unwavering devotion as a badge of honor — blissfully passing these values onto me in hopes that I would replicate their work ethic in my career.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I entered the workforce with my parents&#39; worth ethic, fearless spirit, and integrity to carry me through my future endeavors. Unfortunately, history repeated itself in an unexpected way. I was exploited for my hard work. My boundaries were constantly being violated by senior leadership. I was petrified when it came to seeking support from my team because I was convinced that this would be a sign of weakness and would tarnish my professional image, ultimately hindering growth opportunities. It created a version of me that I despised: insecure, hesitant, and incredibly docile.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Working as a First-Generation American &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;My formative years were spent thinking my family environment was unique, but this was far from the truth. Many first-generation Americans face similar challenges as they navigate the societal expectations of two cultures at a very young age, resulting in a unique phenomenon called the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://srcd.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/cdep.12071&quot;>;immigrant paradox&lt;/a>;“.&amp;nbsp;First-generation Americans experience diminishing developmental outcomes, educational achievements, and even mental health challenges because of the racial and ethnic disparities in the US — challenges our parents or even recent immigrants do not face since they immigrate normally post-adolescence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To exacerbate this experience, first-generation Americans also face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2022/10/26/health/mental-health-children-of-immigrants-wellness/index.html&quot;>;immigrant guilt&lt;/a>; as they try to desperately hold onto the traditions they inherited while harmonizing within a culture their families could not provide any guidance about. Adapting to the Western culture while feeling “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-othering-5084425&quot;>;othered&lt;/a>;” can lead to the inability to forge an identity that neatly falls within both cultures, traditions, and experiences. While our families may have had the best intentions in providing us with their wisdom and perceived values of success, it did not translate well into a workplace construct that was built for people who never shared our identities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is the cultural seesaw effect that many first-generation Americans face when trying to be successful in the workplace. The Asian American and Pacific Islander (AAPI) community (and many cultures alike) find it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-we-need-to-talk-about-asian-american-mental-health?cid=other-eml-dre-mip-mck&amp;amp;hlkid=a774e1a8976d4a078406df70a8406fd5&amp;amp;hctky=12012649&amp;amp;hdpid=9ae1a3af-4f90-48c7-84bd-0389613c0228&quot;>;challenging to self-promote&lt;/a>;, as it goes against our values. We&#39;re taught to be humble and stay under the radar. We have been taught from a very young age to never correct authority figures, as a sign of respect. Similar to how my parents navigated their careers, many AAPI community members hope their hard work will simply speak for itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So why is this important for workplaces and leaders to consider as they seek to create equitable and inclusive work environments? &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/savvy-self-promotion&quot;>;Self-promotion&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/glennllopis/2012/03/19/6-reasons-employees-must-speak-up-to-thrive-at-work/&quot;>;voicing your opinion&lt;/a>; have become key elements needed to thrive in Western workplaces, but this clearly advantages some and disadvantages others. Further, first-generation Americans and other marginalized communities endure numerous generational, societal, and workplace traumas that create &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/cultural-competency/education/mental-health-facts#:~:text=Racial%2Fethnic%2C%20gender%2C%20and,of%20awareness%20about%20mental%20health&quot;>;mental health disparities&lt;/a>;, which can result in an apprehension to advocate for themselves in work environments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, if employers take an approach that commits to prioritizing inclusivity across all identities and backgrounds, then we can make progress in our distorted definition of success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How Leaders Can Change the Narrative and Help Fix a Flawed System&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders cannot control how their employees will cope with societal and generational trauma. Yet, it is their responsibility to foster environments where all employees can feel secure in raising their hands for support. In order for this to successfully occur, organizations should closely look at whether current employee behaviors are in fact promoting inclusivity, or if processes and norms need to be modified to provide an equitable landscape for all workers. In my experience in working with global organizations, taking this critical pause before churning out solutions has proven to be a pivotal factor in revamping inclusion.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assess Your Inclusion Efforts &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In order to understand what practices are supportive of inclusion and which are not, a thorough assessment is required. In previous leadership roles, I have successfully conducted this assessment that ultimately evaluates inclusion across organizational and management practices through three specific dimensions: Co-creating success as a team, fostering communities with purpose, and evaluating the effectiveness of feedback mechanisms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These three dimensions serve as a comprehensive approach to further understanding the organization&#39;s context, culture, and intent in creating substantive inclusion. It also serves as a foundation for leaders to deep dive into prevailing processes to determine if the current company climate integrates the differences first-generation employees bring to the table, and allows them to be part of the decision-making process to achieve strategic objectives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once each dimension is thoroughly examined, taking action and prioritizing specific areas that need immediate attention is key. It will foster a culture of continuous learning and improvement from an organizational level, while simultaneously creating new practices where first-generation employees have the security to thrive.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Co-Create Success as a Team&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We start with this dimension because our traditional workplace practices define success by emphasizing specific individual behaviors, instead of creating practices that benefit the entire employee population. This &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/how-to-infuse-liberatory-practices-into-work-practices&quot;>;divide and conquer&lt;/a>; approach specifically prevents first-generation employees from determining what success looks like for them, furthering the narrative that their unique insights are less important than the dominant group.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As leaders, you can rectify these practices by first evaluating the level of collaboration and inclusion you provide for your own team. Commence reparative practices and invite all team members to define what success looks like for them. By doing so, you are providing first-generation employees the permission to relinquish their previous notions of the perfect employee, and create a culture of solidarity where they will be more likely to voice their opinions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Additionally, forging rules of engagement, understanding preferred communication styles with others, and finalizing what support leadership should provide at the start of a project maintains boundaries for each first-generation employee. Eventually, if you keep inviting opinions to the table — and revisit conversations about success definitions on an agreed-upon timeline — the stigma associated with raising concerns will slowly diminish. Further, maintaining these work relationships and reciprocally committing to meet each other&#39;s needs will allow for an equitable decision-making process and boost morale among all team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Foster Communities With Purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Arguably, this may be the most important component of the inclusion assessment, because it offers up a safe haven for first-generation employees to discuss how they navigate unique workplace stressors that only apply to them. Employee resource groups (ERGs), for example, have been incredibly popular for organizations trying to increase their inclusion efforts. However, they often &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at-work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;fall short&lt;/a>; because they lack accountability or a specific mission. In my experience, I have seen ERGs solely being leveraged as an after-work social gathering — which is important, but does not cultivate corrective practices in the workplace that first-generation employees deserve. In order to make these communities more effective, I recommend finding a business sponsor who is already practicing &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/why-inclusive-leaders-are-good-for-organizations-and-how-to-become-one&quot;>;inclusive leadership&lt;/a>; to lead the ERG with empathy and strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a previous role, I acted as the business sponsor and supported the launch of a similar ERG with a six-month action plan. The first two months were to simply connect as a community — to decompress and speak about how our community is marginalized in particular ways. The third and fourth months were used to transition into strategy. We examined questions such as: &lt;em>;How can we empower ourselves to ask for support? What specific actions do we need leadership to take for us to continuously feel empowered in order to bring value back to the organization? &lt;/em>;These conversations were often difficult, and sometimes quite emotionally draining because it required many of us to revisit how our immigrant guilt manifests itself in the workplace. This is why the business sponsor of any ERG should be well-equipped and skilled to facilitate these conversations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Lastly, the fifth and sixth months were dedicated to building a case to senior leadership in the specific work practices that needed to be amended in order for us to feel valued, included, and guarded in the workplace. A specific proposal was then developed with a coherent communication plan derived from the roundtable discussions we had in previous months. As we co-created this plan, each member of the ERG was invited to provide feedback and voted for the top concerns we wanted to address.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With this collective support of the ERG community, we were able to establish new norms across client projects to address capacity constraints, enhance cross-collaboration with teams, and determine accountability measures across all levels. For many of the ERG members, this success came with a unique sense of ownership of their careers that had seemed foreign before. People in the community had been accustomed to remaining silent, trailing back to the generational trauma many of us carried as we navigated through various challenges into the workforce. However, this success was a glimmer of hope that self-promotion could actually lead to tangible results, fundamentally changing the way the business operates.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate the Effectiveness of Feedback Mechanisms &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While employee feedback through engagement surveys has become popular over the years as a definitive measure for enhancing inclusion, many first-generation employees will hesitate to offer their insights. Due to our complex identities, feeling othered, and lack of role models that share our identity, we feel compelled to assess the work environment first to determine if speaking up will be celebrated or punished — regardless of whether the feedback is imperative to change working conditions. To counteract this, leaders should actively analyze what type of culture they are promoting in order to retrieve an accurate glimpse of the work environment. Without this core component in psychological safety, employee engagement surveys will remain a false illusion of the organization&#39;s actual reality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, if your goal is to decrease employee burnout by seeking suggestions through engagement surveys, evaluate the type of behavior you are celebrating prior to seeking feedback. If you are amplifying an employee working at all hours, allowing others to accept every client demand, or creating &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90662451/its-very-time-sensitive-why-a-fast-paced-work-environment-hurts-all-employees&quot;>;a false sense of urgency&lt;/a>;, you are not fostering an inclusive environment for others to raise their hand for support. In fact, you are telling your employees that this is the golden rule for everyone to follow. First-generation employees will not feel safe to provide feedback in addressing these negative workplace stressors because the organization inadvertently supports this type of burnout behavior. Regardless of how well-intentioned your surveys are, harmful work environments will negate any efforts to make substantial change and eradicate any creditability amongst your first-generation employees. However, if the end goal is to create sustainable and inclusive work environments, call out toxic behaviors as regularly as you can, making it known these are not expectations for employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once there has been a careful examination of workplace practices, seeking individual feedback via engagement surveys, team forums, or even via 1:1 meetings can further prove to empower first-generation employees. This continued course of action achieves a positive cycle of consistency where self-advocacy is encouraged, rather than expecting first-generation employees to overcome their reservations without the proper groundwork.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Furthermore, as you seek feedback, carefully analyze the perspectives of your first-generation employees. You may not always agree with their feedback or even fully understand their point of view. However, it is still your responsibility to do your best to implement changes if your end goal is inclusivity. Once this process is underway, an important consideration is not to have the feedback stay idle. Ultimately, if feedback goes unheard, it can create an environment of mistrust between you and first-generation employees. Keep in mind that this specific group would have done a great deal to overcome their own internalized stigma in providing the feedback, in hopes that the culture of work would be transformed. Communicate how you will address the feedback and remain agile. It may be possible that you will need to spend some time deciphering feedback from your first-generation employees or have another follow-up questionnaire to clarify points when it comes to their working conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As organizations continue to correct a flawed system by building inclusion for all communities, it is imperative to support those who may not be able to advocate for themselves. First-generation employees sit at a unique juncture in applying determination and diligence in a new era of work, continuously shifting between cultures. Organizations need to create an environment where we can shed our layers and authentically thrive in the hopes of creating a more equitable world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Benefits of Being Bored at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_XLRivrl9mNI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&amp;#8217;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life. Based on the body of research exploring this emotion, the authors highlight some of boredom&amp;#8217;s benefits and detriments and offer insights into how you might harness the best of boredom.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Bored at work?我们都去过那里。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/1745691612456044&quot;>;Boredom&lt;/a>; is that experience of wanting to be occupied in a satisfying activity, yet somehow being unable to do so. And being busy is no antidote: You may be both very busy — and very bored — simultaneously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Early in life we learn that boredom is no fun, and as we age we might begin to see it as a waste of time, or a missed opportunity to do something more productive (or at least more interesting). At best, boredom has been considered an unpleasant to &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691612456044?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;aversive &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/152c9TgGipX6UOMCIbfTdrGy_vN6kopCv/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;experience&lt;/a>;, and at worst, a state that evokes a deep sense of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springer.com/journal/13164&quot;>;meaninglessness&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XXpz4j8kTTtUdXJdlak3e3_kuIJLNskz/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;.&lt;/a>; In addition, when feeling the discomfort of boredom, time &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gNy8bUlah9IHjM1CZZjkS6EnRV7AxXzX/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;tends to pass slowly&lt;/a>;, which can make work days seem endless.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Considering this, it&#39;s no surprise that boredom often triggers an intense desire to escape the situation (or job!) that evokes it. In today&#39;s ultra-connected world, this escape is just one tap away. At your fingertips, you find a world of data, breaking news, shows and stories, messages from friends and family, or gifs, memes, and video clips that help you avoid feeling bored — at least at the surface level. Research shows that use of smartphones not only distracts the mind, it offers an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/IJPHM-08-2016-0044/full/html&quot;>;addictive hit&lt;/a>; of dopamine, which &lt;em>;temporarily&lt;/em>; replaces the discomfort of boredom with pleasure. However, this&amp;nbsp;feeling is short lived, as this mindless scrolling results in long-term decreases in overall mental health and quality of life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next time you&#39;re feeling that creeping sense of boredom at work, pause before you pick up your phone. Boredom can have important benefits, and you&#39;ll miss them if you&#39;re not tuned in to what you&#39;re feeling and why.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Pros and Cons of Workplace Boredom&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Boredom has a negative reputation for a reason. At work, it&#39;s often viewed as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;counterproductive state&lt;/a>; that ignites discomfort, desperation for a new role, or perhaps simply a desire for the day to end. Boredom at work has been linked to &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2160&quot;>;risky decision-making&lt;/a>;, costly mistakes, and accidents triggered by inattention or lack of focus — and that&#39;s not to mention the fatigue that being bored can generate. Boredom can also incite other types of problematic behavior, such as “cyberloafing” (that is, non-work-related browsing) and childish emotional responses. Prolonged exposure to monotonous activities can even cause &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-pathology-of-boredom/&quot;>;hallucinations&lt;/a>;. In addition, when it comes to well-being, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000187912200118X&quot;>;one recent study found&lt;/a>; a linkage between boredom at work and burnout, as well as decreases in job satisfaction and increased desire to quit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the flip side, recent research shows that boredom — when handled constructively — has big “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;bright sides&lt;/a>;.” Moments of boredom can offer a pause, or a short respite for your brain and body in a world designed to distract, overwhelm, and overstimulate. A sense of boredom can create the space to daydream, which can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2014.901073&quot;>;hatch creativity&lt;/a>;, new ideas, and innovation. Prolonged boredom can prompt you to reflect and ask yourself, “Am I on the right path? Am I doing the right thing?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Your Boredom for the Better&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re not advocating that you seek out jobs where you&#39;ll spend large parts of the day feeling bored. However, getting better at working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; your boredom — and harnessing it for the good — can help you capture its bright sides. Here&#39;s how:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Notice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you feel that discomfort of boredom setting in, avoid acting on it immediately. The fact that you&#39;ve noticed you&#39;re bored means that you&#39;ve managed to (briefly) resist the urge to instantly engage in mindless scrolling. Noticing and naming your boredom in order to intentionally direct it opens up the opportunity to develop your resilience and the potential to use boredom for positive ends. Most importantly, in a bout of boredom, don&#39;t make snap decisions (like to quit your job) as a way to escape the discomfort.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Decipher.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Not all experiences of boredom are the same — &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11031-013-9385-y&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that various “types” of boredom manifest differently in the body and mind, giving rise to different behaviors. Decoding which types you&#39;re feeling early on can help you make a game plan to deal with boredom, or prevent it from escalating or clouding your decision making.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ask yourself what your boredom is telling you. Could it be that you simply need a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research&quot;>;micro-break&lt;/a>; because you&#39;ve worked too long without pausing and you&#39;re tiring? Or maybe your tasks are becoming monotonous and you&#39;re losing motivation and energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider what you&#39;re bored with specifically: Is it your role, the content or form of the work, or your prospects for the future in your job that bore you? Can you decipher a pattern with a typical type of work that ignites this uncomfortable feeling? This can be an opportunity to consider your goals and values and whether you feel you&#39;re moving forward or feel “stuck.” Here are five research-based types of boredom to consider as you work to decipher yours:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Indifferent boredom.&lt;/strong>; This is one of the more positive types of boredom. It can feel like relaxation or a sense of cheerful fatigue and reflects a general indifference to (and withdrawal from) the external world. This type of boredom can help boost rest and recovery, particularly during busy days.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Calibrating boredom.&lt;/strong>; This one&#39;s slightly more unpleasant and is one of the most common types. It occurs when you&#39;re not fully engaged in a task or activity and your mind starts to drift. It can show up as wandering thoughts or not knowing what to do to change the situation, yet wanting to get out of it somehow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Searching boredom.&lt;/strong>; This type reflects a restlessness and active search for alternative actions and distractions to ease the negative experience (eg, through other activities, leisure pursuits, interests, and hobbies). While unpleasant, this type of boredom ignites activity and the pursuit of change and often has positive outcomes, such as creativity, innovation, and personal growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Reactive boredom.&lt;/strong>; Reactive boredom arises in situations where a person is required to do a repetitive or tedious task (such as being stuck in a long and ineffective meeting with no chance of escape). It&#39;s an action-oriented and deeply unpleasant type of boredom, which causes restlessness and frustration that might be expressed in a more angry or aggressive fashion toward others or toward the boring experience. Those experiencing it may persistently fantasize about other options and feel anxious to make a change or escape quickly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Apathetic boredom.&lt;/strong>; This can relate to feelings of disinterest, lack of motivation, and emotional detachment toward activities or events one would normally find stimulating or enjoyable. Apathetic boredom isn&#39;t necessarily accompanied by feelings of frustration or restlessness but rather a sense of disengagement and indifference. It can occur as a result of chronic stress, depression, or other mental health issues and can lead to feelings of hopelessness and helplessness. People experiencing apathetic boredom may feel like they&#39;re going through the motions of life without any real purpose or enjoyment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Decide what to do.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Based on the type of boredom and what it&#39;s telling you about yourself or your situation, decide what to do about it. Maybe your boredom is simply allowing you to relax and unwind after a period of intensity at work. Or perhaps it&#39;s telling you something about your role itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All roles have certain elements that are monotonous, frustrating, or simply boring, and sometimes these tasks must be done to get to the “good stuff.” If you find yourself persistently bored, try to harness the boredom to catalyze change, perhaps by engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>; to bring out the elements of your role that you really enjoy. This could involve, for example, making changes to the type, variety, complexity, or significance of your tasks. You might intentionally evade boredom by seeking out, envisioning, and championing new ideas at work, which can also boost your leadership abilities and potential. Reflecting and engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23163710/&quot;>;nostalgia&lt;/a>; can also counteract the sense of meaninglessness you might feel when bored.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Cultivate mindful boredom.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Moments of boredom can be opportunities to help you unwind from a fast-paced and hyper-connected world and allow you the opportunity to simply be in the present moment. Use moments of boredom for positive intentions rather than mindless distraction, for example, by taking a moment to breathe, doing another activity you find simulating, or simply mindfully allowing the discomfort to pass. As boredom can spark &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20200522-how-boredom-can-spark-creativity&quot;>;creativity&lt;/a>;, you could even include space for it as unstructured time in your work routine, for example, before you&#39;re required to innovate, come up with new ideas, and be at your best.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&#39;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Ways to Earn the Respect of a More Powerful Colleague]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_03_144694173.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;retales botijero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When you are stuck in an unequal power dynamic, it helps to remember that not only is the placement of power temporary, but you can equalize it. In this article, the author outlines four strategies you can use to creatively pivot in the moment and frame the connection differently, so that you are building the respect you deserve and positively shifting the perception of your power.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/4-ways-to-earn-the-respect-of-a-more-powerful-colleague?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Whether we want to acknowledge it or not, in many colleague relationships there is a power differential, often based on each party&#39;s status in the organization and who has more control over what the other needs at a given time. For instance, the engineering leader whose team ultimately determines a product line&#39;s time-to-market may hold more power over the sales leader trying to deliver for impatient customers, and the leader of a mature and “unexciting” business unit may find their needs consistently deprioritized by the IT department, which is rushing to support a fast-growing division, instead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s a deeply frustrating dynamic for those in the “inferior” position — but to develop a mutually respectful relationship with colleagues (and perhaps even claim more relative power), it&#39;s vital to take steps toward rebalancing the equation. With a willingness to assert yourself in creative ways, you develop more agency for yourself, particularly at times when feeling dismissed or dependent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.columbia.edu/~da358/publications/ames_pushing_up_to_a_point.pdf&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; there is a “Goldilocks” effect when it comes to assertiveness in interpersonal relationships, where you&#39;re able to hit a sweet spot between being too assertive and not enough. When done properly, &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/why-we-should-be-disagreeing-more-at-work&quot;>;healthy dissent&lt;/a>; can lead to deeper trust and mutual respect. Based on my work as an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.partnerexec.com/&quot;>;executive coach&lt;/a>; for senior leaders at global companies, here are four strategies you can deploy in your relationships to distribute power more evenly.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Choose to decline certain requests. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It may feel incredibly challenging to decline a more powerful colleague&#39;s request. But in any interaction, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Framing_effect_(psychology)&quot;>;framing effect&lt;/a>; takes place where each party is sizing up who has more power and influence. Since power is comprised of many factors and is situational, even if you find yourself typically powerless relative to a colleague, there do emerge situations where they need something from you just as much as you need them. Even if you&#39;ve always acceded in the past, in occasional moments, it&#39;s important to capitalize on the opportunity to politely refuse the more powerful person&#39;s demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/meet-catch-and-keep/201602/4-truths-about-power-in-relationships-including-yours&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; on relationships defined power as not only having a greater ability to influence the other, but also having the stronger &lt;em>;resistance to the other&#39;s influence&lt;/em>;. So, the next time you sense your colleague is overly exerting their power over you (for instance, making another last-minute request even though they have been inaccessible for yours), it may be a good idea to not immediately drop what you&#39;re doing and jump to the rescue.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I once coached a leader whose peer often dumped work on her but managed to stay above the fray when others needed her help. This colleague would frequently cite her interactions with their shared boss as a way of justifying her power and drop their name while making requests that purely served her.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are in a similar position as my client, respond to your colleague by saying something like, “I wanted to let you know I got your request. I&#39;m happy to help but have other commitments I must address at the moment. In the meantime, feel free to send me more information in case I can suggest another solution.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ideally, you want to send a message that you expect them to invest their limited time as well into the relationship. If you are true to the minimum promises you&#39;ve made, then you can confidently hold your ground as an equal partner. This not only encourages them to respect you but forces them to make sacrifices as needed for the relationship as much as you do.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Connect them to other people in power who value you.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Another way to shift the power in the relationship is by subtly reminding them of your social value by connecting them to other people they respect, with whom you&#39;ve cultivated a relationship. This does three valuable things: first, it shows them (through the principle of social proof) that you must have something to offer if people they admire see value in you; second, it may tip the scales in your relationship dynamic because you possess access they&#39;d like to enjoy; and third, it sends a signal that you already have high-profile access, so are not desperate to chase their approval.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I worked with a leader who struggled to be seen as a “strategic” executive and was continuously downplayed for higher level roles by HR when succession planning discussions took place. But in truth, he was quite innovative and eager to contribute to more forward-looking aspects of the business; it was because he was so good at operational execution that HR and his boss didn&#39;t want to rock the boat through a promotion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To disrupt this power dynamic, which was limiting his advancement, my client started to develop relationships with other senior leaders and socialized ideas that could help their business needs. And then he started making introductions between his new contacts and some of the colleagues in HR and his business who held influence over his career. By showing his access to other powerful leaders and sharing it as well through connecting others, his brand began to rise toward the perception of an enterprise-level leader.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Help them surface their blind spots as a way of supporting them.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Even the most powerful people can&#39;t see themselves exactly the way other people perceive them. In other words, they have blind spots just like the rest of us. And when you can help them gently recognize an aspect of their thinking or behavior that is getting in the way of their goals, they can begin to view you as a highly trusted partner, rather than someone below their level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of my clients was an SVP at a technology company who was privy to the chatter across the organization about the CEO&#39;s lack of decisiveness and how it was creating confusion for employees and teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While she agreed with the general sentiment, she was happy with how the CEO treated her. While he had more power than her, she generally accepted the idea of working under his leadership and meeting his expectations as best as she could. After all, she thought, why risk her relationship with the CEO and give him tough feedback that could backfire on her for being the messenger?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But she also recognized that to become a trusted partner to him, she would need to truly be in his corner, through good and bad, and that required being honest with him for his benefit. So, she decided in her next one-on-one to share her observations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The SVP said, “I know how important it is to you to do the right thing for the business and our people. And sometimes our strengths can be over-leveraged to the point of becoming a weakness. I think because you care so much about listening to all sides of an issue, it&#39;s starting to delay making decisions. And I wanted to offer this possibility because you may be too close to this style to see how it&#39;s impacting others.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In taking the risk of putting a mirror up to the CEO, the SVP earned a high measure of respect and gratitude from him. Their relationship became one of trusted advisor and not just direct report.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you meet with people in power and simply tell them everything they&#39;ve heard before or the same things as others in your position, you will be forgotten and relegated to the status quo. But by stepping out of your comfort zone to — kindly, but assertively — point out something that the powerful person had not noticed, you not only become memorable but start to gain influence and respect with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Make them work to earn your attention.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gaining the respect of colleagues more powerful than you is an interesting paradox: by putting them in a position to work for your approval, you earn more of their respect. So, a fourth strategy is to create conditions where they must “sell” their value to you. Basically, work less at earning their respect and put the burden on them to explain why they should be worth your attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Over the years, I&#39;ve coached leaders at companies that had undergone a merger or reorganization that required many employees and leaders to “reapply” for a job, either within their division or in a new part of the company. This experience can be unsettling, not just because they are back to being a candidate competing against others for a job, but because unlike applying to a new company from the outside, their reputations precede them and provide more subjective input that will influence interviewers when evaluating them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The natural mistake many people make in these situations is to overprepare for the questions they think they will be asked and try their best to hedge their answers to please the hiring colleague. This seems like the path of least resistance but in fact positions them as forgettable and unremarkable in the eyes of the other party.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, find ways to be generous with your answers but unafraid to also ask questions that put them a bit on their heels. When your colleague asks you that oft-repeated question, “Why should we hire you for this job?” your first instinct may be to prove your value to their satisfaction, even though you and they know that most everyone is applying for jobs because of the reorganization, not because they wanted to try something new.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, take a beat and say something like, “Actually, I&#39;m not sure you should hire me just yet. I&#39;d like to explore if there&#39;s a mutual fit between my experience and your vision of where this team is going. Anything you could share about your management style would be helpful as I&#39;m exploring my next steps.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Expecting people in power to “earn” your interest rather than take it for granted can bring positive results. Not only can it set you apart from the competition, but it can ensure you are working with colleagues who respect you rather than keep you under their power and whims.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you are stuck in an unequal power dynamic, it helps to remember that not only is the placement of power temporary, but you can equalize it. By adopting these strategies, you can creatively pivot in the moment and frame the connection differently, so that you are building the respect you deserve.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Explain a Gap in Your Resume]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_1105032.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Audshule/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Since the pandemic, most employers have been more understanding and less discriminating regarding resume gaps &amp;#8212; but you have to be ready to explain the gaps clearly, confidently, and without stumbling. Owning your career trajectory means connecting all the dots for the recruiter and hiring manager. Shaping the narrative around any gaps yourself will help make them a non-issue. The author discusses five common reasons for work-history gaps &amp;#8212; and how to own the gap during the interview process.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-explain-a-gap-in-your-resume?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;At least once in every interview process you&#39;ll be asked some version of, “Can you walk me through your resume?” In addition to your skills and experience, you need to be able to explain your transitions between jobs, including gaps. This is critical: When you ignore gaps between jobs when discussing your resume, you lose the opportunity to control the narrative about your job transitions or time away from the commercial workforce.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Based on my research of employment gaps for my book, &lt;em>;Wanted → A New Career: The Definitive Playbook for Transitioning to a New Career or Finding Your Dream Job&lt;/em>;, here are five common reasons for work-history gaps — and how to own the gap during the interview process:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Stay-at-home parenting&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you took time off from the commercial workforce &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/helping-stay-at-home-parents-reenter-the-workforce&quot;>;to raise children&lt;/a>;, explain how you used that time to gain skills, knowledge, or experience that&#39;s relevant to the job. For example, did you volunteer at your kids&#39; school? Organize events or fundraising efforts? Were you the parent who arranged travel for sports team activities? All of those things can be translated to the job you&#39;re applying for. For example, say you&#39;re looking to continue your career in global fundraising. You could tell the interviewer, “I took time off to care for our children but I was able to keep my skills fresh while volunteering for the kids&#39; sports league, developing fundraising goals and helping the team successfully achieve fundraising quotas to provide financial assistance for those who needed it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Bereavement or caring for a sick family member&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you took time away to care for a parent or family member, own the choice you made to spend that important time with them. Take a look at that experience through the lens of the job. For example, if you&#39;re trying to move back into a customer service role, you could focus on your role as a liaison with your family member&#39;s health care providers:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I took time off to care for my father. During that time I was able to leverage my effective communication skills with multiple health care providers, as well as my organization skills in coordinating meetings with his financial planner, brokers, and legal representation, which gave him peace of mind. I would like to use those same problem-solving skills plus my ability to remain calm under pressure in this job.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;re applying for a finance job, you could focus on your role as executor:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I took time off to spend with my mother before she passed away. I was named executor because I am highly responsible, organized, and have financial acumen. I was able to leverage my finance skills in reconciling her estate as well as soft skills, such as using effective communication with multiple creditors, including utilities, credit card companies, medical facilities, and banking institutions. My skills enabled me to quickly and efficiently close out the estate, and now I&#39;m looking to bring my skills to a new challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h2>;Traveling the world&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When moving back into a corporate work setting after taking time off to explore, focus on how you used that time to gain new perspectives. For example, if you&#39;re interviewing with a multinational company, you could discuss the nuances of interacting with people from different cultures and how experiencing life in other countries gave you a perspective many people don&#39;t have in the workplace. If you&#39;re pursuing an operational role, you could focus on your efficiency in travel planning, budgeting as it relates to a P&amp;amp;L, and how you used critical thinking to determine where to travel to next. If you spent time learning a second, third, or fourth language, explain how your ability to be conversational or fluent will make you a higher-performing candidate than those who aren&#39;t multilingual.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Going back to school&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Perhaps you went back to school to obtain an MBA or doctorate. If you went to school full time, explain how specific projects you worked on are directly relevant to the job and how they, along with any past work experience, will allow you to bring unique value to the position. Perhaps you achieved an MBA and want to work in business operations. Did you work on projects for real companies? Include them on your resume to so you can discuss them during an interview.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you developed your skills &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/5-ways-to-acquire-new-skills-without-going-back-to-school&quot;>;without going back to school&lt;/a>; for a traditional degree — for example, by taking a course or getting a certification — describe how those skills apply to the prospective job and set you apart from other candidates. If you read specific books to gain a new perspective on your field or enhance your leadership capabilities, talk about how you would apply the principles you learned at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Terminated employment&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you were &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/what-to-do-after-being-laid-off&quot;>;impacted by a mass layoff&lt;/a>; that wasn&#39;t performance related, explain to the interviewer that the business strategy changed and your department or team were let go in the latest wave of layoffs. You can even position the unfortunate situation positively: “But it has been a blessing because I was considering looking for a new challenge.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you were terminated for performance, clearly your employer didn&#39;t think you were successful in your job, but perhaps you have a different perspective or didn&#39;t feel the role was what you expected. In this case, you can explain that the job was different than you believed it to be and didn&#39;t leverage your skills and capabilities in the most effective way. Always explain what you learned from the experience and how you&#39;re actively working to make sure your next move is closer to your expectations. For example:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I knew soon after I started that the job wasn&#39;t as described, but since I committed to the company, I wanted to give it my best effort. In the end, my skills of A, B, and C weren&#39;t being utilized effectively to bring value to the business. So we amicably separated, which is allowing me to take the time to find the right job where I can bring the most value based on business need.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;If you were in a toxic environment or decided to quit for any other reason, don&#39;t bring that negativity into job interviews. Find a positive perspective on why you departed — for example, “I needed focused time to find a job that&#39;s more in line with my values, and I couldn&#39;t find the time to do it while working 60 hours a week.” Most importantly, don&#39;t ever badmouth anyone, because that behavior makes you look like someone who blames others without taking accountability — and who could do the same at the new company. This is the time to take the high road.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Since the pandemic, most employers have been more understanding and less discriminating regarding resume gaps — but you have to be ready to explain the gaps clearly, confidently, and without stumbling. Owning your career trajectory means connecting all the dots for the recruiter and hiring manager. Shaping the narrative around any gaps yourself will help make them a non-issue.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[13 Principles for Using AI Responsibly]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_30_200245321-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Boris SV/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The competitive nature of AI development poses a dilemma for organizations, as prioritizing speed may lead to neglecting ethical guidelines, bias detection, and safety measures. Known and emerging concerns associated with AI in the workplace include the spread of misinformation, copyright and intellectual property concerns, cybersecurity, data privacy, as well as navigating rapid and ambiguous regulations. To mitigate these risks, we propose thirteen principles for responsible AI at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/13-principles-for-using-ai-responsibly?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Love it or loath it, the rapid expansion of AI will not slow down anytime soon. But AI blunders &lt;a href=&quot;https://cmr.berkeley.edu/2022/01/the-reputational-risks-of-ai/&quot;>;can quickly damage a brand&#39;s reputation&lt;/a>; — just ask Microsoft&#39;s first chatbot, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2016/3/24/11297050/tay-microsoft-chatbot-racist&quot;>;Tay&lt;/a>;. In the tech race, all leaders fear being left behind if they slow down while others don&#39;t. It&#39;s a high-stakes situation where cooperation seems risky, and defection tempting. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://heritage.umich.edu/stories/the-prisoners-dilemma/&quot;>;“prisoner&#39;s dilemma”&lt;/a>; (as it&#39;s called in game theory) poses risks to responsible AI practices. Leaders, prioritizing speed to market, are driving the current AI arms race in which major corporate players are rushing products and potentially &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies-cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;short-changing critical considerations&lt;/a>; like ethical guidelines, bias detection, and safety measures. For instance, major tech corporations are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/03/30/tech-companies-cut-ai-ethics/&quot;>;laying off their AI ethics teams&lt;/a>; precisely at a time when responsible actions are needed most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s also important to recognize that the AI arms race extends beyond the developers of large language models (LLMs) such as OpenAI, Google, and Meta. It encompasses many companies utilizing LLMs to support their own custom applications. In the world of professional services, for example, PwC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/pwcs-4000-legal-staffers-get-ai-assistant-law-chatbots-gain-steam-2023-03-15/&quot;>;announced&lt;/a>; it is deploying AI chatbots for 4,000 of their lawyers, distributed across 100 countries. These AI-powered assistants will “help lawyers with contract analysis, regulatory compliance work, due diligence, and other legal advisory and consulting services.” PwC&#39;s management is also considering expanding these AI chatbots into their tax practice. In total, the consulting giant plans to pour $1 billion into “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bcg.com/x/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai&quot;>;generative AI&lt;/a>;” — a powerful new tool capable of delivering game-changing boosts to performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a similar vein, KPMG launched its own AI-powered assistant, dubbed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afr.com/companies/professional-services/custom-chatgpt-tool-to-help-kpmg-s-consultants-win-new-work-20230321-p5cu3m&quot;>;KymChat&lt;/a>;, which will help employees rapidly find internal experts across the entire organization, wrap them around incoming opportunities, and automatically generate proposals based on the match between project requirements and available talent. Their &lt;a href=&quot;https://kpmg.com/au/en/home/media/press-releases/2023/03/kpmg-unveils-cutting-edge-private-chatgpt-software-march-2023.html&quot;>;AI assistant&lt;/a>; “will better enable cross-team collaboration and help those new to the firm with a more seamless and efficient people-navigation experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slack is also incorporating generative AI into the development of &lt;a href=&quot;https://slack.com/blog/news/introducing-slack-gpt&quot;>;Slack GPT&lt;/a>;, an AI assistant designed to help employees work smarter not harder. The platform incorporates a range of AI capabilities, such as conversation summaries and writing assistance, to enhance user productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These examples are just the tip of the iceberg. Soon hundreds of millions of Microsoft 365 users will have access to &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/&quot;>;Business Chat&lt;/a>;, an agent that joins the user in their work, striving to make sense of their Microsoft 365 data. Employees can prompt the assistant to do everything from developing status report summaries based on meeting transcripts and email communication to identifying flaws in strategy and coming up with solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This rapid deployment of AI agents is why &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/04/20/ibm-ceo-work-ai-artificial-intelligence-careers-tech-arvind-krishna/&quot;>;Arvind Krishna&lt;/a>;, CEO of IBM, recently wrote that, “[p]eople working together with trusted AI will have a transformative effect on our economy and society … It&#39;s time we embrace that partnership — and prepare our workforces for everything AI has to offer.” Simply put, organizations are experiencing exponential growth in the installation of AI-powered tools and firms that don&#39;t adapt risk getting left behind.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI Risks at Work&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, remaining competitive also introduces significant risk for both employees and employers. For example, a 2022 &lt;a href=&quot;https://unesdoc.unesco.org/ark:/48223/pf0000380861&quot;>;UNESCO publication&lt;/a>; on “the effects of AI on the working lives of women” reports that AI in the recruitment process, for example, is excluding women from upward moves. &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1408.6491&quot;>;One study the report cites&lt;/a>; that included 21 experiments consisting of over 60,000 targeted job advertisements found that “setting the user&#39;s gender to &#39;Female&#39; resulted in fewer instances of ads related to high-paying jobs than for users selecting &#39;Male&#39; as their gender.” And even though this AI bias in recruitment and hiring is well-known, it&#39;s not going away anytime soon. As the UNESCO report goes on to say, “A &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3450077&quot;>;2021 study&lt;/a>; showed evidence of job advertisements skewed by gender on Facebook even when the advertisers wanted a gender-balanced audience.” It&#39;s often a matter of biased data which will continue to infect AI tools and threaten key workforce factors such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raconteur.net/responsible-business/ais-threat-to-diversity-equity-inclusivity/&quot;>;diversity, equity, and inclusion&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Discriminatory employment practices may be only one of a cocktail of legal risks that generative AI exposes organizations to. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bloomberglaw.com/tech-and-telecom-law/openai-hit-with-first-defamation-suit-over-chatgpt-hallucination&quot;>;OpenAI is facing its first defamation lawsuit&lt;/a>; as a result of allegations that ChatGPT produced harmful misinformation. Specifically, the system produced a summary of a real court case which included fabricated accusations of embezzlement against a radio host in Georgia. This highlights the negative impact on organizations for creating and sharing AI generated information. It underscores concerns about LLMs fabricating false and libelous content, resulting in reputational damage, loss of credibility, diminished customer trust, and serious legal repercussions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to concerns related to libel, there are risks associated with &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/generative-ai-has-an-intellectual-property-problem&quot;>;copyright and intellectual property infringements&lt;/a>;. Several &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/27/the-current-legal-cases-against-generative-ai-are-just-the-beginning/&quot;>;high-profile legal cases&lt;/a>; have emerged where the developers of generative AI tools have been sued for the alleged improper use of licensed content. The presence of copyright and intellectual property infringements, coupled with the legal implications of such violations, poses significant risks for organizations utilizing generative AI products. Organizations can improperly use licensed content through generative AI by unknowingly engaging in activities such as plagiarism, unauthorized adaptations, commercial use without licensing, and misusing Creative Commons or open-source content, exposing themselves to potential legal consequences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The large-scale deployment of AI also &lt;a href=&quot;https://siliconangle.com/2023/06/06/new-report-warns-cybersecurity-risks-generative-ai-technology/&quot;>;magnifies the risks of cyberattacks&lt;/a>;. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/opinion/Generative-AI-the-next-biggest-cyber-security-threat&quot;>;fear amongst cybersecurity experts&lt;/a>; is that generative AI could be used to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consent.yahoo.com/v2/collectConsent?sessionId=3_cc-session_e69b334f-36d8-44b0-9f52-93ea6089aa5a&quot;>;identify and exploit vulnerabilities&lt;/a>; within business information systems, given the ability of LLMs to automate coding and bug detection, which could be used by malicious actors to break through security barriers. There&#39;s also the fear of employees accidentally sharing sensitive data with third-party AI providers. A notable instance involves Samsung staff unintentionally &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-generative-ai-tools-like-chatgpt-after-april-internal-data-leak/&quot;>;leaking trade secrets&lt;/a>; through ChatGPT while using the LLM to review source code. Due to their failure to opt out of data sharing, confidential information was inadvertently provided to OpenAI. And even though Samsung and others are taking steps to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2023/05/19/apple-joins-a-growing-list-of-companies-cracking-down-on-use-of-chatgpt-by-staffers-heres-why/&quot;>;restrict the use of third-party AI tools&lt;/a>; on company-owned devices, there&#39;s still the concern that employees can leak information through the use of such systems on personal devices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On top of these risks, businesses will soon have to navigate nascent, varied, and somewhat murky regulations. Anyone hiring in New York City, for instance, will have to ensure their AI-powered recruitment and hiring tech doesn&#39;t violate the City&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/new-york-city-s-automated-employment-6844706/&quot;>;automated employment decision tool&lt;/a>;” law. To comply with the new law, employers will need to take various steps such as conducting third-party bias audits of their hiring tools and publicly disclosing the findings. AI regulation is also scaling up nationally with the Biden-Harris administration&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/ostp/ai-bill-of-rights/&quot;>;Blueprint for an AI Bill of Rights&lt;/a>;” and internationally with the EU&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://artificialintelligenceact.eu/&quot;>;AI Act&lt;/a>;, which will mark a new era of regulation for employers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This growing nebulous of evolving regulations and pitfalls is why thought leaders such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/your-7-biggest-chatgpt-questions-answered&quot;>;Gartner&lt;/a>; are strongly suggesting that businesses “proceed but don&#39;t over pivot” and that they “create a task force reporting to the CIO and CEO” to plan a roadmap for a safe AI transformation that mitigates various legal, reputational, and workforce risks. Leaders dealing with this AI dilemma have important decision to make. On the one hand, there is a pressing competitive pressure to fully embrace AI. However, on the other hand, a growing concern is arising as the implementation of irresponsible AI can result in severe penalties, substantial damage to reputation, and significant operational setbacks. The concern is that in their quest to stay ahead, leaders may unknowingly introduce potential time bombs into their organization, which are poised to cause major problems once AI solutions are deployed and regulations take effect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/06/08/1180838096/an-eating-disorders-chatbot-offered-dieting-advice-raising-fears-about-ai-in-hea&quot;>;National Eating Disorder Association&lt;/a>; (NEDA) recently announced it was letting go of its hotline staff and replacing them with their new chatbot, Tessa. However, just days before making the transition, NEDA discovered that their system was promoting harmful advice such as encouraging people with eating disorders to restrict their calories and to lose one to two pounds per week. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/06/13/1074551/an-algorithm-intended-to-reduce-poverty-in-jordan-disqualifies-people-in-need/&quot;>;World Bank&lt;/a>; spent $1 billion to develop and deploy an algorithmic system, called Takaful, to distribute financial assistance that Human Rights Watch now says ironically creates inequity. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-chatgpt-courts-e15023d7e6fdf4f099aa122437dbb59b&quot;>;two lawyers from New York&lt;/a>; are facing possible disciplinary action after using ChatGPT to draft a court filing that was found to have several references to previous cases that did not exist. These instances highlight the need for well-trained and well-supported employees at the center of this digital transformation. While AI can serve as a valuable assistant, it should not assume the leading position.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Principles for Responsible AI at Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To help decision-makers avoid negative outcomes while also remaining competitive in the age of AI, we&#39;ve devised several principles for a sustainable AI-powered workforce. The principles are a blend of ethical frameworks from institutions like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsf.gov/od/recr.jsp&quot;>;National Science Foundation&lt;/a>; as well as legal requirements related to employee monitoring and data privacy such as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bja.ojp.gov/program/it/privacy-civil-liberties/authorities/statutes/1285&quot;>;Electronic Communications Privacy Act&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecpra.org/&quot;>;California Privacy Rights Act&lt;/a>;. The steps for ensuring responsible AI at work include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Informed Consent. &lt;/strong>;Obtain voluntary and informed agreement from employees to participate in any AI-powered intervention &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; the employees are provided with all the relevant information about the initiative. This includes the program&#39;s purpose, procedures, and potential risks and benefits.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Aligned Interests. &lt;/strong>;The goals, risks, and benefits for both the employer and employee are clearly articulated and aligned.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Opt In &amp;amp; Easy Exits. &lt;/strong>;Employees must opt into AI-powered programs without feeling forced or coerced, and they can easily withdraw from the program at any time without any negative consequences and without explanation.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Conversational Transparency. &lt;/strong>;When AI-based conversational agents are used, the agent should formally reveal any persuasive objectives the system aims to achieve through the dialogue with the employee.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Debiased and Explainable AI. &lt;/strong>;Explicitly outline the steps taken to remove, minimize, and mitigate bias in AI-powered employee interventions—especially for disadvantaged and vulnerable groups—and provide transparent explanations into how AI systems arrive at their decisions and actions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;AI Training and Development. &lt;/strong>;Provide continuous employee training and development to ensure the safe and responsible use of AI-powered tools.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Health and Well-Being. &lt;/strong>;Identify types of AI-induced stress, discomfort, or harm and articulate steps to minimize risks (eg, how will the employer minimize stress caused by constant AI-powered monitoring of employee behavior).&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data Collection. &lt;/strong>;Identify what data will be collected, if data collection involves any invasive or intrusive procedures (eg, the use of webcams in work-from-home situations), and what steps will be taken to minimize risk.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Data. &lt;/strong>;Disclose any intention to share personal data, with whom, and why.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Privacy and Security. &lt;/strong>;Articulate protocols for maintaining privacy, storing employee data securely, and what steps will be taken in the event of a privacy breach.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Third Party Disclosure. &lt;/strong>;Disclose all third parties used to provide and maintain AI assets, what the third party&#39;s role is, and how the third party will ensure employee privacy.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Communication.&lt;/strong>; Inform employees about changes in data collection, data management, or data sharing as well as any changes in AI assets or third-party relationships.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Laws and Regulations. &lt;/strong>;Express ongoing commitment to comply with all laws and regulations related to employee data and the use of AI.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;We encourage leaders to urgently adopt and develop this checklist in their organizations. By applying such principles, leaders can ensure rapid &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; responsible AI deployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make Leadership Positions More Enticing to Primary Care Physicians]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_1293518427.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/The Good Brigade/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the brink of collapse due to historic highs of physician stress, burnout, and exhaustion; mass departures from the profession; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective advocacy to improve primary care on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Healthcare organizations who understand and work to address the issues PCPs face &amp;#8212; and encourage their professional development &amp;#8212; will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-make-leadership-positions-more-enticing-to-primary-care-physicians?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Primary care in the US is being pushed to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://catalyst.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/CAT.23.0029&quot;>;brink of collapse&lt;/a>; due to historic highs of &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-help-primary-care-physicians-craft-sustainable-careers&quot;>;physician stress&lt;/a>;, burnout, and exhaustion; mass &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bostonglobe.com/2023/03/16/metro/months-long-waits-accessing-care-leave-patients-sicker-anguish/&quot;>;departures from the profession&lt;/a>;; and the inability to care for vulnerable populations due to an inequitable health system. These problems are compounded due to a lack of effective &lt;a href=&quot;https://nap.nationalacademies.org/catalog/25983/implementing-high-quality-primary-care-rebuilding-the-foundation-of-health&quot;>;advocacy to improve primary care&lt;/a>; on a national scale and a reimbursement system that chips away at time with patients while keeping primary care physicians (PCPs) on a volume-based hamster wheel. The end result is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/why-is-it-so-challenging-to-find-a-primary-care-physician-202209282822&quot;>;shortage of doctors who want to practice primary care&lt;/a>; under these challenging circumstances, which can lead to potentially devastating consequences for the future of healthcare in America.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If primary care is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/16/opinion/pandemic-recovery-primary-care.html&quot;>;touted as the foundation of a well-functioning health care system&lt;/a>; — the front line of clinical care and the initial point of contact for most patients — how can it be allowed to deteriorate without unified and passionate intervention? Our research suggests that the answer may be straightforward. While primary care accounts for roughly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aamc.org/data-reports/workforce/data/active-physicians-largest-specialties-major-professional-activity-2021&quot;>;one in three&lt;/a>; practicing physicians and is seen as the bedrock of the health care system, it is also the most overlooked and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jabfm.org/content/primary-care-physician-leadership-top-ranked-us-hospitals&quot;>;underrepresented in the realms of health care leadership&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Transformational changes to primary care will require leadership with holistic training, a clear vision, an insider&#39;s perspective, and skin in the game. PCPs are &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/early/2022/05/19/leader-2022-000591.abstract&quot;>;uniquely positioned to lead&lt;/a>; this change. They are the Swiss Army Knives of medicine, offering an increasingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cfp.ca/content/68/11/801&quot;>;rare generalist perspective, requiring strong communication skills, and a community-focused&lt;/a>; approach to care delivery. Not only are they responsible for managing day-to-day concerns for their patients, they also coordinate care across specialties and organizations for those who may have medically complex diagnoses. These clinicians are accustomed to leading teams every day to care for their patients, and must be adaptable, thoughtful, and flexible, given their vast breadth of clinical responsibilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, it is paradoxical that those best poised to lead are often reluctant to do so. In fact, many physicians are not only &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/healthcare-network/2014/sep/01/nhs-leadership-doctors-reluctant-manage-lead&quot;>;reluctant&lt;/a>; but &lt;em>;averse&lt;/em>; to taking on leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We interviewed PCPs in leadership roles to better understand what they believe prevents so many other physicians from pursuing such positions. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.lww.com/jhmonline/Abstract/2022/08000/Engaging_Physicians_in_Leadership__Motivations,.6.aspx&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; highlights three key deterrents:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;PCPs viewed leadership roles as a path to losing autonomy and limiting their ability to develop long-term therapeutic relationships with patients — a key reason many physicians chose careers in medicine in the first place.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs associated leadership roles with major resource constraints, evaporating both time and earnings potential.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;PCPs lamented the loss of camaraderie with other physicians when taking on leadership roles, feeling that the roles interrupted collaboration with peers and generated uncomfortable conflict.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Despite these concerns, PCPs are fundamentally poised to make an impact on the organizations they lead. Health care organizations who understand and work to address these deterrents will have a distinct competitive advantage. They will be able to better engage and recruit PCPs in leadership and thereby reap the benefits of better &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1097/HMR.0000000000000173&quot;>;quality of care, higher patient satisfaction, and decreased provider burnout&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three ways that health organizations can counteract these disincentives and support PCPs embracing leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Provide the On-Ramp&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs crave system change and personal growth, but often feel disempowered. They see their experience as valuable and want to leverage it to make a positive impact on the health care system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can tap into this motivation by framing leadership as a constructive opportunity to be a change agent. While organizations may not have the ability to alter a &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/05/creative-job-titles-can-energize-workers&quot;>;position&#39;s specific title&lt;/a>;, the job description can be used to reflect openness to an entrepreneurial mindset and an opportunity for improving perceived system deficits. Instead of drafting a typical (and often dry) administrative job description, frame it to emphasize how the role will enact change or address major obstacles in health care. Postings should speak to a PCP&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicfootprints.org/7-top-tips-on-recruiting-doctors-to-non-clinical-or-leadership-roles/&quot;>;adaptability based on the breadth of their training and diversity of practice experience&lt;/a>;, and PCPs should be encouraged to apply.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By using the frustration PCPs experience with the status quo and their frontline experience, health care organizations can promote vacant or novel leadership roles as opportunities to expand the impact on patients and to garner a broader scope of knowledge and expertise for PCPs identified as having leadership interest or potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Role Design and Definition&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs want to grow and develop professionally, but our study showed that they also identified clear disadvantages in taking on leadership roles. They identified the least attractive aspect of leading, in a word, as “loss.” They feared the loss of autonomy, time, close patient relationships, and camaraderie with peers. This can be due, in part, to their exposure to disappointing experiences observed in peers who have assumed leadership roles.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Executives and health administrators can help mitigate this with the use of strategic &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/06/why-managers-design-jobs-to-be-more-boring-than-they-need-to-be&quot;>;job design&lt;/a>;, where organizations create an optimal job role, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>;, which allows PCPs to define and customize their role themselves. These two complementary pieces of the puzzle yield large gains in employee satisfaction and fulfillment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When organizations realize that fear of loss is a major barrier, they are better positioned to design purposeful and motivating work for PCPs taking on leadership roles. To address the concern for loss of autonomy, the role should be intentionally constructed to allow PCPs the agency to make decisions per their expertise. For those apprehensive about losing time, the role can be devised to encourage a flexible approach in how goals are achieved, including the freedom to decide how they will balance their clinical responsibilities with their new leadership role. In order to address concerns about losing relationships, organizations must provide opportunities for leaders to meet with their colleagues in informal settings and encourage leaders to continue to be actively engaged as a member of their clinical team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Empowering PCPs to engage in job crafting allows them to adjust aspects of the job to suit individual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-job-crafting-how-to-do-it-work-satisfaction-2022-6&quot;>;interests, values, and passions&lt;/a>;, making them more likely to be&lt;a href=&quot;https://positiveorgs.bus.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/What-is-Job-Crafting-and-Why-Does-it-Matter1.pdf&quot;>; engaged and more likely to thrive&lt;/a>; at work, while being successful in their leadership role. PCPs can independently alter the &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/what-job-crafting-looks-like&quot;>;type and scope of tasks; relationships and with whom they work; and how to think&lt;/a>;, communicate about, or conceive of the job. When PCPs have some degree of ownership and authority over how the job is defined, they will have the opportunity to include more of their passion points, while also thoughtfully reducing those aspects of the job that are seen as pain points.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Tools, Training, and Mentorship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PCPs may want system change and growth, but they also need the tools, training, and mentorship to be successful. In most cases, PCPs &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/most-doctors-have-little-or-no-management-training-and-thats-a-problem&quot;>;aren&#39;t taught finance, accounting, management, or leadership skills&lt;/a>; in medical school, nor is there an emphasis on systems operations, despite the fact that, as physicians enter residency, they immediately begin leading medical teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are stark contrasts, both operationally and culturally, between &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/04/turning-doctors-into-leaders&quot;>;business and medicine&lt;/a>;. Executives and health administrators should provide opportunities for PCPs to cross-train with current administrators and to have access to mentors who can help with the transition. Providing resources to support the transition into leadership can help highly qualified and motivated PCPs avoid the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/robertpearl/2016/02/04/five-reasons-why-even-the-best-of-physicians-may-fail-as-leaders/?sh=1c79323bce22&quot;>;common pitfalls than can derail&lt;/a>; their ability to influence others and be successful in their expanded role. This may include offering or supporting continuing medical education (CME) or credentialing opportunities that feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mgma.com/practice-resources/human-resources/the-importance-of-physician-leadership-education&quot;>;management and leadership skills building&lt;/a>;, partnering with institutions of higher education to create pathways into &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.nejmcareercenter.org/article/eyeing-physician-career-boost-via-formal-business-education/&quot;>;graduate business or policy programs&lt;/a>;, or engaging with organizations that specialize in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.physicianleaders.org/about&quot;>;physician leadership training&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having PCPs in leadership roles has never been more important. Without a highly functioning and sustainable primary care system, all health care in the US will suffer. If we want a system that promotes effective and sustainable primary care, PCPs need to be involved in co-designing that system and leading change. Ultimately, this will benefit the entire health care system, and all of us who will, at any stage of our lives, depend on it for our own care and that of our families and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>