<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Managers Are Burned Out. Here&rsquo;s How to Help Them Recharge.]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_02_1501196141.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;作为领导者中的领导者，您“创造天气”；为您的团队。你的工作不仅是支持精疲力尽的领导者，还要防止他们继续精疲力尽。在本文中，作者提供了六种策略来帮助团队中精疲力尽的管理者重新充电：1）认识并承认他们的倦怠； 2）创造面对面和虚拟的个人联系机会； 3）重新评估、重新确定优先顺序并重新分配工作； 4) 修改关于如何协同工作的团队协议； 5）定期与领导进行一对一的接触； 6) 与团队成员设定期望，让他们利用所有假期时间——当有很多事情要做时，很容易推迟或跳过假期。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href= &quot;/2023/08/managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08 /managers-are-burned-out-heres-how-to-help-them-recharge?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;您组织中的经理很可能&lt;a href =&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;感觉精疲力竭&lt;/a>;。中层管理人员感到必须从上层执行战略，同时指导和发展其下属的团队，从而感到压力——通常无法从更高级的管理人员那里获得相同类型的发展或授权。他们往往资源不足，经常卷起袖子与团队一起工作，特别是考虑到过去几年的人员流动率较高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/podcast/2023/07/麦肯锡的研究&lt;/a>;显示，除了管理职责外，一些中层管理人员每周最多花两天时间进行个人贡献者工作，每周花一天时间进行行政任务。太多的工作，再加上太少的时间和资源，导致许多经理精疲力竭，他们几乎&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/more-than-50-of-managers-feel-burned-out&quot;>;两倍根据微软的研究，&lt;/a>; 他们更有可能离开雇主。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;职业倦怠不仅仅只是因为疲劳或压力——因此，从中恢复并不是一个快速的解决办法。不仅需要时间、意图和组织支持才能重新获得平衡感，而且还要再次感到精力充沛、投入和积极主动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可以肯定的是，每个人的倦怠经历都会&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/your-burnout-is-unique-your-recovery-will-be-too&quot;>;不同&lt;/a>;，因此解决这个问题的各种方法会对它们产生不同的影响。同样，也没有灵丹妙药。采用包括以下策略在内的多管齐下的方法将有助于您的经理完成职业倦怠恢复之旅。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;认识&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;此策略有两个方面。首先，认识到并关心一个人正在经历倦怠，可以帮助他们感到被关注、被理解，甚至被关心。承认倦怠也可以将其摆到桌面上，以便解决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第二个方面是认可经理的持续努力以及对业务的积极贡献或影响。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.work human.com/resources/reports-guides/from-thank-you-to-thriving-work human-gallup-report?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_campaign=2023q2_wh_sem_nb_awareness_secondary_na_phr_pros&amp;amp ;utm_content=workers_burnout&amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwv8qkBhAnEiwAkY-ahmQoboWxnUHCOMtoK16gZ4GmZrzXKVd2RIKjn2OYTEAWhGeyBUPOBBoC3ZgQAvD_BwE&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;超过 12,0 00 员工、Workman 和盖洛普显示员工认可度和幸福感之间存在很强的正相关关系，这也带来了更好的结果业务成果。此外，这种认可可以向个人表明他们正在做出改变，特别是当他们的影响可能对他们来说不那么明显时。这可以帮助他们克服工作效率下降的感觉，减少他们的愤世嫉俗或与工作的心理距离，并从他们的工作中获得更多的意义。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“当我们花时间去认识别人时，它不仅具有对他们和我们自己都有积极的影响。”员工赞赏和工作场所文化专家克里斯托弗·利特菲尔德 (Christopher Littlefield) 分享道。 “关注进展顺利、庆祝进步以及分享工作影响的行为有助于我们产生意义、希望和归属感——所有这些都可以促进幸福。这可以很简单，只需花五分钟写一封&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/how-to-write-a-meaningful-thank-you-note&quot;>;有意义的感谢信&lt;/a>;，给快速&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/how-to-give-and-receive-compliments-at-work&quot;>;赞美&lt;/a>;，甚至使用反思性识别。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;重新联系&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在管理者之间创造个人联系（无论是面对面还是虚拟）的机会，可以消除倦怠中常见的孤立感，特别是对于那些远程工作的人来说。创造一种社区意识，让管理者可以与同事分享他们的挑战（和成功），不仅可以促进支持，还可以减少倦怠带来的孤立感，并创造一种“在一起”的感觉。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;同样，在手头的工作之外进行一对一的联系也很有效，并且对某些人来说可能更有意义。 “拿起电话向同事汇报情况可以帮助提醒别人，你在他们身边，”工作场所归属感主题演讲者亚当·斯迈利·波斯沃尔斯基 (Adam Smiley Poswolsky) 分享道。 “与一段时间没有联系的同事重新联系可以为他们提供能量和灵感，尤其是当他们在压力或倦怠中挣扎时。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Poswolsky 补充道：“一个简单的善举 —就像记住同事的生日，或者给同事买他们最喜欢的咖啡一样，会让人们有归属感。当我们在工作中&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/01/the-little-things-that-make-employees-feel-appreciated&quot;>;为人际关系提供更多的时间和空间&lt;/a>;时，我们就会正常化谈论完整的员工关系。人类情绪的范围很广，其中倦怠是最常见的一种。当我们正常化谈论倦怠、压力或孤独时，我们可以帮助人们减少孤独感，从而帮助他们感觉更好。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;重新评估、重新确定优先顺序和重新-分配工作&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当管理者感到精疲力竭时，很可能在很大程度上是由于工作量过多、持续不断，并且随着新的优先事项出现，现有项目的优先级并没有降低。一切都变得很重要，并留在他们的盘子里，使工作量变得不可持续。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对您的经理每个人的工作内容以及占用他们大部分时间的内容进行审核。确定对实现组织目标最有影响的三个领域。将经理的精力集中在这些方面，而不是优先考虑其余的事情。在此过程中，确定哪些内容可以暂时搁置，哪些截止日期可以延长，或者哪些内容可以完全取消。同样，&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/managers-adjust-your-expectations-without-lowering-the-bar&quot;>;重新评估&lt;/a>;某些工作产品或指标所需的细节或质量水平&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为重新评估的一部分，请花时间了解每个人的工作量和能力以及&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/08/help-your-team-achieve-work-life-balance -even-when-you-cant&quot;>;根据需要重新分配工作&lt;/a>;。此外，将此作为一种常规做法，以帮助您的经理持续重新评估和管理优先事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然您无法在一天中创造更多时间，但您可以调整范围工作量与可用资源（即人员、时间和预算）相称，或主张提供更多资源，例如雇用更多人员的预算或聘请外部承包商分担工作量，即使只是暂时管理高峰&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;修改团队协议&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;授权团队中的经理通过修改有关大家如何合作的协议来帮助解决倦怠问题。您和您团队的经理可以同意尊重哪些界限？这可能包括不发送晚上或周末电子邮件或避免其他&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/dont-let-micro-stresses-burn-you-out?autocomplete=true&quot;>;微压力&lt;/a>; 。通过制定新规范来寻找更好的共同前进之路，有助于建立一种在精疲力竭的情况下经常缺失的代理感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一个团队，您可以决定如何让彼此负责等事情遵守各自的承诺，允许对方推迟或拒绝，并确定特定的非会议日来开展重点工作。达成此类协议可以减少浪费的时间、精力和挫败感，并为他们的未来体验创造一种授权感和主人翁感。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;定期签到&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ h2>; &lt;p>;定期与您的经理进行一对一的接触，尤其是那些表现出倦怠迹象的经理。查看他们的表现以及您如何才能最好地支持他们。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/ask-your-team-what-are-you-stuck-on&quot;>;询问他们遇到的困难&lt;/a>;。让他们在感到&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/how-to-deal-with-constantly-feeling-overwhelmed&quot;>;不知所措&lt;/a>;时可以安全地大声说出并告诉您，以便你们可以讨论如何通过适当地清除障碍或把事情从他们的盘子上移开来减轻他们的工作负担。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;放松并重置&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;虽然单独不足以从倦怠中恢复过来，从工作中进行一次有意义的休息来减压是恢复经理能量水平并帮助他们在精神和身体上重新调整的必要步骤。设定期望，让他们&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-take-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot;>;利用所有假期时间&lt;/a>;——这很容易被推迟或者当有很多事情要做时&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/thinking-of-skipping-vacation-dont&quot;>;跳过假期&lt;/a>;。现实是，总会有更多事情要做，所以试着等到你感觉&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/youre-never-going-to-be-caught-up- at-work-stop-feeling-guilty-about-it&quot;>;忙于工作&lt;/a>;就像跑一场没有终点线的马拉松。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，通过休假&lt;a href= “/2017/08/what-one-company-learned-from-forcing-employees-to-use-ir-vacation-time&quot;>;强制&lt;/a>;，您可以帮助抵制组织文化中可能存在的任何战士心态是导致倦怠的一个因素。这可以在团队成员之间以交错的方式完成，以避免业务中断，或者某些组织选择在一年中的特定几周内完全关闭。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论您采取哪种方法，都要允许您的员工完全拔掉电源。当他们不在的时候，为你的团队树立榜样。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/07/dont-work-on-vacation-seriously&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，在休息时间工作（遗憾的是，三分之二的美国人这样做）会降低内在动力，从而如果一个人一开始就精疲力竭，他的人生就已经处于低谷。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;治疗倦怠的方法不是一劳永逸的单一解决方案，也不是万能的。随着时间的推移，结合使用上述策略不仅可以为精疲力尽的领导者提供支持和充电，还可以防止他们继续精疲力尽。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A More Ethical Approach to Employing Contractors]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/a-more-ethical-approach-to-employing-contractors]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_02_645973167.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;对于公司来说，将劳动力外包给第三方的做法变得很有吸引力：他们可以获得经过预先筛选的灵活劳动力，并且能够卸载合法就业对其他人的责任。这一引人注目的机会已远远超出科技领域，扩展到医疗保健和物流等行业。不幸的是，这种劳动力模式对工人和公司来说都是有代价的。雇主有一种方法可以在不让工人受到伤害的情况下将责任外包出去——以及他们自己增加的责任&amp;#8212;采取六大支柱：1) 所有工人都应获得足以维持家庭生活的工资和福利，2) 同工同酬，3) 提供工作场所安全协议并给予工人发言权，4) 要求公平采购，5) 提供途径全职就业，6) 透明。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/a-more-ethical -approach-to-employing-contractors?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/a-more-ethical-approach-to-employing-contractors?language= pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;2022 年 11 月 3 日星期四，成千上万的 Twitter 员工不知道他们早上是否能找到工作。那些被推特直接聘用的人醒来时会收到一封电子邮件，里面要么是新的任务，要么是遣散费。但像梅丽莎·英格尔这样的合同工却一无所获。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;英格尔受雇在 Twitter 处理政治错误信息，努力确保中期选举不会受到机器人和恶作剧的影响。她和她的合同工同事赶紧检查收件箱中是否有决定电子邮件，但他们从未收到过。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;梅丽莎随后试图在接下来的一周专注于她的工作，在接下来的几天里解决错误信息到了 2022 年中期选举，她一直在想那一天是否会是她在公司的最后一天。 11 月 12 日星期六，当 Ingle 与女儿和朋友在商场时，她收到一条通知，上面写着“您的一个或多个访问令牌已被撤销”。她尝试打开工作电子邮件和 Slack，却收到一条通知：“不存在这样的用户”。梅丽莎就是这样被解雇的。没有开会讨论这个问题，甚至没有一封电子邮件——她就被删除了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/07/05/tech-layoffs- Contract-temp-workers/&quot;>;梅丽莎的经历并非独一无二&lt;/a>;。据估计，仅在加利福尼亚州，&lt;a href=&quot;https://americanstaffing.net/research/fact-sheets-analysis-staffing-industry-trends/staffing-statistics-by-state/&quot;>;每年就有近 200 万人&lt;/a >;&lt;a href=&quot;https://americanstaffing.net/research/fact-sheets-analysis-staffing-industry-trends/staffing-statistics-by-state/&quot;>;人们&lt;/a>;通常是合同工与直接雇用的同行做同样的工作，但工资更低，福利更差，保护也更少。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于公司来说，将劳动力外包给第三方的做法变得有吸引力：他们获得预先筛选的、灵活的劳动力劳动力以及将合法就业的责任转移给其他人的能力。这一引人注目的机会已远远超出科技领域，扩展到医疗保健和物流等行业。人力资源服务公司 Gusto 发现，其平台上使用合同工的雇主数量&lt;a href=&quot;https://gusto.com/company-news/us-contract-work-2022-survey&quot;>;已自疫情爆发以来增加了 28%&lt;/a>;，平均公司的合同工与普通员工的比例接近 1 比 5。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，这种劳动力模式的对工人和公司来说都是成本。我们的研究表明，合同工——&lt;a href=&quot;https://contractwork.techequitycollaborative.org/&quot;>;更有可能是黑人、原住民、拉丁裔、女性和非二元性别&lt;/a>;——经常做同样的事情与直接受雇的同事一样工作，但赚的钱更少，领取的福利更少，而且工作不稳定。这种动态不仅让合同工受到伤害，也让公司面临一些巨大的风险。最初被认为是减少公司持续财务责任的系统，外包已成为一种法律、财务和声誉责任。法院和监管机构越来越多地发现，当工人受到伤害时，雇主应对这种伤害承担责任——无论他们是否是直接雇主。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;雇主有一种方法可以在不暴露工人的情况下承担责任。伤害——以及他们自己增加的责任。通过实施负责任的合同标准，确保工人享有基本保护和获得机会的途径，雇主可以降低他们的风险。实施这些标准还可以通过释放合格的多元化人才库来实现多样性、公平和包容性承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为我们在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techequitycollaborative.org 的研究的一部分/&quot;>;TechEquity Collaborative&lt;/a>;，我们创建了负责任的合同标准，作为公司实施明确、高标准合同实践的蓝图，使工人和公司都受益。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;危害和风险合同工&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;1996 年，长期服务的“临时”合同工起诉微软，要求其获得如果被归类为直接雇员的话可以获得的福利。工人们辩称，与直接雇员履行相同的工作职能并为相同的经理工作，他们有权获得相同的报酬。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/archive/business/2000/12/13/microsoft-to-settle-with-temp-workers/6f59576a-0725-4bea-93cc-3e2d759bda45/&quot;>;微软2000 年，该诉讼达成和解&lt;/a>;，此案为科技公司提供了从那时起如何处理合同工与直接雇佣之间的分离的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司已建立（通常很脆弱）防火墙和流程来避免分类合同工作为雇员——要求他们使用不同颜色的徽章进入大楼，禁止他们使用内部系统，禁止他们参加年度假日聚会等全员活动。同时，许多合同工的绩效管理和日常职责都由科技公司直接控制。与此同时，在微软诉讼之后，许多公司将他们的合同设计成不断旋转的门：员工从一份初始合同开始，通常为期六个月，而他们的经理则以重复的、较短的增量延长他们的工作时间。这些合同可以随时取消或不续签，使工人始终处于不稳定状态。这些工人中的许多人都处于这种短期无保障合同延期的模式长达两年，期间他们被迫休息，以免公司违反微软和解协议中规定的直接雇员资格标准。一旦他们离开公司长达六个月，他们中的许多人就会被重新雇佣，重新开始这个过程，暴露了他们是“临时”员工的闹剧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不仅是合同他们自己脱节了，但他们所从事的工作也是脱节的。合同工常常陷入双重管理结构的中间：他们的日常工作由母公司的经理监督，而他们的雇佣运作方面——处理工资、管理福利和处理工作场所投诉——则由母公司的经理监督。雇用他们的人事代理机构的职权范围。与合同工保持一定距离——无论是因为无法接触公司人力资源、内部工具和信息，还是职业发展——都会造成沟通渠道漏洞、权力失衡以及潜在的工人伤害。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;不幸的是，种族和性别不平等加剧了合同工作的不稳定（及其给公司带来的风险）。在科技行业，我们发现&lt;a href=&quot;https://contractwork.techequitycollaborative.org/&quot;>;合同工和临时工更有可能是黑人、原住民、拉丁裔、女性和非二元性别&lt;/a>;在直接就业的劳动力中。对伊利诺伊州蓝领工作临时工作的研究发现&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-temporary-staffing-agcies-racial-discrimination-20210223-34sof3i56rhjxhzu42xtcshx44-story。 html&quot;>;黑人和拉丁裔工人占芝加哥蓝领临时工作的 85%&lt;/a>;，但只占人口的 40%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有这些潜在危害，因种族和性别而更加复杂不平等，造成潜在的法律责任。如果一名工人遭受伤害——无论是工资和工时违规、骚扰、歧视还是充满敌意的工作环境——并决定针对这种伤害寻求补救措施，公司不一定能摆脱困境，即使他们辩称自己没有受到伤害。工人的合法雇主。法院和监管机构越来越多地发现这些公司与人才中介机构是共同雇主，因此应对合同工遭受的任何违法行为或伤害承担责任。过去五年来，科技行业发生了多起引人注目的此类动态实例。&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;2021 年，Meta 同意&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.saverilawfirm. com/our-cases/facebook-content-moderators-safe-workplace-litigation/#:~:text=viewing%20objectionable%20conduct.-,The%20award%20also%20builtes%20a%20%2452%20million%20fund% 20for%20ongoing,financial%20compensation%20for%20content%20moderators.&quot;>;向内容版主支付 5200 万美元&lt;/a>;，这些内容版主是通过第三方人才中介机构聘用的，负责审查从儿童色情到自杀和兽交等令人不安的内容，而无需支付任何费用采取适当的健康和安全措施。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;在针对 Riot Games 的集体诉讼中，法官裁定合同工应纳入 2021 年&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost. com/video-games/2021/12/27/riot-discrimination-100-million-settlement/&quot;>;针对遭遇工作场所性别歧视和骚扰的 1 亿美元和解金&lt;/a>;。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;动视暴雪 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2022/03/29/1089577389/judge-activision-blizzard-settlement- Sex-harassment&quot;>;支付了 1800 万美元的和解金&lt;/a>;，以惩罚女性工人，包括直接员工和合同工，以及性骚扰和怀孕歧视。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;不采用高端合同做法的公司会造成逐底竞争，降低工作质量和职业流动性。制定高标准做法，并要求与您公司合作的任何供应商采取这些做法，有助于首先减轻工人受到伤害的可能性，从而有助于减少未来的责任和风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;前进之路：负责任的合同标准&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;简单地说，避免工人伤害责任的最佳方法是首先减少伤害的可能性。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://techequitycollaborative.org/download-responsible-contracting-standard/&quot;>;责任承包标准&lt;/a>;提供了公司可以采取的六种明确途径，以减少工人伤害、降低企业风险并关闭工作场所合同工的股权差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;维持家庭的工资&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这一点非常简单 - 所有工人都应该获得维持家庭的工资和福利。通过明确您期望承包机构向合同工支付多少工资，您​​可以确保合同工获得足以维持家庭生活的工资——通常根本不需要提高您的合同预算。其他最佳实践包括要求人事代理机构提供维持家庭的福利、可预测的时间表、合同续签时的清晰沟通等等。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;同工同酬&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;所有现有研究表明与全职雇员从事相同工作的合同工的工资往往较低。您可以通过以下方式确保同工同酬：提供透明且响应迅速的加薪和晋升系统、要求职介机构报告薪资数据、将薪资与全职员工进行比较以及实施公平的招聘做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 >;工作场所安全协议和工人的声音&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;合同工经常面临选择，是大声说出工作场所的问题还是取消合同。建立清晰的报告问题渠道以及让合同工参与全公司的沟通流程，可以对直接员工和合同工等员工的工作场所士气做出积极贡献。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;公平采购&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一次性合同与全职劳动力相比，工人可能会遇到薪资差距，因为人事代理机构从合同中抽取的费用比您讨价还价的要高。通常，公司认为他们雇用合同工的速度与团队中其他员工相同，却没有意识到人才中介机构会大幅削减工资。要求人才中介机构披露他们的“加价”费用或工人的工资率可以帮助提高流程透明度，并帮助您的公司避免不公平的薪酬结构，而不必增加您的总体成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;直接就业的途径&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;有色人种合同工，尤其是黑人工人，更有可能经历过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.americanprogress.org/article/elimination-black-white-wealth-gap- Generational -挑战/&quot;>;积累财富的结构性障碍&lt;/a>;。解决职业隔离问题的一种方法是提供从合同职位到公司全职职位的有意义的途径。一些最佳实践包括允许员工在简历中分享他们为贵公司工作的经验、授予进入内部招聘委员会的权限、终止合同工的竞业禁止协议以及提供专业发展培训。通过打造真正的职业流动机会，您的公司可以利用经过资格预审的多元化人才库，这不仅可以提高公平性，还可以降低招聘成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;透明度&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;展示您的人才通过负责任的合同透明，体现公司对股东、员工和公众的价值观和承诺。衡量供应商对这些实践的采用情况、审核标准的实施情况以及直接与员工进行核对以了解更多有关他们的经验 - 所有这些都有助于确保您雇用的人才中介机构正确应用您的书面政策。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•••&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;负责任的签约不仅仅涉及风险缓解。除了作为固有商业价值的“做正确的事”之外，负责任的承包是一项吸引和培养人才、提高员工士气、产生回报和提升品牌的投资。前期投资将帮助您的公司实现包容性承诺并获得收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Pandemic Changed Marketing Channels]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Adrià Voltà 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;疫情无疑改变了营销人员实施渠道策略的方式，并且没有单一的成功途径。由于渠道比以往任何时候都多，营销人员需要确定哪些渠道可以增加明显的价值，而忘记其他渠道。进入某个渠道可能很诱人，因为那里有你的竞争对手。但由于客户时间和注意力有限，营销人员必须战略性地确定他们可以在哪些渠道中产生最大的影响。作者研究了从 CMO 调查中收集到的五种大流行后渠道策略，并分析了营销人员如何运用这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how-the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/how- the-pandemic-changed-marketing-channels?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 大流行促使公司快速适应和响应新的客户需求。这种动态最明显的方式之一是公司为与客户互动并向客户销售产品而采用的营销渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，发生了什么变化？最新版本的&lt;a href=&quot;https://cmosurvey.org/results/&quot;>;CMO 调查&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;从 314 位美国营销领导者那里收集到了五个主要趋势。我们还提供分析和建议，帮助营销人员落实这些趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;渠道正在扩大。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;近三分之二 (61%) 的公司表示增加了他们使用的渠道数量。虽然 B2B 和 B2C 公司都如此，但 B2C 服务领先，77% 的公司表示有所增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;渠道扩张的一个好处是，消费者现在可以选择自己喜欢的与公司互动的方式。然而，拓展渠道需要大量的努力和投资。在介入之前，营销团队应该问：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;新渠道是否会吸引新客户进入该类别，从竞争对手那里抢走现有客户，还是增加现有客户的钱包份额？&lt;/li>; &lt; li>;从品牌和客户体验的角度来看，更多的渠道是否一致？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;接触点是否指向相同的利益和品牌形象？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;渠道是否无缝连接？&lt; /li>; &lt;li>;客户是否了解他们通过使用不同渠道获得的价值以及如何在这些渠道之间轻松移动？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;面对面 (F2F) 渠道仍然存在好吧。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;只有 6.7% 的公司表示他们的 F2F 渠道已完全数字化，这意味着大多数公司仍保持 F2F。此外，28% 的公司正在开设新的 F2F 渠道。&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;鉴于公司和市场的数字化转型，我们预计 F2F 渠道将大幅减少。我们认为渠道持续存在的原因有三个。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，消费者&lt;a href=&quot;https://siteefy.com/how-many-ads-do-we-see-a-day/ &quot;>;每天&lt;/a>;接触 5,000 到 10,000 个广告。这种数字混乱很难渗透，因此保持面对面的方式可能会为营销人员提供不同的方式来接触消费者并实现突破。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，消费者表示，由于使用的应用程序数量和屏幕交互次数过多，他们感到数字疲劳。 an average day — a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lxahub.com/stories/what-is-digital-event-fatigue-and-how-can-marketers-avoid-it&quot;>;level&lt;/a>; that has increased by more than 100% during the pandemic. As a result, we suspect that many people are craving human interactions from their all-consuming digital lives. Consumers also &lt;a href=&quot;https://escp.eu/news/why-consumers-seek-refuge-products-branded-authentic-pandemic-and-post-pandemic-era&quot;>;want more authenticity&lt;/a>;, a natural response to the risk and uncertainty of the last three years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, many companies view F2F channels, such as brick-and-mortar stores, as labs for learning about consumer behaviors. They&#39;re leveraging advanced technology, such as IoT-connected merchandise and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/customer-footfall-analysis-why-important-geoiq-io/&quot;>;footfall analyses&lt;/a>;, to learn more about what customers want and how they behave during the journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We did, however, observe several differences in our sample that may be useful in diagnosing the need for F2F channels in your industry. Product companies are less likely to go fully digital and are more likely to report opening new F2F channels (31%) compared to services companies (22%). Only pure-play internet companies are not opening F2F channels. New F2F channels are most prevalent in the real estate, retail, and communications/media sectors and least likely in health care, pharma/biotech, and technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Brand social media use is expanding. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Nearly half (45%) of companies are now using social channels to sell products and services, and (61.5%) of B2C services companies are. In this sector, real estate firms (100%), communications/media companies (82%), and retailers/wholesalers (70%) lead the pack.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Social media companies such as Snapchat, Facebook, and Instagram achieved record-high e-commerce sales during the first year of the pandemic. Instagram&#39;s rollout of in-app checkout in 2020 may have accelerated this process, opening the door to reach more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/183585/instagram-number-of-global-users/&quot;>;1.2 billion&lt;/a>; users scrolling their social feeds. Furthermore, the ease of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.hootsuite.com/how-social-commerce-is-reshaping-customer-experience/#Social_channels_are_the_new_storefronts&quot;>;social messaging&lt;/a>; allows marketers to engage in real time with customers to answer questions. In 2022, more than half of US adults &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.insiderintelligence.com/insights/social-commerce-brand-trends-marketing-strategies/&quot;>;purchased&lt;/a>; something through a social media channel, and a Sprout Social &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/data/social-shopping-2022/&quot;>;survey&lt;/a>; found 98% expected to use this channel to make a purchase in the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take the example of Scrub Daddy, which has established a cheeky TikTok personality and collaborated with up-and-coming social media influencers, resulting in billions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foodandwine.com/scrub-daddy-review-trend-7483598#:~:text=Designed%20to%20make%20the%20often,3%20billion%20views%20on%20TikTok.&quot;>;views&lt;/a>; and millions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90756764/how-to-find-tiktok-influencers-scrub-daddy&quot;>;followers&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizjournals.com/philadelphia/news/2022/02/21/how-viral-tiktok-fame-propelling-scrub-daddy-100m.html&quot;>;online sales&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When we think about brands on social media, we tend to envision B2C brands. Indeed, those companies are more likely to sell their products and services on social channels (58%) compared to B2B brands (37%). However, there is a place for B2B companies in this world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take the case of &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1525/cmr.2014.56.3.142?casa_token=cu8dtuoZwScAAAAA:dv3SkiOmyT4Vr0cgFpqQlEI8v_hFu0w9ij_uacVoe61fl5egMUdQnKhWj3py-wCL1w2d1ioAWetWakc&quot;>;Maersk&lt;/a>;, the Danish shipping company, which launched a social media campaign more than a decade ago to build its brand reputation. Managers were surprised to find that 22% of its 850,000 Facebook followers were actual customers (even though Maersk was not yet selling shipping services online). Leveraging this channel for feedback and follow-up sales was a natural next step for the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, it has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/linkedin-statistics/&quot;>;reported&lt;/a>; that 89% of B2B marketers turn to LinkedIn to generate leads. These numbers are encouraging and we expect they will only increase as younger, social media-savvy consumers move into management positions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The D2C revolution has begun. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Almost a quarter (24%) of companies added a direct-to-customer (D2C) channel in 2023. B2C product companies led the charge with 41% of brands adopting this channel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Why are brands moving into D2C channels? First and most importantly, D2C allows companies to gather valuable firsthand insights into customer online behavior and needs — an opportunity companies in certain sectors, such as consumer packaged goods (CPG), have historically lacked. This first-party data is more important than ever given growing privacy restrictions on access to third-party data around the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, D2C lets companies test new strategies and collect valuable feedback. If used wisely, this type of experimentation should yield more effective and efficient strategies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, D2C means companies can control the customer experience with the brand. This is especially important for premium and unique brands that deliver their benefits, in part, through the channels experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given these reasons, we weren&#39;t surprised to find that 55% of CPG companies report adding D2C. B2C services made the biggest leap — up from 15% in 2022 to 45% in 2023.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tesla has fully embraced the D2C revolution. The company sells its vehicles directly to customers through its online platform and national network of retail stores in major urban centers in US By bypassing traditional car dealerships, Tesla is able to control the sales experience (and markups), which most consumers find unpleasant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies should consider two important factors before entering this space. First, does the company have a robust &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adroll.com/blog/what-is-d2c-and-why-does-it-matter#:~:text=A%20Better%20Connection%20With%20Customers&amp;amp;text=By%20offering%20a%20more%20streamlined,loyalty%20and%20encourage%20repeat%20business.&quot;>;digital&lt;/a>; footprint in place to analyze and execute D2C strategies? This is important considering D2C models&#39; reliance on digital marketing, social media, and data analytics skills to deliver positive returns. Also, does the brand have customer-service structures ready to handle the likely increase in customer interactions from this direct channel?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To prevent partners from moving direct to consumers, we recommend distributors and other intermediaries provide value-added services in marketing, inventory, or logistics. Sharing customer data and analytics can also foster long-lasting and mutually beneficial partnerships between organizations. Another powerful partnership strategy is to leverage cross-category perspectives to share recommendations with key partners for new products, in-store advertising and promotion strategies, and even potential acquisition targets. The point is: provide value!&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gamification is underutilized. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Gamifying shopping and other customer interactions via rewards, points, competitions, or other similar fun interactions is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/PressReleases/gamification.asp&quot;>;expected&lt;/a>; to grow from $9.1B in 2020 to $30.7B in 2025 — a 237% increase.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite this, only 4.8% of marketers integrated gamification into digital channels to sell. B2C product companies (13%) and companies with sales of $10 billion or higher (23%) are outpacing other sectors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large-scale research of the effect of gamification on brand outcomes has not been performed. However, practitioner &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/growth-marketing-and-sales/our-insights/coping-with-the-big-switch-how-paid-loyalty-programs-can-help-bring-consumers-back-to-your-brand&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; has shown that loyalty programs do increase the likelihood that customers will choose the brand over competitors, pay higher prices, and increase their spending levels. Gamification, we suspect, is only likely to heighten these effects. Given this, we think this low percentage is a missed opportunity for many companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The key to making gamification work is brand fit – the game has to make sense given the brand&#39;s position and associations. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webpronews.com/business-leveraging-gamification/&quot;>;Fitbit&lt;/a>;&#39;s exercise milestones and friendly competitions help consumers gain more benefits from their devices and increase the likelihood they&#39;ll buy more products and recommend them to their friends. The game also needs to be engaging, but low-cost or free. If either of these elements are missing, current and potential customers will not play. Therefore, marketers must understand what motivates and delights their customers and use small-scale experiments to test different approaches to assess these costs and benefits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Gamification is more daunting for B2B companies. Our findings show only 1% of B2B companies are using this strategy, compared to 13% of B2C companies. Using gamification with employees who serve B2B customers, including your salesforce, is perhaps the easiest way to begin the process. Another option is to introduce gamification during webinars that are generally somewhat boring. This may provide a way to keep attending prospects paying closer attention to sales pitches.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate and Deploy New Channels Strategically &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The pandemic undoubtedly changed how marketers approach channel strategy, and there is no single route to success. With more channels than ever, marketers need to map which channels add clear value and forget the rest. It can be tempting to enter a channel because your competitors are there. But with limited customer time and attention, marketers must strategically determine in which channels they can have the greatest impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:55:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Using AI to Build Stronger Connections with Customers]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_01_1500238081.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As companies learn to use generative AI to create value, there&amp;#8217;sa risk that they take the wrong approach when applying the technology to the customer experience. In fact, research shows AI can help boost customer satisfaction when it&amp;#8217;s used to offer customers more personalized solutions or to help human employees provide better service than they would without the technological assist. Some examples of companies experiencing early success with this are in the financial services industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/using-ai-to-build-stronger-connections-with-customers?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The surge of generative artificial intelligence (AI) applications is spurring exciting innovations and consumer experiments, but it also worries many people who are concerned about data privacy or only being able to communicate with a company through a bot. These concerns are especially acute in industries where customer interactions and data privacy are critical, such as banking or healthcare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some level of anxiety typically accompanies breakthrough technologies, and it&#39;s natural to worry about a technology that mimics human intelligence. As this new class of large language models has emerged, however, most companies have put model risk, accuracy of the model&#39;s output, and ethical use of data at the heart of their risk frameworks. They aim to ensure responsible uses of new AI technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Less appreciated is the risk that companies will cede the customer experience to models and bots designed to extract value in the short term, not to foster long-term customer loyalty. Companies might increasingly pair traditional AI and machine learning models with generative AI to deliver messages and offers to customers in more human-like ways. If we are not careful, profit-seeking bots, algorithms, and predictive models could indeed lead to dystopian experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even in the world of AI, customer love should lead the way. Traditional metrics of customer sentiment, such as Net Promoter Score (NPS), may start to look different, but one premise will endure: Every interaction enhances or diminishes a customer&#39;s perception the company involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Informing each decision with the goal of enriching customers&#39; lives will lay down a reliable route to an AI-enabled future that creates more value for customers, employees, and shareholders. In fact, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w31161/w31161.pdf&quot;>;early published results&lt;/a>; from researchers at Stanford University and Massachusetts Institute of Technology show favorable effects from the rollout of an AI-based conversational assistant tool to 5,200 customer support agents in several countries. Not only did the tool raise agent productivity by 14% on average, but the AI-assisted interactions had higher average NPS, and monthly agent attrition dropped by 9%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Make It Personal&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Orienting AI around customer love requires a fundamental rethink of objective functions. Most existing algorithms optimize around ROI for a particular moment rather than around an entire experience. AI-enabled customer engagement holds the promise of a company learning more from each interaction and finding more ways to create value for customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s a good sign because customers increasingly expect more personalized, relevant experiences and are open to sharing their data in return. Bain &amp;amp; Company&#39;s latest survey of almost 30,000 banking customers in 11 countries found that the respondents who agreed that their bank personalizes the experience are more likely to reward it with a higher NPS. There&#39;s a 123-point difference in NPS between respondents who strongly agree that their bank interacts based on knowing who they are and those who strongly disagree.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One way AI refines personalization is through digital assistants for customers, as shown by emerging efforts in banking and payments. Royal Bank of Canada uses an AI-enabled assistant called NOMI to personalize digital money management for customers. Features include timely tips pushed to clients, personalized budgets, and savings recommendations based on spending behavior and cash flow. In the year following its launch, the results were promising, with 50% more&amp;nbsp;digital interactions for NOMI customers relative to the entire customer base, 93% more time spent on financial accounts, and 2% attrition of NOMI customers vs. 8% for their peers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Generative AI digital assistants are also helping employees to strengthen their customer connections, reinforcing the places where a human touch may be a source of differentiation. Morgan Stanley Wealth Management, for instance, is rolling out an AI assistant to help its thousands of financial advisers better support their clients in a personalized way. The assistant combines search and content creation so that financial advisers can quickly find and tailor the right information for each client at any moment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large language models will enable a new era of personalization. Machine learning techniques already turn each customer&#39;s pattern of digital interactions into a unique behavioral “fingerprint,” and recent AI advances will now enable these fingerprints to include speech and text interactions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Help employees help their customers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Companies should start with a few no-regrets cases to get the organization comfortable with generative AI technology. These typically use AI to help employees who deliver aspects of the customer experience so that humans can vet the model&#39;s output. Examples include suggestions to relationship managers for the next conversation with a customer based on recent engagement or providing specific actions for handling collections with customers facing financial hardship.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next wave of cases would feature AI embedded in standard operating procedures for employees. Promising cases include predictive routing of a customer&#39;s inquiry to the agent best equipped to handle a particular issue or real-time script recommendations for relationship managers. The technology will listen to a customer call in real time and help agents know whether their interactions are creating a promoter or a detractor Other employee-supporting features in the near future could include devising a personalized offer with images and text that evoke a customer&#39;s favorite hobby or reminding a relationship manager to call on a customer during key life stages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a few industries such as retail, a fully AI-enabled front line is starting to support automated engagement directly with customers. Over time, this digital front line could deliver service with the same thoughtful empathy as traditional human front lines. Bots will engage with customers and learn to serve up relevant products and information just as the best employees have always done. The best uses of AI may even completely reimagine the overall experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a time of high inflation and tight economics, some managers may be tempted to use generative AI technology only to cut costs and improve efficiency. That would be misguided. While generative AI has the potential to bend the cost curve in many industries, the greatest value will come to those companies that focus on enriching the lives of their customers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Secure Support for Your ERG&rsquo;s Initiatives]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_1058899848.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Maren Caruso/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Employee resource groups are essential in fostering belonging and advancing potential, and they need support to be able to continue to do that. But given cost cutting, lack of cultural awareness, and increasing pressure&amp;#160;to slash DEI budgets,&amp;#160;the challenges many identity groups or social causes face can slip through the cracks.&amp;#160;In such challenging circumstances, how can ERG members galvanize and get the attention their networks need to influence and have impact? The author presents several strategies based on her work with people facing similar challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-secure-support-for-your-ergs-initiatives?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Employee resource groups, more commonly known as staff networks in the UK, have served as important vehicles for promoting inclusion and advocating for traditionally underestimated segments of workers with shared identities and interests. Unfortunately, many ERGs aren&#39;t given the resources, budget, and attention they need to fulfill that promise. Here are some concerns I&#39;ve seen in my work coaching individuals and delivering talks to ERGs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;How can I secure more budget allocation to support my faith-based ERG?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Why is my organization not running charity campaigns for floods in Pakistan or earthquakes in Turkey and Syria?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;My organization has an active women&#39;s network but lacks focus on intersectionality. How do I get them to prioritize this?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Given cost cutting, lack of cultural awareness, and increasing pressure&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mo-house-passes-budget-that-slashes-diversity-initiatives-defunds-libraries/ar-AA19jWvC&quot;>;to slash DEI budgets&lt;/a>;,&amp;nbsp;the challenges many identity groups or social causes face can slip through the cracks.&amp;nbsp;In such challenging circumstances, how can ERG members galvanize and get the attention their networks need to influence and have impact? Here are a few strategies based on how I&#39;ve supported people with similar challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Know Your Why&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, get clarity on what exactly you want to achieve and what the added support would mean for you and your fellow ERG members. For example, Nadia* sought my advice on how to request a dedicated Wudu area for &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;Muslim colleagues&lt;/a>;, while Hamza wanted to host an annual Iftar party during Ramadan. Despite the existence of faith networks at their companies, both faced obstacles due to their organizations&#39; reluctance to make “&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy&quot;>;special religious arrangements&lt;/a>;.” Meanwhile, Akua, who was member of a women&#39;s network at her company, wanted to organize a conference for women of color that would focus solely on the challenges faced by women from Black, Asian, and multiethnic backgrounds. However, she was told that the organization would only fund the women&#39;s network initiatives that championed “all women.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As disappointing as this was and despite the resistance from their respective organizations, I encouraged all three to take time to reflect on why these initiatives were essential to them. My goal was to help them solidify their ask and improve their chances of achieving their outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To get others on board with your ideas, start affirming your outcomes based on what you want to happen, not what you want to avoid. Additionally, take the time to consider the resources required, potential obstacles, and how your desired outcome will impact the system as a whole. By staying focused on your purpose, you can increase your sense of ownership and strengthen your conviction when presenting your idea to others. Here are some of the questions I asked Nadia, Hamza, and Akua to answer:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Why do you want this? What purpose does it serve and value does it provide?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What, where, when, and with whom will you achieve this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What are the internal and external resources required to realize this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What will you gain or lose by achieving this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is your action plan?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What changes would your desired outcome bring about in the larger system, and what will happen if you don&#39;t get to that outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will you monitor progress or overcome any challenges?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will you measure the impact of this outcome?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Once these questions have been answered, it&#39;s time to move on to preparing the business case. It may be helpful to keep revisiting the above as priorities evolve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Prepare Your Business Case&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that you&#39;ve identified your why, it&#39;s time to get ready to make your case to leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most organizations operate on a “what&#39;s in it for me?” basis.&amp;nbsp;Cherron Inko Tariah MBE, author of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em>;The Incredible Power of Staff Networks&lt;/em>;, encourages asking yourself the following questions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Are you aware of what&#39;s happening in the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Do you know the workplace culture and the issues facing the business? What&#39;s at the top of your CEO&#39;s inbox?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What was discussed at the last board meeting?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What are the HR leader&#39;s priorities?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s important to ensure that any new initiative aligns with the company&#39;s overall goals and strategies. This is exactly what Nadia did when she presented her case for a &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-leaders-can-better-support-muslim-women-at-work&quot;>;Wudu sink&lt;/a>;. She was able to clearly show how this provision would support the company&#39;s goal of becoming one of the top inclusive employers within three years. By linking her proposal to that larger goal, she was able to gain the support needed to move forward and make it a reality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Measuring and regularly tracking progress can significantly impact how an ERG and its activities are seen and valued. To make a compelling business case, ERG leaders must gauge their work&#39;s effectiveness and calculate the&amp;nbsp;return on investment&amp;nbsp;for their efforts. Metrics such as membership numbers and participation, satisfaction, and retention rates are excellent tools to leverage. To help you substantiate the need for and interest in your initiative, use pulse surveys to capture sentiment and solicit feedback from your members. Equally important is making adjustments as necessary to ensure that your ERG is meeting its goals and adding value to your organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, you can also help build your case by evaluating the global and intercultural benefits of your ERG&#39;s activity. Help leaders consider a macro perspective: How will the initiative affect individuals, work groups, customers, and the global organization? For example, Salman, a member of the Black Asian multiethnic network at his company&#39;s London office, wanted to initiate a campaign to collect funds for victims of floods in Pakistan during South Asian Heritage Month last year. However, he received little support from colleagues and managers, as they had recently donated to refugees of the war in Ukraine. Additionally, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2022/mar/02/civilised-european-look-like-us-racist-coverage-ukraine&quot;>;people tend to support those they can relate to&lt;/a>; or champion causes that get more international attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salman reached out to his colleagues in the company&#39;s South Asia location and used their help and experience to garner interest at the London office through storytelling. After learning how the floods had affected families of employees working in the Pakistan region, the London office was more inclined to take action.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s also valuable to collect information and share examples of how best-in-class companies (including competitors) are addressing your cause and encouraging others to join the alliance. To help get support at her company, Hamza gathered information on similar organizations that had successfully led Ramadan campaigns at their respective organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At this stage, it&#39;s understandable that you&#39;re keen to press forward, but making your case tactfully is crucial; engaging in the conversation with humility while avoiding comparisons and “&lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/whataboutism-what-it-is-and-why-its-such-a-popular-tactic-in-arguments-182911&quot;>;whataboutism&lt;/a>;” is more likely to yield a successful result. Attempts to minimize other groups or initiate a competing narrative when fighting for your right to be heard or seen will backfire and make you lose support from different identity groups. When we draw comparisons, we neither heal nor drive positive change. It shouldn&#39;t be a case of “this or that” but rather “this &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; that.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider starting your conversation with leadership like this: “I appreciate the organization&#39;s focus on inclusion. I have thoroughly enjoyed being part of XYZ network and can see the positive impact it has created. Encouraged by the influence, I propose an initiative for XYX.” Then you can elaborate on why what you&#39;re asking for is essential, including the data you&#39;ve gathered.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Gather Support&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The company will only consider your case if there&#39;s sufficient interest, so once your “why” is clear and you&#39;ve prepared a business case, it&#39;s time to rally support.&amp;nbsp;When I asked Nadia if there were other employees she could rely on, she affirmed there were quite a few. She then created an internal Google form survey and gathered responses from colleagues who shared the benefits of a separate a Wudu sink for their Muslim and non-Muslim colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, it was necessary to get senior leaders involved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at-work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;McKinsey research found&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;that ERG leaders who have strong ties to executives are better able to obtain resources and funding than those with weak ties. Speaking to allies and sponsors you can count on for&amp;nbsp;support is vital. Hamza did exactly this and was able to bring many on board for her Iftar celebration — in fact, some were even eager to participate in a Ramadan Challenge before partaking in the Iftar celebration. Taking advantage of solid connections and visible supporters higher up within the ranks can be a significant bolster for the initiative to be taken seriously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even if you don&#39;t have sufficient numbers from your identity group to advocate for your initiative, you can look to other ERGs to support you. Here&#39;s one possible way to approach the conversation with ERG leaders:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;I loved being part of your network&#39;s initiative; my participation has helped me recognize why your network is important and why it&#39;s essential to have our needs seen and acknowledged. Inspired by you, I&#39;ve asked management to allocate resources to XYZ. Can I count on the support of your network as I prepare to approach them?&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;The advantage of this is twofold: Not only will you have their backing, but because it&#39;s not uncommon for ERGs to combine resources and jointly advocate for social impact initiatives, they may even organize or run programs for you if you&#39;re unsuccessful securing what you need. But remember that such mutually beneficial associations rely on reciprocity — if you expect them to help, you must also be a visible ally for them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Be Specific and Prepare to Pivot&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the earlier example, when Salman wanted to organize a charity drive for flood victims in Pakistan, he took charge of the initiative. He asked for specific things he needed: using the office&#39;s hall to hold a bake sale, mentioning the campaign in the company newsletter and a company-wide email, and using the office kitchen to store goods.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Be prepared to pivot when you don&#39;t get what you ask for. Prepare a sliding scale of asks and try to secure minimum commitment to start the conversation. If the company doesn&#39;t grant the budget for an event, perhaps ask them to at least send a company-wide email showing support and solidarity. Also, see if you can tie in with other networks and share resources or budgets. Remember, a “no” doesn&#39;t mean a “no” forever — revisit the ask in a few weeks or months as circumstances change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;ERGs are essential in fostering belonging and advancing potential, and they need support to be able to continue to do that. Organizations need to include all identity groups and champion all social causes equally, but it&#39;s naïve to expect that to happen without a substantial push. Systemic inequities and organizational bias permeate most organizations, and leaders will remain complacent if they aren&#39;t actively challenged. Navigating a system where some voices are often trivialized or go unheard altogether requires ERG leaders and members to be resourceful and project their asks more strategically. Waiting for organizations to take that initiative may translate into a very long wait — better to push and be heard than not be heard at all.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* Names have been changed throughout to protect privacy.&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Value of Digital Transformation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_31_NiyiAdeogun.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Niyi Adeogun&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort. Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate. To see where digital transformation creates value, the authors used McKinsey&amp;#8217;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. They found that digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards, often by creating value that&amp;#8217;s hard to copy.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-value-of-digital-transformation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“Show me the money!” Cuba Gooding Jr., playing Rod Tidwell, made those words a cultural touchstone in the movie &lt;em>;&lt;i>;Jerry McGuire&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;. He was not just voicing his concerns about committing to a sports agent, played by Tom Cruise in this case; he was also questioning Cruise&#39;s commitment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Business leaders, shareholders, and board members have increasingly been saying the same thing — albeit using different words — when it comes to their company&#39;s digital and AI transformations. While 89% of large companies globally have a digital and AI transformation underway, they have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/three-new-mandates-for-capturing-a-digital-transformations-full-value&quot;>;only captured 31% of the expected revenue lift&lt;/a>; and 25% of expected cost savings from the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That track record begs some tough questions: Is all this digital effort worth it? Do I really need to lead my industry or is being a fast-follower a smarter strategy? Can I create digital and AI capabilities that give me a lasting competitive advantage or is this just the price of doing business in the modern age?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Until business leaders are convinced of the value and confident in how to get it, they are unlikely to do the difficult, hands-in-the-dirt changes needed to improve their success rate, as we argue in our book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/rewired&quot;>;&lt;em>;&lt;i>;Rewired: How to Outcompete in the Age of Digital and AI&lt;/i>;&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;. But using proprietary data, we&#39;ve found just how and where digital transformations create value — and what businesses can do to beat the competition.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Hard Evidence, Real Value&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Hard evidence that directly ties digital and AI transformation to improvements in operational KPIs and financial performance is scant.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To redress this issue, we turned to banking, a sector that has enough of a history with digital transformations to produce meaningful findings and where we own a unique longitudinal dataset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we used McKinsey&#39;s Finalta benchmark, which tracked the performance of 80 global banks every year from 2018 to 2022 against a set of 50 normalized metrics, such as digital/mobile adoption, digital sales by banking product, number of people in contact centers, and number of branches. We then isolated performance in two metrics — the percentage of mobile adoption by their customer base and the percentage of sales originated in digital channels — to define 20 digital leaders and 20 digital laggards. These two metrics are broadly recognized in the industry as core indicators of a digital retail banking model.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, we combined this data with McKinsey&#39;s Corporate Performance Analytics to see how banks ultimately perform against financial metrics (eg, total shareholder return, growth, expenses). We then ran a blind assessment (ie, the identity of the banks was hidden) of the maturity of digital and AI capabilities of the leading and lagging banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The findings have been striking: Digital leaders are creating much more shareholder value than laggards. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders achieved average annual total shareholder returns of 8.1% vs. 4.9% for laggards. Leaders also had significantly better return on pre-tax tangible equity (ROTE), growing it from 15.5% in 2018 to 19.3% in 2022, vs. a more modest growth from 13.6% to 15.3% for laggards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This financial outperformance is a result of leaders&#39; success in growing revenue and better containing expense growth. Between 2018 and 2022, digital leaders have grown their active customer base at 0.5% and their retail revenues at 0.8% annually, while digital laggards saw zero growth in their active customer base and a decline of 1.4% per year on retail revenues. During the same period, leaders&#39; operating expenses grew at 1.3% per year, while laggards grew at almost twice that (2.3% per year). So, how are leaders able to outcompete so demonstrably?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Creating Value That&#39;s Hard to Copy&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Where does value come from? Let&#39;s look under the “digital hood.” Both digital leaders and laggards are growing adoption of their mobile app at the same rate, with a gap of 14 to 15 percentage points between them staying constant over time. (See below chart.) This is not surprising. As soon as a bank introduces a new mobile app feature, others see it and follow suit relatively quickly. The mobile app is table stakes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Turning to digital sales provides a much more insightful answer. Here, the gap between leaders and laggards is growing fast, with leaders almost doubling their advantage over laggards over the five-year period. In fact, digital leaders grew digital sales from 40% to 70%, while digital laggards grew from 8% to 17%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reason for this large differential is that to drive digital sales, leading banks go well beyond the mobile app to digitally transform what&#39;s hard to see and hard to copy: the end-to-end process from origination to fulfillment to servicing. To do this, they must orchestrate hundreds of teams capable of developing digital and AI innovations, day-in, day-out, across all their customer journeys and core business processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the front end of this process, for example, leading digital banks deploy personalization analytics and digital marketing campaigns to bring relevant offers to (potential) customers. In the middle of this process, they create an omnichannel experience where branch and contact center professionals have the tools and data to support customers at any stage of the sales journey, even if that journey was started online. These leading banks also provide customer approvals in real time, thanks to automated credit-risk decisioning. At the back end of the process, they drive customer self-servicing through well-designed digital workflows enabled by a modern data architecture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The value of this approach to transformation is also revealed in contact center staffing. Laggards saw an increase of 20% over the past five years, as they were unable to contain inbound calls from customers that enter digital channels. In contrast, digital leaders were able to decrease contact center staffing by 11% as they benefited from their ability to fully fulfill customer demand online and provide effective self-servicing capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361201&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Knowing what to do is important, but executing on the “how” is what makes the difference. Let&#39;s see how a US bank did it for its secured lending business. Traditionally, the bank took about 45 days for a customer to secure a loan, on average. The process involved multiple documentation requests to customers (eg, pay stubs, W2s, letters of explanation), and back-end processes (eg, initial file review, file assignment, ad hoc reports) were highly manual.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To transform this journey, the bank&#39;s leadership team reinvented the entire process. To speed pre-approvals, they developed a database of tens of millions of US households combining credit, property and income attributes using internal and external data sources. This data allowed them to generate personalized pre-approved offers that customers could accept with one click. They built a mobile-first customer experience, where customers could personalize their offers based on real-time data and finalize a pre-filled application, either on mobile or with the assistance of a bank employee. They redesigned key processes (eg, specialized loan “assembly lines”), automated key tasks (eg, initial file scrub), and developed digital tools for operators to drive productivity (eg, daily workflow management). And they modernized credit policy execution to enable greater use of data in underwriting (eg, using direct deposit data for income), while maintaining or increasing risk controls for the bank.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To enable all these innovations, they implemented key technology and data capabilities, including a customer data platform, AI/ML models (eg, propensity models), data products (eg, income), a digital app for customers and a workflow tool for the fulfillment center, all deployed on a cloud-based platform-as-a-service infrastructure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, this transformation required more than a dozen use-cases across the entire journey and massive change management programs (eg, training, retooling) for agents in branches, contact centers, and operations. But, only 18 months after the initial launch, the approval process was shortened from 28 to 7 days. This leap allowed the bank to become a leading secured lending originator and increase originations by 35%, while reducing origination cost by 20%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Capabilities Needed to Outcompete&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;A company that aspires to outperform needs to do the kind of end-to-end changes the bank above did across dozens of customer journeys and core business processes. That&#39;s only possible when it is rewired with differentiated capabilities. Our study of more than 200 large-scale digital and AI transformations isolated the six core capabilities rewired companies develop:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Creating ambitious and focused transformation roadmaps&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. This requires business leaders to align their efforts on specific domains (eg, journeys or processes) that matter to customers and generate significant value.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Building a quality digital talent bench&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;. Leaders prioritize creating an environment that attracts top-notch engineers and allows them to thrive (eg, tailored career tracks, autonomy).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;An operating model &lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>;where hundreds of small cross-functional “pods” made up of business, engineering, and resources from control functions are mobilized against priority solutions. A single journey (or product) owner responsible for the end-to-end experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;A distributed technology environment and modern software engineering practices&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; to allow the entire organization&amp;nbsp;— not just IT&amp;nbsp;— to develop digital and AI-based solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Data products and modern data architecture&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; that make it easy for different parts of the organization to consume data for their own applications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;b>;Change management to ensures digital solutions are adopted and can scale&lt;/b>;&lt;/strong>; by making them easy to use and reuse across the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our blind assessment of these capabilities for the leaders and laggards, we found that leaders stand out across the board on these capabilities. No single one explains their success. All are needed. With that baseline, the most differentiated capabilities are talent and operating model, not technology. Over time, these capabilities create ever-improving customer experiences and drive lower unit cost. Financial rewards follow.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-361204&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230606_LAMARRE_DIGITAL_ADOPTION_CAPABILITIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While our research has focused on banking, our experience reflects similar lessons and patterns in every industry, whether B2B or B2C, products, or services. A digital and AI transformation, however, cannot be done in “special project” mode. To pull this off, the entire organization must be able to deliver constant digital innovation, which requires a holistic set of capabilities. The effort is significant, but so is the reward.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:55:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Keep Your Audience Focused During a Presentation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_1029427796.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;AndreyPopov/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&amp;#8217;s focus is critical to communication success. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it. In this piece, the author outlines three techniques &amp;#8212; physical, mental, and linguistic &amp;#8212; to engage your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-keep-your-audience-focused-during-a-presentation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Attention is our most precious commodity. In today&#39;s fast-paced world of always-on digital devices and round-the-clock media cycles, getting our audience&#39;s attention is critical to our communication success. With so many distractions vying for our time, we must actively seek and gain our audience&#39;s attention first.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, capturing ears and eyes isn&#39;t enough. Getting attention is only the first battle; keeping it is another challenge entirely. That&#39;s why smart communicators not only actively deploy ways to capture attention, but they work to sustain it. Sustained attention is what I call &lt;em>;engagement&lt;/em>;. If you can engage your audience, they will stay focused and be less distracted. Plus, you will have a better shot at demonstrating the relevance and significance of your topic to them. To that end, here are three approaches to engaging your audience.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Three Ways to Engage Your Audience&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Physical Engagement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Where the body goes, the brain will follow. Anything that gets your audience doing something with their bodies will create engagement. Whether you are giving an in-person pitch or presentation, or conducting a virtual meeting, think about how you can include physical engagement in your activities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, you can have people watch a video, read a handout, click on something on their screens, raise their hands, or use virtual reactions. All of these require your audience to become participants in your communication, not just observers. A simple invitation to “Turn to the person next to you and greet them” or “Read what is on the slide and share your thoughts” can get them involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Mental Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Fight back against your audience&#39;s tendency to zone out or multitask by fostering cognitive engagement. There are three simple ways to do this: ask questions throughout your presentation; incorporate provocative statements, data, and stats; and introduce smart analogies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you ask a question, people almost automatically start to consider their answer, thereby moving them from passive listening to active participation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Provocative statements or &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/present-your-data-like-a-pro&quot;>;compelling data&lt;/a>; ignite curiosity and encourage your audience to internally ask their own questions. For example, if you&#39;re trying to justify headcount for your training department, you could say: “30% of our customer service tickets could be eliminated by training users better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Analogies are where we compare what we know to what we don&#39;t know; in other words, we &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/finding-the-right-metaphor-for-your-presentation&quot;>;use the familiar to explain the unfamiliar&lt;/a>;. Invoking analogies invites involvement by making us actively think. One caveat: When you use analogies, make sure they&#39;re ones people can readily relate to. Over-reliance on sports metaphors or on complex comparisons people cannot follow or understand will work against your goal of engagement and greater understanding.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Linguistic Engagement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Linguistic engagement refers to the use of inclusive words, time-traveling language, and references to shared perspectives or experiences. Inclusive wording means inviting people into your communication. For instance, we&#39;re hardwired to perk up when we hear our own name, as well as when we hear the word “you.” Mention participants&#39; names, and use phrases like “As you know…” or “You may be wondering…” or “Today, you will learn…”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Time-traveling language takes people from the present into the future or the past. You can use phrases like “Imagine…” or “What if you could…” or “Picture this…” to take people into the future. “Remember when…” or “Think back to when…” will take people into the past. Connect people through shared experiences or beliefs to create common ground. For instance, highlighting your company&#39;s mission and values or referencing a previous shared experience can draw people in, much like when you and your friends or family share old stories and jokes.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Combining Engagement Techniques&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;You don&#39;t need to rely on only one engagement technique at a time. Instead, combine them to increase and enhance their effect. For example, polling is a great way to get both brains and bodies involved with a triple-whammy of activity. It works with a poll question as simple as, “By show of hands, which of the following do&lt;em>; you&lt;/em>; believe is the most important element of XYZ?” The synergy of the physical, mental, and linguistic engagement techniques deployed in this one question get attendees out of neutral and in the flow with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Note that when polling, you must first tell your audience how to respond (eg, “By show of hands…” or “Type into the chat…”). It&#39;s also imperative that you comment on the response you get (eg, “That&#39;s what I expected…about half of you,” or “Wow, that is everyone”). If you fail to comment, your audience might feel tricked into complying, or worse, that you did not care about the answer and were just using the poll as a gimmick.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, these suggestions might not be appropriate for your situation (for example, if you&#39;re polling the three executives in the room), so choose options that fit the occasion and group size.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While engagement techniques can be used any time in a communication situation, they&#39;re especially critical when starting meetings, presentations, or pitches. Think about how an action movie opens. You&#39;re thrown into the midst of action with the actor doing something impressive, interesting, and curiosity provoking right away. Only after your attention is engaged and your interest piqued do the title and credits appear. If you start out with the traditional “Hi, my name is..,” you&#39;ve missed a prime opportunity to&amp;nbsp; engage your audience immediately. Similarly, engaging your audience by asking a question, taking a poll, showing a video, or using an analogy before introducing yourself sets an energetic tone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;&lt;strong>;. 。 .&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Grabbing and keeping your audience&#39;s focus is critical to communication success. If you think about any communication and communicator that you find compelling, they&#39;re likely leveraging some of the physical, mental, or linguistic engagement techniques discussed above. What you have to say is important, so give yourself the best chance to convey your message to your audience by first gaining attention, but then, more importantly, sustaining it.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s OK to Fail, but You Have to Do It Right]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;6331954317112&amp;quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;Loading... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;div>;Harvard Business School professor Amy Edmondson is probably best known for her work on psychological safety in the workplace. She has authored a number of books, including the forthcoming &lt;em>;Right Kind of Wrong: The Science of Failing Well&lt;/em>;, and she spoke with HBR editor in chief Adi Ignatius about the right&amp;#8211;and wrong&amp;#8211;ways to fail. Experimentation and risk-taking are crucial for an organization&amp;#8217;s success, but failing twice in the same way is probably a mistake.&lt;/div>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/its-ok-to-fail-but-you-have-to-do-it-right?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When you or your team try new things — and not all of them succeed — that&#39;s called experimentation. Learning from experiments is essential for your company&#39;s growth. On the other hand, when you deviate from proven practice because of inattention or lack of training, that&#39;s probably a mistake. It&#39;s critical to know the difference, and to create a workspace where individuals feel psychologically safe to take smart risks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For this episode of our video series “The New World of Work”, HBR editor in chief Adi Ignatius sat down with Harvard Business School professor Amy Edmondson, an expert in psychological safety and author of the upcoming book &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Right-Kind-Wrong-Science-Failing/dp/1982195061&quot;>;&lt;em>;Right Kind of Wrong: The Science of Failing Well&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, to discuss:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Productive, intelligent ways to fail&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Dangers of not experimenting enough&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Balancing individual employees&#39; needs with those of the team and organization&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Edmondson says that leaders should do a thorough post-mortem after every failure, whether it was productive or not, to ensure that it does not repeat itself. “A failure, even an intelligent failure, in new territory, new discovery, is no longer intelligent the second time it happens.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“&lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;The New World of Work&lt;/a>;” explores how top-tier executives see the future and how their companies are trying to set themselves up for success. Each week, Ignatius talks to a top leader on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/harvard-business-review/&quot;>;LinkedIn Live&lt;/a>; — previous interviews included &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/microsofts-satya-nadella-on-flexible-work-the-metaverse-and-the-power-of-empathy&quot;>;Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/indra-nooyi-former-ceo-of-pepsico-on-nurturing-talent-in-turbulent-times&quot;>;former PepsiCo CEO Indra Nooyi&lt;/a>;. He also shares an inside look at these conversations —and solicits questions for future discussions — in a newsletter just for HBR subscribers. If you&#39;re a subscriber, you can sign up &lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences?movetile=newworldofwork&quot;>;here&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Amy, welcome to The New World of Work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Great to be here, Adi. Thanks for having me.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New World of Work&quot; dek=&quot;Previous episodes&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New World of Work&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Previous episodes &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your book is primarily about failure. I was under the impression that we all understood that failure is noble and not shameful, and provides useful learning lessons. But you&#39;re writing a book that seems to be saying that we need to think hard and maybe differently about failure. What are you trying to accomplish with this book?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I was with you and then I poked around and realized that the truth is many people were still confused about failure. There is a lot of happy talk about failure out there. There&#39;s the virtual mantra of Silicon Valley to fail fast, fail often, failure&#39;s good, let&#39;s learn from failure, let&#39;s have failure parties, let&#39;s have failure resumes and so forth. And the truth is, the future of work will be riddled with failure. We can&#39;t just wish it away, even if we wanted to, we have to work with it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think no one can really take to heart the happy talk about failure unless they have a coherent framework. You could think of it as two camps: the Silicon Valley fail fast, fail often camp. And then the other camp, which is, “I live in the real world, failure&#39;s not an option.” And they&#39;re both right or they&#39;re both partially right, but neither is terribly helpful nor context specific.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So I think the happy talk, when it&#39;s not qualified with a coherent way of making distinctions between the good kind of failure and the not-so-good kind, is possibly more destructive than helpful. It drives the honest conversation underground. It&#39;s important to talk about the kinds of failure for which we really should be welcoming it with open arms and the kinds where we maybe shouldn&#39;t.&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;The New World of Work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href=&quot;/resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Subscribe to our Weekly Newsletter &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; The New World of Work &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; Candid conversations on talent, tech, and the future of business. A special email series for subscribers. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>; Sign Up&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Thanks for signing up, &lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>;&lt;/span>;! &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; You can view our &lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;other newsletters&lt;/a>; or opt out at any time by managing your &lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;email preferences&lt;/a>;. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think the best thing you can say about failure is if you have a culture that permits failure, that tolerates failure, it means you&#39;re stretching, you&#39;re pushing, you&#39;re trying to innovate, you&#39;re trying to do things that are difficult. That&#39;s part of the definition of what a digital company is. A digital company experiments frequently and tries and fails, and is able to tolerate failure. I would guess if you talk to most companies, they&#39;d say, “Yeah, we do that. That&#39;s the culture we have. We didn&#39;t used to, but we do that.” So I want to push you a little bit more: the rhetoric, that&#39;s the happy talk, but in reality that&#39;s not really how the world works?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First of all, it&#39;s not how most incentives are set up. I&#39;m not saying uniformly that&#39;s the case, but most of the time, failure is not rewarded in organizations, and people would rather do anything but fail.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And you&#39;re right, maybe a better way to talk about this is not as failure, but as experimentation. We have to be very pro-experimentation. But we have to be pro-&lt;em>;smart&lt;/em>;-experiments. And I think smart failures are the result of smart experiments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Smart experiments are ones that happen in new territory — honestly, if you can look up the answer, find the recipe, find the blueprint, please do, no need to experiment — new territory in pursuit of a goal that&#39;s consistent with the value proposition of the organization, with a hypothesis you&#39;ve done your homework on and importantly, as small as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Those are the kinds of both experiments and failures we must welcome with open arms. They are discoveries and they allow us to figure out quickly what to try next. But a portion of the book is devoted to best practices for failure-proofing that which can be failure-proofed. The activities, the operations in your company that are in known territory, are ones that should be well set up to make failure extremely rare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Are there industries that do not tolerate failure? Airline pilots? You don&#39;t really want them to fail. This isn&#39;t a rhetorical question. Are there industries that really don&#39;t tolerate failure? And can you look at them and say, “You actually can get interesting results if you have that kind of policy?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s start with airlines because clearly none of us want them to be comfortable with failure. Yet I think the reason why airlines have an extraordinary record of success and safety is because they&#39;re willing and able to talk about failure. The failures that they do tolerate happen in the simulator. There&#39;s training, there&#39;s a lot of emphasis on speaking up early to prevent something worse from happening. So their safety record does not come from being intolerant of failure, but rather being intolerant of major accidents.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Therefore, we have to be very tolerant of the reality of human error so that we can catch and correct, we can train, we can allow people to take the kinds of risks and experiments we were just talking about in safe settings like the simulator, not in the execution of the real duties.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I don&#39;t think it&#39;s possible to describe industries in the way your question implies. I think there&#39;s variation across companies. Pick an industry like fast-moving consumer goods. It&#39;s going to be not that hard to find differences in cultural failure tolerance within those industries across companies. So a more sensible way to put that is that some companies are doing better than others in having a healthy tolerance of intelligent failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What does a productive failure look like? You did mention that there are good and bad failures. What&#39;s the difference and how does one try to make sure their failures are the good kind?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In known territory where we have a process or a formula for getting the result we want, it&#39;s best practice to use that process, use that formula and get the result we want. So when a Citibank employee a number of years ago accidentally made a small human error and accidentally wired $800 million to a client that he shouldn&#39;t have, that was a basic unproductive failure. Turns out they were not even able to get the money back. So, not celebrating that kind of failure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A productive failure is one where we get new and useful knowledge, new knowledge that helps us go forward in creating the kind of value we&#39;re trying to create in our market, for our customers. So we discovered something that we could not have discovered without trying it, without the experiment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Would you recommend that there be an elaborate postmortem? I think the military is very focused on doing detailed postmortems: what happened, what went wrong, why? Presumably to learn from that and not have it happen again.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is not the case that a postmortem has to take inordinate amounts of time, but it should be thorough. It should be analytical, and look carefully at the different facets of the failure, to understand accurately what happened and why, for the express purpose of preventing that exact failure from happening ever again. So a failure, even an intelligent failure, in new territory, new discovery, is no longer intelligent the second time it happens.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I want to shift gears a little bit to talk more generally about the workplace. The question really is: Are we OK? &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-to-reenergize-your-team-when-morale-is-low&quot;>;You wrote a recent piece in Harvard Business Review&lt;/a>; that suggested maybe things are not so great, with relatively low levels of engagement and productivity, high rates of burnout. We can speculate as to why that&#39;s true, but is that accurate? It&#39;s hard to generalize, but you know, are we suffering? And if so, how do we respond to that as managers?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Well, I don&#39;t have a kind of systematic worldwide dataset from which I can make solid inferences about how people are doing. My impression comes from informal conversations, qualitative research, reading HBR and so many other outlets, to see how people are doing. So really, in a way, I&#39;m commenting on the conversation in HBR and so many other business media contexts, maybe LinkedIn and elsewhere.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One thing I think I can say for sure is that the anxiety is real, and people are worried about the future. They&#39;re worried about it on so many fronts. They&#39;re worried about climate change. They&#39;re worried about AI. They&#39;re worried about burnout, as you mentioned. I&#39;ll come back to burnout.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But that anxiety tends to push us toward a retreat to our individual corner, and people start to think, “Am I going to be OK?” They become more focused on their own wellbeing than on the health of the team or health of the organization. And that gives rise to a real potential for erosion, even vicious cycles, where organizations find themselves in the trap of responding to requests and issues in isolation, one by one.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We need a more holistic way of thinking about it. And I see limited evidence of companies being at least described as pausing to think about the larger picture, their value proposition, what it implies for how they must be structured and led, to get the necessary work done, and how to organize that work, with all its variety and variable needs, in a thoughtful way, and how to inspire and motivate people to do it well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let me just briefly go to the burnout issue, because there actually has been some recent data, some studies that have caught my eye, showing that burnout is systematically higher when psychological safety is lower, right? For instance, it seems to me that some portion of the burnout is associated with loneliness and isolation. I think it&#39;s fair to say that we can endure many challenges when we feel genuinely that we&#39;re in it together, that we&#39;re connected and engaged with our colleagues in trying to sort of navigate these challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One can&#39;t help but think, “Okay, is some of this related to the pandemic?” Which for many of us, broke up teams, created new work environments with work from home, that in many ways is fantastic for people who are balancing their work and life. It must take a toll on maybe the teaming imperative that you&#39;ve written about. Is that your hunch?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I do think the pandemic took a toll on us, on all of us. It created such an obvious uncertainty. It was such an obvious disruption. It wasn&#39;t the gradual shifts that we&#39;re normally used to. It was a very abrupt shift, and it gave rise to wonderful—and I think productive—experiments on different work arrangements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now it&#39;s time for a very systematic assessment of what&#39;s working and what isn&#39;t? And it can&#39;t be incremental, right? And it also can&#39;t be based on what people say they want. Because oftentimes, what we say we want is not actually what we need or truly want in the longer term, bigger picture, to get where we need and want to go.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You talked a second ago about trying to have a comprehensive policy and approach that, if I heard you right, is not dealing with people always individually, but that&#39;s sort of the nature of management now. Suddenly, managers are expected to be, in addition to everything else, almost like psychiatrists, that there&#39;s an openness for people to share their personal situations, challenges, problems, and that it&#39;s the role of the manager, increasingly, to engage with that in an intelligent way. So you end up where management becomes hyper-personalized, but I think maybe you&#39;re already on to the risks in that, which is losing the sense of the teaming and the collective effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s almost as if we&#39;ve lost sight of tensions and trade-offs. There will always be a tension between me and we, right? There will always be a tension between my desires in the moment and my aspirations over the long term. If you ask me what I want: pay me infinitely and don&#39;t ask me to do anything, and let me eat ice cream all day, right? But that&#39;s not going to get me where I really, really need to go, and want to go. I want to make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think we&#39;re in a moment of not helping people value the collective. As human beings, we&#39;re social creatures. That&#39;s part of it, but it&#39;s also that we want to matter. We want to matter to others. We want to matter in some way that&#39;s larger than ourselves and our hedonistic desires.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can think of an old-fashioned management theory of the firm, right? If markets worked by themselves, we would just have only contractors doing tasks, and it would be efficient, it would be sensible, it would be logical. But it doesn&#39;t work, because a lot of the work we have to do is inherently collaborative, and dynamically so. And it isn&#39;t easily parceled out, dividing-and-conquering style. It requires us to really work together in meaningful ways. The good news is, that can be a very engaging, rewarding, exciting experience. The bad news is, it&#39;s not easy to manage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think we can go down that rabbit hole of each person has to be managed differently, each person, you&#39;re almost a psychiatrist to that person, versus let&#39;s step back and rethink, how do we design our activities, our operations, so that we create the most value for those we serve?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yeah, I love that, and I have to say that I don&#39;t think companies have figured that out yet. The disruption of Covid opened our eyes to some flexibility. But I think the things you&#39;re putting your finger on, we&#39;re trying to solve for that, and I think a lot of us haven&#39;t yet and need to keep experimenting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So we&#39;re in this age of anxiety, where there&#39;s burnout. And then, you throw on top of that generative AI, and a fear—possibly irrational, possibly not—that generative AI will be able to do all of our jobs at almost no cost. I assume you haven&#39;t done quantitative research. But qualitatively, what&#39;s your advice for people as generative AI enters the workplace at every level and the possibilities become clearer and clearer?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you indicated, it&#39;s a little outside my wheelhouse, except for the effects on people and culture. I speak from the perspective of someone listening at the margins to the many conversations in work and social gatherings alike, and I think you&#39;re right. I think fear is the dominant emotion, that certainly some are excited, some are super optimistic about the amazing changes to come, but I think casually I hear more fear than optimism.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The truth is we need both. We need some positive, thoughtful, design-oriented approaches to experiment and figure out what&#39;s going to work. But I don&#39;t think they&#39;re going to be simple solutions to the dramatic shakeup of what&#39;s possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s a question from Omar from Monterrey, Mexico. What kind of metrics can be used to measure smart failures?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My first response is that it&#39;s a good idea to have metrics. One of the things that I&#39;ve spent the most time studying is how many failures just don&#39;t even get the chance to be measured, because people don&#39;t speak up about them. This was how I got into this topic in the first place: the discovery of dramatic differences across groups, even within the same organization, and their willingness to speak up about things that go wrong rather than just things that go right.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s the challenge more broadly than just people not necessarily speaking up: the category of intelligent failure covers vast territory. I think the metrics have to be tailored to the context — and let me illustrate vast territory. A well-run clinical trial on a new cancer drug is an intelligent failure when it turns out it doesn&#39;t have the efficacy that we hoped. It was in new territory. There was no other way to find out but to do a clinical trial. It&#39;s the right size, it&#39;s no bigger than it has to be. It&#39;s hypothesis-driven in pursuit of a goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But so is a really bad blind date. That&#39;s intelligent failure. Maybe your friend thought you&#39;d like each other. You are willing to go out and have a coffee. Smallest possible new territory in pursuit of a goal, all the rest. So a bad blind date and a failed clinical trial are clearly apples and oranges, yet they both qualify under the category.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I think the best way to answer the measurement question is, let&#39;s make sure the criteria are adhered to. And then, let&#39;s think about what the right frequency is, given the work we&#39;re trying to do, of intelligent failures?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another way to say that is: What&#39;s the right frequency of experimentation? How often should we be trying new things to push the envelope, to discover new possibilities, even to discover efficiencies? And are we doing that often enough? The answer is usually no, because most of us would rather succeed than fail, and most of us would rather keep doing what we&#39;re doing because we&#39;re kind of good at it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So here&#39;s another question along those lines from Mohammed in Pakistan. Employees may be hesitant to offer feedback that could be perceived as negative, which can impede professional development, hinder organizational progress. How does one tackle this situation?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such a good question because it&#39;s true. We are very reluctant to do things, to speak up with negative or difficult information, because frankly it will always be easier not to. It will always be easier to hold back than to speak up candidly and forthrightly about something that you hope could be made better.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The way to make this very difficult thing easier is to set the stage by pointing out how valuable it is. Periodically, I would say even frequently, refer to the fact that “We need to do this hard thing. We need to do it well if we want to be as good as we can as a team.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But even individuals who have the ambition to grow and develop in their roles and in their careers have to train themselves to be willing to do this and receive it because of its value. So we&#39;ve got to call attention to its value. We&#39;ve got to call attention to the fact that it&#39;s hard and then do it anyway and support each other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This question is from Don from Calgary in Canada. If it&#39;s true that we learn acutely from mistakes, what are some ways to encourage permission from our leaders who may be risk averse?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re all risk averse, and maybe leaders even more than others, maybe not. But first of all, I make a distinction between mistakes and failures. I&#39;m not anti-mistake because I&#39;m a human being, and I make them, we all do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But a mistake is not the same thing as a failure. A failure is something that went wrong that we wish were otherwise. A mistake is a deviation from a known practice. Now, that could happen because of inattention, because of lack of training, because of exhaustion, you name it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I think it&#39;s helpful for leaders, and others for that matter, to talk about the reality that we will make mistakes because we&#39;re human. The very best practice is not to never make a mistake. It&#39;s to catch and correct them quickly, and then also to make that distinction between smart experiments in new territory that we also want to see more of because it&#39;s the secret to future value creation. And we welcome those, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Furthering that, here&#39;s a question from Benny from California. What&#39;s the best way to speak to subordinates after a failure to boost morale and communicate that, “This was a good failure. It&#39;s OK”?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;m going to say “honestly.” You can be honest about, “Wow, this was disappointing for all of us, and let&#39;s get everything we can out of it. Let&#39;s learn as much as possible.” And in fact, given that something substantial that goes wrong nearly always has multifaceted aspects to it, it&#39;s helpful to have a thoughtful and data-driven conversation about what happened. Not “Who did it?”, but, “What happened?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We may go around the team and ask, “What did you see?” And we&#39;re really looking for what happened, what contributed to that, and that&#39;s both commission and omission, things that you did that may have contributed, things that you didn&#39;t do that may have helped. It&#39;s a thoughtful, deliberately learning-oriented conversation designed to help us be better next time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How do you reenergize your team these days? How do we reenergize our team particularly now, in 2023, where it feels like there&#39;s a lot of stuff swirling around?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It starts with personally taking the time to reconnect with your own sense of purpose for doing the job, the role that you are currently doing. And consider why it matters to you and why what you are doing or leading matters to the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Having done that, share it. Share it often and then just as quickly invite others in to help navigate the necessarily stormy waters that lie ahead. I think it starts with you and then it&#39;s an honest sharing of why you care, why it&#39;s challenging, why you very much need and are interdependent with others. Because all of us want to be needed. We want to be needed. We want to matter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The last few years, with the pandemic, I&#39;d say certainly in the US, there&#39;s been increased attention to social issues, which on the one hand I think felt right to people in the workplace. On the other, it brought more challenges into the workplace. One imagines there&#39;s a pendulum, and it might swing between leadership needing to be very empathetic to, I don&#39;t know, the backlash if that&#39;s the right word. Leaders need to achieve productivity. That&#39;s what it&#39;s all about. Do you believe in that pendulum or are we in a different place? And if you do, where are we right now on that swing?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I believe in the pendulum. I believe that the pendulum happens and I believe there may be a better way. It&#39;s often thought of as empathy versus productivity. And I looked this up actually: Productivity is defined as the effectiveness of productive effort as measured in terms of the rate of output per unit of input.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first problem is that not all work is easily measured for productivity. The second problem is, often it&#39;s not the right way to measure excellence. Productivity is often a short-term measure, and it has limited predictive value for the future performance of the firm. For example, one way to be really productive is to just push people to their limits. But that has time constraints. Eventually they will burn out, leave, etc. It&#39;s like Buckminster Fuller used to say that it was foolish to burn down the house to keep warm on a cold winter&#39;s night. The excessive pressure can be the equivalent of that error.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And also innovation work in particular, we have case study after case study where the work actually suffers when productivity metrics are brought to bear.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a way, I wish the pendulum were more about excellence than productivity, because I think productivity is really tricky and variable to measure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I see the pendulum existing, but maybe it&#39;s a false dichotomy. Maybe it&#39;s not empathy versus productivity. Maybe we need smart, caring leaders who understand the importance of both. And given that that&#39;s very challenging, they&#39;re open about it being challenging. They&#39;re asking for help. They&#39;re sharing the burden of caring and excellence with their teams and considering, again, the fundamentals of what it is the organization must do well to stay alive in its market, to perform in its market. And talk about it honestly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I sometimes think we don&#39;t talk often enough about the fact that work is work. It&#39;s supposed to be a little bit of work, but that doesn&#39;t mean it can&#39;t be fun, energizing, collaborative, and full of empathy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I love that. Well, that&#39;s a good point to end on. Amy Edmondson, thank you for being on the show.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AMY EDMONDSON:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thanks for having me. All the best.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 23:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Hybrid Work Can Become Toxic]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_27_1425175448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Toxicity can be an unfortunate reality of some work environments. Toxic cultures share five attributes: they&amp;#8217;re disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive. Undeniably negative as these attributes are, there is no absolute, uniformly accepted scale against which we can measure any of them. Making matters more complicated, a hybrid environment by definition means that employees are experiencing their work in very different contexts &amp;#8212; some face-to-face, others remote &amp;#8212; and those may vary by the day. As a result, hybrid workspaces aren&amp;#8217;t uniform; some people may experience a hybrid environment as toxic while others do not. The author presents four mechanisms through which hybridity can lead to toxic behaviors, as well as four strategies for preventing and addressing toxic behavior in a hybrid environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-hybrid-work-can-become-toxic?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Toxicity at work — no matter where or how we do our jobs — is caused by a range of factors. It is important to recognize that some aspects of hybrid and remote work make toxicity more likely to occur.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, though, let&#39;s quickly outline what “toxic” actually means. It doesn&#39;t refer to the misunderstandings, tensions, and conflicts that are a natural (and needed) part of any healthy organization. Nor does it refer to a one-off incident or a coworker who is a jerk every now and again. These kinds of irritations, for the most part, are best thought of as normal parts of (working) life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, what actually is considered toxic? A study by Donald Sull and his colleagues identified &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/why-every-leader-needs-to-worry-about-toxic-culture/&quot;>;five attributes of a toxic culture&lt;/a>;: disrespectful, noninclusive, unethical, cutthroat, and abusive. In a recent discussion I had with two colleagues who are experts on the subject, Amy Edmondson of Harvard Business School and Constance Hadley of the Questrom School of Business, we agreed that toxicity also implies the behavior in question is both pervasive and ongoing. And that, we believe, is what makes bad behavior rise — or perhaps fall — to the level of toxic. Toxicity carries a sense of inescapability, which is part of what makes it so painful to experience at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Undeniably negative as these attributes are, there is no absolute, uniformly accepted scale against which we can measure any of them — all five are subjective, anchored in each person&#39;s experience. Making matters more complicated, a hybrid environment by definition means that employees are experiencing their work in very different contexts — some face-to-face, others remote — and those may vary by the day. As a result, hybrid workspaces aren&#39;t uniform; some people may experience a hybrid environment as toxic while others do not. That does not make a toxic hybrid environment any less painful or damaging to those who experience it as such. However, it does mean that some behaviors may be toxic even as a result of well-meaning — or at least not ill-meaning — actions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When talking with executives about toxicity, I encourage them to think like social scientists, to understand the mechanisms through which hybrid working can lead to increased toxicity. Here&#39;s what they should know.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How Hybrid Work Can Lead to Toxicity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;My research and consulting experience has led me to think in terms of four mechanisms through which hybridity can lead to toxic behaviors.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Remoteness changes dynamics&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Working hybrid means that, compared with full-time in-office work, more communication will take place via technologies like email, text, phone, or video. One of the early findings in research on the effects of technology-mediated communication was that people become more disinhibited and exhibit less self-monitoring and self-control &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/227445694_Reducing_Social_Context_Cues_Electronic_Mail_in_Organizational_Communication&quot;>;when communicating through technology&lt;/a>;. In other words, when we talk to one another electronically, we are more likely to blurt out things that might be hurtful. Think about heated exchanges you&#39;ve had with colleagues both in person and electronically — chances are, you were much more tempted to try to slip in a sharp quip in an email than face-to-face.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This dynamic is not (necessarily) about being a nasty person. We all have moments of anger, frustration, or passion, and if handled badly, those feelings have the potential to turn toxic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In face-to-face interactions, though, the human on the other side of the conversation is far more salient to us, leading most of us to recognize the potential costs of a less-careful word and bite our tongues. The point isn&#39;t that we shouldn&#39;t speak our minds (if we feel that we can&#39;t, that&#39;s bad for psychological safety), but that we should choose our words well. While the reduced self-monitoring and self-control that come with remote interactions do not necessarily cause toxicity, they certainly make it more likely for &lt;em>;disrespectful&lt;/em>; or &lt;em>;abusive&lt;/em>; (two of Sull&#39;s toxicity characteristics) comments to come out.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Hybridity is fundamentally imbalanced&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Hybrid also means different people are working in different contexts. Some may be at home, while others are in the office — and those locations have undeniable differences. People in the office have greater access to resources and higher visibility, often leading to more credit and quicker promotion as a result. Remote workers, meanwhile, often feel left out and shunned. Negative as these effects may be, they are not strictly toxic if everyone is equally disadvantaged at some point. The problem is when some people (likely remote/hybrid workers) feel &lt;em>;consistently&lt;/em>; excluded — as was the experience of one manager I recently worked with.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Company policy was to allow all employees to work remotely two days a week, and the manager had allowed her team members to choose those days. She quickly discovered her team had effectively split on the basis of different (but consistent) patterns of which days people chose to come into the office. Compounding the issue, team members&#39; remote-work choices were heavily driven by commutes and children&#39;s school schedules, which aligned them with demographic differences in the team. Problems arose when some team members felt they were being excluded from the discussions and meetings that occurred on the in-office days of the other group. The split led to interpersonal tensions and conflict, people feeling &lt;em>;excluded&lt;/em>; and &lt;em>;disrespected&lt;/em>; (two toxicity characteristics), and it ultimately resulted in turnover.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Hybridity can reduce cohesion and trust&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/11/a-study-of-1100-employees-found-that-remote-workers-feel-shunned-and-left-out&quot;>;Research shows&lt;/a>; that lack of close contact reduces connection and trust, which are key elements of a healthy culture. During the pandemic, I spoke to many employees who had started new jobs remotely, and I consistently heard that they hadn&#39;t gotten to know their colleagues and felt disconnected. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/hybrid-work&quot;>;Research from Microsoft&lt;/a>; found remote working leads employees to have smaller, less-well-developed networks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Remote (and by extension hybrid) working does not necessarily mean organizations will have a weak or inconsistent culture. Take Linux as an example. Its open-source software development from day one has been carried out by a loosely structured community of developers who have never met in person, yet extensive research on the group has found it has strong social norms governing behavior. However, it is hard to deny that the group&#39;s structure (or lack thereof) removes or impedes many of the mechanisms we traditionally use to establish, transmit, and maintain culture. Note that Linux &lt;em>;started &lt;/em>;with a remote, dispersed culture. While many companies have embraced remote and hybrid since the pandemic started, their cultures were already established and then adjusted to handle the crisis.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Culture is so important because it is the compass organizations use to eschew &lt;em>;cutthroat&lt;/em>; and, in more extreme cases, &lt;em>;unethical&lt;/em>; behavior. To be clear, hybridity does not inherently lead people to be more cutthroat or unethical (though one might argue the sense of distance between people makes them less aware of the negative ramifications of their actions). However, in every social system we find a range of behaviors, and culture typically helps us rein in the negative ones. On top of that, while people are less likely to exhibit toxic behaviors toward those they feel close and connected to, the distance that a remote/hybrid environment brings makes us more likely to view some of our colleagues not as “us” but as “them” — and it&#39;s much easier to act poorly toward “them.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Hybridity makes it hard to resolve issues&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s one more key challenge in remote and hybrid work: We have fewer face-to-face interactions with colleagues, and research shows that it is harder to resolve disputes (like those around toxic behaviors) virtually. Think about trying to address a sensitive topic over Zoom with someone and worrying about everything from where they&#39;re looking to how fast they reply. &lt;em>;Are they giving me their full attention? Am I sure my sincerity is coming through over video? Was their slow response because they disagreed or are just lagging?&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When we&#39;re face-to-face, we have more interpersonal tools at our disposal. We have better data, as we can more easily read facial expressions and can see off-camera behaviors. We also have better tools, as face-to-face interactions allow us to synchronously work together to resolve differences. And the propinquity effect (essentially, we like people we have more exposure to) means all of this happens from a starting point of a closer relationship.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One other issue it&#39;s important to mention is microaggressions, which some people have argued happen less often in remote settings because we&#39;re around one another less. However, I would caution leaders and employees alike to stay vigilant for signs of microaggressions (often reflected in toxic behaviors like &lt;em>;noninclusion&lt;/em>;) in hybrid settings. While these settings may have fewer touchpoints where microaggressions can occur, they do not remove the underpinnings of why microaggressions happen — nor do they prevent them from coming out in other outlets, such as Slack, messaging apps, or videoconferencing. In effect, hybrid work can obscure the problem without resolving it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What Leaders Can Do&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I advise leaders to approach toxic behaviors in hybrid work in four ways: educate, lay a foundation, have ongoing conversations, and intervene quickly.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Educate employees&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The first step toward avoiding toxic behavior in hybrid teams is to help people learn how it can arise. You may think, “Of course they know not to be disrespectful, abusive, or noninclusive,” but that&#39;s not the issue. Sit down with your employees and have a conversation about how these outcomes can happen as unintended consequences of hybrid work arrangements and decisions. Remind them that toxicity is about behavior — and that what matters isn&#39;t what your intention was but how others perceive your actions. A good starting point is to ask employees to reflect on hybrid work behaviors they may have experienced as toxic (for example, feeling routinely excluded from a social group or reading comments on Slack that they found abusive or disrespectful). The goal of this step is not to identify particular issues or point fingers but rather to increase employees&#39; self-awareness and the number of eyes out there looking for toxic behaviors or their antecedents.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Lay a foundation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As Benjamin Franklin famously said, “An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure.” One of the most effective tools you can put in place is a culture with built-in antibodies against toxic behaviors. In particular, focus on promoting empathy and psychological safety. A culture with a core of empathy encourages employees to consider the impact of their actions on their colleagues, increasing the likelihood that employees catch themselves before behaving in a way another might find troubling. In turn, a culture that includes psychological safety is critical for those cases that empathy doesn&#39;t prevent. We don&#39;t always recognize the impact of our actions, and building psychological safety ensures that employees can speak up about the behaviors they perceive as toxic. Research has provided excellent practical advice for promoting both &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/empathy-rules&quot;>;empathy&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychological safety&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Have ongoing conversations&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Because the experience of hybrid work is different among employees and dynamic over time (someone may be in the office today, surrounded by colleagues, and at home alone tomorrow), toxicity is a moving target. The only truly effective way to manage such dynamism is with an ongoing process — and the cornerstone is repeated, ongoing conversations. I encourage hybrid teams and organizations to have periodic check-ins where everyone is encouraged to raise concerns or flag toxic experiences. There is no hard-and-fast rule for frequency, as it depends on how dynamic the organization&#39;s hybrid environment is: The more and faster it changes, the more frequent those conversations should be. As a starting point, aim for a monthly check-in and adjust as needed. Make sure the psychological safety foundation is in place if you want people to share honestly, and treat these conversations as more than a superficial box-ticking exercise.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Intervene quickly&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Even with a good understanding of the issues, a positive cultural foundation in place, and ongoing discussions, hybrid working may still lead to behaviors that your employees find toxic. A big problem with toxic environments is that they tend to get worse: Toxic behaviors either feed on themselves, breeding more toxicity, or cause disgruntled employees to disengage, creating new tensions due to workloads needing to be redistributed. To break the cycle, you need to not only keep an eye out for toxic behaviors but also be ready to move fast when you see them, help all parties engage in a dialogue, and work to reach a mutually acceptable solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s say you notice a situation like that of the manager whose team was split over their WFH days. In a case like that, call a team meeting and share your concerns of how the situation might feel exclusionary. It may turn out your concerns aren&#39;t shared — but you&#39;re still creating buy-in and ownership of the issue, making it easier to address later if it does become a problem. If, however, you&#39;ve recognized a budding concern for some of your team members, you have a forum to discuss and collectively resolve it before it gets too far along.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Toxicity can be an unfortunate reality of some work environments. While hybrid work does not necessarily cause toxicity any more than in-person work does, it is important to recognize that hybrid introduces some different mechanisms through which toxicity may arise. Keeping these in mind can help leaders recognize, guard against, and eliminate toxicity when it occurs — or ideally before.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 28 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Why Employees Accept Lower Pay at Mission-Oriented Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_27_AnChen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by An Chen&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Today&amp;#8217;s companies are likely to tout how their work benefits human welfare or &amp;#8220;makes the world a better place.&amp;#8221; Recent research suggests that this may come with a potential financial drawback for workers, as it can inhibit them from negotiating for higher pay. Over five studies, job candidates consistently reported that they worried asking for higher pay from these companies would be seen as greedy or inappropriate. This suggests they are aware of a common bias, known as motivation purity bias, where managers believe employees interested in material rewards of work (such as pay) are less motivated than those motivated by intrinsic rewards, such as the nature of the work. In reality, research has shown that extrinsic and intrinsic motivations operate jointly to predict high performance. Job candidates should invest in building their negotiation skills so they are less thrown off when companies use social impact framing. And organizations should train managers to be aware of the motivation purity bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-why-employees-accept-lower-pay-at-mission-oriented-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In an amusing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B8C5sjjhsso&quot;>;episode&lt;/a>; of the HBO sitcom &lt;em>;Silicon Valley&lt;/em>;, one awkward startup founder after the other pitches their company by proclaiming that it “makes the world a better place.” The satirical comedy highlights how common it has become for companies to tout how their work benefits human welfare.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend — which academics call &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/orsc.2017.1172?&quot;>;social impact framing&lt;/a>; — appears to be on the rise. We see it across job postings, company websites, and consumer advertisements, with for-profits and non-profits alike looking to hire “passionate” and “mission-oriented” workers seeking to “make an impact.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such emphasis on social impact isn&#39;t without merit. For one, it can reflect organizations&#39; earnest desires to make a positive difference. It can also &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2008-00266-008&quot;>;motivate&lt;/a>; employees by instilling a greater sense of self-worth and meaningfulness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, in our recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1287/orsc.2023.1675&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; published in &lt;em>;Organization Science&lt;/em>;, we uncover that organizations&#39; use of social impact framing can come with a potential financial drawback for workers, as it can inhibit them from negotiating for higher pay.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Perceived Norm Violation&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We explored this effect over five experimental studies. Consistently, job candidates in the social impact framing condition reported that asking for higher pay would likely be viewed as greedy and inappropriate by the hiring organization. As a result, they refrained from negotiating.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our first study, we recruited 392 participants from an online research platform to examine workers&#39; attitudes in response to different types of organizational messaging. Approximately half of the participants read about a company that emphasizes social impact, while the others read a more generic company description. We asked participants to write open-ended responses about whether or not they would negotiate a job offer to work for the company, and why. We found that those who received the company descriptions that included social impact framing condition were 32% less likely to negotiate. The most common reason for this reticence was participants&#39; belief that negotiating would be seen as selfish and counter-normative, and put them at risk of being passed up for the job.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our second study involved 438 undergraduate students responding to an on-campus job opportunity in which they would be recruiting fellow students to work for a startup in the educational industry. The students watched an introductory video where the purported company founder and CEO — played by a trained actor — described his hiring organization. Approximately half of participants watched a video in which the founder emphasized social impact, while the other half watched a video in which the founder described a more generic organization focused on high-quality work and success. After viewing the video, participants were given the opportunity to ask for a higher wage for the job versus accept the initially offered wage. Consistent with our first study, students in the social impact condition were 43% less likely to negotiate. Again, this effect was driven by the perception that showing interest in higher pay would violate the organization&#39;s norms for employee motivation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We replicated these results in three other studies. We found that the effects held true in a workplace simulation and across a range of industries, including education, health care, manufacturing, and finance. We also found that social impact framing largely affects job candidate requests for monetary job rewards, such as salary and bonuses. It does not seem to deter them from asking for non-monetary rewards like vacation time and health care benefits.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assumptions About Money and Doing Good&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;What explains the effects on monetary job rewards?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The answer lies in widespread and longstanding beliefs that money taints love of the work itself and attempts to do good.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers, for instance, have been shown to hold a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2017.0617&quot;>;motivation purity bias&lt;/a>;,” where they believe that employees interested in the material rewards of work (extrinsic rewards) are less motivated by the nature of the job itself (intrinsic rewards), and are thus less worthy of being hired.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This belief is based on a false premise. Research has shown that extrinsic and intrinsic motivations operate &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/a0035661&quot;>;&lt;em>;jointly&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>; to predict high work performance. Furthermore, more of one type of motivation doesn&#39;t mean less of the other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nonetheless, in our research, job candidates seem to act as if they are aware of this managerial bias against workers&#39; interests in material rewards. Consequently, in social impact contexts — where workers are especially expected to be driven by loftier motivations such as a sense of higher purpose — job candidates self-censor on any indications that they might also care about the money.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Takeaways for Job Candidates and Hiring Managers&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;From a Marxist perspective, social impact framing might be viewed as yet another cultural trend that inadvertently operates in favor of the owners of capital and at the expense of workers. Yet, given that social impact framing is often rooted in organizations&#39; genuine efforts to contribute to society and can benefit employees as well, it would be overly simplistic to suggest that organizations stop communicating their emphasis on the greater good. We thus offer several suggestions to help minimize the financial downside for workers of exposure to such messaging.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From the perspective of workers, job candidates can invest in &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-to-evaluate-accept-reject-or-negotiate-a-job-offer&quot;>;building their negotiation skills&lt;/a>;, so that they can avoid being easily thrown off in their approach when organizations use social impact framing. They can also investigate how organizations that claim to care about human welfare &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-tell-if-a-potential-employer-has-a-burnout-culture&quot;>;treat their own employees&lt;/a>;. It would be ironic if a company that emphasizes social impact neglects its own workers&#39; well-being, financial or otherwise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations might also consider training managers about their biases against employee extrinsic motivation which, as described above, can be unfounded. Indeed, the desire to &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2014.0898&quot;>;provide&lt;/a>; for one&#39;s family, for instance, has been found to be a robust predictor of work performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By romanticizing intrinsic motivation and reflexively dismissing job candidates who express any interest in extrinsic job rewards, organizations might be turning away perfectly good candidates who are also passionate about the work and might well have been high performers. Not least, organizations that strive to take an ethical approach to business can avoid deploying social impact framing in a Machiavellian manner, as a tool to intentionally suppress pay.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Companies Can &mdash; and Should &mdash; Recommit to DEI in the Wake of the SCOTUS Decision]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_28_1401985.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Ruth Black/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In the wake of the US Supreme Court ban on affirmative action at colleges and universities, state legislation attaching diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts on campus, and more general attacks on DEI, companies are considering whether they need to change their DEI strategies. The short answer is they don&amp;#8217;t. But it is a good time to review corporate values, personnel policies, and engage with employees on these issues. The first step should be to remember the moral and business cases for DEI. They remain strong.&amp;#160; Second, you might reconsider using DEI labels, as some have suggested. But given employee support for such initiatives, proceed cautiously. Next, review HR practices like recruiting (including casting a wider net for candidates since the college pipeline will now be less diverse); onboarding (since some students will have less exposure to DEI than others); and performance reviews, pay, and promotion (to ensure there is no racial bias).&amp;#160; Finally, communicate carefully with what is sure to be a polarized workforce. Present credible research, solicit opinions, work to bridge divides. Ultimately, you want your organization to move forward in a way that is aligned with your organizational values.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/why-companies-can-and-should-recommit-to-dei-in-the-wake-of-the-scotus-decision?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The recent US Supreme Court decision banning affirmative action, specifically race-conscious admissions in colleges and universities, may not directly impact US workplaces, but there&#39;s no question that corporate America needs to consider the effect this — and potential future judicial rulings and state legislation — will have on their DEI practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At a minimum, any changes we see in student body composition at institutions of higher education will also affect hiring pipelines. For example, when the University of California&#39;s system eliminated affirmative action in 1995, Black student representation at UCLA dropped from 7% (compared with 13.6% for the US population and 6.5% for the state&#39;s) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;to 3.9% in just three years&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epi.org/blog/the-supreme-courts-ban-on-affirmative-action-means-colleges-will-struggle-to-meet-goals-of-diversity-and-equal-opportunity/&quot;>;to less than 2% by 2006&lt;/a>;. Likewise, when affirmative action was banned at the University of Michigan, Black undergraduate enrollment declined from 7% in 2006 (compared with 13.6% for the state population) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/31/us/politics/affirmative-action-ban-states.html&quot;>;to 4% in 2021&lt;/a>;. These case studies suggest that when universities eliminate affirmative action, they produce a less diverse candidate pool for employers to tap, and this is now likely to happen across the country.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Exacerbating the situation, there are also now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bestcolleges.com/news/anti-dei-legislation-tracker/&quot;>;more than 30 state or local bills&lt;/a>; targeting DEI funding, practices, and promotion at schools. For example, Texas has a ban beginning January 1, 2024, on all DEI offices, diversity training and “ideological oaths and statements” at public institutions, which could mean that companies recruiting on campus need to review their messaging.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There is much more at stake than diversity recruitment, however. As management thought leaders and expert scholars on race in the workplace, we anticipate many additional ripple effects. The ruling has already been interpreted as an invitation for DEI critics to challenge the validity, legality, and necessity of such efforts. For example, Will Hild, the executive director of Consumers&#39; Research, a right-wing advocacy group, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;has already gone on record&lt;/a>; to say that the SCOTUS decision on affirmative action “will put the wind in the sails of groups like ours, who want to get the woke, racially based hiring and promotion schemes out of corporate America.” The attorneys general of 13 Republican-led states have also sent&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tn.gov/content/dam/tn/attorneygeneral/documents/pr/2023/pr23-27-letter.pdf&quot;>; a letter&lt;/a>; to the CEOs of Fortune 100 companies warning that labels of “diversity, equity, and inclusion” are now “unlawful and wrong, per SCOTUS.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, college admissions are governed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crt/fcs/TitleVI&quot;>;Title VI&lt;/a>; of the Civil Rights Act, which prohibits discrimination on the basis of race, color or national origin under any program or activity receiving federal financial assistance. Private employment falls under &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/statutes/title-vii-civil-rights-act-1964&quot;>;Title VII&lt;/a>; and is enforced by the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), currently led by Charlotte A. Burrows, who has emphasized that the SCOTUS decision has no bearing on its work. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/statement-eeoc-chair-charlotte-burrows-supreme-court-ruling-college-affirmative-action&quot;>;a statement&lt;/a>;, she said, “It does not address employer efforts to foster diverse and inclusive workforces or to engage the talents of all qualified workers, regardless of their background. It remains lawful for employers to implement diversity, equity, inclusion, and accessibility programs that seek to ensure workers of all backgrounds are afforded equal opportunity in the workplace.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That means most corporate DEI efforts are formally safe for now. However, it&#39;s important for organizations to pay attention to the changing landscape.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Taking a Step Back &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s consider whether we still believe race should be considered when making organizational decisions. That depends in part on whether we believe racism still affects our society. If we do, it seems plausible and just to recommend interventions that consider race. If we don&#39;t (or if we are okay with racism), it would seem implausible and unjust to recommend interventions that consider race. So, we ask you, does racism still affect our society? And do we care?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the systematic oppression of Black Americans, who have long been erroneously held up as the face of affirmative action in the United States (while research shows that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-who-benefits-white-women/70371219007/&quot;>;white women&lt;/a>; are instead the biggest beneficiaries of such policies). Even after the abolishment of slavery in 1865, the United States continued to codify the oppression of Black people in legal, political, and social systems. From the post-war &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/brown-v-board-50th-anniversary/southern-black-codes.html&quot;>;Black Codes&lt;/a>; to the 1896 &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.gov/milestone-documents/plessy-v-ferguson&quot;>;Plessy v. Ferguson&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; SCOTUS decision to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crf-usa.org/black-history-month/a-brief-history-of-jim-crow&quot;>;Jim Crow laws&lt;/a>; in the US South, white power structures denied Black people full citizenship and equal protection under the law. Counter measures, including Congressional actions such as the landmark 13th, 14th and 15th Amendments, the Supreme Court&#39;s 1954 Brown vs. Board of Education decision, and the Civil Rights Act of 1964, which finally banned racial discrimination from public places, schools and workplaces, represented progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, having been denied the ability to advance professionally and create wealth for more than a century post-slavery, Black people remain disproportionately underrepresented in professional workplaces and leadership roles. As fellow researchers Tony Mayo and Laura Morgan Roberts have &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/toward-a-racially-just-workplace&quot;>;described&lt;/a>;, they are less likely than their white peers to be hired, developed, and promoted. Other racioethnic populations — Latino, Native American, Pacific Islanders — have faced different types of discrimination and are also underrepresented in higher-earning roles and occupations, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/opub/reports/race-and-ethnicity/2020/home.htm&quot;>;data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://extramural-diversity.nih.gov/diversity-matters/underrepresented-groups&quot;>;industry groups&lt;/a>;. This suggests that racism does still affect our society. The United States is not living up to its founding ideals of allowing all citizens to pursue life, liberty, and happiness in equal measure. We should care — and keep working toward those goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A next question to ask is whether we believe diverse teams benefit organizational performance. Ample research shows that they make &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;smarter decisions&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/the-other-diversity-dividend&quot;>;better investments&lt;/a>;, are &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-investing-in-dei-helps-companies-become-more-adaptable&quot;>;more adaptable&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/how-and-where-diversity-drives-financial-performance&quot;>;drive innovation&lt;/a>; when the corporate culture in which they operate is a supportive, &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/research-to-excel-diverse-teams-need-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychologically safe&lt;/a>; one. Diverse and well-trained workforces and leadership teams are also better suited to interact with diverse employees, customers and vendors. Thus, there is still both a moral and a business case for supporting DEI efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some corporate leaders still might be wondering whether they should rethink their whole DEI strategy in light of recent attacks on affirmative action. The short answer is no. Now is not the time to reverse the commitments they made to racial equity in the aftermath of George Floyd&#39;s 2020 murder. Instead, it&#39;s time to clarify organizational values around DEI, clearly communicate them, and ensure that people management processes are aligned with them. Here, we explain how to go about this at this critical moment in US history.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Rethinking L&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;abels&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Given the SCOTUS ruling, other pending state legislation, and the warning from those 13 attorneys general, some legal scholars &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/affirmative-action-business-diversity/&quot;>;have suggested&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;that companies preemptively protect themselves by moving away from DEI labels to ones clearly protected by law. For example, instead of a chief diversity officer, you would have a Title VII compliance officer. Another option is to use words like “inclusion,” “belonging,” and “engagement” to emphasize that the goal is improving organizational culture not necessarily racial diversity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We urge caution on this front because DEI remains important to employees. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.bfldr.com/ZZ11QL2O/at/6bpw94vrt588vtc8gr3fgw5/C001_Benevity_TheStateofWorkplaceDEI_Final.pdf?hsCtaTracking=e0c17c58-a6ca-4e73-978b-87718706789f%7C57928514-8a0c-4227-bf1f-498f3e23c304&quot;>;a 2023 Benevity survey&lt;/a>; found that 95% of people weigh a prospective employer&#39;s DEI efforts when choosing between job offers with similar salary and benefits and that 78% would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; consider working for a company that fails to commit significant resources to DEI initiatives. Employees from historically marginalized backgrounds will almost certainly feel disregarded and devalued if their organizations shy away from DEI labels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, any good DEI strategy requires regular evaluation to ensure it is performing against goals set and having the intended impact on employees. And when faced with a big organizational change or new rules and regulations, leaders should have a system in place to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ellavatesolutions.com/the-ellavate-approach&quot;>;tune-up existing DEI&lt;/a>; strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reviewing Processes &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recruitment&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As highlighted earlier, we can expect a smaller percentage of racially marginalized individuals to be admitted to predominantly white institutions (PWI), so companies still seeking diversity in their candidate pool will need to look elsewhere to find as much of it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One solution is to increase recruiting at institutions such as historically Black colleges and universities (HBCUs), Hispanic-serving institutions (HSIs), and tribal colleges and universities (TCUs). Another is to consider non-traditional pathways such as community colleges and building partnerships with community organizations that focus on racially diverse pipelines, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://oneten.org/about/mission/&quot;>;OneTen&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend a shift to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/skills-based-hiring-is-on-the-rise&quot;>;skills-based hiring&lt;/a>;, a well-established DEI best practice that focuses on matching skills between job candidates and roles instead of focusing on only education and experience. Consider partnering with organizations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://opportunityatwork.org/stars/&quot;>;STARS&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlt.org/&quot;>;MLT&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://reachingoutmba.org/&quot;>;ROMBA&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://toigofoundation.org/&quot;>;Toigo Foundation&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fortefoundation.org/site/PageServer&quot;>;Forte Foundation&lt;/a>; (full disclosure: the latter two are clients of Tina) that help identify talent employers need.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Onboarding&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many companies now include DEI education as part of their onboarding programs. But they can no longer make assumptions about employee readiness for these conversations. For example, a student educated at a public institution in Florida is now expressly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wbur.org/onpoint/2023/05/23/what-the-desantis-agenda-means-for-higher-education-in-florida&quot;>;prohibited&lt;/a>; from taking a course that “teaches identity politics, or is based on theories that systemic racism, sexism, oppression, and privilege are inherent in the institutions of the United States.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers might therefore need to implement surveys to understand how much new hires know about DEI and take greater care in explaining to new team members why those principles matter to the organization, not just how they&#39;re implemented.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Performance reviews, pay, promotions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As DEI efforts become more highly scrutinized, there is even more reason to make sure your people processes are equitable. Performance evaluations and pay and promotion decisions should be based on standard and objective data — yet a multitude of research indicates that they remain riddled with bias, especially for members of historically marginalized racioethnic groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;one study&lt;/a>; found that 90% of people of color but only 72% of white people received notes about their personalities in their reviews. Now is a good time to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/how-one-company-worked-to-root-out-bias-from-performance-reviews&quot;>;audit these processes&lt;/a>; so no one can argue that you are favoring people of one race over another.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Communicating Carefully &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2023/06/08/more-americans-disapprove-than-approve-of-colleges-considering-race-ethnicity-in-admissions-decisions/&quot;>;public polling&lt;/a>; is any indication employee reaction to the affirmative action ruling will depend on their race and ethnicity, political affiliation, and how they have seen affirmative action framed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Adept managers should be able to surface and address different opinions, show empathy, create employee feedback and support systems, and regularly communicate about these issues. Tools to use include one-on-one meetings (if a few employees are highly concerned); town halls (if many people are worried); emails (if many people have low-intensity interest); or simply monitoring the situation for now (if awareness remains low among most people.) &amp;nbsp;Conversations might be difficult, but it is important for teams to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/dig-bridge-collectively-act&quot;>;dig into sometimes polarizing topics, bridge divides, and agree on collective action&lt;/a>; where possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A cornerstone of successful communication is to include research from credible outlets but, in these polarized times, it can be challenging to find &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/journalism/2020/01/24/us-media-polarization-and-the-2020-election-a-nation-divided/&quot;>;sources&lt;/a>; trusted by all employees. We recommend identifying multiple ones and explaining the vetting process to employees. Organizations will also benefit from conducting surveys to learn about differing views and identifying and seeking input on informal leaders on all sides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With both facts and opinions in hand, leaders will be better equipped to communicate effective messages about their DEI plans. They might, for example, acknowledge that some employees disagree with race-conscious recruiting, or think DEI efforts should be dropped for legal or cost-saving reasons, but explain that the organization prioritizes the increased innovation that comes from having a more diverse team or simply having a workforce that represents the broader society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is important that everyone engages on this issue. While some organizations relegate DEI to HR and HR alone, this is a mistake. Messaging on — and commitment to — DEI should be understood and communicated by everyone from frontline managers to the CEO, especially now when racial tensions remain high and policies like affirmative action are being questioned.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Moving Forward&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Now that the media furor over &lt;em>;Students for Fair Admissions v Harvard University and the University of North Carolina&lt;/em>; has slightly abated, organizations have a moment to strategically reflect on how their DEI efforts may be affected. We believe corporate leaders should resist the urge or pressure to backpedal on DEI commitments. Instead, they should enhance DEI in a manner that complies with the law, aligns with their organizational values, and benefits their businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>