<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Will AI Replace the Front Office in Pro Sports?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_516776669.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论员工/Gizelka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;通过对所有活跃玩家的准确玩家可用性预测，人工智能驱动的决策在三个方面得到显着改进：1) 风险管理：例如，如果一名高效的外接手可能受伤，球队可能会在有天赋的替补上投入更多，以尽量减少受伤期间球队表现的下降。 2) 训练和有针对性的干预：如果人工智能表明一名球员容易受伤，球队可以针对该球员进行定制训练、营养或其他方案，以减少受伤的可能性。或者，球队可能会选择减少球员的工作量，同时降低风险。 3) 人事决定：通过识别预测伤病或其他无法上场的因素，球队可以选秀、交易或以其他方式获得他们认为更有可能在整个赛季都上场的球员。此外，球队可能会选择交易可能受伤的球员。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will -ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the- front-office-in-pro-sports?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;2023 年 3 月 15 日，标志着国家橄榄球联盟新赛季的正式开始。这也意味着 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcsports.com/boston/patriots/nfl-free-agency-tracker-2023-top-players-signings-start-time-cap-space&quot; 的开始>;自由代理期&lt;/a>;，当球队与不再与前球队签订合同的球员进行交易时；每一份新合同都可能意味着团队预算的数百万美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此正确招聘至关重要。与任何企业一样，NFL 高管和其他职业运动队的领导者必须就如何最好地分配他们有限的预算做出决定，对他们将从资产（在这种情况下为球员）中获得的投资回报率进行明智的押注，包括与预期表现相关的投资回报率（场上和场下）、未来的伤病和其他因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但如果今年，人工智能可以告诉我们一名球员在他们的职业生涯中还剩下多少场比赛，他们接下来会得到多少分呢？赛季，或者他们是否会在不久的将来遭受重大伤病？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然自由球员和其他招募机制已经存在了几十年，&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;关于球员的决定正在发生变化迅速。具体而言，将基于 AI 的技术应用于大量体育数据集正在增强前台部门对球员做出决策的能力——招募、培养、替补或交易谁。它将永久性地改变所有职业运动的运作方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是 AI 会很快取代运动队的前台吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这项新技术肯定会增强人类的决策-我们认为它不会在不久的将来取代体育或其他行业的一般管理团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;改变游戏规则的预测能力&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Amid越来越多的以人工智能为基础的以体育为中心的产品，其中一些旨在帮助团队决策者预测运动员的受伤和寿命。了解在特定时间范围内受伤的可能性对招募有很大影响，因为球队自然会瞄准有望更长时间保持无伤病的球员。对于导致受伤的因素，例如时间和现场“里程”，行业高管总是有一些基于经验的直觉。有时，这些预测是正确的，但通常情况下并非如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在的不同之处在于，人工智能可以支持一些传统智慧——例如，在 NFL 中，30 岁以上的外接手更适合例如，容易受伤和其他挑战——但也可以提供更具体的受伤或表现下降可能性的估计，以及这对给定球员的可用性意味着什么，以及这可能会让球队付出什么代价。一家名为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://probility.ai/&quot;>;Probility AI&lt;/a>; 的公司声称，预测哪些球员下赛季将缺席比赛的准确率为 96%。高管们可以使用这些结果，从“我认为这可能是一个重要因素”转变为“我知道这是一个重要因素，并且可以以前所未有的信心估计其影响和成本。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI 生成的见解远远超过现有的或直觉支持的。例如，Probility AI 根据来自特定 NFL 球队的数据以及其他公共和私人数据源训练其伤害预测模型，以了解特定球员上大学的地点、他们担任的主教练和助理教练的组合等因素的影响根据和随之而来的实践和工作量需求。虽然这些新生的见解值得进一步研究，但它们显示了 AI 在其预测分析中可以深入到什么程度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，与其让总经理试图确保总体上最好的广泛接受者，他们可以找到根据 AI 对未来伤病和表现的预测，&lt;em>;他们团队的最佳接球手&lt;/em>;。由于球员在接受不同的教练、场地条件或队友时通常有不同的预测职业生涯长度和表现结果，这就造成了套利情况，即球员市场价值因球员效力的球队而异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多支 NFL 球队正在部署 Probility AI 和 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/techtank/2021/03/18/how-the-nfl-is-using-ai-to-evaluate-players /&quot;>;其他来源&lt;/a>;，有充分的理由：不这样做会使他们与配备 AI 的同行相比处于劣势。当然，此类模型也被用于其他运动，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/12/22/artificial-intelligence-is-the-new-competitive-edge-in-sports /&quot;>;足球和篮球&lt;/a>;创造价值，并跨业务部门&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2022/11/21/the-top-five- ways-ai-is-transforming-business/?sh=139d9da98e7f&quot;>;增强活动&lt;/a>;，包括告知决策、提高生产力和更好地为客户服务。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;增强，而非替代&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;因此，随着 AI 在运动的关键方面（伤病、交易时机等）获得预测能力，它会取代前台吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;简而言之，不会。现在，将 AI 视为&lt;em>;增强&lt;/em>;人类决策。它不会取代高管，但会帮助他们做出更好的决策，尤其是在更容易出现人为错误和偏见的领域，例如主要根据直觉进行招聘和做“以前行之有效的事情”。过去 20 年的&lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2016/04/02/moneyball-is-dead-long-live-moneyball/&quot;>;点球成金运动&lt;/a>;一直是关于使用以更严格、系统的方式进行球员统计，AI 使用更深入的学习来更好地预测性能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过对所有活跃球员的准确球员可用性预测，决策制定在三个方面得到显着改善：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;风险管理&lt;/strong>;：例如，如果高效的外接手可能受伤，团队可能会在有天赋的替补上投入更多，以尽量减少流失&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;训练和有针对性的干预：&lt;/strong>;如果 AI 表明一名球员容易受伤，球队可以针对该球员进行定制训练、营养或其他方案，以减少受伤的可能性。或者，球队可能会选择减少球员的工作量，同时降低风险。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人事决定&lt;/strong>;：通过确定预测受伤或其他不可用的因素，球队可以选秀、交易、或者以其他方式获得他们认为更有可能在整个赛季可用的球员。此外，球队可能会选择交易可能受伤的球员。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;精明的高管还会将伤病预测纳入财务决策。也就是说，AI 不仅可以生成关于球员可用性的预测，还可以将这些预测输入财务决策引擎，使团队领导者能够针对每花费一美元的预期生产率创建细化指标。例如，一名预计在给定年份仅参加 50% 比赛的跑卫在功能上的成本是可以参加每场比赛的类似费用的跑卫的两倍。通过考虑为每个结果支付的价格（获得的码数、铲球次数、得分等），团队可以以最有效的方式分配他们的资金，优化花费的每一美元的生产率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，该技术由本身是不够的。虽然软件可以分析球员引擎和资源分配，但体育高管的判断力和风险承受能力最终必须在不可避免的权衡中做出选择，并决定所做的决定。我们在上一节中分享了更多相关信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，AI 绝对是职业运动的游戏规则改变者，并且正在取代非正式甚至基于统计的决策，成为由以下因素推动的综合系统的引擎大数据和前所未有的预测能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;很容易看出由 AI 生成的更好的预测将如何对任何企业产生巨大影响。这里的一个类比是预测建筑等劳动密集型行业的工人绩效何时会受到影响，或者为制造厂或炼油厂提供动力的大型设备何时会发生故障或失效，并在发生代价高昂的事件之前采取预防措施。该方法适用于任何资源老化的企业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;更广泛地说，预测从服装到玉米等任何事物的需求将使企业领导者能够就生产做出更好的决策，包括与供应链和其他领域相关的决策。其他基于人工智能的算法可以预测竞争。这样的例子不胜枚举，AI 已经以这些方式和其他方式应用于各个行业，这有助于解释为什么 AI 初创公司获得了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/artificial-intelligence-trends-2023-business -healthcare-2023-1&quot;>;2022 年将获得近 14 亿美元的资金&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;不要越界&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当然使用预测性 AI 有局限性，进一步强化了增强与替代的想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，关于预测 NFL 伤害，虽然新技术可以指导有关招募、交易和支付多少的决策对于给定的球员，教练团队必须从战略上考虑整个团队的动态。 AI 可能会告诉您是时候用具有给定特征的球员替换容易受伤的跑卫了，但是高管必须考虑如何最好地将新招募的人融入团队。毕竟，总风险分散在所有参与者及其互动中。在这方面，AI 也越来越善于理解团队的大局及其影响，从起始团队规模较小的运动开始，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://uwaterloo.ca/news/media/artificial- intelligence-makes-it-faster-easier-analyze&quot;>;曲棍球&lt;/a>;，它在给定时间让不超过 6 名球员在冰上。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，重要的是要了解 AI-基于产品的产品并没有提供明确的“答案”，而是在其置信区间内进行预测。随着技术的进步，这个间隔会缩小，但总会有一些与预测相关的松动，而这又是人类判断至关重要的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，人工智能绝对是体育运动的游戏规则改变者，赋予管理层和教练前所未有的预测能力，使他们能够做出越来越多的决策，对绩效和回报产生重大影响，为球员提供延长职业生涯的洞察力，并让更多球员继续上场，这让球迷兴奋不已。但这仍然是一个增强的故事，在这个故事中，领导者使用新技术来告知他们基于经验的直觉，必须尽其所能做出战略决定，并对现场和资产负债表上发生的事情保持责任感。&lt;/p>; &lt; !-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Scale Local Innovations in Big Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_1157569960.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Magnetic-Mcc/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;太频繁的创新 &amp;#8212;包括新产品、吸引和留住人才的新人力资源政策，以及新的生产流程——在企业的某个部分开发的。其他可以从中受益的群体并不知道​​它们的存在。这会导致收入损失和成本增加，因为世界各地的团队通常最终会在解决常见问题时进行重复（或三倍或四倍）投资。本文确定了扩展创新的三个常见障碍，并描述了克服这些障碍的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-scale-local -innovations-in-big-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;规模和范围的业务优势得到广泛认可，但大型全球企业往往未能充分意识到这些优势说到创新。在一个地理区域或业务部门开发的创新——取悦客户的新产品、吸引和留住人才的新 HR 政策、推动效率提高的新生产流程——往往停留在他们内部，而不是传播到整个企业。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;考虑一家全球消费品公司及其三个区域业务部门的经验。 （Innosight 是该公司的顾问）。 Region 1 开发了一个针对年轻消费者的新品牌，他们越来越寻求更健康的产品。区域 2 以提高盈利能力的方式改变了生产流程。 3 区开发了新的以可持续发展为重点的商业模式。由于我们一再看到的原因，本可以引进这些创新的地区忽视了它们，或者更糟的是，根本没有意识到它们，因为它们在孤岛中进行创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;并非所有事情都需要在全球范围内扩展。针对本地市场的本地创新很重要。但是，如果不扩大许多在本地诞生但确实具有巨大全球潜力的创新，就会带来重大的不利影响。其中包括收入损失，因为源自一个地区的新产品可能会出售给其他地区的客户，以及更高的成本，因为世界各地的团队通常最终会在解决常见问题时进行重复（或三倍或四倍）投资。麦当劳首席执行官 Chris Kempczinski 在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/mcdonalds-shutters-us-offices-ahead-of-layoffs-report/448927&quot;>;a 中强调了这一点最近的备忘录&lt;/a>;，他在其中指出跨地区合作不足意味着“我们试图多次解决相同的问题，并不总是分享想法，并且创新速度可能很慢。”&lt;/p>; &lt; p>; 全球扩展不足引起的其他缺点不太明显，但也很重要。当以相似产品组合起步的区域性企业不共享创新，而是彼此孤立地发展时，这些产品组合会随着时间的推移变得更加分歧。这导致了产品线的激增，这使得企业中心更难优化资源分配，也更难让股东评估公司并了解其增长前景。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;扩大规模存在三个常见障碍从一个市场到多个市场的创新。为了说明障碍和克服这些障碍的解决方案，我们将使用 Innosight 建议的全球零售银行的案例。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;关于本地唯一性的谬误&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt; p>;虽然每个地区都不同，但当地领导者往往会高估他们的市场、客户和运营条件的独特性。但通常情况下，新产品和其他创新——以及从它们的开发中获得的能力和知识——比他们想象的更容易转移，尤其是当它们与跨地区共享的创新优先事项保持一致时。创新重点或“战略重点领域”本质上是创新的广阔猎场。例如，在消费品公司，一项创新重点是包装，这导致了材料、尺寸和格式方面的具体创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们转向银行。它的一个区域单位已投入大量资金开发数字抵押贷款申请平台，进一步自动化其抵押贷款申请流程，使其更快、对消费者更友好。尽管抵押贷款是跨地区的重要产品线，但大多数人不愿意考虑采用这种创新，认为抵押贷款在各自市场中的不同监管方式使其不可行。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;监管框架确实因国家/地区而异当然，但不会以阻止这种创新被广泛采用的方式，因为该平台的实施可以适应每个市场监管要求的差异，这与现有抵押贷款申请流程的定制方式非常相似到当地市场。此外，该平台符合各地区共享的创新优先事项，包括数字化和改善现有产品旅程中的客户体验，以及提高抵押贷款的盈利能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为克服这一障碍，该银行的中央企业战略团队促进了确定跨区域共同创新优先事项的过程。首先，要求各地区以标准方式定义各自的创新重点（例如，“新的电子商务支付和融资解决方案”），确定相关的目标客户群、要解决的客户问题，以及广泛的技术和创新类型。所需的能力。该银行的四个区域中的每个区域都定义了 5 到 10 个创新优先事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，公司战略团队促进了每个区域的高级领导之间的一系列讨论，以比较和确定他们创新优先事项的共同点。这浮现出所有四个地区共有的多个优先事项。除了与抵押贷款申请平台相关的那些之外，它们还包括为千禧一代和 Z 世代消费者开发新的纯移动产品，以及减少呼叫中心的使用和等待时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与这些优先事项相一致的创新然后可以将其识别为可共享的，无论它们来自何处。跨地区团队对共同创新优先事项的认识也促使设计师和产品开发人员之间的&lt;a href=&quot;/2000/01/communities-of-practice-the-organizational-frontier&quot;>;实践社区&lt;/a>;有机地出现。他们定期召开会议，交流想法、传播经验教训，并共同创造符合这些共同优先事项的新创新。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;激励和文化错位&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;各种正式和非正式的抑制因素是扩大创新的另一个障碍。例如，区域领导者的奖金通常基于其所在部门的损益表 现，这可能使他们不愿意花费时间、精力和资源来输出有益于另一个区域的创新。相反，“不是在这里发明”的心态会使经理们不愿引进外部产生的想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该银行的奖金计划严重惩罚了未能实现雄心勃勃的盈利目标的当地领导者。这使他们不愿将资源用于出口创新。此外，“不是在这里发明”的心态很普遍——从想要证明自己独立创新能力的地区领导者到更愿意编写自己的代码而不是使用其他地区同行开发的软件的开发人员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为解决这些问题，该银行根据具体情况向地区提供损益减免，允许他们偏离盈利目标而无需冒奖金风险，这样他们就可以将自己的资源投入到规模化创新中，以实现其他地区的利益。它还建立了一个中央基金和团队来支持全球扩展工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;正在开发可以解决共同优先事项的创新的区域被邀请提交简短的“全球扩展资源请求”，其中总结了扩展所需的额外投资他们到其他地区，而不仅仅是他们自己的地区。该请求可能是为了支付以使其可在全球技术环境中运行的方式构建产品的成本，例如，或者培训和支持其他地区用户所需的团队时间以及潜在的年内损益权衡&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由公司最高管理层领导以及中央战略和财务主管组成的全球扩展委员会决定批准哪些请求。大多数为解决共同优先事项的规模创新而提交的资源请求都获得了批准。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该银行的企业领导者还试图通过公开表彰分享其地区创新和采用他人创造的创新的管理人员来改变态度。他们在地区高管出席的全天季度业务回顾会议上重点介绍了全球扩展计划，出口和进口地区共同讨论了创新及其扩展过程。该银行的领导还在公司简报中强调了此类创新和参与这些工作的团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，该银行的领导鼓励并经常提醒区域经理在否定其他人开发的潜在创新之前问自己一系列问题地区。它们包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;我们能否通过采用这项创新更好地服务我们拥有或寻求的客户？&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;如果创新不是它是否特定于我们的一个或多个当地情况——例如，如果它是在不同的技术、监管或竞争环境的背景下开发的，或者需要我们缺乏的生产或分配方式——它是否可以适应？ &lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;如果我们的第一直觉是拒绝这项创新，我们是否会因为拥有“不是这里发明”的心态而感到内疚？&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;缺乏透明度&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;正如我们所提到的，业务部门不分享创新而经常重复工作的一个主要原因是缺乏对彼此所拥有的知识的了解开发或正在开发。解决这个问题的一种方法是创建一个中央机制，使各地区可以轻松地从最早阶段分享其创新追求的知识。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑我们提到的所有银行地区共享的一个创新优先事项：为千禧一代开发仅限移动设备的产品。跨地区与这一优先事项一致的创新包括不同的支付、储蓄和投资产品；新产品功能，如综合储蓄、现金返还和奖励；创新以简化仅移动应用程序中的客户旅程，并与吸引千禧一代受众的预算和账单分割工具集成。但各地区对彼此的努力缺乏了解，在某些情况下甚至在相同事物的开发上重复支出。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该银行通过两种方式解决了这个问题：通过建立识别跨地区共同创新优先事项的流程我们之前描述的，并通过建立一个创新组合管理系统来描述和跟踪创新。要求各地区在 IT 系统中输入每个创新项目的描述，包括相关的创新优先级、目标客户群、其收入潜力和预期的投资要求。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;除了支持全球扩展外，该系统还帮助每个地区更好地了解和管理自己的创新渠道。当发现区域在不知不觉中相互重复工作的实例时，它们能够协作并汇集他们的见解、开发能力和数据资产。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;太多的全球企业没有充分利用本地创新。通过系统地克服扩大它们的障碍，他们可以更快、更有效地传播它们，并产生更高的创新投资回报。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women in Leadership Face Ageism at Every Age]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_14_1415442562.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/aldomurillo/Imagehit/Hero Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close- caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;最初，年龄歧视被理解为针对年长员工的偏见、刻板印象和歧视行为。但随着越来越多样化和多代的劳动力，年龄偏见现在出现在整个职业生命周期中——特别是对于女性。 “青年主义”指的是对年轻人的年龄歧视，这是由于将年龄与成熟度混为一谈，以及认为能力需要终身任职的误解。甚至中年女性也感受到了年龄偏见的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;工作场所的年龄多样性会产生更好的组织绩效，而感知到的年龄歧视会降低工作满意度和敬业度。好消息是，领导者可以采取切实可行的措施来打击这种永远不对的性别年龄偏见。首先，认识到您组织中的年龄歧视；你可以解决不存在的问题。接下来，与您的员工一起解决“外表主义”，并专注于技能，无论谁拥有技能。最后，培养创造性的合作以鼓励跨年龄段的学习。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in -leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at- every-age?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当一位大学副校长有一个职位空缺，可以聘请一位在等级制度中仅次于她的主管时，董事会成员告诉她要寻找一个“年长的男人”来补充她。自从她 37 岁开始担任副总裁以来，董事会成员经常批评她的年龄，称她 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90569439/we-need-to-talk-about-using-pet -names-for-women-at-work&quot;>;减少昵称&lt;/a>;，例如“kiddo”和“young lady”。但年纪大了不一定会有所不同，正如另一位女士所解释的那样：“我正处于应该获得更高级别工作的年龄；我这个行业的人现在想把工作交给 30 岁和 40 岁以下的有‘新鲜、新想法’的人，而不是让有经验的人去。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最初，年龄歧视被理解为&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.0021-9029.2006.00062.x&quot;>;针对年长员工&lt;/a>;的偏见、刻板印象和歧视行为。由于人们错误地认为随着年龄的增长，绩效会恶化并且能力会下降，年长的员工预计只会 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias -hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;悄悄离开&lt;/a>;，让年轻的人才可以接管工作。随着越来越多样化和跨代的劳动力，年龄偏见现在&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1468-0432.2004.00222.x&quot;>;贯穿整个职业生命周期&lt;/a>;。 “&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/xge0001064&quot;>;Youngism&lt;/a>;”指的是对年轻人的年龄歧视，其原因是将年龄与成熟度混为一谈，并误认为获得终身职位才能获得能力.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，研究才刚刚开始调查年龄是如何被用来为特别针对女性的偏见和歧视辩护的。性别年龄歧视位于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/bonniemarcus/2021/09/20/gendered-ageism-affects-womens-job-security-and-financial-viability/&quot;>;年龄和性别偏见的交集&lt;/a>;并且是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/fighting- the-double-whammy-of-ageism-sexism.aspx&quot;>;double whammy&lt;/a>; 职业女性“没有合适的年龄”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们最近对 913 的开放式调查研究中来自美国四个行业（高等教育、基于信仰的非营利组织、法律和医疗保健）的女性领导者，我们发现许多女性都患有这种“永远不对”的年龄偏见。年轻、中年和老年的概念通常基于感知，并且因工作场所和环境而异。在解释我们的结果时，我们认为“年轻”是指 40 岁以下，中年是指 40 到 60 岁之间，老年女性是指 60 岁以上。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;性别“老年主义”&lt;/strong>; &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;随着女性年龄的增长，她们往往不像男性那样被视为有价值或相关的。在我们的研究中，年长的女性表示她们被认为不值得提升。 “当男人随着年龄的增长而成为智慧之源时，年长的女性则被认为是过时的、狡猾的、刺耳的，”一位医生指出。 “我们的声音被低估了。”例如，一位 61 岁的副首席信息官 (CIO) 没有被纳入 CIO 继任计划的考虑范围。相反，现任 CIO 正在培养一名男同事担任该职位。另一位退休年龄的女性补充说：“我在很大程度上被忽视了。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些女性中的许多人感到灰心、精疲力尽，并因不再继续前进而辞职。正如一位 66 岁的信仰领袖所说，“在我这个年纪，而且我们组织的心态是他们需要高层管理人员，所以没有下一步的专业步骤。”同一行业的另一位女性指出，一旦她年满 60 岁，她就不再“值得投资培训或指导”。 Others felt compelled to find opportunities outside of their organization: “I am tired of proving myself to others and may as well do it in the interests of my own company,” a 60-year-old lawyer indicated.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Youngism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Younger women — and those who looked young — were called pet names or even patted on the head, as one 39-year-old woman reported. Young women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/when-people-assume-youre-not-in-charge-because-youre-a-woman&quot;>;role incredulity&lt;/a>;. They reported being mistaken for students, interns, trainees, support staff, secretaries, paralegals, and court reporters. Such inaccurate assumptions were especially prevalent for non-White women, such as an Asian higher-education executive who appeared young and was presumed to be in a junior position.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many younger women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;https://rowman.com/ISBN/9781538170960/Glass-Walls-Shattering-the-Six-Gender-Bias-Barriers-Still-Holding-Women-Back-at-Work&quot;>;credibility deficit&lt;/a>;, which occurs when women&#39;s statements and expertise are not believed. “I am often told that I don&#39;t have the experience so I can&#39;t know what to do,” one 34-year-old woman explained. In the face of such bias, women (and especially women of color) must expend extra effort to prove themselves. One young-looking Black university chief financial officer noted that she is often “pressed to provide a synopsis of her resume to establish credibility.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other younger women had their appearance scrutinized. One physician noted that between ages 20 and 40, men focused on her looks. After she gave a scientific presentation that she was very proud of, a male colleague told her that she “looked like a Barbie doll up there!”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Middle-ageism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unlike previous notions of a middle-aged “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias-hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;sweet spot&lt;/a>;,” women between ages 40 and 60 in our study fared no better than their younger or older counterparts. One college leader described how some search committees chose not to hire women in their late forties because of “too much family responsibility and impending menopause.” Other search committees declined to hire women in their fifties because they have “menopause-related issues and could be challenging to manage.” And still other committees said that “women in their fifties and sixties may not have &#39;aged well&#39; and do not &#39;look vital.&#39;” Yet the jobs were given to similarly aged men.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lawyer summed up the never-right age bias problem in her field:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we are too young to be responsible or to supervise. This lasts into our mid- to late-thirties but does not for men. (Perhaps they are waiting to make sure we don&#39;t have kids). Then in an instant, we are too old to be hired for anything or anywhere new. Once again, men are still “young enough” at the same age…. Women are young or old, we get no prime time even if we aren&#39;t out for childbearing or rearing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our research we found no age was the right age to be a woman leader. There was always an age-based excuse to not take women seriously, to discount their opinions, or to not hire or promote them. Each individual woman may believe she&#39;s just at the wrong age, but the data make the larger pattern clear. Any age can be stigmatized by supervisors and colleagues to claim that the woman is not valued or is not a fit for a leadership role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Age diversity in the workplace yields better &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/apl0000497&quot;>;organizational performance&lt;/a>; while perceived age discrimination creates &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/josi.12161&quot;>;lower job satisfaction and engagement&lt;/a>;. Similarly, gender diversity also matters. Organizations with diverse leadership teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0148296320303490?via%3Dihub&quot;>;perform better&lt;/a>;, especially in times of crisis; &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2729348&quot;>;earn more&lt;/a>;; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1748-8583.12079&quot;>;have lower turnover.&lt;/a>; The business case is clear — if organizational leaders pay attention. The good news is that there are practical steps for leaders to combat this never-right gendered age bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Combat Gendered Ageism&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recognize age bias&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;You can&#39;t fix a problem you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinessdevelopmentcouncil/2020/09/28/gendered-ageism-is-the-new-sexism/?sh=65b14a2214b1&quot;>;won&#39;t admit is there&lt;/a>;. Whereas sexism and racism are the focus of most workplace diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, ageism has been largely neglected. All employees should be trained on gendered age bias, just as they are on other forms of discrimination. Use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-news/pages/avoiding-age-discrimination-.aspx&quot;>;interactive case studies&lt;/a>; that include “gray areas” in age-related assumptions and address false stereotypes that older age reduces an individual&#39;s commitment, agility, and ability to learn. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/global-campaign-to-combat-ageism-toolkit&quot;>;Company social media can also be leveraged to get the word out&lt;/a>; about ageism using messaging that taps into both emotions and facts. When the problem ceases to be ignored, necessary improvements can be made.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Address “&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;lookism&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;.” &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Much of gendered ageism is hinged on looks or appearance as a function of societal value. The incessant pressure to look young and attractive is something that &lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/lookism-beauty-still-trumps-brains-in-too-many-workplaces-148278&quot;>;typically impacts women more than men.&lt;/a>; Include &lt;a href=&quot;https://fisherpub.sjf.edu/sfd/vol2/iss1/6/&quot;>;lookism&lt;/a>; in DEI training and ensure that it&#39;s not used as a hidden metric for hiring, promotion, or performance evaluation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Focus on &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;skills&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;, no matter who has them&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Younger women are often limited — whether intentionally or not — by the assumption of lack of experience. Middle-aged women may be thought of as difficult to manage or having too many family responsibilities. Women who are older are often constrained by perceptions that they are no longer invested in the organization, are less productive, or cannot be promoted. These falsehoods perpetuate the problem. Rather than focusing on age when hiring, making promotion decisions, or bringing on new team members for a growth opportunity, leaders should focus on each woman&#39;s skills, not their tenure or external demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Cultivate creative collaborations.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Develop intergenerational, mixed-gender teams and professional relationships to encourage &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2018/11/13/what-older-workers-and-younger-workers-can-learn-from-each-other/?sh=5c7f9a9e2117&quot;>;learning from each other and collaborating on solutions&lt;/a>;. Middle-aged and older employees have years of experience, while younger employees have perspectives from growing up in a more recent time. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springtideresearch.org/research/work-life&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>; of Generation Z&#39;s expectations at work showed that one of their highest desires was for mentoring relationships; they long for connection with older workers who take &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/organizational-and-employee-development/pages/generation-z-seeks-guidance-in-the-workplace.aspx&quot;>;an interest in them&lt;/a>;. Too often women lack connections that would help them develop professionally due to exclusion from informal networks and events. Intentionally pairing younger women with older mentors and sponsors will aid their learning and career success and enhance your company&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The research is clear: Any age can be viewed as “the wrong age” for a woman, allowing her capacity to be questioned and her fitness for leadership challenged. But we can stop stigmatizing women&#39;s age — benefitting not just women, but the whole organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Retailers Can Capitalize on the &ldquo;Refund Effect&rdquo;]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_113908305.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Lori Andrews/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In 2022, US consumers returned 16.5% of purchases, costing retailers an estimated $816 billion in lost revenue. Research suggests that cross-selling products during the return process is an effective strategy to reduce this revenue loss. Across a number of experiments, researchers found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so it&amp;#8217;s less painful to spend these funds on another purchase, so long as cross-selling occurs before the money is reissued to the customers&amp;#8217; original payment method and consumers initially expected to keep the goods they were planning to buy. The researchers also found that this &amp;#8220;refund effect&amp;#8221; applies across categories. Creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can reduce revenue loss from product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Product returns pose a major challenge for retailers. In 2022, US consumers returned &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;16.5%&lt;/a>; of merchandise purchases, costing retailers an estimated &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;$816&lt;/a>; billion in lost revenue. Typical strategies to reduce revenue lost to product returns include reducing the likelihood of returns by providing more information about products (eg, reviews and FAQs) and increasing the financial and transaction costs to consumers who do return products (eg, shipping costs and limited return windows). But the former strategy is costly to retailers, and the latter is costly to consumers. Our recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://myscp.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jcpy.1354&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; identifies an effective strategy for reducing this loss of revenue that benefits everyone: cross-selling products during the product-return process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In six experiments we found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so spending these funds on another purchase feels less painful. Research participants were more likely to spend money from a product refund than from a bonus, and even more likely to spend refunded money than unexpected income, like lottery winnings and tax refunds. We call this “the refund effect.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one laboratory experiment, for instance, we gave all participants $4. Some of the participants were asked to use the money to buy a stress ball that they later learned they could return, which most did. Others in a control group made no initial purchase. We then offered everyone the opportunity to keep their $4 or use it to buy a $5 Starbucks gift card at a discount. Only 48% of the control group used their $4 to buy the gift card, whereas 78% of participants who received the refund bought the gift card. We replicated this study with an online sample where the returned product was a gift card from a big-box retailer (ie, Best Buy or Kohls). In this experiment, only 10% of the control group chose to purchase the Starbucks gift card, whereas 25% of participants with refunded money used it to buy the Starbucks gift card.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Retailers who understand the dynamics of the refund effect — when, why, and how it works — stand to mitigate one of the perennial headaches of the industry. Here are three findings retailers should keep in mind to make the most of the refund effect:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cross-selling opportunities occur during the returns process — before money is reissued to the customers&#39; original payment method.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The refund effect is far less likely to boost sales after money has been refunded to a credit card or checking account.为什么？ The refund effect depends on creating and maintaining an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/e/earmarking.asp&quot;>;earmark&lt;/a>;” that reminds consumers the money has been lost. Our research found that if refunded money is pooled with money from other sources the earmark is removed and consumers spend it no differently than money from other sources. For example, research participants were more likely to use a refund from a pair of sneakers to buy a shirt if they had yet to receive their money back. If the money had already been deposited in their checking account, they were no more likely to buy the shirt than participants who simply saw the shirt online.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some retailers already effectively use this cross-selling strategy. By default, Amazon asks customers if they&#39;d like to use their return to buy a gift card. Customers who decline this cross-sell then receive their refund. Clothier Todd Snyder lets customers use their refund to immediately buy other products before they mail their return. The remainder of their refund is issued when the return is received. These cross-selling strategies are likely to work because customers shop out of the refund before getting money back from their returns.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect only works when consumers expect to lose money.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our research showed that consumers have to initially expect to keep the goods and services they buy to create the earmark that makes the refund effect work. “Try before you buy” strategies, where consumers do not expect to pay for returned goods, are unlikely to create a refund effect if those goods are returned.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, research participants who imagined buying two pairs of shoes to try on with the expectation that they would return one pair were no more likely to spend their refund on a jacket than controls who simply imagined seeing the jacket and paying out of pocket. By contrast, participants who did not expect to return a pair of shoes when they bought them were more likely to use the refund from the shoes to buy the jacket&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect applies across categories.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Because refunded money feels as if it has already been lost, the refund effect applies both to cross-sold products in the same category and products in other categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, research participants in a fifth experiment were more likely to spend a refund from a returned bottle of wine on either a gift card from a grocer or from an athleisure brand than buy either kind of gift card with money out of their pocket. This is good news for retailers who offer a range of product categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sale strategies like upselling and exchanges during the product return process should similarly benefit from the refund effect, and they may be better for customer relationship management than increasing the cost of product returns. New companies have stepped into this market. For example, Loop Returns helps 1,500 Shopify merchants, such as Allbirds and Brooklinen, cross-sell, upsell, and exchange products during the product return process, saving &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.loopreturns.com/the-ecommerce-returns-benchmark-report/&quot;>;28% of revenue&lt;/a>; that would otherwise be lost.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The lesson for retailers? Instead of resorting to practices whose harsh transaction costs can &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0008125617741125&quot;>;alienate customers&lt;/a>;, sometimes permanently, creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can be an effective way to reduce the revenue loss incurred by product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Ways Companies Are Addressing Skills Gaps in Their Workforce]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_TylerComrie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Tyler Comrie&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;We&amp;#8217;re in an unusual economic situation, one where recession fears are high but the job market is tight. As training budgets inevitably come under pressure, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The author examines five of the biggest developments in this space: 1) digital apprenticeships that are helping fill jobs in the digital and tech sectors; 2) tuition-assistance programs aimed at frontline workers; 3) learning-experience platforms with features like skills assessments, algorithmic-driven recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking; 4) the democratization of coaching; and 5) the rise of cohort-based courses.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For years, business and HR leaders &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/can-moocs-solve-your-training-problem&quot;>;pinned their hopes&lt;/a>; for better workplace learning on MOOCs, or massive open online courses. Unfortunately, the evidence &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1921417117#ref-3&quot;>;continues to show&lt;/a>; that these are not enough on their own, particularly for those who most need them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies now have more options, thanks to better technology, innovative funding mechanisms, and old approaches reimagined to meet today&#39;s needs. Below, I explain five of the biggest developments in this space.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The New Digital Apprenticeship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a medieval practice is propelling thousands of workers onto the career ladder&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The apprenticeship is perhaps the oldest form of workplace learning, stretching back to ancient times, and boasting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/apprenticeship&quot;>;some illustrious alumni&lt;/a>;, including Benjamin Franklin. There are more than 580,000 active apprentices working in the US right now — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apprenticeship.gov/data-and-statistics&quot;>;up 103% in the past 10 years&lt;/a>;, according to Department of Labor figures.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For companies that consistently struggle to fill important roles, apprenticeships may be an effective solution. While apprenticeships have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/global/2020/feb/04/tanners-tailors-and-candlestick-makers-a-history-of-apprenticeships&quot;>;historically&lt;/a>; been associated with blue-collar jobs, they&#39;re increasingly becoming a way to fill white-collar jobs in the digital and tech sectors. Apprenticeships in the IT and telecommunications sector grew by more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027040416/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/telecommunications#:~:text=In%202020%20there%20were%203%2C654%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20telecommunications%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20300%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years.%20%5B2%5D&quot;>;300%&lt;/a>; between 2011 and 2020, while cybersecurity apprenticeships grew by &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027023746/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/cybersecurity#:~:text=In%202020%2C%20there%20were%202%2C716%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20cybersecurity%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20600%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years%20%5B2%5D.&quot;>;600%&lt;/a>; during the same period, according to the Department of Labor.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend is powered by a growing number of companies, many of which are focused on fast-growing fields like software engineering and data science, that recruit, support, and train apprentices on behalf of large employers. One UK-based provider, Multiverse, was recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://tcrn.ch/3H0ebPR&quot;>;valued&lt;/a>; at $1.7bn and claims to have served &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/multiverse-community-reaches-10-000-apprentices-and-alumni&quot;>;10,000 apprentices&lt;/a>;. “We&#39;ve long been believers in the apprenticeship model, and we&#39;ve found it particularly effective for tech and digital jobs,” said Rashitha Jayasekara, chief of digital manufacturing at Rolls-Royce, which works with Multiverse to&amp;nbsp;upskill existing employees. “The experiential learning that apprentices get through hackathons and project work allows them to combine theory and practice in a way standard training doesn&#39;t, and to continuously develop skills we need within the company.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Verizon, another Multiverse customer, uses the apprenticeship model to fill software engineering jobs and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/creating-software-engineering-jobs-verizon&quot;>;reports&lt;/a>; that 95% of an initial cohort accepted full-time offers at the company after completing an apprenticeship program. The Verizon program was designed to “lower barriers to entry to software jobs while training truly great software developers that we fundamentally believe can propel our business through digital innovation,” said Shankar Arumugavelu, Verizon&#39;s chief information officer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Apprenticeships aren&#39;t right for all training needs. For one thing, they require a significant investment of time — in the US, formal apprenticeships are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2017/article/apprenticeships_occupations-and-outlook.htm#:~:text=Formal%20apprenticeship%20programs%20usually%20last,Department%20of%20Labor%20(DOL).&quot;>;usually four years long&lt;/a>;. In some markets they can also come with restrictive regulation. In the UK, for instance, the government&#39;s apprenticeship funding program &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/news/365530295/Government-urged-to-address-broken-apprenticeship-levy-system&quot;>;has been criticized&lt;/a>; for being too rigid and not in line with employers&#39; needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Fresh Approach to Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a historically elite benefit is becoming accessible for all&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Large companies have long offered to pay for their employees&#39; continuing education. However, these benefits have historically been reserved for a small number of white-collar employees, for example, those pursuing an executive MBA. Or employees were asked to pay for their courses out of pocket and get reimbursed afterwards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the labor market has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/themes/how-to-better-support-and-retain-frontline-workers&quot;>;changed&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/companies-offer-tuition-assistance-so-workers-can-go-back-to-college.html&quot;>;more companies&lt;/a>; are offering tuition benefits as a way to retain their frontline employees — store clerks, baristas, drivers, and hourly workers. In response, a new class of companies has emerged to smooth and synchronize the relationship between training providers, employers, employees, and (in some cases) the government. Employees receive coaching, advice, and support to help them find the training program that&#39;s right for them, and the training programs are paid for by the employer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, in 2021, Target announced a tuition-assistance program called &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.target.com/article/2022/09/dream-to-be-anniversary#:~:text=Our%20%24200%20million%20investment%20in,skills%20and%20build%20their%20careers.&quot;>;“Dream to Be&lt;/a>;” in partnership with Guild, one of the leading players in this growing space. According to Chief Diversity and Inclusion officer Kiera Fernandez, “Target has offered a traditional tuition reimbursement program for more than two decades. Now, through our partnership with Guild to offer Dream to Be, team members can attend classes at more than 40 schools, colleges, and universities … with no out-of-pocket tuition costs.” Fernandez said that as of April 2023, more than 25,000 employees have been approved for the program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If designed effectively, the benefits of tuition assistance programs for employers are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/small-business/human-resources/articles/tuition-reimbursement/&quot;>;clear&lt;/a>;. For example, Jack Hartung, chief financial officer of fast-casual restaurant chain Chipotle, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/video/2021/04/09/chipotle-cfo-says-debt-free-degree-is-a-way-to-invest-in-employees.html&quot;>;told CNBC&lt;/a>; that “employees who take advantage of the company&#39;s free degrees are three and a half times more likely to stay with the company and seven times more likely to move up into management.” However, research suggests that while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180108006550/en/New-Study-Shows-Lasting-Impact-Tuition-Assistance#:~:text=84%25%20say%20access%20to%20a%20tuition%20assistance%20program%20was%20important%20in%20their%20decision%20to%20join%20the%20company&quot;>;84%&lt;/a>; of employees value tuition reimbursement benefits highly, on average, &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholarlycommons.law.northwestern.edu/nulr/vol117/iss6/5/#:~:text=Yet%2C%20despite%20their%20increasing%20availability%2C%20only%202%25%20of%20employees%2C%20as%20a%20percentage%20of%20those%20interested%20in%20pursuing%20further%20education%2C%20are%20utilizing%20these%20reimbursement%20programs&quot;>;only 2%&lt;/a>; of eligible employees use this benefit. This implies employers must do more to take advantage of this powerful tool.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Shift to Learning Experience Platforms&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How employees know what to learn next&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Organizing and tracking what employees are learning can be a cumbersome task. For years, this work has been done by software known as “learning management systems” (LMS), which are relatively simple tools that store learning material, typically in the form of presentations, videos, and text. Most large companies &lt;a href=&quot;https://trainingmag.com/2021-training-industry-report/#:~:text=Some%2098%20percent%20of%20large%20companies%20and%2096%20percent%20of%20midsize%20ones%20currently%20use%20LMSs%20vs.%2080%20percent%20of%20small%20companies.&quot;>;have one&lt;/a>;, but few employees &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinkruse/2021/04/27/usage-of-degreed-is-double-that-of-traditional-learning-platforms/?sh=58ba9a1a2d3d#:~:text=most%20LMS%20and%20online%20content%20companies%20only%20see%205%25%20to%2015%25%20of%20licensed%20seats%20used%20in%20any%20given%20month.&quot;>;spend much time&lt;/a>; on them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the last few years, a new wave of tools has transformed the LMS into “Learning Experience Platforms” (LXP), with features like skills assessments, Netflix-style recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking. LXPs “make learning relevant for individuals, not just managing training programs,” according Todd Tauber senior vice president of strategy at Degreed, one of the leading providers in this space. Industry analyst Josh Bersin estimates the market for LXPs is &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/06/corporate-learning-bombshell-degreed-acquires-learnin-david-blake-returns/&quot;>;$500m,&lt;/a>; up from &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2018/07/edcast-expands-the-lxp-market-with-focus-on-global-upskilling/&quot;>;$200m&lt;/a>; in 2018.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Customers report that the model is working. Chris Harry is the chief learning officer of TEK Systems, a staffing firm that&#39;s been using Degreed. “Since moving our various employee development programs onto Degreed, we&#39;ve seen our highest-ever engagement and satisfaction rates,” he said. According to Harry, 96% of TEK employees have created an account in Degreed, and the company consistently sees 40 to 50% of them actively using the platform each month, which he says is “far higher than anything we&#39;ve seen before.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Results like these require real investment beyond simply buying the technology. For &lt;a href=&quot;https://get.degreed.com/hubfs/Client%20Case%20Studies/Ericsson/Ericsson+Degreed%20Case%20Study_Q2-22_EN-US.pdf?utm_campaign=Ericsson%20Case%20Study%20May%20%2722&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsmi=214005662&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-_8Z515BnP5WAJI5xGCg8ZF2Zi2ftiYmmfHEKikOYkDheoBPQzXBzi5mM6FOcyAZGppjQgdYXltDyoeVeVVC1bEnUM8xfnubGHUldzPilsSLH3Yk90&amp;amp;utm_content=214005662&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_automation&quot;>;example&lt;/a>;, another Degreed customer, Ericsson, said it hired internal champions and developed an extensive internal marketing campaign to roll out its program.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Democratization of Coaching&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How all of us can have a Sherpa for our careers&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Professional coaching is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2009-12395-008&quot;>;well-understood&lt;/a>; way to boost workers&#39; learning, confidence, and effectiveness. However, it has typically been an &lt;a href=&quot;/2009/01/what-can-coaches-do-for-you#:~:text=they%E2%80%99re%20usually%20called%20executive%20coaches%2C%20and%20they%20can%20earn%20up%20to%20%243%2C500%20an%20hour.&quot;>;expensive&lt;/a>; tool, reserved only for senior executives. Moreover, even for those who can afford it, finding a coach can be a challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;New platforms have emerged that use technology to make it easier to find, match, and work with coaches. New companies provide tools to assess what each employee needs from their coach, match them with a coach who has the right experience and expertise, and even conduct coaching sessions via a digital platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The space is growing. According to the International Coaching Federation, there were &lt;a href=&quot;https://coachfederation.org/app/uploads/2020/09/FINAL_ICF_GCS2020_ExecutiveSummary.pdf&quot;>;71,000&lt;/a>; practicing coaches in 2021, up 33% from 2016. Investors expect growth to continue: The leading digital coaching startup, BetterUp, raised $300m in 2021 at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/betterup&quot;>;$5bn valuation&lt;/a>; as part of a wave of &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/01/online-coaching-is-so-hot-its-now-disrupting-leadership-development/&quot;>;investment&lt;/a>; into coaching startups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of this growth is powered by large companies offering coaching services more broadly to their employees. Danone, the France-based food products company, has been working with one provider, CoachHub, to offer this benefit to 250 employees. According to Maxime Hollande, who leads diversity and inclusion for Danone in the Netherlands, “these coaching sessions have been of big added value for employees… One of the metrics we watch closely is the extent to which each employee has progressed toward the personal goals each of them define with their coach. The average score on this metric is 4.9 out of 5.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Chevron, the American global energy company, has made coaching sessions available to 7,000 of its managers around the world via BetterUp. “Prior to BetterUp, we utilized an assortment of internal coaching resources and multiple external coaching vendors,” explained Rhonda Morris, Chevron&#39;s chief human resources officer. “BetterUp&#39;s virtual coaching model … has matured our coaching culture making it more accessible for all who want it.&amp;nbsp; Coaches no longer have to travel to meet our employees. Our employees have been very vocal about their positive experiences with BetterUp.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Because coaching sessions are inherently private experiences, it can be hard for employers to ensure a focus on the topics that are most important to them. At Chevron, they measure the success each quarter by asking employees to rate the effectiveness of leaders who&#39;ve received coaching. “Leadership Effectiveness is consistently one of our highest scoring categories across our organization,” Morris said. “This shows that our BetterUp offerings are having a positive impact on our workforce and culture.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Rise of Cohort-Based Courses &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How to build real skills online&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When it comes to online learning, most participants &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aav7958&quot;>;don&#39;t finish&lt;/a>; the courses they start, mainly because the learning experience is asynchronous. Individuals must be disciplined and diligent enough to complete large amounts of the learning material on their own. This is particularly difficult in today&#39;s workplace, where the number of meetings and distractions has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/great-expectations-making-hybrid-work-work&quot;>;ballooned&lt;/a>; in recent years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now, a new delivery format called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://future.com/cohort-based-courses/&quot;>;cohort-based courses&lt;/a>;” has emerged as a way to improve completion rates. Groups of participants together take a course with defined start and end dates, regular homework assignments, and an instructor to run periodic live online discussion sessions. Within this more structured format, participants still access much of the learning material on their own time, making it easier for them to complete the course and have the chance to apply what they learn over its duration. One of the pioneers of this space, altMBA, says its learners have achieved a &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/behavior-design/how-to-design-an-online-course-with-a-96-completion-rate-180678117a85&quot;>;96% completion rate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boston Consulting Group (BCG) is one leading employer that has embraced cohort-based courses, working in partnership with Emeritus (where I work). Lidia Juszko, BCG&#39;s executive director of global learning and teaming, describes how the format works particularly well for a professional services firm like hers. “We&#39;ve found that cohort-based courses offer a level of structure and support that makes them more engaging than standard online learning,” she said. “Our colleagues report that the combination and cadence of &#39;office hours&#39; with instructors, live discussion sessions with the rest of the cohort, and short videos and exercises to be completed each week are a more accessible way for them to learn. Learning and development opportunities like this allow us to continue to attract and retain the best talent.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;HSBC, the global banking organization, recently began piloting cohort-based online courses as well, and the early results are promising. According to David Morris, global head of people capability, “One of our challenges has been to deliver in-depth learning in an online format, given the range and complexity of our markets. Our early results show that the online cohort-based format is achieving significant improvement across key indicators like completion, confidence, and capability.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The downside of this format is that the live learning elements that make it effective come at a substantial cost. A single license to an open library of standard online courses costs about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.classcentral.com/report/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/comparing-subscription-pricing-2023.png&quot;>;$30 to $60&lt;/a>; per month for access to thousands of courses (most providers also offer significant volume discounts). Meanwhile, cohort-based courses can cost between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/serenitygibbons/2021/12/17/how-cohort-based-learning-is-transforming-online-education/#:~:text=Another%20notable%20difference%20is%20the%20price%3B%20cohort%20based%20courses%20can%20range%20anywhere%20from%20%24500%20up%20to%20more%20than%20%245%2C000.&quot;>;$500 and $5,000&lt;/a>; per course&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>; This means cohort-based learning is unlikely to be an option for all employees, and employers must carefully decide who can benefit the most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We are in an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmoore/2022/12/02/many-indicators-imply-a-2023-recession-the-jobs-market-disagrees/&quot;>;unusual&lt;/a>; economic situation, one where recession fears are up but the job market is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/b1b710a1-6d12-43e5-8508-ae4584a7289a&quot;>;still tight&lt;/a>;. As training budgets inevitably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1812542/half-organisations-looking-cut-ld-costs-amid-economic-difficulty-survey-reveals&quot;>;come under pressure&lt;/a>;, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The five approaches outlined above can help companies move beyond the MOOC to find a learning program that&#39;s right for their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Editor&#39;s Note: Harvard Business Publishing has a content creation and distribution partnership with Emeritus.&amp;nbsp;Neither the author or editor who worked on this article are involved in that partnership.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A More Humane Model for Eldercare in the U.S.]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-u-s]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_200015318-001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daly and Newton/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;On the whole, the care for elderly poor people with chronic illnesses leaves a lot to be desired in the United States. PACE, a comprehensive, integrated, community-based care approach that lets older adults continue to live at home as long as possible, can serve as a model for improving the needs of this population. This article examines PACE Southeast Michigan, an outstanding PACE program.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-us?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-more-humane-model-for-eldercare-in-the-us?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The US health care system is not set up to improve the quality of life of the most vulnerable, chronically ill, elderly people, especially those who are poor. Older poor people often face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3016701/&quot;>;loneliness, depression,&lt;/a>; a lost sense of purpose, and an inability to live independently in their homes. They also encounter many health service hurdles, including inadequate care coordination, &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/07/how-to-pay-for-health-care&quot;>;fee-for-service reimbursement&lt;/a>; that often reflexively encourages medical treatment over other forms of care, and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2759755&quot;>;dysfunctional&lt;/a>; nursing home industry.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help improve services for these patients, we analyzed the design and implementation of a national program called PACE: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/Medicare-Medicaid-Coordination/Medicare-and-Medicaid-Coordination/Medicare-Medicaid-Coordination-Office/PACE/PACE&quot;>;Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly&lt;/a>;. We focused on this program because all PACE participants are vulnerable: They require nursing home–level care, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npaonline.org/sites/default/files/PDFs/Issue%20Brief_Medicaid%20Rate%20Setting%20for%20PACE%202.21.pdf&quot;>;90%&lt;/a>; are eligible for &lt;em>;both&lt;/em>; Medicare and Medicaid. Few integrated-care programs serve this dual-eligible population, which now numbers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kff.org/medicare/issue-brief/a-profile-of-medicare-medicaid-enrollees-dual-eligibles/#:~:text=The%2012.5%20million%20people%20who,from%20their%20state%20Medicaid%20program.&quot;>;12.5 million&lt;/a>; Americans.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In-depth interviews with PACE staff and program participants conducted by two of us (Len Berry and Sunjay Letchuman); collaborations with PACE leaders, including two coauthors of this article (Mary Kummer Naber and Peter Fitzgerald); and our collective analysis of the features and daily operations of a PACE model in southeastern Michigan (led by Mary) reveal how PACE successfully delivers individualized, home-centered care to poor older adults while lowering overall costs. Given that PACE currently serves only about 60,000 of these patients, expanding the program has useful management and cost implications for health care systems nationally. Although nursing home and other institutionalized elder care clearly demand improvement, the United States also must invest in reimagining what elder care can be. PACE provides a roadmap.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;More Comprehensive, Less Costly Care&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The PACE program, first developed in San Francisco in 1973, is a comprehensive, integrated, community-based care model that lets older adults continue to live at home as long as possible. There are now 150 PACE programs in 32 states. The basic philosophy is that care should include what matters most to older poor people: all-inclusive care comprising nutrition, social interaction, transportation, and home upkeep, in addition to medical and related services. The goal is to treat patients with dignity as they safely live at home, rather than in an institution, and receive every needed service from one entity — all while lowering costs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All Medicare beneficiaries needing nursing home–level care but wishing to live at home are eligible for PACE. However, Medicare beneficiaries who do not meet their state&#39;s Medicaid income requirement are required to pay an amount equivalent to the monthly Medicaid payment, limiting access to millions of seniors who could benefit from the program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The program offers patients (called “participants”) all their Medicare- and Medicaid-covered benefits, including primary care, adult day care, rehabilitative care, and meals at a local PACE center. PACE provides transportation and various in-home services and is the payer for medical care that it cannot offer internally, such as emergency room visits and hospital stays. PACE organizations are paid on a monthly, risk-adjusted, capitated basis by Medicare and Medicaid, meaning they are paid &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/outreach-and-education/american-indian-alaska-native/aian/ltss-ta-center/info/pace#:~:text=The%20program%20receives%20capitated%20reimbursements,each%20patient%20the%20program%20serves.&quot;>;a set amount per month&lt;/a>; based, in part, on participants&#39; medical complexity. PACE programs bear full financial risk for all care, and participants do not pay anything out of pocket.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Available &lt;a href=&quot;https://agsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jgs.12637&quot;>;evidence&lt;/a>; shows that PACE reduces health care utilization and costs. Compared with similar populations, PACE participants have substantially lower rates of hospitalization (539 vs. 962 admissions per 1,000 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430746/&quot;>;person-years&lt;/a>;). &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/biomedgerontology/article/68/1/47/549686?login=true&quot;>;South Carolina&lt;/a>;, for example, annually saves nearly $9,000 per PACE participant compared with residents in alternative long-term care settings such as nursing homes; &lt;a href=&quot;https://health.wyo.gov/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/SFY-2020-Wyoming-Medicaid-Annual-Report.pdf&quot;>;Wyoming&lt;/a>; saves over $12,000 per PACE participant. However, PACE is about far more than saving money — it is about restoring dignity and joy to people&#39;s lives.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;An Exemplary Model&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One outstanding PACE program is PACE Southeast Michigan (PACE SEMI), which the National PACE Association identified as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npaonline.org/sites/default/files/PDFs/2018%20AC%20PowerPoint.pdf&quot;>;“bright spot”&lt;/a>; for its growth and quality metrics. PACE SEMI is organized as a tax-exempt nonprofit and is owned by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.henryford.com/&quot;>;Henry Ford Health&lt;/a>; (55%) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pvm.org/&quot;>;Presbyterian Villages of Michigan&lt;/a>; (45%). With seven centers serving 1,600 participants and employing 700 people, PACE SEMI increases its net enrollment by an average of 30 participants each month, compared with two participants each month in PACE centers nationally. Approximately 15% of PACE SEMI participants visit an emergency room each year for any reason, compared with &lt;a href=&quot;https://aspe.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/documents/9739cab65ad0221a66ebe45463d10d37/dual-eligible-beneficiaries-integrated-care.pdf&quot;>;25%&lt;/a>; of PACE participants nationally and 31% of Medicare Advantage enrollees. PACE SEMI participants also use inpatient hospital services less frequently: In 2019, PACE SEMI participants had 302 fewer &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.cms.gov/summary-statistics-on-use-and-payments/medicare-service-type-reports/cms-program-statistics-medicare-advantage-inpatient-hospital&quot;>;hospitalizations per 1,000 persons&lt;/a>; compared to Medicare Advantage enrollees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The PACE model is built on interdisciplinary teamwork. All PACE SEMI staff members are expected to see themselves as physical, mental, emotional, and spiritual “healers.” They include the primary care doctor who emphasizes preventing illness and injury as much as ordering treatments, the nurse and social worker who coordinate care, the onsite pharmacist who stays alert for prescribed drugs that may do more harm than good for specific patients, the kitchen chef who customizes meals to participants&#39; tastes and allergies, the participant-care associate who gives supportive care for daily activities (including showers), and the drivers who transport participants to and from PACE centers and other important destinations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike some PACE programs, PACE SEMI has behavioral health and spiritual care specialists at each center who get to know each participant they serve. In one case mentioned by a PACE physician, a spiritual care provider asked clinic staff to immediately check on a patient who seemed “off.” It turned out the patient was having a stroke and quickly received life-saving care. In a less-dramatic case, a social worker took it upon herself to persuade a local Trader Joe&#39;s store to donate flowers for participants to take home each week. Team members hold weekly meetings where everyone has equal input about how to prevent avoidable emergency room visits and advance the quality of life for their participants.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Whole-Person Care&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At its core, the PACE model is relationship-based: Participants and staff members know each other well, which facilitates “whole-person healing” customized to each individual. Indeed, members are called “participants” precisely because of their active role in planning their care, which goes far beyond medical services and addresses head-on the isolation that many older people who live alone endure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A day at a PACE SEMI center includes needed medical and rehabilitative services and is filled with customized activities such as music, painting, games, breakfast and lunch with friends, and regular group sessions where participants share “what I am grateful for,” cultivating a sense of belonging and community. Participants can get their hair shampooed, cut, and styled. They receive instruction on living safely at home and are given iPads (called “GrandPads”), designed for senior use, that let them easily contact family or PACE staff or play games. The kitchen prepares food for participants to take home at the end of the day. Participants can also use the onsite gym staffed with physical and occupational therapists. (“To see a 90-year-old working out is amazing,” one therapist said.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“Dancing Kathy” arrived at PACE SEMI in a wheelchair. Aided by the rehabilitation staff, she eventually graduated to a walker and, months later, a cane. In an interview one year after starting at PACE, Kathy said she no longer needed the cane most of the time and could now dance. She then joined several staff members to dance the “Hustle” in front of the cafeteria lunch crowd.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Proactive Investments in Health&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Most of the enormous amount spent on health care in the United States is reactive. Patients get sick, treatment ensues, costs are incurred. PACE shows the potential of investing in health, not just health care, proactively. PACE SEMI and other well-run PACE programs do just about anything to help people continue to live at home safely. For instance, if a participant needs a shower chair at home to prevent a fall, PACE SEMI buys the chair, sets it up, and teaches the participant how to use it. With money generated by community fundraising, PACE SEMI fixes porches and stairs, replaces heaters, improves lighting, and even roots out bedbugs. It partners with an ambulance service whose paramedics often provide in-home care that prevents ER visits.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such spending can greatly improve the quality of people&#39;s lives while reducing downstream costs. One of PACE SEMI&#39;s participants, “Mr. B,” had a career as a musician but now lives alone. After leaving the PACE center each week, Mr. B was a frequent visitor to ERs for mental health–related issues and anxiety. After the PACE staff realized Mr. B was missing music in his life, the center bought him a headset and player so he could listen to his favorite music. The ER visits stopped.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Service with a Soul&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;PACE SEMI&#39;s secret sauce is its culture. Hiring for caring, not just competence, is as central as intensively training staff to distinguish between nonmedical healing and medical interventions. Some staff members with traditional health care backgrounds must “unlearn” their bias for episodic care. And in working with a vulnerable population, staff must move beyond risk aversion, common in institutional elder care.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Keeping people safe does not require stealing their freedom, as Atul Gawande discussed in &lt;a href=&quot;https://atulgawande.com/book/being-mortal/&quot;>;&lt;em>;Being Mortal&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;: “…our elderly are left with a controlled and supervised institutional existence, a medically designed answer to unfixable problems, a life designed to be safe but empty of anything they care about.” With creativity, compassion, and commitment, a carefully selected, well-trained staff who are themselves treated with dignity can instill dignity, a sense of belonging, and even joy in PACE participants. As Renee, a food service worker at PACE SEMI, puts it, “We add love to the food.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;PACE is about investing in people&#39;s well-being, keeping them as well as possible for as long as possible. It offers older adults the chance to live at home with a higher quality of care — and of life. The current model serves primarily low-income seniors; however, the bigger opportunity is to expand it to include all chronically ill older adults. Such models will be useful as Congress &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthaffairs.org/content/forefront/congress-considers-strategies-improve-medicare-and-medicaid-integration-dual-eligible&quot;>;crafts legislation&lt;/a>; to expand PACE, as health care organizations plan how to launch PACE programs efficiently and effectively, and as program leaders and managers seek to develop the nuts and bolts of care that offers healing to patients and energizes staff.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: Your Love for Work May Alienate Your Colleagues]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1344042166-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;humanmade/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Research shows that employees who are passionate about their work are more productive, innovative, and collaborative. New research suggests that these employees also see passion for work as a moral imperative, and they&amp;#8217;re more likely to judge colleagues who are motivated by other reasons, such as financial stability, social status, or familial obligations. The research also found that these employees were more likely to offer help to their more passionate colleagues. Leaders must recognize the diverse motivations that drive their workforce and create an inclusive environment that supports and values all forms of motivation, rather than penalizing those who do not fit the passion-centric mold.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/research-your-love-for-work-may-alienate-your-colleagues?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0191308522000132?casa_token=fZzxkx3ayVAAAAAA:y_RucibVaoH6Kq9rhrKEOJPv3EKW-Ht94rTqrsXT8ajB4cqEKH_Y3RYdJfDwnqXCDP_i7d774A&quot;>;growing number of companies&lt;/a>; are seeking out employees whose passion for their work is the driving force behind their performance, and they&#39;re investing in strategies to encourage and nurture this motivation. The research on this topic &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/job.2434?casa_token=qK7aO_h5mzMAAAAA:00L4l-RKd7-sc3yfdVz-ToizgtmmobloM6Cvvd4-yWz19BX5JUsGmKTIzANA9GpjMzDpoGdT_LYoiw&quot;>;is clear&lt;/a>; — more passionate employees are more productive, innovative, and collaborative, and they demonstrate higher levels of commitment to their organizations. Fostering passion is a winning strategy for organizations that aspire to achieve sustained growth, innovation, and success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, in the pursuit of nurturing passion, &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2020.1761?af=R&quot;>;our recent research&lt;/a>; reveals that employers may have overlooked and neglected the needs of employees driven by other sources of motivation, such as financial stability, social status, or familial obligations. These employees &lt;a href=&quot;/2003/06/lets-hear-it-for-b-players&quot;>;play a critical role in the success of their companies&lt;/a>;, but may be subject to an invisible penalty due to their perceived lack of passion for their work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Doing What You Love Makes You “Moralize” Loving Your Work&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our research involving 1,245 full-time employees across several organizations that varied in size and industry revealed a novel phenomenon in the contemporary workplace: The more people love their work, the more they see it as a moral imperative. Employees who were more passionate about their work agreed more strongly with sentences like “Working for personal enjoyment is morally virtuous” and “Being intrinsically motivated is moral.” For these individuals, loving their work had moral significance beyond personal fulfillment, and they were more likely to judge their colleagues&#39; work motivations against their own moral yardstick or ask, “Are my colleagues here for the &lt;em>;right&lt;/em>; reasons?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This emphasis on loving your work as a moral obligation has far-reaching implications. Our research suggests that those who love their work more are also more likely to view working for external rewards less favorably. Those who agreed with sentences like “Being intrinsically motivated is moral” also agreed with sentences like “Those who do their work for money alone are not virtuous employees” and “Employees who are motivated by external rewards tend to be immoral.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Critically, we found consequences to these character judgements. Employees who love their work more also prioritized helping their more passionate colleagues, whom they consider morally superior. In contrast, employees who worked for other reasons received less help from their more passionate colleagues, making it more difficult for them to advance in their organizations and making them more likely to be excluded from important projects. Such treatment can have severe consequences for employee morale, retention, and overall organizational performance. By contrast, employees who worked for external rewards treated their colleagues equally, regardless of why they worked.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Creating an Environment that Values Employees&#39; Diverse Motivations&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managers need to be aware that organizations that valorize passion can create a sense of alienation for some employees. Recognizing and celebrating the unique contributions of all employees, regardless of their underlying motivations, will help create a sense of belonging and purpose among your workforce, leading to increased engagement and productivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Managers should also strive to foster an open and inclusive workplace culture where employees feel comfortable discussing their motivations and goals, even when they are misaligned with a passion-driven ethos. This can both encourage dialogue between employees who vary in their motivations for working and provide opportunities for employees to explore and develop their passion both inside and outside the workplace. For example, mentorship, networking relationships, or job crafting (ie, spending more time on tasks that are more meaningful to them) can expose employees to roles they may be more excited about.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are an employee who loves their work, keep in mind that this could make you more judgmental about your colleagues and affect how much you help them. Not everyone needs to do the work because they are passionate about it. Some employees may have families to take care of, need benefits as a safety net, or have not yet discovered their true passion for work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, organizations should examine whether their benefits and perks appeal to employees with diverse motivations. While some employees may be attracted to work because they are passionate about it, others may be motivated by flexible work arrangements, or access to professional development opportunities. By offering a range of benefits and perks, leaders can create a workplace that appeals to employees with diverse motivations and help retain top talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the prevalent belief that passion is crucial for success, all employees should be appreciated for who they are and how they contribute — regardless of their motivations for working. Leaders should recognize the diverse motivations that drive their workforce and create an inclusive environment that supports and values all forms of motivation, rather than penalizing those who do not fit the passion-centric mold.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Apple&rsquo;s Vision Pro Really For?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1496199364_1363676153.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Justin Sullivan/ Damian Pawlos/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To understand the value of Apple&amp;#8217;s new goggles, it&amp;#8217;s helpful to think about how virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) correspond to two fundamental tasks in decision making. VR presents new information; AR distills information from an existing environment. But previous headsets and internet-enabled glasses haven&amp;#8217;t tapped into the potential for either of these in a decision-making context. Apple is betting that it can build an ecosystem of app developers who can.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-is-apples-vision-pro-really-for?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Apple announced a new computer last week, to great fanfare. The Vision Pro is a computer that is worn on your face, but the novel aspect is how you use it. Rather than view the computer&#39;s output through a physical screen, that output is projected directly into your eyes with two very small but high-resolution displays a very small distance in front of you. Rather than control the computer through a keyboard, mouse, or touch screen, the primary user interface is through eye tracking and gestures. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Just as they removed the stylus for screens when they launched the iPhone, Apple requires no physical controller to use the computer. The computer senses what you are interested in interacting with by watching your eye movement and then looks at your hands to determine what you want to do. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;There have been antecedents to each of these things — a myriad of worn devices for viewing such as the Google Glass or Meta&#39;s Quest Pro and technologies such as &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/reviews/leap-motion-controller-review/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Leap Motion&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; and the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jVDPrFvBvWw&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Myo Armband&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; for gesture control. But none of these predecessors put it all together as a coherent vision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Apple has termed this new device &lt;/span>;a spatial computer&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;. The name is apt, because the device can use any physical space around you as a canvas to display digital outputs. There is no need for a desk (or lap) to place the device, and there are no limits on the size of the perceived viewing area. That means you could technically sit in a small space, like an airplane seat, and watch a cinema-sized movie. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;What should you be aiming to do with a spatial computer? Right now, Apple has outlined use cases that seem pedestrian. You can use it like a normal computer or iPad but with the current 2D information presented on a much more flexible and unconstrained display. There&#39;s demand for that. It will be of value where you do not have much space. And it will be of value to those who currently use their space with a host of large displays. In that sense, the closest analogue is a very large-screen TV. Would people pay $3,500 for that? They do right now. Even Apple sells a display (the Pro Display XDR) that can cost up to $6,000. From that perspective, it is easily in the cost ballpark for current use cases. This strategy also has the benefit of seeding this new platform with the vast number of applications that already exist for the iPad and the iPhone.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;A better and more convenient display for 2D content, however, does not appear to justify the technological and R&amp;amp;D weight that has gone into the Vision Pro. The real question is whether this device can lead to the augmented and virtual reality applications that would justify strapping a computer to your head. It certainly has the technical capabilities to do so. The Vision Pro can display 3D objects in your current space or even transport you to new spaces. Apple, however, barely mentioned the terms AR and VR during their announcement. In doing so, they drew a line people have not drawn before. This is no AR or VR device or technology. The technology is a spatial computer, and if there is a role for AR and VR, it is in applications that run on a spatial computer.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Let&#39;s review those concepts. Augmented reality (or AR) involves taking the environment around you and changing your perception of it. Google Glass did this by showing you notifications via smart glasses. The Vision Pro does this by placing 2D displays in that environment and fixing them so that when your head moves, the display does not. It appears to be there in your current environment. This is achieved by passing a very accurate video of the real world through the device to you. You don&#39;t see your environment directly, but you think you are doing so. Thus, technically, Apple is augmenting a video capture of your environment, not overlaying things on your direct viewing of it. To a user, there&#39;s no real difference.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Virtual reality (or VR) involves taking the user and immersing them in a virtual environment. The Vision Pro captures the full attention of your eye, and so you are, by definition, immersed in a virtual environment. In one mode, that looks like the environment you are actually in. Turn the dial, and that can change, and you can be transported somewhere else. The video pass-through from your current environment is replaced by a digitally created 3D environment. From that perspective, this is clearly a VR device. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The important thing to note is that despite being capable of AR and VR, these use-cases were not emphasized by Apple. Thus, they have produced a device capable of both but have not found compelling use cases in either domain. This is one of the reasons that they announced it at their annual developer conference. Apple needs apps, and they need other people to imagine them.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In a &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.16872&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;recent paper&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, we outlined what we believed were the ways that AR and VR apps could add unique value. Beyond gaming and entertainment, our focus is on economic uses — specifically, those that would increase users&#39; productivity. In this respect, we ask: Which AR and VR applications can create real value by assisting users in making better decisions? For someone looking to build applications for the platform Apple has created, understanding the possibilities is crucial. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Most decisions involve some degree of uncertainty. Information is the cure for that, allowing you to know more and, therefore, make fewer errors. But there are two aspects to using information in decisions. First, you need to have the right information available. Second, you need to have the cognitive space to distill and parse that information for usefulness.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;As it turns out, AR and VR map into each of these things. VR has the ability to present the user with more relevant information, especially when that information is either not with them or is costly to acquire. By immersing users in new contexts, what it does is bring that information to them. In some cases, it may be a realistic view of what is going on inside a building, say, during a fire. In other cases, it presents a safe, simulated environment, such as a flight simulator that facilitates training without the high stakes.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;By contrast, AR takes information presented in a given context and parses it to yield the information that is relevant. For instance, when you meet someone at a conference, it provides identification of who that person is without you having to search your own memory. Or, it can provide a helpful overlay with exit routes if you are dealing with a fire. In each case, the goal is to distill the quantity of information from the user&#39;s environment and present the information that is needed. The one thing to note is that the Vision Pro is not meant to be a portable computer to be used outside of the home or the workplace, which limits its applicability in navigating external environments (such as while driving).&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This perspective highlights why many previous AR and VR purported use cases have been of low value. VR meetings with avatars in pretty rooms do not provide information that is obviously more useful to those in the meetings that might arise from a Zoom call. AR glasses that provide text notifications as you walk around are increasing your cognitive load rather than decreasing it. Our framework suggests that the best use cases will be in contexts where it is normally expensive or dangerous to get information, highlighting the value of VR, or where the environment is so complex that the value of digital overlays to clarify it via AR is high &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;— &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;or both. Think applications like prototyping the design of a new aircraft or building, or assisting in remote medical procedures. The Vision Pro exhibits capabilities of being able to do each of these things but the job of experimenting and designing for these use cases has been left to others. Developers looking to profit off the platform Apple has created would do well to focus on applications that provide users with hard-to-access contextual information at just the right level of detail.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;This is par for the course for Apple when they first introduce a device. The iPod was a digital walkman. The iPhone was a connected iPod. The iPad was a bigger iPhone. The Apple Watch was a better smartwatch. And the Vision Pro is an unconstrained 3D screen. In the previous cases, the device is outgrown and becomes more than that initial use by enabling developer innovation. The Vision Pro is a welcome new&lt;/span>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshuagans.substack.com/p/apples-big-experiment&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;experiment&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; along a well-trodden path in computing.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Proactively Defuse Tension on Your Team]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_691050121.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Unaddressed and unresolved interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior can lead to organizational failure. They can impact team performance, collaboration, and productivity, create operational friction among teams, and cause employees to feel disengaged, distrustful, and unmotivated. While conflict at work is inevitable, we often have our own agency to proactively root out problems and stop them from escalating swiftly with empathy, accountability, self-awareness, and courage. The author, a Chief People Officer, offers five steps to do this: 1) Root out toxic behavior and tensions, 2) seek to understand, not just be understood, 3) assess the right time to intervene, 4) ask for help, and 5) repair harm; repair trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-proactively-defuse-tension-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As a chief people officer, I have seen firsthand how unaddressed and unresolved interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior can lead to organizational failure. A subtle racial slight, an argument over a project&#39;s deliverables, or gossip over perceived unfair advantages can negatively impact team performance, collaboration, and productivity, create operational friction among teams, and cause employees to feel disengaged, distrustful, and unmotivated. These issues can arise due to various factors, including differences in personality and perspectives, racial,&amp;nbsp;class&lt;strong>;,&lt;/strong>; and gender privilege, work and communication styles, power imbalances, and/or lack of transparency and clarity over work processes and business goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-navigate-conflict-with-a-coworker&quot;>;interpersonal conflict at work is inevitable&lt;/a>;, we often forget our own agency to root out problems and stop them from escalating swiftly with empathy, accountability, self-awareness, and courage. Doing so can feel scary and dangerous, especially when you&#39;re a junior team member or belong to one or more underrepresented groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Recently, a young woman of color, a rising star at my organization, expressed reservations about joining a new team that could significantly advance her career. During a conversation with the team&#39;s manager, she was troubled when he made an insensitive remark about what he perceived as racial segregation of employees at a social event. Concerned about her career and the potential for a racially hostile or uncomfortable work environment where this manager may not respect her identity and experiences, she sought guidance from her HR business partner, who directed her to me.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We discussed her desired outcome of joining the team while holding the manager accountable for the impact of his words and encouraging improvements in his behavior. I offered her the choice of addressing the issue directly or receiving support from me in the conversation, prioritizing her safety and dignity. After careful consideration, she chose to engage directly. I coached her on how to express herself confidently and thoughtfully. Subsequently, she shared a positive outcome—the manager demonstrated empathy, offered a genuine apology, and committed to openly acknowledging the dismissive comments with the entire team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Based on the experience of this employee and many others I&#39;ve coached throughout my career, here are five actions that you&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;can take to reduce or stop interpersonal tensions and toxic behavior if you witness or experience harm in the workplace:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Identify the root cause of the tension.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When dealing with interpersonal friction in the workplace, the first step is to identify the root causes — the true sources of tension. In her book, &lt;em>;The Fearless Organization&lt;/em>;, Amy Edmondson explores the cost of a lack of psychological safety in organizations, including toxic work environments, burnout, and human capital loss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Removing unhealthy behaviors that reduce individuals&#39; and teams&#39; safety, comfort, and performance requires us to face what needs to be changed. Power imbalances and differences of opinion over how to run a project, which partners to engage with, and performance measures are often the root cause of misunderstandings, disagreements, and collaboration collapse. In those situations, junior employees, women of color, and underrepresented employees are often afraid to speak up about conflict for fear of retaliation or being judged negatively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the above example, the root cause of tension was the manager&#39;s racially insensitive comment, leading to concerns about a potentially hostile or uncomfortable work environment, lack of respect, and disregard for the lived experiences of this woman of color and others. By approaching such situations with support, empathy, and courage, we can uncover and address the underlying causes of tensions and prevent them from negatively impacting individuals&#39; well-being and professional development. It&#39;s important to recognize that this approach may not always be feasible or safe. In this case, the employee trusted that I would intervene if the conversation veered off course.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Seek to understand, not just be understood.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Professional relationships are human relationships fraught with shared misunderstandings. A wrongly placed, unintentional word in a stressful moment, especially those fed by gender and racial biases, can drive a deep wedge between coworkers. To build shared understanding, it is important to hold space for others&#39; opinions, empathize with complex and nuanced situations, and take responsibility for nurturing a sense of safety and trust among colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this instance, the manager embraced the opportunity to connect, learn, and grow, seeking to comprehend the impact of their words and actions instead of adopting a defensive stance. This response demonstrated a willingness to acknowledge mistakes and make an effort to change without fearing appearing incompetent or being canceled. Rather than deflecting or bemoaning leadership challenges, the manager prioritized their team&#39;s well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By helping the manager see and understand her concerns, the employee demonstrated a remarkable level of empathy. Though it would have been fair for her to write off this manager, she recognized the opportunity for growth and engaged in a constructive dialogue. This approach allowed her to assert her agency in addressing the manager&#39;s lack of awareness regarding insensitive comments. She chose to model a collaborative approach where others could learn and improve.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Their interaction vividly demonstrated the transformative power of open, safe, and trusting communication, highlighting the remarkable potential for positive change when both parties approach tricky, uncomfortable conversations with an authentic intention to understand and be understood.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Assess the right time to intervene.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Saying something and not saying something are both choices that carry profound consequences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sometimes, an intervention can occur in the moment or shortly after that. If you&#39;re alone with someone who has just shared an offensive, denigrating, or derogatory comment and feel at risk of saying something that may be misunderstood or weaponized against you, wait until there are others around that can offer support or report it to HR or an anonymous hotline. Alternatively, if you feel comfortable, you can try saying, “When you said ___, I felt ____” or “I&#39;m sure you didn&#39;t mean it, but that comment didn&#39;t land well on me.” The person receiving the feedback may need to be made aware of the impact of their words and actions. Waiting too long risks negative feelings lingering and growing within yourself and others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Had the employee not shared her concerns, or had the manager responded defensively and retaliated, it would have resulted in a missed opportunity to cultivate a healthy and thriving workplace environment. Moreover, it could have perpetuated a culture of fear and burdened her and other employees who share similar fears, ultimately hindering their growth and well-being throughout their careers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Ask for help.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As I advanced in my career, I yearned for leaders who would use their position of authority to challenge toxic behavior. As I assumed leadership roles myself, I realized the responsibility fell on me to exemplify the behaviors I desired.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you lack guidance from a manager or leader on navigating tricky situations or your organization&#39;s conflict resolution, grievance, and disciplinary procedures, turn to your HR team. I understand the hesitation in reaching out, especially if your relationship with HR isn&#39;t strong. Nevertheless, HR is there to advocate for employee voice, agency, and safety. They can assist you in gathering information, understanding root causes, and determining appropriate actions. An HR partner can facilitate constructive dialogue, coach you and others involved, and find proactive solutions to address behavioral issues. It&#39;s important to approach this option carefully, as it may intensify tensions or discomfort among team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/mckinsey/featured%20insights/diversity%20and%20inclusion/women%20in%20the%20workplace%202022/women-in-the-workplace-2022.pdf&quot;>;Women in the Workplace 2022&lt;/a>;, LeanIn and McKinsey&#39;s annual report about the state of women in corporate America, women overall, and Black women and women with disabilities in particular, frequently experience microaggressions at work, such as having their judgment questioned or receiving criticism for their demeanor. Seeking support from the resources available in the workplace can make a significant difference in fostering a thriving and healthy career. Holding colleagues, managers, and leadership accountable is crucial in addressing and mitigating these harmful experiences.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this example, the employee approached HR for coaching to navigate this complex situation. By utilizing available resources, she empowered herself to address the issue effectively, making a significant difference in her experience and that of others on the team. Her proactive approach, seeking assistance, being open to feedback, and engaging in self-reflection, played a pivotal role in achieving a positive outcome.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Repair harm; repair trust.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Repeated acts of harm, such as subtle &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/research-the-real-time-impact-of-microaggressions&quot;>;microaggressions&lt;/a>;, can weigh heavily on well-being, workplace satisfaction, and productivity. To heal from interpersonal tensions that arise from misunderstandings, misaligned perspectives or expectations, hurtful language, abuses of power, or breaches of trust, the person harmed must feel heard, respected, and valued.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to Kay Pranis, a national leader in restorative justice, assuming accountability and implementing measures to rectify the damage caused and prevent its recurrence requires &lt;a href=&quot;https://irp.cdn-website.com/76b5fa75/files/uploaded/Kay%20Pranis%20Article%20for%20March%20Blog.pdf&quot;>;five elements&lt;/a>;:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Acknowledge that your actions caused harm.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Acknowledge that you had agency in those actions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Understand the full impact of your actions on anyone who was impacted.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Take steps to repair the harm and make amends.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Identify patterns or habits that led to causing harm and take steps to change those habits.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Repairing harm can manifest in various ways: acknowledging the harm, expressing remorse, admitting guilt, and committing to behavioral change through new policies, commitments, or agreements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a woman of color, I&#39;ve heard my fair share of comments that offend, upset, or hurt me, and I have regrettably done the same to others. Whenever I&#39;ve been the target of microaggressions, I try to collect my thoughts and emotions before addressing a coworker, respond assertively with “I” statements, and often reply with kindness and humor to defuse the tension. For example: “When you restated my recommendation in the recap meeting without giving me credit, I felt erased from our conversation. I&#39;d like us to have a healthy working relationship. Can you help me understand why you omitted my contribution?” Or: “When you confused me for the other Latina on the floor, I felt we were both invisible to you. And I think I&#39;m pretty memorable!”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When I unintentionally make an insensitive comment, such as misgendering someone, I immediately approach the impacted individual with humility. I sincerely listen to understand the impact of my words and offer a heartfelt apology while taking complete accountability for my words and actions. I also encourage them to call me in if I repeat such behavior because I am committed to learning from my mistakes and growing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear, it is not the responsibility of women, BIPOC, or members of marginalized communities to educate their colleagues on how to foster healthy interactions. To proactively create more meaningful relationships, ask yourself these questions: How can I focus on what the person is saying, and not solely on how they say it or how they look? What else do I need to know to understand what my colleague is trying to communicate instead of dismissing or avoiding what they say? And before addressing someone&#39;s uncomfortable comment, ask yourself: Am I responding to being shut down, ignored, or offended, or am I trying to be right? If both parties are willing, there are ways of responding that can lead to constructive conversations and shared understanding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Repeated acts of harm in particular must be addressed. MIT&#39;s Sloan School of Management conducted &lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/toxic-culture-is-driving-the-great-resignation/&quot;>;a study in 2022&lt;/a>; that found that employee turnover is 10 times more influenced by a toxic corporate culture than compensation. Taking responsibility means understanding the wide range of perspectives and experiences across teams and proactively identifying sources of tension. A good starting point is asking yourself, “What do I need to hear, what do I need to say, and what would I like to see as an outcome?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this example, the manager took essential steps to repair the trust his insensitive comments had initially broken. He demonstrated accountability by acknowledging the harm his words caused and engaged in open dialogue. By actively working to understand the impact of his words and offering to take tangible steps to change his behavior, he successfully began repairing the trust with his new employee and, quite possibly, his relationship with the broader team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of us want to change workplace conditions so everyone can thrive, yet sometimes, we are terrified of messing up, saying the wrong thing, or not being able to do enough. Addressing interpersonal tensions and toxicity requires an ongoing, proactive effort that fosters empathy, intentionality, and courage. By identifying the true source of the tension, seeking understanding, assessing when to intervene, involving neutral third parties if necessary, and repairing harm and trust quickly and often, you can prevent conflict from escalating and build a stronger, more connected, and more effective team.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Game Plan for Funding Carbon Offsets]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_-537715290_-1363813940.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration: Edmon de Haro; Baloncici/Getty Images (chimney); Vitalina/Getty Images (butterflies)&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The most common types of carbon offsets are nature-based offsets such as forests. Unfortunately, while emissions remain in the atmosphere around 1,000 years, possibly longer, a tree can only remove carbon for its lifespan of 10o or so years, which means a forest planted as a carbon offset must be maintained with trees replanted at least ten times to &amp;#160;match the emission it is offsetting. Most businesses will be reluctant to tie up capital in this way, but such projects can be (and have been) financed by perpetual bonds, which represent attractive investments for investors such as university endowments that have very long liability streams extending far into the future. The use of financial instruments such as perpetual bonds can make considerable quantities of capital available to offset producers, spurring the production and the creation of spot markets in offsets that can definitively and reliably be offset against emissions.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/a-game-plan-for-funding-carbon-offsets?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;In September 2015, a curator from Yale&#39;s Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library traveled to Amsterdam to collect the previous 12 years&#39; worth of interest on &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.yale.edu/2015/09/22/living-artifact-dutch-golden-age-yale-s-367-year-old-water-bond-still-pays-interest&quot;>;a bond issued on May 15, 1648&lt;/a>;. At the bond&#39;s issuance, the borrower, an autonomous Dutch water authority, had promised to pay the holder interest &lt;em>;in perpetuity&lt;/em>;. Cash from sale of the bond had been used to pay for an infrastructure project that protected against rising sea levels.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Such perpetual bonds may prove useful in today&#39;s fight against climate change by enabling the funding of projects that will remove and store carbon indefinitely. Carbon removals can be used to offset carbon-emissions liabilities (or &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/11/accounting-for-climate-change&quot;>;E-liabilities&lt;/a>;), thereby helping businesses and other organizations achieve net-zero goals. Perpetual bonds can also support the development of efficient &lt;em>;spot markets&lt;/em>; in removal offsets, spurring both their production and their use.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Perpetual bonds help resolve a key mismatch between the duration of many carbon offsets and the duration of the E-liabilities they are to be netted against. As we note in our July-August HBR print article, “&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/accounting-for-carbon-offsets&quot;>;Accounting for Carbon Offsets&lt;/a>;,”&amp;nbsp;E-liabilities from greenhouse gas emissions pose a particular challenge to financial markets since emissions produced today are expected to linger in the atmosphere for more than 1,000 years, a duration far longer than typical financial liabilities. Given that, we establish the need for offsetable carbon-emission assets (E-assets) to also have &lt;em>;indefinite &lt;/em>;duration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Certain E-assets such as carbon capture and storage via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usgs.gov/news/featured-story/making-minerals-how-growing-rocks-can-help-reduce-carbon-emissions&quot;>;subterranean mineralization&lt;/a>; explicitly meet this criterion, but such E-assets are currently uncommon. Far more widespread today are nature-based offsets (NBOs) such as virgin forestation programs, which typically have shorter durations stemming from the &lt;em>;finite&lt;/em>; (unreplenished) lifetime of forests (potentially less than 100 years). At issue, then, is whether NBOs can be used to net E-liabilities: if they cannot, then most removal offsets being supplied today are only down-payments against long-term emissions liabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For NBOs to have indefinite duration, the issuer must commit to managing the underlying (forest) asset in perpetuity — that is, replanting the forest as its constituent trees naturally decay or are destroyed by disease, fire, etc. To finance this operation, the offset provider needs capital not only to buy the land and plant trees but also to provide for predictable outlays in perpetuity. In other words, they must invest part of any capital raised in an endowment fund, the returns on which can go towards financing the management of the forest so that the carbon remains sequestered indefinitely (defined as, say, 1,000 years, a reasonable scientific estimate of how long carbon emitted today will stay in the atmosphere).&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Moreover, given the indefinite commitment, an issuer wanting to qualify some fraction of its presently delivered (or “earned”) removal offsets as being immediately and fully nettable against the purchaser&#39;s E-liabilities will have to set aside a separate (significantly larger) fraction of its available earned offsets against future commitments to sequester carbon.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;All this implies that providers of capital to producers of NBO offsets can expect relatively low returns on their investments, albeit distributed in perpetuity. Individual offset buyers (usually for-profit businesses) will not find it attractive to tie up their own capital in this way. But such an investment might well be attractive to institutions that require endowments to cover predictable liabilities far into the future, such as universities and churches. The investment would take the form of a perpetual bond — such as that issued by the Dutch water authority — or of preferred equity with a fixed dividend. Ordinary equity is likely not suitable to finance indefinite-duration removal offsets since investors usually want a guaranteed return for tying up capital in perpetuity with limited upside.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Consider, as a hypothetical example of how a perpetual bond approach can work, an indigenous tribe in Canada that wants to sell nettable E-assets from a virgin forest that it will plant on its land and manage indefinitely. To do so, it must raise capital to develop and maintain the forest. The tribe can issue a perpetual bond and place some of the capital in an everlasting financial endowment. The tribe uses the interest from the endowment to pay for the costs of managing the forest. As offsets from the forest become “earned” — that is, trees mature and sequester carbon — the tribe can sell some portion of these E-assets to pay for expenses, including the interest on the perpetual bond.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Let&#39;s assume that 20 megatons of CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; equivalent (MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e) of offsets from the forest&#39;s current trees is “captured” this year and will be so for the next 100 years, but the trees will then have to be replanted at least 10 more times to be nettable against a 1,000-year E-liability. To distribute the risks of this commitment, the tribe can sell 2 MtCO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>;e of this year&#39;s offset as “earned” in perpetuity (ie, 20 Mt divided by 10).&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;If there are enough producers of NBO offsets and enough demand for them, the nettable offsets can be sold into a liquid market, which distributes the future risks of the forest across a range of offset purchasers and helps the tribe to meet its interest obligations. Next year&#39;s spot buyers may be different from this year&#39;s, and, indeed, spot buyers hundreds of years thence likely will be very different, but collectively, through contributing to the perpetual bond&#39;s interest costs, they share in the long time-series risks of NBOs. The scheme is profitable for the tribe as long as the proceeds from spot sales of nettable offsets and from endowment returns exceed the bond&#39;s interest expenses and the ongoing forest-management costs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Very likely, no one 375 years ago expected the Dutch seawall-management bonds would make interest payments in the present day to a New England university library 3,500 miles away. Likewise, we cannot predict how financial markets will develop to meet the needs of emissions liability management. But the pathway set out here suggests a feasible market solution to mitigate the long-term consequences from today&#39;s carbon emissions.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Company Prepared for the Effects of Wildfires?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_13_1258513476.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Angela Weiss/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Today&amp;#8217;s wildfires and smoke can travel hundreds of miles, blurring the lines between what happens within and outside the workplace when it comes to workforce health. Now is the time for employers to develop a plan to get ahead of this and other climate change-driven health issues. The author recommends taking six actions: 1) Connect global wildfires to local health; 2) Collect and assess air quality data, developing thresholds for workforce advisories; 3) Identify the key stakeholders in your corporate response team and activate your command center; 4) Identify when to take action for outdoor workers; 5) Identify how to support indoor office employees; and 6) Develop communication and education plans for your employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/is-your-company-prepared-for-the-effects-of-wildfires?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Wildfires. The word has struck fear into the hearts of small and midsize rural communities for generations. Now, thanks to smoke blanketing parts of North America, urban America and the corporations headquartered there are beginning to understand themselves as vulnerable, too. Last week, East Coast cities from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/live/2023/06/07/us/canada-wildfires-air-quality-smoke&quot;>;New York&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/air-quality-toronto-fires-smoke-1.6868010&quot;>;Toronto&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-wildfire-smoke-canada-updates-june-7/&quot;>;Montreal&lt;/a>; saw air quality rapidly decline to some of the worst in the world as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/smoke-air-quality-nyc-northeast-canadian-wildfires-6b5ffc01&quot;>;smoke from wildfires in Canada&lt;/a>; drifts south. This means the conversation in Corporate America has moved beyond indoor air circulation or filtration, to encompass outdoor air quality as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Poor air quality impacts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ishn.com/articles/113569-how-poor-iaq-impacts-employee-safety-and-productivity&quot;>;employee health and productivity&lt;/a>;, from diminished &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/news/press-releases/office-air-quality-may-affect-employees-cognition-productivity/&quot;>;cognitive function&lt;/a>; and poor &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w20648&quot;>;concentration&lt;/a>; to lowered &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/09/air-pollution-is-making-office-workers-less-productive&quot;>;productivity&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/ab8b8c&quot;>;sentiment&lt;/a>;. It can also exacerbate health conditions like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7503605/&quot;>;asthma&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2022.926534/full&quot;>;anxiety&lt;/a>; and lead to increased &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unicef.org/mongolia/media/2926/file/UNICEF-Absenteeism-ENG-final.pdf&quot;>;absenteeism&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9554460/&quot;>;presenteeism&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.graduateinstitute.ch/sites/internet/files/2021-04/HHW_2020.pdf&quot;>;leaves of absence&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Wildfires and smoke have disrupted corporate travel, postponed company activities, and sent employees to their doctors for a host of related health issues, including difficulty breathing. Unfortunately, there&#39;s likely more to come in the future — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epa.gov/climate-indicators/climate-change-indicators-wildfires&quot;>;climate change&lt;/a>; means increases in wildfire season length, frequency, and burned area.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a physician working for an international organization advising corporate leaders, we are seeing a rapid rise in employer inquiries related to employee health and the best practices around air quality concerns. HR teams are fielding complex questions from employees and leaders — and many don&#39;t feel prepared with the right information.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is reminiscent of the height of Covid in March 2020, when leaders asked: Is this an issue we need to respond to? What do I need to know? What action do I need to take now? Here are six actions for employers to consider as they navigate this ongoing issue.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Connect global wildfires to local health.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Air pollution can harm anyone. But it is more dangerous for specific employee segments and their family members. This includes infants and young children, seniors over 65, pregnant women, anyone who exercises or works outdoors, and people with existing illness or chronic health conditions, such as diabetes, lung, or heart conditions. During heavy smoke conditions, all employees may be at risk regardless of their age or health. Impacts can be both physical and psychological, especially for employees experiencing the trauma of wildfire evacuation from their homes and workplaces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Smoke can travel thousands of miles from an initial fire zone, which means that wildfires in other parts of the world will impact your people in the local communities where your company operates. Smoke from wildfires includes a complex mixture of pollutants, like fine particulate matter. Invisible to the human eye, these particles get deep into our lungs and bloodstream, sometimes leading to serious health effects.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There is no evidence of a safe level of exposure for some pollutants, meaning that smoke can impact employees&#39; health even at very low levels. And as local smoke levels increase, the health risks to your workforce will generally increase as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Collect and assess air quality data.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Data can typically be found through an Air Quality Index (AQI), which is a system used to warn the public when air pollution reaches dangerous levels. In the US, the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) issues year-round AQI forecasts with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airnow.gov/&quot;>;maps&lt;/a>; showing how pollution levels change and move throughout the day, and other countries have similar resources. This “real-time” information can help employers to quantify current outdoor air quality that impacts both their employees and customers far before it hits front-page news.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also recommend working with health care experts such as physicians or medical consultants to develop specific thresholds for workforce advisories that go along with these levels. Doing so will help you take steps to protect your employees from unhealthy levels of air pollution and enable them to proactively seek appropriate supports for their health and safety. Specific thresholds paired with health care guidance will also prepare managers to communicate with and guide their teams in line with corporate policy. Once your organization understands how to use air quality data and sets monitoring thresholds, it will help trigger your corporate response at the right time and place.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Activate your command center.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Identify who needs to be brought together to respond when AQI thresholds are met, especially if there is an immediate physical health and safety threat to employees. Wildfire-related local evacuations &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/12/how-kaiser-permanente-prepares-for-disasters&quot;>;are particularly high stakes&lt;/a>;, especially when hundreds of thousands evacuate all at once as seen in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/dec/11/southern-california-wildfires-blaze&quot;>;Southern California&lt;/a>;. Your corporate response team may include local business leaders in impacted areas, communications specialists, medical advisors, HR leaders and even risk practitioners given broader enterprise issues involved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Your multi-disciplinary approach may look similar to governance models &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmjleader.bmj.com/content/leader/early/2020/04/07/leader-2020-000244.full.pdf&quot;>;developed during the Covid pandemic&lt;/a>; and will ensure timely information is continuously flowing to and from the right stakeholders, including executives and the board. It will also enable rapid, holistic decision-making and related corporate response. This may range from meeting occupational health and safety standards to regulatory compliance for different employee segments like indoor versus outdoor workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Focus on outdoor workers, and comply with regulation.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Depending on your industry, outdoor work exposure to wildfire smoke is regulated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/niosh/topics/firefighting/wffsmoke.html&quot;>;occupational health and safety&lt;/a>; standards and regulatory bodies like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134&quot;>;Occupational Safety and Health Administration&lt;/a>; (OSHA). Long work schedules and physical work demands may impact a worker&#39;s exposure risk and health response. Geography matters, as local regulations differ. For example, California&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dir.ca.gov/title8/5141_1.html&quot;>;emergency regulation&lt;/a>; applies to workplaces where AQI is greater than 151 or if employees are expected to be exposed to wildfire smoke.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers should know their local air quality regulations and take action to limit outdoor workers&#39; exposure, particularly when wildfire smoke is in or around the work environment. This may include relocating or rescheduling work tasks to smoke-free or less smoky areas or times of the day, reducing levels of physical activity when possible, providing workers with frequent breaks in places that are free from smoke, and offering special accommodations where required.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In some situations, the use of personal protective equipment (PPE), such as well-fitted N95 respirators, should be considered to limit workers&#39; exposure. When US employers require use of respiratory protection to limit exposure to smoke, this should occur as part of a comprehensive respiratory protection program as outlined in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134&quot;>;OSHA Respiratory Protection Standard&lt;/a>;. (When use is voluntary, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/laws-regs/regulations/standardnumber/1910/1910.134AppD&quot;>;other OSHA standards&lt;/a>; apply.)&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Support indoor office employees.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Air quality can be unexpectedly complex for indoor office workers. Corporate safety standards related to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://deloitte.wsj.com/articles/staying-compliant-in-an-era-of-hybrid-and-remote-work-c0e0938e&quot;>;home office&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalguardian.com/global-digest/at-home-duty-of-care&quot;>;worker travel&lt;/a>; have been elevated in recent years. And while it is arguable whether an employer&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1741438/does-employers-duty-care-extend-commuting&quot;>;duty of care&lt;/a>; extends to the employee journey to and from work, the commute matters, especially if an employee needs to navigate significant outdoor air pollution to get to and from the office. Taking a holistic “employee experience journey” approach can help calibrate potential risks for employee segments in hard-hit local areas or where there are specific individual health risk factors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As many office buildings have advanced heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC) systems and optimized Minimum Efficiency Reporting Value (MERV) ratings, the air quality at the office may be superior to that of the average home during wildfire season. Employers may need to take additional actions to reduce exposure to and protect occupants from wildfire smoke. This may include installing air cleaners equipped with high-efficiency particulate air (HEPA) filters, ensuring that windows and other building openings are kept closed to reduce overall smoke exposure inside, operating HVAC systems in the re-circulate setting, or temporarily reducing the amount of outdoor air supplied to the building. If you currently lease office space, engage your landlord to ensure that they optimize protection of your indoor workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More broadly, consider security, medical, and mental-health coverage to keep your people safe in times of crisis. This includes extending fulsome protection to the entire workforce, whether they commute or work indoors or outside. Employees working from home in your local corporate backyard might need that same 24/7 evacuation coverage you previously only considered for international travelers. This coverage applies equally to wildfires as it does to other natural disasters, like flooding or hurricanes, when companies often provide assistance such as food and water, shelter, or emergency evacuation. At many companies, this extra layer of coverage requires a mentality shift, but it is one worth making today.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6. Communicate and educate broadly.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Depending on the scope and scale of a wildfire and its impact on your organization, consider what should be communicated proactively (eg, that your organization is aware of and actively responding to worsening local air quality) and reactively (eg, messaging from HR in relation to very specific individual circumstances requiring accommodations).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Education is an important part of any communication plan related to wildfires and air quality, so alert your employees to symptoms of wildfire smoke exposure. Milder and more common symptoms include headaches, mild cough, sore and watery eyes, and nose, throat, and sinus irritation. More serious but less common symptoms include dizziness, chest pains, severe cough, shortness of breath, wheezing, and even irregular heartbeat. Encourage employees to seek care from a health care provider and consider urgent medical attention if warranted for severe cases such as risks for asthma attacks, stroke, or heart attack.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the case of severe wildfire events, communication may include addressing immediate physical health and safety threats and extend to longer-term practices around air quality and respiratory health. Providing individual employee guidance on what to do to safeguard their health when air quality level is at different thresholds can help. For example, at higher levels, employees can be guided to avoid prolonged vigorous activity outdoors and stay away from high-traffic areas. It may also mean postponing or cancelling certain corporate and team-building events, or moving outdoor gatherings indoors. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.canada.ca/en/health-canada/services/publications/healthy-living/how-prepare-wildfire-smoke.html#:~:text=Checklist%20for%20wildfire%20smoke%20season%20preparedness,-Are%20you%20or&amp;amp;text=Do%20you%20have%20an%20adequate%20supply%20of%20food%20and%20water,a%20break%20from%20the%20smoke%3F&quot;>;Preparedness checklists&lt;/a>; can help and may cover home, office, and personal medical preparedness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Today&#39;s wildfires and smoke can travel hundreds of miles, blurring the lines between what happens within and outside the workplace when it comes to workforce health. Now is the time to get ahead of this and other climate change-driven health issues. Source new resources, pilot novel approaches, and translate them into productive corporate action to support employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>