<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Can the Construction Industry Be Disrupted?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_08_1299614411.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论工作人员/丹·雷诺兹摄影/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot; close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;建筑业经常被诟病为技术落后的行业。行业观察家经常嘲笑建筑行业缺乏先进的技术，并将其视为过时的行业，落后于制造业等更具前瞻性和目标的行业。但这种观点忽略了该行业的进步——具体来说，在信息管理系统方面已经取得了显着的成果。此外，它没有考虑到为什么自动化和机器人技术在工作现场不起作用，因为它们通常不适合与工厂车间几乎没有相似之处的动态环境。然而，了解为什么有些技术扎根而有些技术没有扎根，对于对新工具和系统进行明智投资至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div >; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07 /can-the-construction-industry-be-disrupted?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;1910 年，法国艺术家 Villemard 创作了一系列想象 2000 年生活的插图. 在他的一幅绘画中，一位建筑师&lt;a href=&quot;https://wearereplicants.wordpress.com/2011/03/10/french-artist-villemards-vision-of-the-future/&quot;>;坐在一个展位上按下控制台上的按钮&lt;/a>;来操纵在建筑工地常见废墟中运行的一系列机器。各种机器切割、成型、提升和放置石块来建造房屋。他的设想中没有人类劳动者——机械化已经使人类劳动者过时了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，维尔玛德的愿景并没有实现。相反，行业观察家经常嘲笑建筑行业缺乏技术成熟度，并将其视为过时的、落后于制造业等更具前瞻性和目标的行业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这故事已经讲了又讲了。在二战后房地产繁荣之后，《财富》的编辑们于 1947 年发表了一篇文章，题为“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biblio.com/book/fortune-magazine-volume” -xxxvi-number-2/d/1489550271&quot;>;工业资本主义被遗忘了&lt;/a>;”，他们在其中嘲笑了住宅建筑的“封建特征”和“皮卡尤恩规模”。 2006 年，麻省理工学院教授 John Fernandez 总结了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/books/edition/Material_Architecture/AtMrBgAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;dq=the+slowest+ 时的传统智慧of+all+industries+of+such+scale+in+implementing+proven,+scienceically+sound+technological+innovation&amp;amp;pg=PA11&amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;>;他写道&lt;/a>;：“人们普遍认为，建筑在如此规模的所有行业中，实施经过验证的、科学合理的技术创新是最慢的。”十年后，麦肯锡顾问&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/operations/our-insights/reinventing-construction-through-a-productivity-revolution&quot;>;继续鼓噪&lt;/a>;，将生产力提高有限归咎于“项目管理和执行不善……技能开发、研发和创新投资不足”。 2023 年初，芝加哥大学经济学家 Austan Goolsbee 和 Chad Syverson 发表了一篇题为《&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w30845&quot;>;美国建筑行业奇怪而可怕的生产力之路》的文章&lt;/a>;”，他们得出的结论是，总体数据“表明建筑业生产力在长达数十年的时间里大幅下降。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有关反对变革的轶事也描绘了类似的情况。无论在哪个时代，担心节省劳动力的设备可能会加深行业固有的生活不安全感的工人们有时都会对在建筑工地引入新机械感到不满。木匠 Joseph Emanuello &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/j.ctv941wxz.19?seq=2&quot;>;回忆&lt;/a>;他第一次遇到电动圆锯时：“一个人拿着斯基尔锯开建筑物的屋顶并将其扔掉。他说，‘锯子太快了，我要用手切割。’”承包商办公室也对采用创新犹豫不决。 1983 年，刚从工程学校毕业的约翰·托奇 (John Tocci) 为他的几代家族总承包公司购买了一台昂贵的大型计算机，他的父亲（所有者）看着这件笨重的东西，抱怨道：“当那个奇怪的东西可以砌砖时，我会学习如何使用它。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是很容易夸大阻力程度。 1993年，一位研究人员对商人进行了采访，了解他们对技术创新的态度。除了少数例外，他们欢迎新工具，这些工具使工作更安全、体力要求更低，并且在大多数情况下，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/23746019&quot;>;他们对产量增加的自豪感压倒了他们对流离失所的恐惧&lt;/a>;。总的来说，建筑业采取了渐进式而非革命性的变革步伐。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，并不是每个人都希望它保持这种状态：Villemard 拥有当代的追随者，他们继续展望建筑业的全机械化未来，只是越过地平线。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.roboticsbusinessreview.com/construction/more-than-7000-robots-will-work-in-construction-by-2025-report-says/&quot;>;Tractica 的 2019 年报告&lt;/技术市场情报公司 a>; 宣称，由于技术不发达的历史，建筑业“颠覆的时机已经成熟”，并预测到 2025 年建筑机器人的购买量将增加十倍。Built Robotics 副总裁 Gaurav Kikani 表示：将会出现“机器人技术的爆炸式增长”，它将用全天候的自动化活动取代八小时的工作日。最近的一项全球调查表明&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forconstructionpros.com/construction-technology/article/21451998/abb-group-robotic-automations-potential-to-enhance-productivity-efficiency-and-safety -on-construction-sites&quot;>;81% 的建筑企业&lt;/a>;将在未来十年引入或增加机器人和自动化的使用。在 2020 年报告中，麦肯锡公司公司未来主义者&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/McKinsey/Industries/Capital%20Projects%20and%20Infrastruct/Our%20Insights/The%20next%20normal%20in%20construction/The- next-normal-in-construction.pdf&quot;>;预测行业价值链的 45%&lt;/a>; 将在未来 15 年内从传统流程转变。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;乐观主义者和悲观主义者都在努力解决什么问题然而，这就是为什么一些技术在行业中扎根——通常会显着提高生产率——而其他技术（例如工地机器人）却不能的原因。了解这一点将有助于建筑公司和为其供货的公司预测哪些投资会获得回报，哪些最终会成为尘埃落定的好奇心。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;为什么某些技术无法占据主导地位&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;许多被行业媒体大肆吹捧的发明仍然处于行业的边缘。最先进的六轴关节型机器人可能已经改变了汽车行业，但它们的固定特性在建筑工地上不起作用。无法移动且无法适应建筑项目的崎岖地形和多层性质的机器人在功能上毫无用处。自主土方机械可以挖掘和准备地基。机器人可以做简单的布局。无人机可以导航作业现场并记录每日进度。外骨骼可以减轻举起重物的负担，YouTube 视频描绘了 3D 打印的奇迹。然而，其中许多进步仍然是新颖的项目，只有少数拥有资源和意愿的公司才能使用这些设备和系统，而这些设备和系统尚未始终被证明具有质量或成本效益。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; “人们认为机器人很聪明。他们正在好转，但仍然很愚蠢。”&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/db2b5d64-10e7-11e8-a765-993b2440bd73&quot;>;Jeremy Hadall 说道&lt;/a>;英国制造技术中心机器人和自动化首席技术专家。 “机器人在建筑行业提高生产力方面占有一席之地，但你必须现实地认识它们的能力。十年后我们会看到完全自动化的机器人建筑工地吗？不。”同样，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autodeskresearch.com/groups/robotics-lab&quot;>;Autodesk 机器人实验室&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autodeskresearch.com/groups/robotics-lab&quot;>;机器人技术总监 Erin Bradner forbes.com/sites/charlestowersclark/2020/01/10/construction-co-bots-need-to-be-smarter-more-adaptive-part-two/?sh=126d2c296a79&quot;>;表明当前 co 的复杂程度-机器人可能被夸大了&lt;/a>;：“它们遇到障碍时会停止，但你不希望你的项目在每次有人打喷嚏时停止。”圣地亚哥州立大学工程学教授 Reza Akhavian 获得了美国国家科学基金会 691,000 美元的资助，用于研究建筑中的机器人技术。 “目前以及在可预见的未来，机器人领域，特别是建筑机器人领域，甚至还没有达到机器人可以取代人类工人的状态，”&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive. com/news/contech-conversations-sdsu-professor-says-robots-not-close-to-replacing/600771/&quot;>;Akhavian 争论&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不愿意接受新技术是基于不仅仅是行业参与者暴躁和逆行的态度。机器人和其他形式的自动化成本高昂，并且需要较长的时间才能提供令人满意的资本回报。鉴于该行业的分散性和中小型企业的主导地位，很少有业主有财力购买昂贵的设备，而这些设备可能只能在很长一段时间内提供利润。尽管大型总承包商手头可能有更多现金，但分包商雇用了大部分劳动力。一家资本雄厚的公司几乎没有动力去投资一项最终将使另一家小公司受益的技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，其他行业的公司传统上一直有动力在自动化和昂贵的新程序上投入资金，以减少成本。劳动力成本不断上升。不幸的是，建筑高管找到了更简单的方法来削减劳动力成本，通过将员工错误分类为独立承包商、现金补偿以及降低工资和安全标准——所有这些都是&lt;a href=&quot;https://lwp.law.harvard.edu/ files/lwp/files/erlich_ilrr_final_article_11.28.20.pdf&quot;>;在该国许多地区成功地破坏了工会部门&lt;/a>;。当劳动力本身不那么昂贵时，购买机器人来取代高价劳动力的动力就会减弱。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;建筑业的数字化转型&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;尽管如此，二十一世纪的数字革命推动了建设，特别是建筑功能和项目管理系统。建筑信息模型 (BIM) 是一种将传统蓝图转换为数字图像的软件流程，将协调的关键因素引入到以前来自各个设计学科（建筑、结构、机械、电气、土木）的孤立产品中，并允许管理团队基本上要两次构建一个项目：一次虚拟地在办公室台式机和平板电脑上构建，第二次与现场的实际贸易工人和材料构建。 Suffolk Construction 的执行副总裁 Jeff Gouveia 在一次采访中向我描述了 BIM 出现之前的工作方式：“在建模之前，协调是通过一张上面有一块透明塑料的灯桌来完成的。您将 2D 绘图叠加在 2D 绘图之上。你把它们弄对了，把它们粘在角落里，确保它们的比例合适，然后你基本上就开始盘旋冲突，一根管道系统或管道进入一根柱子或一根梁。”建模可以实现从现场工作到完成硬件的整个开发的高级可视化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建模可以降低总施工成本，但它需要的前期投资规模只有较大的总承包商和少数精英分包商有能力负担软件费用，最重要的是，有能力雇用和培训具有高度计算机知识的员工。大学和医院等机构所有者预计其项目将持续数十年，他们比倾向于关注底线、仅通过保修和短期翻转目标生存的开发商更有可能接受建模的初始成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然 BIM 最初只涉及专业人士，但后来建模已经渗透到该领域的工作人员中，以对正在展开的设计提供建议和批评。 Gouveia 描述了标准任务的过渡，例如通过混凝土甲板布置管道和电气管道的套管。 “以前，你展开图纸，风在吹，一侧有一根钢筋，另一侧有一块砖，你试图按住它。然后你缩放它并检查并使用你的磁带。现在，有人拥有一台笔记本电脑、平板电脑或 iPad，模型就在那里，地板也已布置好。只需 90 分钟即可完成布置，而在此之前可能需要 5 个小时。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管目前仅限于较大的项目，但数字化和建模将继续进一步渗透到行业中。 2021 年 1.2 万亿美元基础设施投资和就业法案 (ILJA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constructiondive.com/news/construction-tech-praise-110-million-infrastruct-bill-push-for-more/610126 /&quot;>;包括 1 亿美元&lt;/a>;用于先进的数字施工管理系统和相关技术。虽然该法案中的措辞并不具体，但这些资金预计将支持先进的数字管理工具、3D 建模、无人机可视化和数据分析。 2016 年，英国强制要求在公共项目中使用 BIM，国家建筑科学研究所 (NIBS) 于 2021 年初主办了一次会议，考虑在美国采用 BIM 标准。建模正在扩展到三个维度之外，纳入 4D （调度）、5D（成本）甚至 6D（设施管理）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在工作现场，工头将公司发行的平板电脑作为其工具包的一部分，因此可以即时传输计划和修改。过去可靠的工棚内装有工人过夜存放的工具，现在还可以在盖子下面配备 Wi-Fi、打印机和平面屏幕，以电子方式显示最新的施工图纸。大多数工会培训项目已将 CAD 和 BIM 纳入其课程中。来自不同人口和社会经济背景的年轻新进入该行业的人也许能够将他们的家庭计算机专业知识转化为该领域的建模能力。 “我们总是需要机械师来组装东西，”约翰·托奇在接受采访时告诉我。 “但未来的机械师也将是视频游戏人员。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然 Villemard 的愿景现在看起来像是科幻小说中的东西，但已经采取了稳定但不引人注目的步骤来改变行业。建造摩天大楼所需的工人数量比一两年前要少得多。工具和材料不断升级，BIM 代表了一种新颖且卓越的项目设计和建造方法。然而，在一个基本上仍然分散的行业中，不太可能发生剧烈的变化。投资改变游戏规则的技术的能力仅限于合同社区的上层。在可预见的未来，绝大多数中小型分包商和行业工人将会调整和适应，而不是扰乱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;本文改编自作者的书&lt;/em>;我们的建筑方式：恢复建筑工作的尊严。&lt;em>;这是两部分系列的第一部分。&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is Responsible Computing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_4689448.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;雅罗斯拉夫·丹尼琴科/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;对于企业而言，技术具有各种相互关联的影响，包括意外后果、数据风险和技术使用的适当性，以及更广泛的环境问题。作者提供了一个系统的负责任计算框架，它将能源消耗和排放等环境挑战与许多其他社会和治理方面结合起来。这是一个实用的蓝图，企业可以利用它来使其 IT 更加绿色、道德、值得信赖和可持续，其基础是领导者需要解决的六大支柱，以使其企业成为负责任的计算提供商：数据中心、基础设施、代码、数据、系统和影响。对于每个指标，他们都提供了领导者应重点关注的几个 KPI。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is -responsible-computing?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-is-responsible-computing?language=pt&quot;>;阅读葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在过去几年中，IBM 与数百位首席技术官 (CTO) 进行了交谈，反映了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibm.com/thought- Leadership/institute-business-value/en-us/c-suite-study/cto&quot;>;一系列架构决策点报告&lt;/a>;。显然，企业领导者认识到技术将成为交付未来企业的核心部分。然而，他们也清楚地意识到，社会正在寻求企业证明他们可以按照他们所拥护的价值观生活——而计算可以发挥关键作用。这些首席技术官提到，技术的社会影响让他们彻夜难眠。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于企业来说，技术具有各种相互关联的影响，包括意想不到的后果、数据风险和技术使用的适当性。作为更广泛的环境问题。领导者担心会给公司带来漏洞，担心部署带有有害偏见的系统，担心内部和公众如何看待人工智能，以及使用某些技术对环境的影响。这些问题都是相互关联的，尽管它们经常被单独讨论。如果公司想要确保他们是负责任的技术用户，他们需要一种整体方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们在 IBM 与我们的 CTO 外展合作中开发了一个系统性的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://responsiblecomputing .net/&quot;>;负责任的计算框架&lt;/a>;将能源消耗和排放等环境挑战与许多其他社会和治理方面相结合。这是一个实用的蓝图，企业可以利用它来使其 IT 更加绿色、道德、值得信赖和可持续。我们的负责任计算框架强调了企业领导者需要解决的六大支柱，以使其企业成为负责任的计算提供商：数据中心、基础设施、代码、数据、系统和影响力。对于每一个，我们都提供了几个可用于进行比较的 KPI。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的数据中心&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;负责任计算的第一个支柱是开发和提供 IT 服务所需的物理基础设施 —无论您是否自己运营数据中心。全球数据中心电力容量增长了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/02/23/2390642/0/en/The-Global-Data-Center-Market -Size-to-Reach-288-30-Billion-by-2027-Arizton.html&quot;>;过去三年占 43%&lt;/a>;，效率低下是一个重大问题：&lt;a href=&quot;https:// /www.nrdc.org/sites/default/files/data-center-efficiency-assessment-IP.pdf&quot;>;平均服务器&lt;/a>;以其容量的 12% 至 18% 运行，但消耗了 30% 至 60% 的资源最大功率。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks&quot;>;国际能源署 (IEA)&lt;/a>; 预测全球数据中心的能源使用将从占全球电力需求的 1% 跃升至&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-06610-y&quot;>;超过 20%&lt;/a>;十年。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;要衡量数据中心的影响，您需要考虑能源来源、与冷却相关的能源使用&lt;strong>;、&lt;/strong>;和用水量，以及&lt;a href=&quot;https ://www.techtarget.com/searchdatacenter/feature/Words-to-go-6-key-data-center-sustainability-metrics&quot;>;跟踪每个指标的 KPI&lt;/a>;。如果您不运行自己的数据中心，则可以选择最成熟的云服务提供商，例如 &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sustainability/&quot;>;AWS&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https ://newsroom.ibm.com/IBM-Cloud-Carbon-Calculator-Aims-to-Help-Organizations-Address-Greenhouse-Gas-Emissions-to-Advance-their-Sustainability-Objectives&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;，或&lt;a href=&quot;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/how-microsoft-measures-datacenter-water-and-energy-use-to-improve-azure-cloud-sustainability/&quot;>; Microsoft&lt;/a>; 将其作为其服务的一部分进行衡量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，考虑碳足迹，即数据中心使用能源时排放的二氧化碳量。考虑数据中心每天产生多少二氧化碳（碳使用效率）；数据中心消耗的能源有多清洁（技术碳效率）；以及现场产生了多少可再生能源（绿色能源系数）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;接下来是效率足迹，或者说数据中心对其计算基础设施的优化程度。为了衡量这一点，您可以查看数据中心基础设施专门使用了多少能源、数据中心内有多少能源在设施的其他地方重复使用，以及 HVAC 系统的有效性或冷却系统的整体效率。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，还有数据中心在运营过程中使用的水量，或者说水足迹。这需要分解水的使用方式，考虑基础设施、发电以及有多少水被回收用于其他目的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过清楚地了解数据中心的电源、冷却和用水情况，企业领导者可以开始批判性地思考解决这个问题。如何转向可持续能源？如何使用碳补偿？将您的基础设施转移到气候凉爽的地方会节省能源吗？您可以将基础设施产生的热量用于其他目的吗？如何节约用水？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的基础设施&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第二个支柱是减少计算对环境的影响。这要求您评估您所在的整个计算生态系统，而不仅仅是您自己的基础设施，包括开发、测试、交付、监控、控制和支持 IT 服务所需的硬件、软件和网络。虽然大多数制造商在询问时都会分享这些信息，但也有多个行业举措，例如来自 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.itu.int/en/ITU-D/Environment/Documents/Toolbox/GEM_2020_def.pdf &quot;>;国际电信联盟&lt;/a>;，标准化数据并制定最佳实践。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，考虑现在使用的计算硬件。这可以通过用电 KPI 来衡量，例如每个硬件单元的平均耗电量、计算硬件的使用频率以及一个月内使用的硬件与已安装硬件的比例。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下一步，您需要了解单位硬件的温室气体排放量，或单位碳足迹。该关键绩​​效指标衡量单个硬件单元在其生命周期的不同阶段产生的温室气体排放总量——从最初的资源开采到前体的制造、单元的制造、运行，以及一次处置的排放量。它已被取代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，测量计算产生的浪费量。这可以包括有多少硬件被送往垃圾填埋场，以及有多少硬件被翻新、再利用、转售或回收（电子废物率）。它还可以评估您的塑料足迹，根据所用塑料的总重量或所用塑料聚合物的类型以及它们的潜在最终目的地或被回收的可能性进行计算。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦您有了考虑到您的基础设施，您可以开始考虑采取措施来解决您的计算影响。您可以使用哪些技术来降低单位功率？如何才能获得更多收益——例如，通过整合、合理化或删除不使用的系统？将闲置容量用于其他目的怎么样？如何更有效地回收或再利用？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的代码&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第三个支柱是代码的效率，以及所使用的代码对环境、社会和经济的潜在影响。这涉及将责任落实到各个开发人员的层面，并确保开发负责任的设计原则或架构，以帮助他们做出正确的选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;理解负责任的代码如何工作的关键是“功能点”，即“功能点”。是表达代码提供的业务功能量的一种方式。有多种软件工具（&lt;a href=&quot;https://owasp.org/www-community/Vulnerability_Scanning_Tools&quot;>;开源&lt;/a>;和商业工具）可以帮助组织进行分析。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;首先测量功能点的效率，例如页面大小或每个进程的 HTTP 请求。您还应该测量每个功能点的碳影响 - 整个系统、单个功能点甚至功能点内单个流程的电力消耗。衡量功能点的安全性（例如已识别的漏洞数量）也至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其次，仔细查看您的代码架构。它的可扩展性如何？将代码转移到另一个平台有多容易？将一个系统中的功能点与其他系统中的功能点集成所花费的时间或成本也是一项有价值的 KPI。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，衡量代码的质量 - 例如，每个功能点的缺陷数量 -及其维护和返工属性。您还应该衡量代码的可靠性，例如整个系统、功能点甚至单个流程每季度的平均正常运行时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦您了解了功能点的效率以及整体架构和质量那么你就可以开始考虑如何改进。您应该使用开放代码还是专有代码？您的代码的安全性如何？你的代码有多开放？让代码可重用是否弊大于利？能否通过近似计算来降低计算的分辨率？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的数据&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;负责任计算的第四个支柱是数据的隐私、透明、共享和获取。该支柱直接解决了您了解在整个生命周期中处理数据的道德、法律和社会责任的责任，并允许领导者就数据的保护和隐私及其使用承担或委托所有权和责任。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;值得庆幸的是，这一领域正在进行大量工作，我们建议一个 KPI：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ictworks.org/responsible-data-maturity-model/&quot;>;负责任的数据成熟度模型&lt; /a>; 深入了解您的企业如何在 15 个领域（意识和能力、政策和治理、问责制、合作伙伴关系、库存、隐私、法律、风险、最小化、传输、安全、共享、组合）管理数据、保留和事件响应）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过此分析，您可以了解如何改进每个领域，以及如何跟踪改进。您是否有足够的数据治理？您是否了解您的企业负责的所有数据？谁对哪些数据负责？您当前的数据和法律风险是什么？您对数据事件的响应速度有多快？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的系统&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;负责任的系统是公平、负责和透明的系统。第五个支柱要求企业领导者了解他们的“系统”——工作中使用的硬件、数据、代码、模型和服务的集成集——以及使用它们的道德影响。这一支柱的核心是您组织内的系统所具有的公平性（或偏见），以及您的公司对这些系统以您的名义所做的事情负有多大的责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，考虑您的一个系统如何承担责任。系统可能会基于种族、性别、年龄或残疾等特征歧视或伤害人们。通过比较各组之间的结果来衡量这一点。更复杂的比较可以认识到群体在多个维度上存在差异。另一种方法可以衡量收到了多少关于系统公平性的投诉以及如何解决这些投诉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;接下来，确定哪些系统指定了特定个人对结果负责，并衡量对法规的遵守情况、采取什么法律手段是否可以获得补救措施，以及企业对可能发生的任何损害承担的责任。这些观点将帮助您使这些系统更加透明。通过清楚地了解您的系统的公平性、责任性和透明度，您可以开始批判性地思考解决该问题。我们如何减少系统中的偏差？我们如何才能最大限度地减少责任风险？谁负责什么系统？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个重要的 KPI 是对可审计系统结果数量的分析，另一个是系统结果的可解释性。此外，衡量解释系统目标、方法和局限性的知识工件的数量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;负责任的影响&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;最后一个支柱考虑如何利用技术来做好事——为了例如，解决社会流动性或排斥问题。但仅仅因为您的组织可以做某事，并不意味着它应该做。我们建议产生负责任影响的最佳方法是在联合国 17 个可持续发展目标 (SDG) 的背景下考虑您的计算。 Some impacts are more general, such as enabling gender equality in hiring (SDG 5), providing decent work (SDG 8), or reducing inequality in income (SDG 10). KPIs here can consider how IT investment has led to such impacts by looking at before and after statistics. Similarly, actions to meet climate change goals (SDG 13) can be measured through KPIs such as the carbon impact per employee, per customer, and per SKU (stock taking unit).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, other impact measures will be specific to industries. For instance, the type of impact your IT use can have in agriculture is different to retail. Agricultural firms can measure how their IT investments have reduced the amount of water required to irrigate the crops (SDG 6). Similarly, retail firms can measure how their IT investments have enabled more sustainable consumption and production (SDG 12).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once you have insight into how your computing impacts your performance on the SDGs, then you can start to critically evaluate how to improve in the future. How can your IT help to save lives, or improve life, in a similar way? How can you create new jobs, or help people develop new skills? How could you help speed up the response to disasters or emergencies?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Way Forward&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;World events since the pandemic and geopolitics have shown business leaders very clearly that their workers need protection, and that their supply chains are shakier than they thought. That has focused attention on corporate responsibility and how we use scarce resources. In IT specifically, the new normal is all about being fast, efficient, effective, and responsible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The task facing business leaders is to position their firms for both scale and success while taking an ethical and responsible approach to how, where, and why they use IT. The CTOs we spoke to agreed that achieving real and lasting change requires a holistic approach that encompasses every aspect of the computing ecosystem, from emissions and materials right through to ethical sourcing, data stewardship, and social responsibility work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, business leaders can&#39;t do it all on their own. They need to ensure that the entire IT function is aligned behind their responsible computing vision. Every member of the IT function will need to appreciate the ethics that underpin the responsible computing vision, as well as being accountable for their actions. This will require a professionalized IT function that has both the competence to be able to deliver on the vision, as well as the inclusivity to ensure diversity of opinion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond the IT function, the entire C-suite, employees, suppliers, partners, and customers will need to be more mindful about how they consume and conserve valuable resources—which means offering them the right incentives to do so. Everyone will have a part to play: infrastructure experts and application developers, but also professionals in sales, marketing, operations, finance, procurement, and facilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, it&#39;s a big task, but the reward will be greater trust in the organization — and, ultimately, a better world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[6 Science-Backed Ways to Improve Your Well-Being at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_1326122153.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Westend61/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;background: white&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #282828&quot;>;Employee well-being is an organizational issue, not just an individual one. Many factors impact and influence it, including your workload and flexibility, your manager, and the culture within your team. But while you may not have the ability to change your organization or your boss, there are some simple, science-backed things you can do daily to improve your emotional fitness and well-being. This article covers six&lt;span style=&quot;background: white&quot;>; simple yet surprisingly powerful emotional fitness practices to help you better manage stress and improve your well-being&lt;/span>;.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/6-science-backed-ways-to-improve-your-well-being-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In the past two and a half years, I&#39;ve given more than 360 virtual and in-person talks, workshops, and seminars about emotional fitness, well-being, and avoiding burnout. I&#39;ve had the privilege of working with people from every kind of industry, including doctors on the frontlines of Covid, employees at large and small companies, and nonprofit professionals. And I&#39;ve had the gift of staying connected with many of them to learn about which emotional fitness practices had a positive impact on their well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And here&#39;s my big learning: When it comes to improving well-being at work, small things make a big difference if you practice them consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear: Employee well-being is an organizational issue, not just an individual one. Many factors impact and influence it, including your workload and flexibility, your manager, and the culture within your team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But while you may not have the ability to change your organization or your boss, there are some simple, science-backed things you can do daily to improve your emotional fitness and well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I define emotional fitness as the skill of creating a more supportive relationship with yourself, your thoughts and emotions, and other people. When you improve your physical fitness, you improve your ability to handle physical challenges. When you improve your emotional fitness, you improve your ability to handle emotional challenges with less struggle, stress, and overwhelm.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are six simple yet surprisingly powerful emotional fitness practices to help you better manage stress and improve your well-being:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Check in with yourself daily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Ask yourself: &lt;em>;How am I doing today? How am I feeling?&lt;/em>; Don&#39;t judge your answers or immediately try to “fix” how you&#39;re feeling. Just become aware.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I shared this practice during a recent keynote and a young woman came up to me afterward to say that she&#39;d heard me talk about it before.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“At that time, I was feeling so burned out,” she told me. “I wasn&#39;t sure it would make a difference, but I decided to give this daily check-in a try. I was surprised at how much it helped me feel better. Instead of being consumed by my feelings of stress or overwhelm, I become aware of them and now feel more in control.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Research supports what she experienced: People who practice emotional awareness are &lt;a href=&quot;https://bmcpsychology.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40359-021-00593-8&quot;>;more likely to report greater well-being&lt;/a>;. Becoming aware of your difficult feelings reduces the intensity with which you experience them and gives you an opportunity to do something to support yourself to feel a little better.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Take a few short, quality breaks during the day. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The key word here is “quality.” This means doing something that helps you disconnect from work, refuel, and recharge. Scrolling social media or reading the news is not a quality break, and neither is catching up on your to-do list.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The human brain needs to take a break every 90 to 120 minutes to function at its best and avoid accumulated stress and overwhelm. Microsoft recently conducted a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/brain-research&quot;>;large-scale study&lt;/a>; and found that &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/to-build-a-top-performing-team-ask-for-85-effort&quot;>;taking five- to 10-minute breaks between meetings&lt;/a>; significantly reduced accumulated stress and overwhelm and improved focus.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My favorite way to disconnect from work during the day is to take a short walk outside. As mountains of research show, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27100368/&quot;>;it boosts your mood&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/dont-underestimate-the-power-of-a-walk&quot;>;improves focus and motivation&lt;/a>;, and has lots of health benefits if you do it consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice acceptance to focus on what you can control. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Acceptance involves two steps: First, acknowledge the situation with clarity, focusing on the facts you know to be true. Second, identify one step you could take to move forward with less stress and struggle.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We tend to underestimate how much ruminating on stressful situations drains our energy. Practicing these two steps of acceptance when you find yourself caught in a loop of negative thoughts helps to focus your attention on what you can control and take a productive action, however small. This &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/small-wins-and-feeling-good&quot;>;small win&lt;/a>; gives your brain a sense of progress, which feels good and often motivates you to find other useful steps you can take.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the women who participated in my leadership program where we learned the skill of acceptance told me recently that it&#39;s been her main go-to skill during the ongoing challenges and uncertainty at work. “Whenever I become overwhelmed with stress about work situations, the economy, or things with my team, I pause, take a breath, and ask myself what step I could take to move forward given how things are and what is in my control. Asking this question as a team has also been helpful for our team focus and stress level,” she told me.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Prioritize micro-moments of connection with colleagues.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Make it a point to greet your colleagues with genuine enthusiasm when you&#39;re on a call or when you see them for the first time during the day. In virtual meetings, where there is a tendency to just dive into the agenda, begin by asking everyone to share something good from their week so far. Be intentional about reaching out to a colleague to just check in, without focusing your conversation on work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re all starved for human connection after the years of pandemic isolation and it&#39;s negatively impacting our well-being. As human beings, we&#39;re wired to connect, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6125010/&quot;>;studies&lt;/a>; show that social support and feeling connected improve mental health and reduce stress and anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, take the initiative and create a daily moment of connection with a colleague. It doesn&#39;t take a lot of effort or time, but you&#39;ll feel uplifted and help the other person feel less alone.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice gratitude to counter your brain&#39;s negativity bias. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;If you don&#39;t have one, create a daily gratitude practice, which can be as simple as writing down three things you appreciate every morning or in the evening.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Developing a grateful mindset is always beneficial for your well-being, but even more so during these uncertain times. Uncertainty is extremely stressful and energy-draining — it&#39;s the hardest thing for the human brain to handle. When your brain encounters uncertainty, it focuses on finding possible danger and enters the &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/09/our-brains-were-not-built-for-this-much-uncertainty&quot;>;“fight or flight state”&lt;/a>; so it can protect you. This can lead to increased anxiety and rumination about negative outcomes and worst-case scenarios.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By practicing gratitude, you ask your brain to widen its lens and focus its attention on things that are positive, meaningful, or comforting. The goal isn&#39;t to deny the difficulties you might be facing, but to remind yourself that they are not the entirety of your life. This fuels your emotional energy and helps improve your resilience, which is your ability to positively adapt amidst challenges.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Practice active rest outside of work. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Finally, it&#39;s important to spend time outside of work doing things you love. Spend time on your favorite hobby. Dedicate time to reading or gardening. Try a new creative activity, like watercolor or writing. The key is to do something that actively fuels your energy and feeds parts of you other than just your work self. (In contrast, zoning out in front of Netflix for hours is not active rest, although watching an episode of your favorite show from time to time is a great option.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I picked up painting after my own burnout, and having something that allows me to completely disconnect from work and feed the creative/artist part of myself has been a huge gift for my well-being. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/43532701_On_the_Role_of_Passion_for_Work_in_Burnout_A_Process_Model&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>; of burnout in nurses supports what I&#39;ve found to be true in my experience: Nurses who spent time actively resting when they weren&#39;t working, either by engaging in hobbies or spending time with friends or family, were less likely to burn out than nurses who weren&#39;t intentional about disconnecting from work after their shift was finished.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As the cliche goes: “You are not your job.” Even, and perhaps especially, if you&#39;re passionate about your work, you need to be intentional about doing things you enjoy outside of work. If your productivity-obsessed brain objects, remind yourself that active rest is an investment in your ability to bring your full capacity to your work for a long period of time.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Managers Can Dismantle &ldquo;Benevolent Marginalization&rdquo;]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_07_4689448-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jayme Burrows/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While there is a growing recognition of the significance of diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, many firms fail to break down the subtle barriers obstructing progress because they engage in patronizing behavior that the authors call &amp;#8220;benevolent marginalization.&amp;#8221; Drawing on insights from a decade of research on benevolent discrimination experienced by women and individuals with disabilities in the workplace, the authors propose three key strategies to help discard such protectionism while forging a path toward genuine inclusion: shifting the focus from help to empowerment, engaging allies in non-managerial roles, and creating supportive spaces by handing over responsibilities for shaping their own professional lives to marginalized individuals.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-managers-can-dismantle-benevolent-marginalization?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;The old proverb about teaching people to fish so they can eat for a lifetime, rather than gifting a fish that lasts just a day, also applies to how organizations can empower, rather than merely help, disadvantaged groups.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;There has been a remarkable surge in diversity initiatives at companies, fueled by belief in the benefits of a diverse workforce and the collective fight against discrimination. As organizations strive to build inclusive workplaces, they often try to tackle overt discrimination and negative stereotypes against disadvantaged groups.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Yet these well-intentioned efforts often include a key oversight: Many DEI initiatives are founded on the flawed assumption that disadvantaged groups are helpless without assistance from those in power. Such protectionist beliefs give rise to the frequently overlooked yet deeply concerning phenomenon of benevolent marginalization, whereby good intentions can lead to harm.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Benevolent marginalization occurs when a dominant group paternalistically controls a weaker or marginalized group while portraying their actions as supportive and in solidarity with that group. Behind the façade of well-intentioned actions aimed at uplifting marginalized groups, a subtle power imbalance persists. Managers may even expect gratitude for their affectionate and helpful efforts, while those who are marginalized find themselves pressured into accepting or internalizing the subordinating order as the norm and even expressing gratitude in return. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Our analysis draws upon over a decade of extensive research conducted in diverse contexts. We utilized interviews, archival documents, and observations of individuals navigating subtle forms of marginalization. We also examined the pivotal role of internal activists and managers who actively support and become allies to overcome benevolent marginalization&lt;i>;.&lt;/i>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Subtle Discrimination Perpetuates Gender Inequality&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Benevolent marginalization manifests as subtle discrimination that impacts various groups and makes them unlikely to intervene or dissent, thereby hindering their advancement and perpetuating organizational inequality.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Imagine the scenario of &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/06/dismantling-benevolent-sexism&quot;>;benevolent sexism&lt;/a>;. Despite the decline of overtly sexist attitudes, women still face subtle forms of discrimination that may contribute to their underrepresentation in executive positions. Women are often stereotyped as the “weaker sex” needing chivalrous protection, but this seemingly favorable treatment conceals male dominance and can have negative consequences. When women are shielded from challenging assignments at work, for example, it inadvertently encourages stereotypes and fosters self-doubt, ultimately hampering their professional performance.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/AMBPP.2021.10710abstract&quot;>;three-year study&lt;/a>; examining benevolent sexism, we took a closer look at women-only networking initiatives. These initiatives, touted as essential components of diversity guidelines within organizations, are often devised by male managers to assist women. However, women frequently perceive them as a superficial attempt or mere tokenism aimed at fulfilling diversity quotas and creating a facade of inclusivity. Many such initiatives place the burden of overcoming gender disparities on women, often treating them as a homogenous group while failing to address the underlying systemic bias that fuels gender inequality. Paradoxically, in our study, these women frequently found themselves obligated to participate in such initiatives, only to experience feelings of patronization and occasional polite dismissal. They also encountered instances of “mansplaining,” where men condescendingly or patronizingly explain the intricacies of networking, assuming women to have lesser or inferior knowledge of the subject. These experiences can result in women feeling disillusioned and disengaged from such initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Yet, a remarkable transformation can occur when women take charge of these initiatives and tailor them to meet their individual needs. This can be achieved through collaborating with women across different levels of seniority to foster an inclusive networking environment that promotes diverse voices, offers mentorship and sponsorship opportunities, and creates spaces where women can openly and genuinely engage.&lt;i>; &lt;/i>;Our research suggests that women need to adopt a strategic, long-term perspective in their networking endeavors, prioritize follow-ups to build strong relationships, delineate tangible goals for professional advancement, and engage in ongoing evaluation and improvement of these initiatives. As a result, women can gain a sense of empowerment and find their voices to collectively combat gender inequality head-on.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;“Ableist Assumptions” Hinder Efforts to Help Workers with Disabilities&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Let us explore another compelling example: benevolent ableism, which refers to well-intentioned but problematic behaviors such as pity, protectiveness, and patronization toward employees with disabilities. Managers, guided by ableist assumptions, often impose their own definitions of disability, attempting to create “inclusive” environments that reinforce ableist norms in organizations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2020.1689&quot;>;longitudinal study&lt;/a>; of sheltered workshops, published in the Academy of Management Journal, disabled workers report that many inclusion initiatives at work are based on power imbalances rooted in pity. Sheltered workshops provide employment to disabled workers in segregated facilities with limited exposure to the broader public under the guise of care and protection. We show that well-intentioned managers often devise inclusion initiatives based on simplified assumptions that all workers with disabilities share identical needs of help and assistance — a paternalistic or even infantilizing approach that perpetuates inequality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, a transformational moment may occur when these managers confront their own fallibility, let go of their defensive positions, abandon their patronizing behaviors, and provide opportunities to people with disabilities to bring out their untapped potential. This requires a change in communication from telling to listening and a change in behavior to promote inclusive practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One example of a patronizing initiative in this context involved assigning jobs that could be carried out within the confines of the sheltered workshop, limiting public engagement. These jobs encompassed metal processing, industrial assembly, packaging, and shipping. In contrast, a successful inclusive practice involved establishing a farmer&#39;s market in consultation with these workers and their representatives. Engaging directly with people from outside the sheltered workshop environment while selling farm produce gave these workers newfound self-belief, autonomy, and a sense of empowerment. This experience was a moment of epiphany that boosted workers&#39; confidence in their abilities to perform tasks they had never envisioned or been given the responsibility to perform. Managers also realized that they had unwittingly stifled the potential of some of these workers while trying to be protective and creating a secluded environment. This shift marked a profound turning point as managers transitioned from guardians to true allies of workers with disabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Three Key Strategies to Tackle Benevolent Marginalization at Work&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In creating inclusive workplaces, managers need to invest time and resources in understanding and dismantling benevolent marginalization to ensure that equality in organizations becomes more than just a buzzword.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After studying this phenomenon across diverse settings, we present three key insights that serve as tools for managers aiming to go beyond good intentions:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Shift your perspective from help to empowerment.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In the pursuit of creating inclusive workplaces, the traditional approach of providing help can unintentionally reinforce unequal power dynamics. Managers must view disadvantaged individuals as equal colleagues. However, this is often easier said than done. Our findings reveal that practitioners may resist change, seeking to preserve deeply entrenched structures and the benefits they bring.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Instead, managers need to call out and confront such resistance to pave the way to a profound shift from protectionism toward self-determination and empowerment. This requires introspection that can prompt managers to scrutinize and challenge their own paternalistic assumptions and biases. Managers must recognize and address the often-hidden power dynamics at play when interacting with people with whom they have a significant power differential. Building trust, actively listening, and gaining awareness of the emotions behind their behaviors are crucial steps. Seeking candid feedback from colleagues, mentors, or coaches about one&#39;s paternalistic behaviors is vital for self-reflection, sensitization, and remediation. Lastly, it is important to display empathy toward marginalized perspectives, even when they differ from one&#39;s own, and refrain from making decisions on their behalf, regardless of good intentions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Harness allies in non-managerial roles.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Effectively addressing benevolent marginalization across an organization means tailoring initiatives that align with the unique interests of disadvantaged individuals. However, doing so requires the help of others beyond managers or designated diversity officers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is critical to leverage the power of intermediaries, such as support staff, close&amp;nbsp;colleagues, and friends, who are closer to the experiences and challenges faced by their marginalized peers. Identifying and designating these allies involves seeking out individuals who&amp;nbsp;are known to have actively supported marginalized communities. One way to select these allies is by letting marginalized groups participate in anonymous voting. This allows them to choose and elect individuals they trust and believe in as champions of inclusion based on their proven dedication and commitment. For example, at the sheltered workshop, workers with disabilities were given the opportunity to vote for their allies, who subsequently collaborated with management to improve inclusion initiatives. This approach is also seen in academia, where committees are frequently selected through voting to represent the interests of junior or disadvantaged faculty members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Organizations also need to recognize and reward allies who actively contribute to creating an inclusive environment. Managers can implement allyship programs or resource groups that offer tailored training and toolkits for allies, equipping them with the necessary skills to support marginalized peers. This comprehensive guidance should address issues such as identifying invisible bias, uncovering instances of benevolent marginalization, and actively advocating for and amplifying the voices of marginalized peers in their day-to-day interactions and decision-making processes. More generally, organizations can establish confidential feedback channels or suggestion boxes where support staff and colleagues can provide input on potential improvements to policies and practices to avoid paternalistic behaviors. By regularly reviewing and taking action based on this feedback, organizations demonstrate their commitment to “walk the talk” on inclusivity.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Create supportive spaces by handing over responsibilities to disadvantaged individuals.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Overcoming benevolent marginalization requires the creation of both formal and informal supportive or “safe” spaces in the workplace where marginalized groups can freely express themselves and expose behaviors they perceive as paternalistic or patronizing. However, it is not enough to unite marginalized employees in, say, an employee resource group (ERG) and expect them to form an empowering collective without further support. True inclusion demands a recognition of the diverse experiences and unique needs of&amp;nbsp;everyone within these spaces, and these individuals must have the choice to shape these spaces themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations must relinquish control and hand over the reins to disadvantaged individuals to shape their own professional lives. By doing so, organizations can become confidence-building, encouraging, and inspiring environments to challenge the status quo and overcome existing paternalistic norms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;Building effective diversity programs can be a challenging endeavor, especially when hidden barriers hinder progress despite the best intentions. While by no means exhaustive, these three evidence-based strategies offer a solid starting point for advancing true inclusion. Shifting perspectives from help to empowerment, identifying hidden allies, and handing over responsibilities to create supportive spaces are crucial steps toward giving a platform to those who have long felt silenced or not listened to and creating a workplace where everyone feels heard and valued.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Let the Urgency of Your Customers&rsquo; Needs Guide Your Sales Strategy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_AdriaVolta.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Adrià Voltà&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When companies are creating profiles of possible target customers, there is a dimension they often overlook: the urgency of the need for the offering. This article provides a process for segmenting prospective customers in this fashion and creating a sales strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/let-the-urgency-of-your-customers-needs-guide-your-sales-strategy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Many business leaders believe that they fully understand their best target customers. They&#39;ve developed clear profiles (aka personas) that are richly detailed with well-researched parameters, such as standard characteristics (eg, age, education level, years at the company, role) or firmographic (eg, annual revenues, number of employees, industry, geography, years in business). While such characteristics are important, they ignore another crucial characteristic: urgency of need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A company that offers a software-as-a-service billing solution for small and mid-sized private dental practices may focus on classic demographics, such as the size of the practice (number of employees or number of dentists), the age of the practice (since older practices may more likely have outdated systems), or the amount of insurance billing the practice does each year.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These variables are useful in helping to produce a list of prospects, but they don&#39;t determine which of these dental practices the sales team should call on first. If, however, the company added data that reflects which of these practices&#39; needs is most urgent — say, those that have advertised for billing and claims administration help more than twice in the past year (suggesting that they are struggling to keep up with billing) — salespeople would be able to prioritize their attention on these prospects.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Four Segments&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This needs-based approach entails segmenting potential customers into four segments:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Urgent&lt;/strong>;. The customer recognizes that it has an immediate need. &lt;em>;(We just had another billing person quit!)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Non-urgent.&lt;/strong>; The customer recognizes the need, but it isn&#39;t a high priority at this time. &lt;em>;(We realize that our billing needs are changing and our current system will need to be revamped. We plan to start looking into this in the next year.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Currently met&lt;/strong>;. The customer believes it already has an adequate solution to address the need at this time but recognizes it may not be a long-term solution. &lt;em>;(We have an older billing system in place that still does the trick for now.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;None&lt;/strong>;. The customer simply has no need nor expects such need anytime soon. &lt;em>;(Our small practice has a limited number of patients who pay out of pocket. Since all payments are made at the time of service, we simply don&#39;t need a complex new billing system.)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;This focus on the urgency of target customers&#39; needs may sound like common sense, but we have found in our work with B2B companies — from mid-sized firms to Fortune 50 giants in an array of industries such as financial services, enterprise information technology, utilities, industrial solutions, and health care technology — that they often fail to consider this dimension. Here is a process a firm can employ to apply this approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Identify new customers.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To identify prospects outside of your existing customer base, you can use available information. One is a source we mentioned: help-wanted ads that reflect a particular need.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there are plenty of others. For instance, if a company sells inventory management solutions, a source of valuable data might be manufacturing industry merger-and-acquisition data, which could reveal companies with an urgent need to change or merge systems such as those for managing inventories. If a company sells quality-management solutions, a source of valuable data could be companies that are getting hammered for poor quality on social media.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gather the necessary information.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Identifying your customers&#39; true urgency of needs requires looking beyond your typical demographic and firmographic profiling. This starts with an outreach initiative to talk to customers and prospects. The purpose is to ask questions to identify new target customer parameters that may be impacting the customer&#39;s urgency of needs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Frustrations. &lt;/strong>;How urgent is the need to resolve these frustrations? Which frustration would best accelerate success if resolved?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Goals. &lt;/strong>;Are your goals clear, consistent, reasonable, and measurable? Have your goals shifted recently?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Roadblocks. &lt;/strong>;What keeps you from reaching your goals? (ie, What keeps you up at night?) What is the magnitude of the impact of these roadblocks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Environmental and situational factors. &lt;/strong>;Are you experiencing any industry consolidation, organizational or executive management changes or instability, competitive changes, regulatory changes, and so on? What is the magnitude of the impact of these factors?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Technology factors. &lt;/strong>;Are there new or changing technologies that will impact your ability to achieve your goals? Are you at risk due to technology end-of-life issues or incompatibility?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assess your firm&#39;s ability to serve lower-level segments.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once a company has performed its needs-based segmentation effort, it should seek to answer the following questions about each of the four levels. The findings will dictate the sales and marketing strategy, level of investment and resource allocations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 1. Urgent need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;How quickly can we meet their need? How can we best serve them? Is the market opportunity large enough to focus only on these prospective customers? Given the customer&#39;s urgency, how do we price our products to optimize margins without damaging relationships by appearing exploitive?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 2. Non-urgent need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Can we convince them that their need is more urgent than they currently believe? How do we effectively stay in touch with them so we remain top of mind when they perceive that their need has become urgent?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 3. Need currently met&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Should we walk away from these prospects? If so, when and how do we touch base with them to see if their needs have changed? Or is there an opportunity to continue to work to convince them that their need is either more significant than they realize or could be much better addressed? If so, what&#39;s the best approach to get them to reconsider their current situation and recognize their true need and its urgency?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Level 4. No need&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Should we completely remove these contacts as any potential prospect? Is there some other need we may be able to address for them — perhaps with another product? Should we be in contact on a planned basis to see if their situation has changed? How do we best do that?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The ideal customers are those who clearly understand and recognize they have an urgent need for your offering. However, if that opportunity is not enough to meet the company&#39;s sales volume target, it may be necessary to extend efforts beyond Level 1. Gaining the attention of these additional target customers, challenging their perceptions of their needs, and educating them on how your offering could benefit them will require resources. Consequently, a critical assessment is required to determine whether the opportunity outweighs the investment necessary to address customers in these other levels.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Test your new targets.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Before committing to a complete revamp of how your salespeople are prioritizing opportunities, select one or two experienced salespeople to help you test your new target customer parameters. Identify a few prospects that align to your revamped target profiles, and see how the selected salespeople are able to penetrate them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Revamp your sales messaging and training.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Include prospective customers&#39; level of need in your sales messaging — the language that the sales team uses in its interactions with customers. Revamp your sales tools (materials such as brochures, technical papers, and customer testimonials used in the selling process) to include the urgency of need. And teach salespeople how to read and react to the prospective customer&#39;s level of need and adapt their language appropriately.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By adding urgency of need to target customers&#39; profiles, companies can do more than differentiate their offerings more effectively. They can also identify new growth opportunities and successfully pivot away from slowing or tightening markets. They can accelerate the sales of new products. Last but not least, they can turn underachieving sales teams into strong performers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Help Your Team Grow, Give Them Space to Struggle]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/to-help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_1198521996.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Catherine Falls Commercial/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;When you see an employee struggling with a task you could do easily, it&amp;#8217;s only natural to want to step in and help. But from the other side, this can feel more like micromanagement than support. And when leaders over-function by keeping too much work for themselves, they allow those around them to under-function. We all know how important it is to delegate &amp;#8212; both to help employees grow and to create a more collaborative, empowered, productive team. How can you get better at this key leadership skill?&amp;#160; First, shift from a doer to a leader mindset. Second, embrace the discomfort of the learning process. Third, identify low-stakes tasks that are less risky to delegate. Finally, be curious and facilitative instead of prescriptive.&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-help-your-team-grow-give-them-space-to-struggle?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“How are you justifying the sales and expenses estimates?” the CEO asked. My face glowed red as I stuttered. My heart rate skyrocketed and my throat tightened. I looked at my boss, Valerie. She made eye contact, held a soft gaze, and said nothing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;She could have eased some of the heat directed my way by chiming in and saving me, but she didn&#39;t. That&#39;s because I had asked Valerie for an opportunity to present to our organization&#39;s leadership team. Prior to the meeting, she&#39;d informed the head of our banking division and the CEO that I was taking on this stretch assignment and that she would be an observer. So, instead of taking over from me when I was facing tough questions, she let me figure my own way out of the discomfort.&lt;/span>; I did muddle through it, albeit not as well as I would have liked, but in a way that left me better prepared for my next meeting with him.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;I remember Valerie as a good boss because she often gave me developmental opportunities like these. The stakes were usually low like that small, internal meeting, where everyone knew I was still green and would be supportive. Valerie was present but in the background, allowing me to succeed or stumble but learn from the experience either way. Afterward, she never gave me long lists of suggestions on how to improve. Instead, she asked great questions that prompted me to think about what I could have done differently.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;In theory, most leaders know how important it is to delegate challenging tasks to employees both to help them grow and create a collaborative, empowered, productive team. But, faced with real workplace demands, it can be tough to put this into practice. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many of my clients say things like “I&#39;m the only one who can do the job” or “If this project doesn&#39;t go smoothly, the whole team will suffer.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Empathy can &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/connect-with-empathy-but-lead-with-compassion&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;get in the way&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, too. When you see an employee struggling, it&#39;s only natural to want to step in and help. But from the other side, this can feel more like micromanagement than support. And when leaders over-function by keeping too many tasks, they allow their teams to under-function.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here are some strategies you can use to make delegation easier.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Shift from doer to leader mindset&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;In my corporate job, we promoted the best doers into leaders. This came with an assumption that they would magically shift from being good at and motivated by performance excellence and rewards to excelling at and caring deeply about developing others&#39; potential. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The mindset shift may be the hardest part of all. So, how can you facilitate this in yourself?&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Notice your payoff from &lt;em>;doing&lt;/em>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The thrill of achievement provides a quick &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.noesislearning.com/2019/11/19/the-neuroscience-of-achievement/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;dopamine hit&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. But that&#39;s something you need to resist to get to the greater fulfillment of having helped others improve.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Claim your leadership identity by getting clear on values. Ask yourself: What three words do I want people to use to describe my leadership style? For example: Do I want to lead with control, urgency, and expertise? Or, with patience, curiosity, and empowerment?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Be intentional about responding, not reacting. In the moments where you are triggered to step in, ask yourself:&amp;nbsp; Would that be aligned with my values and who I want to become as a leader?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Embrace the discomfort of the learning process&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many leaders tell me that, after witnessing an employee falter, taking back the work felt like the most supportive thing to do. I&#39;ve felt this tension too. But Valerie taught me the power of holding space for struggle. Yes, this creates discomfort for both leader and employee because it&#39;s a new way of working for everyone. However, as &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/389807/top-things-employees-next-job.aspx&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Gallup reminds us&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, one of the keys to engagement at work is the opportunity for stimulating challenges. And when you push through the struggle, the result is growth for all parties.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;How can you embrace, rather than resist, the discomfort of learning?&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Name your emotions, which &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/3-ways-to-better-understand-your-emotions&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;according to&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; psychologist Susan David, offers clarity and resiliency and can empower you to respond in an intentional way, aligned with your values.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Normalize being uncomfortable. &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.edutopia.org/article/neuroscience-behind-productive-struggle/&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Neuroscientists know&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; that these are the periods in which learning happens and perseverance is developed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Reframe the situation. One potential reframe is: “I was allowed to struggle and that&#39;s where I gained confidence in my skills. So I&#39;m going to give my employee the same gift of time to solve the problem on their own.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Distinguish between high- and low-stakes tasks&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Leaders often tell me they remain stuck as doers because employees make too many high-impact mistakes that require intervention. But this usually happens when the bosses themselves hold on to all the work for far too long and are then forced to delegate at the wrong moment. The key is to instead hand off tasks when the stakes are low and missteps tolerated, or even expected..&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;What makes an environment low-stakes? Failure will support learning more than it would hurt reputation. Mistakes will not impact team or company success. The environment is safe for stops and do-overs. The people involved have support and compassion for less experienced colleagues on learning curves.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;To know which tasks are ripe for delegation, consider ones that now feel easy or rote to you but would be good development opportunities for those on your team? Also think about work that drains your energy and doesn&#39;t align with your skills, talents, and strengths but might excite and feel like a perfect fit for others.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For example, if your employee&#39;s goal is to develop better presentation skills, try a low-stakes activity like asking them to lead the next staff meeting before a high-stakes one like conducting a client meeting. Or, if they want to get better at influencing others, challenge them to get buy-in from a small team on using a new tool or work process before asking them to persuade your whole division to implement it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Be curious and facilitative&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Early in my corporate career as a trainer, people told me that I was visibly nervous during sessions I was leading. I explained to my boss that I was worried about not having answers to participants&#39; questions. Her response: “What if your role isn&#39;t to have all the answers but to facilitate the expertise in the room?” This changed my perspective.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Like trainers, leaders can&#39;t be expected to have all the answers. But they do need to have patience and curiosity and ask insightful questions to facilitate learning. For example: What has your current approach been? Can you apply past experience to this problem? What is this situation teaching you?&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Finally, practice compassion and grace. This doesn&#39;t mean tolerating poor effort or careless mistakes. Instead, it means offering understanding and accommodation in the face of someone not doing something exactly how you would do it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Valerie&#39;s approach that day with our CEO didn&#39;t feel good at the time. But had she intervened, I wouldn&#39;t have learned how to respond to unexpected questions or later reflected on how to better prepare for executive presentations. If she&#39;d followed up with advice, I wouldn&#39;t have discovered my own authentic ways of improving. To this day, I credit her with helping me to develop the ability to present calmly in high-stakes situations. She&#39;s also the reason I have&amp;nbsp;the courage to delegate to colleagues and team members even if it means watching them struggle. That&#39;s the only way that all of us — leaders and employees — grow. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Train Generative AI Using Your Company&rsquo;s Data]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_06_1488880093.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anton Vierietin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Leveraging a company&amp;#8217;s propriety knowledge is critical to its ability to compete and innovate, especially in today&amp;#8217;s volatile environment. Organizational innovation is fueled through effective and agile creation, management, application, recombination, and deployment of knowledge assets and know-how. However, knowledge within organizations is typically generated and captured across various sources and forms, including individual minds, processes, policies, reports, operational transactions, discussion boards, and online chats and meetings. As such, a company&amp;#8217;s comprehensive knowledge is often unaccounted for and difficult to organize and deploy where needed in an effective or efficient way.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to-train-generative-ai-using-your-companys-data?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Many companies are experimenting with ChatGPT and other large language or image models. They have generally found them to be astounding in terms of their ability to express complex ideas in articulate language. However, most users realize that these systems are primarily trained on internet-based information and can&#39;t respond to prompts or questions regarding proprietary content or knowledge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leveraging a company&#39;s propriety knowledge is critical to its ability to compete and innovate, especially in today&#39;s volatile environment. Organizational Innovation is fueled through effective and agile creation, management, application, recombination, and deployment of knowledge assets and know-how. However, knowledge within organizations is typically generated and captured across various sources and forms, including individual minds, processes, policies, reports, operational transactions, discussion boards, and online chats and meetings. As such, a company&#39;s comprehensive knowledge is often unaccounted for and difficult to organize and deploy where needed in an effective or efficient way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Emerging technologies in the form of large language and image generative AI models offer new opportunities for knowledge management, thereby enhancing company performance, learning, and innovation capabilities. For example, in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w31161&quot;>;study&lt;/a>; conducted in a Fortune 500 provider of business process software, a generative AI-based system for customer support led to increased productivity of customer support agents and improved retention, while leading to higher positive feedback on the part of customers. The system also expedited the learning and skill development of novice agents.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Like that company, a growing number of organizations are attempting to leverage the language processing skills and general reasoning abilities of large language models (LLMs) to capture and provide broad internal (or customer) access to their own intellectual capital. They are using it for such purposes as informing their customer-facing employees on company policy and product/service recommendations, solving customer service problems, or capturing employees&#39; knowledge before they depart the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These objectives were also present during the heyday of the “knowledge management” movement in the 1990s and early 2000s, but most companies found the technology of the time inadequate for the task. Today, however, generative AI is rekindling the possibility of capturing and disseminating important knowledge throughout an organization and beyond its walls. As one manager using generative AI for this purpose put it, “I feel like a jetpack just came into my life.” Despite current advances, some of the same factors that made knowledge management difficult in the past are still present.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Technology for Generative AI-Based Knowledge Management&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The technology to incorporate an organization&#39;s specific domain knowledge into an LLM is evolving rapidly. At the moment there are three primary approaches to incorporating proprietary content into a generative model.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Training an LLM from Scratch&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;One approach is to create and train one&#39;s own domain-specific model from scratch. That&#39;s not a common approach, since it requires a massive amount of high-quality data to train a large language model, and most companies simply don&#39;t have it. It also requires access to considerable computing power and well-trained data science talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One company that has employed this approach is Bloomberg, which recently announced that it had created BloombergGPT for finance-specific content and a natural-language interface with its data terminal. Bloomberg has over 40 years&#39; worth of financial data, news, and documents, which it combined with a large volume of text from financial filings and internet data. In total, Bloomberg&#39;s data scientists employed 700 tokens, or about 350 billion words, 50 billion parameters, and 1.3 million hours of graphics processing unit time. Few companies have those resources available.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Fine-Tuning an Existing LLM&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A second approach is to “fine-tune” train an existing LLM to add specific domain content to a system that is already trained on general knowledge and language-based interaction. This approach involves adjusting some parameters of a base model, and typically requires substantially less data — usually only hundreds or thousands of documents, rather than millions or billions — and less computing time than creating a new model from scratch.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Google, for example, used fine-tune training on its &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/healthcare-life-sciences/sharing-google-med-palm-2-medical-large-language-model&quot;>;Med-PaLM2&lt;/a>; (second version) model for medical knowledge. The research project started with Google&#39;s general PaLM2 LLM and retrained it on carefully curated medical knowledge from a variety of public medical datasets. The model was able to answer 85% of US medical licensing exam questions — almost 20% better than the first version of the system. Despite this rapid progress, when tested on such criteria as scientific factuality, precision, medical consensus, reasoning, bias and harm, and evaluated by human experts from multiple countries, the development team felt that the system still needed substantial improvement before being adopted for clinical practice.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The fine-tuning approach has some constraints, however. Although requiring much less computing power and time than training an LLM, it can still be expensive to train, which was not a problem for Google but would be for many other companies. It requires considerable data science expertise; the &lt;a href=&quot;chrome-extension://bdfcnmeidppjeaggnmidamkiddifkdib/viewer.html?file=https://arxiv.org/pdf/2305.09617.pdf&quot;>;scientific paper&lt;/a>; for the Google project, for example, had 31 co-authors. Some data scientists argue that it is best suited not to adding new content, but rather to adding new content formats and styles (such as chat or writing like William Shakespeare). Additionally, some LLM vendors (for example, OpenAI) do not allow fine-tuning on their latest LLMs, such as GPT-4.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Prompt-tuning an Existing LLM&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Perhaps the most common approach to customizing the content of an LLM for non-cloud vendor companies is to tune it through prompts. With this approach, the original model is kept frozen, and is modified through prompts in the context window that contain domain-specific knowledge. After prompt tuning, the model can answer questions related to that knowledge. This approach is the most computationally efficient of the three, and it does not require a vast amount of data to be trained on a new content domain.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Morgan Stanley, for example, used prompt tuning to train OpenAI&#39;s GPT-4 model using a carefully curated set of 100,000 documents with important investing, general business, and investment process knowledge. The goal was to provide the company&#39;s financial advisors with accurate and easily accessible knowledge on key issues they encounter in their roles advising clients. The prompt-trained system is operated in a private cloud that is only accessible to Morgan Stanley employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While this is perhaps the easiest of the three approaches for an organization to adopt, it is not without technical challenges. When using unstructured data like text as input to an LLM, the data is likely to be too large with too many important attributes to enter it directly in the context window for the LLM. The alternative is to create vector embeddings — arrays of numeric values produced from the text by another pre-trained machine learning model (Morgan Stanley uses one from OpenAI called Ada). The vector embeddings are a more compact representation of this data which preserves contextual relationships in the text. When a user enters a prompt into the system, a similarity algorithm determines which vectors should be submitted to the GPT-4 model. Although several vendors are offering tools to make this process of prompt tuning easier, it is still complex enough that most companies adopting the approach would need to have substantial data science talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, this approach does not need to be very time-consuming or expensive if the needed content is already present. The investment research company Morningstar, for example, used prompt tuning and vector embeddings for its Mo research tool built on generative AI. It incorporates more than 10,000 pieces of Morningstar research. After only a month or so of work on its system, Morningstar opened Mo usage to their financial advisors and independent investor customers. It even attached Mo to a digital avatar that could speak out its answers. This technical approach is not expensive; in its first month in use, Mo answered 25,000 questions at an average cost of $.002 per question for a total cost of $3,000.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Content Curation and Governance&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As with traditional knowledge management in which documents were loaded into discussion databases like Microsoft Sharepoint, with generative AI, content needs to be high-quality before customizing LLMs in any fashion. In some cases, as with the Google Med-PaLM2 system, there are widely available databases of medical knowledge that have already been curated. Otherwise, a company needs to rely on human curation to ensure that knowledge content is accurate, timely, and not duplicated. Morgan Stanley, for example, has a group of 20 or so knowledge managers in the Philippines who are constantly scoring documents along multiple criteria; these determine the suitability for incorporation into the GPT-4 system. Most companies that do not have well-curated content will find it challenging to do so for just this purpose.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Morgan Stanley has also found that it is much easier to maintain high quality knowledge if content authors are aware of how to create effective documents. They are required to take two courses, one on the document management tool, and a second on how to write and tag these documents. This is a component of the company&#39;s approach to content governance approach — a systematic method for capturing and managing important digital content.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At Morningstar, content creators are being taught what type of content works well with the Mo system and what does not. They submit their content into a content management system and it goes directly into the vector database that supplies the OpenAI model.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Quality Assurance and Evaluation&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;An important aspect of managing generative AI content is ensuring quality. Generative AI is widely known to “hallucinate” on occasion, confidently stating facts that are incorrect or nonexistent. Errors of this type can be problematic for businesses but could be deadly in healthcare applications. The good news is that companies who have tuned their LLMs on domain-specific information have found that hallucinations are less of a problem than out-of-the-box LLMs, at least if there are no extended dialogues or non-business prompts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies adopting these approaches to generative AI knowledge management should develop an evaluation strategy. For example, for BloombergGPT, which is intended for answering financial and investing questions, the system was evaluated on public dataset financial tasks, named entity recognition, sentiment analysis ability, and a set of reasoning and general natural language processing tasks. The Google Med-PaLM2 system, eventually oriented to answering patient and physician medical questions, had a much more extensive evaluation strategy, reflecting the criticality of accuracy and safety in the medical domain.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Life or death isn&#39;t an issue at Morgan Stanley, but producing highly accurate responses to financial and investing questions is important to the firm, its clients, and its regulators. The answers provided by the system were carefully evaluated by human reviewers before it was released to any users. Then it was piloted for several months by 300 financial advisors. As its primary approach to ongoing evaluation, Morgan Stanley has a set of 400 “golden questions” to which the correct answers are known. Every time any change is made to the system, employees test it with the golden questions to see if there has been any “regression,” or less accurate answers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Legal and Governance Issues &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Legal and governance issues associated with LLM deployments are complex and evolving, leading to risk factors involving intellectual property, data privacy and security, bias and ethics, and false/inaccurate output. Currently, the legal status of LLM outputs is still unclear. Since LLMs don&#39;t produce exact replicas of any of the text used to train the model, many legal observers feel that “fair use” provisions of copyright law will apply to them, although this hasn&#39;t been tested in the courts (and not all countries have such provisions in their copyright laws). In any case, it is a good idea for any company making extensive use of generative AI for managing knowledge (or most other purposes for that matter) to have legal representatives involved in the creation and governance process for tuned LLMs. At Morningstar, for example, the company&#39;s attorneys helped create a series of “pre-prompts” that tell the generative AI system what types of questions it should answer and those it should politely avoid.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;User prompts into publicly-available LLMs are used to train future versions of the system, so some companies (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-ai-like-chatgpt-for-staff-after-misuse-of-chatbot.html&quot;>;Samsung&lt;/a>;, for example) have feared propagation of confidential and private information and banned LLM use by employees. However, most companies&#39; efforts to tune LLMs with domain-specific content are performed on private instances of the models that are not accessible to public users, so this should not be a problem. In addition, some generative AI systems such as ChatGPT allow users to turn off the collection of chat histories, which can address confidentiality issues even on public systems.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In order to address confidentiality and privacy concerns, some vendors are providing advanced and improved safety and security features for LLMs including erasing user prompts, restricting certain topics, and preventing source code and propriety data inputs into publicly accessible LLMs. Furthermore, vendors of enterprise software systems are incorporating a “Trust Layer” in their products and services. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/salesforce-aims-to-plug-ai-trust-gap-with-new-tech-tools-19e11750?mod=djemCIO&quot;>;Salesforce&lt;/a>;, for example, incorporated its Einstein GPT feature into its AI Cloud suite to address the “AI Trust Gap” between companies who desire to quickly deploy LLM capabilities and the aforementioned risks that these systems pose in business environments.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Shaping User Behavior &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Ease of use, broad public availability, and useful answers that span various knowledge domains have led to rapid and somewhat unguided and organic adoption of generative AI-based knowledge management by employees. For example, a recent survey indicated that more than a third of surveyed employees used generative AI in their jobs, but 68% of respondents didn&#39;t inform their supervisors that they were using the tool. To realize opportunities and manage potential risks of generative AI applications to knowledge management, companies need to develop a culture of transparency and accountability that would make generative AI-based knowledge management systems successful.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to implementation of policies and guidelines, users need to understand how to safely and effectively incorporate generative AI capabilities into their tasks to enhance performance and productivity. Generative AI capabilities, including awareness of context and history, generating new content by aggregating or combining knowledge from various sources, and data-driven predictions, can provide powerful support for knowledge work. Generative AI-based knowledge management systems can automate information-intensive search processes (legal case research, for example) as well as high-volume and low-complexity cognitive tasks such as answering routine customer emails. This approach increases efficiency of employees, freeing them to put more effort into the complex decision-making and problem-solving aspects of their jobs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some specific behaviors that might be desirable to inculcate — either though training or policies — include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Knowledge of what types of content are available through the system;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How to create effective prompts;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What types of prompts and dialogues are allowed, and which ones are not;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How to request additional knowledge content to be added to the system;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How to use the system&#39;s responses in dealing with customers and partners;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How to create new content in a useful and effective manner.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Both Morgan Stanley and Morningstar trained content creators in particular on how best to create and tag content, and what types of content are well-suited to generative AI usage.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;“Everything Is Moving Very Fast”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;One of the executives we interviewed said, “I can tell you what things are like today. But everything is moving very fast in this area.” New LLMs and new approaches to tuning their content are announced daily, as are new products from vendors with specific content or task foci. Any company that commits to embedding its own knowledge into a generative AI system should be prepared to revise its approach to the issue frequently over the next several years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While there are many challenging issues involved in building and using generative AI systems trained on a company&#39;s own knowledge content, we&#39;re confident that the overall benefit to the company is worth the effort to address these challenges. The long-term vision of enabling any employee — and customers as well — to easily access important knowledge within and outside of a company to enhance productivity and innovation is a powerful draw. Generative AI appears to be the technology that is finally making it possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Making the Air in the Office Cleaner]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/making-the-air-in-the-office-cleaner]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_04_1400864430.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/fizkes/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Pressure on employers is increasing to ensure that the air is clean in their facilities. The CDC has set a target for air changes in occupied spaces to reduce the risk of airborne infections such as Covid-19. The federal Pregnant Workers Fairness Act, which took effect on June 27, 2023, mandates that employers provide &amp;#8220;reasonable accommodations&amp;#8221; for pregnant workers. And the recent intense air pollution from Canadian wildfires that extended across much of the United States highlighted yet another reason: forest fires. This article describes three steps that organizations can take to improve air quality in a cost-effective fashion.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/making-the-air-in-the-office-cleaner?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/making-the-air-in-the-office-cleaner?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In May, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention set five air changes per hour (ACH) as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/community/ventilation.html&quot;>;target&lt;/a>; amount of ventilation needed in occupied indoor spaces, such as offices and stores, to better reduce the risk of airborne infections such as Covid-19. This level will better protect everyone and is especially important for immunocompromised and other at-risk groups who can&#39;t be adequately protected by vaccines. (The CDC still advises both &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/need-extra-precautions/people-who-are-immunocompromised.html&quot;>;immunocompromised&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/need-extra-precautions/pregnant-people.html&quot;>;pregnant&lt;/a>; people to avoid crowded or poorly ventilated indoor spaces.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond this recommendation, there are additional reasons that organizations should take this target seriously. One is the federal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/wysk/what-you-should-know-about-pregnant-workers-fairness-act&quot;>;Pregnant Workers Fairness Act&lt;/a>;, which took effect on June 27. Similar to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/wysk/what-you-should-know-about-covid-19-and-ada-rehabilitation-act-and-other-eeo-laws&quot;>;Americans with Disabilities Act&lt;/a>;&#39;s required protections for the immunocompromised, it mandates that employers provide “reasonable accommodations” for pregnant workers. (Like those who are immunocompromised, pregnant people and their developing babies are also at greater risk of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/cases-updates/special-populations/pregnancy-data-on-covid-19/what-cdc-is-doing.html&quot;>;serious complications&lt;/a>; from Covid-19.) Another is a phenomenon that seems to be occurring much more frequently: forest fires. The recent intense &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/opinion/story/2023-06-16/air-quality-new-york-pollution-wildfires-climate-change&quot;>;air pollution&lt;/a>; from Canadian wildfires that extended across much of the United States is a glaring case in point.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Upgrading central air systems to achieve five ACH would, for many buildings, require extensive and costly renovations. Even once completed, these systems would incur exorbitant &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CathNoakes/status/1586299281752920064&quot;>;energy costs&lt;/a>; to cycle large amounts of air through them. Alternatively, businesses could take three steps to readily achieve five ACH by using cost-effective in-room, portable air cleaners.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Install portable air cleaners (purifiers).&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048969722029813&quot;>;Portable, low-noise air cleaners&lt;/a>; such as HEPA purifiers and do-it-yourself (DIY) air cleaners &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.patientknowhow.com/safe.html&quot;>;assembled&lt;/a>; from box fans, filters, and other off-the-shelf materials are a cost-effective method to implement the CDC target by recycling the air in each room. Based on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/san-francisco/san-francisco-unified-seeks-nearly-3-million-to-buy-air-purifiers-for-every-classroom/2639904/&quot;>;experience&lt;/a>; in San Francisco schools, three DIY purifiers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2022.11.05.22281734v1&quot;>;exceed&lt;/a>; the CDC target for as little as $250 to $400 (about $0.25 to $0.50 per square foot) for a typical 900-square-foot &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EYtmnUc8cBE&quot;>;classroom&lt;/a>; with 10-foot ceilings — and a monthly energy bill of less than $10. Since HEPA can be store bought and DIY &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EN3kYm7bXJs&quot;>;quickly&lt;/a>; constructed, they can be implemented as an effective clean air solution within a matter of days — results that have been verified by the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0360132322011507&quot;>;CDC&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/ina.13163&quot;>;US Environmental Protection Agency&lt;/a>;. DIY air cleaners are being offered &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.projectn95.org/free-air-purifiers/&quot;>;for free&lt;/a>; to organizations that serve the disadvantaged. Even more energy-saving DIY models using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cleanairkits.com/&quot;>;personal computer cooling fans&lt;/a>; have recently come to market.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In general, the number of purifiers needed and their total cost rises in proportion to both room volume and air exchange target. Many purifiers come with variable speeds. They need to be set to run at a speed needed reach the CDC target of five ACH; otherwise they will be less effective and may not reach the intended target. Once installed and running, the air exchange rate can be checked using handheld &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2022.08.09.22278555v10&quot;>;particle counters&lt;/a>; to measure the change in air particles present in a room.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Exceed the new CDC target with 12 ACH in crowded situations.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To limit bacterial growth, fish tanks typically use filtration systems to clean water at least four times an hour (every 15 minutes), analogous to four air ACH for air in a room. Until recently, there has been a lack of clarity on the degree of air cleaning needed to effectively reduce viral transmission in buildings. So in 2022 we &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2799161&quot;>;wrote to the CDC&lt;/a>; in the Journal of the American Medical Association, asking it to say clearly how many ACH are necessary to stop Covid. CDC researchers &lt;a href=&quot;https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799159&quot;>;replied&lt;/a>; that although they were not aware of Covid-19 outbreaks in spaces with five to six ACH, 12 ACH or more (like an airplane inflight or airborne isolation room in a hospital) may be needed in some situations. As the number of people in the space increases, the probability of transmission increases, which could require more ACH and distancing to reduce risk. For example, the California Department of Public Health &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdph.ca.gov/Programs/CCDPHP/DEODC/EHLB/IAQ/CDPH%20Document%20Library/School_ventilation_and_filtration_ADA.pdf&quot;>;recommends&lt;/a>; a minimum of six and ideally 12 ACH in schools.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Run air cleaners during business hours to reduce costs and replace filters periodically.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Filters and fans can either be replaced on a regular schedule recommended by the manufacturer or, if an organization wants to be conservative, after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0048969722029813&quot;>;testing&lt;/a>; shows that their performance has dropped below acceptable levels. Testing can reveal when filter or fan lasts longer than expected or if its performance dips sooner than expected (eg, a filter has clogged up with particles or has lost its ability to filter particles after an intense wildfire smoke event). In some places, such as hospitals, they may need to be run 24×7, but for many businesses, if turned on only during typical business hours (eg, 9 am to 5 pm) when people are present, they can last up to four times longer and consume four times less power. They can either be turned on and off manually by someone in the room or via low-cost &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B009KSECO8&quot;>;motion sensors&lt;/a>;, which can be set to turn them off automatically after 20 minutes of inactivity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Businesses can implement these three steps to cost effectively support the new CDC standard and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/wellness/air-purifier-smoke-covid-best/2021/08/29/28ea4176-0740-11ec-a266-7c7fe02fa374_story.html&quot;>;protect&lt;/a>; people from Covid, &lt;a href=&quot;https://aaqr.org/articles/aaqr-21-03-tn-0046&quot;>;wildfire smoke&lt;/a>;, allergens, and any other airborne dangers that might arise. These simple steps to clean the air will end up benefiting everyone and create a much more inclusive environment for at-risk groups of people, including the immunocompromised, pregnant people, the elderly, children, and those with chronic heart and lung conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Your Company Have a Culture of Quiet Retaliation?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_05_1423429755.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Quiet forms of retaliation are incredibly common and can be contagious in the workplace. The organizations that accept this form of retaliation as a standard practice have difficulty hiring and retaining great people. Retaliation &amp;#8212; in all its forms &amp;#8212; not only harms current team members, but a culture that tolerates retaliation results in harm to the mission and the organization&amp;#8217;s ability to deliver to its customers and stakeholders. To create cultures where psychological safety is the norm, innovation thrives, and team effectiveness is high, it&amp;#8217;s critical to address the retaliation that happens in the shadows.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/does-your-company-have-a-culture-of-quiet-retaliation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Most of us are familiar with the textbook or HR policy definitions of retaliation. Overt, loud moments of retaliation absolutely do happen, like when someone is fired after speaking up or formally sharing a concern. However, in our work with teams, we often witness much more subtle forms of retaliation that occur frequently and are commonly dismissed or ignored. Subtle, often silent, retaliation destroys careers, erodes the targeted individual&#39;s sense of worth, and damages the team&#39;s effectiveness.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have yet to meet any leaders who would describe themselves as retaliatory, but we regularly see retaliation occurring on teams. When the leader only sees retaliation through the lens of overt and audacious actions, they&#39;re overlooking its more subtle manifestations, whose consequences are just as serious. If leaders are unable to recognize these behaviors in themselves and others, they risk causing both short- and long-term harm to individuals, teams, and the organizations they serve. To create cultures where psychological safety is the norm, innovation thrives, and team effectiveness is high, we must tune into the retaliation that happens in the shadows.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Reality of Retaliation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the United States, employee retaliation was cited in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/newsroom/eeoc-releases-fiscal-year-2020-enforcement-and-litigation-data&quot;>;55.8% of claims&lt;/a>; filed with the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) in FY20 — and that&#39;s just what gets reported. Reporting retaliation can come with significant risk to individuals&#39; financial stability, future career advancement, and reputation. And the amount of time and emotional energy required to report it serves as a deterrent for many people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some of the most common acts of retaliation involve actions managers &lt;em>;don&#39;t&lt;/em>; take.&amp;nbsp;This quiet — sometimes covert — retaliation is incredibly harmful because it can continue undiscovered, unnamed, or unreported for years. And it doesn&#39;t just impact the targeted individual, but can decrease the level of trust, creativity, and productivity in team members who witness it and perpetuate a culture of abuse. In her article “&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/06/times-up-for-toxic-workplaces&quot;>;Time&#39;s up for Toxic Workplaces&lt;/a>;,” Villanova professor Manuela Priesemuth shares how a culture of abuse and retaliation can “spread throughout the organization, creating entire climates of abuse. Because employees look to and learn from managers, they come to understand that this type of interpersonal mistreatment is acceptable behavior in the company.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are five specific examples of covert retaliation we&#39;ve observed in our work coaching leaders and the teams they serve:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Withholding coaching, feedback, or professional development opportunities&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Withholding resources for a project or division&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Intentionally giving a challenging assignment with little support or giving a challenging assignment that&#39;s destined to fail&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Discouraging others from listening to or valuing a team member&#39;s voice, expertise, or contributions&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Excluding a team member from essential meetings or withholding information that&#39;s essential to their job function&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Mark*, who was known to be retaliatory, served as the CEO of a large retail company for over a decade before retiring. As we worked with the remaining leadership team under the new CEO, it quickly became clear that Mark&#39;s departure alone wasn&#39;t enough to quell employees&#39; fears. Even though Mark was no longer there, an observable level of fear continued in the company. We heard from several leaders that any disagreement with Mark would mean the end of your growth within the company. “He had a look he would get when he was disappointed with someone for speaking up,” we heard from several leaders. “He would draw a line through your name instead of under it. Everyone knew and it was basically game over. You&#39;re stuck.” For Mark, retaliation took the covert forms of social undermining and exclusion. The impacts on the organization were significant: Innovation stalled, the culture suffered, and the business stagnated.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Julia is the CFO of a midsize technology company. When she received notification of a hostile work environment complaint from within her department, she shared that she was aware of the issues because they had been occurring for years but had avoided addressing them. Julia had always been vocal about not wanting people on her team to discuss any problems with HR. “Why can&#39;t people just put their heads down and get their work done? And why is it my job to deal with their childish behavior?” she asked her peers. Julia proceeded to strip the complaining team member of her access to information and documentation that were essential to performing her job. Julia also stopped responding to her emails in a timely fashion and hoped the lack of correspondence would lead to delays in projects being completed on time to further make the team member look bad in front of her peers. When questioned about these actions, Julia responded, “It can&#39;t be retaliation because I didn&#39;t fire them.” We often see leaders engaging in quiet acts of retaliation that carry big impacts, but they don&#39;t see them as retaliation because they narrowly define retaliation as terminating the employee.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ron had served as the charge nurse in a hospital emergency room for 15 years and was favored for a substantial promotion within the year. While the formal leaders within the hospital appreciated Ron&#39;s strict, traditional style of management, the other ER staff had a very different experience. “If you do something that bothers him — maybe express a concern or point out that certain supplies are low — you can expect that everything you say or do in the future will be scrutinized. He can&#39;t take any feedback, even about straightforward things like the inventory of masks or gloves,” we heard from one shift leader. In this particular situation, the negative impact on the culture and the logjam created by the ongoing negative scrutiny impacted not only the department, but also jeopardized public safety.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How Leaders Should Self-Assess Their Impact&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders often see themselves as the gatekeepers of what is right in their department or organization. In each of the situations we just described, the leaders believed that&#39;s what they were doing. The danger lies not in failing to see the disconnect between your intention and your impact. The ripple effect of a leader&#39;s retaliation is immense. When leaders lack the tools needed to deepen the self-awareness of their actions and their impact, the consequences can be dire for all stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We tend to judge ourselves by our good intentions and others by their impact. One of our guiding leadership principles is: You don&#39;t determine your impact; other people do. So how can you better assess the impact of your actions and understand the root cause of your behavior? Start with these three practices:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Conduct a courageous audit.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Examine your own behavior and dig deep into the motives behind your actions. We highly recommend the practice of a “courageous audit” grounded in the work of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gse.harvard.edu/hgse100/story/changing-better&quot;>;Immunity to Change&lt;/a>; by Robert Kegan and Lisa Lahey. The Immunity to Change model is particularly effective in this situation because it challenges us to think about how our actions (or lack thereof) are getting in the way of creating a psychologically safe work environment. Think about the situations with team members that have frustrated you the most and look for ways you behaved that were unproductive or potentially retaliatory. Challenge yourself to curiously ask and courageously answer: What am I doing or not doing that&#39;s getting in the way of a safe culture?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Becoming aware of counterproductive behaviors is the first step to changing them. We hear regularly from leaders that reflecting on themselves in this way feels too vulnerable in front of colleagues, so working with an experienced coach is an effective way to enhance your self-awareness around your thoughts and actions in the workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Identify your shadow intentions.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Shadow intentions are when we act (consciously or unconsciously) from a place of ego and self-protection. Push back on your own stated desire to “be helpful” or to “protect your department.” In what ways have your thoughts or actions been intended to hurt a team member through covert or passive methods? When have you been driven by self-protection in a way that has gone unchecked? When might you have allowed your first, stress-driven reaction to negatively affect the impact you&#39;re making on others?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Elizabeth was part of a growing IT company and by all accounts a vital member of the leadership team. She was also passed over for promotion numerous times when mergers occurred and “room had to be made for the incoming leaders.” While she wanted to continue to prove her worth and lead her team well, she needed support to actively untangle from her shadow intentions of wanting the new leaders to fail so she could be rewarded for her excellence and ongoing commitment. By working to loosen the grip her shadow intentions had on her, she was able to bring more of her focus back to her own division and better supporting innovation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Explore your in-group/out-group.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Assess your thoughts and assumptions about those around you. Who gets to be honest with you, even disagree with you? Whose opinions do you value? Why? Whom do you struggle with? What commonalities exist between the people in your in-group versus your out-group?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Identifying your own patterns is the pivotal first step of working toward a team where everyone is included and can contribute fully. Dan, the CEO of a midsize firm, wanted to think differently about several leadership changes that were occurring due to retirements. He wanted to bring the new executives in and build a cohesive team with the remaining members. In an audit of his own in- and out-groups, he discovered that two leaders of the executive team were in his out-group. Both had started during the pandemic, and Dan hadn&#39;t had the one-on-one time with them he usually invests in new executives on his team. Dan decided to start building connections with them more intentionally by scheduling individual lunches once a month and initiating a 15-minute one-on-one with each of them once a week.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are many strategies help leaders in connect with their out-group, but the most important point thing to keep in mind is that the person with the most power must initiate the connection.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Quiet forms of retaliation are incredibly common and can be contagious in the workplace. The organizations we serve that accept this form of retaliation as a standard practice have difficulty hiring and retaining great people. Retaliation — in all its forms — not only harms current team members, but a culture that tolerates retaliation results in harm to the mission and the organization&#39;s ability to deliver to its customers and stakeholders. Organizations are defined by what they celebrate and what they tolerate. Leaders who engage in or tolerate retaliation can create lasting scars on individuals and organizations alike. The humans we serve deserve better.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;em>;* Names have been changed throughout to protect privacy.&lt;/em>; &lt;/div>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Removing the Roadblocks That First-Generation Americans Face at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_03_1369183308.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Many first-generation Americans face a cultural seesaw effect when trying to be successful in Western workplaces. For example, members of the Asian American and Pacific Islander (AAPI) community can find it challenging to self-promote, as it goes against their values. They&amp;#8217;re taught from a very young age to be humble, to stay under the radar, and to never correct authority figures, as a sign of respect. They hope their hard work will simply speak for itself. But self-promotion and voicing opinions have become key elements needed to thrive in Western workplaces, which clearly advantages some and disadvantages others. Further, first-generation Americans and other marginalized communities endure numerous generational, societal, and workplace traumas that create mental health disparities, which can result in an apprehension to advocate for themselves in work environments. While leaders cannot control how their employees will cope with societal and generational trauma, it is their responsibility to foster environments where all employees can feel secure in raising their hands for support. In order for this to successfully occur, organizations should closely look at whether current employee behaviors are in fact promoting inclusivity, or if processes and norms need to be modified to provide an equitable landscape for all workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/removing-the-roadblocks-that-first-generation-americans-face-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When my family immigrated from India to the US nearly four decades ago, they had no indication of what a new world would bring. They were filled with hope that this relocation would provide a surplus of opportunities unavailable before. With that hope came a justified reservation about acceptance in a new community, so they applied a strategy many immigrant families deploy: assimilate and prosper.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The goal was not to suppress our identities. In contrast, it was to engage in a new environment with foreigners in a non-burdensome way. Rather than demanding a promotion at their jobs, my parents patiently waited until their hard work was finally rewarded — years after their American peers. Instead of asking for support in their daily duties, they silently took on additional responsibilities to prove their worth. Both of my parents wore their sense of altruism, undying commitment, and unwavering devotion as a badge of honor — blissfully passing these values onto me in hopes that I would replicate their work ethic in my career.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I entered the workforce with my parents&#39; worth ethic, fearless spirit, and integrity to carry me through my future endeavors. Unfortunately, history repeated itself in an unexpected way. I was exploited for my hard work. My boundaries were constantly being violated by senior leadership. I was petrified when it came to seeking support from my team because I was convinced that this would be a sign of weakness and would tarnish my professional image, ultimately hindering growth opportunities. It created a version of me that I despised: insecure, hesitant, and incredibly docile.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Working as a First-Generation American &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;My formative years were spent thinking my family environment was unique, but this was far from the truth. Many first-generation Americans face similar challenges as they navigate the societal expectations of two cultures at a very young age, resulting in a unique phenomenon called the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://srcd.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/cdep.12071&quot;>;immigrant paradox&lt;/a>;“.&amp;nbsp;First-generation Americans experience diminishing developmental outcomes, educational achievements, and even mental health challenges because of the racial and ethnic disparities in the US — challenges our parents or even recent immigrants do not face since they immigrate normally post-adolescence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To exacerbate this experience, first-generation Americans also face &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2022/10/26/health/mental-health-children-of-immigrants-wellness/index.html&quot;>;immigrant guilt&lt;/a>; as they try to desperately hold onto the traditions they inherited while harmonizing within a culture their families could not provide any guidance about. Adapting to the Western culture while feeling “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-othering-5084425&quot;>;othered&lt;/a>;” can lead to the inability to forge an identity that neatly falls within both cultures, traditions, and experiences. While our families may have had the best intentions in providing us with their wisdom and perceived values of success, it did not translate well into a workplace construct that was built for people who never shared our identities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is the cultural seesaw effect that many first-generation Americans face when trying to be successful in the workplace. The Asian American and Pacific Islander (AAPI) community (and many cultures alike) find it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/mckinsey-on-books/author-talks-we-need-to-talk-about-asian-american-mental-health?cid=other-eml-dre-mip-mck&amp;amp;hlkid=a774e1a8976d4a078406df70a8406fd5&amp;amp;hctky=12012649&amp;amp;hdpid=9ae1a3af-4f90-48c7-84bd-0389613c0228&quot;>;challenging to self-promote&lt;/a>;, as it goes against our values. We&#39;re taught to be humble and stay under the radar. We have been taught from a very young age to never correct authority figures, as a sign of respect. Similar to how my parents navigated their careers, many AAPI community members hope their hard work will simply speak for itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So why is this important for workplaces and leaders to consider as they seek to create equitable and inclusive work environments? &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/savvy-self-promotion&quot;>;Self-promotion&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/glennllopis/2012/03/19/6-reasons-employees-must-speak-up-to-thrive-at-work/&quot;>;voicing your opinion&lt;/a>; have become key elements needed to thrive in Western workplaces, but this clearly advantages some and disadvantages others. Further, first-generation Americans and other marginalized communities endure numerous generational, societal, and workplace traumas that create &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/cultural-competency/education/mental-health-facts#:~:text=Racial%2Fethnic%2C%20gender%2C%20and,of%20awareness%20about%20mental%20health&quot;>;mental health disparities&lt;/a>;, which can result in an apprehension to advocate for themselves in work environments.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, if employers take an approach that commits to prioritizing inclusivity across all identities and backgrounds, then we can make progress in our distorted definition of success.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How Leaders Can Change the Narrative and Help Fix a Flawed System&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Leaders cannot control how their employees will cope with societal and generational trauma. Yet, it is their responsibility to foster environments where all employees can feel secure in raising their hands for support. In order for this to successfully occur, organizations should closely look at whether current employee behaviors are in fact promoting inclusivity, or if processes and norms need to be modified to provide an equitable landscape for all workers. In my experience in working with global organizations, taking this critical pause before churning out solutions has proven to be a pivotal factor in revamping inclusion.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Assess Your Inclusion Efforts &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In order to understand what practices are supportive of inclusion and which are not, a thorough assessment is required. In previous leadership roles, I have successfully conducted this assessment that ultimately evaluates inclusion across organizational and management practices through three specific dimensions: Co-creating success as a team, fostering communities with purpose, and evaluating the effectiveness of feedback mechanisms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These three dimensions serve as a comprehensive approach to further understanding the organization&#39;s context, culture, and intent in creating substantive inclusion. It also serves as a foundation for leaders to deep dive into prevailing processes to determine if the current company climate integrates the differences first-generation employees bring to the table, and allows them to be part of the decision-making process to achieve strategic objectives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once each dimension is thoroughly examined, taking action and prioritizing specific areas that need immediate attention is key. It will foster a culture of continuous learning and improvement from an organizational level, while simultaneously creating new practices where first-generation employees have the security to thrive.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Co-Create Success as a Team&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We start with this dimension because our traditional workplace practices define success by emphasizing specific individual behaviors, instead of creating practices that benefit the entire employee population. This &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/how-to-infuse-liberatory-practices-into-work-practices&quot;>;divide and conquer&lt;/a>; approach specifically prevents first-generation employees from determining what success looks like for them, furthering the narrative that their unique insights are less important than the dominant group.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As leaders, you can rectify these practices by first evaluating the level of collaboration and inclusion you provide for your own team. Commence reparative practices and invite all team members to define what success looks like for them. By doing so, you are providing first-generation employees the permission to relinquish their previous notions of the perfect employee, and create a culture of solidarity where they will be more likely to voice their opinions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Additionally, forging rules of engagement, understanding preferred communication styles with others, and finalizing what support leadership should provide at the start of a project maintains boundaries for each first-generation employee. Eventually, if you keep inviting opinions to the table — and revisit conversations about success definitions on an agreed-upon timeline — the stigma associated with raising concerns will slowly diminish. Further, maintaining these work relationships and reciprocally committing to meet each other&#39;s needs will allow for an equitable decision-making process and boost morale among all team members.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Foster Communities With Purpose&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Arguably, this may be the most important component of the inclusion assessment, because it offers up a safe haven for first-generation employees to discuss how they navigate unique workplace stressors that only apply to them. Employee resource groups (ERGs), for example, have been incredibly popular for organizations trying to increase their inclusion efforts. However, they often &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/effective-employee-resource-groups-are-key-to-inclusion-at-work-heres-how-to-get-them-right&quot;>;fall short&lt;/a>; because they lack accountability or a specific mission. In my experience, I have seen ERGs solely being leveraged as an after-work social gathering — which is important, but does not cultivate corrective practices in the workplace that first-generation employees deserve. In order to make these communities more effective, I recommend finding a business sponsor who is already practicing &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/why-inclusive-leaders-are-good-for-organizations-and-how-to-become-one&quot;>;inclusive leadership&lt;/a>; to lead the ERG with empathy and strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a previous role, I acted as the business sponsor and supported the launch of a similar ERG with a six-month action plan. The first two months were to simply connect as a community — to decompress and speak about how our community is marginalized in particular ways. The third and fourth months were used to transition into strategy. We examined questions such as: &lt;em>;How can we empower ourselves to ask for support? What specific actions do we need leadership to take for us to continuously feel empowered in order to bring value back to the organization? &lt;/em>;These conversations were often difficult, and sometimes quite emotionally draining because it required many of us to revisit how our immigrant guilt manifests itself in the workplace. This is why the business sponsor of any ERG should be well-equipped and skilled to facilitate these conversations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Lastly, the fifth and sixth months were dedicated to building a case to senior leadership in the specific work practices that needed to be amended in order for us to feel valued, included, and guarded in the workplace. A specific proposal was then developed with a coherent communication plan derived from the roundtable discussions we had in previous months. As we co-created this plan, each member of the ERG was invited to provide feedback and voted for the top concerns we wanted to address.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With this collective support of the ERG community, we were able to establish new norms across client projects to address capacity constraints, enhance cross-collaboration with teams, and determine accountability measures across all levels. For many of the ERG members, this success came with a unique sense of ownership of their careers that had seemed foreign before. People in the community had been accustomed to remaining silent, trailing back to the generational trauma many of us carried as we navigated through various challenges into the workforce. However, this success was a glimmer of hope that self-promotion could actually lead to tangible results, fundamentally changing the way the business operates.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Evaluate the Effectiveness of Feedback Mechanisms &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While employee feedback through engagement surveys has become popular over the years as a definitive measure for enhancing inclusion, many first-generation employees will hesitate to offer their insights. Due to our complex identities, feeling othered, and lack of role models that share our identity, we feel compelled to assess the work environment first to determine if speaking up will be celebrated or punished — regardless of whether the feedback is imperative to change working conditions. To counteract this, leaders should actively analyze what type of culture they are promoting in order to retrieve an accurate glimpse of the work environment. Without this core component in psychological safety, employee engagement surveys will remain a false illusion of the organization&#39;s actual reality.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, if your goal is to decrease employee burnout by seeking suggestions through engagement surveys, evaluate the type of behavior you are celebrating prior to seeking feedback. If you are amplifying an employee working at all hours, allowing others to accept every client demand, or creating &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90662451/its-very-time-sensitive-why-a-fast-paced-work-environment-hurts-all-employees&quot;>;a false sense of urgency&lt;/a>;, you are not fostering an inclusive environment for others to raise their hand for support. In fact, you are telling your employees that this is the golden rule for everyone to follow. First-generation employees will not feel safe to provide feedback in addressing these negative workplace stressors because the organization inadvertently supports this type of burnout behavior. Regardless of how well-intentioned your surveys are, harmful work environments will negate any efforts to make substantial change and eradicate any creditability amongst your first-generation employees. However, if the end goal is to create sustainable and inclusive work environments, call out toxic behaviors as regularly as you can, making it known these are not expectations for employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Once there has been a careful examination of workplace practices, seeking individual feedback via engagement surveys, team forums, or even via 1:1 meetings can further prove to empower first-generation employees. This continued course of action achieves a positive cycle of consistency where self-advocacy is encouraged, rather than expecting first-generation employees to overcome their reservations without the proper groundwork.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Furthermore, as you seek feedback, carefully analyze the perspectives of your first-generation employees. You may not always agree with their feedback or even fully understand their point of view. However, it is still your responsibility to do your best to implement changes if your end goal is inclusivity. Once this process is underway, an important consideration is not to have the feedback stay idle. Ultimately, if feedback goes unheard, it can create an environment of mistrust between you and first-generation employees. Keep in mind that this specific group would have done a great deal to overcome their own internalized stigma in providing the feedback, in hopes that the culture of work would be transformed. Communicate how you will address the feedback and remain agile. It may be possible that you will need to spend some time deciphering feedback from your first-generation employees or have another follow-up questionnaire to clarify points when it comes to their working conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As organizations continue to correct a flawed system by building inclusion for all communities, it is imperative to support those who may not be able to advocate for themselves. First-generation employees sit at a unique juncture in applying determination and diligence in a new era of work, continuously shifting between cultures. Organizations need to create an environment where we can shed our layers and authentically thrive in the hopes of creating a more equitable world.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Benefits of Being Bored at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_29_XLRivrl9mNI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&amp;#8217;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life. Based on the body of research exploring this emotion, the authors highlight some of boredom&amp;#8217;s benefits and detriments and offer insights into how you might harness the best of boredom.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-benefits-of-being-bored-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Bored at work? We&#39;ve all been there. &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/1745691612456044&quot;>;Boredom&lt;/a>; is that experience of wanting to be occupied in a satisfying activity, yet somehow being unable to do so. And being busy is no antidote: You may be both very busy — and very bored — simultaneously.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Early in life we learn that boredom is no fun, and as we age we might begin to see it as a waste of time, or a missed opportunity to do something more productive (or at least more interesting). At best, boredom has been considered an unpleasant to &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691612456044?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;aversive &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/152c9TgGipX6UOMCIbfTdrGy_vN6kopCv/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;experience&lt;/a>;, and at worst, a state that evokes a deep sense of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springer.com/journal/13164&quot;>;meaninglessness&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XXpz4j8kTTtUdXJdlak3e3_kuIJLNskz/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;.&lt;/a>; In addition, when feeling the discomfort of boredom, time &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gNy8bUlah9IHjM1CZZjkS6EnRV7AxXzX/view?usp=share_link&quot;>;tends to pass slowly&lt;/a>;, which can make work days seem endless.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Considering this, it&#39;s no surprise that boredom often triggers an intense desire to escape the situation (or job!) that evokes it. In today&#39;s ultra-connected world, this escape is just one tap away. At your fingertips, you find a world of data, breaking news, shows and stories, messages from friends and family, or gifs, memes, and video clips that help you avoid feeling bored — at least at the surface level. Research shows that use of smartphones not only distracts the mind, it offers an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/IJPHM-08-2016-0044/full/html&quot;>;addictive hit&lt;/a>; of dopamine, which &lt;em>;temporarily&lt;/em>; replaces the discomfort of boredom with pleasure. However, this&amp;nbsp;feeling is short lived, as this mindless scrolling results in long-term decreases in overall mental health and quality of life.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next time you&#39;re feeling that creeping sense of boredom at work, pause before you pick up your phone. Boredom can have important benefits, and you&#39;ll miss them if you&#39;re not tuned in to what you&#39;re feeling and why.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Pros and Cons of Workplace Boredom&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Boredom has a negative reputation for a reason. At work, it&#39;s often viewed as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;counterproductive state&lt;/a>; that ignites discomfort, desperation for a new role, or perhaps simply a desire for the day to end. Boredom at work has been linked to &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2160&quot;>;risky decision-making&lt;/a>;, costly mistakes, and accidents triggered by inattention or lack of focus — and that&#39;s not to mention the fatigue that being bored can generate. Boredom can also incite other types of problematic behavior, such as “cyberloafing” (that is, non-work-related browsing) and childish emotional responses. Prolonged exposure to monotonous activities can even cause &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-pathology-of-boredom/&quot;>;hallucinations&lt;/a>;. In addition, when it comes to well-being, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000187912200118X&quot;>;one recent study found&lt;/a>; a linkage between boredom at work and burnout, as well as decreases in job satisfaction and increased desire to quit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the flip side, recent research shows that boredom — when handled constructively — has big “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053482222000766&quot;>;bright sides&lt;/a>;.” Moments of boredom can offer a pause, or a short respite for your brain and body in a world designed to distract, overwhelm, and overstimulate. A sense of boredom can create the space to daydream, which can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2014.901073&quot;>;hatch creativity&lt;/a>;, new ideas, and innovation. Prolonged boredom can prompt you to reflect and ask yourself, “Am I on the right path? Am I doing the right thing?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Use Your Boredom for the Better&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We&#39;re not advocating that you seek out jobs where you&#39;ll spend large parts of the day feeling bored. However, getting better at working &lt;em>;with&lt;/em>; your boredom — and harnessing it for the good — can help you capture its bright sides. Here&#39;s how:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1. Notice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you feel that discomfort of boredom setting in, avoid acting on it immediately. The fact that you&#39;ve noticed you&#39;re bored means that you&#39;ve managed to (briefly) resist the urge to instantly engage in mindless scrolling. Noticing and naming your boredom in order to intentionally direct it opens up the opportunity to develop your resilience and the potential to use boredom for positive ends. Most importantly, in a bout of boredom, don&#39;t make snap decisions (like to quit your job) as a way to escape the discomfort.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2. Decipher.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Not all experiences of boredom are the same — &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11031-013-9385-y&quot;>;research shows&lt;/a>; that various “types” of boredom manifest differently in the body and mind, giving rise to different behaviors. Decoding which types you&#39;re feeling early on can help you make a game plan to deal with boredom, or prevent it from escalating or clouding your decision making.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ask yourself what your boredom is telling you. Could it be that you simply need a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/how-to-take-better-breaks-at-work-according-to-research&quot;>;micro-break&lt;/a>; because you&#39;ve worked too long without pausing and you&#39;re tiring? Or maybe your tasks are becoming monotonous and you&#39;re losing motivation and energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider what you&#39;re bored with specifically: Is it your role, the content or form of the work, or your prospects for the future in your job that bore you? Can you decipher a pattern with a typical type of work that ignites this uncomfortable feeling? This can be an opportunity to consider your goals and values and whether you feel you&#39;re moving forward or feel “stuck.” Here are five research-based types of boredom to consider as you work to decipher yours:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Indifferent boredom.&lt;/strong>; This is one of the more positive types of boredom. It can feel like relaxation or a sense of cheerful fatigue and reflects a general indifference to (and withdrawal from) the external world. This type of boredom can help boost rest and recovery, particularly during busy days.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Calibrating boredom.&lt;/strong>; This one&#39;s slightly more unpleasant and is one of the most common types. It occurs when you&#39;re not fully engaged in a task or activity and your mind starts to drift. It can show up as wandering thoughts or not knowing what to do to change the situation, yet wanting to get out of it somehow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Searching boredom.&lt;/strong>; This type reflects a restlessness and active search for alternative actions and distractions to ease the negative experience (eg, through other activities, leisure pursuits, interests, and hobbies). While unpleasant, this type of boredom ignites activity and the pursuit of change and often has positive outcomes, such as creativity, innovation, and personal growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Reactive boredom.&lt;/strong>; Reactive boredom arises in situations where a person is required to do a repetitive or tedious task (such as being stuck in a long and ineffective meeting with no chance of escape). It&#39;s an action-oriented and deeply unpleasant type of boredom, which causes restlessness and frustration that might be expressed in a more angry or aggressive fashion toward others or toward the boring experience. Those experiencing it may persistently fantasize about other options and feel anxious to make a change or escape quickly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Apathetic boredom.&lt;/strong>; This can relate to feelings of disinterest, lack of motivation, and emotional detachment toward activities or events one would normally find stimulating or enjoyable. Apathetic boredom isn&#39;t necessarily accompanied by feelings of frustration or restlessness but rather a sense of disengagement and indifference. It can occur as a result of chronic stress, depression, or other mental health issues and can lead to feelings of hopelessness and helplessness. People experiencing apathetic boredom may feel like they&#39;re going through the motions of life without any real purpose or enjoyment.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3. Decide what to do.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Based on the type of boredom and what it&#39;s telling you about yourself or your situation, decide what to do about it. Maybe your boredom is simply allowing you to relax and unwind after a period of intensity at work. Or perhaps it&#39;s telling you something about your role itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All roles have certain elements that are monotonous, frustrating, or simply boring, and sometimes these tasks must be done to get to the “good stuff.” If you find yourself persistently bored, try to harness the boredom to catalyze change, perhaps by engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2001.4378011&quot;>;job crafting&lt;/a>; to bring out the elements of your role that you really enjoy. This could involve, for example, making changes to the type, variety, complexity, or significance of your tasks. You might intentionally evade boredom by seeking out, envisioning, and championing new ideas at work, which can also boost your leadership abilities and potential. Reflecting and engaging in &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23163710/&quot;>;nostalgia&lt;/a>; can also counteract the sense of meaninglessness you might feel when bored.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4. Cultivate mindful boredom.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Moments of boredom can be opportunities to help you unwind from a fast-paced and hyper-connected world and allow you the opportunity to simply be in the present moment. Use moments of boredom for positive intentions rather than mindless distraction, for example, by taking a moment to breathe, doing another activity you find simulating, or simply mindfully allowing the discomfort to pass. As boredom can spark &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20200522-how-boredom-can-spark-creativity&quot;>;creativity&lt;/a>;, you could even include space for it as unstructured time in your work routine, for example, before you&#39;re required to innovate, come up with new ideas, and be at your best.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While boredom can be an unpleasant feeling, it can also be an opportunity to reflect on your interests, values, and goals. By recognizing the type of boredom you&#39;re experiencing and identifying the underlying causes, you can take steps to address them and find new ways to engage with the world around you. Working with your boredom can also help you develop creativity, resilience, and the ability to adapt to new situations. So rather than trying to avoid or ignore your boredom, consider working with it as a valuable tool for personal growth and a way to lead a more fulfilling life.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>