<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Smaller Companies Must Embrace Risk Management]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_08_125412697.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;卡罗琳·珀瑟/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;中小企业没有相同的监管压力可以导致大公司衡量和减轻风险，但它们也没有较少的缓冲资源来抵御意外风险震动。它们是远离破产的一大潜在事件。这就是为什么中小企业可以从采取三项行动中受益：设计与所面临的风险相称的控制措施，分析成功的教训（不仅是失败的教训），以及利用风险管理来提高和保护业务绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=es&quot;>;阅读更多西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;有风险管理很无聊，这是一种不幸的刻板印象。风险经理是悲观的职员。合规官员是危言耸听者。太多的管理者都有这样的想法。因此，风险管理是一门不受喜爱和误解的学科。在灾难发生之前，对大多数人来说，风险管理是一项艰苦且代价高昂的苦差事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，在一个日益动荡的世界中，风险管理从未如此重要。尽管如此，面对更直接的商业压力，风险管理者很难发出自己的声音。对于具有创业文化、监管要求较少、资源限制较多的中小型企业来说尤其如此。这些企业往往将风险管理视为一种昂贵的奢侈品，因此他们可能更容易面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;本文基于二十年的应用、研究、向学术和专业观众教授风险管理。它将帮助管理者——包括中小企业的管理者——更好地了解风险并应用有效、积极的风险管理技术。该框架依赖于三项行动：设计与所面临的风险相称的控制措施、分析成功的教训（不仅是失败的教训）以及利用风险管理来提高和保护业务绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong >;积极的风险管理是适度的&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;适度意味着小风险需要小题大做；大风险需要高度关注。日常风险是可以接受的，例如：忘记电子邮件附件、重复支付少量发票、错过内部报告的截止日期。像这样的错误和失误只能说明我们有多忙。对于快速发展的企业，尤其是团队精简且资源稀缺的中小企业，这是可以理解的监督。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;新运营时代&quot; dek=&quot;提高效率并增强弹性。&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style= &quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;运营新时代&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 提高效率并增强弹性。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;相反，极端风险值得更加警惕：网络钓鱼链接发起网络攻击，造成的损失一家创新型初创企业的关键知识产权，是一家疗养院供水系统中的细菌感染。忽视真正的危险会造成数百万人的损失、心痛和生命——这时我们就会后悔没有更加警惕、更加小心、更加无聊。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，组织经常错误地计算风险。较小的事件是最常见的；它们引起了人们的注意，但并不重要。从多年来银行 500,000 起运营损失的&lt;a href=&quot;https://orx.org/download/annual-operational-risk-loss-reports-2022&quot;>;样本&lt;/a>;来看，数据显示，最小尺寸类别最常见 (61%)，但总体破坏性最小（占总损失严重程度的 6%）。真正的损失来自最大、最罕见的事件：每年，前 0.3% 的事件平均造成总损失的 63%。尽管存在这种不平衡，风险管理者和企业仍将更多的时间和注意力投入到小问题上，而不是防止严重损害。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果过度应用风险管理，成本就会很高。例如，过度的网络保护会减慢计算机和登录的速度，对每笔付款和交易的双重检查会浪费时间，而这些时间本来可以更好地用于创造性活动。可信来自克制。当风险管理者在呼吁审慎时表现出实用主义时，他们就会受到尊重。有能力的风险管理者会为严重和可能发生的情况做好准备，同时容忍有限的事故。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;适当的风险管理可以减少因控制过多或过少而导致的低效率。过于谨慎会导致缓慢、僵化和机会成本。粗心大意会导致事故、不稳定和补救成本。非金融风险具有风险回报权衡 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.semanticscholar.org/paper/Measuring-and-Managing-Operational-Risk-in-the-An-Chapelle-Crama/5920d87080830026d615a39cb9e63ba143fe5ef4 &quot;>;喜欢他们的金融等价物&lt;/a>;。通过取消一些运营控制来提高生产率来节省成本是对运营风险的回报。有效的风险管理者和精明的业务领导者清楚地了解他们准备接受多少风险以及获得哪些收益。这一概念被广泛称为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bis.org/review/r151023i.htm&quot;>;风险偏好&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;积极的风险管理值得庆祝成功&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;剖析事故的根本原因，特别是那些潜在损害最大的事故，是一种良好的风险管理实践。然而，当仅关注过去的损失和未来的错误时，风险管理者无法识别和强化成功的原因。回顾失败的原因很有价值，但它可能会通过隐含的批评产生阻力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，伦敦一家票据交换所的高级风险官在发现失败的某些原因时冲出了车间。所讨论的损失被认为是他的管理风格造成的。他否决了进一步的演习，六个月后因其他原因被解雇。该公司现已关闭。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;反思成功故事是鼓舞人心的。 “&lt;em>;我们为什么赢了？&lt;/em>;比“&lt;em>;我们为什么输了？&lt;/em>;更能激发分析热情。剖析过去的成就是令人鼓舞和富有洞察力的。成功是存在的，但常常被忽视：周一早上，没有人注意到周末顺利进行的 IT 迁移，也没有人称赞由于员工的高效表现而没有出现客户投诉。人类大脑的&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1998-12834-004&quot;>;消极偏见&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;意味着消极经历会烙印在我们的记忆中比积极的更快、更持久。对过去的胜利进行深思熟虑是对常见风险管理关注问题的一种受欢迎的平衡。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有效风险管理有公认的规则：保持警惕是关键，快速干预可以减少影响。 “&lt;em>;如果你看到什么，就说出来&lt;/em>;”是纽约地铁防止恐怖袭击的座右铭。 “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btp.police.uk/police-forces/british-transport-police/areas/campaigns/see-it-say-it-sorted/&quot;>;&lt;em>;看看，说出来，排序&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;”相当于伦敦地铁。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于中小企业来说，纪律和警惕也是成功的关键。初创企业要想蓬勃发展，需要的不仅仅是伟大的想法；它们依赖于创始人的不懈关注，创始人必须不断监控绩效并对可能出现的问题保持警惕。新兴品牌的国际扩张需要严格的规划、市场知识、彻底的尽职调查以及能够在无数潜在问题演变成灾难之前解决它们的有能力的管理人员。例如在个人生活中，及早发现盗窃、火灾或疾病可能会导致惊吓和悲剧。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;赞扬良好的风险管理实践可以强化获胜行为并避免不当批评，积极的风险管理者成为导师，而不是末日预言者。风险管理受到欢迎和接受，成为成就的一个组成部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;积极的风险管理可以保护绩效&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;管理风险与管理绩效密不可分。积极的风险管理旨在捕捉不确定性带来的好处，并尽可能防止其带来的负面影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;梦想大，风险大：承担风险是必要的，甚至是可取的。但这需要方法。特技演员是伟大的风险管理者，否则他们将无法在第一部电影中幸存下来。企业家必须平衡大胆与谨慎，否则注定会失败。企业和政府必须关注并应对威胁，否则就会给自己和他人造成严重破坏，正如我们多次目睹的那样。当风险管理失败时，组织就会垮台。金融危机、Covid-19，或者最近的硅谷银行倒闭，都是风险管理失败的根源。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;风险管理是雄心勃勃的条件：目标越雄心勃勃，就越能实现目标。更重要的是风险管理是为了实现它。酒店和度假村需要完美的流程才能获得满意的客户体验；金融科技银行必须由一流的网络安全专家才能运营；医疗保健提供者需要无可挑剔的患者安全程序才能生存。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;特别是对于较小的公司来说，增长伴随着风险，而快速增长的初创企业产生运营风险的速度比收入更快，因为复杂性的增长速度快于规模的增长速度。只有那些拥有健全的风险管理系统的公司才能成为明天的谷歌、亚马逊、迪士尼或麦当劳。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着对气候变化的日益关注，金融监管机构和贝莱德等投资者&lt;a href=&quot;tcfd: %20https://www.fsb-tcfd.org&quot;>;期望&lt;/a>;组织了解、评估和沟通其面临的气候相关风险。然而，现在气候相关风险的要求适用于所有类型的业务风险：为了保护其业务模式和绩效，管理者需要监督其运营环境的所有相关变化。例如，区块链创新和加密货币与支付平台提供商最相关，而钴的开采条件和稀土元素的可用性对于监控锂离子电池生产商至关重要。生成式人工智能让很多人感到害怕，但如果使用得当（通过适当的风险管理），这个工具可以成为一个令人惊叹的生产力助推器，值得拥抱而不是对抗。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;结论&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;中小企业没有像大公司那样的监管压力来衡量和减轻风险，但它们抵御意外冲击的缓冲资源也较少。它们是远离破产的一大潜在事件。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过对风险管理持积极态度，专业人士可以为他们的学科带来鼓舞人心的叙述，认识到承担风险的价值和保护绩效的必要性。乐观主义者与悲观主义者之间、敢于冒险者与谨慎者之间的建设性对话，是业务增长的强大引擎，不会出现繁荣和萧条。在追求成功和幸福的过程中，我们需要决定什么可以赌，什么不能输。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Skills the Next Generation of Data Scientists Needs to Develop]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sept23_08_1298126402.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR 员工； Westend61/盖蒂图片社； Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span >; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;随着对数据和分析的依赖不断扩大，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source= prnewswire&amp;#38;utm_medium=referral&amp;#38;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;农业&lt;/a>;至&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/ &quot;>;制造&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed-data-network-partnerships&quot;>;医疗保健&lt;/a>;到&lt;a href =&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial-services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot; >;金融服务&lt;/a>;，毫无疑问，下一代数据领导者将发挥影响战略、决策、运营和无数其他职能的深远作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next- Generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=es &quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next- Generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=pt&quot;>;阅读em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我每年都会为有抱负的数据科学家教授一门课程。在第一节课开始时，我问我的学生他们希望学到什么。通常，他们的答案是“分析数据”或“建立良好的模型”。将这些回应与我与实践数据科学家举办的研讨会进行比较，他们在讨论他们所做的事情时使用不同的术语。他们称之为“解决问题”——朝着正确方向迈出的一步——但即使这样也太狭窄了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着对数据和分析的依赖不断扩大，&lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source=prnewswire&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;农业&lt;/a>;至&lt;a href=&quot;https://www. weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/&quot;>;制造&lt;/a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed -data-network-partnerships&quot;>;医疗保健&lt;/a>;至&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial- services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot;>;金融服务&lt;/a>;，按理说，下一代数据领导者将发挥影响战略和决策的深远作用、操作和无数其他功能。为了帮助培养这种新人才，我开发了一个由四个关键技能和能力领域组成的框架，它将帮助当前和未来的数据科学家磨练他们的能力，为企业增加最大价值。这是通过确保数据科学工作被业务职能部门视为重要且不可或缺的来实现的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;使用此框架，并更好地了解每个业务领域的含义，当今的数据科学家和那些进入这个领域可以看到他们的知识和经验如何叠加，以及他们在哪些方面需要进一步发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1.发现问题：看到真正的问题&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当数据领导者深入研究整个业务的分析时，他们几乎在每个操作和职能中都处于前排位置。这为他们提供了解决问题和发现新问题的独特优势。这是一个现实世界的例子。一家中档连锁酒店的宾客关系主管因入住流程评价低而受到高层管理人员的批评。调查显示，客人认为办理入住手续管理不善、耗时太长，并且没有提供他们想要的结果，特别是无缝且愉快的体验。管理层还发现，入住评分较低的人返回酒店的比例较低。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;宾客关系部门联系数据分析团队，以找出入住问题的根源。即使他们查看客户人口统计数据、他们想要的房间类型以及他们是在前台、自助服务终端还是通过电话办理入住，以及一天中的时间、一年中的时间以及客户是否忠诚计划 - 数据团队无法确定根本原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，一名员工建议他们查看滚动收集的客户调查。一些自然语言文本分析揭示了一些主题——即酒店基础设施并不理想。客人抵达时可能会遇到 Wi-Fi 问题、房间钥匙有时无法使用、家具损坏或房间不干净。这些问题与入住没有直接关系，但客人将其归因于入住过程，因为他们记得的是这样的。底线 — 问题在于酒店的管理方式，而不是入住流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;要点：&lt;/strong>;解决摆在您面前的问题可能意味着错过寻找机会以其他方式帮助业务改进。那些使用数据的人通常可以获得对业务的许多方面的深入、独特的见解。为了善于发现问题，数据领导者需要拥抱大局观并获得更深入的见解，并提高对业务领导者最重要的事情的透明度。通过这种方式，数据领导者可以通过识别原本无法注意到的问题来增加价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2.问题范围：明确和具体&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一旦发现问题，下一步就是确定其范围，即明确问题的本质以及分析如何帮助解决问题。如果业务领导者向数据团队提出了模糊的担忧或挑战，这一点尤其重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我的课程和研讨会中，我们通过练习来练习范围界定。我扮演产品、战略或营销领导者的角色，脑子里有一个明确的问题。例如，也许我管理客户，并希望能够识别哪些客户有可能给出较低的净推荐值 (NPS) 评级，以便我们可以干预并改善他们的体验。任何理性的数据科学家都会知道如何选择正确的数据和数据科学技术来解决这个问题。但商界领袖很少这样说话。因此，我使用夸张的行话和过于笼统的术语来界定问题。它的内容是这样的：“我们正在努力实现客户满意度目标 - 我们需要将我们的市场战略归零。这可能是管道问题，但我们只是没有协调一致。我认为我们正在正确的沙盒中进行游戏，现在我们只需要知道是谁以及为什么。听起来不错？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;学生扮演数据科学家的角色，练习提出澄清性问题 - 可能从“你所说的‘一致性’是什么意思？”和“我们如何衡量客户满意度”开始目标？”以及“哪些指标表明我们已经成功（或失败）？”接下来是一个提取信息的迭代过程，以帮助制定一个可以通过数据分析工具和概念解决的明确定义的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我的首席分析官与客户的合作中，最重要的之一（并且具有挑战性）我工作的一部分就是将商业领袖头脑中的想法转化为一个范围广泛的商业问题。我有一个要问的探究性问题清单，例如：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;我们要解决的问题到底是什么？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;如果改进的话会产生什么结果，将表明问题实际上已得到解决？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;理想情况下可以使用哪些数据来解决问题，以及实际上可以使用哪些数据？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;分析将如何得出结果解决方案？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;回答最后一个问题可以说是最重要的部分，因为它将确定适当的分析技术 - 例如，一些简单的见解或更正式的预测或因果推理模型。在这里，我与业务团队一起经历了许多“假设”场景；例如，“如果结果显示这样或那样怎么办？这将如何帮助你做出更好的决定？”通常，企业领导者会试图回避这个问题，建议我们在获得分析结果后就可以考虑采取行动。这是一个错误 - 了解分析如何转化为解决方案是制定分析计划的关键部分。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;要点：&lt;/strong>;要擅长确定问题范围，数据领导者需要良好的沟通技巧，可以与业务领导者讨论问题，以获得必要的细节，使数据分析工具和概念能够为业务做出有意义的贡献。只有这样才能将问题交给数据团队进行分析。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3.问题引导：获取更新、收集反馈&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一旦问题被识别并确定范围，许多数据分析师就会陷入孤立状态，只有在找到解决方案后才会出现。这种方法是有很大问题的。为了最有效，这个过程需要大量的信息共享和设定期望——或者我所说的问题引导。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于数据领导者来说，这意味着让他们的团队能够更轻松地提供&lt;em >;向业务团队提供初步结果&lt;/em>;。每次交流都成为收集反馈的机会。例如，“业务团队对这些初步结果感兴趣吗？”以及“我们对术语的定义是否正确？”从一个更新到下一个更新，结果会随着顺序更新一起出现，直到项目结束。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种方法与一些数据科学家喜欢的工作方式背道而驰。有时他们会迷恋自己的模型和创造性的解决问题的技巧，并且迫不及待地等待重大揭晓。但“大揭露”是一种不好的做法——有适得其反的危险。最终演示中过多的惊喜可能会让观众处于守势。原因？令人惊讶的结果常常促使人们开始质疑底层数据和方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;每个数据模型都需要假设（例如，如何处理丢失的数据、如何处理异常值等）。如果积极进行分析的数据团队不提前披露和讨论他们的假设，而是等到最后，业务团队就会提出一堆问题并挑剔弱点。然而，通过让业务团队一路参与决策，他们就会相信结果并给予信任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多业务领导者与我分享，最好的最终数据交付成果是那些能够交付结果的数据。没有什么意外。他们一直与数据团队密切合作，最终的交付成果或演示文稿只是他们迄今为止工作的顶峰。这就是问题引导如何通过协作获得支持，从而暴露数据科学家需要做出的艰难选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;要点：&lt;/strong>;问题引导建立了一个提供过程定期更新并收集业务团队的反馈。在该领域实力雄厚的数据科学家和团队领导者能够鼓励和促进坦诚的讨论，确保最终的交付成果符合业务团队的要求，不会出现意外。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4.解决方案翻译：用观众的语言说话&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;此时，我们从问题过渡到解决方案，其成功取决于数据领导者及其团队在前三个步骤上的执行情况。数据团队不仅要确定最终答案，还必须提供易于理解、因此可操作的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这不仅仅是将数据放在图表或其他视觉显示中。相反，解决方案（无论是数据洞察还是模型推荐的新行动方案）必须以业务团队可以理解的语言来传达。我推荐的一种工具是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-go-from-awful-awesome-presenting-data-analytics-joel-shapiro/&quot;>;两页数据分析备忘录&lt;/a>;，突出显示了要解决的问题的最重要要素。虽然两页可能看起来非常简洁，特别是与数据团队经常生成的大量报告相比，但简洁是这个秘密武器背后的力量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;两页的限制可以避免继续下去的诱惑。了解数据分析的细节，并鼓励关注所提出的建议及其证据。我当然不是唯一一个主张缩短备忘录的人。亚马逊创始人杰夫·贝佐斯要求高管在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/04/23/what-jeff-bezos-learned-from-requiring-6-page-memos- at-amazon.html&quot;>;六页备忘录&lt;/a>;（相对于 PowerPoint 演示文稿），可以轻松消化和讨论。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;要点：&lt;/strong>;解决方案翻译需要数据领导者退后一步，考虑如何通过他们的分析和建议产生最大的影响。通过使用简单的语言，同时不影响复杂性，在该领域表现出色的数据领导者可以发表相当于电梯演讲的内容，以引人注目且易于理解的解决方案吸引业务领导者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着数据和分析变得越来越嵌入式在业务决策和解决方案中，数据团队必须不仅仅解决分配给他们的问题。数据领导者及其团队必须关注“协作和沟通”一词。这意味着要更加擅长担任更广泛的角色，帮助他们发现真正的问题，确定其性质和重要性，通过定期更新来引导流程，并交付和翻译真正产生影响的解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;!--引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target =&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx .最佳&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Inside PepsiCo&rsquo;s Effort to Reach Net Zero Emissions]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1316393475.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;对于像百事可乐这样的公司来说，大多数温室气体 (GHG) 排放都源自供应链，这对管理来说是一项挑战。百事公司相信三个要素：期望、经济和支持——对于有效的供应链参与和行动至关重要。明确的期望指导供应商合作伙伴，同时了解经济现实有助于创造有利可图的温室气体减排。最后，通过支持和资源为供应商提供帮助可以促进向共同的净零目标的平稳过渡。百事公司的计划反映了这些原则，开辟了一条通往可持续和有弹性的未来的道路。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-努力达到净零排放？language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;设定净零目标只是气候战略的开始。现在面临着取得实质性进展的压力。对于许多公司来说，大部分温室气体 (GHG) 排放位于其供应链业务范围之外，称为“范围 3”排放。了解、量化并最终管理这些排放是很困难的。虽然这些影响超出了公司的直接控制范围，但利益相关者的期望、报告框架和业务需求要求大公司激活其合作伙伴并取得进展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你能做对，回报会很高。这不仅是为了减少对地球的影响，也是为了建立一个价值链，使我们能够实现未来的增长，并能够应对气候变化。全球气候危机是我们启动&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pepsico.com/who-we-are/our-commitments/pepsico-positive&quot;>;百事积极 (pep+) &lt;/a>;转型的催化剂并设定了到 2040 年实现净零排放的目标。从那时起，百事公司已将供应链关系提升到新的协作水平，并制定了一系列战略，旨在让供应商合作伙伴加入我们的旅程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从根本上说，百事公司的业务植根于农业。气候变化将影响农作物，也会影响农民及其所能提供的产量。我们必须制定明确的业务战略，以管理我们对气候的影响，并使我们的公司在未来更具弹性和竞争力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在内部，我们不断努力将净零思维融入我们的团队。例如，百事公司通过将范围 1 和范围 2 的减排量纳入公司 200 名高管薪酬审查流程的一部分来激励进步，我们正在努力能够更准确地量化范围 3 的排放量，以便我们可以将该指标纳入其中&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;运营新时代&quot; dek=&quot;提高效率并增强弹性”。 cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style= &quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;运营新时代&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 提高效率并增强弹性。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;在我们的价值链中，拥有超过 100,000 个不同规模和能力的供应商，一个一刀切的方法无法实现净零所需的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;可以采取的方法有很多，我们也在此过程中吸取了教训。但我们相信，为了成功实现供应链合作伙伴的参与，以及更重要的是供应链合作伙伴的行动，您必须正确把握三个基本要素——期望、经济性和支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;期望&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与供应链合作伙伴设定明确且一致的期望是成功的基础。 Companies must let suppliers know emissions reductions are important, particularly when it is something that will be measured over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our agricultural supply chain, for example, farmers have different levels of understanding around emissions. Some are aware of climate change and its impacts, while for others, it isn&#39;t even on their radar screens. As leaders, we must provide clear and consistent guidelines for our suppliers and other supply-chain partners, so they can understand their role in our journey now and into the future. We set out these expectations at our annual Global Supplier Summit and are asking our partners to take four specific, near-term actions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Report Scope 1 &amp;amp; 2 emissions to us by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Set, or commit to setting, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sciencebasedtargets.org/how-it-works&quot;>;a science-based target (SBT)&lt;/a>; by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Convert PepsiCo&#39;s portion of electrical load to renewable electricity, where available, by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;For agricultural suppliers, collaborate with us to develop an action plan for sustainable ingredients and to build regenerative agriculture acres by the end 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Setting an SBT for emissions reductions provides a clear structure and framework. Tracking data across the value chain is vital to understanding the breadth and pace of progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a big shift for some of our suppliers&#39; operations. In some cases, this is not just about investment but also about making changes in the way they operate. More than ever, supplier relationships need to move from transactional to partnership. That&#39;s where companies can use their scale and knowledge to help suppliers&#39; transition – acting as partners and providing support along the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Economics&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When engaging supply-chain partners, companies often make the mistake of supporting them only with financial incentives (or disincentives). While economics are certainly critical, they come into play only after the foundation and expectations have been set.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the most powerful things to do is clarify for suppliers the economic realities and tradeoffs that come with GHG reductions. Decarbonization can be expensive, but the reality is it won&#39;t always cost more. Reducing inputs, such as water and fertilizer, minimizing plastic use, and investing in renewable energy can all save money. Companies can help their suppliers do the math and understand the concrete ways they can come out ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies must also consider how to better structure partnerships to lead toward a sustainable transition. Long-term agreements that incentivize and support sustainable transformation can be a great catalyst. PepsiCo signed a seven-and-a-half-year strategic commercial agreement with ADM to share costs and resources and closely collaborate on projects that aim to significantly expand regenerative agriculture by up to 2 million acres by 2030 across our shared North American supply chains. The length of the contract helps to instill confidence to invest in sustainable practices as well as achieving carbon reduction goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Enablement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When it comes to net zero, the challenges are too complex and interconnected to leave implementation up to chance. As partners, we have offered guidance to help enable our suppliers as they navigate the interplay of strategies so that they can more easily make progress against our shared goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, we&#39;ve created programs to guide on setting SBTs and have provided resources that outline different options for emissions reductions, particularly in moving to renewable electricity, as this can vary based on each supplier&#39;s situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies, like PepsiCo, can also help solve sustainability challenges by using their scale and networks to invest in, and scale-up, promising start-ups and leverage relationships with some of the largest companies in the world.&amp;nbsp; In doing so, making them more cost-efficient and accessible to our partners. For agriculture technologies, we are doing trials of promising solutions on demonstration farms around the world and investing in suppliers that we believe can make a real impact. For farmers, proven approaches are key to achieving buy-in and implementing solutions quickly and effectively. Through our pep+ REnew program, we are also working towards helping our supply-chain partners with aggregated buys of renewable energy to create scale and cost efficiencies that individual suppliers cannot achieve on their own.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Creating a sustainable value chain is difficult, but with the right approach, it is a powerful means to meet sustainability goals, create a more resilient organization and fuel improved business performance. At PepsiCo, that&#39;s our end game, and the three fundamental elements – expectations, economics and enablement – will set us, as well as our supply chain partners, on the path to truly sustainable growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop Overworking After Vacation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1438950079.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;After a vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for &amp;#8220;lost&amp;#8221; time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&amp;#8217;re still valuable to the organization. Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? The authors offer several strategies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As summer winds down and many of our coaching clients and research participants are returning from vacation, we&#39;re seeing increased levels of return-to-work anxiety. As one client, “Leslie,” put it:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Coming back from vacation almost makes [it] seem not worth it. For me, it&#39;s like psychologically accelerating from a cruising pace of 30 mph to a speed of 80 so I can get through my inbox, catch up on all the meetings I missed, and reconnect with my neglected clients. And that&#39;s on top of the guilt I&#39;ve been feeling about overburdening my team while they&#39;ve been covering for me.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to respond to these intense feelings like Leslie did, by throwing yourself into &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest&quot;>;overworking&lt;/a>;, overcompensating, and overachieving the minute you disable your out of office responder — especially in work cultures that don&#39;t exactly encourage time off in the first place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, there&#39;s a healthier, more balanced approach that can help you ease back into your routine without losing all the stress-reducing and performance-enhancing benefits of unplugging from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Time Off Is Essential&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s be clear that taking periodic breaks in order to reset and recover from work stress (what researchers refer to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;work recovery&lt;/a>;) isn&#39;t a “nice to have” — it&#39;s essential for sustained performance and growth. Just as athletes engage in regular periods of rest and recovery in order to perform at their best and avoid injury, workers need periods of time away from their jobs to recuperate from the strain of work and replenish their physical and mental energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that those who don&#39;t take the opportunity to rest, recharge, and recover are at higher risk of exhaustion, low motivation, poor performance, and burnout, while those who engage in regular periods of work recovery enjoy better sleep, higher job satisfaction, more engagement, and higher job performance. Human bodies and brains simply aren&#39;t built to endure chronic stress, and there&#39;s plenty of evidence showing how disconnecting from the strains and demands of work not only lowers stress, but increases &lt;a href=&quot;https://kops.uni-konstanz.de/server/api/core/bitstreams/63f6ae78-86f7-47fc-96b1-17654a0d2bf6/content&quot;>;productivity&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8733151/&quot;>;boosts creativity&lt;/a>;. Even &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9432722/&quot;>;micro-breaks&lt;/a>; taken throughout the workday, such as stretching, doing some deep breathing exercises, or stepping outside for some fresh air, can halt the stress cycle and return you to baseline.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the clear benefits of time away, however, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/03/30/how-americans-view-their-jobs&quot;>;nearly half&lt;/a>; of American workers don&#39;t take all the paid time off their employer offers. Chief among their reasons are worries that they&#39;ll fall behind, or that time off will hurt their chances for advancement or even increase their risk of losing their job, as well as guilt over coworkers having to take on additional work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These are sentiments we hear often, including from our senior executive clients, who frequently express a fear of losing momentum if they step away. Part of our role as executive coaches is empowering clients to invest in themselves and their performance with the practice of regular work recovery.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Resisting the Urge to Overwork After Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Post-vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for “lost” time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&#39;re still valuable to the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? Here are some strategies that have worked for our research participants and clients:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Shift to a performance mindset.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;High performance and sufficient recovery were never meant to function separately, yet in the corporate world, performance tends to be overemphasized while recovery is overlooked. Rather than treating time away as a last resort only &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; you&#39;re depleted and unproductive, or as a special reward when your to-do list is finally done, take a cue from top athletes and include work recovery as &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-to-recover-from-work-stress-according-to-science&quot;>;an essential component&lt;/a>; of a high-performance strategy. Work recovery works best when it&#39;s practiced regularly and consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Prevent or ease “reentry shock.”&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;“Reentry shock” refers to the discombobulation you feel when you transition from a place of calm and equilibrium to one that pulls you into the frazzle and fray. You can prevent this by using buffers. Schedule a free day between your return from vacation and your return to work so you can mentally and physically prepare for the change in environment. Keep your calendar light just after your return, which will give you a chance to reacclimate and avoid overwork. For example, one of our clients has a two-day “no meetings” buffer after his return.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Bring some vacation magic home with you.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;What exactly was it during your period of recovery that helped you decompress and feel more like yourself? Was it exercise? Reconnecting with loved ones? An artistic pursuit or hobby that&#39;s neglected during the work week? Simply enjoying some unscheduled leisure time? As much as possible, build these activities and conditions into your normal weekly routine. Remember, even small doses of downtime make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Before saying yes to new requests when you return to work, consider what&#39;s getting in your way of saying no.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Are you concerned about not being recognized, rewarded, or promoted? If so, stop, breathe, and check your assumptions. It may be possible to get the recognition and rewards you&#39;re looking for without overcommitting yourself and sacrificing your health and well-being. If you can&#39;t identify the problem areas — or if you need help figuring out what to do about them — consider working with a coach.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Review, communicate, and maintain your boundaries.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Returning from a recovery period is a great time to review and refresh your work boundaries. Let everyone know when you will and will not be available for work, and if work demands begin to creep past your role or your comfort level, speak with leadership about shifting responsibilities, or see if you can delegate. Boundaries should help define others&#39; expectations of your role, and they should protect your downtime and allow you to mentally detach from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Leave a toxic work environment that discourages time away or that rewards employees for excessive hours and self-sacrifice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This kind of unhealthy work environment will leave you ripe for exhaustion and burnout. If you can&#39;t leave right away, start creating an exit strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Preventing the Urge to Overwork Before Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Next time you&#39;re planning to take time off, try in advance to make things easier for future you. Weeks before you leave, arrange for who&#39;s covering your responsibilities during your absence, and include their contact information in your out-of-office message. Set clear expectations for when/if you should be contacted during vacation. Structure a reentry routine ahead of time so you can plug into an existing process and more easily get back into work mode. Finally, consider conducting a premortem before finalizing your plans. What specific challenges or failures&amp;nbsp;might you expect or imagine?&amp;nbsp;What were their main causes? What was not yet accounted for? And ultimately, what additional preventive steps can you take now? This simple but powerful process helps further refine your pre–time off planning, which can prevent most reentry problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Periodic time away from work is one of the best ways to ensure that you&#39;ll be able to sustain your energy and productivity. With some planning before your time away and some sensible guardrails after your return, you can bring all the stress-lowering benefits of work recovery back with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Accelerating Digital Integration in Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_06_16aIvW0lxOk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Unsplash; A Mokhtari/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Regional integration, similar to the European Union&amp;#8217;s, has been cited as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration. Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate Africa&amp;#8217;s digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 2021, the combined &lt;a href=&quot;https://statisticstimes.com/economy/africa-gdp.php#:~:text=GDP%20of%20Africa&amp;amp;text=The%20African%20economy%2C%20comprising%2054,largest%20economy%20in%20the%20world.&quot;>;GDP of Africa&#39;s 54 countries&lt;/a>; was less than 15% of the United States&#39; GDP. The continent consists of many relatively small countries, economies, and markets, which is a disadvantage on the world stage, where countries with huge populations and GDPs wield the most influence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. Regional integration, similar to the European Union&#39;s, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/news-and-events/importance-of-regional-and-continental-integration-for-africas-development-18773&quot;>;been cited&lt;/a>; as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this context, “digital integration” refers to creating shared systems and standard rules for digitalization across Africa. It entails digital cooperation, particularly in finance, governance, and security. In practice, digital integration will feature concepts such as a harmonized digital financial system, consistent continent-wide laws for digital activities, and shared regulatory technology like identity verification, electronic taxation, and business registration systems. Among other things, digital integration will facilitate optimal trade, resulting in cost savings, better information flow for improved participation in global commerce, and greater market access, particularly for small businesses, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/edar2022&quot;>;dominate trade in Africa&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate this digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Private Sector Collaboration&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many private African organizations have successfully established themselves across national boundaries, driven by profit-making ambitions and unrestricted by bureaucracy or politics. Despite inherent challenges, corporations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/organizations/naspers-limited&quot;>;Naspers&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtn.com/about/&quot;>;MTN Group&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ecobank.com/group/about-us/history&quot;>;Ecobank&lt;/a>;, for example, have found ways to expand across national borders. They can serve as reference points and potential partners for the digital integration of Africa&#39;s economies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fostering digital integration requires collaborations between these private players, governments, and regional bodies. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://papss.com/&quot;>;Pan-African Payment and Settlement System&lt;/a>; (PAPSS) demonstrates that this approach is feasible. While PAPSS is the product of a partnership between the African Union and the African Export-Import Bank, it depends on a network of some of Africa&#39;s largest private commercial banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A centralized payment and settlement system for intra-African commerce, officially introduced in January 2022, PAPSS facilitates continental commerce and deeper economic integration. It enables payments for intra-African trade transactions in local currencies (Africa has roughly 42 currencies), reducing expenses and accelerating trade settlement and payment. Before PAPSS, the typical payment route between two African countries required that an African currency be first exchanged for dollars, pounds, or euros and then swapped a second time for a different African currency. This raises the cost of intra-African currency transactions by an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/09/Digital-Journeys-Africa-freeing-foreign-exchange-wellisz&quot;>;estimated $5 billion&lt;/a>; each year.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Building for Interoperability&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Building continent-wide digital systems will take time and significant resources, but immediately prioritizing interoperability could create the foundation for digital integration. Thus, public digital systems being built in African countries should be interoperable — that is, have capabilities for the exchange and use of information with other similar systems in other countries. Inevitably, some economies and sectors move faster than others with digitalization. Therefore, building with interoperability in mind will allow for easy integration in the near future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With identity systems, for example, an ideal scenario would be for ID obtained in Nigeria to be easily digitally verifiable by a bank in Namibia. This would be possible if Nigeria&#39;s digital identity system had the capacity for interoperability. Moreover, interoperable ID systems across the continent would allow for continent-wide know-your-customer systems, enabling access to financial services anywhere in Africa and thus making intra-African commerce easier.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, interoperable public systems require significant policy and regulatory interventions. Governments and regional bodies must address challenges such as harmonizing standards, enhancing current legal frameworks, and adopting cybersecurity, consumer, and data protection regulations to facilitate successful interoperability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Power and Internet&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Digital integration has no chance if digital services are only accessible to a fraction of the population, as in many African countries. While physical infrastructure like roads, rails, and ports connecting the continent is critical to Africa&#39;s physical integration, power and the internet will determine the success of digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many African countries still have less than half of their population as internet users, with countries such as Burundi and the Central African Republic having &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1124283/internet-penetration-in-africa-by-country/&quot;>;less than 15%&lt;/a>; internet penetration. Similarly, 600 million people, or&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/africa-energy-outlook-2022/key-findings&quot;>; 43% of the entire African population&lt;/a>;, do not have access to electricity, with the majority living in sub-Saharan Africa. Therefore, accelerating universal access to power and the internet should become a priority.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Africa desperately needs digital integration, but it&#39;s critical to recognize its inherent difficulties — for example, concerns about sovereignty and divergent national objectives. What&#39;s more, active steps toward digital integration require deliberate government commitment, which requires governments to recognize their importance and have the resources to pursue them.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Negotiate Your Salary in the Age of Pay Transparency Laws]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_06_7aWvQdR36Y0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&amp;#8217;s possible. But how should you negotiate for yourself when a pay band is exceptionally large? In this article, the author shares insights from two experts on compensation and negotiation. They recommend not focusing on &amp;#8220;fairness&amp;#8221; &lt;/span>;when making your case, but rather &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;focusing the conversation on yours and the employer&amp;#8217;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Having more information to gauge your worth should, in theory, give you more leverage in salary negotiations. But the reality is complicated. Companies could be less willing to stray from their set ranges, and you might feel hesitant to push for fear of looking unreasonable. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;How should you approach salary conversations in this new era of pay transparency laws? What&#39;s the best way to advocate for yourself when the pay band is exceptionally large? And is it better to be direct or subtle? &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;What the Experts Say&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/3-new-us-employment-regulations-that-companies-should-prepare-for-now&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pay transparency laws&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; vary from state to state,&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; but in a nutshell, they require employers to disclose information about pay, such as salary ranges, in job postings or in offers to candidates. The aim is to create more visibility in pay practices and &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/how-salary-transparency-can-help-you-and-your-workplace&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;help close gender and racial wage gaps&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For job seekers, the upshot is more agency in salary negotiations, says D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;avid Buckmaster, the author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Pay-Raise-Stronger-Businesses/dp/1665098317&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Fair Pay&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, who&#39;s worked on employee compensation projects for companies including Nike and Starbucks&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. Before these laws existed, Buckmaster says that compensation was like a mysterious black box. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Job candidates&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; were in the dark about what comparable employees made and how the company benchmarked salaries to the rest of the market,” he says. “Now, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;having a pay range takes away some of those unknowns.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The downside is that it can cause job seekers to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;hyper-fixate on salary&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, rather than the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/negotiating-your-next-job&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;big picture of an employment offer&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, according to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Victoria Medvec, a professor at the Kellogg School of Management at Northwestern and author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Negotiate-without-Fear-Strategies-Maximize/dp/1119719097&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiate Without Fear&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Your pay is a piece of it, but there are other aspects of the job to consider like your role, responsibilities, benefits, and flexibility,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here are some tips to help you navigate the conversation and get the compensation you deserve.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Appreciate your newfound power.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-ask-for-what-you-want-and-get-it&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating your salary&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; requires information, tact, confidence — and the right mindset, says &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec.&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “Knowledge is power, and&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;y&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ou now have an advantage because you know what&#39;s possible.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While some salary bands might seem too broad to be useful, they underscore the power of negotiation, she says. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The range exists because &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiation is a dynamic interaction between the employee and employer and &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;some people do it more effectively.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;After all, she says, it&#39;s not &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/how-women-can-get-what-they-want-in-a-negotiation&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;just about being willing to ask for more&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, it&#39;s also about having the information and self-assurance to make your case.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Don&#39;t get in your own head and don&#39;t be intimidated or discouraged — even if a certain number feels out of reach, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;adds Buckmaster. For example, if you make $70,000 and you&#39;re being offered a comparable job with a listed range of $100,000-$150,000, you might feel as if you can&#39;t ask for the top of the range. But the fact is, your current salary has little bearing on what another company is willing to pay you, he says: “What you made before &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;doesn&#39;t matter.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do your research.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your goal is to go into the negotiation with an objective, realistic understanding of how the employer views your market value. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This requires some homework to figure out where you might land within the company&#39;s published&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; compensation &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;bands: at the top, in the middle, or toward the bottom. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Before pay transparency laws existed, people may have assumed that HR has been randomly throwing darts at a dartboard to determine what people got paid, but there&#39;s rigor behind the numbers,” says Buckmaster. He says that behind the listed range lies an “approval matrix” that&#39;s invisible to candidates. “Every company has a trigger point that requires extra approvals to justify placing someone at the very top of the range.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;on&#39;t be disheartened; rather, use that &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/work-speak-the-right-way-to-negotiate&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;knowledge to make a compelling case&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; for yourself. Visit j&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ob search websites and databases, such as Glassdoor, Ladders, and Salary.com, and talk to recruiters and industry colleagues. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Take a good, hard look at your experience and qualifications and be honest about your work history. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Evaluate your actual job level and the scope of your past responsibilities. De-emphasize titles. Being a director at a startup is not the same as being one at a large company,” Buckmaster says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Be savvy about the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many, but not all, &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/04/15-rules-for-negotiating-a-job-offer&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;salary negotiations take place&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; after the company has extended an offer. But you might consider signaling your salary expectations earlier in the process if you think your pay ought to be on the high-end of the range, says Buckmaster. He suggests saying something along the lines of, “I&#39;m looking forward to seeing the offer and trust that my starting position in your pay range will align with my significant experience doing this work at XYZ company.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Once the company has made an offer, the opportunity to negotiate for more is usually quite narrow, so Buckmaster advises making your case wisely. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Don&#39;t go back multiple times, otherwise it might affect your reputation on the way in,” he says. “You don&#39;t want to come across as being challenging to work with.” Make your argument concise, crisp, and reasonable. “Most companies don&#39;t want to have custom, complicated negotiations with everyone who comes in.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;State your case…&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating a higher salary requires clearly articulating why you&#39;re worth more. Medvec recommends&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; focusing on your &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;differentiators: your background, skill set, and special abilities that match the company&#39;s needs. You&#39;ve &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/5-ways-to-stand-out-in-your-next-job-interview&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;already outlined your past achievements&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; in the hiring process&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, of course. Now it&#39;s time to talk about how you&#39;ll add value in the future — and how that should be reflected in your pay. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec suggests laying out how you&#39;ll help the company generate new lines of revenue, cut costs, attract talent, or enter new markets. “Talk about your exact role and responsibilities, including what specifically you&#39;ll be doing,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pinpointing how &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/10/to-land-a-great-job-talk-about-why-you-love-your-work&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;you&#39;re going to tackle their challenges&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; puts you in a stronger position, she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Bear in mind that approval matrix, adds Buckmaster. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Help the recruiter tell your story internally,” he says. “Make their job easier with solid arguments oriented around the business. Otherwise they&#39;re going to have a hard time getting it approved.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;… and bring your A-game if you&#39;re aiming extra high.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While it&#39;s possible to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiate above the stated pay range, your case has to be bulletproof. Many companies are comfortable with roughly 5% of their employees being paid over the maximum, according to Buckmaster. Pay bands are not an exact science and “sometimes people break the system and end up with higher salaries,” he says. This can happen for many reasons. Perhaps the new hire is joining a smaller company, or maybe their manager is more like a peer, or maybe the new employee is taking on a specialized role, or perhaps they know esoteric coding language that the company needs. “Or it could be that they&#39;re uniquely gifted and hard to get,” he says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;A word of warning though: If you&#39;re paid over the maximum, you might be ineligible for salary increases in the future, so be sure to inquire about the company&#39;s policies. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For senior roles, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; recommends booking a half hour with an employment lawyer in the city where the company is based. “Find out not just how much others ask for, but also what&#39;s in their contracts, like stock, equity, and employment guarantees,” she says. “It will be an expensive 30 minutes, but well worth it for senior-level jobs.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t focus on “fairness,” but rather mutual interests.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;P&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ay-transparency laws were created to help ensure equitable compensation, but it&#39;s not a good idea to frame your individual negotiation around fairness, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;according to Medvec. “Don&#39;t create a rationale based on what&#39;s right or what&#39;s fair,” she says. Instead, “reference information about what others earn to anchor your request, but keep the conversation focused on the employer&#39;s interests.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For example, Medvec recommends saying something along the lines of: “I know from publicly available information that this role pays up to $190,000. I believe I&#39;m at the top end of that pay range because I&#39;m uniquely positioned to do XYZ, and I&#39;m confident in what I bring to the table. But I&#39;m also comfortable getting a base salary of $160,00 with a $50,000 annual bonus when I achieve the objectives that are important to you.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This way, you&#39;re making strategic compromises that benefit both you and the organization.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Principles to Remember&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Appreciate your newfound advantage. Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&#39;s possible.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Carve out time to do your homework so you can build a strong argument for the salary you want.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Make sure the recruiter can tell your story to the decision-makers by framing your argument in terms of the business.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Doubt yourself even if a certain number feels out of reach. If you think you&#39;re worth it, make a strong, rational case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Belabor what&#39;s fair or what&#39;s right; &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;rather, focus the conversation on yours and the employer&#39;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;M&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ake the mistake of assuming you can negotiate indefinitely; companies usually have a clear process and don&#39;t want a drawn-out back-and-forth.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is India the World&rsquo;s Next Great Economic Power?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_05_638755428.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论工作人员/anand purohit/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;印度经济崛起是不可避免的吗？有充分的理由认为，最新一轮的印度乐观主义可能与之前的迭代有所不同，但该国仍然面临着兑现这一承诺的重大挑战。就驱动因素而言，需求“以消费繁荣、适合环境的创新和绿色转型的形式——和供应&amp;#8212;以人口红利、融资渠道和重大基础设施升级的形式——正在帮助推动国家前进。政策改革、地缘政治定位和侨民红利促进了这一点。即便如此，该国仍面临成功的障碍，包括增长不平衡、人口潜力未实现、营商便利性和创新潜力未实现。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div >; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power? language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;2002年，印度政府推出了无处不在的国际旅游业这场运动被称为“不可思议的印度”。如果今天发起类似的活动，不妨称之为“不可避免的印度”。不仅是印度国内的狂热分子，还有全球分析师齐声宣称印度是下一个经济大国：高盛预测印度将成为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages /how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html&quot;>;到 2075 年成为世界第二大经济体，&lt;/a>; 以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft .com/content/c9de715e-2e29-4a7f-880b-1509c04bf11b&quot;>;《金融时报》的 Martin Wolf 表示&lt;/a>;，到 2050 年，其购买力将比美国高 30%&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们有以前也经历过类似的印度乐观主义浪潮。但即使是最热心的印度拥护者，实际的现实仍然让他们感到沮丧。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/04/28/india-revolutions-economy-growth-future/&quot;>;大胆预测&lt;/a>;它将超越中国（一个经济体）仍比印度大五倍），麦肯锡 2007 年&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/asia-pacific/the-bird-of-gold&quot;>;“金鸟”&lt;/印度消费者的承诺从未完全兑现，到放松管制、随之而来的政策逆转和与印度做生意的信心危机，再到大流行的毁灭性时期，该国承诺的不可避免的崛起仍然难以捉摸。现在有什么不同？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;印度商业生态系统的不同方面汇聚了一些积极的趋势：需求、供应和全系统的促进因素；结合起来，它们可以超越经济周期、宏观冲击和政策逆转。有些是新的，而较旧的已经达到临界质量，它们最终可以相互加强，创建一个&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/the-flywheel.html&quot;>;增长飞轮&lt;/一个>;。但与所有飞轮一样，重要的是要对嘎嘎声和燃烧气味保持警惕，而在印度，这些声音大量存在。企业和政府领导人都必须在飞轮损坏之前予以关注并采取行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;需求&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;三股力量正在需求侧汇聚，为印度的经济增长提供动力。&lt;/p>; >; &lt;h3>;消费繁荣&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;任何有关印度承诺的讨论的出发点始终是印度消费者的承诺。印度拥有 14 亿人口和无数未满足的需求，其增长速度&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy .html&quot;>;主要由国内消费和投资驱动&lt;/a>;。实际工资预计将增长 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/01/apac-salary-asia-leads-2023-real-wage-growth-jumps-in-india-china .html&quot;>;4.6%&lt;/a>;，而可支配收入将继续增长超过&lt;a href=&quot;https://tradingeconomics.com/india/disposable-personal-venue&quot;>;15%&lt;/a>; 。在西方成熟的行业在印度正在快速增长：例如，私人健康保险几乎统计数据/&quot;>;2015 年至 2021 年期间增长了两倍&lt;/a>;，而耐用消费品预计将在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisil.com/en/home/newsroom/press-releases/2022/09 之间增长/volume-vault-to-lift-consumer-durables-revenue-15-18-percent.html&quot;>;今年分别为 15% 和 18%&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;适合具体情况的创新&lt;/h3 >; &lt;p>;国际公司一直在努力了解印度“中产阶级”的构成并制定适当的价值主张。而&lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/middle-class-nearly-1/3rd-of-indias-population-to-be-2/3rds-by-2047- report/articleshow/95239621.cms&quot;>;一些分析师&lt;/a>;认为，三分之一的印度人是“中产阶级”，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021 /03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrink-and-poverty-spreads-while-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;6600万&lt;/a>;是真正的“中等收入”全球标准，而巨大的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrinks-and-poverty-spreads -而-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;11.6亿&lt;/a>;属于低收入。然而，第二类人中的许多人构成了一个巨大的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/be53790c-ea16-4e5c-9410-bac189fb2636&quot;>;有抱负的消费阶层&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这有很多含义。一方面，在印度竞争意味着以低得多的价格销售，这反过来又需要以竞争对手难以模仿的方式重新配置活动、生产和供应链。印度最畅销的汽车是 Wagon R，售价 7,000 美元，由日本铃木公司制造，该公司&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/10/31/business/corporate- business/suzuki-india-market-share/&quot;>;印度 41% 的市场份额&lt;/a>;在全球汽车行业中属于异常值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也就是说，&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.firstpost.com/entertainment/explained-why-netflix-is-failing-big-time-in-india-10580421.html&quot;>;Netflix 通过在该国的挫折而发现&lt;/a>;，它需要的不仅仅是低价格在印度取胜。本地化内容、使用多种印度语言以及利用印度消费者想要的产品之间的协同效应（就像亚马逊或迪士尼所做的那样）至关重要。在一个截然不同的领域，麦当劳整合了素食选择、印度小吃和多代家庭菜单，构建了切合实际的价值主张。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那些能够破解印度消费者密码的人将获得丰厚的回报：许多麦当劳在印度的特许经营商都是亿万富翁。家用电器制造商 Havells 推出了一系列“适合印度”的产品，例如净水器和无压缩机空气冷却器，这些产品既满足印度消费者的需求，又满足印度消费者的承受能力。自上市30年来，&lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/havells-india-ltd/stocks/companyid-10507.cms&quot;>;Havells&lt;/a>;利润增长了826倍，市值暴涨5800倍。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;绿色转型&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;印度对绿色转型的迫切需求，成为新兴的需求增长源。其经济潜力的规模意味着其能源需求将是巨大的。作为第三大能源消费国，它已经&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investindia.gov.in/sector/renewable-energy#:~:text=印度的%20installed%20renewable%20energy%20capacity ，增加%20of%209.83%25%20in%202022。&quot;>;可再生能源装机容量世界第四&lt;/a>;。该国制定了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/india-s-clean-energy-transition-is-rapidly-underway-benefiting-the-entire-world&quot;>;雄心勃勃的目标&lt;/ a>;：到 2030 年，安装 500 吉瓦的可再生能源产能，每年生产 500 万吨绿色氢，减少 45% 的排放，同时减少 10 亿吨二氧化碳。 weforum.org/docs/WEF_Mission_2070_A_Green_New_Deal_for_a_Net_Zero_India_2021.pdf&quot;>;世界经济论坛 2021 年报告&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;预计到 2070 年，印度将新增 5000 万个“绿色经济”就业岗位（这意味着更多的消费者），并带来 15 万亿美元的经济机会，到 2030 年将达到 1 万亿美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;供应&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;供应方面也汇聚了多种积极力量。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;人口统计股息&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;供给方故事的一部分是旧闻：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_in/india-at-100/reaping-the-demographic-dividend &quot;>;到 2030 年&lt;/a>;，印度的劳动年龄人口预计将达到 10.4 亿，抚养比将达到历史最低的 31.2%，占全球劳动力增量的不到四分之一。劳动年龄人口激增预计将持续到 2055 年。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“亚洲奇迹”就是在利用这一趋势的基础上建立起来的：日本于 1964 年进入这一最佳点，韩国于 1967 年，中国于 1994 年进入这一最佳点。印度还拥有世界上最多的说英语的 STEM 毕业生。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;获得金融服务&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;印度的金融市场状况比以往任何时候都好。随着中国机遇的降温，投资者需要替代方案，而印度是最接近的。相比之下，MSCI 印度指数今年上涨了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/india-investing-china-stocks-growth-exports-demgraphics-31252a80&quot;>;12%&lt;/a>; MSCI 新兴市场指数为 2%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;银行资产负债表为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/with-stronger-balance-sheets- indias-banking-sector-at-an-inflection-point/articleshow/96702845.cms&quot;>;走强&lt;/a>;，信贷市场运转良好。很明显，许多印度银行&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/finance/banks/news/indian-banks-better-placed-than-their-us-peers-due-to-attractive- valuations-and-stickier-deposits/articleshow/98859627.cms&quot;>;估值高于&lt;/a>;美国同行。 HDFC 银行与其母公司抵押贷款机构 HDFC 合并，市值达 1,710 亿美元，成为美国第四大金融公司。世界。甚至在合并之前，这家 29 岁的新贵就比 154 年历史的高盛更有价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种变化甚至在传统上资金不足的非正规部门也能看到，该部门占非正规部门的 86% 以上。印度的劳动力。印度领先的投资银行 Avendus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avendus.com/crypted_pdf_path/msme-lending-report-formattedvf-img-642a719b97ccc-.pdf&quot;>;计算&lt;/a>;，印度小中型企业部门的债务总需求为1.5万亿美元。其中，有 7,250 亿美元因缺乏抵押品而无法解决，而正规信贷只能提供约 2,890 亿美元。这激励贷方深化其产品。小企业贷款机构的新信贷客户比例从 2017 年的 9% 上升了 34%。小企业贷款机构的贷款在过去两年中每年猛增 43%。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;基础设施升级，无论是物理和数字&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;任何访问过印度的人都会印象深刻的一个关键障碍是其落后的基础设施。从历史上看，&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/programmes/from_our_own_correspondent/9483756.stm&quot;>;投资施舍&lt;/a>;在政治上可能更为有利，但现任政府的受欢迎程度赋予它&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/modi-should-focus-on-people-not-just-big-projects/2023/02/06/ceb85dc4-a66b-11ed- b2a3-edb05ee0e313_story.html&quot;>;基础设施投资有更大的余地&lt;/a>;。资本支出占政府总支出的百分比已从 2010 年的 11% 增加到今年预计的 22%。今年的基础设施支出将增长 33%，达到 1,220 亿美元。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;结果是惊人的。印度已新增 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;10,000 公里的高速公路每年。自 2014 年以来，印度机场数量&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot; >;翻倍&lt;/a>;并且升级后的火车系统将有&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-运输升级&quot;>;连接印度经济中心的新高效“货运走廊&lt;/a>;”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，最显着的变化之一是数字基础设施。与 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/info-tech/indias-internet-subscribers-increased-to-88125-million-as-of-march-end-trai-report/article67219636.ece&quot;印度拥有超过 8.8125 亿互联网用户&lt;/a>;，拥有世界第二多的互联网用户，仅次于中国&lt;a href=&quot;http://english.scio.gov.cn/m/pressroom/2022-11/ 07/content_78506468.htm&quot;>;10.5亿&lt;/a>;。依靠这种访问，有一个&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-case-for-investing-in-digital-public-infrastruct&quot;>;数字公共基础设施&lt;/a>;——其他国家正在研究的一个模型— 结合了人口规模的独特身份系统、实现数字支付无缝的支付接口以及数据管理系统，公民可以通过该系统在线访问重要文件，例如税务文件、疫苗接种证书等。所有这些都有助于公开更广泛的人口更容易获得服务和信贷。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为由此产生的变化的指标，印度有 &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/gadgets-news/ india-tops-world-ranking-in-digital- payments-beats-china-by-huge-margin-report/articleshow/100944643.cms&quot;>;在数字支付方面以巨大优势击败中国，位居榜首&lt;/a>;。有趣的是，印度的支付量超过了紧随其后的四个主要国家的数字支付总和。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;促进者&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;除了这些正在发挥作用的力量之外，还有几个全系统的促进者&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;国内政策改革&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;许多&lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/india/1734728/india-may-soon-achieve-modis-ease- of-doing-business-goal&quot;>;监管和政策改革&lt;/a>;已经到位，从实施 2016 年破产法到废除 39,000 多项法规以促进营商便利化。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;许多其他改革，例如建筑许可和电力连接，是州政府的职责范围，并且这些层面上也有变革的动力。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/05/11/how-indias-states-compete-for-investment&quot;>;各州政府正在通过帮助加快进程来参与竞争&lt;/a>;设立企业，提供投资激励，甚至吸引竞争企业集群，从而在全国更多地区创造更加有利于营商的环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;地缘政治最佳点&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;另一次转型对于印度来说，这是一种更加独特的地缘政治定位，最重要的是，它是由中国与西方经济体，特别是美国之间日益扩大的裂痕引发的。这正在为印度转化为新的商机，最明显的是——&lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-65784719&quot;>;苹果智能手机的制造&lt;/a>;。以每年生产 2000 万部 iPhone 的目标，仅一个这样的项目就将创造 50,000 个新就业岗位。此外，在用于航天发射的军用级技术方面，印度作为东道主的信心比中国更大，并且已经有了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07 /04/business/india-space-startups.html&quot;>;蓬勃发展的生态系统&lt;/a>;到位。自 2020 年以来，印度已举办&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_foreign_satellites_launched_by_India&quot;>;111 次国际太空发射&lt;/a>;，并成功&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes .com/interactive/2023/science/india-moon-landing-photos.html&quot;>;八月下旬，月球车登陆月球&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑另一个突出的例子，芯片制造商美光科技技术，&lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.micron.com/news-releases/news-release-details/micron-announces-new-semiconductor-assemble-and-test-facility&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>;计划建设新的组装和测试设施，作为中国以外地区多元化举措的一部分。事实上，世界银行新任行长表示，印度实现&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-should-cash-china-plus- one-strategy-world-bank-chief-2023-07-19/#:~:text=In%20recent%20years%2C%20many%20companies,World%20Bank%20chief%20last%20month.&quot;>;“兑现” &lt;/a>; 公司寻求供应链和制造多元化，摆脱对中国的严重依赖，背后的增长趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;侨民股息&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;值得注意的是，两位首席执行官美光科技公司的总裁和世界银行行长都是印度出生的，这让我们想到了第三个关键推动者：印度侨民，他们现在是世界上规模最大、影响力前所未有的群体。仅在商业世界就说明了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/06/12/indias-diaspora-is-bigger-and-more-influenceial-than-any- in-history&quot;>;标准普尔 500 强公司中有 25 位首席执行官出生于印度。除此之外，许多公司的高级管理层都是印度人。这是&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.economictimes.com/tech/startups/indians-are-driven-the-us-startup-story-nfap-study/india-is-the-leading-country-of -origin-for-immigrant-Founders-of-us-unicorns/slideshow/93165270.cms&quot;>;美国独角兽移民创始人的主要原籍国&lt;/a>;。这些联系有助于建立与印度企业的全球联系，并促进印度融入全球价值链。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;障碍&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;虽然这些因素相辅相成，但许多障碍仍然存在 — — 它们可能会导致乘数效应达到失速的效果。考虑一下道路上的三个主要障碍以及所需采取的行动。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;增长不平衡&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;尽管国家层面的增长数字令人印象深刻，但经济效益却非常不平等。印度前 10% 的人拥有 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;77%&lt;/a>; 的国民财富。仅因为医疗保健费用，几乎&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;每秒就有 2 人&lt;/a>;陷入贫困。印度的人口密度是世界上最高的之一，加剧了资源分配和环境压力的零和性质。区域失衡——印度南部和西部的增长速度比印度北部和东部快 12%——随着时间的推移将会加剧。在这种语言断层之上，新的地区间紧张局势可能会浮现出来。处理这些问题需要对政治经济进行灵活的管理。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于政治分歧，其他失衡现象也在加剧。一种日益自信的形式&lt;a href=&quot;https://frontline.thehindu.com/columns/india-this-side-ganesh-devy-putting-the-useless-to-use-the-divisive-politics-of- the-word-hindutva/article67045226.ece&quot;>;印度教意识形态&lt;/a>;掩盖了创造就业、提高生产力和共享经济利益等核心问题。这个问题的根本原因是，社会上大部分人都相信，在新独立的印度，最初作为平权行动项目的项目应该有日落条款，导致对政治领导人绥靖少数群体的不满。现在钟摆已经转向另一个方向，带来了排斥和身份政治的新挑战。对于许多印度观察家来说，印度在&lt;a href=&quot;https://rsf.org/en/index&quot;>;世界新闻自由指数&lt;/a>;中的排名下降并没有带来什么帮助。因此，大部分不满情绪和少数群体中压抑的情绪可能会爆发，引发螺旋式下降。这种发展可能会破坏共同繁荣的目标。对于国际投资者和贸易伙伴来说，这可能会增加印度这样一个宗教、语言和社会文化多样性的国家的多数主义风险溢价。更重要的是，这些发展耗尽了政治资本，而这些资本本来可以用于社会和经济转型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;应对这些挑战至少有两种解决方案。一是政党从身份政治转向包容性增长和创造就业机会，以此作为赢得该国最广泛人口的最可靠手段。第二，印度不断举行州级选举，这扭曲了公众对话，偏离了以长期经济增长为导向的观点。简化和集中选举将为公众话语提供喘息空间，并推动政治领导层和选民走向更长远的视野。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;未实现的人口潜力&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .reuters.com/world/india/despite-world-beating-growth-indias-lack-jobs-threatens-its-young-2023-05-30/&quot;>;不到一半&lt;/a>;的城市工人拥有充分的时间工作，而印度的大部分就业机会都在生产力低下的非正规部门。教育、技能建设和医疗保健严重不足。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://do3n1uzkew47z.cloudfront.net/siteassets/pdf/ISR_Report_2023.pdf&quot;>;2023 年印度技能报告&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;发现只有一半的年轻印度人有工作能力。即使是“皇冠上的明珠”科技服务业也很脆弱；外包需求是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/ai-why-india-risks-falling-behind-in-the-tech-race/d8236bc2-16bb -11ee-9de3-ba1fa29e9bec_story.html&quot;>;下降&lt;/a>;和劳动力成本套利模式将因编码和日常功能向云计算和人工智能的长期转变而受到破坏。令人担忧的是，印度女性劳动力参与率一直在&lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/SL.TLF.CACT.FE.ZS?locations=IN&quot;>;稳步下降&lt;/a>;，从 2005 年的 32% 下降到 2021 年的 19%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;效仿 &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.rmresults.com/a-spotlight-on-vietnams-transformation-in -education&quot;>;越南&lt;/a>;，必须优先考虑对技能提升的公共和私人投资，这可能会增加&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dw.com/en/india-youth-lack-skills/a- 56879385&quot;>;为印度经济带来 5700 亿美元&lt;/a>;。一个主要障碍是制造业——在可比经济体中创造就业机会的关键——其已稳定在 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot; >;GDP 的 13.3%&lt;/a>;。当前的基础设施推动、政策改革、地缘政治驱动力和资本流入可能有助于释放印度制造业的潜力，但这里讨论的障碍必须消除。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在新兴领域，人工智能潜力的激增可能是印度制造业的机遇。鉴于该国&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/50-global-hubs-for-top-ai-talent&quot;>;新兴人工智能人才中心&lt;/a>;，印度将在尖端领域发挥领导作用与印度积累的&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/01/which-countries-are-leading-the-data-economy&quot;>;海量数据池&lt;/a>;相结合，可以大规模扩展。需要进行文化和组织变革，为女性进入职场创造机会并留住她们。此类项目的酝酿期较长，因此需要有一个重点突出、纪律严明的长期计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;未实现的商业便利性和创新潜力&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在印度开展业务有所改善，但仍然存在许多挑战。征地可能会阻碍建设项目，而法院则是行动缓慢的机构。土地记录可能不存在或已经过时，环境许可也造成了额外的障碍。除此之外，合同执行仍然具有挑战性。根据《经济学人》创建的指数，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/05/02/the-2023-crony-capitalism-index&quot;>;印度排名第十&lt;/a>;尽管过去三十年进行了大规模的自由化，但裙带资本主义依然盛行。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot;>;保护主义&lt;/a>;的遗留问题仍然存在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;印度的国家能力需要改变。与普遍的看法相反，印度政府并不庞大且笨拙，而是软弱且衰落。从监管机构到公民机构再到司法机构，各种机构经常兼顾相互冲突的需求，并努力追赶市场和社会现实。许多重要决策都是以危机为参照系做出的，印度的胜利故事往往是制度失败中的个人英雄主义。让印度的国家机器走在前沿很可能是印度的关键项目。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 &lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;总而言之，尽管障碍依然存在，但积极的力量确实可以产生多米诺骨牌效应：“不可避免的印度”指日可待。印度面临的最大挑战将是让许多希望看到印度成功的选民切实且相信其必然性。为了从针对游客的“不可思议的印度”转变为将全球经济带到自己的门口，印度的下一个活动应该是“可信的印度”。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI and the New Digital Cold War]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_02_792DVvbiBBo-scaled.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;全球化并未消亡，但正在发生变化。美国和中国正在创建两个独立的技术领域，而人工智能处于这场新的“数字冷战”的前线。如果民主国家想在这个“重新全球化”的新时代取得成功，就必须这样做。他们需要在政府之间以及私营和公共部门之间进行协调。无论我们喜欢与否，人工智能即将到来。我们正处在一个岔路口，社会各阶层都需要参与构建人工智能系统，为人类繁荣发展的公正和民主的未来做出贡献。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;我们正在进入一个新的世界秩序，其特点是民族主义抬头和地缘政治竞争加剧。虽然各国不会撤销过去三十年在美国单极统治下形成的所有全球经济体系，但某些关键部门将在我们之前称为的过程中脱钩&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/地缘政治正在改变风险资本必须太“重新全球化。”&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最重要的是，技术生态系统将主要分为两个领域，由世界两个国家决定经济强国美国和中国。其他国家需要决定自己想参与哪个领域，从而向美国和中国施加压力，要求它们超越对方并确立技术主导地位。展现在我们面前的是一种更加激烈的经济竞争形式，我们将其理解为“数字冷战”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;数字冷战将是一场经济战争，技术创新日益决定地缘政治实力。人工智能（AI）具有快速、彻底改变社会的能力，将成为这一领域最具决定性的技术。人工智能以信息为基础，其最强大的用例将通过其在公共和私营部门的应用而出现。为了让民主世界取得进步，公司和国家需要采取一种新的方法，将合作和转型置于竞争和破坏之上。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;民主协调的新时代&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们无处不在看到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/24/business/dealbook/globalization-fink-marks.html&quot;>;声称&lt;/a>;“全球化已死”。这种声明从根本上来说是误导性的。我们正在走向的系统比全球互联的恢复更为复杂。在许多情况下，贸易只是被改变路线而不是被关闭。大多数商业行业将保持开放和全球化，但某些关键部门将转向国内，转向本地化供应链。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这一趋势不是始于美国及其政策，而是始于习近平和他的 &lt;a href =&quot;http://english.www.gov.cn/policies/latest_releases/2015/05/19/content_281475110703534.htm&quot;>;2015年中国制造计划&lt;/a>;，明确表明中国政府已开始优先考虑国家对市场效率的弹性。习近平制定了一项计划，旨在在经济主导领域（尤其是高科技领域）击败美国和其他全球大国。事实上，中国继续朝着到 2025 年关键技术自给自足 70% 的目标迈进。此后，美国也采取了一系列雄心勃勃的措施来保持技术霸主地位。这一现实引导我们进入一个两极的高科技未来。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当谈到人工智能（可以说是这场全球竞争中最具决定性的技术）时，我们正在走向两个密封的生态系统：一个支持开放系统，但也与民主、隐私和个人权利相关，而不是支持国家控制、信息流限制和政治上对开放性施加的限制。尽管我们可能希望中国的政治模式能够发展，其技术能够受到民主反馈，但我们不应该天真：这不是它所走的轨道。为了实现崇尚开放和个人权利的未来，民主国家需要成为人工智能市场的领导者。确保这一点的唯一方法是促进国际合作，特别是民主国家与其他基于规则的秩序捍卫者之间的合作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在以前的时代，美国可以在技术上进行创新，而其他国家只需简单地进行技术创新即可。采用它。 When American technology leaders made groundbreaking advancements with personal computers and the internet, they operated under the assumption that American companies could work in isolation and spread their technologies across the world in a top-down fashion. The cloud revolution amplified this further, with Amazon, Microsoft, and Google owning 65% of the global market for cloud computing. This strategy may have worked when technologies were intended for pure disruption. AI, however, is geared for societal transformation. This requires a new kind of collaboration across stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Along with computing capabilities, the power of AI is based on the amount of aggregated data that is fed to it. This means that the United States, or any country, working in isolation with restricted data flows will fail to maximize the potential of its technology — and yet data localization policies &lt;a href=&quot;https://itif.org/publications/2021/07/19/how-barriers-cross-border-data-flows-are-spreading-globally-what-they-cost/&quot;>;doubled worldwide&lt;/a>; from 2017 to 2021, further obstructing cross-border collaboration. The summation of human knowledge and capabilities is not siloed in any one country or culture. Even Wikipedia&#39;s knowledge base is only 11% in the English language. For AI to thrive in its ability to help us solve our hardest problems, we have to unlock the world&#39;s capacity — from French nuclear scientists to Korean philosophers, from Indian researchers to Kenyan artists, and indeed to Chinese researchers who choose to leave China and work and live in the West.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Plus, the capital requirements for investments in the sector are so large at present that very few national markets are big enough to succeed with AI on their own. For example, consider investment in semiconductors — a key input into AI progress. The UK&#39;s recently announced 100 million GBP &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gov.uk/government/news/initial-100-million-for-expert-taskforce-to-help-uk-build-and-adopt-next-generation-of-safe-ai&quot;>;AI plan&lt;/a>; and 1 billion GBP &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gov.uk/government/news/new-1-billion-strategy-for-uks-semiconductor-sector&quot;>;semiconductor investment&lt;/a>; pale in comparison to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/senate-approves-280-billion-bill-to-boost-us-science-chip-production-11658942295&quot;>;US&#39;s&lt;/a>; $280 billion and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-25/eu-enacts-43-billion-chips-act-in-bid-to-boost-production&quot;>;EU&#39;s&lt;/a>; 43 billion EUR chips packages — and even these packages are constrained compared to the scale of the investment required to fully develop these technologies. Certainly, few investors globally can support fundraising rounds for startups like the one-year-old Inflection AI&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/inflection-ai-raises-13-bln-funding-microsoft-others-2023-06-29/&quot;>;$1.3 billion round&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the center of this all, a disjointed approach with various patchworks of regulatory frameworks across the West will harm any ability to compete and win against Chinese AI systems. It is not just a function of population, but a function of data points. Chinese society,&amp;nbsp;with a population more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.visualcapitalist.com/the-population-of-china-compared-with-the-rest-of-the-world/&quot;>;four times larger&lt;/a>; than the US&#39;s, &amp;nbsp;has become so digitized with data freely shared between its government and domestic technology champions. Soon their models, based largely on American and foreign research, can leapfrog the capabilities of those in the West.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With its size, centralized government, and inroads in other countries, China has the potential to develop one comprehensive AI model that outcompetes the multiplicity of models coming out of democratic nations if there is no international coordination. While the United States is still the AI leader — with the companies that are doing the most cutting-edge research — and while AI seems to have a bias toward open systems with unfettered access to information, the United States risks losing its edge if it fails to coalesce around a uniform strategy with other democratic nations. If this were to happen, Chinese companies could bring their technology to Western markets, influencing democratic politics and signaling to the world China&#39;s economic dominance — and its broader colonization of digital infrastructure around the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI is becoming an increasingly critical part of this global infrastructure, and the West must act swiftly and in a unified fashion to ensure the technology remains open and democratically controlled. To develop the most powerful AI models across sectors, the United States will need to collaborate with other allied countries — to name a few, India, Singapore, Japan, South Korea, and European nations — by adopting data-sharing policies and encouraging the co-creation of technological innovations. Much can be gleaned from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.european-data-governance-act.com/#:~:text=What%20is%20the%20European%20Data,of%20EU%20citizens%20and%20businesses.&quot;>;European Data Governance Act&lt;/a>; approved by the EU in 2022, which facilitates data-sharing across member countries to maximize benefits for its citizens and businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to course correct will severely limit the impact of AI. For models tackling climate change, siloed data is an immediate death sentence. Medical and healthcare data and innovations are not limited to any one country, nor any one research institution. Industrial AI powering global supply chains cannot be effective without the constant flow of interconnected data. In consumer applications, varying copyright frameworks would stymie cultural relevance and influence, favoring those with free access to data over others. Moreover, piecemeal data regulation and sovereignty requirements raise compliance costs and complexity, harming the innovation economy&#39;s ability to succeed.&amp;nbsp;This is not to suggest that governments should abstain from regulating AI, but rather that they should work together to establish uniform standards and practices across countries. Coordination among democratic nations will empower each country to individually feel resilient when it comes to AI, but also elevate the West as a bloc to be the leader in AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Innovation for AI Transformation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In addition to collaborating across states, if Western companies want to become true market leaders, they will also need to collaborate within states, namely with governmental institutions and civil society. While most of the current discourse surrounding AI focuses on large language models and other generative capabilities, AI&#39;s most significant long-term impacts will come from the ways in which it transforms industries and society as a whole. And genuine transformation cannot come about if private actors are disconnected from the wider society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Already we are seeing AI&#39;s transformative potential beginning to take shape. AI has the capacity to massively level the playing field for who has access to information and insights. In the classroom, AI can give&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lot of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/30/tech/ai-industry-statement-extinction-risk-warning/index.html&quot;>;recent attention&lt;/a>; has fixated on the existential threat AI could pose to humanity in the somewhat distant future. But AI is also destabilizing democratic systems in the here and now, providing new avenues for mis- and dis-information through sophisticated bots and realistic deep-fakes. AI will also throw into question the value of democracy itself. What happens when authoritarian systems, augmented by AI, can outperform their democratic counterparts, for instance by massively reducing crime with expanded surveillance? Or by providing vastly better healthcare because of access to centralized information with no restrictions for privacy? Undemocratic alternatives will only become more tempting as AI develops, and these possibilities are not too far off.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We are at a fork in the road when it comes to AI. We can go down the path that leads to automation and destruction, replacing human work and meaning, or we can go down the path that leads to copiloting and enablement, making us more productive, helping us live more balanced lives, and becoming greater masters of our craft. Unlike the social media revolution, which, if regulators really wanted to, they could have slowed or redirected, the AI revolution can only charge forward. Unlike previous &lt;em>;platform&lt;/em>; revolutions, this is a &lt;em>;technological&lt;/em>; revolution, and its mantle has already been picked up by stakeholders across society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The most successful companies will be those that embrace this forward-looking vision and build to endure, by centering a core set of values that align with society and abide by self-regulatory mechanisms. Taking the further step of partnering with the public sector and incumbent ecosystems is also crucial. We cannot risk AI going awry and putting democracies off track in this competitive race. Since the impacts of AI will be felt across every sector of society, accounting for broad stakeholder interests is both a moral responsibility and the only way to bring about sustainable transformation. In the age of AI, companies will need to pursue an agenda of responsible innovation, working outside of the usual technological silos.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To win the Digital Cold War, the United States and its allies must be the market leaders in AI. And to build the best AI companies, they need to prioritize international collaboration and engender a new mindset — one that aims to innovate responsibly and unleash human potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Challenges of Networking as an Executive]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_02_200428479-007.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Martin Barraud/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Networking is critical for senior executives who are making job and career transitions, but it&amp;#8217;s hard to find advice on how best to manage the process. In this article, the authors &amp;#8212; who have decades of experience working with executives during periods of transition &amp;#8212; identify six networking hurdles that executives often encounter, and they provide guidance on how to get over them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Look online at any of the thousands of articles available on the challenges of networking for a job, and you&#39;ll find that 100% of them give advice on how relatively junior professionals can network “up.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But surprisingly little advice is available for senior executives, who experience a different but equally challenging set of networking hurdles. That&#39;s a problem, because knowing how to reap networking&#39;s full benefits is crucial for people at the top of the pyramid, especially a time when CEO turnover is at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/04/27/ceo-turnover-high-pandemic/&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have decades of experience working with and studying senior executives who are making career changes. In this article, we&#39;ll identify six common hurdles that that they often struggle with when it comes to career networking, and we&#39;ll provide some guidance on how to get over them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1) Reluctance to ask for help&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Networking for a next role means asking for help. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0749597897927461&quot;>;Research in social psychology&lt;/a>; shows that people with high status are more apt to feel pressure to maintain an image of strength and competence and to value self-reliance, all of which can make them reluctant to seek assistance. They fear rejection and worry that asking for help might expose perceived weaknesses, potentially undermining their status, position, or reputation. This is ego-driven reluctance, and we see it frequently. As one of Herminia&#39;s students put it, “I give help — I don&#39;t ask for it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One way around this tendency, which is a natural one, is to start your networking process by reaching out to lower-risk (and lower-yield) contacts — ideally, executives who you know well, who have done their own networking, and who can share not only how they approached others for help but also what they got out of asking for it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can probably do this with more people than you realize: As the Stanford social psychologist Xuan Zhao has found, people regularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/09567976221097615?journalCode=pssa&quot;>;underestimate&lt;/a>; others&#39; willingness to help, because they don&#39;t realize how happy it makes those others to do so. Low-risk warm-ups and rehearsal practice — what Spish calls “hearing the dreaded words come out of your mouth” — will help you fine-tune your message, defuse your emotions, and experience success. And having a few positive experiences under your belt will make your later, more-challenging calls and emails easier.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2) &amp;nbsp;Prioritizing secrecy &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The more senior an executive, the more likely they are to want secrecy, especially if they&#39;ve been laid off. One of Spish&#39;s clients, for example, asked: “How do I go out into the market without letting the market know that I&#39;m looking? I&#39;d like to reach out to people, but I don&#39;t want them to know that I&#39;m interested in looking.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such worries limit your exposure to others, which is a problem in its own right. But they also force you to be secretive as you work on networking and career change — a process, according to Herminia&#39;s research, that often takes far longer than people expect. That burden of secrecy, carried for a long time, can exact a significant psychological toll.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Limiting your exposure to others can be especially pernicious when it keeps you from stepping back and exploring broadly what you would really like to do next. And try as you might, you won&#39;t fool people by obfuscating. At senior levels, it&#39;s a small world: The people you talk to can figure out what you&#39;re up to, perhaps by making a call to a source in their own network, or perhaps just by doing a search online. If you do succeed in concealing your story, it&#39;s likely to tax your nerves and cost you a lot of energy to get the same result that just speaking honestly and directly would have gotten you. With rare exceptions, honesty is the best policy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3) &amp;nbsp;Unrealistic expectations &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Because they&#39;re reluctant to ask for help and don&#39;t want word to get out that they are in the market for a new role, senior executives typically want to get their networking done fast. Or they simply assume that because they&#39;re senior, the process won&#39;t take very long. Unfortunately, the more senior you are, the more time you&#39;re likely to need to find and align on the right fit. In Spish&#39;s experience, the shortest possible search is about three months, and the longer ones can take as much as 18 months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only does effective networking take a long time, it also involves a great deal of work, stamina, efficiency, and patience. There are three primary reasons for this.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, as both of us have found, only a small percentage of people looking for their next role know exactly which handful of companies they&#39;d like to work for. Because they don&#39;t know enough about the market or what they really want to be able to come up with a targeted search, they have to start with research and very general exploratory networking. That all takes time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, what you want and are best suited for may not actually be available to you. Both of us have seen highly qualified and experienced people take an excruciatingly long time to find their next role. &lt;span>;O&lt;/span>;ne executive that Herminia recently observed thought, given his past experience, that he&#39;d be an ideal candidate for the audit committee of a big corporate board, but as the selection criteria shifted to include a greater diversity of professional profiles, he found himself waiting to get a nod.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, most companies today have elaborate, time-consuming, and unpredictable vetting processes, which can often add months at the tail end of the hiring process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the senior-executive job market, it helps to recognize that in the messy meeting of supply and demand you have surprisingly little control. A great proactive tactic that can help you compensate for that as you do your networking is to fill your calendar with stimulating, parallel activities (community work, pro-bono consulting, short-term advising, adjunct teaching) in which you can have a more immediate impact and receive a more gratifying response. This compensates for the tedium, if not burden, of asking and waiting for help. It also provides battered egos with positive, if provisional, identities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4) Not wanting to put in the work &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Executives who are used to having things done for them often balk at devoting time to tedious work that they can&#39;t delegate. But to network successfully, you need to treat the task as fully worth your time and energy — and you need to be methodical and organized about it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help with that, Spish has developed a networking process that consists of identifying and then contacting three kinds of contacts: information givers, door openers, and decision makers. Information givers are people who can tell you about the market, companies, and hiring trends; they can help you get smart and get over your fear of networking. Door openers are typically people you&#39;ve worked with in the past. They&#39;re responsive, and because they know you and your work style, they&#39;re willing to vouch for you and can introduce you to the decision makers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;d like to use this process, the best way to start is by first making a list of all your employers, clients, and customers, and then by writing down the names of the people you met in those roles. You might find you easily come up with 100 names.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;No matter what approach you use to organizing, targeting, and segmenting your search, you&#39;ll always need to start by generating a long list of people you&#39;ve worked with and then methodically following a system for reaching out to them. Because it&#39;s a learning process, you can&#39;t plan it all out in advance; you&#39;re better off adopting a “snowball” approach” in which you ask each contact who else you should meet. This is especially true if you&#39;re looking in markets that are unfamiliar to you. In that case, you&#39;ll need to network in what Spish calls “the valleys below the clouds.” There are lots of opportunities in these valleys, but they unfamiliar and require exploration. If you don&#39;t explore them, you limit your options and can hurt your career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s a high-cost, high-yield game, but it pays off. Spish has found that once you&#39;ve reached out to 50 or more contacts on your list, the network will start to reach out to you, at which point you can let the process carry you forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5) Overly focusing on “the narrative” &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once you&#39;ve made a contact, there is the important matter of what to say. All too often, executives spend the bulk of a networking conversation in small talk about shared contacts or experiences without getting to the point (that they need a new job) until the very end of the conversation. This is especially common when they feel they need to conceal the reality of what&#39;s going on — that they don&#39;t get along with their boss, say, or that they&#39;ve been fired. When that happens, they often enter into the conversation already on the defensive, they speak evasively, and they devote their energy to protecting their public image instead of learning all they can. The end result is that they waste a lot of their — and their contacts&#39; — time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another unproductive tack is to spend 80% of your time trying to explain why you&#39;re unhappy, or leaving, or got fired — a negative approach that anchors your conversation in the past when it should be positive and focused on the future. You&#39;re much better off spending 20% of your allotted time explaining your situation and focusing the remaining 80% on what you&#39;re looking for instead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The best practice in networking conversations is to be direct, succinct, and positive. People want to know why you&#39;re calling them and what you want from them, and the more senior they are, the more likely they&#39;ll be to expect a brief, executive summary of this sort: “This is why I&#39;m calling you. This is what I want from you. I hope that there&#39;s enough in these two points for us to have a 10-minute conversation.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6) &amp;nbsp;Failing to tailor your story&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Executives looking to make a transition often spend inordinate amounts of time perfecting a single script — the fabled “elevator pitch” about their “core skills and abilities.” They do this assuming that this script will make them universally relevant, but almost invariably what they end up with just isn&#39;t satisfactorily tailored to the needs of the receiver.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;ve seen a lot of executives try to approach networking the way they would work with head-hunters: They write a generic email, just changing the name and one or two sentences, attach their resume, and send it out to a bunch of people. Likewise, many walk into a meeting and robotically state their one-minute pitch even if it doesn&#39;t fit the unique circumstances and requirements of the person who&#39;s listening.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That just doesn&#39;t work. Yes, figuring out your core storyline (Who am I, and why am I here?) is important. But you can&#39;t assume that you&#39;re going to be saying the same thing about yourself to every person you meet. Nor can you assume that every listener is capable of translating your pitch into their own business context.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the end, here&#39;s what you need to remember: It&#39;s not about you. If you hope to clinch a role for which you&#39;re truly well suited, you need to figure out how to make the switch from talking about yourself to talking knowledgeably about the company and its problems — and then to articulating how well equipped you are to solve those problems. As Spish has found, that&#39;s how you create opportunities for yourself: A large percentage of the most senior executives he&#39;s coached have ended up moving into roles that didn&#39;t even exist before they had their conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;* * *&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re a senior executive, networking is a delicate, complex, and time-consuming task. Ego and impatience, left unchecked, will sabotage your success. The best approach is to think of networking as an opportunity not just to scout out your next role but also to strengthen or deepen relationships you already have — and, even better, to add new relationships that will help you be a better professional in your new job and the others that come after it.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Your Vacation Wasn&rsquo;t Exactly Relaxing]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/when-your-vacation-wasnt-exactly-relaxing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_05_82836891.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Williams+Hirakawa/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Time off doesn&amp;#8217;t always go as planned. So, what can you do when you come back to work more exhausted than when you left &amp;#8212; especially when everyone assumes you&amp;#8217;re well rested and raring to go but you feel just as depleted (or more) than before? The author recommends five strategies: 1) Take inventory of your health and energy; 2) Ease back into work; 3) Reflect on the positives; reframe and learn from the negatives; 4) Use the fresh start effect to set up new routines; and 5) Clarify what you need for future time off.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/when-your-vacation-wasnt-exactly-relaxing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/when-your-vacation-wasnt-exactly-relaxing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Vacations are meant to be rejuvenating. Time off can not only help you &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot;>;restore your mind, body, and soul&lt;/a>;, it also has a positive impact on your work life: One study found that employees who take 11 or more vacation days &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/07/the-data-driven-case-for-vacation&quot;>;are more likely to receive a raise or bonus&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/02/when-a-vacation-reduces-stress-and-when-it-doesnt&quot;>;not all vacations are as restorative&lt;/a>; or energizing as we hope they&#39;ll be. Chronic work stress can interfere with our plans. The phenomenon of getting sick as soon as you start to relax even has a name: &lt;a href=&quot;https://community.thriveglobal.com/the-five-key-steps-to-take-to-avoid-leisure-sickness/&quot;>;leisure sickness&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;.&lt;/u>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even when pacing yourself, your time off doesn&#39;t always go as planned. The &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/06/going-on-vacation-doesnt-have-to-stress-you-out-at-work&quot;>;vacation itself can be a source of stress&lt;/a>; for a variety of reasons, from strained relationships, pre-vacation stress of getting everything done, unexpected travel delays, or the weight of &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/how-to-minimize-stress-before-during-and-after-your-vacation&quot;>;impending deadlines and workload when you return&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, what can you do when you come back to work more exhausted than when you left — especially when everyone assumes you&#39;re well rested and raring to go but you feel just as depleted (or more) than before? Here are five steps you can take to refresh on your return.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Take inventory of your health and energy.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unless you&#39;ve been on a rejuvenating health retreat, it&#39;s possible that you&#39;ve veered away from your healthy routines, maybe skipping out on physical activity or finding yourself caught up in a full schedule and indulging a bit too much.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On your return, assess and acknowledge your energy levels, taking inventory of how you&#39;re feeling to determine what you need. Research has found that optimizing your energy along the following domains can help boost wellbeing and performance: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.deloitte.com/uk/en/insights/focus/behavioral-economics/sleep-benefits-impact-employee-performance.html&quot;>;sleep&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/to-improve-your-work-performance-get-some-exercise&quot;>;movement&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/feeling-it/201208/connect-thrive&quot;>;connection&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/why-you-should-tell-your-team-to-take-a-break-and-go-outside&quot;>;time outdoors&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/09/to-cope-with-stress-try-learning-something-new&quot;>;relaxation&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2023/04/05/how-relational-energy-impacts-employee-engagement/?sh=7a3861a047c2&quot;>;meaningful &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2023/04/05/how-relational-energy-impacts-employee-engagement/?sh=7a3861a047c2&quot;>;engagement&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Start by rating yourself on a scale of 1-10 in terms of your current energy levels in each of the above areas. Then identify where you would like to be in each domain and one action you can take to reinforce or improve each of these elements of your wellbeing. Reassess daily for a week, tracking how your energy shifts as you re-engage in healthier habits.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Ease back into work.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/09/what-to-do-on-your-first-day-back-from-vacation&quot;>;Coming back from a vacation&lt;/a>; can be a challenging experience when you are feeling overwhelmed or stressed about catching up with emails and conversations that were piling up while you were supposed to be relaxing and enjoying time off.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Resist the temptation to dive into work headfirst by building in a day of transition and recovery before returning to normal. You might even consider drafting an auto-response or &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/06/ease-the-pain-of-returning-to-work-after-time-off#:~:text=Block%20off%20significant%20chunks%20of,something%20to%20look%20forward%20to.&amp;amp;text=Stay%20in%20stealth%20mode.&quot;>;extending your OOO&lt;/a>; for an extra day or two.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Before you enter into a full day&#39;s work, set some guard rails for your time so that you can get off to a good start.&amp;nbsp; Begin with essential and time-sensitive tasks and give yourself a buffer to catch up on emails and updates that can come later. Block time out on your calendar also for activities that energize you.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Reflect on the positives; reframe, and learn from the negatives.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to get overwhelmed or disappointed by things that may not have gone as well as you had hoped — but there are likely some positive memories to hold onto. Take some time to reflect and savor those experiences, as well as &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/the-mental-benefits-of-vacationing-somewhere-new&quot;>;lessons and insights gained&lt;/a>;. Capture them on paper, so you can share them with your team members, and reinforce the benefits of your time away. If the trip left you feeling in a rut, maybe you can find solace in the fact that you&#39;re home again getting back to normal.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. Use the fresh start effect to set new habits and routines&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The fresh start effect is &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/02/research-explores-how-fresh-starts-affect-our-motivation-at-work&quot;>;the phenomenon of increased success in behavioral change&lt;/a>; associated with new beginnings, such as birthdays, the new year, and other milestones. You can harness this effect by using your return to work as an opportunity to reset.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Coming back from a vacation is a good time to establish new practices that further enhance your energy and productivity, like &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/to-improve-your-work-performance-get-some-exercise&quot;>;exercising&lt;/a>;, shutting off notifications, blocking distractions, or writing in a journal each night. Seek out habits and routines that feel replenishing in your day-to-day life. You can leverage practices such as &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/12/how-timeboxing-works-and-why-it-will-make-you-more-productive&quot;>;timeboxing&lt;/a>; to optimize your energy for the things that matter to you.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It can be tempting to try to overcompensate but don&#39;t let remorse drive your actions. Rather think about the routines that will work within the context of your daily life so that your habits can be sustainable.&amp;nbsp; Determine what you need to do today to &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/09/is-your-motivation-still-on-vacation&quot;>;get back on track&lt;/a>;, leave remorse out of the equation and do what you need to create forward momentum.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. Clarify what you need for future time off.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Use this experience as a learning opportunity to set the ground for a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-taking-a-vacation-improves-your-well-being&quot;>;more replenishing vacation in the future&lt;/a>;. Decide how much structure was energizing versus draining on your energy. Who do you want to spend time with and how far do you want to travel? How much &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/set-these-5-boundaries-before-you-go-on-vacation&quot;>;communication with your team&lt;/a>; do you need for your own wellbeing and connection needs?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even a good vacation can sometimes be exhausting. If you don&#39;t properly manage your time and energy when returning, your exhaustion can have a cumulative impact on your wellbeing, work, relationships, and performance. If you didn&#39;t get what you needed from this vacation, use it as motivation to ensure that you build sustainable, energy-preserving practices into your daily life.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Avoid These Pitfalls When Measuring Your Strategy&rsquo;s Performance]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/avoid-these-pitfalls-when-measuring-your-strategys-performance]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sept23_01_1391375157.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Luis Alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;This article explores three common traps that managers fall into when measuring their strategy&amp;#8217;s performance and explains how to avoid them. The first trap is when the strategic framework and measurement system don&amp;#8217;t align. To fix it, you must organize both around key stakeholders. The second trap is when companies measure what they do rather than what they achieve. To fix this, focus on stakeholder outcomes. The third trap is a lack of focus. To fix it, cascade rather than amalgamate your metrics.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/avoid-these-pitfalls-when-measuring-your-strategys-performance?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/avoid-these-pitfalls-when-measuring-your-strategys-performance?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Measuring the performance of a business goes hand in glove with its business strategy. Or it should. But surprisingly, as I&#39;ve witnessed firsthand over an extended period, organizations in all sectors struggle to match their strategy design with their performance measurement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is hugely important because it&#39;s almost impossible to track the success of a business strategy if there are no reliable key performance indicators (KPIs). Conversely, poor performance measurement can encourage misdirected strategic targets. Both can lead to repeat performances of the same failed decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here I explore three common traps that managers fall into when measuring their strategy&#39;s performance and explain how to avoid them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Non-matching frameworks&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Roger is the CEO of a state government&#39;s main roads department. When he was appointed, he installed his favored strategy framework based on “areas.” These came with their own acronym – KRAs, key result areas. So, he organized the main roads strategic plan under items such as energy reduction, governance, and material sourcing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The trouble was that it didn&#39;t match main roads&#39; existing performance measurement framework, which was organized around programs such as road safety, road efficiency, and road maintenance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The disconnect was hugely dysfunctional with much executive time and energy expended trying to make things work. As one executive wryly observed, “it was like trying to put parts of a Ford into a Mercedes Benz. They just wouldn&#39;t fit.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How to fix it: Organize around key stakeholders.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Marjorie heads up a not-for-profit entity which looks after people with autism. When she joined the organization as CEO, she was faced with what she describes as “a disconnect between our strategic planning framework and how our KPIs were assembled.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The organization&#39;s strategic plan was structured around “key issues” like budget overruns, obtaining grants, and hiring staff. The KPIs were a hotchpotch of metrics drawn from a variety of sources including HR, accounting and finance, and operations including operating expenses and the number of staff training courses run.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Her solution was to refocus both strategy and the KPIs around the &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;organization&#39;s key stakeholders.&lt;/a>; These were people with autism and their families, government, donors and supporters, and staff.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, in the case of the stakeholder staff, Marjorie&#39;s organization wanted to ratchet up innovation around the services they provided for people with autism and their families. This required attracting first-rate clinicians by boosting the organization&#39;s position on employment conditions. One indicator of success was an increase in the number of job applications from suitably qualified psychologists. “At last,” she says, “our organization&#39;s strategic plan and scorecard can speak to each other.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Measuring activity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s how I illustrate this problem to groups of managers at my workshops. I say to them: “I propose to measure my performance today by measuring the number of slides I use. And if I&#39;m really tired at the end of the day I&#39;ll know I&#39;ve done a good job. Would you be happy with those as measures of my performance?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My audience always says no. “为什么？” I ask. “Because they&#39;re measures of activity, not of results,” they say. “And who decides on those results ?” I inquire. “We do,” comes the universal response. In that moment my audience “gets it.” I can see it in their faces.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How to fix it: Focus on outcomes.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Angelo heads up the national office of a well-known brand of construction tools. When it came to measuring the performance of his business, he explained: “We would get together and focus on what we do. The KPIs we produced were invariably about processes.” They broke this fixation by focusing on the outcomes his organization produced for its key stakeholders – customers, suppliers, employees, and the parent company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Measuring this performance involves a two-way street with outcomes going both ways – for the business and for stakeholders. Angelo and his team avoided making assumptions about what the outcomes would be for their stakeholders. Instead, they interviewed key stakeholders to learn if the outcomes important to them had been identified. The interviews also revealed new KPIs that Angelo and his team would never have thought of.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Lack of focus&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Sebastian is CEO of a suburban council. He wanted to develop a scorecard of the council&#39;s performance linked to the council&#39;s strategic plan. So, he collected measures from departments below him, such as community development, environment and planning, and corporate services, and he created a composite list. This list was long and left him dissatisfied. Many of the measures didn&#39;t seem at all related to the council&#39;s objectives.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How to fix it: Cascade rather than amalgamate your metrics.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Helen is a newly installed principal of a large, prestigious, and very expensive private girls&#39; school. To develop a scorecard for the school, she gathered measures from academic departments such as science, English and mathematics. But, as with Sebastian, the composite set of KPIs didn&#39;t work as measures of the school&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;She fixed this by starting again. This time, rather than amalgamating measures from bottom to top, she developed KPIs in the reverse order — from top to bottom. The process she says, “allowed me to kill two birds with the one stone. It uncovered gaps in the KPI set for the school and provided a fit between the school&#39;s strategic plan around students, parents, teachers and staff, government, [and] the community… [It also] provided an effective scorecard based on the results for these same groups.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Helen had learned a fundamental concept in performance measurement – level of analysis. Measures that apply at one level, eg, profit at the corporate level, don&#39;t apply at another level, eg, an internal department like HR. Similarly, measures that are apt at a department level are not appropriate at the corporate level.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy for gaps to develop between your strategic plan and your KPIs if you don&#39;t apply a framework consistently across both – and you&#39;re certainly not alone if this has happened to you.&amp;nbsp; As you close the gaps, however, remember above all that measuring performance is fundamentally about measuring your relationships with your &lt;a href=&quot;/2014/03/five-questions-to-identify-key-stakeholders&quot;>;organization&#39;s key stakeholders.&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp; Your KPIs, therefore, need to be shaped by what those stakeholders expect from you and not by what you think you should be doing.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 04 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>