<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/<item><title><![CDATA[Keeping Your Spirits Up When You Really Need a Win at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/keeping-your-spirits-up-when-you-really-need-a-win-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_13_5426399.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Giada Canu/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;您是否感觉已经很久没有在工作中取得重大胜利了？虽然总会有起起落落，但没有什么是永恒的，即使感觉上是这样。有时，你处于领先地位，事情进展顺利；有时，你处于领先地位，事情进展顺利；其他时候，你很难维持生计。&amp;#160;如果您很难相信经济衰退会永远结束，并且需要从其他人那里听到这一点，请联系可以提供您观点的朋友或导师。如果你觉得自己无法赢得胜利或无法推进某个项目，那么是时候调整你的心态了。即使是最小的胜利也要庆祝。请记住，最微小的胜利也可以让您取得领先。依靠你的导师和同事，让反对者远离你。随着时间的推移，这些积极行动的累积效应将推动你前进，而那些微小的胜利将累积成巨大的胜利。请记住，即使您不确定何时，这种情况也会逆转。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/keeping-your-spirits-up-when-you-really-need-a-win-at-work?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br >; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/keeping-your-spirits-up-when-you-really-need-a-win-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div >; &lt;p>;社交媒体可以让您轻松看到每个人的胜利。但如果你正处于一个苦苦挣扎的时期，并且感觉自己已经有一段时间没有取得任何胜利，那么看到朋友和同事在 LinkedIn 上发布的快乐公告可能会让你感到痛苦。也许你过去所做的事情已经取得了成功，但现在却一事无成。如果你觉得自己的工作没有进展，那么是时候重新调整、检查你的心态并专注于让你快乐的活动，而不是把自己与他人进行比较。以下是当您确实需要胜利时前进的技巧。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;请记住，这是一个&lt;em>;赛季。&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;将会有总是有起有落；没有什么是永恒的，即使感觉是这样。有时你处于领先地位，事情进展顺利；其他时候，你很难维持生计。没有一个“正确”的季节。请记住，这只是一个短暂的时期，不会永远持续下去。如果您很难相信经济衰退会永远结束，并且需要从其他人那里听到这一点，请联系可以提供您观点的朋友或导师。请记住，这种情况&lt;em>;将会&lt;/em>;逆转，即使您不确定何时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的一位客户不断向&lt;em>;她的&lt;/em>;客户提出想法，但从未出现过以获得牵引力。她提出的一切都被采纳了。我的客户感到沮丧，因为她觉得她的想法永远不会得到批准；但她仍继续采取行动。我的客户认为这是一个“苦苦挣扎的季节”；她学会了脱离结果，继续前进。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;庆祝（微小的）胜利。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;你以前可能听过：“庆祝小胜。”但是，如果您觉得自己没有&lt;em>;任何&lt;/em>;胜利，无论胜利多么小，该怎么办？ Teresa M. Amabile 和 Steven J. Kramer 在他们的文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/the-power-of-small-wins&quot;>;小胜的力量&lt;/a>;”中分享了这一点：“当我们思考进步，经常想象实现长期目标或经历重大突破的感觉有多好。”这些重大胜利固然伟大，但相对罕见。如果您正在寻求小额胜利，但效果不佳，请尝试以下方法：甚至更小。列出最近工作项目中的每个细节。其中哪一个顺利进行？哪一个比预期的要好？即使是微小的胜利也能改变工作的轨迹并振奋你的精神。一位前同事决定记录他的微胜利。随着时间的推移，他看到了微小的胜利是如何积累起来的。最终结果是，他感觉自己的角色更加强大和有能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;为允许进入你的空间的人设定严格的界限。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;甚至是同事和同事善意的朋友可能会让你怀疑自己。想想你的同事中谁让你感觉良好？谁让你的风帆不再风帆？设定界限并毫不留情地避开那些让你失望的人。 Greg McKeown 在他的文章“&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/07/the-emotional-boundaries-you-need-at-work&quot;>;工作中需要的情感界限&lt;/a>;”中创建了一个矩阵，人们可以通过该矩阵可以确定他们的界限。麦基翁写道：“为了在工作或家庭中发展有意义和成熟的关系，我们需要建立两个过滤器。第一个过滤器可以保护您免受其他人的侵害。第二个过滤器可以保护其他人免受你的侵害。”这并不意味着你会变成隐士；相反，你会变成隐士。相反，这意味着你只花时间和那些让你感觉良好的人在一起（即使只有一个人）。请记住，您不必永远有如此严格的界限。然而，当你重新站起来时，要无情地避开那些让你崩溃的人。这也可能意味着暂时远离社交媒体。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;忘记感恩；忘记感恩吧。看看自己的优势。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;表达感激之情会让您感觉更好，并扩展您对正确事物的看法。然而，如果你情绪低落，“感恩”可能会让人觉得太过牵强。与其列感恩清单，不如试试这个；在一天结束时，回顾一下你的行为并欣赏你做得好的事情。这可以是像“今天我对咖啡师微笑”这样简单的事情；或者，“我在高层领导会议上分享了宝贵的见解。”每天至少写三件事。随着时间的推移，看到你的积极行动不断积累，会增强你的自信心，并有助于推动你前进。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;欣赏正在发生的事情。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您感觉效率低下，您可能认为您需要&lt;em>;做&lt;/em>;某事。但通常情况下，并不需要采取行动。如果您感到有动力&lt;em>;去做&lt;/em>;，请控制冲动；相反，尝试坐着什么也不做。我指导许多客户在日历上留出时间什么也不做。 “没什么”可能意味着坐下来读一本时尚杂志来理清思绪。或者这可能意味着坐下来思考上周进展顺利的会议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关键是让你的思绪安静下来，并尝试注意至少一件进展顺利的事情。如果你不去寻找好的一面，你就会错过它，并陷入“对我来说一事无成”的消极信念。一整天，我们很容易注意到“叮当声”，或者似乎没有朝着正确方向发展的事情。同样，人们很容易忽视一切正常运转的安静嗡嗡声。每天注意并写下三件进展顺利的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;看看别人的胜利，但永远不要让自己感到羞耻。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;有时你需要跳出自己的视野，看看别人的胜利。你不需要比较自己，也不需要为你想要达到的目标制定一个衡量标准；相反，利用别人的胜利来推动自己前进。采取这种心态：“如果那个人能做好那件事，那么我也能。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我曾与一位喜欢观看励志 YouTube 视频的客户合作。当他需要“获胜”（即完成销售）时，他会在 YouTube 上观看汤姆·布雷迪 (Tom Brady) 的蒙太奇。我的客户利用汤姆·布雷迪的干劲、动力和努力来提升自己，并向自己发出信号：“我也能赢。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;拓展你的视野。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;如果您情绪低落，您可能会倾向于蹲下来并做尽可能少的事情。更好的主意是寻找 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/annesugar/2022/10/18/embracing-uncertainty-with-nathan-and-susannah-furr/?sh=131b3a4441f7 &quot;>;范式转变&lt;/a>;方式来挑战自己。 Nathan 和 Susannah Furr，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Upside-Uncertainty-Guide-Finding-Possibility/dp/1647823013/ref=sr_1_1?crid=KVH6BX94C0QV&amp;amp;keywords=upside+of+ 的作者uncertainty&amp;amp;qid=1674426725&amp;amp;sprefix=upside+of+%2Caps%2C94&amp;amp;sr=8-1&quot;>;&lt;em>;不确定性的好处&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;，在书中分享他们经历的大起大落当他们搬到法国并学会在新环境中蓬勃发展时，以及停止尝试控制风险的重要性。相反，请考虑如何为积极的改变创造条件。当 Furrs 面临看似无法克服的挑战时，他们不断前进并寻找新的可能性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你觉得自己无法赢得胜利或在项目上取得进展，那么是时候调整你的心态了。请记住，最微小的胜利也可以让您取得领先。依靠你的导师和同事，让反对者远离你。随着时间的推移，这些积极行动的累积效应将推动你前进，而这些微小的胜利将累积成巨大的胜利。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How a Remote Australian Mine Became a Gender-Balanced Workplace]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-a-remote-australian-mine-became-a-gender-balanced-workplace]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_13_W2eS79faT0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然许多行业都在努力实现“并维持&amp;#8212;性别平等方面，采矿业和其他传统上由男性主导的行业的进展尤其缓慢。虽然全球其他大型矿山的女性工人仅占 10%，但必和必拓运营的西澳大利亚铁矿 South Flank 的员工队伍中，869 名一线员工中，40% 是女性，六分之四的高级管理人员是女性是女性。作者的研究专门研究改变传统上以男性为主的环境中的性别歧视和恐同行为，他们最初受聘在南侧举办有关该主题的研讨会，但在在那里的六周内，通过观察和访谈研究了该地区的劳动力。他们确定了使该矿实现性别平等和女性工人包容的五个关键因素：1）高层领导的大力参与，制定了严格的性别平等目标；2）总部领导的大力支持；3）在培养女性员工方面进行了大量投资。一个热情且安全的采矿营地，4) 使用科学和数据驱动的方法来推动变革，5) 认识到性别平等很难实现和维持，需要持续努力。他们还概述了维持未来进步的潜在障碍，例如根深蒂固的男性规范损害了女工的福祉和保留，以及缺乏支持希望重返采矿业的所有性别父母的系统。&lt;/p>; &lt; /span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/a-remote-australian-mine-became-a-gender-balanced-workplace？ language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-a-remote-australian-mine-became-a-gender-balanced-workplace?language=pt&quot;>; Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;工作场所性别平等的进展速度为“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsweek.com/2022/03/11/gender-equity -work-advances-glacial-pace-new-harvard-survey-shows-1685659.html&quot;>;冰川&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;。&lt;/u>;”联合国发现这将需要近&lt;a href=&quot; https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/blog/2022/09/achieving-full-gender-equality-is-still-centuries-away-warns-the-un-in-new-report/&quot;>;300年&lt;/a>; 帮助女性在全球范围内实现充分的工作场所和社会平等。采矿业和其他传统上由男性主导的行业的进展尤其缓慢。最近的一份采矿业&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.responsibleminingfoundation.org/app/uploads/EN_Research-Insight_Gender_Feb2022.pdf&quot;>;报告&lt;/a>;发现，高管们非常注重增加在头脑中工作的女性人数办公室，但一线业务中的性别平衡几乎没有变化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unwomen.org/en/digital-library/publications/2022/ 09/progress-on-the-sustainable-development-goals-the-gender-snapshot-2022&quot;>;联合国发现&lt;/a>;跨行业进步的一个关键障碍是来自那些认为自己受到个人影响的男性的“强烈反对”由于需要纠正妇女几个世纪以来所经历的不利地位而处于不利地位。采矿业的批评者&lt;a href=&quot;https://ojs2.e-journal.unair.ac.id/IJOSH/article/view/24849/0&quot;>;通过声称女性“&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.exis.2021.02.002&quot;>;不感兴趣&lt;/a>;”或“&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/getting-serious-about-diversity-enough-已经-with-the-business-case&quot;>;无法&lt;/a>;”或“&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.resourpol.2020.101962&quot;>;不适合&lt;/a>;”执行以下操作高薪、安全、可操作的工作，例如钻孔、爆破岩石、驾驶巨型卡车或维护重型机械。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;现在，西澳大利亚州的一个偏远矿井证明了这些批评者是错误的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;位于&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bhp.com/careers/get-to-know-our-business/south-flank&quot;>;South Flank&lt;/a>;，由全球第二大矿业公司必和必拓，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bhp.com/news/media-centre/releases/2021/10/bhp-marks-of-south-flank&quot; 869 名一线员工中，>;40%&lt;/a>; 是女性。更值得注意的是，大多数高级管理人员（六分之四）都是女性。作为背景，国际劳工组织&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ilo.org/sector/Resources/publications/WCMS_821061/lang--en/index.htm&quot;>;发现&lt;/a>;平均只有 10世界各地其他大型矿山的工人中有 % 是女性。据我们所知，South Flank 是澳大利亚乃至全世界性别最平衡的大型矿山。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当我们收集本文中报告的数据时，我们只是受委托为南翼的领导人举办一系列五场研讨会，讨论改变传统男性主导环境中的性别歧视和恐同行为。我们没有被委托进行任何研究。然而，在举办研讨会时，我们意识到该矿在性别平等方面取得了独特的进展。这就是为什么我们决定通过观察和访谈来收集数据（在获得许可的情况下），以了解这一进展是如何取得的，以便我们可以与其他组织分享这些信息（通过类似的文章）。随后，南侧翼与我们的教师和大学的行为科学研究所合作，为改变有害和排斥行为提供额外支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;为什么 40% 很重要&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;国际组织通常 &lt;a href= &quot;https://www.ilo.org/global/about-the-ilo/newsroom/news/WCMS_701767/lang--en/index.htm&quot;>;将&lt;/a>;性别平衡的工作场所定义为拥有 40-60 名员工% 女性（或男性）以及男性和女性拥有&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oecd.org/tax/forum-on-tax-administration/publications-and-products/advancing-gender -balance-in-the-workforce-a-collective-responsibility.pdf&quot;>;平等的权力和影响力&lt;/a>;。国际劳工组织确定的可持续发展基线为 40%，采矿作业中的每个船员（通常为 8-12 人）可能至少有 3-4 名女性（或男性）。这很重要，因为人们通常不希望成为船员中唯一的同性别的人。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/00049530.2021.1883409&quot;>;一个世纪&lt;/a>;的证据表明，人们在身处环境时会感受到更大的归属感和安全感与来自相似背景的其他人组成的小组。重要的是，&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/weykd6IKTp8&quot;>;负面行为&lt;/a>;，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/02678373.2022.2129514 &quot;>;欺凌&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0261927X12456383&quot;>;歧视性语言&lt;/a>;在性别平衡的工作环境中不太常见，部分原因是性别规范的负面影响减弱。事实上，必和必拓&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bhp.com/news/prospects/2019/10/the-gender-equation&quot;>;自己的分析&lt;/a>;发现，其性别平衡的团队效率更高、更快乐，更加投入，更重要的是，他们更加安全，可记录伤害率降低了 67%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;城市地区类似类型企业的领导者&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.igi-global .com/chapter/the-continuous-struggle-for-the-existence-of-females-in-the-construction-industry-in-the-21st- century/298290&quot;>;努力&lt;/a>;吸引女性。例如，在美国，女性&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nawic.org/statistics&quot;>;建筑行业工人仅占 10.9%&lt;/a>;，而且在传统的女性行业中，女性所占比例过高。办公室职位占主导地位（例如营销、人力资源、财务），而在 South Flank，大多数人从事一线职位（例如机械师、卡车操作员、电工），传统上由女性主导的办公室职位很少。&lt;/p>; &lt; h2>;为什么不能在所有企业都这样做？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;南翼位于地球上最热的地方之一。员工经常在室外工作，温度超过 45 °C (113 °F) 的情况并不少见。该矿距离最近的主要城市（珀斯）也超过 1300 公里（800 英里）。这意味着大多数员工必须从珀斯乘坐两小时的航班，然后连续八天轮班 12 小时，然后飞回家享受六天的休息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们很好奇这个孤立的矿井是如何运作的在性别平等方面取得了进展，而全球类似的工作场所却陷入困境。 2022 年底，南翼克领导委托我们举办一系列关于改变传统男性主导环境中消极行为的科学研讨会，我们在矿井待了六周，这是我们研究了数十年的主题。我们每周飞进飞出，像其他员工一样工作、睡觉和吃饭。我们获得了完全且不受限制的访问权限，这就是为什么在获得许可的情况下，我们决定利用这个机会通过观察、访谈和调查来收集数据。我们想了解南翼的独特之处。 （为了披露，南翼的管理人员有机会在提交本文之前审阅这篇文章。他们主要关注的是确保我们不会泄露有关他们运营的机密信息。他们没有对我们的研究结果进行更改。）我们的研究确定了南翼性别平等进步的五个驱动因素，但也发现了对这一进步的可持续性和当前性别关系的一些新威胁。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.高层领导的大力参与，制定了严格的性别平等目标&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;该矿总经理 (GM)，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bhp.com/news/articles/2022/04/bhp -2022 年女性资源奖决赛入围者&quot;>;史蒂夫·坎贝尔&lt;/a>;和他的高级管理人员通过深思熟虑的规划、大量投资、辛勤工作和创造力推动了进步。这与大量研究结果一致，这些研究发现工作场所多元化不会“随着时间的推移”或&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/how-to-close-the-gender-gap&quot;>;意外发生&lt;/a >;，或通过&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hup.harvard.edu/catalog.php?isbn=9780674276611&amp;amp;content=reviews&quot;>;强制性&lt;/a>;在线培训计划（这些计划在某些情况下实际上可以使事情&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/07/why-diversity-programs-fail&quot;>;更糟&lt;/a>;）。像他们这样的进步不仅需要高层领导者对多元化的“支持”，还需要更多的支持。这种类型的变革需要他们&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/09/gender-equality-is-within-our-reach&quot;>;深度参与&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;提高领导者的参与度在运营层面，South Flank 的总经理为中层管理人员设定了性别平等目标。这些目标与他们通常为铁矿石生产设定的目标相同。目标&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/10/companies-need-to-think-bigger-than-diversity-training&quot;>;努力&lt;/a>;推动多元化行动，重要的是，它们是正常且高效的挖掘中使用的工具，以实现更好的业务成果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，中层管理人员就得到支持，找到实现目标的方法。例如，他们被允许重组部门以重新创建入门级角色，这增加了潜在员工的渠道。这一点很重要，因为大多数从事采矿工作的男性都是没有技能的，并且有在工作中学习的机会。问题在于，对于女性来说，现代技术密集型采矿作业中大多数初级职位已被取消。通过重新创建初级角色，南翼克已经能够雇用具有各种专业背景的女性（例如农民、护士、卡车司机、机械师、运动员、教师、发型师），她们后来成为熟练的采矿员工。&lt; /p>; &lt;h3>;2.总部领导的大力支持&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;South Flank 的总经理和高级管理人员本身也得到了必和必拓高管的大力支持。该矿山相对较新，我们与必和必拓高层领导的对话表明该公司明白，它无法像经营传统矿山那样经营多元化和性别平衡的矿山。 South Flank 希望成为未来矿山的原型。必和必拓意识到在采矿业实现性别平衡的财务和社会重要性，但是，没有运营性别平衡矿山的路线图。 South Flank 和位于南美洲的另一个必和必拓矿场，性别比例达到 30%，正在帮助全球采矿业找到如何构建性别平等之路。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;必和必拓高级领导人的支持让许多人受益匪浅。形式，例如允许南翼雇佣更多培训师来支持刚接触采矿业的女性。南侧翼还被允许试点一系列成功的创新。例如，已经投资改造机器和设备，以便不同体型和体型的人都可以使用它们。还聘请了一名社会学家直接与管理者合作，帮助他们培养更加积极和包容的团队。另一项创新是独特的为期三天的入职和现场熟悉计划，该计划旨在支持新员工。它由专家团队以及高级领导（包括矿山总经理）提供。我们对最近招聘的员工进行了采访和调查，他们告诉我们，他们在上任的第一天从未受到过总经理或高级经理的亲自欢迎。新员工表示，这种独特的入职计划让他们感到受欢迎、有归属感，并为开始工作感到兴奋。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;3.大力投资打造温馨安全的采矿营地&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;采矿员工在工作时通常住在居住营地。传统上，下班后的焦点是在公司经营的现场小酒馆喝酒社交。南翼的领导人有意提供替代的社交方式，并培养一种对所有人，尤其是女性有吸引力的积极的、乡村式的文化。他们似乎成功了。例如，我们对微笑并为彼此敞开大门的人数感到震惊，这是我们在其他采矿作业中从未见过的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;必和必拓在南侧翼的娱乐设施上投入了大量资金，包括两个健身房、足球场、一个室外游泳池、一个图书馆、一个音乐室、一个位于山上俯瞰群山的土著教育中心、步行和健身赛道、篮球和壁球场，甚至还有一个室内高尔夫模拟器。此外，酒馆外还有许多草地供人们社交。为了鼓励新员工与其他人互动，团队会组织日常活动，例如问答之夜、美食节、有氧课程、客座演讲者（例如专业运动员）以及在专门建造的“MasterChef”风格厨房中举办夜间烹饪课程。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;该公司还在安全系统方面进行了重大投资，特别是自 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parliament.wa.gov.au/Parliament/commit.nsf/(Report+Lookup+ by+Com+ID)/EF1DF1A3F5DF74A848258869000E6B32/$file/20220621%20-Report%20No%202.pdf&quot;>;政府调查&lt;/a>;去年举行，调查采矿业内性侵犯和性骚扰的高发率更广泛地说（调查研究发现，36% 的女性和 10% 的男性在去年经历过某种形式的性骚扰）。 South Flank 已花费超过 1 亿美元用于新照明、闭路电视、电子门锁和安全。此外，还出台了新政策，例如严格限制每日饮酒量（四种中等强度酒精饮料）。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4.使用科学和数据驱动的方法来推动变革&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这些酒精限制是科学研究被用来确定基于证据的方法以降低性骚扰和性侵犯风险的一个例子。该矿目前正在与社会科学家合作，寻找其他&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/01/using-people-analytics-to-build-an-equitable-workplace&quot;>;数据驱动的方法&lt;/a>;来阻止排他性和有害行为。例如，我们受聘为 100 多名主管和中层领导举办一系列研讨会。他们对改变行为的最新研究感兴趣，特别是性别歧视和恐同语言（笑话、玩笑），这些语言仍然普遍存在，并且是一种&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.respectatwork.gov.au/individual/understand-workplace -性骚扰/什么原因-工作场所性骚扰&quot;>;性骚扰和性侵犯的关键风险因素&lt;/a>;。此外，我们还支持实施与其他大学的研究人员共同开发的新的“主动旁观者”培训计划。该计划正在必和必拓的所有业务中推广。旁观者培训让人们有机会练习挑战他们观察到的不尊重行为。令人惊讶的是，已经发表了多项关于学校此类培训有效性的试验，但我们没有发现在工作场所进行的已发表的试验。 South Flank 正在帮助解决这一研究空白。我们正在与 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.behaviourworksaustralia.org/&quot;>;BehaviourWorks&lt;/a>; 的同事一起，与 South Flank 的领导者合作，在采矿领域进行世界首次试验，以衡量短期以及提供工作场所旁观者培训的长期好处。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5.认识到性别平等很难实现和维持，需要持续的工作&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;南翼的领导人已经认识到，实现性别平等不仅仅是实现数字；而是实现性别平等。这是一个学习和改变的过程，需要持续的专注和努力。这项正在进行的工作体现在他们最近努力制止可能损害员工福祉和保留的规范性性别歧视和恐同语言。结束这种行为需要改变采矿业根深蒂固的男性规范和文化。这种文化本身就是为什么长期保留女性被证明是一个关键因素&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/metals-and-mining/our-insights/为什么女性要离开采矿业以及矿业公司可以做些什么“采矿业面临的挑战&lt;/a>;，女性因为缺乏包容性和成长机会而离开。还迫切需要开发&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.responsibleminingfoundation.org/app/uploads/EN_Research-Insight_Gender_Feb2022.pdf&quot;>;有效的系统&lt;/a>;和流程来支持想要重返校园的父母生完孩子后，他们在偏远矿山的一线工作。除非得到解决，否则采矿业和类似行业中的这一新问题将构成&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-15/the-battle-to-keep-women -in-mining/10118930&quot;>;对性别平等进展可持续性的重大威胁&lt;/a>;。更广泛地说，高级管理人员和董事会成员需要准备好&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dewr.gov.au/employing-and-supporting-women-your-organise&quot;>;重新设计商业模式&lt;/a >; 依赖于主要由男性组成的劳动力，而且传统上不承担家庭和育儿责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;我们必须停止因缺乏进展而指责女性&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;南翼克的领导人粉碎了“女性不想要驾驶卡车、爆破岩石和修理重型机械等高薪采矿工作”的神话。如果西澳大利亚州的一个偏远矿山能够实现 40% 的女性劳动力和超过 60% 的高级领导层，那么我们相信任何企业都可以做到这一点。重要的是，女性和男性都告诉我们，他们赞赏为创建性别平衡的劳动力队伍所做的努力。例如，一位二十岁出头的自卸车女司机说：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;“在我的老矿井，工作人员中只有我和另一名女性，我会收到尖刻的评论和人们很粗鲁。但这里更加平衡，人们更加友善，我在这里感到非常安全。 [在另一个矿井]你真的必须为自己的位置而战。尤其是从新手开始，要向上发展，你真的必须努力奋斗才能到达任何地方。而在这里，你所要做的显然就是表现出良好的职业道德，做一个好人，与每个人相处融洽，然后你就会发现自己在进步。”&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;A一位五十多岁的男性生产主管也同样表示，“现在所有女性都在这里工作，这是一个更好、更友好、更有支持性的工作环境。”然后他补充说，他很高兴 23 岁的女儿现在在 South Flank 工作：“这是一个很好的环境，她适应得很好。所以我很高兴她能从事采矿业。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;South Flank 是一个案例研究，它再次证明任何组织在性别平等方面取得进展都需要 &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/why- Sex-harassment-programs-backfire&quot;>;高层领导的深入参与&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/how-to-close-the-gender-gap&quot;>;辛勤工作&lt;/a>;。然而，我们的研究还发现，可持续进步需要大量持续的投资来开发&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/getting-serious-about-diversity-enough-already-with-the-business- case&quot;>;有意义地改变&lt;/a>;仍然排斥女性的工作场所行为和文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href= “https://feedx.best” style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 21:55:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Threads Foreshadows a Big &mdash; and Surprising &mdash; Shift in Social Media]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/threads-foreshadows-a-big-and-surprising-shift-in-social-media]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_13_1426548819_1484622203.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Jasmin Merdan/MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Threads, Meta&amp;#8217;s Twitter competitor, has become the fastest downloaded app in history. One of the reasons for this is because it allows users to port over their profiles and follows from the already popular social media platform Instagram, also owned by Meta &amp;#8212; a feature that may soon extend to open social media protocol Activity Hub. In doing so, Threads suggests that an alternative approach to social media, in which user data is portable, interoperable, and not controlled by the platform, may be going mainstream.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/threads-foreshadows-a-big-and-surprising-shift-in-social-media?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/threads-foreshadows-a-big-and-surprising-shift-in-social-media?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;On July 5, Facebook parent company Meta released &lt;a href=&quot;https://about.fb.com/news/2023/07/introducing-threads-new-app-text-sharing/&quot;>;Threads&lt;/a>;, a Twitter competitor that drew &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threads.net/t/CuZsgfWLyiI/&quot;>;70 million users&lt;/a>; in its first few days, dramatically outpacing other would-be Twitter replacements and becoming the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/threads-hit-100-million-users-in-under-a-week-breaking-chatgpts-record/&quot;>;fastest-growing&amp;nbsp;app&lt;/a>; in history.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A big part of the reason so many users joined so quickly was because it was easy: Threads was built as a sibling to Meta&#39;s established social photo sharing app Instagram, which already had &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-10-26/meta-s-instagram-users-reach-2-billion-closing-in-on-facebook&quot;>;2 billion users&lt;/a>;. This meant that users could port over their Instagram profile information — and, more crucially, the set of accounts they follow. Thus anyone joining Threads could, at least to some degree, transfer over their content preferences and social network directly — and anyone who had already built up a following on Instagram could carry that audience over.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It was only easy, however, for users who wanted to import their life from Instagram. Threads users whose previous social media focus had been Twitter had to re-build their social connections and audience from scratch. Many people (including both authors of this article) had to spend hours tracking down the people they followed on Twitter in the new environment. And everyone, even those who had previously been well-established on Instagram, had to build up a new content base from scratch.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nevertheless, the launch of Threads signals an important shift: It&#39;s the first mainstream glimpse of what social media based on partially or fully open software protocols — shared social media infrastructure that many different applications can leverage at once — could look like. Protocol-based social media allows users to transfer profiles, content, who they follow, and reputation information flexibly across platforms. While this may seem minor, it represents the transition from an era where users are locked into individual social media platforms to one in which they can move freely across them — a multi-application ecosystem powered by shared infrastructure.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear, Threads isn&#39;t an open ecosystem at present. But Instagram head Adam Mosseri &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/07/05/adam-mosseri-says-metas-threads-app-wont-have-activitypub-support-at-launch/&quot;>;has said&lt;/a>; that Threads aims to eventually enable access to an open social media protocol called &lt;a href=&quot;https://activitypub.rocks/&quot;>;ActivityPub&lt;/a>; (which powers the decentralized social media platform Mastodon), which would allow users to port over their follow graph and social media identity to a range of other apps. Meanwhile, a number of entrepreneurs are already designing social media products as open protocols from the get-go, and encouraging third-party developers to build various applications on top of them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This shift to protocol-based social media will have major implications for both users and companies. If this trend continues, users will increasingly have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://a16zcrypto.com/posts/article/decentralized-identity-on-chain-reputation/&quot;>;unified social media identity&lt;/a>; across different applications, and the flexibility to switch platforms without having to start over each time. For companies, a protocol model would catalyze third-party developer ecosystems to innovate on top of social media content and network architecture, contributing to broader innovation in the space.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Problems of Social Media Walled Gardens&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Today&#39;s top social media applications such as Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn are designed as “walled gardens” — self-contained ecosystems that lock users&#39; data inside the platform, and tightly control access. Although a user can export the posts, photos, and other content they&#39;ve created, there&#39;s no easy mechanism to migrate it elsewhere (other than re-uploading it manually, piece by piece). Moreover, there&#39;s typically no way to extract reputation information such as “likes” or network information such as the follow-graph, which means that whenever users join a new platform, they have to re-establish their following and reputation. Power users — those with the most curated content feeds, and/or the biggest audiences — are particularly disincentivized from switching.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All of this helps social media platforms entrench their market dominance. Because it&#39;s a pain to move to a competitor, users stick around even when their experience degrades. Platforms don&#39;t always make content curation decisions in their users&#39; best interests, and even when they try to, they don&#39;t always do a good job, as with Twitter&#39;s recent, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/technology/2023/2/16/23603155/elon-musk-twitter-worse-degrading-quality-glitches-superbowl-boost-feed&quot;>;widely&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/twitter-for-you-page-has-been-a-mess-under-elon-musk-1850008544&quot;>;criticized&lt;/a>; feed algorithm changes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For people who rely on platforms for their livelihoods, this can create even bigger headaches. Content creators can spend years building an audience and then lose it in an instant for a variety of reasons dictated by the people running the platform. Meanwhile, developers who build businesses leveraging social media platform APIs are also at the whim of platform owners. Walled-garden platforms can choose to change their API pricing, or revoke access entirely — as both &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.socialmediatoday.com/news/Twitter-Shuts-Down-Free-API-Access/641818/&quot;>;Twitter&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/new-reddit-api-pricing-strategy-could-mean-big-trouble-for-popular-third-party-apps&quot;>;Reddit&lt;/a>; recently did.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are downstream impacts, as well: With walled gardens, people&#39;s digital identities and social networks end up being disconnected and siloed across different platforms. People often have to focus on one or a few social media environments, which means the content they create may not reach the widest audience possible. Many of our colleagues, for example, have active followings for their business and technology posts on Twitter, but have never had time to build up engagement on LinkedIn, even though people there would probably appreciate their posts, too. When people do cultivate audiences on multiple platforms, they either have to split their content across them, or go through the inefficient process of reposting more or less the same content in each place.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;From Platforms to Open Protocols&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Social media based on open protocols, however, could address some of these problems. Making data interoperable across platforms would unlock cross-platform content consumption and reputation formation. It would also open up the potential for developers to remix and experiment with alternative feed algorithms and content delivery modes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Protocols are the software that makes up platforms&#39; inner machinery. They determine functionality, such as what information each user account holds and what types of content users can create, alongside the state, ie, the history of user data and interactions. Users interface with this interior machinery through front-end “application” layers called clients. For example, people interact with Twitter&#39;s backend protocol through a number of different applications, including the Twitter web and mobile clients, as well as clients like TweetDeck and HootSuite. But with Twitter, the platform itself controls access to the protocol; and indeed, it has recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/19/twitter-officially-bans-third-party-clients-after-cutting-off-prominent-devs/&quot;>;shut down&lt;/a>; a number of clients that compete with its main in-house apps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;An open protocol approach, on the other hand, puts the core software protocols on public computing infrastructure out in the open — often on blockchains — and records data in a standardized format that can be plugged into other apps. That allows users to link a single social account to many different platforms at once, complete with their followers/connections, and perhaps even the specific content they create and the reactions it receives. It&#39;s a bit like “login with Google,” but without the middleman.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In short, open protocol-based social media identities become unified and portable. A content creator might use a single protocol to syndicate short content to platforms like Threads and Twitter, photos to a platform like Instagram, and longer-form videos to a platform like YouTube or Twitch — with the “views” and “likes” statistics shared across all these platforms at once. A content consumer, meanwhile, could use a unified, protocol-level follow-graph to stay in touch with their favorite creators on all the social media platforms they visit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This use of open software protocols instead of closed platforms for social media is part of a &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/what-is-web3&quot;>;broader movement&lt;/a>; in Internet technology called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://a16zcrypto.com/posts/article/why-web3-matters/&quot;>;Web3&lt;/a>;,” which centers on &lt;a href=&quot;https://readwriteown.com/&quot;>;giving users direct control&lt;/a>; of their data and other digital assets, and making those digital assets usable flexibly across different platforms. As one of us (Kominers) &lt;a href=&quot;https://a16zcrypto.com/posts/article/decentralized-identity-on-chain-reputation/&quot;>;wrote&lt;/a>; with koodos labs co-founder Jad Esber and describes further in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0593545109&quot;>;forthcoming book&lt;/a>; with web3/marketing expert Steve Kaczynski, this model gives users an opportunity and an incentive to invest in building more complete, unified digital identities. Users can retain their identity and reputation as they move across different digital environments, just like they are used to doing in the physical world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Open protocol systems have clear theoretical advantages for users, developers, and businesses. For one, they allow for more competition by changing the relationship between social media users and platforms. If a given platform&#39;s quality declines — or if a new, better platform enters — then users can easily take their data and audiences with them to a competitor. As one of us (Kominers) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.competitionpolicyinternational.com/can-web3-bring-back-competition-to-digital-platforms/&quot;>;wrote&lt;/a>; with Lightspark Co-Founder and &lt;a href=&quot;https://mitsloan.mit.edu/centers-initiatives/cryptoeconomics-lab/welcome-mit-cryptoeconomics-lab&quot;>;MIT Cryptoeconomics Lab&lt;/a>; Founder Christian Catalini, this should hopefully &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.competitionpolicyinternational.com/can-web3-bring-back-competition-to-digital-platforms/&quot;>;enhance market competition&lt;/a>; and, in particular, encourage clients to compete on quality. But this process only works if the protocol creator credibly commits that the system will be open and accessible on an ongoing basis — typically by building the protocol on decentralized infrastructure, such as a blockchain, where it is not fully controlled by any single entity or individual.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Blockchain-based social media protocol Farcaster, for example, manages a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.farcaster.xyz/protocol/concepts/identity.html&quot;>;Name Registry&lt;/a>;” that gives each user an ID and username that can be used with any client that works with the Farcaster protocol. These are stored on the Ethereum blockchain, and attached to the user&#39;s personal Ethereum account. These accounts are in the user&#39;s locus of control, and so users can take their Farcaster protocol identities with them to any client in the ecosystem. Third-party developers are empowered (and encouraged) to build a diverse array of clients for different content formats and user segments. In fact, there is already a fledgling ecosystem of &lt;a href=&quot;https://farapps.farcase.xyz/&quot;>;third-party applications&lt;/a>; built on the Farcaster protocol. Non-blockchain based decentralized social media projects like Bluesky and Mastodon are building towards similar open ecosystems and benefits for their users, but with different technical backbones&lt;strong>;.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Threading the Needle&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Ironically, the ease of onboarding onto Threads for existing Instagram users gives a hint of the power of protocol-based social media by highlighting how valuable portable social media identity can be. At the same time, the difficulty of rebuilding Twitter followings on Threads illustrates how far we have to go to get there. And moreover, the quick growth of Threads relative to other Twitter competitors that have been around longer highlights the continued dominance of platform giants such as Meta in the social media space.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While the Threads news is significant, it&#39;s early days yet. At least for now, Threads is still part of a closed ecosystem controlled by Meta. And decentralized social media protocols have just a sliver of the user base seen on platforms like Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter. But if they do gain traction, they have the potential to become more embedded in our lives than even the current wave of social media applications. A unified digital identity makes it easier to connect it to a wider world of applications. Open-protocol social media encourages developers to experiment with new applications and variations on the technology to meet those users&#39; needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The biggest possible shift here, however, is the rules of the game. Right now, platforms hold onto their dominance by making users feel like they&#39;d be losing something if they walked away. But similar to open-source software, in a world of open-protocol social media the dominant market player is not the platform that manages to most effectively ensnare users, but rather the protocol that &lt;a href=&quot;https://a16z.simplecast.com/episodes/network-effects-moats-the-business-of-web3-eWugU00I&quot;>;becomes most embedded and useful&lt;/a>; across different applications. That&#39;s an overall more collaborative outcome that could create significant value for consumers, creators, and developers — and could lead to fast growth if/when user adoption does take off.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the same time, to gain widespread adoption, these protocols have to overcome significant hurdles. On top of all the ordinary barriers to entry in social media — people needing to re-establish their social graphs and content networks — there&#39;s a user education challenge. Mainstream social media users are used to the existing, platform-based landscape, and are mostly unfamiliar with the benefits of protocol-based approaches (as well as the blockchain technology many current social media protocols are built on).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The Threads launch proves that users can and will develop identities in new social media environments if given sufficient cause and opportunity. And there&#39;s been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2018/03/27/americans-complicated-feelings-about-social-media-in-an-era-of-privacy-concerns/&quot;>;growing&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://today.yougov.com/topics/technology/articles-reports/2023/04/18/what-do-americans-want-social-media-platform&quot;>;demand&lt;/a>; for social media applications where users have more direct control over their data and experience – owing in part to user frustration with centralized social media platform operators.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ironically, if Threads follows through with their promise to allow users to export and transfer their identities and social graphs to other platforms, this could prove to be a major catalyst for adoption of decentralized social media. But like with existing social media platforms, the biggest drivers of adoption will be killer applications. For Facebook, this was full-network social connection; for Twitter, it was real-time news media. With social media protocols, the most valuable applications will likely be those that leverage the protocol&#39;s interoperability — for example, by making it possible to creators to experiment with different content formats, and then syndicate and link related material across different clients.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whatever the case, with multiple clients feeding into the same protocol, the network feedback loop can be fast: Once someone finds their way to a protocol-based social media environment, they quickly build up an identity that can be used throughout the entire ecosystem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A social media future powered by open protocols should lead to more portable digital identities, as well as a panoply of competing applications catering to different user segments. The winning apps should be those that the most users freely choose to move to, unencumbered by switching costs. This both raises the bar for applications and creates an environment in which many of them can flourish in parallel — with users maintaining unified identities and reputations across them. This carries the potential of a more open and transparent social media landscape on the Internet — a place where we increasingly spend more of our lives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the meantime, you can find us on Twitter, Threads, and Farcaster.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Acknowledgments: The authors thank Cameron Armstrong, Shai Bernstein,&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;Sonal Chokshi, Kerry Herman, Miles Jennings, Steve Kaczynski, Eddy Lazzarin, Das Narayandas, Tim Sullivan, Mary Sun, Scott Walker, and especially Chris Dixon and Sriram Krishnan for helpful conversations and comments.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Disclosures: &lt;/em>;&lt;i&quot;>;Kominers is a Research Partner at &lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;ahttps://a16zcrypto.com/&quot; href=&quot;https://a16zcrypto.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot;>;&lt;i&quot;>;a16z crypto&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;i&quot;>;, which reviewed a draft of this article for compliance prior to publication.&amp;nbsp;a16z has invested in several decentralized social media platforms, as well as Twitter&amp;nbsp;(see general a16z disclosures&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;ahttps://a16z.com/disclosures/&quot; href=&quot;https://a16z.com/disclosures/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener noreferrer&quot;>;&lt;i&quot;>;here&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;i&quot;>;). Additionally, both Kominers and Wu hold various crypto assets; advise crypto and web3 projects; and regularly use both centralized and decentralized social media platforms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Nail Your Presentation &mdash; Even When Your Time Is Cut Short]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jun23_12_1285616.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Juan Moyano/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;One of the most common unpleasant surprises that you&amp;#8217;ve likely faced as a public speaker is getting your time cut short. You go into the meeting with a plan for what you&amp;#8217;re going to cover based on the allotted time you&amp;#8217;ve been given. And then, the technology doesn&amp;#8217;t work until 15 minutes into the meeting. Or the decision-maker shows up late, and you&amp;#8217;ve waited to start until they arrive. Or someone (and maybe everyone) in the group runs a few minutes over, and by the time it&amp;#8217;s your turn, those few minutes have compounded and you&amp;#8217;re left rushing to finish. Being an excellent public speaker requires planning as well as flexibility and resilience. Just because you don&amp;#8217;t have as much time as you&amp;#8217;d planned doesn&amp;#8217;t mean you can&amp;#8217;t have as much impact as you intended. This article covers three Plan B&amp;#8217;s that every speaker needs in case time gets cut short.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/nail-your-presentation-even-when-your-time-is-cut-short?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As a professional speaker for three decades, I&#39;ve had to deal with my fair share of surprises that could have completely derailed my presentation. Like what?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Like speaking during two separate blackouts without lights, AV, or functional toilets. Like facilitating a two-day training session where, in the middle of the first day, all participants got an email letting them know that layoffs were imminent. Like presenting in a glass-enclosed conference room inside the Congo exhibit at the Bronx Zoo, where a gorilla pounded the windows every time I advanced a slide. (I turned off the projector pretty quickly and proceeded anyway.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the most common unpleasant surprises that you&#39;ve likely faced as a public speaker is getting your time cut short. You go into the meeting with a plan for what you&#39;re going to cover based on the allotted time you&#39;ve been given. And then, the technology doesn&#39;t work until 15 minutes into the meeting. Or the decision-maker shows up late, and you&#39;ve waited to start until they arrive. Or someone (and maybe everyone) in the group runs a few minutes over, and by the time it&#39;s your turn, those few minutes have compounded and you&#39;re left rushing to finish.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This can be a lose-lose for both the participants and the presenters.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First of all, the participants are likely to experience an uneven distribution of content if the first speakers in a group get to take their time but later speakers have their messages truncated. Second, participants may miss the opportunity to ask questions, clarify understanding, and participate in a discussion if a presentation is shortened or accelerated. Participants are also less likely to understand what the speaker is saying if they&#39;re speaking quickly to finish before their time is up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Presenters don&#39;t have it much better. They&#39;re likely to feel pressured for time and frustrated with the situation (or their team members), which doesn&#39;t lend itself to an engaging presentation style. They may miss out on delivering &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/the-best-public-speakers-put-the-audience-first&quot;>;information that&#39;s important to the audience&lt;/a>; in favor of sharing what they really would prefer to talk about. And if they haven&#39;t practiced a shorter version of what they&#39;re planning to say, they may sound unprepared, nervous, and disjointed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One way to manage this dynamic in advance is to require everyone to practice their section of the presentation with a timer, and cut down their own presentations to meet their allotted time. This can help prevent the inevitable “time creep” in a group setting. A second step in managing this is to make sure that the host or chair doesn&#39;t over-program the meeting. They should ensure that the event has enough slack to allow for questions, comments, tangents, and even a glitch or two. Third, whoever is running the meeting should be skilled in managing questions, comments, and tangents against the time allotted for the meeting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And another way to deal with all of this is to make sure that everyone participating has a Plan B that they are willing and able to adapt to ASAP. Here are three Plan B&#39;s that every speaker needs in case time gets cut short:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Come prepared with two versions of your presentation.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Come with the full version of the presentation you planned, and a version that&#39;s 50% of what you&#39;ve planned. Make sure that you have practiced delivering both (just having a shorter deck won&#39;t prepare you to deliver an effective, shorter presentation). As soon as you start to realize that you&#39;re not going to have your full allotted time, revert to your shorter version. You might need to make some quick decisions about whether you still need to cut some content. And plan to let your listeners know that you&#39;ll provide additional context or content in writing after the meeting. Take the advice of English writer Sir Arthur Quiller-Couch, who &lt;a href=&quot;https://tinhouse.com/murder-your-darlings/&quot;>;coined the phrase&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;“murder your darlings”, which means being willing to cut content you care about objectively, and without sentimentality.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Just hit the headlines.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This means that you have to build your presentation headlines instead of headers. What&#39;s the difference between a header and a headline? A header is a neutral catch-all for what you&#39;re going to talk about in the slide whereas a headline provides the story of the slide right up top. It lets both the speaker and the audience know the bottom line first.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Compare these:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slide header: “2023 Economic Outlook”&lt;br>; Slide headline: “2023 Economic Outlook Looks Optimistic”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slide header: “Q2 Sales”&lt;br>; Slide headline: “Q2 Sales Bounce Back after Disappointing Q1”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Slide header: “Next Steps”&lt;br>; Slide headline: “Next Steps: Hiring, Onboarding, and Training”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you have a limited amount of time to present your findings, you can deliver an effective (albeit brief) narrative by just covering the headlines of your deck even if you don&#39;t get to explain the details of each slide.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Don&#39;t apologize, don&#39;t throw your colleagues under the bus, and don&#39;t sulk.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Behave as if this is exactly the version you&#39;d always planned to present. (It is highly likely that your audience won&#39;t know unless you tell them.) As much as you might be tempted to say something like, “If only our tech team had been prepared this morning…” or “Since my colleagues went overtime…,” don&#39;t do it. Stay professional and be collaborative. All of those conversations can happen &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; the meeting — not during.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, do some &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/managing-your-teams-emotional-dynamic&quot;>;emotional management&lt;/a>; so that you don&#39;t come across to your audience as angry, frustrated, resentful, or resigned. Emotions are contagious, and negative emotions are especially so. Unless you want your audience to feel the tension you feel, take a deep breath or two, and lean into your current reality of how it is rather than how you wished it could be.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Being an excellent public speaker requires planning as well as flexibility and resilience. Just because you don&#39;t have as much time as you&#39;d planned doesn&#39;t mean you can&#39;t have as much impact as you intended.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Simple Power of Communicating with Kindness]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-simple-power-of-communicating-with-kindness]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_12_1494065747.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Olena Koliesnik/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In today&amp;#8217;s world a host of issues are eating away at our connections with each other: Lack of focus, high-speed interactions, political polarization seeping into professional interactions, lack of trust. It&amp;#8217;s easy to let daily civilities go by the wayside &amp;#8212; or to approach difficult conversations with anger and ferocity &amp;#8212; but, the author tells us, her experience as a corporate communications executive points to the benefits for leaders who double down on kindness instead. She outlines three tactics that work: Breaking down defensiveness with graciousness, giving credit, and making space.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-simple-power-of-communicating-with-kindness?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-simple-power-of-communicating-with-kindness?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;I believe that in every interpersonal communication, leaders should err on the side of kindness. This pronouncement is seemingly simple but it takes courage to live — especially now.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We live in a world in which a host of issues are eating away at our connections with each other. Take lack of focus: When was the last time you had a conversation without one of the people involved checking their phone or multitasking? Or speed: We run from one thing to the next without reflecting on the human implications of what we just did.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But the challenge becomes harder when you consider that people may not &lt;em>;want&lt;/em>; to be kind. Of those who felt strongly about a particular social or political issue, only 30% of people said they would help someone who held a different point of view on the latest &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.edelman.com/trust/2023/trust-barometer&quot;>;Edelman Trust Barometer survey&lt;/a>;. As a result of political polarization, everything is becoming a political statement (think about masking coming out of the pandemic). Perhaps as a result of these factors, common incivility is &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/frontline-work-when-everyone-is-angry&quot;>;rampant&lt;/a>; in the workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From my four decades of working in government, business, and politics — in communications at the highest corporate levels, currently as executive vice president and chief corporate affairs officer at Pfizer — I&#39;ve found that great leadership is all about connecting with people by making them feel seen and heard. That means standing against all of these trends and impulses and instead practicing what I call “gracious communication.”&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;p>;This article is one in a series on “Creative Resilience: Leading in an Age of Discontinuity,” the theme of the 15th annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.druckerforum.org/&quot;>;Global Peter Drucker Forum.&lt;/a>; See the conference program &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.druckerforum.org/2023/program/&quot;>;here&lt;/a>;. &lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This involves small gestures and an overall demeanor that allow for connection. For a senior leader — as well as any aspiring leader — this kind of communication is important in day-to-day interactions as well as in big, difficult conversations. You&#39;ll find yourself enjoying stronger relationships and a respected leadership presence, as well as more creativity, resilience, and, ultimately, stronger leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here are three ways to do it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Break down defensiveness with graciousness. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Walking into an acrimonious situation is when I am at my kindest.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When I go to a tough environment such as a Senate hearing, or if I am being interrogated by a combative attorney, I always start by saying, “Thank you so much for inviting me here today.” I wear a smile when I say this, and I mean it. It shows that I&#39;m here to listen and contribute, not to stonewall anyone. And that&#39;s disarming: It lightens the mood and opens the ears. At the same time, it takes courage and shows your maturity. That allows for more creative, productive problem-solving.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To be clear, I&#39;m not saying that there is no place for showing anger to someone. If they hurt you or your family, for example, anger is an appropriate response. But it&#39;s not the most effective tool for opening minds and moving hearts. Anger shuts the other person down; kindness opens them up.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And, as a leader, others are always watching your communications, and if you are known to be someone who blows, you will be isolated from important negative news. An angry or volatile organizational culture makes it less likely that people will &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/make-it-safe-for-employees-to-speak-up-especially-in-risky-times&quot;>;speak up&lt;/a>; about important risks or problems. That makes your organization less able to respond quickly to crises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Give credit where credit is due.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;People like to be seen and appreciated. Recognizing those who deserve it engenders enthusiasm, hard work, trust, and loyalty. I remember the thank-you cards I received from my bosses years later and I&#39;ve made a practice of writing these for my team and giving them moments of recognition ever since.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Practicing gratitude also spurs my creativity: Reflecting on my interaction with someone after the fact often sparks an idea for another opportunity with them, or another way to continue the conversation. It helps me to slow down long enough for those ideas to emerge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Giving recognition is as powerful for your peers as it is for those you lead. I sit on an executive committee and every time I see someone in the group recognized (a scientist who won a prestigious award, or a manufacturing person achieved a new safety standard), I circulate it to the rest of the group. I do this because I admire the people I work with, and honestly believe what I&#39;m saying. But I also believe that it makes me, the credit-giver, look good too: It communicates that I have the maturity and self-confidence to appreciate someone else.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a surprising move because claiming credit is the big thing in the corporate world these days. Think about humblebragging: the trend in which someone bemoans how many horrible nights they stayed up late to finish an important project (the point for the audience being how important the project was and how big their role on it). Or posting on social media about how blessed or humbled they are to have achieved a huge promotion. It&#39;s endless and nauseating, because the need to claim credit for everything is destructive and counterproductive in the end.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The urge to claim recognition can be particularly strong if someone has just taken credit for your idea or your work. But before you step in to correct the record, think twice. People are observant; they can often see who is doing the work. Staying silent in that moment, rather than rushing to say “No, &lt;em>;I&lt;/em>; did it!” shows a lot about how confident you feel about yourself and can keep the door open for a connection with the other person.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;During the pandemic, for example, my boss and I originated an idea with the other big pharmaceutical firms to create a pledge that we would all abide by certain high safety standards and refrain from cutting corners in our race to a vaccine. You can imagine my surprise when, at a conference in 2022, I heard someone from one of the other firms claiming credit. The hairs went up on the back of my neck, my hands clenched, and for a moment I thought about interrupting the conversation and angrily issuing a correction. But didn&#39;t do it. I realized that if I had claimed my due credit I would have purposefully embarrassed someone else in public, and I would have cast doubt on the whole idea of us all being such good collaborators. I would have looked worse, and it cost me nothing to stay silent instead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there are situations where you should raise your hand and take a bow, such as when you are leading a team that achieved a stretch goal (in which case, say “we”) or when your company reputation is at stake. In the end, giving credit to others can be more powerful for you than taking it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Give the other party space and clarity.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;No matter what conversation you want to have with someone, don&#39;t catch them off their guard or off their game. Whether it&#39;s an innocuous quick question or a serious piece of bad news, always ask if it&#39;s a good time and try to give them a sense of what you want to discuss.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This gives your counterpart an opportunity to prepare themselves for any surprises or tough news that you need to share, and makes it clear that you are interested in listening to their response. It can also calm them down — they go from not knowing what to expect to understanding the lay of the land. It gives them a roadmap for your ramble.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This can be as simple as reaching out to a colleague and saying “Is now a good time to discuss our fall campaign?” (rather than just FaceTiming them at odd hours, which I used to do). It could be giving some emotional context for news that could be perceived in different ways.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For big issues this can require a little more preparation: I had something important to talk to my boss about the other week. I told him, “I&#39;d really appreciate it if we could find a few minutes during the offsite to talk about this issue I&#39;m having related to my team,” and sent him a few slides so he would know what it was about and knew to find me when he had 15 minutes, not two.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You won&#39;t always have time to prepare, but there are still ways to give the other person space. If the need to push back on something or deliver bad news comes up in the moment in a conversation, you can say “lLet&#39;s stop right there” and be candid. But if it is a group situation, if possible, wait until the meeting is over and then call them back. Let&#39;s say they said something offensive. Give them a call and say, “You may not know how that landed,” and discuss it from there. Shaming people publicly is not a good idea, but trying to educate others in private is a great idea.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whatever tactics you choose, the idea is not to burden the other person in your conversation, and instead to be outward focused — on the other person, not yourself. However hard that is, especially in today&#39;s polarized and fast-paced world, it pays big dividends toward your relationships, your leadership, and your own well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What SCOTUS&rsquo;s Affirmative Action Decision Means for Corporate DEI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_12_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Anja Sušanj&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While the Supreme Court&amp;#8217;s recent ruling on affirmative action is focused on government actors and universities, it&amp;#8217;s inevitable that some corporate leaders will use it as a reason to abandon diversity, equity, and inclusion programs they already opposed. However the authors argue that the court has left plenty of room to continue advancing DEI in the workplace. Three common practices will endure even if the law continues to evolve in a conservative direction: 1) practices to counteract bias, such as removing stereotypical language from job descriptions or conducting structured interviews with a standardized list of questions; 2) ambient policies that work to advance overall diversity, such as employee resource groups, mentorship programs, or family-friendly policies; and 3) universal policies, such as increasing psychological safety. These strategies are legally safe because they benefit everyone, but it&amp;#8217;s the people at the margins who stand to benefit most, precisely because they feel most excluded from workplaces without such initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-scotuss-affirmative-action-decision-means-for-corporate-dei?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Prior to the Supreme Court&#39;s recent bombshell decision on affirmative action, some predicted that a ruling to ban the practice would “&lt;a href=&quot;https://nypost.com/2023/05/31/affirmative-action-scotus-case-could-take-down-diversity-industry-too/&quot;>;take down&lt;/a>;” the diversity industry or deliver a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2023-06-22/supreme-court-affirmative-action-ruling-jeopardizes-corporate-diversity-too&quot;>;concussive&lt;/a>;” blow to workplace diversity and inclusion efforts. After the court effectively abolished race-conscious college admissions, some voices doubled down. The organization America First Legal — founded by former Trump advisor Stephen Miller — &lt;a href=&quot;https://aflegal.org/america-first-legal-puts-woke-corporations-law-firms-and-hospitals-on-notice-all-dei-programs-and-workplace-balancing-based-on-race-national-origin-and-sex-violate-the-law/&quot;>;declared&lt;/a>; that “all DEI programs” were now “illegal.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not so fast. We believe the court has left plenty of room to continue advancing diversity and inclusion in the workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We don&#39;t mean this in the most obvious sense, which is that the court&#39;s opinion focused on governmental actors and universities rather than on private employers. When the right case reaches the court, the same justices who just endorsed a “colorblind” approach to higher education could also hold that private employers cannot consider race, sex, or other protected characteristics in workplace decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such a ruling would indeed imperil the most aggressive pro-diversity policies. Reserving hiring or promotion slots for underrepresented groups, instructing managers to use race or sex as a “tiebreaker” when choosing between candidates, or setting strict demographic targets tied to manager compensation are all vulnerable to a judicial rebuke.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet diversity and inclusion initiatives extend far beyond the policies that travel under the moniker of affirmative action. Even assuming the law continues to evolve in a conservative direction, we believe at least three varieties of diversity and inclusion work will endure. We call these debiasing work, ambient work, and universal work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many common diversity and inclusion practices involve debiasing the workplace. In a canonical example, several decades ago, women composed only 5% of musicians in the top five orchestras in the United States. As of 2016, they were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/What-Works-Gender-Equality-Design/dp/0674089030&quot;>;more than 35%&lt;/a>;. Researchers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hup.harvard.edu/catalog.php?isbn=9780674986565&quot;>;attribute&lt;/a>; this dramatic increase in part to a simple design fix: The orchestras obscured the gender of musicians by requiring them to audition behind a screen.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While using a physical screen to improve the hiring process is impractical in most workplaces, many employers &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/7-practical-ways-to-reduce-bias-in-your-hiring-process&quot;>;adopt similar initiatives&lt;/a>; to debias their environments, such as purging stereotypical language from job advertisements, conducting structured interviews with consistent questions, and refining promotion processes to make them more transparent and merit-based. Most unconscious bias training — whatever you think of it — seeks to remove barriers to equal opportunity, so it&#39;s consistent with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-66058664&quot;>;the “colorblind” philosophy&lt;/a>; laid out by the six conservative justices in the court&#39;s recent ruling.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, while anti-discrimination law regulates discrete employment decisions, such as hiring and promotion, diversity and inclusion programs are often ambient. In our experience, it&#39;s a rare employer that explicitly tells managers to consider race or gender when choosing between job candidates. Instead, they typically adopt a variety of initiatives to advance workforce diversity overall, such as conducting outreach to diverse colleges, establishing employee resource groups, creating mentorship programs, and implementing family-friendly policies like nursing rooms and flexible work options. Even if a future Supreme Court decision declares that employers can no longer use race or gender to balance their workforce, these broader diversity initiatives involve no such thing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Importantly, a disgruntled employee cannot challenge an employer&#39;s diversity policies under the main federal statute regulating employment — Title VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 — merely because they feel frustrated or resentful. Rather, in a typical claim, the employee needs to show that they suffered an “adverse employment action” like being denied a job opportunity, refused a promotion, or fired. Then they need to show that the action was taken because of their race or sex. Simply pointing to the existence of the Black employee network or Women&#39;s History Month celebrations as evidence of discrimination won&#39;t cut it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, instead of interventions targeted at specific demographic groups, many organizations we work with are leaning into universal diversity and inclusion frameworks that lift all boats together. For example, the concept of “allyship” has swept corporate America in recent years, in part because the concept applies to everyone: We all have a mix of advantages and disadvantages, so we can all be allies to each other and receive allyship in return.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other universal frameworks focus on creating work cultures that allow for greater authenticity and self-expression, or that increase employees&#39; “&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/what-is-psychological-safety&quot;>;psychological safety&lt;/a>;” to speak up without fear of punishment. These strategies are legally safe because they benefit everybody, including members of historically dominant groups. But it&#39;s people at the margins who stand to benefit most, precisely because they are the ones who feel most excluded from workplaces without such initiatives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The court&#39;s colorblind turn is, unfortunately, a symptom of a broader cultural backlash that has put advocates of diversity and inclusion increasingly in a defensive crouch. Three years ago, on the heels of a resurgent Black Lives Matter movement, organizations were clamoring to demonstrate their commitment to social justice. Now, under pressure from activists and politicians on the right, many organizations are watering down their diversity initiatives and using economic conditions to &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-labor-report/corporate-diversity-pledges-fizzle-amid-layoffs-gop-backlash&quot;>;lay off&lt;/a>; the professionals who work on them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is perhaps inevitable that some corporate leaders will pounce on this Supreme Court ruling as a reason to abandon programs they already opposed. Yet these three varieties of work — debiasing, ambient, and universal — show that the era of diversity and inclusion is far from over. So long as employers do not use protected characteristics like race and sex when making concrete employment decisions, they are free to promote a more inclusive culture and break down barriers preventing women, people of color, and other marginalized groups from thriving in their workplaces. Given the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/research/why-diversity-and-inclusion-matter/&quot;>;benefits&lt;/a>; of a diverse and inclusive workforce for innovation, productivity, and employee engagement, such initiatives are not just an ideal, they&#39;re a necessity for businesses in the 21st century.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At a time of rapid demographic and social change, it is more urgent than ever to shape institutions so that everyone — regardless of their identity and background — can belong. That work remains essential and, crucially, legal, even under this activist Supreme Court.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Ecodesign Can Help the Environment and Your Bottom Line - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM SIEMENS]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/how-ecodesign-can-help-the-environment-and-your-bottom-line]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359826&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Header-visual_HBR.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;While many commitments to building a circular economy have been signed around the world, industries are still consuming more resources than can be regenerated. Today, it would take 1.75 Earths to feed global demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, only a little more than 7% of materials is preserved for further use, while the rest is sent to waste disposal (a sequence called “linear use of resources”). Thus, there will be more supply risks and price peaks ahead, putting economic growth at risk.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The linear use of resources endangers our environment. Natural resource extraction contributes to both climate change and more than 90% of biodiversity loss, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/biodiversity-report&quot;>;a recent study by the Ellen MacArthur Foundation&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So humanity has good reasons to get to work fast and implement circular economy principles in global businesses. In doing so, we can decouple resource consumption from growth in absolute terms. We can do more with less.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Circular Economy and Ecodesign&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What&#39;s key to successfully transitioning from a linear to a circular economy? It&#39;s product design. Up to 80% of a product&#39;s life cycle environmental impact is determined by its design. And that&#39;s where ecodesign comes in.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;How does ecodesign work?&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;While traditional product development focuses primarily on factors such as usability, safety, cost, and quality, ecodesign emphasizes ecological factors. This means finding ways to reuse materials, while maximizing the safe use and value of the product.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike traditional approaches to product design, ecodesign takes the entire product life cycle into account, including resource extraction, procurement, prototyping, series production, multiple product use, the end-of-life phase, and all logistics and transportation processes. Ecodesign product development goes far beyond the company gates, from “cradle to grave.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Implementing ecodesign represents a significant change for any organization. Making the strategy work requires the commitment of top executives, and it means teams must embrace new ways of thinking and working.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Robust Eco Design: Three Phases &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In 2020, Siemens introduced a dedicated, holistic ecodesign approach to its development processes called Robust Eco Design (RED). With RED, Siemens aims to systematically identify ways to achieve the same or greater customer value, while consuming less energy and fewer resources, minimizing the dissemination of nonnatural substances into the environment, and managing the required technical and biological resources in a circular loop.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On their way to environmentally compatible products, Siemens&#39; design departments follow a three-step-approach.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, teams specify environment-related customer requirements, such as energy efficiency or product longevity, and regulatory targets, such as the EU&#39;s Circular Economy Action Plan.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Then they collect comprehensive data on all inbound and outbound material and energy flows from the entire life cycle, including emissions to air, water, and soil as well as resources taken from nature. Subsequently, they quantify different designs&#39; environmental impacts and effects on human health and make those findings transparent to their stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Finally, they give recommendations for environmentally optimized design specifications that don&#39;t require trade-offs in areas such as safety or quality. Recommendations might include an increased use of recyclates or changes that allow for easy reuse, repair, refurbishment, remanufacturing, or recycling.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;How Digitalization Boosts Ecodesign &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some may argue that adding new environmental parameters to product design doesn&#39;t make decision making any easier. And to some extent, that&#39;s true. Organizations might face more conflicting requirements, such as stronger materials that enable more product longevity but also require more energy-intensive processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, digitalization and simulation can solve such challenges. “Digital twins” of real-life products can simulate the repairability or robustness of a product without wasting real-life resources. They can also support factories in cutting energy and resource consumption, CO&lt;sub>;2&lt;/sub>; emissions, and waste production by simulating production processes. Future-forward organizations need to bring in the technology and expertise that help them integrate these&amp;nbsp;powerful tools&amp;nbsp;with their operations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Digitalization also allows organizations to share emission data without disclosing strategic secrets. In open, cross-industry networks like Estainium, manufacturers, suppliers, and customers can exchange trustworthy product carbon footprint data.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;A Strategy That Makes Sense &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ecodesign is not just a matter of protecting climate and biodiversity. It&#39;s also a smart business strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By adopting ecodesign principles, companies can simultaneously reduce costs, minimize waste, and gain a competitive edge. The potential benefits are significant, including billions of dollars in cost savings for materials and new revenue streams through innovative business models like anything-as-a-service (XaaS). Collaboration across industries in open ecosystems can further amplify environmental and economic advantages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Taking the leap into circular economy practices is a major transformation. So make your sustainability efforts worthwhile and focus on product design, because that&#39;s how you maximize your impact—on both your bottom line and our environment.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Learn more about ecodesign and how to build your “circular advantage” in Siemens&#39; white paper &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.siemens.com/global/en/company/sustainability/environment.html?stc=decg211247&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Ecodesign: Multiplying impact, shaping the world&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;. &lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[To Get Better Customer Data, Build Feedback Loops into Your Products]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Daniel Creel&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Thanks to the increasing availability of AI, including machine learning algorithms, deliberately creating &lt;em>;customer data feedback loop&lt;/em>;s is now possible for most products and services. This means that as a firm gathers more customer data, it can feed that data into machine learning algorithms to improve its product or service, thereby attracting more customers, generating even more customer data. For some products, it is easy; for others, one needs to find more creative ways to engineer the data feedback loops. This article explains how to do so.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/to-get-better-customer-data-build-feedback-loops-into-your-products?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The combination of user data and AI often creates data feedback loops. This means that as a firm gathers more customer data, it can feed that data into machine learning algorithms to improve its product or service, thereby attracting more customers, generating even more customer data. Think, for example, of search engines: the more people search on Google and click on the links provided, the more data Google gathers, which allows its algorithms to provide more accurate and relevant search results, attracting even more users and searches, and so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such data feedback loops can help create a &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/01/when-data-creates-competitive-advantage&quot;>;sustainable competitive advantage&lt;/a>;, provided that &lt;a href=&quot;https://platformchronicles.substack.com/p/six-questions-to-evaluate-data-enabled&quot;>;certain conditions exist&lt;/a>;. But the strength of these data feedback loops can vary greatly, and companies can make deliberate choices in their products or services to strengthen them. How to do so is the focus of this piece.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Not All Data Feedback Loops Are Created Equal&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Some products have naturally very strong data feedback loops. Think of smart thermostats, where every temperature adjustment by a user provides a valuable data signal that the device can use to achieve better personalization. Or Google Maps, where every user&#39;s choice of route and the time taken to reach the destination help the algorithm improve its route recommendations and traffic predictions. Or Spotify, whose recommender system learns directly from users&#39; choices of which recommended songs to include in their playlists and how often they listen to those songs. The reason these feedback loops are so strong is that users reveal clear and unambiguous signals of their preferences in the natural process of consuming the product, which are leveraged to further improve the product or the service for those users.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the other end of the spectrum are products with naturally weak data feedback loops. Their usage is hard to track or does not reveal useful information about user preferences, or it is difficult and slow to gather informative feedback from users.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is obviously true of traditional “dumb” products like cars, furniture, and clothes: They are not digitally connected, so the only way to create any data feedback loops from customers is to manually collect feedback via focus groups and surveys, which can only help for future product releases. And it is also true of products where the feedback loops involve very long cycles of learning and improvement such as financial institutions&#39; credit scoring systems (feedback mainly comes from defaults, which take years to materialize), or venture investing (it takes years to figure out which startups succeed and which fail).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Less obvious is that even some digital products that collect lots of user data may have weak data feedback loops. This means most of their value comes from pre-programming and in-house data training and does not increase much, if at all, via learning from users.&amp;nbsp;For instance, popular wearables such as Fitbit, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whoop.com/&quot;>;Whoop&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://to.nutrisense.io/&quot;>;Nutrisense&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ouraring.com/&quot;>;Oura&lt;/a>; have fairly weak data feedback loops, even though they provide lots of data insights.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the latest Fitbit tracker, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;Charge 5&lt;/a>;, which has an impressive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/products/trackers/charge5?sku=421BKBK&quot;>;list of features&lt;/a>;. The tracker measures a wide array of data from the user (heart rate, speed and distance of movement, sleep, skin temperature) and provides valuable insights such as heart rate variability, time spent in different heart rate zones, a cardio fitness score, a readiness score for working out, a quality of sleep score. However, these insights do not appear to get better with more usage or more users. They are straightforward summary statistics of what is being measured by the tracker, or the result of comparisons between user data measured by the Fitbit tracker and relevant reference points based on pre-existing research, which are pre-programmed in the Fitbit system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Fitbit &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.fitbit.com/articles/en_US/Help_article/2096.htm&quot;>;explains&lt;/a>; that “the cardio fitness score is determined by your resting heart rate, age, sex, weight, and other personal information.” Similarly, the readiness score &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitbit.com/global/us/technology/daily-readiness-score#:~:text=Your%20Daily%20Readiness%20Score%20uses,to%20gauge%20your%20energy%20levels.&amp;amp;text=Heart%20rate%20variability%20(HRV)%20is,contribute%20to%20a%20high%20score.&quot;>;is based on&lt;/a>; the user&#39;s recent sleep patterns as measured by the tracker — which are presumably compared to some stable reference points. In other words, these are estimates of the “true” state of a user, but they do not improve with more usage data, simply because Fitbit has no way of figuring out how close its estimates came to the “true” state and adjusting them accordingly.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, there may be some limited ways in which wearables could improve the value provided to each user based on usage data from that user or other users. At the most basic level, any connected product can learn which user interface is more engaging (eg, via A/B testing), which is technically a form of data feedback loop, albeit a limited one — table stakes for most products.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;And there are correlations that wearables could analyze to recommend behavior. For instance, a correlation between the time users go to bed and the quality of their sleep, which can be used to recommend an optimal time to go to bed; or between the time users exercise and the quality of their sleep, which can be used to recommend an optimal time to exercise. In these cases, as users adjust their behavior based on the recommendations, the wearable gets some feedback on whether this is helping or not, and so can further improve by learning from users. Still, this type of process requires lots of data from lots of users, and the wearable provider may never really know the extent to which correlation means causation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, consider the data feedback loops of large language models (LLMs) such as Open AI&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://chat.openai.com/&quot;>;Chat GPT&lt;/a>; or Google&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://bard.google.com/&quot;>;Bard&lt;/a>;. These models ingest enormous amounts of data from the web and use machine learning models to generate answers to user questions. In the early versions of these models, their capabilities are largely determined by pre-launch “in-house” training and testing — the quality of their answers improves only to a moderate extent with more users or more usage. Indeed, as of this writing, there are two main mechanisms that create data feedback loops around LLMs:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Users click on the thumbs-up or thumbs-down buttons at the end of the answers. (Most users probably ignore this most of the time.)&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Users ask follow-up questions, which could signal whether an answer was satisfactory or not. (This inference is likely difficult in most cases.)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Note the difference with regular search (on Bing or Google), where the user&#39;s choice of which displayed links to click on provides a much clearer signal of the relevance of the search results. Of course, things may change drastically as the LLMs are updated and start incorporating more reliable ways to generate data feedback loops — a topic we discuss in the next section.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to Enhance Data Feedback Loops&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The key question is then, for those products where the data-enabled learning feedback loops are not naturally strong, what can be done to enhance them?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;(Re)design the product to create natural data feedback loops.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Ideally, one would want to (re)design the product or service in such a way that customers, in the natural course of using the product, are creating data that signals how useful/effective the product is for users. This data can then be used by the provider to improve the quality of the product or service.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, LLMs could add new features that allow users to save and organize the responses they found most helpful into folders of favorites (akin to bookmarks) and delete those they don&#39;t want to keep. They could add a document-creation feature (akin to Microsoft Word) where they would copy and edit LLM responses. They could also create challenge games (AI vs. users) and leader boards where the AI and users seek to answer questions, and users vote on the answers. And so on. The idea is to create opportunities for users to provide reliable signals of the perceived quality of the LLMs&#39; answers, which can then be used to improve their algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fitbit and other wearables could add standardized fitness tests or challenges (eg, run one mile or do three sets of 20 sit-ups) and measure users&#39; total time, heart rate, and other biometrics before and after. This would allow the wearables&#39; AI to more accurately predict users&#39; readiness for working out as they observe more data from more users. Which in turn should induce users to rely on the wearables more and more for deciding when to work out. Of course, this still relies on assumptions about unobserved user behavior, but the key point is that the devices need to perform some sort of quasi-experiments on users in order to obtain data that can help them learn and improve.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Integrate with other products to create data feedback loops.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In many cases, redesigning the actual product or service to engineer feedback loops may be challenging (as illustrated by the wearables example above). An alternative way of achieving the same goal is to integrate your offering with other existing products that customers already use or could use.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Fitbit (or Whoop or Oura) could create an integration with smart thermostats to enable the wearable to automatically control the ambient temperature during a user&#39;s sleep. This would allow the wearable&#39;s AI to adjust the temperature and determine its effect on the quality of a user&#39;s sleep as measured by the wearable. The more a customer uses the wearable (ie, wears it to sleep), the closer the wearable can come to figuring out the ideal temperature pattern for any given user. This can be achieved by automatically experimenting with many different temperature patterns as the user sleeps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Or the wearables could integrate with Peloton or Tonal, which provide standardized workouts, so that Fitbit&#39;s AI could correlate a user&#39;s biometrics with the type and intensity of workouts. The advantage relative to the option described above (where the wearables are simply asking users to perform specific workouts) is that here the actual workout behavior can be observed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, LLMs could integrate with whatever software or tools their answers are being used in. For example, they could integrate with content creation/editing software (eg, Google Docs, Substack, Salesforce), which would allow them to observe which parts of their answers end up being used in the content created by users and use that data to improve their answers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Ask users for feedback in a minimally intrusive way that makes the benefits clear to them.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Still, for many products, finding such ways of making user feedback inherent to product usage — directly or via integration — may be hard or impossible. Short of that, the next-best option is to explicitly ask users for feedback. Most online products and services do this to a certain extent. As mentioned above, LLMs ask users for thumbs-up or down after every answer generated; Netflix asks users for a thumbs-up or down after each piece of content they watch in order to improve its recommendation system; Amazon asks buyers to rate the products they purchased; Airbnb asks both travelers and hosts to rate each other, and so on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, the difficulty with asking for explicit feedback is obtaining useful information while not inconveniencing users too much. Nobody likes being badgered with surveys that “only take three minutes of your time,” or seeing feedback polls (“how likely are you to recommend us to your friends?”) pop up every other screen.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to making requests for user feedback as easy and painless as possible, it helps to clearly communicate to users how that feedback might benefit them personally whenever possible (eg, “by rating this movie, Netflix will be able to give you better recommendations of which other movies you are likely to enjoy”). This ensures that they have an incentive to provide honest feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Include humans in the loop.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;An important way to manufacture a data feedback loop while minimizing the feedback burden on users is to include humans in the loop to complement (or even replace) user feedback. A good example of this is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexi.com/&quot;>;Alexi&lt;/a>;, an AI-powered legal research service offered to law firms. Customers can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.alexsei.com/howitworks&quot;>;submit legal questions&lt;/a>; along with any relevant case facts, and Alexi sends back a legal research memo containing an answer, complete with summaries of the relevant case law and litigation. The memos are generated by Alexi&#39;s AI but then reviewed and amended (when necessary) by Alexi&#39;s in-house legal team — the humans in the loop. Thus, Alexi&#39;s AI gets the benefit of learning from customer queries and the implicit feedback provided by the in-house team&#39;s corrections, without burdening customers. This works well here because customers do not expect instant answers. (Alexi promises an answer within 24 hours, a very reasonable turnaround in this context.) Nor do they ask hundreds of questions a day like Chat GPT or Bard users might.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another example of good use of humans in the loop is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.grammarly.com/&quot;>;Grammarly&lt;/a>;, an AI-powered writing assistant that helps users improve grammar, spelling, punctuation, and style. Grammarly provides suggestions in real time, while users are writing in any application or site (eg, word processing, email, social media, communication apps). Users have the option to accept or reject the suggested edits, which obviously helps improve the algorithm and creates a data feedback loop. However, Grammarly also uses human reviewers to check the suggestions made by the AI model and review ambiguous cases (a user rejects a suggested edit, but it is unclear why he did so), instead of asking users for feedback.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other examples of AI-based products or services that use humans in the loop to complement or replace user feedback include content moderation on social media platforms (human moderators get involved in the most complex cases that the AI has trouble with), AI-powered radiology services such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gleamer.ai/&quot;>;Gleamer&lt;/a>; (human specialists complement AI diagnostics and would correct any issues in the diagnosis the system automatically writes up), and AI-powered security services such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deepsentinel.com/&quot;>;Deep Sentinel&lt;/a>; (the AI detects threats and decides when to escalate to human guards, who can then decide whether the AI made the correct call).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, the main weakness of the humans-in-the-loop approach is that it does not scale well to hundreds of thousands or millions of customers or to services with very high frequency of usage and expectation of quick turnaround times. Not many companies can afford to hire armies of over 15,000 content moderators as Meta does for Facebook. This is why most companies employing humans in the loop try to minimize the time required from humans in the process. Nevertheless, the humans-in-the-loop approach can be very effective in the early stages of a product/service, when the learning curve is steepest. The hope is that the need to involve humans decreases rapidly over time as the AI system learns.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The increasing availability of artificial intelligence, including machine learning algorithms, means that deliberately creating data feedback loops is now possible for most products and services. For some products, it is easy; for others, one needs to find more creative ways to engineer the data feedback loops — via integrations or minimally intrusive requests for user feedback that provide benefits for the users. When they are strong, these feedback loops can create a form of network effect (more users bring more data, which makes the product better, in turn attracting more users, and so on) and compounding competitive advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Factors That Make for a Great Employee Experience]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_200021503-002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daly and Newton/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Decades of business strategy have urged leaders to concentrate the bulk of their business efforts on the customer experience. While prioritizing customers over employees can drive short-term revenue growth, it will cost companies in long-term employee retention and engagement. The author and colleagues conducted a new study of thousands of employees and executives from around the world and across multiple industries. Using regression analysis, they pinpointed the five most important factors in creating a better employee experience: mutual trust, C-suite accountability, alignment of employee values and company vision, recognizing success, and seamless technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/5-factors-that-make-for-a-great-employee-experience?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;We&#39;ve heard the adage that happy employees make happy customers, but new data reveals just how significant the impact of the employee experience is — and how to use it to unlock organizational growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Decades of business strategy have urged leaders to concentrate the bulk of their business efforts on the customer experience. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=4215010&quot;>;recent Columbia study&lt;/a>; found “that executives talk about customers 10 times more often [in earnings calls] than employees. And when they do, executives perceive customers to be analogous to opportunities and employees to risks.” And even when companies talk a good employee-experience game, they still actually act on customer experience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While prioritizing customers over employees can drive short-term revenue growth, it will cost companies in long-term employee retention and engagement. According to research my Salesforce colleagues and I conducted, a company could increase revenues by up to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/research-how-employee-experience-impacts-your-bottom-line&quot;>;50% by improving the employee experience&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I wanted to identify the key drivers of the employee experience in order to help executives improve it. For my forthcoming book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Experience-Mindset-Changing-Think-Growth/dp/059354269X&quot;>;&lt;em>;The Experience Mindset&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, my colleagues and I conducted a new study of thousands of employees and executives from around the world and across multiple industries. Using regression analysis, we pinpointed the five most important factors in creating a better employee experience:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Mutual trust&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;There are two kinds of trust: your employees&#39; trust in your organization and your organization&#39;s trust in its employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Mutual &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/begin-with-trust&quot;>;trust&lt;/a>; results in employee empowerment. It demonstrates management&#39;s confidence in its workforce, which fuels employees&#39; trust in leadership and each other. It also motivates employees, promotes creativity and collaboration, improves retention, and reduces risk aversion, all helping the bottom line. That empowerment and trust is evident at companies like Apple, where store employees needn&#39;t request special approvals to solve many customer problems, and Ritz-Carlton, where workers can spend up to $2,000 to fix a guest issue without managerial approval.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Mutual trust also helps workers feel heard. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/hybrid-work-making-it-fit-with-your-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-strategy&quot;>;According to McKinsey&lt;/a>;, that kind of inclusion leads to a 47% increased likelihood that employees will stay with a company and a 90% increased likelihood they&#39;ll go out of their way to help each other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When Clear Co, a Toronto-based financial lending firm, started experiencing hyper-growth, CEO Michele Romanow wanted to &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/whats-next-podcast/enter-the-dragons-den-with-serial-entrepreneur-michele-romanow&quot;>;modernize its processes&lt;/a>; while maintaining its entrepreneurial culture. So she set up an email inbox with the colorful title, “The stupid sh*t we do!” and asked employees for ideas on streamlining the business and removing preventable frustrations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to Romanow, this simple exercise accomplished two goals. First, it gave employees a sense of ownership and involvement in improving their day-to-day lives and helping the company. Second, it created a feedback loop permitting leadership to build employee trust while surfacing and addressing issues before they metastasized.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. C-suite accountability&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Closely related to trust, C-suite accountability means ensuring company leadership is committed and responsive to both the business and its workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On one level, accountability is about a willingness to ask questions and actively listen to the answers. A leader can&#39;t address employee needs they don&#39;t know about. More broadly, it speaks to culture: An enterprise with strong C-suite accountability understands the importance of employee experience and prioritizes it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s often a difference between companies&#39; talk and their actions. We found in our research that while 49% of C-suite executives believed their company excels at acting on employee feedback (honestly, a low number), only 31% of workers agreed. That gap can swallow growth, momentum, and talent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Create a culture in which everyone understands that employee experience is a collective responsibility. Hilton, for example, established cross-functional teams that ensure a formal, structured way for the C-suite to keep tabs on employee experiences. As Chris Silcock, Hilton&#39;s EVP and chief commercial officer, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/salesforce/2020/11/05/how-hilton-uses-the-golden-rule-to-drive-commercial-success/?sh=4661f676733c&quot;>;has observed&lt;/a>;, “How you treat your team members guides how they treat your customers.” Hilton has repeatedly been named one of Fortune&#39;s “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greatplacetowork.com/best-companies-to-work-for&quot;>;Best Companies to Work For&lt;/a>;.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At your company, this could look like an experience advisory board to help break down traditional barriers and facilitate brainstorming and ideation; a center of excellence to deliver best practices where there are knowledge or skills gaps; employee resource groups to provide peer-to-peer counseling and boost career development; or “voice of the employee” surveys to solicit and gather employees&#39; needs, wants, and expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Alignment of employee values and company vision&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Employees want to align with their company&#39;s values, but that makes the C-suite responsible for clearly enunciating them — and then making sure corporate actions are consistent with them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Clear goals with well-defined milestones and success metrics connect employees to their company&#39;s mission and help them understand their role in advancing it. We found in our research that ensuring employees feel valued and core to the company vision is a significant driver of reported increases in revenue. However, only 36% of employees reported feeling that way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A company culture that supports an experience mindset understands the intrinsic connection between what it does internally for employees and how that translates into its customers&#39; experiences. Airbnb, for example, hired the first head of employee experience at a major US corporation, in 2013. “Culture is simply a shared way of doing something with passion,” CEO Brian Chesky wrote then in a Medium post titled “&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@bchesky/dont-fuck-up-the-culture-597cde9ee9d4&quot;>;Don&#39;t F*^k Up the Culture&lt;/a>;.” “The stronger the culture, the less corporate process a company needs. When the culture is strong, you can trust everyone to do the right thing.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Alignment is a major part of that culture, starting before employees even join Airbnb. The company conducts two separate “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegrowthfaculty.com/blog/Employeeexperiencestaffretention?recacheSoql=true&quot;>;core values interviews&lt;/a>;” run by team members outside of the hiring function so they can assess cultural fit independent of the job opening&#39;s specific needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4. Recognizing success.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As the activist and philanthropist &lt;a href=&quot;https://chopra.com/articles/what-you-appreciate-appreciates&quot;>;Lynne Twist has observed&lt;/a>;, “What you appreciate appreciates.” Recognition can be a &lt;a href=&quot;https://focus.kornferry.com/employee-recognition-the-secret-ingredient-to-high-employee-engagement-asean/&quot;>;cost-effective way to boost employee engagement&lt;/a>;, which has positive spillover effects on loyalty, retention, and productivity. Workers who believe their success will be recognized are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quantumworkplace.com/future-of-work/importance-of-employee-recognition&quot;>;2.7 times more likely to be highly engaged&lt;/a>; than peers who don&#39;t, according to the employee engagement firm Quantum Workplace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Praise is not the sum total of recognition, of course. It also involves identifying and nurturing potential, giving employees the skills needed to grow. &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/use-purpose-to-transform-your-workplace&quot;>;Unilever&lt;/a>;, for example, created a leadership development program encompassing the entire organization. In leadership development workshops, employees create individually tailored “future fit plans,” each focused on a purpose that&#39;s both important to the individual and in keeping with company goals. The result? Ninety-two percent of those who attended a workshop said that their jobs inspire them to go the extra mile, while only 33% of those who had not attended felt the same way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;5. Seamless technology to reduce employees&#39; day-to-day friction&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Too often, executives throw technology at problems as a way to fix company performance, productivity, and costs but give too little thought to how it fits into the rest of the organization&#39;s infrastructure, existing processes, and people&#39;s workflows. As engineer and management consultant W. Edwards Deming put it almost 40 years ago, “Eighty-five percent of the reasons for failure are deficiencies in the systems and process rather than the employee. The role of management is to change the process rather than badgering individuals to do better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/survey-employees-want-business-technologies-to-be-more-collaborative&quot;>;common employee complaint&lt;/a>; is the sheer volume of applications they need to navigate between to do their work. &lt;a href=&quot;https://resources.mulesoft.com/ty-report-connectivity-benchmark.html#loaded&quot;>;Enterprises use an average&lt;/a>; of more than 1,000 different applications, only 29% of which are integrated (ie, communicate with one another).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Technology is not an end in itself but a tool for increasing productivity and reducing effort. And yet our research shows that technology is one of the most poorly rated dimensions of employee experience: Fewer than one in three employees said their company&#39;s technology works effectively, and fewer than one in four said they&#39;re equipped with seamless technology. Even the C-suite gets this: Only 52% of executives said that their company provides employees with tech that works effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Can you imagine asking your customers to toggle between multiple tabs just to place an order with you? Probably not — most companies work hard to reduce this kind of friction for customers. Yet that&#39;s what we ask of our employees every day when the systems they use aren&#39;t integrated. The result is reduced satisfaction and a terrible employee experience. We must ensure that both the customer experience and employee experience get equal resources. Saving customer time nets out little or no gain if you&#39;re shifting that effort to your employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Revitalize the Employee Experience&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Covid-19 and the Great Resignation inspired workers to reevaluate their priorities and empowered them to act. That has spurred companies to relearn what was once a given: that their most valuable resource is their people.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What began as a wakeup call for how leaders can save their companies from a talent exodus can also be an opportunity for growth and competitiveness — but only if they learn to balance their customers&#39; experiences with those of their workers by focusing on trust, C-suite accountability, alignment, recognition, and technology.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These five elements are intertwined. Each builds on the others to establish a stronger employee experience and unleash new value. Happy workers make happy customers, and managing the nexus between the two will make leaders and investors happy, too.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The State of Globalization in 2023]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_11_1383390211.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Grizelj/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Plummeting flows of trade, capital, and people at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic prompted a wave of speculation about the end of globalization, and Russia&amp;#8217;s invasion of Ukraine brought even more predictions of a retreat toward national self-sufficiency. But, according to research for the latest DHL Global Connectedness Index, international flows show no signs of a sustained downturn. The data shows a broad pattern of decoupling between the US and China, but the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China do not &amp;#8212; at least yet &amp;#8212; indicate a broader split between rival blocs. Nor is there evidence that globalization is giving way to regionalization. While companies do need to adjust for heightened geopolitical tensions, they should not abandon global strategies. Corporate deglobalization, in fact, could be a riskier path than making focused adjustments to mitigate geopolitical risks.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/the-state-of-globalization-in-2023?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Three key questions lie at the heart of debates about whether global crises and escalating geopolitical tensions have begun to reverse globalization: Has the growth of cross-border trade, capital, information and people flows gone into reverse? Are geopolitical tensions fracturing the world economy into rival blocs? And is globalization giving way to regionalization? The answer to all three questions — despite evidence of US-China decoupling — is still “no.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This result — decoupling without deglobalization — implies that most multinational firms should respond to elevated geopolitical tensions with focused adjustments to their global strategies and risk management. While the public-policy environment has become less conducive to globalization, the resilience of global flows cautions against more dramatic strategy changes predicated on the notion that markets will become substantially less globalized.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Has the Growth of Global Flows Gone into Reverse?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Plummeting flows of trade, capital, and people &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/will-covid-19-have-a-lasting-impact-on-globalization&quot;>;at the beginning&lt;/a>; of the Covid-19 pandemic prompted a wave of speculation about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://foreignpolicy.com/2020/04/03/coronavirus-end-globalization/&quot;>;end of globalization&lt;/a>;, and Russia&#39;s invasion of Ukraine brought even more predictions of a retreat toward &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/breakingviews/ukraine-speeds-global-rush-self-sufficiency-2022-03-09/&quot;>;national self-sufficiency&lt;/a>;. But international flows show no signs of a sustained downturn.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;DHL Global Connectedness Index&lt;/a>;, developed by our team at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://stern.nyu.edu/globalization&quot;>;NYU Stern Center for the Future of Management&lt;/a>;, measures the “depth” of globalization by comparing the growth of international flows to the growth of domestic economic activity. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/global-en/delivered/globalization/global-connectedness-index.html#parsysPath_download_box_copy_co&quot;>;latest report&lt;/a>; shows that the globalization of trade, capital, and information flows was already above pre-pandemic levels by 2021 and that the recovery of international people flows accelerated in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360176&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_INDEX_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;Source: DHL Global Connectedness Index 2022&quot; title=&quot;Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;626&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Global Flows Have Mostly Returned to Above Pre-Pandemic Levels. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International trade rebounded quickly after &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/will-covid-19-have-a-lasting-impact-on-globalization&quot;>;plummeting at the beginning&lt;/a>; of the pandemic. The volume of world trade in goods &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-november-2022&quot;>;reached 10%&lt;/a>; above pre-pandemic levels in mid-2022, and trade in services was also back above &lt;a href=&quot;https://documents.worldbank.org/en/publication/documents-reports/documentdetail/099444311022220882/idu026d6c21108fa504c770ae550637a6bc89aa7&quot;>;pre-pandemic levels&lt;/a>;. Preliminary data &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;indicate&lt;/a>; the value of world exports as a share of GDP rose in 2022, matching the &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/NE.EXP.GNFS.ZS&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>; set in 2008. In late 2022, slowing global economic growth caused trade &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpb.nl/en/world-trade-monitor-march-2023&quot;>;to weaken&lt;/a>;, but the International Monetary Fund (IMF)&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/04/11/world-economic-outlook-april-2023&quot;>;latest forecast&lt;/a>; still calls for trade to grow at a modest 2.4% pace in 2023 before accelerating to a more typical (3.5%) rate in 2024.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International business investment also recovered swiftly from declines at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic. Foreign direct investment (FDI) flows, which reflect companies buying, building, or reinvesting in operations abroad, collapsed in 2020, but were &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;back above pre-pandemic&lt;/a>; levels in 2021. FDI flows, like trade, &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/system/files/official-document/diaeiainf2022d5_en.pdf&quot;>;weakened&lt;/a>; after the start of the war in Ukraine, but there are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oecd.org/daf/inv/investment-policy/FDI-in-Figures-April-2023.pdf&quot;>;no signs&lt;/a>; of a collapse similar to the one at the beginning of the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other measures of corporate globalization affirm that businesses are not broadly retreating from foreign markets, even as FDI flows remain below historical peak levels. Payments for the use of foreign intellectual property &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/BM.GSR.ROYL.CD&quot;>;continue to grow&lt;/a>;, while the cross-border share of M&amp;amp;A transactions is &lt;a href=&quot;https://dhl.com/gci&quot;>;holding steady&lt;/a>;, and the share of global output generated by the foreign operations of multinational firms has just &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;slipped back&lt;/a>; modestly from a record high set in the mid-2000s.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While the Covid-19 pandemic temporarily reduced trade and capital flows, it caused a spike in the growth of international data flows. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://techblog.comsoc.org/2022/09/19/telegeography-global-internet-bandwidth-rose-by-28-in-2022/#:~:text=According%20to%20Telegeography%2C%20Global%20internet,%2Dyear%20CAGR%20of%2029%25.&quot;>;growth rate of international internet traffic&lt;/a>; doubled in 2020 as in-person interactions were replaced by online activity, and it continued growing at 20% to 30% per year in 2021 and 2022. More than twice as much data crossed national borders in 2022 compared to 2019.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;International people flows suffered the worst blow from the Covid-19 pandemic, but they are on their way to making a full recovery. The latest UN forecast &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.e-unwto.org/doi/abs/10.18111/wtobarometereng.2023.21.1.2&quot;>;predicts&lt;/a>; the number of people traveling to foreign countries will be just 5% to 20% below its pre-pandemic level in 2023. Migration has also proven resilient, with the share of people living outside of their birth countries &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldmigrationreport.iom.int/wmr-2022-interactive/&quot;>;continuing to rise&lt;/a>;, even in 2020.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All in all, data on the growth of global flows strongly rebuts the notion of a mass retreat from international to domestic activity. Most types of international flows are at or near all-time highs, and the weakness of some flows, such as trade, in late 2022 and early 2023, primarily reflects slowing global economic growth following large interest rate increases aimed at curbing inflation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Are Geopolitical Tensions Fracturing the World Economy into Rival Blocs?&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As tensions continue to escalate between the US and China, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/06/shifting-geopolitical-tectonic-plates-straight-talk&quot;>;there is a growing fear&lt;/a>; that a new cold war could lead to a costly bifurcation of the world economy. The latest data on international flows do show a broad pattern of decoupling between the US and China, but the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China do not — at least yet — indicate a broader split between rival blocs, an outcome that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/News/Articles/2023/03/25/032623md-china-development-forum-remarks&quot;>;IMF has warned&lt;/a>; would “leave everyone poorer and less secure.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To measure US-China decoupling, the DHL Global Connectedness Index report examines 11 types of trade, capital, information, and people flows, and finds that the US and China have both substantially reduced their focus on flows with each other since 2016. The share of US flows that were to or from China declined in eight out of 11 categories, falling on average from 9.3% to 7.3% (weighted average using our index&#39;s flow weights). The share of China&#39;s flows with the US fell in seven out of 10 categories, dropping on average, from 17.8% to 14.3%.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Measuring the US China Decoupling. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360174&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Measuring the US China Decoupling. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The extent of US-China decoupling, however, should not be overstated. The US and China are still connected by larger combined trade, capital, information, and people flows than any other pair of countries without a common border. And the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.piie.com/blogs/realtime-economics/five-years-trade-war-china-continues-its-slow-decoupling-us-exports&quot;>;dollar value&lt;/a>; of trade between the US and China grew to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/foreign-trade/balance/c5700.html&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>; in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even more importantly, at a global level, the flows of countries that are geopolitically aligned with the US and China indicate no meaningful fragmentation of the world economy into rival blocs. Close allies of the US and China (as classified by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.capitaleconomics.com/clients/publications/china-economics/china-economics-focus/mapping-decoupling&quot;>;Capital Economics&lt;/a>;) have not substantially reduced the shares of their flows with the rival bloc. In some areas, such as imports and scientific research collaboration, US allies have even increased the share of their flows with China and its allies, while the US has pulled back from those exchanges.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360175&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_DECOUPLING_ALLIES_360.png&quot; >; &lt;p>;Sources: IMF Direction of Trade Statistics, UN Comtrade, fdi Markets, Thomson Reuters, IMF CPIS, Clarivate Web of Science, UN DESA International Migrant Stock, UN WTO Tourism Statistics, Capital Economics&quot; title=&quot;Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1157&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- Global Flows Are Not Fracturing into Rival US China Blocs.-->;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Has Globalization Given Way to Regionalization?&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rising geopolitical tensions — along with supply disruptions during the Covid-19 pandemic — have also prompted many observers to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;predict a shift&lt;/a>; from globalization to regionalization. In other words, many expect that a rising proportion of international flows will take place within rather than between regions. Data on actual flow patterns, however, do not show that such a shift has (yet) taken place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We prefer to analyze the possibility of rising regionalization by measuring the average distance traversed by international flows, since the more common measure — the share of flows happening within regions — &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;yields very different results&lt;/a>; depending on where one chooses to draw the region boundaries. If international flows were becoming more regionalized, they would take place over shorter distances, on average. In fact, trade and many other types of flows have tended to take place over longer distances. The main exception to this pattern involves people flows, due to a higher proportion of travel taking place between nearby countries during the Covid-19 pandemic. Capital flows also took place over shorter distances in 2020 and 2021, but it is still unclear whether that reflects a meaningful shift toward more regionalized investment patterns, since the volatility of these flows often results in short-term fluctuations of a similar magnitude.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- Start -- No Evidence that Globalization Is Giving Way to Regionalization. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360177&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/W230615_ALTMAN_GLOBALIZATION_NO_REGIONALIZATION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- End -- No Evidence that Globalization Is Giving Way to Regionalization. -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Trade flows even stretched out over longer distances in 2020 and 2021, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eiu.com/n/campaigns/the-great-unwinding-covid-19-supply-chains-and-regional-blocs/&quot;>;contrary to predictions&lt;/a>; that pandemic-related disruptions would prompt greater reliance on nearby suppliers. The &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/05/trade-regionalization-more-hype-than-reality&quot;>;key driver of this pattern&lt;/a>; was the resilience of Asian manufacturing, leading to more trade between Asia and distant regions. Preliminary data also show an increase in the average distance over which countries traded in 2022, due in part to effects of the war in Ukraine on trade patterns and commodity prices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It remains an open question whether world trade will become substantially more regionalized in the future. Many companies are &lt;a href=&quot;https://supplychaindigital.com/supply-chain-risk-management/nearshoring-happening-faster-than-expected-says-gartner&quot;>;focused on nearshoring&lt;/a>; to produce goods closer to their customers, and major supply-chain reconfigurations can take several years to execute. Governments in many countries are supporting these regionalization efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;On the other hand, the fact that international flows are already highly regionalized limits the scope for large increases in regionalization. As shown above, more than half of trade already takes place within roughly continent-sized regions. In addition, many companies, rather than nearshoring, have adopted other strategies to boost resilience, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/operations/our-insights/how-covid-19-is-reshaping-supply-chains&quot;>;digitization and dual sourcing&lt;/a>;. Meanwhile, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/d739cd47-e434-43c3-9b4e-472bcef4abaf&quot;>;container shipping costs&lt;/a>; have come back down while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2023/01/31/world-economic-outlook-update-january-2023&quot;>;inflation remains high&lt;/a>;, boosting the attractiveness of low-cost sources that may be located in distant regions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Geopolitical Turbulence and Global Strategy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While global flows have remained resilient, the public policy environment has become more challenging for global business. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heritage.org/index/trade-freedom&quot;>;Trade protectionism&lt;/a>; has increased, &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/publication/world-investment-report-2022&quot;>;international investments&lt;/a>; face heightened scrutiny on national security grounds, &lt;a href=&quot;https://itif.org/publications/2021/07/19/how-barriers-cross-border-data-flows-are-spreading-globally-what-they-cost/&quot;>;data-flow restrictions&lt;/a>; are proliferating, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hinrichfoundation.com/research/article/wto/international-trading-system-threatened-by-erosion-of-trust/&quot;>;international institutions&lt;/a>; struggle to function amid strained relations among their member countries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Core principles of global strategy can &lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/the-new-global-road-map-enduring-strategies-for-turbulent-times/10172&quot;>;help business leaders navigate&lt;/a>; this turbulent environment. The key &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbsp.harvard.edu/product/2620BC-PDF-ENG&quot;>;business drivers of globalization&lt;/a>; — more growth and innovation, coupled with lower costs and better diversified risks — remain strong, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/strategy-and-corporate-finance/our-insights/global-flows-the-ties-that-bind-in-an-interconnected-world&quot;>;new technologies&lt;/a>; continue to expand international opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But the challenges and risks of operating across geopolitical divides &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/how-companies-can-navigate-todays-geopolitical-risks&quot;>;have increased&lt;/a>;. Global strategists often find it useful to think of such shifts as changing the &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;metaphorical distance&lt;/a>; between countries. Rising tensions put more distance between geopolitical rivals, and they bring friendly countries closer together, at least in relative terms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the foundational concepts of global strategy is that domestic firms have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1075425312000543?casa_token=y_2Xo8t1_UwAAAAA:29n5LgCrPdVFnV9rfY1GksXnPbZQZ6OscJKksAyd7DAw_sK87s3-jNyiDEMdoYmWEnRmQRY&quot;>;home-court advantage&lt;/a>; over foreign firms, and firms that have to &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;bridge less distance&lt;/a>; — not only geographically but also politically — are usually advantaged over firms that have to bridge greater distance. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/41411007&quot;>;firm&#39;s unique assets&lt;/a>; — technologies, brand value, and so on — &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1017/9781316678503.007&quot;>;exert a large influence&lt;/a>; over how much distance it can bridge successfully. So does the &lt;a href=&quot;/2001/09/distance-still-matters-the-hard-reality-of-global-expansion&quot;>;sensitivity of its business&lt;/a>; to geopolitics and other sources of cross-country distance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders should examine how strong their competitive positions are in countries that are becoming more — and less — distant, to see if they need to rebalance their geographic portfolios. Remember that shifting geopolitical relationships can create opportunities as well as challenges. A company may be able to win business away from competitors from geopolitical adversaries.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If a company has strong-enough advantages to compete across geopolitical divides, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/the-strategic-challenges-of-decoupling&quot;>;changes to how it operates&lt;/a>; in politically distant markets may be required. A common approach is to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-based-managers-gain-more-autonomy-from-global-companies-ac8f66d3&quot;>;afford more autonomy&lt;/a>; to local managers, to better tailor operations to increasingly divergent conditions. This can be useful, but it is important not to overestimate how far a foreign company can go to be regarded as a local player. When push comes to shove, a company&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/05/the-cosmopolitan-corporation&quot;>;home base is still central&lt;/a>; to its perceived — and often real — allegiances.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As many Western firms operating in Russia saw after the full-scale invasion of Ukraine, tensions can escalate to a point where there is no alternative to exiting a market. Companies with large operations across geopolitical divides should be prepared for the contingency of a gradual decoupling turning into a sudden separation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news, though, is that most companies do not need to fundamentally restructure their global strategies to prudently address geopolitical tensions. As we have seen, US-China decoupling has not — at least yet — begun to split the world economy into rival blocs, globalization has not given way to regionalization, and most types of international flows continue growing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Decoupling without deglobalization generally calls for focused adjustments to global strategies not only because of the resilience of global flows but also because most international business already takes place between nearby and friendly countries. The US, for example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bea.gov/news/2023/us-international-trade-goods-and-services-december-and-annual-2022&quot;>;imported&lt;/a>; 66% more from Canada and Mexico in 2022 than it did from China, and 35% more from Europe. Globally, half of the flows measured on the DHL Global Connectedness Index take place inside major world regions, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhl.com/content/dam/dhl/global/dhl-spotlight/documents/pdf/10-years-lessons-gci-2021-report.pdf&quot;>;three times more&lt;/a>; than one would expect in a world where the distance and differences between countries had no effects. Nearshoring and friendshoring are actually longstanding features of globalization, and increases that address specific vulnerabilities would be consistent with the “interdependence without overdependence” that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wto.org/english/news_e/spno_e/spno32_e.htm&quot;>;WTO Director-General Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala envisions&lt;/a>; as the “future of trade.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Focused adjustments to how companies operate internationally also align well with the increasingly prevalent view in policy circles that “de-risking” is a better response to geopolitical tensions than complete decoupling. European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen proposed this emphasis on “de-risking” &lt;a href=&quot;https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/speech_23_2063&quot;>;in a March 2023 speech&lt;/a>; that characterized most EU-China trade as “mutually beneficial and &#39;un-risky&#39;” but highlighted the EU&#39;s problematic reliance on China for 98% of its supply of rare earths, 97% of its lithium, and 93% of its magnesium. Less than two months later, the US and other large advanced economies &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/05/20/g7-hiroshima-leaders-communique/&quot;>;formally embraced&lt;/a>; “de-risking, not de-coupling” at the May 2023 G7 Summit.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bottom line is that companies do need to adjust for heightened geopolitical tensions, but they should not abandon global strategies on the assumption that US-China decoupling will necessarily lead to deglobalization. Corporate deglobalization, in fact, &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/abandoning-globalization-will-only-hurt-us-businesses&quot;>;could be a riskier path&lt;/a>; than making focused adjustments to mitigate geopolitical risks. Another principle of global strategy is that firms should align their strategies with the globalization of their markets. As long as markets are not de-globalizing, firms that retreat from globalization may put their competitive positions at risk.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[In Uncertain Times, Embrace Imperfectionism]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_10_1192111806.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Gety Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Change is accelerating, with uncertainty and threat of disruption in every industry segment. The pace of change and rise of global winner-take-all competition means that conventional product-market-structure approaches to strategy, as well as core competencies thinking, are difficult to implement in practice and may yield misleading answers. Under today&amp;#8217;s conditions, the authors argue that real-time problem solving should be the heart of strategy development rather than theoretical frameworks, and they present a framework for this approach. This approach requires companies to look at strategy through multiple lenses or vantage points, typically anchoring these outside the company in its ecosystem or beyond. Looking at your business through the eyes of your suppliers, customers, current rivals, and potential outside entrants will give you much more perspective on both threats and opportunities than you will get from staying inside your company&amp;#8217;s prevailing mindsets and routines. It should also seek to generate new data on these perspectives through experimentation, augmenting this new data by crowdsourcing external ideas and technologies to bring collective intelligence to bear.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/in-uncertain-times-embrace-imperfectionism?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;If you are an Amazon customer, chances are you have encountered household names such as Amazon Prime and Zappos. It&#39;s less likely that you would have noted the baby steps Amazon took to expand beyond its core business into consumer financial services.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The acquisition of TextPayMe, the investment in Bill Me Later, the hiring of a team from GoPago, and the launch of a remote card payment device, Amazon Local Register were modest moves that involved little financial outlay and attracted relatively little attention at the time. They also ended in apparent failure, with TextPayMe closing in 2014, Local Register withdrawing from the market in the face of competition from Square, and Bill Me Later being acquired by rival PayPal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet today Amazon is a powerhouse in consumer finance, boasting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/611981/us-amazon-payments-awareness-usage/&quot;>;a 24% user share in the US for its pan-economy Amazon Pay service&lt;/a>;, and is positioned to develop further as a global finance player. How did the company craft success at scale from a series of pint-sized and seemingly unpromising moves?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The answer is that Amazon is an imperfectionist, a concept we&#39;ve developed over several decades of helping companies and nonprofits, and one that we believe is vital for organizations striving to prosper in today&#39;s uniquely uncertain economic environment. As we will explain, imperfectionism is an approach in which companies grow not by following a strategic framework or plan, but through multiple and frequent experimentation in real time, incrementally building up valuable knowledge, assets, and capabilities on the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Why a New Approach Is Required&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We all experience it: Change is accelerating, with uncertainty and threat of disruption in every industry segment. Artificial intelligence, programmable biology, robotics and other technologies are transforming existing industries and spawning new ones. External shocks cut across boundaries and impact all businesses, even those that appear to enjoy structural advantages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this volatile and fluid environment, established approaches to strategy development no longer work. There is no stable industry structure or new market equilibrium to return to. The pace of change and rise of global winner-take-all competition means that conventional product-market-structure approaches, as well as core competencies thinking, are difficult to implement in practice and may yield misleading answers. The player to topple a dominant company in a particular space is more likely to enter from outside with a &lt;em>;de novo &lt;/em>;approach than to be an existing rival. Just look at the battle of Instagram, Quibi, and TikTok in the short-form video social media space — the now-winning player was unknown five years ago. &amp;nbsp;We need responsive strategy approaches to match external volatility.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One repercussion of this changed environment is that most company strategic planning processes are unsuited to an uncertain and fast changing world, leaving many management teams stuck in a nervous wait-and-see posture.&amp;nbsp; Other company leaders avoid stasis by making panicky bets, including “leap before you look” acquisitions in an attempt to “own” new spaces, typically with little success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What should you do instead?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Embrace the Imperfect &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As we describe in our book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Imperfectionists%3A+Strategic+Mindsets+for+Uncertain+Times-p-9781119835677&quot;>;&lt;em>;The Imperfectionists&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, Amazon didn&#39;t wait for a moment of strategic clarity, nor did it use its large balance sheet to acquire an indigestible bank. It edged out into uncertainty by taking small steps: investing in young companies with interesting technologies, hiring a team from a failed fintech, and launching internally developed services and tools. It ran multiple, parallel initiatives and learned what worked and what didn&#39;t. It built valuable capabilities and assets with moves that were mostly low consequence and reversible. There is no notion of strategic frameworks in its approach to building a major financial services business. &amp;nbsp;The end result is what we term a staircase of initiatives, a pragmatic revealed strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359260&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_STAIRCASE_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This step-by-step approach was no accident — Amazon followed the same modus operandi in its entry to commercial finance and in its creation and dominance of cloud computing. It now appears to be doing something similar in health care.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Under today&#39;s conditions, we believe that real-time problem solving, not theoretical frameworks, should be the heart of strategy development. This starts with a hypothesis, often framed as an audacious question that when answered will provide strategic insight on the first steps of a solution staircase.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Strategy development then moves to seeing things through multiple lenses or vantage points, typically anchoring these outside the company in its ecosystem or beyond. Looking at your business through the eyes of your suppliers, customers, current rivals, and potential outside entrants will give you much more perspective on both threats and opportunities than you will get from staying inside your company&#39;s prevailing mindsets and routines.&amp;nbsp; Perspective-taking workshops at all levels of the organization can help surface novel observations that can be the nucleus of a new strategic path.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next it seeks novel data on these perspectives via experimentation, augmenting this new data by crowdsourcing external ideas and technologies to bring collective intelligence to bear. To be sure, few organizations are adept at having others toil in their garden, but one path to accessing fresh capabilities is crowdsourcing new technologies and approaches.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This leads to a pragmatic plan to step into uncertainty, gathering more information from small moves, while adding capabilities and assets, laying off risk to others where possible, and learning from mistakes and successes. It involves recognizing that strategic decisions are probabilistic wagers, and moves are made commensurate with an assessment of the odds.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Large enterprises, in particular, struggle with this. They are often reluctant to think in terms of probabilities that, in turn, gives rise to a powerful form of risk aversion, as documented in a &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/03/your-company-is-too-risk-averse&quot;>;2020 HBR article&lt;/a>; by Dan Lovallo, Tim Koller, Robert Uhlaner, and the Nobel laureate Daniel Kahneman. They found that that managers insist on making risk-averse choices even where favorable odds are clear. A starting point to overcome this deep-set bias is to insist that all discussions of strategies include probability estimates and ranges of potential outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359259&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/W230524_CONN_STRATEGY_IMPERFECTION_360.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Our research suggests that this approach to strategy under uncertainty is being effectively employed not just by the likes of Amazon but by other savvy firms and nonprofits alike. Here are four examples, each illustrating one of the four main components of the process.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Invisalign: Seeing Through New Lenses&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Until the early 1990s, orthodontic braces had hardly changed for decades.&amp;nbsp; Incremental improvements came from inside the practice of dentistry, but significant innovation was missing. Kelsey Wirth and Zia Chishti, MBA students at Stanford Business School with no qualifications in dentistry, worked to apply a fresh and different lens to orthodontics.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Zia only had the financial means to correct his teeth as an adult, shortly before business school.&amp;nbsp; When he finally got his braces off, he noticed something interesting: His retainer was almost invisible, but it still moved his teeth, which he could feel if he forgot to wear it for a few days. This small insight inspired a revolutionary hypothesis: If a simple plastic retainer could move teeth a little, perhaps the technology could be improved to move teeth a lot, but without affecting a person&#39;s appearance as much as conventional braces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Chishti and Wirth proposed a series of transparent, custom-manufactured removable plastic alignment retainers, developed through software-designed treatment plans. They called their solution Invisalign, emphasizing that the aligners would be inconspicuous to others. By changing to a new set every few weeks, the patient&#39;s teeth would gradually move into the desired position without the need for metal braces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By looking at the problem of straightening teeth through these novel customer and technology-centered lenses, Zia and Kelsey made orthodontic treatment less painful, less embarrassing, and more affordable. &amp;nbsp;Today the company has transformed orthodontics and has a market capitalization over $15 billion.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;SpaceX: Relentless Experimentation&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Everyone knows about software companies using A/B testing to refine products. But could this approach create strategic success in the ultimate heavy industry? In only two decades, SpaceX has massively transformed near-Earth space travel through relentless experimentation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;SpaceX engineers have learned to make small moves that add up to big improvements by repeatedly testing new hypotheses. This rapid test-and-improve approach enables them to acquire new information at a reasonable cost and to more quickly travel down the experience curve. They refer to their decision system as “fly, test, fail, fix” and accept that failure (“unplanned disassembly”) is a necessary part of testing the boundaries of what is possible. They&#39;ve pioneered lower-cost 3D printing for rocket components, as well as making more components re-useable, and shifting away from expensive external contracting, with 80% of components produced in-house.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moving down the cost curve required substantially increased frequency of launches. During the 30-year period of its space shuttle program, NASA averaged 4.5 flights per year. In 2021 Space X launched 31 rockets in orbit, up from 26 the prior year. &amp;nbsp;In early 2022 it was launching three to five missions per month.&amp;nbsp; More frequent launches and other innovations have dramatically reduced the cost of putting a kilogram of mass into space. &amp;nbsp;For the period from the 1970s to the early 2000s, this cost was largely unchanged, costing an average of $54,550 per kilo. &amp;nbsp;SpaceX has slashed the per-kilo cost down to $2,720, a reduction of 95%.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;TNC FishFace: Tapping Collective Intelligence&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The Nature Conservancy (TNC), a global conservation organization interested in protecting endangered fish stocks, was searching for effective strategies to implement conservation measures onboard fishing boats at sea. TNC wondered if digital techniques could be deployed by fishing boats to identify endangered species that they could return to the sea while still alive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But TNC did not have the necessary AI skills to develop a solution itself, so it decided to crowdsource solutions via Kaggle, an online platform that hosts machine-learning competitions. The TNC competition attracted 2,293 entries over five months with a $150,000 prize. After selecting a winning entry, TNC now has a prototype operating with 90% to 95% accuracy.&amp;nbsp; It is called FishFace.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To solve the complex fisheries regulatory compliance problem, TNC anchored outside its own organization&#39;s capabilities, inviting the best AI developers in the world to provide a novel strategic solution.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI swarm platforms are a variant of this approach and are particularly useful for predicting uncertain events. &amp;nbsp;A study&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;at Stanford medical school found that groups of doctors using Swarm AI algorithms were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medicaldevice-network.com/news/swarm-ai-system/&quot;>;22% more accurate&lt;/a>; in making diagnoses than the most advanced deep-learning algorithm that only used historical data. &amp;nbsp;The difference is that participants in swarms “think together” in real time and converge on solutions through interactions governed by algorithms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Quibi versus TikTok: Anchoring Inside vs. Outside&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In each of these examples, a substantial part of the strategic insight that led to breakthrough strategic ideas is the idea of anchoring outside the conventional boundaries of the industry.&amp;nbsp; Getting this right isn&#39;t easy — consider the experiences of Quibi.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Quibi was a short-form streaming platform launched with great fanfare in April 2020; by December 1, the company was dissolved at a loss of more than $1 billion.&amp;nbsp; An A list of investors included Alibaba, Disney, Google, and Goldman Sachs. &amp;nbsp;An all-star management cast was led by Meg Whitman, the former CEO of eBay and Hewlett Packard, and Jeffrey Katzenberg of Dreamworks. Investors were sure that this was a team of insiders who knew what the market wanted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The Quibi app was downloaded 4.5 million times during the second quarter of 2020, but by the third quarter of 2020 Quibi had only 710,000 paying subscribers and it was losing 90% of early users after their free trials expired. Quibi was anchored inside the old Hollywood model and failed just as short-form video competitor TikTok was explosively rising, with 315 million downloads in the first quarter of 2020.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The difference?&amp;nbsp; TikTok embraced the collective intelligence of its users with a highly sophisticated AI-curation of user-provided content.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When you look in retrospect at Amazon&#39;s stepped entry into consumer financial services or the other examples above, they look like the work of a master strategist. But that disguises the reality: There were many small moves to build the capabilities and assets that supported those positions, including missteps and failures along the way. Strategically nimble organizations explicitly map potential pathways into new areas and update their models with their experiences. They understand the difference between modest cost, reversible strategic moves that build position and bet-the-farm decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>