<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Collaboration Technology Is the Key to Better Planning and Sourcing - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM WORKDAY]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/collaboration-technology-is-the-key-to-better-planning-and-sourcing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img 咏叹调-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359057&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/HBRSourcingAds-CollaborativeTechnology-Hero-1200x675-1.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;协作技术：更好地规划和采购的关键&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;财务规划和分析 (FP&amp;A) 以及跨行业的采购团队正在努力应对因持续挑战的三重打击而中断的全球供应链&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;供应链波动和经济不确定性加剧了企业部署协作工具以消除运营孤岛和简化采购的需求。许多着眼于未来的组织正在采用基于云的采购和规划软件来促进实时规划、预算编制和利益相关者协作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;克服运营限制&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >; 内部和外部利益相关者无法就共享数据集进行协作是运营和财务规划与采购不一致的主要原因。许多组织使用依赖手动和低效流程进行规划和采购的遗留解决方案，这可能导致阻碍增长的孤立信息系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;弥合这些数据差距有助于促进跨学科合作，并可以推动积极的发展结果。在最近一项针对财务规划和采购主管的&lt;a href=&quot;/resources/pdfs/comm/workday/OptimizingTheSupplyChainByAligningThePlanningAndSourcingFunctions.pdf&quot;>;哈佛商业评论 (HBR) 分析服务调查&lt;/a>;中，51% 的受访者表示更好的数据集成导致更准确的预算预测并减少超支。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;孤立的组织信息系统是 FP&amp;A 和采购团队之间协作的重大障碍。 47% 的调查受访者表示，除了需要集成技术平台外，组织结构本身可能也需要重新调整，因为让规划和采购团队向不同部门负责人报告会阻碍协作。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;协作瓶颈会损害组织的供应链弹性。在服务行业，准确预测就业水平直接影响办公空间和设备的采购。对于制造商和零售商而言，计划和采购之间的脱节可能会导致库存超支或将错误的库存运到错误的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;更新遗留解决方案&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;规划和采购团队需要基于云的技术来代替繁琐的传统供应链管理工具，例如手动更新的电子表格和电子邮件链。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;自动化可以使采购部门确保运营团队拥有他们需要的信息用于反映协商节省和价格上限的采购。实时采购数据还可以帮助 FP&amp;A 团队更新他们的计划和预算，以反映不断变化的市场状况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在来自高绩效组织的调查受访者中，42% 的人表示他们的计划和采购职能共享实时访问相同的数据。最能促进协作的组织已做出使用最佳可用技术解决方案的战略承诺。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://haslam.utk.edu/people/profile/chad-autry/&quot;>;Chad Autry&lt;/ a>;，田纳西大学供应链管理教授。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;旨在促进利益相关者参与和合作的解决方案可以带来丰厚的回报。许多投资于支持协作的技术的公司正在获得竞争优势，因为促进无缝数据共享可以提高他们的效率并降低他们的成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;帮助公司解决现实世界的问题&lt;/strong>;&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;组织可以根据特定的客户需求定制他们的云原生采购和规划平台，并根据需要扩大或缩小规模。易于配置的框架使组织能够部署和管理自己的平台——因此他们无需重写代码或重新开始即可进行更改。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/ javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;企业投资&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workday.com/en-us/products/spend-management/strategic-sourcing.html?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIjenVtPTb_gIVkxJlCh37yQ2-EAAYAiAAEgKmOvD_BwE&amp;amp;eid=enus_ppc_gg_gg_spmgt_fileat_web_20.1 975&amp;amp;utm_medium=ppc&amp;amp; ;utm_source=gg&amp;amp;productfocus=spmgt&amp;amp;aud=fileat&amp;amp;assettype=web&amp;amp;assetid=20.1975&amp;amp;pblr=gg&amp;amp;ef_id=EAIaIQobChMIjenVtPTb_gIVkxJlCh37yQ2-EAAYAiAAEgKmOvD_BwE:G:s&amp;amp;s_kwcid=AL !8892!3!599852364149!b!!g !!strategic%20sourcing&amp;amp;_bt=599852364149&amp;amp;_bk=strategic%20sourcing&amp;amp;_bm=b&amp;amp;_bn=g&amp;amp;_bg=142252694332&quot;>;战略采购&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www. workday.com/en-us/products/adaptive-planning/overview.html&quot;>;planning&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a>;解决方案需要一个开放、可扩展和可互操作的平台，以实现与其他生产力应用程序和协作工具的连接。实施使用机器学习优化工作流程和分析实时数据以获得可操作的业务见解的技术也很重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在任何组织中，最佳技术都应该反映其独特的供应链需求和流程，并且应该易于实施和使用。成功的自动化反映了企业的规划、采购和财务流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workday.com/en-us/customer-stories/ip/ntt-global-sourcing -data-insights-meet-stakeholders-needs.html&quot;>;NTT Global Sourcing&lt;/a>; 用战略采购软件取代了其遗留的工作流程，该软件有助于采购合同系统提供对预计节省的实时洞察。该平台简化了与内部和外部利益相关者的协作，支持使用通用数据集的共享工作流，并提供可靠的审计跟踪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;改善规划和采购团队之间的协作可以提高供应链的弹性和效率。当他们的计划和采购团队不再依赖传统的手动沟通和协作方法时，组织可能知道新技术何时发挥作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“当计划和采购很好地集成并使用相同的数据时，好事发生，”&lt;a href=&quot;https://gufaculty360.georgetown.edu/s/contact/0031Q000027S70cQAC/linda-dunn&quot;>;Linda Dunn&lt;/a>; 说，他是乔治敦大学供应链管理助理教授。 “您对您的供应商有更深入的了解，有助于良好的供应商关系管理。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;改善您组织的规划和采购团队之间的一致性可以帮助您提高运营效率并降低成本。更好的供应链风险管理能力还可以帮助您的 FP&amp;A 和战略采购团队更快、更高效地采取行动，从而实现更高效的采购、生产和分销，以及在快速变化的经济环境中实现您所在行业的增长和领导地位。 &lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;如需更详细地了解战略采购和协作技术的优势，请下载 HBR-Analytic Services 研究报告“&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href =&quot;/resources/pdfs/comm/workday/OptimizingTheSupplyChainByAligningThePlanningAndSourcingFunctions.pdf&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;通过调整计划和采购功能优化供应链&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em >;”&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引文 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href= &quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You Ready to Become a Manager?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_1094310820.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Rawpixel/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;关闭&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当你正在努力晋升到管理职位时，证明你已经准备好只是过程的一部分。要成为一名强有力的管理者，您需要成为最高级别的问题解决者。发现你还不知道的东西是很重要的。除了收集可证明您的管理资历的具体示例外，还要客观评估您在经验、知识和管理技能方面的差距。要确定您需要提高或发展哪些技能和知识才能成为有效的新任经理，请问自己这 10 个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06 /are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;第一次过渡到管理层是一个重要的职业里程碑。我仍然记得当我得知我将领导一个团队时的准确时刻。我耐心但坚持不懈地追求我的晋升。我战略性地换了工作，使自己走上了在一家享有盛誉的大公司的快速管理轨道。我确信我已经准备好了。在庆祝我晋升到管理层之后，我很快发现我有很多东西要学。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我决定升职是从分析我工作场所的领导力格局开始的。我开始在心里将自己的长处和成就与他们的进行比较。&amp;nbsp;我发现自己会想起一些重要人物对我工作的影响公开表扬我的场合，或者有人私下感谢我完成一项重要任务的时刻.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一名职业教练，我从我支持的积极追求晋升的专业人士那里听到了类似的故事。您的结果、能力和外部验证很重要。但要成为一名有效的经理，必须发现您还不知道的事情。除了收集可证明您的管理资历的具体示例外，还要客观地评估您在经验、知识和管理技能方面的差距。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我强调这一点，不是要阻止您，而是要推动你前进。要成为一名强有力的管理者，您需要成为最高级别的问题解决者。当您为下一步做准备时，我希望您考虑的不仅仅是证明您已准备好晋升。我希望你能积极主动地制定职业发展计划，使你能够驾驭转变并在晋升的角色中继续学习。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为职业教练，我的工作重点是提出问题、反思的反应，找出差距和弱点，并提出解决这些问题的步骤。作为第一步，我在辅导课程中提出的自我评估问题可以开始激发想法并阐明挑战。要确定您需要提高或发展哪些技能和知识才能成为有效的新任经理，请问自己这 10 个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;管理技能&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;我的领导风格是什么？&lt;/p>; h3>; &lt;p>;您的领导风格源自您的优势、个性和价值观以及您的愿景和目标。反思其中的每一个组成部分，然后决定你想以什么为人所知。请记住，随着时间的推移，您可以在不断学习和进步的过程中调整您的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我如何帮助我的团队发展？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;了解如何衡量绩效并评估差距和增长机会在您的团队中，对于您作为经理的角色至关重要。花点时间想想你的晋升会如何影响团队结构和动态。集思广益，讨论在团队发展中发挥关键作用的潜在机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我将如何有效地确定工作的优先级和委派工作？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;我经常被要求支持那些正在努力应对竞争的经理需要。学习如何有效地确定优先次序和授权将决定你作为团队领导者的成功与否。这需要时间来弄清楚。当你这样做的时候，继续问自己这样的问题：我需要停止做什么？我还需要做什么？我需要维护什么？我将如何提供监督和问责制？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我是一个优秀的公众演讲者吗？我可以主持会议吗？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为经理，您的沟通方式是您分配工作的关键驱动因素，推动参与，并与多个利益相关者共享信息。这通常通过会议来完成。当您准备进入管理层的下一步时，诚实地评估您的沟通技巧，并评估您在领导会议和向更大的团队展示时的舒适度。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我如何提供建设性的反馈和解决冲突？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;提供指导、解决绩效差距和解决问题是重要的管理职责。考虑您可能与同事一起目睹的有关流程、项目或人际关系的问题。你从观察到的东西中学到了什么？如果需要，您需要哪些技能来管理绩效和解决冲突？&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;知识&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;贵公司的健康、安全和监管要求政策是什么？&lt;/h3>; &lt; p>;贵公司的人力资源团队将带头确保员工接受有关公司政策的必要培训，但现在是熟悉员工手册和人力资源资源的好时机。作为经理，您的团队成员会向您提出问题，而您将负责帮助确保公司范围内遵守协议和政策。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我是否熟悉州和联邦就业立法？&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;同样，您的人力资源团队将负责影响您工作方式的雇佣法指南，熟悉公司指南并及时了解任何相关新闻或立法变更讨论是明智之举。法规迅速变化的一个典型例子发生在大流行期间，当时美国联邦、州和地方政府引入了新的 Covid-19 工作场所保护措施以保障工人的健康和安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我将如何处理相关查询对公司的薪酬策略、利润分享、福利和股权规划有何影响？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为一名员工，了解薪水的构成很重要。作为负责团队的经理，您可能会收到团队成员关于薪酬、福利和时间政策的询问。晋升为管理职位后，您需要为机密对话做好准备，其中可能包括免税和非免税员工的加班费资格、财政年度周期的财务数据、福利的公开登记期以及公司薪酬决定协议.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我是否参与了整个招聘流程？&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;作为经理，您需要参与人员配置计划的执行。招聘的整个周期包括从评估需求和创建职位描述到选择候选人、延长报价和入职新员工。如果晋升标志着您是第一次参与招聘流程，请准备好向您的人力资源团队寻求有关程序和最佳实践的指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;我是否了解最新的多元化、公平和包容最佳实践？ &lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;了解您的组织是否有 DEI 指南或资源将帮助您回答问题或阐明您将在您的角色中监督的流程。此外，您可以继续跟踪可能影响您的新职责的更广泛的 DEI 发展和新闻。当前的一个例子是新的薪酬透明度法的推出，以解决越来越多州的薪酬公平问题，包括罗德岛州、华盛顿州、纽约州和加利福尼亚州。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot; >;。 . .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;有效地进行晋升不仅仅是获得新头衔。这是一个宝贵的机会，可以考虑可以支持你的优势、特质、专长和知识，以及从长远来看可能降低你效率的弱点、技能差距和缺乏接触。通过客观评估，您可以制定可操作的后续步骤，为未来的管理成功做好准备。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Chief Data and AI Officers Are Set Up to Fail]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/why-chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_107253611.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Paseika/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;随着生成式 AI 和其他强大的新数据工具的爆炸式增长，首席数据和人工智能官 (CDAIO) 比以往任何时候都更加重要，因为公司要驾驭这个新景观。然而，太多的人因为协调不力、缺乏信任、对商业机会的关注不够以及内部对他们工作的理解而失败。公司可以采取五个步骤来更好地设置他们的 CDAIO 以取得成功：1) 让数据成为每个人的业务，2) 让商业领袖成为数据冠军，3) 审查所有数据和 AI 投资以确保资金充足4) 转变为生态系统思维方式，5) 谨慎行事。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/why-chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/why -chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;今年，首席执行官的角色已经很脆弱数据、分析和人工智能官 (CDO/CDAO/CDAIO) 变得更加不稳定。许多公司已经看到了离职和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/cios-meet-your-new-colleagues-chief-data-analytics-and-ai-officers-af6b58b9&quot;>;重新校准&lt; /a>; 企业数据和 AI 领导职责。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些角色仍然相对较新。 CDO 职位是为应对 2008 年至 2009 年的金融危机而在大型银行设立的，随后扩展到制药、医疗保健、消费品、娱乐和联邦政府等多种行业。 2012 年至 2023 年间，&lt;a href=&quot;https://static1.squarespace.com/static/62adf3ca029a6808a6c5be30/t/63a477e23d7f9162b7771d6b/1671722982363/WAVESTONE+NVP--+Data+%26+Analytics+Executive+Le adership+2023--调查+Findings.pdf&quot;>;根据调查数据&lt;/a>;，任命了 CDO 的公司从 12.0% 增长到 82.6%，随着时间的推移，职责范围扩大到包括分析 (CDAO) 和 AI (CDAIO)。然而，只有 35.5% 的大公司表示该角色是成功的并且已经确立，只有 40.5% 的公司表示 CDAIO 的角色在他们的公司内得到了很好的理解。显然，有些地方出了问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于一些数据和分析领导者来说，2023 年感觉像是回到了该角色最早的乏味日子：金融动荡和生成式 AI 的爆炸式增长迫使他们专注于防御风险和监管任务，而不是专注于增长、客户获取以及新产品和服务创造的前瞻性举措。企业领导层要求 CDAIO 部署 GenAI 的潜在变革能力，同时避免伤害——一种高压平衡行为与提供巨大风险和机遇的技术。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在越来越多的公司想要和需要 CDAIO，这个角色一如既往地具有挑战性——而且常常注定失败。公司可以采取以下五个步骤来解决这个问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;CDAIO 工作有什么问题？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;作为合著者，我们是 CDAIO 兴起和发展的第一手见证者和参与者角色。二十多年来，Randy 一直担任领先公司的数据和分析使用顾问。 Allison 曾担任行业 CDO 五年，目前正在就如何实现商业价值向 CDAIO 和公司提供建议。虽然我们都同意这个角色让人感觉不可能，但我们也相信当前的迭代包括为更好、更有效的工作版本奠定基础。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第一代首席数据官经常被聘用到大型公司医疗保健和金融等受监管行业的公司。最初，该角色被理解为侧重于控制和风险的防御性角色，而不是业务角色，尽管这两个功能使用相同的数据和分析技能。银行用来检测欺诈模式的交易数据也被用来发现现有或潜在的客户需求，但公司投资于前者而不是后者。随着重点转向数据商业化，公司往往将其视为技术和人才问题，而不是业务问题。他们在技术和人员方面投入了大量资金，建立了数据基础架构以及数据工程师和数据科学家团队，但没有足够重视业务关系的重要性和最关键的业务问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;结果，公司最终并没有从他们的数据程序中得到他们想要的东西。虽然 91.9% 的公司报告说他们已经从对数据和分析的投资中获得了一些可衡量的价值，但只有可怜的 23.9% 的公司表示他们已经创建了一个数据驱动的组织，而更微不足道的 20.6% 的公司报告说已经建立了一个数据驱动的组织文化。 CDAIO 一直被那些需要巨额投资并涉及到公司各个角落的重大项目所困扰，但往往无法带来可衡量的收益。即使他们完全按照要求完成了任务，也很难说他们已经成功了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们认为有两个因素在很大程度上导致了这种情况：错误的重点和缺乏信任.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;该角色的重点应该放在业务成果上，而不是技术和基础架构问题：确定您要为客户解决的问题，确定业务回报最高的用例的优先级，以及交叉授粉能力，无论目标是商业、风险控制，还是两者兼而有之。 “工作中最困难的部分是了解您要为客户解决什么问题，”Google 首席决策科学家、决策智能领域的先驱 Cassie Kozyrkov 说。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;缺乏信任是一个等效因素。企业领导者需要相信他们在数据、分析和人工智能方面的投资正在带来业务回报——他们的钱花得值。如果没有明确交付商业价值，这种信任就会受到侵蚀，企业领导者将不愿进行进一步投资。 CDAIO，特别是在大公司中，已经建立了人员、政策、流程和管理模型的治理基础设施，以努力联合整个组织对数据的信任所有权。这些努力很复杂，通常不受欢迎，而且收益也难以量化。由于数字经济中的几乎所有问题都可以描述为数据问题，因此除非有商定的衡量进展的指标，否则很难取得胜利。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;如何解决&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;任何创新时代的进步都是断断续续的，而且很难衡量。可以公平地说，数据和业务战略错位，没有成为 C 级和董事会的优先事项，治理工作过于笨拙，无法广泛采用和衡量，而且纪律不完整。生成式 AI 的出现放大了这些问题，并引发了信任、质量和道德方面的新问题we-stop-the-singularity&quot;>;在新闻中&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/05/20/ai-existential-risk-debate/&quot;>;正在引起高管和董事会的关注&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司可以而且必须解决他们管理数据、分析和 AI 的方式，并让 CDAIO 角色为成功做好准备。此要求只会扩展，尤其是当023 --Survey+Findings.pdf&quot;>;83.9% 的公司&lt;/a>;计划明年增加对数据、分析和人工智能的投资。以下是公司今天可以采取的一些具体建议，以修复 CDAIO 的角色并从他们的数据、分析和 AI 投资中创造商业价值：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;让数据成为每个人的业务。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;虽然 CDAIO尽管长期以来一直在宣传数据素养的重要性，但在强有力的治理、政策和标准等实践方面的采用并不一致。数据最成熟和最严格的领域通常是财务和合规相关职能。在这些领域取得的成功，再加上 C 级和董事会的参与，可以作为企业的榜样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在全球能源管理和数字自动化领导者施耐德电气，Philippe Rambach 是首席人工智能官，谈到施耐德如何建立关乎每个人的企业文化：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;认真对待数据管理需要专门的组织。为了支持这一雄心壮志，我​​们决定从 IT 中提取数据，将数据集中在整个公司的治理、业务和绩效议程上。然后我们决定设立首席数据官和首席人工智能官这两个角色。以数据为中心的旅程的关键是努力在公司中拥有单一的事实来源，并使公司内的所有决策者都能轻松访问高质量的数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h3>;让业务领导者成为数据项目的支持者。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;业务领导者需要成为数据和分析投资的支持者和倡导者。成功的数据领导者是业务领导者的重要合作伙伴，他们开始依赖他们作为得力助手，提供关键数据和决策点，以推动成功的业务成果。 CDAIO 不应寻求强加议程（“数据和人工智能很棒；我们应该做得更多”），无论其用意多么好。寻找准备好在其业务线内支持数据和 AI 并通过建立可信度的结果成为值得信赖的合作伙伴的业务领导者。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;审查所有数据和 AI 投资以确保资金用得其所。&lt;/h3 >; &lt;p>;区分“最好拥有”和“需要拥有”投资。仅继续关注那些正在为组织提供可衡量的商业价值或可以在短期内展示快速实现价值的途径。公司必须重新将投资重点放在那些对发展和竞争至关重要且需要的能力上。数据分析和 AI 领导力需要时间、注意力、清晰有效的沟通以及讲故事的技巧来阐明需求、建立切合实际的期望并获得认可。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;转向生态系统思维方式。&lt;/h3 >; &lt;p>;要充分利用数据和人工智能，与供应商、大学和其他合作伙伴建立伙伴关系和协作非常重要。 Schneider 的 Rambach 补充说：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;竞争的新本质实际上与技术无关；人工智能技术发展得太快了。这是关于您为客户提供的价值。无论您提供什么价值，它都可以通过合作伙伴关系得到增强。我们为第三方创新开放我们的物联网平台，这样合作伙伴就可以使用我们的软件开发工具包开发新的应用程序来进行创新，以提高建筑物的效率和可持续性。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h3>;谨慎行事。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h3>;谨慎行事。&lt;/p>; h3>; &lt;p>;虽然生成式 AI 提供了改变游戏规则的机会，但 Rambach 重申了理解风险和谨慎行事的重要性，因为这些模型：&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;…使公司面临新型漏洞，特别是让更多用户更轻松、更快速地访问更大量、更多样化的数据。现在是建立数据治理和网络安全措施以负责任地使用这些新功能的时候了。公司和用户应始终谨慎对待生成式 AI 并注重保密性，例如用户不应在可公开访问的 AI 聊天机器人平台上上传任何机密信息。 LLM 的安全/私有版本应该是首选。&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;许多 CDAIO 领导企业委员会，其领导者来自风险、财务、技术、网络安全、法律/道德、隐私、人力资源和业务线。这些团队需要提高地位和问责制。公司还应在其公司董事会中增加数据、分析和人工智能专业知识。只有 23.8% 的人表示该行业在解决数据和 AI 伦理方面做得足够。如果不以负责任和有效的方式管理，AI 和数据隐私、治理和道德问题将对公司构成威胁。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在许多公司都在认真审视 CDAIO 职能的时候，现在是数据和人工智能领导者必须站出来展示他们如何为公司的商业价值做出贡献的时候。那些对如何从数据和 AI 投资中创造商业价值有着清晰愿景的公司将是未来十年及以后最有可能取得成功的公司。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt; /div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Leading Through a Sustained Crisis Requires a Different Approach]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/leading-through-a-sustained-crisis-requires-a-different-approach]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_506849080.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;CherriesJD/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然疫情已经结束，但许多高管仍在领导着他们的组织，仿佛一场突如其来的危机依然存在。相反，我们现在正处于一场&lt;em>;持续&lt;/em>;危机中&amp;#8212;一段持续存在的巨大困难和不确定性的时期。突发危机和持续危机之间存在关键差异。本文帮助领导者了解他们以及如何重新定位他们的组织以在这个新环境中取得成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/ 2023/06/leading-through-a-sustained-crisis-requires-a-different-approach?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/leading-through -a-sustained-crisis-requires-a-different-approach?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;5 月，世界卫生组织 &lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.nytimes.com/2023/05/05/health/covid-who-emergency-end.html&quot;>;宣布&lt;/a>; Covid-19 全球紧急状态结束。最后。但对于许多领导人来说，这一宣布并没有减轻他们背负的负担。虽然紧急情况已经结束，但危机并未结束。我们已经从大流行病到来的&lt;em>;突然&lt;/em>;危机转变为我们所说的&lt;em>;持续&lt;/em>;危机——一段持续存在的巨大困难和不确定性的时期。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;持续危机的麻烦在于，与突发危机不同，它的到来带有模棱两可的&lt;a href=&quot;/2006/11/facing-ambiguous-threats&quot;>;信号&lt;/a>;，而且没有明确的开始日期。结果，领导者，包括那些擅长处理突发危机的领导者，可能会错过当前需要做的事情。更糟糕的是，一些在突发危机中奏效的领导行为可能会加剧倦怠并限制在持续危机中的适应。我们已经确定了突发危机和持续危机之间的主要区别，以帮助领导者了解未来会发生什么，以及如何重新调整他们的组织，以便他们能够在这个新环境中取得成功。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;领导者当前面临的挑战&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;今天的领导者面临着 Covid 释放或暴露的许多相互交织的问题：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryanrobinson/2023/02/07/new-outlook-on首先，-burnout-for-2023-limitations-on-what-managers-can-do/?sh=b969ee243430&quot;>;倦怠&lt;/a>;和沮丧的员工队伍。管理人员应对&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/02/5-challenges-of-hybrid-work-and-how-to-overcome-them&quot;>;混合会议&lt;/a>;并引入不可避免地&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/recode/23161501/return-to-office-remote-not-working&quot;>;无法满足所有人&lt;/a>;都渴望清晰。教育领导者努力应对&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/education/interactive/school-shootings-database/&quot;>;学校枪击事件&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/01/07/1070969456/kids-are-back-in-school-and-struggling-with-mental-health-issues&quot;>;心理健康&lt;/a>;孩子之间的问题。城市领导人面临&lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/04/24/downtown-revitalize-covid-office-vacancy-rates-housing-real-estate/&quot;>;空荡荡的市中心&lt;/a>;。清单还在继续。在许多方面，当前时刻并不比三年前袭击我们的意外事件容易。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但它&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;不同。以 SickKids 的首席执行官 Ronni Cohn 为例，这是一家一流的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsweek.com/worlds-best-specialized-hospitals-2022/pediatrics&quot;>;儿科专科医院&lt;/a>;。当 Cohn 于 2019 年开始担任首席执行官时，他为精准儿童健康设定了鼓舞人心的愿景。他所在的医院将利用来自儿童健康决定因素（基因、生物学、环境）所有领域的数据整合来显着推进儿科护理。这对儿科医生和著名遗传学家科恩个人来说意义重大。然后 Covid 来袭。可以理解，该计划不再是首要任务。三年后，就在他开始恢复自己的愿景时，流感季节加剧，再加上新冠病毒，再次使他的组织严重紧张。现在愿景的作用是什么？他疲惫不堪的员工需要什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他并不孤单。在一场持续的危机中，问题更加模棱两可，权衡取舍也不那么明确。激动人心的时刻已经过去了。储备已经耗尽。这就是当今如此需要领导力的原因：应对和应对持续危机带来的新挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;认识和阐明当今的不同之处——及其重要性&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2 >; &lt;p>;领导者必须帮助他们的团队理解突发危机和持续危机之间的对比，以培养在这个新领域取得成功的正确心态。考虑突发危机造成的紧急情况——需要立即采取行动的意想不到的、通常是危险的情况——比如 2020 年 3 月 Covid 死亡人数上升或 &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/07/leadership-lessons-from-the-chilean-mine-rescue &quot;>;2010 年智利矿山倒塌&lt;/a>;。一场突如其来的危机提出了限制伤害的&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/04/what-good-leadership-looks-like-during-this-pandemic&quot;>;明确的必要性&lt;/a>;。利害关系显而易见，时间有限。风险承受能力适当高，因为无所作为的风险显然更糟。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;持续的危机是不同的。在困难重重、麻烦重重或充满不确定性的持续时期，首要目标是建立复原力，而不是防止直接伤害。赌注是微妙的，时间框架更长。随着人们试图在资源枯竭的情况下恢复审慎决策，风险承受能力逐渐下降。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人类的反应也不同：突发危机引发恐惧和对威胁的全神贯注。人们想知道：&lt;em>;我们会没事吗？&lt;/em>;在持续的危机中，持续的挑战让人们想知道：&lt;em>;为什么要麻烦？ &lt;/em>;意识到他们的世界发生了多么深刻的变化，人们渴望过去，可能会感到与世隔绝和随波逐流。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;从快速反应到有意主动&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p >;适用于突发危机的方法不适用于持续危机。在后者中，领导者必须练习有意识的主动性，而不是快速反应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于速度在紧急情况下至关重要，因此需要对影响每个人的问题进行集中决策。想一想 2020 年 3 月 CEO 做出关于在家工作的决定的速度。我们工作的哈佛大学校长在 3 月 13 日命令所有不需要在场的人（例如，病人护理）回家&lt;sup>;th&lt;/sup>;。是否进行虚拟教学&lt;em>;不&lt;/em>;由个别教师或团队决定。由于危机，所有人都接受了该决策的集中化和速度——这与以分布式自治和参与决策为常态的大学环境截然不同。果断和执行速度是最重要的。然后，当然，要由个人和团队来弄清楚如何使它全部正常工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天坚持这种方法是很诱人的。做出决定并指挥大胆的行动来解决问题感觉很好。但是，如果习惯将其带入一场持续的危机中，这种方法会使人们筋疲力尽并感到沮丧，同时养成优先考虑紧急事项而不是重要事项的习惯。而且，如果持续时间足够长，这些方法会破坏最初吸引许多领导者担任其角色的目的：对未来的令人信服的愿景。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相比之下，在持续危机中，需要的是广泛的-规模化实验和地方决策，让人们参与广泛的优先事项，以分散的方式寻找新的解决方案，从而激发活力。更强调停下来学习、探索和实验，而不是简单地行动和快速行动。这并不是说突如其来的危机不需要试验。在大流行期间，许多组织通过前所未有的本地实验和学习水平幸存下来。但是重点指令是自上而下设定的，而且通常是没有商量余地的。例如，当一家医院取消择期手术时，工作人员会重新集中精力并进行试验，以弄清楚如何建立额外的肺部重症监护能力。随之而来的是实验和（有时是痛苦的）学习。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多领导者在突如其来的危机中似乎是天生的。控制感觉是对的。要知道何时以及如何摆脱这种方法更加困难。它需要判断力和深思熟虑。例如，在我们中的一个人 (Michaela) 最近与 Ronni Cohn 的谈话中，他反映说：“在大流行初期，我知道我必须成为船长。现在，随着危机的演变和目前的演变，我扮演着多重角色。”他发现了这种转变并随之转变——想方设法在解决眼前需求的同时带回远大的愿景。他在组织的前线认真倾听并重建了积极主动的文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;在动荡的世界中领导&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们确定了三个关键的领导行动可以帮助每个人参与在动荡的世界中茁壮成长所需的持续学习。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;首先，引起人们对转变的关注&lt;/strong>;。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;因为持续的危机冗长且模棱两可，每个人（不仅是领导者！）很容易错过变化。明确声明是时候进行转变以超越员工的自动感知。这种赋予意义是一项核心领导任务。邀请您的人事经理停止说“这是计划”，而开始说“我们可以尝试通过以下方法了解在这个新环境中哪些方法有效。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;其次，停止奖励救火&lt;/strong>;。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在突发危机中，紧急情况优先。但紧迫感可能会变成习惯，让许多团队气喘吁吁地匆忙通过议程项目，在紧急情况消退很久之后，这种方式会抑制问题和思考。领导者在打破这些习惯方面发挥着至关重要的作用。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;第三，拓宽视野。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;建立实验和改进的结构和流程，以吸引更广泛的群体的声音。海尔等一些组织已采取重大措施&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/11/the-end-of-bureaucracy&quot;>;扁平化组织&lt;/a>;，以保持快速执行，同时拒绝自上而下的命令。其他人追求流程转变（没有重大结构变化）以建立更广泛的参与，例如通过建立多元化团队来改进或重新设计工作流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着动荡延伸到未来，通过协商流程重新吸引不同的声音至关重要.经过多年的紧急响应，在此期间指令方法必然优先，如今的领导团队必须有意识地改变他们的惯例并引入（或重新引入）分散和协作决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;新现实&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;今天，我们生活在一个动荡和不确定的世界中。 Covid 不是我们生活中唯一或最后的危机。从气候变化到大量银行倒闭，我们无需放眼未来。正如前美国财政部长和哈佛大学教授劳伦斯萨默斯最近&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/498398e7-11b1-494b-9cd3-6d669dc3de33&quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;，“这是最我记得 40 年来我一直在关注这些事情。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这个新的现实中，识别和转换的能力突发和持续的危机是一项核心领导能力。伟大的领导者将善于在正确的时间选择正确的框架，并使用它来帮助他们的组织蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Should You Start a Generative AI Company?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/should-you-start-a-generative-ai-company]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Anja Sušanj 的插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;许多企业家正在考虑创办公司，利用最新的生成式 AI 技术，但他们必须问问自己，他们是否具备在日益商品化的基础上进行竞争的能力模型，或者他们是否应该在利用这些模型的应用程序上进行区分。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06 /should-you-start-a-generative-ai-company?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/should-you-start-a-generative- ai-company?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;我正在考虑创办一家采用生成式 AI 的公司，但我不确定是否要这样做。离开地面似乎很容易。但是，如果这对我来说很容易，那么对其他人来说岂不是也很容易吗？&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今年，问我这个问题的企业家比其他任何人都多。生成式 AI 令人兴奋的部分原因在于它的优势似乎是无限的。例如，如果你已经设法创建了一个具有某种通用语言推理能力的人工智能模型，那么你就有了一种智能，可以适应各种新产品，这些新产品也可以利用这种能力——比如屏幕写作、营销材料、教学软件、客户服务等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，软件公司 Luka 构建了一个名为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://replika.com/&quot;>;Replika&lt;/a>; 的 AI 伴侣，它使客户能够与“人工智能朋友”进行开放式对话。由于这项技术非常强大，Luka 的管理人员开始收到入站请求，要求为希望改善聊天机器人客户服务的企业提供白标企业解决方案。最后，Luka 的经理使用相同的底层技术衍生出了企业解决方案和直接面向消费者的 AI 约会应用程序（想想 Tinder，但用于“约会”AI 角色）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在决定无论生成式人工智能公司是否适合你，我建议确定以下两个大问题的答案：1）你的公司会在基础模型上竞争，还是在利用这些基础模型的顶层应用程序上竞争？以及 2) 在高度脚本化的解决方案和高度生成的解决方案之间的连续统一体中，贵公司将位于何处？根据您对这两个问题的回答，这将对您在竞争中保护自己的能力产生长期影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;基础模型还是应用程序？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;科技巨头现在正在租赁出他们最通用的专有模型——即“基础模型”——像 Eluether.ai 和 Stability AI 这样的公司正在以极低的成本提供这些基础模型的开源版本。基础模型正在变得&lt;em>;商品化&lt;/em>;，只有少数初创公司有能力在这个领域竞争。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您可能认为基础模型最有吸引力，因为它们将被广泛使用它们的许多应用将为增长提供有利可图的机会。更重要的是，我们生活在激动人心的时代，一些最复杂的 AI 已经可以“现成”使用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;想要将公司建立在基础模型之上的企业家正在不过，这是一个挑战。与任何商品化市场一样，能够生存下来的公司是那些以低价提供非捆绑产品或提供日益增强的能力的公司。例如，Deepgram 和 Assembly AI 等语音转文本 API 不仅相互竞争，而且还通过提供更便宜的非捆绑解决方案与亚马逊和谷歌等公司竞争。即便如此，这些公司仍在价格、速度、模型准确性和其他功能方面展开激烈的竞争。相比之下，亚马逊、Meta 和谷歌等科技巨头进行了大量的研发投资，使他们能够在图像、语言和（越来越多的）音频和视频推理方面不断取得前沿进展。例如，它是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/13/chatgpt-and-generative-ai-are-booming-but-at-a-very-expensive-price。 html&quot;>;估计&lt;/a>; OpenAI 花费了 2 到 1200 万美元来计算训练 ChatGPT——这只是他们提供的几个 API 之一，还有更多 API 正在开发中。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与其竞争在日益商品化的基础模型上，大多数初创公司应该通过提供利用其他公司基础模型的“顶层”软件应用程序来区分自己。为此，他们可以根据客户解决方案独有的高质量专有数据集微调基础模型，为客户提供高价值。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，营销内容创建者，&lt;em >;Jasper AI，&lt;/em>;主要通过利用 OpenAI 的基础模型成长为独角兽。时至今日，该公司仍在使用 OpenAI 帮助客户为博客、社交媒体帖子、网站副本等生成内容。同时，该应用程序为其营销人员和撰稿人客户量身定制，提供专门的营销内容。该公司还提供其他专业工具，例如多个团队成员可以协同工作的编辑器。既然该公司已经获得了牵引力，那么它可以在未来花费更多的资源来减少对基础模型的依赖，而基础模型正是这些基础模型首先使它能够实现增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;由于顶层应用程序是这些公司找到竞争优势的地方，他们在保护数据集隐私免受大型技术玩家攻击之间处于微妙的平衡，即使他们依赖这些玩家的基础模型。鉴于此，一些初创公司可能会想要建立自己的内部基础模型。然而，鉴于上述挑战，这不太可能很好地利用宝贵的启动资金。大多数初创公司最好利用基础模型来快速发展，而不是重新发明轮子。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;从脚本化到生成&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您的公司需要从纯脚本化到连续统一体纯生成的解决方案。脚本化解决方案涉及从预定义的脚本化响应数据集中选择适当的响应，而生成式解决方案涉及从头开始生成新的、独特的响应。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;脚本化解决方案更安全且受限，但也缺乏创造性和人性化，而生成解决方案风险更大且不受约束，但也更具创造性和人性化。对于某些用例和行业（例如医疗和教育应用程序），需要更多脚本化方法，这些应用程序和行业需要明确限制应用程序的功能。然而，当脚本达到极限时，用户可能会失去参与度，客户保留率可能会受到影响。此外，开发脚本化解决方案更具挑战性，因为您从一开始就限制了自己，限制了您以后的选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一方面，更具生成性的解决方案也面临着自己的挑战。由于基于 AI 的产品包括智能，因此消费者在如何与它们互动方面有更大的自由度，从而增加了风险。例如，一位已婚父亲在与 AI 聊天机器人应用程序 Chai&lt;em>;&lt;/em>; 对话后不幸自杀，该应用程序鼓励他牺牲自己来拯救地球。该应用程序利用了 EluetherAI 的基础语言模型（GPT-4 的定制版本）。 Chai 的创始人后来修改了该应用程序，以便在提及自杀意念时提供有用的文本。有趣的是，Chai 的创始人之一 Thomas Rianlan 承担了责任，他说：“将这个悲惨的故事归咎于 EleutherAI 的模型是不准确的，因为所有朝着更情绪化、有趣和引人入胜的优化都是&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑到底层 AI 的“黑匣子”性质，管理人员很难预测高度生成的应用程序可能出错的所有方式。这样做涉及预测可能非常罕见的风险场景。预测此类情况的一种方法是付钱给人工注释者来筛选可能有害类别的内容，例如性、仇恨言论、暴力、自残和骚扰，然后使用这些标签来训练自动标记此类内容的模型。然而，仍然很难提出详尽的分类法。因此，部署高生成解决方案的管理人员必须准备好主动预测风险，这既困难又昂贵。如果以后您决定将您的解决方案作为服务提供给其他公司，情况也是如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因为完全生成的解决方案更接近自然的、类人智能，所以从保留的角度来看，它更具吸引力和增长，因为它更具吸引力并且可以应用于更多新用例。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;strong>;&lt;br>; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;许多企业家正在考虑创办利用最新生成人工智能技术的公司，但他们必须问自己，他们是否具备在日益商品化的基础模型上竞争的能力，或者他们是否应该在利用这些技术的应用程序上脱颖而出&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;他们还必须考虑他们希望在从高度脚本化解决方案到高度生成解决方案的连续统一体中提供什么类型的应用程序，考虑到每种应用程序的不同优缺点。提供更具脚本性的解决方案可能更安全，但会限制他们的保留和增长选择，而提供更具生成性的解决方案充满风险，但更具吸引力和灵活性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们希望企业家会提出这些问题&lt;em >;在 &lt;/em>; 进入他们的第一个生成 AI 企业之前，这样他们就可以就他们想成为什么样的公司做出明智的决定，快速扩大规模，并保持长期的防御能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引文-->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Advance Your Career When Your Company Is Downsizing]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_I6JrdSA3DwE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论员工/Simone Hutsch/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;在公司裁员期间提升你的职业生涯需要转变你的思维方式和行动。在这篇文章中，作者提供了五种策略来将逆境变成你专业成长的垫脚石：1) 重构你的思维。 &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;2) &lt;/span>;填充真空。 3) 寻找速赢。 4) 稍后协商。 5) 横向移动。&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/06/how-to-advance-your-career-when-your-company-is-downsizing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;作为一家制造公司的运营总监，Marlow 走上了发展的快车道。去年，她的团队规模扩大了一倍，这在很大程度上要归功于她带领他们度过动荡的变革并推动一系列重要的供应链计划的能力。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Marlow 的成果和奉献精神使她获得了一个激动人心的机会 - 一个新设立的流程优化副总裁职位。晋升是她设定的目标，代表着在塑造公司未来的同时产生更大影响的机会。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight : 400;&quot;>;不幸的是，就在 Marlow 正处于这一重大职业转变的风口浪尖时，市场开始低迷，公司的利润也随之迅速下滑。面对经济挑战，必须做出艰难的决定。 Marlow 曾经蒸蒸日上的团队被削减了一半，更糟糕的是，她热切期待的副总裁职位也被解散了。她发现自己处于十字路口，质疑当她的愿望是 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/what-to-do-when-youre-passed-over-for-an-internal- 时如何前进position&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;看似出轨&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;许多领导者和专业人士发现自己处于 Marlow 的位置 — 感到沮丧和 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/09/how-to-deal-with-layoff -anxiety&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;不确定&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;随着公司裁员，如何提升他们的职业生涯.难怪什么时候裁员&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/06/layoffs-are-up-nearly-fivefold-so-far-this-year-with -tech-companies-leading-the-way.html&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;2023 年增长近五倍&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight : 400;&quot;>; 金融不稳定看不到尽头。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;组织一直在寻找削减成本的方法，他们的底线。虽然这可能意味着支出冻结和裁员等毁灭性变化，但这不一定会毁掉你的职业前景。事实上，它可以成为增长的跳板。以下是应对成本削减措施带来的干扰并变得更强大的方法。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;重构您的思维。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;经历一系列情绪——悲伤、愤怒、&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/stop-being-so-hard-on-yourself&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;自我怀疑&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; — 在组织动荡时期很自然。但是，关闭、避免这种情况并为自己感到难过会让你无处可去，只会让你感到被困住。相反，将变化和不确定性作为工作描述的一部分。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;无论原因是技术进步、不断变化的市场动态、或不断变化的客户期望，公司正在重组 &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jonesday.com/en/insights/2022/01/recent-trends-in-corporate-debt-and-reorganizations-laying -the-groundwork-for-future-large-chapter-11-cases-or-just-more&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;快速发展&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>; span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;.您必须随时为大大小小的转变做好准备。困难时期揭示了您的性格以及最需要您的领导能力的地方。您可以选择采用这样一种观点，将动荡视为一个严峻的时刻，它提供了提供价值的机会，并成为一个有弹性、有影响力的领导者，推动积极变革。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;填补真空。&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;挺身而出填补流沙造成的空白。变化可能令人不安，这就是稳定性变得至关重要的原因。使您的工作与公司的新优先事项保持一致，这些优先事项通常包括关注核心产品、成本控制和运营效率，以及员工和客户保留。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style= &quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;尽管遇到了挫折，但 Marlow 很快意识到在经济低迷时期降低成本并高度关注关键业务领域的重要性。 Marlow 将她的团队的工作重新调整为仅针对基本操作。列出几个创新项目是一个艰难的决定，但马洛的精明引起了高级管理人员的注意，他们赞赏她展示的战略优先次序。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;寻找快速的胜利。&lt;/ b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;乱世之中，人人都在寻找救世主。从初级员工一直到最高管理层，士气和信心很可能在整个链条上上下波动。通过确定需要改进的领域并迅速采取行动，您可以将自己定位为宝贵的资产，在取得成果的同时将公司的最大利益放在心上。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style =&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;寻找在短时间内产生切实影响的方法。例如，您可以：&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&lt;br>; &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;重新谈判供应商合同&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;寻找更便宜的材料采购方式&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;与其他部门合作以节约资源&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;实施自动化以简化流程&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;向未开发的客户群推出您的产品&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;开展活动以促进重复购买&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;谈判&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;副总裁职位被解散后，Marlow 向她的经理解释说她了解公司的财务限制以及原因她一直期待的流程优化角色被解散了。然后她提出了一种平衡组织需求的方法，同时牢记她的长期目标。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“虽然我理解现在可能无法进行重大更改，我想讨论一下重新审视我的范围的可能性，”她说。 “我现在可以承担 X 项职责，但承诺在未来市场改善时探索流程优化领域的机会。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;像马洛一样，你也想看看房间。现在可能不是要求对你的角色、责任或报酬进行重大改变的时候，但你可以尝试在以后获得承诺。例如，“我很乐意现在接受 X，只要承诺在未来重新审视我的范围。”或者“我想帮忙，但我的最终目标是朝 Y 方向走。你认为你什么时候可以做到这一点？”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;横向移动。&lt;/b>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;&amp;nbsp ;&lt;/span>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;虽然裁员期间向上和向左的职业发展可能受到限制，但横向移动仍然可以提供机会学习新技能并获得新经验。横向移动可以让您拓宽技能组合，从而增强您的多才多艺，并使您成为组织更有价值的资产。假设您担任销售职务。横向跳槽到产品开发团队可以让你深入了解产品开发流程、市场调研和客户需求分析。 Offering your sales insights means the company can better align their offerings with market demands.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Moving laterally also exposes you to new colleagues and expands your professional network. This can open the door to collaboration on future projects, mentorship opportunities, and access to a wider range of knowledge about internal politics. Plus, it exposes you to new stakeholders, decision-makers, and senior leaders. The more people you know — &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/what-to-do-when-your-hard-work-is-being-overlooked&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;and the more people that know you&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; — the more opportunities will come your way.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Advancing your career during a company downsizing requires a shift in your mindset and actions. By adopting these strategies, you can turn adversity into a stepping stone for professional growth.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Will AI Replace the Front Office in Pro Sports?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_516776669.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Gizelka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;With accurate player-availability predictions for all active players, AI-powered decision-making is dramatically improved around three dimensions: 1) Risk management: If a productive wide-receiver is likely to get hurt, for example, a team might invest more in talented backups, to minimize drop-off in team performance during injury. 2) Training and targeted interventions: If AI suggests a player is injury-prone, teams can target that player with customized training, nutrition, or other regimens to reduce the likelihood of injury. Alternatively, a team might choose to reduce a player&amp;#8217;s workload, also reducing risk. 3) Personnel decisions: By identifying factors that predict injury or other unavailability, teams can draft, trade for, or otherwise acquire players that they believe are more likely to be available season-long. Additionally, teams may choose to trade players for whom injury seems likely.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/will-ai-replace-the-front-office-in-pro-sports?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;March 15, 2023, marked the official beginning of the National Football League&#39;s new season. It also meant the start of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcsports.com/boston/patriots/nfl-free-agency-tracker-2023-top-players-signings-start-time-cap-space&quot;>;free agency period&lt;/a>;, when teams make deals with players no longer under contract with their former teams; each new contract can literally mean millions of dollars of a team&#39;s budget.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So it&#39;s critical to get recruiting right. Like any business, NFL executives and leaders of other professional sports teams must make decisions about how best to allocate their limited budgets, placing informed bets on the ROI they will gain from assets (players, in this case), including as related to expected performance (on and off the field), future injuries, and other factors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But what if this year, AI could tell us how many games a player has left in their career, how many points they will score next season, or whether they will suffer a major injury in the near future?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While free agency and other recruiting mechanisms have been around for decades, &lt;em>;how &lt;/em>;decisions about players get made is changing rapidly. Specifically, the application of AI-based technologies to massive sets of sports data is enhancing the front office&#39;s ability to make decisions about players — whom to recruit, develop, bench, or trade. And it will change the workings of all pro sports, permanently.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But will AI replace the front offices of sports teams anytime soon?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While this new technology is definitely augmenting human decision-making, we don&#39;t see it replacing general management teams in the near future — in sports or other businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Game-Changing Predictive Power&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Amid a large, growing number of AI-based sports-focused offerings, some are aimed are helping team decision-makers with predictions about athlete injury and longevity. Knowing the likelihood of injury within a specific time frame has a large impact on recruitment, as teams would naturally aim for players expected to remain injury-free longer. Industry executives have always had some experience-based intuition for factors that go into injury, such as time and “mileage” on the field. Sometimes these predictions hold true, but often they don&#39;t.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The difference now is that AI can back up some conventional wisdom — in the NFL for instance, a wide-receiver over 30 years of age is more prone to injury and other challenges, for example — but can also provide much more specific estimates of likelihood of injury or diminished performance, and what that means for a given player&#39;s availability and what that might cost the team. One company, &lt;a href=&quot;https://probility.ai/&quot;>;Probility AI&lt;/a>;, claims 96% accuracy in predicting which players will miss time next season. Executives can use these results to go from “I think this is probably an important factor” to “I know this is an important factor and can estimate its impact and cost with unprecedented confidence.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI-generated insights go well beyond existing ones or those backed by intuition. For example, Probility AI trained its injury-prediction models on data from specific NFL teams, along with other public and private data sources, to understand the impact of factors like where a given player went to college, combinations of head and assistant coaches they played under, and consequent practice and workload demands. While these nascent insights warrant further research, they show how deep AI can go in its predictive analyses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, instead of general managers trying to secure the very best wide-receiver overall, they can find the best receiver &lt;em>;for their team,&lt;/em>; based on AI predictions of future injuries and performance. Since players typically have different predicted career lengths and performance outcomes with different coaches, field conditions, or teammates, this creates an arbitrage situation whereby player market value varies depending on which team the player plays for.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Multiple NFL teams are deploying AI technologies from Probility AI and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/techtank/2021/03/18/how-the-nfl-is-using-ai-to-evaluate-players/&quot;>;other sources&lt;/a>;, with good reason: failing to do that would put them at a disadvantage against their AI-equipped peers. Of course, such models are also being used in other sports such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/12/22/artificial-intelligence-is-the-new-competitive-edge-in-sports/&quot;>;soccer and basketball&lt;/a>; to generate value, and across business sectors to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2022/11/21/the-top-five-ways-ai-is-transforming-business/?sh=139d9da98e7f&quot;>;enhance activities&lt;/a>; including informing decisions, boosting productivity, and serving customers better.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Augmentation, Not Replacement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;So as AI gains predictive capabilities across key dimensions of sports — injuries, trade timing, others — will it replace the front office?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In short, no. For now, think of AI as &lt;em>;augmenting&lt;/em>; human decision-making. It won&#39;t replace executives but help them make better decisions, especially in areas where human error and bias are more likely, such as basing recruiting largely on intuition and doing “what worked before.” Where the &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2016/04/02/moneyball-is-dead-long-live-moneyball/&quot;>;Moneyball movement&lt;/a>; of the last 20 years has been about using player statistics in a much more rigorous, systematic way, AI uses deeper learning to make even better predictions about performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With accurate player-availability predictions for all active players, decision-making is dramatically improved around three dimensions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Risk management: &lt;/strong>;If a productive wide-receiver is likely to get hurt, for example, a team might invest more in talented backups, to minimize drop-off in team performance during injury.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Training and targeted interventions: &lt;/strong>;If AI suggests a player is injury-prone, teams can target that player with customized training, nutrition, or other regimens to reduce the likelihood of injury. Alternatively, a team might choose to reduce a player&#39;s workload, also reducing risk.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Personnel decisions:&lt;/strong>; By identifying factors that predict injury or other unavailability, teams can draft, trade for, or otherwise acquire players that they believe are more likely to be available season-long. Additionally, teams may choose to trade players for whom injury seems likely.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Savvy executives will also integrate injury prediction into financial decision-making. That is, AI not only generates predictions on player availability, but can input those predictions in a financial decision-making engine, enabling team leaders to create granular metrics on expected productivity per dollar spent. For instance, a running back who is predicted to play in only 50% of games in a given year becomes, functionally, twice as expensive as a similar-cost one who could play every game. By considering price paid per outcome (yards gained, tackles made, points scored, others), teams can allocate their dollars in a maximally efficient manner, optimizing on productivity for each dollar spent.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, the technology by itself isn&#39;t enough. While software can analyze player engine and resource allocation, sports executives&#39; judgment and risk tolerance must eventually choose among inevitable tradeoffs and dictate the decisions made. We share more on this in the last section.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Still, AI is an absolute game-changer in professional sports and is replacing informal or even statistics-based decision-making as the engine of a comprehensive system fueled by big data and unprecedented predictive power.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to see how better predictions — generated by AI — would have massive impact on any business. A close analogy here would be predicting when worker performance in labor-intensive industries like construction may suffer, or when large equipment like that powering manufacturing plants or refineries would malfunction or fail and taking preventative steps before a costly incident. The approach would apply to any business with aging resources.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More broadly, predicting demand for anything from clothing to corn would enable business leaders to make better decisions about production, including as related to supply chain and other areas. Other AI-based algorithms could make predictions about competition. The list goes on, and AI already has been applied in these and other ways across sectors, helping to explain why AI startups received &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/artificial-intelligence-trends-2023-business-healthcare-2023-1&quot;>;nearly $1.4 billion in funding&lt;/a>; in 2022.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Don&#39;t Go Out of Bounds&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Of course there are limitations to using predictive AI, further reinforcing the idea of augmentation versus replacement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With regard to predicting NFL injuries, for example, while new technology can guide decisions about recruiting, trades, and how much to pay a given player, the coaching team has to think strategically about the whole-team dynamic. The AI may tell you it&#39;s time to replace an injury-prone running-back with a player with a given profile, but an executive will have to think about how best to integrate the new recruit into the team. Total risk, after all, is spread out across all the players and their interactions. Here, too, AI is getting better at understanding the big picture of teams and its implications, starting with sports with smaller starting-team sizes, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://uwaterloo.ca/news/media/artificial-intelligence-makes-it-faster-easier-analyze&quot;>;hockey&lt;/a>;, which puts no more than six players on the ice at a given time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Moreover, it&#39;s important to understand that AI-based offerings aren&#39;t providing a definitive “answer” but making a prediction with a confidence interval around it. That interval will shrink as the technology improves, but there will always be some looseness related to prediction and that&#39;s, again, where human judgment is critical.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the end, AI is definitely a game-changer for sports, giving front offices and coaches unprecedented predictive power to make an increasing range of decisions with large implications for performance and returns, giving players insights to extend their careers, and keeping more player playing, which is thrilling the fans. But it&#39;s still a story of augmentation, one where leaders, using new technologies to inform their experience-based intuition, must make strategic calls the best they can and maintain accountability for what happens on the field and the balance sheet.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Scale Local Innovations in Big Companies]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_16_1157569960.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Magnetic-Mcc/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;All too often innovations &amp;#8212; including new products, new HR policies to attract and retain talent, and new production processes &amp;#8212;developed in one part of a business stay there. Other groups that could benefit from them don&amp;#8217;t know they exist. This leads to lost revenues and higher costs, since teams around the world often end up duplicating (or triplicating, or quadruplicating) investments in solving common problems. This article identifies three common obstacles to scaling innovations and describes a way to overcome them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-scale-local-innovations-in-big-companies?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The business advantages of scale and scope are widely recognized, but large, global enterprises often fail to fully realize them when it comes to innovation. Innovations that are developed in one geographic region or business unit — new products to delight customers, new HR policies to attract and retain talent, new production processes that drive efficiency gains — too often stay within them instead of being disseminated across the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider the experience of a global consumer packaged goods company, and three of its regional business units. (Innosight was an advisor to the company). Region 1 had developed a new brand targeted at younger consumers, who were increasingly seeking healthier products. Region 2 had changed its production processes in ways that increased profitability. And Region 3 had developed new sustainability focused business models. For reasons we&#39;ve seen time and again, regions that could have imported these innovations dismissed them, or worse, were simply unaware of them, as they innovated in silos.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not everything needs to scale globally. Local innovations for local markets matter. But there are meaningful downsides of not scaling the great many innovations that are born locally but do have significant global potential. These include lost revenues, since a new product originating in one region could be sold to customers in others, and higher costs, since teams around the world often end up duplicating (or triplicating, or quadruplicating) investments in solving common problems. The CEO of McDonald&#39;s, Chris Kempczinski, highlighted this in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/mcdonalds-shutters-us-offices-ahead-of-layoffs-report/448927&quot;>;a recent memo&lt;/a>;, in which he noted that insufficient collaboration across regions meant that “we are trying to solve the same problems multiple times, aren&#39;t always sharing ideas, and can be slow to innovate.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other disadvantages arising from insufficient global scaling are less obvious but also really matter. When regional businesses that started out with similar product portfolios don&#39;t share innovations and instead evolve in isolation of one another, those portfolios become more divergent over time. This leads to a proliferation of product lines, which makes it more difficult for the corporate center to optimally allocate resources, and for shareholders to value the company and understand its growth prospects.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are three common obstacles to scaling innovations from one to many markets. To illustrate both the obstacles and the solutions for overcoming them we&#39;ll use the case of a global retail bank, which Innosight advised.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Fallacies about Local Uniqueness&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Though every region is different, local leaders tend to overestimate the singularity of their markets, their customers, and the conditions under which they operate. But often, new products and other innovations — and the capabilities and learnings that come from their development — are much more transferable than they assume, in particular when they are aligned with innovation priorities that are shared across regions. An innovation priority, or “strategic focus area,” is essentially a broad hunting ground for innovation. At the consumer goods company, for example, one innovation priority was packaging, which led to specific innovations in materials and size and format.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Let&#39;s turn to the bank. One of its regional units had made significant investments in developing a digital mortgage-application platform that further automated its mortgage-application process to make it faster and more consumer friendly. Though mortgages were an important product line across regions, most were reluctant to consider adopting this innovation, contending that the distinct ways that mortgages were regulated within their individual markets made it unfeasible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regulatory frameworks do vary from country to country, of course, but not in ways that precluded this innovation from being widely adopted, since the implementation of the platform could be adapted to address differences in regulatory requirements in each market, much in the same way that existing mortgage-application processes were customized to local markets. What&#39;s more, the platform was consistent with innovation priorities shared across regions, including digitizing and improving customer experiences across existing product journeys and increasing the profitability of mortgage lending.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To overcome this obstacle, the bank&#39;s central corporate strategy team facilitated a process to identify common innovation priorities across regions. First, regions were asked to define their individual innovation priorities in a standard way (for example, “new ecommerce payment and financing solutions”), identify the associated target customer segment, the customer problems to be addressed, and the broad types of technologies and capabilities required. Each of the bank&#39;s four regions defined between five and 10 innovation priorities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The corporate strategy team then facilitated a series of discussions among senior leaders of each region to compare and identify commonalities in their innovation priorities. This surfaced multiple priorities that were shared across all four regions. In addition to those related to the mortgage-application platform, they included the development of new mobile-only products for millennial and Generation Z consumers and reduction of call center use and wait times.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Innovations aligned with those priorities could then be identified as sharable, no matter where they originated. Awareness of common innovation priorities among teams across regions also led &lt;a href=&quot;/2000/01/communities-of-practice-the-organizational-frontier&quot;>;communities of practice&lt;/a>; among designers and product developers to emerge organically. These convened regularly to exchange ideas, disseminate learnings, and co-create new innovations consistent with those shared priorities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Misaligned Incentives and Culture&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Various formal and informal disincentives are another obstacle to scaling innovations. For example, regional leaders&#39; bonuses are typically based on their own unit&#39;s P&amp;amp;L performance, which can make them reluctant to spend time, energy, and resources on exporting an innovation that will benefit another region. Conversely, a “not invented here” mindset can make managers reluctant to import externally generated ideas.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank&#39;s bonus plans significantly penalized local leaders who missed ambitious profitability targets. This made them reluctant to dedicate resources to exporting innovations. In addition, a “not invented here” mindset was widespread — from regional leaders who wanted to prove their ability to innovate independently to developers who preferred to write their own code rather than use the software developed by peers in other regions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address these issues, the bank offered P&amp;amp;L relief to regions on a case-by-case basis, allowing them to deviate from profitability targets without risking their bonuses so that they could invest their own resources into scaling innovations for the benefit of other regions. It also established a central fund and team to support global scaling efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regions that were developing innovations that could address shared priorities were invited to submit short “global scaling resource requests” that summarized the additional investments required to scale them to other regions beyond just their own. The request could be to cover the cost of building a product in a way that made it operable across global technology environments, for example, or the team hours required to train and support users in other regions and the potential in-year P&amp;amp;L tradeoffs or broader operational challenges that would result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A global scaling committee, comprised of corporate C-suite leaders and central strategy and finance executives, decided which requests to approve. Most resource requests submitted to scale innovations that addressed shared priorities were approved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank&#39;s corporate leaders also tried to change attitudes by publicly celebrating both managers who shared their region&#39;s innovations and those who adopted those created by others. They spotlighted global scaling initiatives in all-day quarterly business-review sessions attended by top regional executives, where exporting and importing regions jointly discussed the innovations and the process of scaling them. The bank&#39;s leaders also highlighted such innovations and the teams involved in these efforts in company newsletters.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Finally, the bank&#39;s leaders encouraged and frequently reminded regional managers to ask themselves a series of questions before dismissing potential innovations developed by other regions. They included:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Could we better serve the customers we have or seek by adopting this innovation?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;If the innovation isn&#39;t specific to one or more of our local circumstances — for example, if it has been developed in the context of a different technological, regulatory, or competitive environment, or requires a means of production or distribution that we lack — could it be adapted?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;And might we be guilty of having a “not invented here” mindset if our first instinct is to dismiss this innovation?&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Lack of Transparency&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As we mentioned, one major reason that business units don&#39;t share innovations and instead often duplicate efforts is a lack of awareness of what one another has developed or is undertaking. One way to address this is by creating a central mechanism that makes it easy for regions to share knowledge of their innovation pursuits from their earliest stages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider one innovation priority shared by all the bank&#39;s regions that we mentioned: developing mobile-only products for millennials. Innovations consistent with this priority across regions included distinct payment, savings, and investment products; new product features like roundup savings and cashback and rewards; innovations to streamline customer journeys within mobile-only apps, and integration with budgeting and bill-splitting tools that appealed to the millennial audience. But regions lacked awareness of each other&#39;s efforts and were in some instances even duplicating spend on development of the same things.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The bank addressed this issue in two ways: by establishing the process for identifying common innovation priorities across regions that we previously described and by instituting an innovation-portfolio-management system to profile and track innovations. Regions were required to enter into the IT system a description of each innovation project, including the associated innovation priority, the target customer segment, its revenue potential, and anticipated investment requirements.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond supporting global scaling, the system helped each region better understand and manage its own innovation pipeline. When it surfaced instances of regions unknowingly duplicating each other&#39;s efforts, they were able to collaborate and pool their insights, development capabilities, and data assets.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Too many global enterprises don&#39;t make the most of local innovations. By systematically overcoming the obstacles to scaling them, they can spread them much faster and more effectively and generate a much higher return on their innovation investments.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Women in Leadership Face Ageism at Every Age]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_14_1415442562.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/aldomurillo/Imagehit/Hero Images/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Originally, ageism was understood to be prejudice, stereotypes, and discriminatory behavior targeted at older employees. But with an increasingly diverse and multigenerational workforce, age bias now occurs across the career life cycle &amp;#8212; especially for women. &amp;#8220;Youngism&amp;#8221; refers to ageism toward younger adults, fueled by the conflation of age with maturity and the misperception that tenure is required for competency. Even middle-aged women are feeling the effects of age bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Age diversity in the workplace yields better organizational performance while perceived age discrimination creates lower job satisfaction and engagement. The good news is that there are practical steps for leaders to combat this never-right gendered age bias. First, recognize ageism in your organization; you can fix a problem that isn&amp;#8217;t there. Next, with your employees, address &amp;#8220;lookism,&amp;#8221; and focus on skills, no matter who has them. Finally, cultivate creative collaborations to encourage learning across age groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/women-in-leadership-face-ageism-at-every-age?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When a university vice president had an opening for a controller sitting just beneath her in the hierarchy, board members told her to seek an “older man” to complement her. Since she began the vice president role at age 37, board members routinely criticized her age, calling her &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90569439/we-need-to-talk-about-using-pet-names-for-women-at-work&quot;>;diminishing pet names&lt;/a>;, like “kiddo” and “young lady.” But being older wouldn&#39;t necessarily have made a difference, as another woman explained: “I am at the age when I should be getting the higher-level jobs; people in my profession now want to give the jobs to the 30- and younger 40-year-olds with the &#39;fresh, new ideas&#39; as opposed to going with the person with experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Originally, ageism was understood to be prejudice, stereotypes, and discriminatory behavior &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.0021-9029.2006.00062.x&quot;>;targeted at older employees&lt;/a>;. Driven by the misperception that performance worsens and capacity decreases as people age, older employees are expected to just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias-hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;quietly leave&lt;/a>; so that younger talent can take the reins. With an increasingly diverse and multigenerational workforce, age bias now occurs &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1468-0432.2004.00222.x&quot;>;across the career life cycle&lt;/a>;. “&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1037/xge0001064&quot;>;Youngism&lt;/a>;” refers to ageism toward younger adults and is fueled by the conflation of age with maturity and the misperception that tenure is required for competency.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, research has only just begun to investigate how age is used to justify bias and discrimination specifically against women. Gendered ageism sits at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/bonniemarcus/2021/09/20/gendered-ageism-affects-womens-job-security-and-financial-viability/&quot;>;intersection of age and gender bias&lt;/a>; and is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/fighting-the-double-whammy-of-ageism-sexism.aspx&quot;>;double whammy&lt;/a>; where there is “no right age” for professional women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our recent open-ended survey research of 913 women leaders from four United States industries (higher education, faith-based nonprofits, law, and health care), we discovered that many women suffered from this “never-right” age bias. Conceptions of young, middle, and old age are often based on perceptions and vary between workplaces and contexts. When interpreting our results, we consider “young” to be under 40, middle age to be between 40 and 60, and older women to be over 60.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Oldism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As women age, they are often not seen as valuable or relevant in the way that male counterparts are. Older women in our research expressed that they were deemed unworthy of advancement. “While men become wells of wisdom as they age, older women are seen as outdated, harpy, strident,” one physician noted. “Our voices are discounted.” For example, a 61-year-old deputy chief information officer (CIO) was not considered in CIO succession planning. Instead, the current CIO was grooming a male colleague for the role. Another retirement-aged woman added, “I am largely ignored.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of these women felt discouraged, burnt out, and resigned to not advancing any further. As a 66-year-old faith-based leader said, “At my age and with the mentality of our organization that they need men at the top, there is not a next professional step.” Another woman in the same industry noted that once she turned 60, she was no longer “worth investing in with training or mentoring.” Others felt compelled to find opportunities outside of their organization: “I am tired of proving myself to others and may as well do it in the interests of my own company,” a 60-year-old lawyer indicated.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Youngism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Younger women — and those who looked young — were called pet names or even patted on the head, as one 39-year-old woman reported. Young women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/when-people-assume-youre-not-in-charge-because-youre-a-woman&quot;>;role incredulity&lt;/a>;. They reported being mistaken for students, interns, trainees, support staff, secretaries, paralegals, and court reporters. Such inaccurate assumptions were especially prevalent for non-White women, such as an Asian higher-education executive who appeared young and was presumed to be in a junior position.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many younger women also experienced &lt;a href=&quot;https://rowman.com/ISBN/9781538170960/Glass-Walls-Shattering-the-Six-Gender-Bias-Barriers-Still-Holding-Women-Back-at-Work&quot;>;credibility deficit&lt;/a>;, which occurs when women&#39;s statements and expertise are not believed. “I am often told that I don&#39;t have the experience so I can&#39;t know what to do,” one 34-year-old woman explained. In the face of such bias, women (and especially women of color) must expend extra effort to prove themselves. One young-looking Black university chief financial officer noted that she is often “pressed to provide a synopsis of her resume to establish credibility.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other younger women had their appearance scrutinized. One physician noted that between ages 20 and 40, men focused on her looks. After she gave a scientific presentation that she was very proud of, a male colleague told her that she “looked like a Barbie doll up there!”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Gendered “Middle-ageism”&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unlike previous notions of a middle-aged “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/sheilacallaham/2022/02/25/workplace-age-bias-hurts-earlyand-late-career-workers/?sh=35faa75b61e7&quot;>;sweet spot&lt;/a>;,” women between ages 40 and 60 in our study fared no better than their younger or older counterparts. One college leader described how some search committees chose not to hire women in their late forties because of “too much family responsibility and impending menopause.” Other search committees declined to hire women in their fifties because they have “menopause-related issues and could be challenging to manage.” And still other committees said that “women in their fifties and sixties may not have &#39;aged well&#39; and do not &#39;look vital.&#39;” Yet the jobs were given to similarly aged men.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lawyer summed up the never-right age bias problem in her field:&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, we are too young to be responsible or to supervise. This lasts into our mid- to late-thirties but does not for men. (Perhaps they are waiting to make sure we don&#39;t have kids). Then in an instant, we are too old to be hired for anything or anywhere new. Once again, men are still “young enough” at the same age…. Women are young or old, we get no prime time even if we aren&#39;t out for childbearing or rearing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our research we found no age was the right age to be a woman leader. There was always an age-based excuse to not take women seriously, to discount their opinions, or to not hire or promote them. Each individual woman may believe she&#39;s just at the wrong age, but the data make the larger pattern clear. Any age can be stigmatized by supervisors and colleagues to claim that the woman is not valued or is not a fit for a leadership role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Age diversity in the workplace yields better &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/apl0000497&quot;>;organizational performance&lt;/a>; while perceived age discrimination creates &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/josi.12161&quot;>;lower job satisfaction and engagement&lt;/a>;. Similarly, gender diversity also matters. Organizations with diverse leadership teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0148296320303490?via%3Dihub&quot;>;perform better&lt;/a>;, especially in times of crisis; &lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2729348&quot;>;earn more&lt;/a>;; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1748-8583.12079&quot;>;have lower turnover.&lt;/a>; The business case is clear — if organizational leaders pay attention. The good news is that there are practical steps for leaders to combat this never-right gendered age bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Combat Gendered Ageism&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Recognize age bias&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;You can&#39;t fix a problem you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinessdevelopmentcouncil/2020/09/28/gendered-ageism-is-the-new-sexism/?sh=65b14a2214b1&quot;>;won&#39;t admit is there&lt;/a>;. Whereas sexism and racism are the focus of most workplace diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) initiatives, ageism has been largely neglected. All employees should be trained on gendered age bias, just as they are on other forms of discrimination. Use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-news/pages/avoiding-age-discrimination-.aspx&quot;>;interactive case studies&lt;/a>; that include “gray areas” in age-related assumptions and address false stereotypes that older age reduces an individual&#39;s commitment, agility, and ability to learn. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/global-campaign-to-combat-ageism-toolkit&quot;>;Company social media can also be leveraged to get the word out&lt;/a>; about ageism using messaging that taps into both emotions and facts. When the problem ceases to be ignored, necessary improvements can be made.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Address “&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;lookism&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;.” &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Much of gendered ageism is hinged on looks or appearance as a function of societal value. The incessant pressure to look young and attractive is something that &lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/lookism-beauty-still-trumps-brains-in-too-many-workplaces-148278&quot;>;typically impacts women more than men.&lt;/a>; Include &lt;a href=&quot;https://fisherpub.sjf.edu/sfd/vol2/iss1/6/&quot;>;lookism&lt;/a>; in DEI training and ensure that it&#39;s not used as a hidden metric for hiring, promotion, or performance evaluation.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Focus on &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;skills&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;, no matter who has them&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Younger women are often limited — whether intentionally or not — by the assumption of lack of experience. Middle-aged women may be thought of as difficult to manage or having too many family responsibilities. Women who are older are often constrained by perceptions that they are no longer invested in the organization, are less productive, or cannot be promoted. These falsehoods perpetuate the problem. Rather than focusing on age when hiring, making promotion decisions, or bringing on new team members for a growth opportunity, leaders should focus on each woman&#39;s skills, not their tenure or external demands.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Cultivate creative collaborations.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Develop intergenerational, mixed-gender teams and professional relationships to encourage &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2018/11/13/what-older-workers-and-younger-workers-can-learn-from-each-other/?sh=5c7f9a9e2117&quot;>;learning from each other and collaborating on solutions&lt;/a>;. Middle-aged and older employees have years of experience, while younger employees have perspectives from growing up in a more recent time. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.springtideresearch.org/research/work-life&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>; of Generation Z&#39;s expectations at work showed that one of their highest desires was for mentoring relationships; they long for connection with older workers who take &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/organizational-and-employee-development/pages/generation-z-seeks-guidance-in-the-workplace.aspx&quot;>;an interest in them&lt;/a>;. Too often women lack connections that would help them develop professionally due to exclusion from informal networks and events. Intentionally pairing younger women with older mentors and sponsors will aid their learning and career success and enhance your company&#39;s performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The research is clear: Any age can be viewed as “the wrong age” for a woman, allowing her capacity to be questioned and her fitness for leadership challenged. But we can stop stigmatizing women&#39;s age — benefitting not just women, but the whole organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Retailers Can Capitalize on the &ldquo;Refund Effect&rdquo;]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_113908305.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Lori Andrews/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In 2022, US consumers returned 16.5% of purchases, costing retailers an estimated $816 billion in lost revenue. Research suggests that cross-selling products during the return process is an effective strategy to reduce this revenue loss. Across a number of experiments, researchers found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so it&amp;#8217;s less painful to spend these funds on another purchase, so long as cross-selling occurs before the money is reissued to the customers&amp;#8217; original payment method and consumers initially expected to keep the goods they were planning to buy. The researchers also found that this &amp;#8220;refund effect&amp;#8221; applies across categories. Creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can reduce revenue loss from product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-retailers-can-capitalize-on-the-refund-effect?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Product returns pose a major challenge for retailers. In 2022, US consumers returned &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;16.5%&lt;/a>; of merchandise purchases, costing retailers an estimated &lt;a href=&quot;https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2022-retail-returns-rate-remains-flat-816-billion#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%93%20Consumers%20are%20expected%20to,Retail%20Federation%20and%20Appriss%20Retail.&quot;>;$816&lt;/a>; billion in lost revenue. Typical strategies to reduce revenue lost to product returns include reducing the likelihood of returns by providing more information about products (eg, reviews and FAQs) and increasing the financial and transaction costs to consumers who do return products (eg, shipping costs and limited return windows). But the former strategy is costly to retailers, and the latter is costly to consumers. Our recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://myscp.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jcpy.1354&quot;>;research&lt;/a>; identifies an effective strategy for reducing this loss of revenue that benefits everyone: cross-selling products during the product-return process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In six experiments we found that consumers treat refunds as money already lost, so spending these funds on another purchase feels less painful. Research participants were more likely to spend money from a product refund than from a bonus, and even more likely to spend refunded money than unexpected income, like lottery winnings and tax refunds. We call this “the refund effect.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one laboratory experiment, for instance, we gave all participants $4. Some of the participants were asked to use the money to buy a stress ball that they later learned they could return, which most did. Others in a control group made no initial purchase. We then offered everyone the opportunity to keep their $4 or use it to buy a $5 Starbucks gift card at a discount. Only 48% of the control group used their $4 to buy the gift card, whereas 78% of participants who received the refund bought the gift card. We replicated this study with an online sample where the returned product was a gift card from a big-box retailer (ie, Best Buy or Kohls). In this experiment, only 10% of the control group chose to purchase the Starbucks gift card, whereas 25% of participants with refunded money used it to buy the Starbucks gift card.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Retailers who understand the dynamics of the refund effect — when, why, and how it works — stand to mitigate one of the perennial headaches of the industry. Here are three findings retailers should keep in mind to make the most of the refund effect:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Cross-selling opportunities occur during the returns process — before money is reissued to the customers&#39; original payment method.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The refund effect is far less likely to boost sales after money has been refunded to a credit card or checking account.为什么？ The refund effect depends on creating and maintaining an “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/e/earmarking.asp&quot;>;earmark&lt;/a>;” that reminds consumers the money has been lost. Our research found that if refunded money is pooled with money from other sources the earmark is removed and consumers spend it no differently than money from other sources. For example, research participants were more likely to use a refund from a pair of sneakers to buy a shirt if they had yet to receive their money back. If the money had already been deposited in their checking account, they were no more likely to buy the shirt than participants who simply saw the shirt online.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some retailers already effectively use this cross-selling strategy. By default, Amazon asks customers if they&#39;d like to use their return to buy a gift card. Customers who decline this cross-sell then receive their refund. Clothier Todd Snyder lets customers use their refund to immediately buy other products before they mail their return. The remainder of their refund is issued when the return is received. These cross-selling strategies are likely to work because customers shop out of the refund before getting money back from their returns.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect only works when consumers expect to lose money.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Our research showed that consumers have to initially expect to keep the goods and services they buy to create the earmark that makes the refund effect work. “Try before you buy” strategies, where consumers do not expect to pay for returned goods, are unlikely to create a refund effect if those goods are returned.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, research participants who imagined buying two pairs of shoes to try on with the expectation that they would return one pair were no more likely to spend their refund on a jacket than controls who simply imagined seeing the jacket and paying out of pocket. By contrast, participants who did not expect to return a pair of shoes when they bought them were more likely to use the refund from the shoes to buy the jacket&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The refund effect applies across categories.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Because refunded money feels as if it has already been lost, the refund effect applies both to cross-sold products in the same category and products in other categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For instance, research participants in a fifth experiment were more likely to spend a refund from a returned bottle of wine on either a gift card from a grocer or from an athleisure brand than buy either kind of gift card with money out of their pocket. This is good news for retailers who offer a range of product categories.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sale strategies like upselling and exchanges during the product return process should similarly benefit from the refund effect, and they may be better for customer relationship management than increasing the cost of product returns. New companies have stepped into this market. For example, Loop Returns helps 1,500 Shopify merchants, such as Allbirds and Brooklinen, cross-sell, upsell, and exchange products during the product return process, saving &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.loopreturns.com/the-ecommerce-returns-benchmark-report/&quot;>;28% of revenue&lt;/a>; that would otherwise be lost.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The lesson for retailers? Instead of resorting to practices whose harsh transaction costs can &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0008125617741125&quot;>;alienate customers&lt;/a>;, sometimes permanently, creating return policies and practices informed by the refund effect can be an effective way to reduce the revenue loss incurred by product returns in a way that benefits both consumers and retailers.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Ways Companies Are Addressing Skills Gaps in Their Workforce]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_15_TylerComrie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Tyler Comrie&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;We&amp;#8217;re in an unusual economic situation, one where recession fears are high but the job market is tight. As training budgets inevitably come under pressure, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The author examines five of the biggest developments in this space: 1) digital apprenticeships that are helping fill jobs in the digital and tech sectors; 2) tuition-assistance programs aimed at frontline workers; 3) learning-experience platforms with features like skills assessments, algorithmic-driven recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking; 4) the democratization of coaching; and 5) the rise of cohort-based courses.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/5-ways-companies-are-addressing-skills-gaps-in-their-workforce?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;For years, business and HR leaders &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/can-moocs-solve-your-training-problem&quot;>;pinned their hopes&lt;/a>; for better workplace learning on MOOCs, or massive open online courses. Unfortunately, the evidence &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.1921417117#ref-3&quot;>;continues to show&lt;/a>; that these are not enough on their own, particularly for those who most need them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies now have more options, thanks to better technology, innovative funding mechanisms, and old approaches reimagined to meet today&#39;s needs. Below, I explain five of the biggest developments in this space.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The New Digital Apprenticeship&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a medieval practice is propelling thousands of workers onto the career ladder&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The apprenticeship is perhaps the oldest form of workplace learning, stretching back to ancient times, and boasting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/apprenticeship&quot;>;some illustrious alumni&lt;/a>;, including Benjamin Franklin. There are more than 580,000 active apprentices working in the US right now — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apprenticeship.gov/data-and-statistics&quot;>;up 103% in the past 10 years&lt;/a>;, according to Department of Labor figures.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For companies that consistently struggle to fill important roles, apprenticeships may be an effective solution. While apprenticeships have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/global/2020/feb/04/tanners-tailors-and-candlestick-makers-a-history-of-apprenticeships&quot;>;historically&lt;/a>; been associated with blue-collar jobs, they&#39;re increasingly becoming a way to fill white-collar jobs in the digital and tech sectors. Apprenticeships in the IT and telecommunications sector grew by more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027040416/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/telecommunications#:~:text=In%202020%20there%20were%203%2C654%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20telecommunications%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20300%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years.%20%5B2%5D&quot;>;300%&lt;/a>; between 2011 and 2020, while cybersecurity apprenticeships grew by &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20211027023746/https:/www.apprenticeship.gov/apprenticeship-industries/cybersecurity#:~:text=In%202020%2C%20there%20were%202%2C716%20registered%20apprentices%20in%20cybersecurity%20occupations%2C%20increasing%20over%20600%25%20in%20the%20last%20nine%20years%20%5B2%5D.&quot;>;600%&lt;/a>; during the same period, according to the Department of Labor.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend is powered by a growing number of companies, many of which are focused on fast-growing fields like software engineering and data science, that recruit, support, and train apprentices on behalf of large employers. One UK-based provider, Multiverse, was recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://tcrn.ch/3H0ebPR&quot;>;valued&lt;/a>; at $1.7bn and claims to have served &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/multiverse-community-reaches-10-000-apprentices-and-alumni&quot;>;10,000 apprentices&lt;/a>;. “We&#39;ve long been believers in the apprenticeship model, and we&#39;ve found it particularly effective for tech and digital jobs,” said Rashitha Jayasekara, chief of digital manufacturing at Rolls-Royce, which works with Multiverse to&amp;nbsp;upskill existing employees. “The experiential learning that apprentices get through hackathons and project work allows them to combine theory and practice in a way standard training doesn&#39;t, and to continuously develop skills we need within the company.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Verizon, another Multiverse customer, uses the apprenticeship model to fill software engineering jobs and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.multiverse.io/en-US/blog/creating-software-engineering-jobs-verizon&quot;>;reports&lt;/a>; that 95% of an initial cohort accepted full-time offers at the company after completing an apprenticeship program. The Verizon program was designed to “lower barriers to entry to software jobs while training truly great software developers that we fundamentally believe can propel our business through digital innovation,” said Shankar Arumugavelu, Verizon&#39;s chief information officer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Apprenticeships aren&#39;t right for all training needs. For one thing, they require a significant investment of time — in the US, formal apprenticeships are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/careeroutlook/2017/article/apprenticeships_occupations-and-outlook.htm#:~:text=Formal%20apprenticeship%20programs%20usually%20last,Department%20of%20Labor%20(DOL).&quot;>;usually four years long&lt;/a>;. In some markets they can also come with restrictive regulation. In the UK, for instance, the government&#39;s apprenticeship funding program &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerweekly.com/news/365530295/Government-urged-to-address-broken-apprenticeship-levy-system&quot;>;has been criticized&lt;/a>; for being too rigid and not in line with employers&#39; needs.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Fresh Approach to Tuition Reimbursement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How a historically elite benefit is becoming accessible for all&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Large companies have long offered to pay for their employees&#39; continuing education. However, these benefits have historically been reserved for a small number of white-collar employees, for example, those pursuing an executive MBA. Or employees were asked to pay for their courses out of pocket and get reimbursed afterwards.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the labor market has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/themes/how-to-better-support-and-retain-frontline-workers&quot;>;changed&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/companies-offer-tuition-assistance-so-workers-can-go-back-to-college.html&quot;>;more companies&lt;/a>; are offering tuition benefits as a way to retain their frontline employees — store clerks, baristas, drivers, and hourly workers. In response, a new class of companies has emerged to smooth and synchronize the relationship between training providers, employers, employees, and (in some cases) the government. Employees receive coaching, advice, and support to help them find the training program that&#39;s right for them, and the training programs are paid for by the employer.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, in 2021, Target announced a tuition-assistance program called &lt;a href=&quot;https://corporate.target.com/article/2022/09/dream-to-be-anniversary#:~:text=Our%20%24200%20million%20investment%20in,skills%20and%20build%20their%20careers.&quot;>;“Dream to Be&lt;/a>;” in partnership with Guild, one of the leading players in this growing space. According to Chief Diversity and Inclusion officer Kiera Fernandez, “Target has offered a traditional tuition reimbursement program for more than two decades. Now, through our partnership with Guild to offer Dream to Be, team members can attend classes at more than 40 schools, colleges, and universities … with no out-of-pocket tuition costs.” Fernandez said that as of April 2023, more than 25,000 employees have been approved for the program.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If designed effectively, the benefits of tuition assistance programs for employers are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/small-business/human-resources/articles/tuition-reimbursement/&quot;>;clear&lt;/a>;. For example, Jack Hartung, chief financial officer of fast-casual restaurant chain Chipotle, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/video/2021/04/09/chipotle-cfo-says-debt-free-degree-is-a-way-to-invest-in-employees.html&quot;>;told CNBC&lt;/a>; that “employees who take advantage of the company&#39;s free degrees are three and a half times more likely to stay with the company and seven times more likely to move up into management.” However, research suggests that while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180108006550/en/New-Study-Shows-Lasting-Impact-Tuition-Assistance#:~:text=84%25%20say%20access%20to%20a%20tuition%20assistance%20program%20was%20important%20in%20their%20decision%20to%20join%20the%20company&quot;>;84%&lt;/a>; of employees value tuition reimbursement benefits highly, on average, &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholarlycommons.law.northwestern.edu/nulr/vol117/iss6/5/#:~:text=Yet%2C%20despite%20their%20increasing%20availability%2C%20only%202%25%20of%20employees%2C%20as%20a%20percentage%20of%20those%20interested%20in%20pursuing%20further%20education%2C%20are%20utilizing%20these%20reimbursement%20programs&quot;>;only 2%&lt;/a>; of eligible employees use this benefit. This implies employers must do more to take advantage of this powerful tool.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;A Shift to Learning Experience Platforms&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How employees know what to learn next&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Organizing and tracking what employees are learning can be a cumbersome task. For years, this work has been done by software known as “learning management systems” (LMS), which are relatively simple tools that store learning material, typically in the form of presentations, videos, and text. Most large companies &lt;a href=&quot;https://trainingmag.com/2021-training-industry-report/#:~:text=Some%2098%20percent%20of%20large%20companies%20and%2096%20percent%20of%20midsize%20ones%20currently%20use%20LMSs%20vs.%2080%20percent%20of%20small%20companies.&quot;>;have one&lt;/a>;, but few employees &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinkruse/2021/04/27/usage-of-degreed-is-double-that-of-traditional-learning-platforms/?sh=58ba9a1a2d3d#:~:text=most%20LMS%20and%20online%20content%20companies%20only%20see%205%25%20to%2015%25%20of%20licensed%20seats%20used%20in%20any%20given%20month.&quot;>;spend much time&lt;/a>; on them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the last few years, a new wave of tools has transformed the LMS into “Learning Experience Platforms” (LXP), with features like skills assessments, Netflix-style recommendations about what to learn next, and internal social networking. LXPs “make learning relevant for individuals, not just managing training programs,” according Todd Tauber senior vice president of strategy at Degreed, one of the leading providers in this space. Industry analyst Josh Bersin estimates the market for LXPs is &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/06/corporate-learning-bombshell-degreed-acquires-learnin-david-blake-returns/&quot;>;$500m,&lt;/a>; up from &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2018/07/edcast-expands-the-lxp-market-with-focus-on-global-upskilling/&quot;>;$200m&lt;/a>; in 2018.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Customers report that the model is working. Chris Harry is the chief learning officer of TEK Systems, a staffing firm that&#39;s been using Degreed. “Since moving our various employee development programs onto Degreed, we&#39;ve seen our highest-ever engagement and satisfaction rates,” he said. According to Harry, 96% of TEK employees have created an account in Degreed, and the company consistently sees 40 to 50% of them actively using the platform each month, which he says is “far higher than anything we&#39;ve seen before.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Results like these require real investment beyond simply buying the technology. For &lt;a href=&quot;https://get.degreed.com/hubfs/Client%20Case%20Studies/Ericsson/Ericsson+Degreed%20Case%20Study_Q2-22_EN-US.pdf?utm_campaign=Ericsson%20Case%20Study%20May%20%2722&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsmi=214005662&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-_8Z515BnP5WAJI5xGCg8ZF2Zi2ftiYmmfHEKikOYkDheoBPQzXBzi5mM6FOcyAZGppjQgdYXltDyoeVeVVC1bEnUM8xfnubGHUldzPilsSLH3Yk90&amp;amp;utm_content=214005662&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_automation&quot;>;example&lt;/a>;, another Degreed customer, Ericsson, said it hired internal champions and developed an extensive internal marketing campaign to roll out its program.&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Democratization of Coaching&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How all of us can have a Sherpa for our careers&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Professional coaching is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2009-12395-008&quot;>;well-understood&lt;/a>; way to boost workers&#39; learning, confidence, and effectiveness. However, it has typically been an &lt;a href=&quot;/2009/01/what-can-coaches-do-for-you#:~:text=they%E2%80%99re%20usually%20called%20executive%20coaches%2C%20and%20they%20can%20earn%20up%20to%20%243%2C500%20an%20hour.&quot;>;expensive&lt;/a>; tool, reserved only for senior executives. Moreover, even for those who can afford it, finding a coach can be a challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;New platforms have emerged that use technology to make it easier to find, match, and work with coaches. New companies provide tools to assess what each employee needs from their coach, match them with a coach who has the right experience and expertise, and even conduct coaching sessions via a digital platform.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The space is growing. According to the International Coaching Federation, there were &lt;a href=&quot;https://coachfederation.org/app/uploads/2020/09/FINAL_ICF_GCS2020_ExecutiveSummary.pdf&quot;>;71,000&lt;/a>; practicing coaches in 2021, up 33% from 2016. Investors expect growth to continue: The leading digital coaching startup, BetterUp, raised $300m in 2021 at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/betterup&quot;>;$5bn valuation&lt;/a>; as part of a wave of &lt;a href=&quot;https://joshbersin.com/2022/01/online-coaching-is-so-hot-its-now-disrupting-leadership-development/&quot;>;investment&lt;/a>; into coaching startups.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of this growth is powered by large companies offering coaching services more broadly to their employees. Danone, the France-based food products company, has been working with one provider, CoachHub, to offer this benefit to 250 employees. According to Maxime Hollande, who leads diversity and inclusion for Danone in the Netherlands, “these coaching sessions have been of big added value for employees… One of the metrics we watch closely is the extent to which each employee has progressed toward the personal goals each of them define with their coach. The average score on this metric is 4.9 out of 5.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Chevron, the American global energy company, has made coaching sessions available to 7,000 of its managers around the world via BetterUp. “Prior to BetterUp, we utilized an assortment of internal coaching resources and multiple external coaching vendors,” explained Rhonda Morris, Chevron&#39;s chief human resources officer. “BetterUp&#39;s virtual coaching model … has matured our coaching culture making it more accessible for all who want it.&amp;nbsp; Coaches no longer have to travel to meet our employees. Our employees have been very vocal about their positive experiences with BetterUp.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Because coaching sessions are inherently private experiences, it can be hard for employers to ensure a focus on the topics that are most important to them. At Chevron, they measure the success each quarter by asking employees to rate the effectiveness of leaders who&#39;ve received coaching. “Leadership Effectiveness is consistently one of our highest scoring categories across our organization,” Morris said. “This shows that our BetterUp offerings are having a positive impact on our workforce and culture.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Rise of Cohort-Based Courses &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;How to build real skills online&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When it comes to online learning, most participants &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aav7958&quot;>;don&#39;t finish&lt;/a>; the courses they start, mainly because the learning experience is asynchronous. Individuals must be disciplined and diligent enough to complete large amounts of the learning material on their own. This is particularly difficult in today&#39;s workplace, where the number of meetings and distractions has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/great-expectations-making-hybrid-work-work&quot;>;ballooned&lt;/a>; in recent years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now, a new delivery format called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://future.com/cohort-based-courses/&quot;>;cohort-based courses&lt;/a>;” has emerged as a way to improve completion rates. Groups of participants together take a course with defined start and end dates, regular homework assignments, and an instructor to run periodic live online discussion sessions. Within this more structured format, participants still access much of the learning material on their own time, making it easier for them to complete the course and have the chance to apply what they learn over its duration. One of the pioneers of this space, altMBA, says its learners have achieved a &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/behavior-design/how-to-design-an-online-course-with-a-96-completion-rate-180678117a85&quot;>;96% completion rate&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boston Consulting Group (BCG) is one leading employer that has embraced cohort-based courses, working in partnership with Emeritus (where I work). Lidia Juszko, BCG&#39;s executive director of global learning and teaming, describes how the format works particularly well for a professional services firm like hers. “We&#39;ve found that cohort-based courses offer a level of structure and support that makes them more engaging than standard online learning,” she said. “Our colleagues report that the combination and cadence of &#39;office hours&#39; with instructors, live discussion sessions with the rest of the cohort, and short videos and exercises to be completed each week are a more accessible way for them to learn. Learning and development opportunities like this allow us to continue to attract and retain the best talent.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;HSBC, the global banking organization, recently began piloting cohort-based online courses as well, and the early results are promising. According to David Morris, global head of people capability, “One of our challenges has been to deliver in-depth learning in an online format, given the range and complexity of our markets. Our early results show that the online cohort-based format is achieving significant improvement across key indicators like completion, confidence, and capability.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The downside of this format is that the live learning elements that make it effective come at a substantial cost. A single license to an open library of standard online courses costs about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.classcentral.com/report/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/comparing-subscription-pricing-2023.png&quot;>;$30 to $60&lt;/a>; per month for access to thousands of courses (most providers also offer significant volume discounts). Meanwhile, cohort-based courses can cost between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/serenitygibbons/2021/12/17/how-cohort-based-learning-is-transforming-online-education/#:~:text=Another%20notable%20difference%20is%20the%20price%3B%20cohort%20based%20courses%20can%20range%20anywhere%20from%20%24500%20up%20to%20more%20than%20%245%2C000.&quot;>;$500 and $5,000&lt;/a>; per course&lt;em>;.&lt;/em>; This means cohort-based learning is unlikely to be an option for all employees, and employers must carefully decide who can benefit the most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We are in an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/simonmoore/2022/12/02/many-indicators-imply-a-2023-recession-the-jobs-market-disagrees/&quot;>;unusual&lt;/a>; economic situation, one where recession fears are up but the job market is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/b1b710a1-6d12-43e5-8508-ae4584a7289a&quot;>;still tight&lt;/a>;. As training budgets inevitably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peoplemanagement.co.uk/article/1812542/half-organisations-looking-cut-ld-costs-amid-economic-difficulty-survey-reveals&quot;>;come under pressure&lt;/a>;, organizations will need to find more targeted ways to address their skills gaps. The five approaches outlined above can help companies move beyond the MOOC to find a learning program that&#39;s right for their employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Editor&#39;s Note: Harvard Business Publishing has a content creation and distribution partnership with Emeritus.&amp;nbsp;Neither the author or editor who worked on this article are involved in that partnership.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>