<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How to Find the Time to Connect with Colleagues When You&rsquo;re Very, Very Busy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_482824941.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HollenderX2/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;我们在工作中常常无休无止的待办事项清单的一个后果是同事之间失去了友情。虽然生产力很重要，但完成任务和花时间与团队联系之间的平衡对于避免倦怠和让工作变得更加愉快至关重要。常见的误解是一天中根本没有足够的时间（或精力）来完成工作和社交；现实情况是，在会议开始或结束时的简短信息、喝咖啡或小组分享都是简单而有影响力的行为，只需要很少的努力和时间，从而使前一个论点变得无效。研究表明，尽管社交感觉像是一项艰巨的任务，但它可以通过让我们充满活力来有效对抗精神疲劳。精力充沛可以提高绩效，因此事实证明，社交活动比埋头工作比培养与同事的联系更有益。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-find-the-time-to-connect-with-colleagues-when-youre-very-very-busy?language=pt&quot;>;勒尔em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当您感觉任务落后并且期限紧迫时，您最不想做的事情就是赶上并与同事联系。您只想低下头，核对待办事项清单上的任务，然后把事情做好。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有时候您绝对应该戴上眼罩，只专注于您的战术目标。但是，仅以事务性方式与同事互动可能会导致您失去任何个人联系感，尤其是在远程工作时。每天花几分钟来培养工作中的融洽感，您就可以解锁&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/to-be-happier-at-work-invest-more-in- your-relationships&quot;>;更强的目标感和幸福感，减少倦怠，甚至提高你的表现。&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，如何为人们腾出时间而不感到更大的压力和不知所措呢？作为一名时间管理教练，我发现只要多一点意图，您就可以建立更有意义的联系，而无需投入太多时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;在一对一会议中聊天&lt;/ strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您已经安排了与团队的一对一会议，请在讨论开始时花几分钟了解他们的进展情况，然后再开始讨论业务议程。你不需要把所有的时间都花在个人更新上，但即使留出五分钟的时间询问他们最近的假期，了解他们的妈妈是否出院，或者看看他们从手术中恢复得如何，都可以让差异。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您可以使用相同的策略与经常一起处理项目的同事进行一对一会议。根据会议的长度和您需要讨论的内容，您可能没有时间每次都跟上。但是，如果每隔几次会议，您在开始或结束时都花几分钟讨论手头的项目之外的内容，那么您就可以加强这些联系。这可能包括因对某个特定运动队的兴奋而建立联系，谈论您的家人，或讨论任何其他可以为您提供超越一维、面向任务的水平的联系空间的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果记住有关的详细信息人们的生活对你来说并不自然，请在你的日历中用记忆线索做一个私人笔记，例如询问他们的新小狗、孩子最近的课外活动，或者他们的副业进展如何。&lt;/p>; &lt; h2>;&lt;strong>;鼓励会议期间进行小组共享&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在大型团队会议中，不会有太多空间供个人交流。但如果您的团队较小，每周或每月花一些时间进行更新可能是合适的。这可以很简单，就像在会议开始时快速分享最近的事件一样，例如参加行业会议。如果您亲自工作并为此指定了特定的论坛，这种情况也可以自然发生：例如，如果您在周一早上带咖啡和百吉饼一起吃早餐，或者如果有周五下午的欢乐时光。即使是 15 到 20 分钟的非结构化谈话也可以增强团队参与感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您是远程或混合团队的一员，有机联系可能会更困难。考虑举办虚拟欢乐时光或让几个人在团队会议期间分享。只需保持这些更新简短，这样&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/irl/highs-lows-weekend-tiktok/&quot;>;高潮和低谷就不会变成病毒式表情包&lt;/a>; .&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;将休息时间变成非正式的社交时间&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在午休时间与同事一起吃点东西。您的会议安排可能不允许每天都有适当的午休时间，但每周至少抽出几天时间不在电脑前处理多项任务，可以让您的午餐更加愉快、更具社交性。这可以提前计划好，你可以与另一个部门中不常见面的人会面，或者可以更非正式地与与你一起工作的团队成员见面。如果您想要一种轻松的方式，只需在您出门或重新加热剩菜时询问某人是否愿意加入您即可。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://creativecloud .adobe.com/discover/article/a-science-backed-guide-to-take-truly-restful-breaks&quot;>;社交休息还可以有效对抗午后低迷时期的精神疲劳&lt;/a>;，并帮助您感觉良好在结束一天的工作之前，您会精神焕发地完成最后的工作。当您发现眼睑下垂且头部摇头时，请站起来并活动一下。如果您在办公室，这是在大厅里散步并与一些人联系或邀请某人喝杯咖啡的绝佳时机。与午餐类似，您可以停下来与自己团队的成员聊天或顺便拜访另一个部门。这些动作和谈话会唤醒你，并成为一个联系和潜在的内部网络的时间。如果您正在远程工作，请向同事发送友好的 Slack 消息，而不是转向滚动社交媒体。即使他们太忙而无法回复，他们也可能会主动提出稍后与您联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;在上下班途中拨打电话&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果您上下班途中无论是办公室还是出差，您的某些旅行时间可能会提供一个与同事进行非正式交流的理想机会。我的一位客户是一位高管，会议日程排得满满的，他开车回家与领导进行了非正式的交谈。这有助于他对他们的想法和担忧有更个人的看法，因为公司正在经历重大转型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当您在路上时，您可以从机场、优步或酒店拨打电话，或者当您排队或乘坐火车时发送消息。即使是五到十分钟的对话也可以增进你们的融洽关系，最重要的是，可以表明您的关心。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;利用虚拟消息传递&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果如果您完全远程工作，非正式社交联系的选择将受到限制。在这些情况下，您只需发送一条快速聊天消息或短信，询问某人的近况或与他们分享快速更新。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您不自觉，这些对话最终可能会花费大量时间他们会持续多长时间，因此您需要限制参与纯粹社交消息传递的频率。但每周联系几次可能会很有趣，并帮助您感受到联系。考虑在自然时间你会说“你好！”的时候联系别人。过去与同事交谈，例如当您第一次到达办公桌时、午餐前后或等待会议开始时。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;找到时间与人交谈可能是一个挑战当您几乎感觉自己没有时间完成任务和项目时。但与同事交流是有好处的。不要低着头只专注于工作，而是在日程安排中找到一些可以与同事进行深思熟虑的时间。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Steps to Prepare Your Culture for AI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_1468369205.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;gremlin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;平台向 AI 的转变正在顺利进行。虽然它有望改变工作方式并赋予组织竞争优势，但如果没有拥抱好奇心、失败和学习的文化，就不可能实现这些好处。领导者处于独特的地位，可以在当今的组织内培育这种文化，以便让他们的团队为未来的成功做好准备。当与人工智能的能力相结合时，这种文化将为每个人开启更美好的工作未来。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href =&quot;/2023/06/3-steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/3- Steps-to-prepare-your-culture-for-ai?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;作为商业领袖，今天我们发现自己处于一个非常熟悉的地方：陌生。正如我们引导我们的团队转向远程和灵活工作一样，我们现在正处于另一个巨大转变的边缘：人工智能。就像向灵活工作的转变一样，组织接受人工智能首先取决于文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;工作的节奏和数量呈指数级增长，我们都在其重压下挣扎。 。领导者和员工都渴望人工智能能够减轻负担。这是我们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/will-ai-fix-work&quot;>;2023 年工作趋势指数&lt;/a>;的关键要点，该调查对 31 个国家/地区的 31,000 人进行了调查，并分析了 Microsoft 365 中数万亿个聚合生产力信号以及 LinkedIn 上的劳动力市场趋势。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;接受调查的员工中近三分之二告诉我们他们没有足够的时间或精力来完成他们的工作。我们在报告中将这种消耗的原因确定为数字债务：数据、电子邮件和聊天的涌入已经超出了我们跟上的能力。如今，员工将近 60% 的时间用于沟通，只有 40% 的时间用于创造和创新。在创造力成为新生产力的世界中，数字债务不仅是一种不便，而且是一种负担。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能承诺通过让员工专注于最有意义的工作来解决这种负担。根据我们的研究，提高生产力、简化重复性任务和提高员工福祉是领导者希望从人工智能中获得的三大好处。值得注意的是，由于担心人工智能将取代工作岗位，减少员工数量被排在最后。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;成为人工智能驱动的组织将需要我们以全新的方式工作。作为领导者，我们今天可以采取三个步骤，让我们的文化为人工智能驱动的未来做好准备：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;选择好奇而不是恐惧&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;人工智能标志着人类与人类之间的新互动模式电脑。到目前为止，我们与计算机交互的方式类似于我们与计算器交互的方式：我们提出问题或给出指示，然后计算机提供答案。但有了人工智能，计算机将更像是副驾驶。我们需要共同发展一种新的化学反应，学习何时以及如何提出问题以及事实核查答复的重要性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;恐惧是对变化的自然反应，因此员工可以理解对人工智能对他们的工作意味着什么感到有些不确定。我们的研究发现，虽然 49% 的员工担心人工智能会取代他们的工作，但人工智能的前景大于威胁：70% 的员工非常愿意委托人工智能来减轻他们的工作量。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们在恐惧中行动很少能得到好处。通过培养好奇心文化，我们可以让员工了解人工智能的工作原理，包括其功能和缺点。这种理解始于第一手经验。鼓励员工通过（安全可靠地）尝试新的&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.microsoft.com/reinventing-productivity/&quot;>;AI 工具&lt;/a>;（例如由 AI 驱动的&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.bing.com/search?form=MY0291&amp;amp;OCID=MY0291&amp;amp;q=Bing+AI&amp;amp;showconv=1&quot;>;搜索&lt;/a>;、智能写作帮助或智能日历，以仅举几个例子。由于每个角色和职能都有不同的方式来使用人工智能并从中受益，因此要求他们在熟悉这些工具后重新思考人工智能如何改进或转变流程。从那里，员工可以开始解锁新的工作方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;拥抱失败&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;人工智能将改变几乎所有工作，几乎每种工作模式都可以从某种程度的人工智能增强或自动化。作为领导者，现在是鼓励我们的团队将创造力重新构想工作的时候了，采用边测试边学习的策略来寻找人工智能能够最好地帮助满足业务需求的方法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能赢了。不可能每次都正确，但即使是错误的，它也是&lt;em>;有用&lt;/em>;的错误。它至少能让你从一张白纸向前迈出一步，这样你就可以直接进入审阅、编辑或增强的批判性思维工作。学习这些新的工作模式并确定哪些流程需要改变以及如何改变需要时间。但是，如果我们创造一种文化，将实验和学习视为进步的先决条件，我们就会更快地实现这一目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为领导者，我们有责任为失败创造合适的环境，以便我们的团队能够成功。人们有权进行实验，以发现人工智能如何融入他们的工作流程。根据我的经验，这包括庆祝胜利以及分享经验教训，以帮助彼此避免浪费时间学习相同的教训两次。无论是正式还是非正式的方式，为人们分享知识创造空间——例如，通过在部门内众包一本快速指南，或者将人工智能技巧作为每月全体员工会议的常设议程项目。敏捷运营将成为人工智能驱动的组织的基本原则。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;成为万事通&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我经常听到这样的担忧：人工智能将成为拐杖，提供捷径和解决方法最终会削弱创新和参与度。在我看来，人工智能的潜力远不止于此，对于那些深思熟虑地使用它的人来说，它将成为一种竞争优势。这些人将成为您最敬业、最具创新精神的员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您从人工智能中获得的价值取决于您投入的价值。简单的问题将得到简单的答案。但复杂的、发人深省的问题将带来更复杂的分析和更大的想法。价值将从拥有所有正确答案的员工转移到知道如何提出正确问题的员工。未来的组织将重视能够对人工智能生成的内容进行有效推理的分析思考者和问题解决者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在 Microsoft，我们相信博学多才的心态将使我们走得更远。一位无所不知的人。虽然使用人工智能的学习曲线可能令人望而生畏，但它是一种必须随着时间的推移而增强的肌肉——我们今天就应该开始加强它。当我与领导者谈论如何在公司和团队中实现这一目标时，我告诉他们三件事：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;建立护栏，帮助人们安全、负责任地进行实验。您鼓励员工使用哪些工具，哪些数据适合输入，哪些数据不适合输入。他们在事实核查、审查和编辑方面需要遵循哪些准则？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;学习使用人工智能需要是一个持续的过程，而不是一次性的培训。将学习机会融入您的业务节奏，让员工了解最新资源。例如，一个团队可能会在周五下午安排学习时间，而另一个团队则每月安排“办公时间”进行人工智能问答和故障排除。并超越传统课程或资源进行思考。点对点知识共享（例如午餐和学习或数字热线）如何发挥作用，以便人们可以互相学习？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;拥抱变革管理的需求。有意和有计划对于成功采用人工智能至关重要。确定成功的目标和指标，并选择人工智能冠军或试点项目负责人来帮助实现愿景。在人工智能方面，不同的职能和学科会有不同的需求和挑战，但当我们都转向新的工作方式时，一个共同的需求将是结构和支持。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;平台向人工智能的转变正在顺利进行。虽然它有望改变工作方式并为组织带来竞争优势，但如果没有拥抱好奇心、失败和学习的文化，就不可能实现这些好处。作为领导者，我们拥有独特的优势，可以在当今的组织内培育这种文化，以便让我们的团队为未来的成功做好准备。当与人工智能的能力相结合时，这种文化将为每个人带来更美好的工作未来。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Commit to the LGBTQ+ Community When Hate Is on the Rise]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/commit-to-the-lgbtq-community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_28_512010335_1421562884_1385767484_109438804_1148780239-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; 咏叹调- label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/william87/ MoMo Productions/FG Trade/David Arky/Yifei Fang/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;随着反 LGBTQ+ 情绪和立法的急剧增加，在美国和世界其他国家，善意的高管与其选民之间的脱节日益严重。正如 LGBTQ+ 员工和社区、民权倡导者以及具有社会意识的消费者希望雇主采取行动一样，许多公司正在收回之前的支持。然而，大多数消费者仍然期望企业通过行动履行其承诺，并继续奖励那些这样做的公司的支持和惠顾。在充满敌意的社会和政治环境中，公司必须将其行动植根于组织的宗旨、价值主张和价值观，以长期将支持 LGBTQ+ 的支持融入到组织的身份中。作者建议采取三个步骤来实现这一目标：1) 将 LGBTQ+ 包容性与您的客户群、运营和价值观联系起来； 2) 协作设计有利于 LGBTQ+ 社区的举措； 3) 采取有目的的立场并捍卫它。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/commit-to- the-lgbtq-community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/commit-to-the-lgbtq -community-when-hate-is-on-the-rise?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;“该组织长期以来一直是 LGBTQ+ 社区的盟友，”一位高管指出。 “但最近，鉴于目前的政治气候，即使在五年前做或说也不会引起争议的事情现在比以前受到了更多的阻力。我们如何表达我们的关心？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“这个组织声称它是我们社区的盟友，”一名员工说道。 “但最近，面对对 LGBTQ+ 人群日益增长的敌意，我们已经到了崩溃的边缘，而我们的领导人却什么也没说。他们为什么不保护我们？是因为他们从来没有关心过吗？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一名 DEI 策略师，我经常从与我合作的组织中的人员那里听到此类评论。他们并不罕见。这些情绪表明，随着企业参与 LGBTQ+ 事业的不断发展，善意的高管与 LGBTQ+ 员工、消费者和社区之间的脱节日益严重。消费者和员工越来越要求企业遵守&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/06/were-entering-the-age-of-corporate-social-justice&quot;>;更高的标准&lt;/a>;，这使得他们的惠顾取决于品牌的内部表现LGBTQ+ 人群的外部待遇与他们华丽的营销相一致，并呼吁他们进行&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/life/a43713768/rainbow-washing/&quot;>;彩虹清洗&lt;/a>;他们失败了。与此同时，&lt;a href=&quot;https://acleddata.com/2022/11/23/update-fact-sheet-anti-lgbt-mobilization-in-the-united-states/&quot;>;戏剧性峰值&lt; /a>; 在反 LGBTQ+ 社会和政治运动中，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.erininthemorning.com/p/may-anti-trans-legislative-risk-map&quot;>;倒退法律的通过&lt;/a >;、仇恨言论和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/jun/07/lgbtq-violence-protest-glendale-unified-school-district&quot;>;身体暴力行为&lt;/a>; 在美国，伴随着世界各地右翼极端主义、威权主义和反民主信仰的相关增加，推动了新一波&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pbs.org/ newshour/nation/online-right-wing-extremists-amp-up-anti-lgbtq-rhetoric-during-pride-month&quot;>;针对 LGBTQ+ 社区以及支持他们的品牌和雇主的活动&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些因素的结合意味着，现在，正如 LGBTQ+ 员工和社区、民权倡导者以及具有社会意识的消费者希望雇主采取行动支持他们之前支持 LGBTQ+ 的承诺一样，一些雇主&lt;a href=&quot; https://nypost.com/2023/05/04/anheuser-busch-ceo-disavows-bud-light-dylan-mulvaney-ads/&quot;>;否认他们的 LGBTQ+ 合作伙伴关系&lt;/a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.npr.org/2023/05/24/1177963864/target-pride-month-lgbtq-products-threats&quot;>;删除骄傲主题商品&lt;/a>;，以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://www .forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2023/06/23/starbucks-union-workers-are-striking-after-accusing-firm-of-banning-pride-decorations/?sh=371a510a511b&quot;>;禁止骄傲装饰&lt;/ a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那些担心现在采取行动支持 LGBTQ+ 社区“风险太大”的领导人可以放心，因为他们知道绝大多数消费者 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc .com/2023/06/01/consumers-say-companies-should-support-lgbtq-community-glaad-survey.html&quot;>;根据 GLAAD 最近的一项调查，70%&lt;/a>; — 希望他们采取通过支持 LGBTQ+ 人群，明确站在公民权利、公平和包容方面。还有有据可查的商业利益：绝大多数消费者，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/13/workers-consumers-prefer-pro-lgbtq-brands-glaad -study.html&quot;>;无论他们本身是否是 LGBTQ+&lt;/a>;，都更有可能从支持 LGBTQ+ 的公司购买产品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管有这些明显的好处，领导者可能仍然不确定未来如何-证明他们在敌对的社会和政治环境中对 LGBTQ+ 包容的承诺。答案在于将他们的行动植根于组织的宗旨、价值主张和价值观，从而将支持 LGBTQ+ 的支持长期融入到组织的身份中。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.将 LGBTQ+ 包容性与您的客户群、运营和价值观联系起来。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;虽然大多数消费者现在期望品牌在社会和政治问题上采取立场，但这并不像发布一次性社交媒体帖子或公然以利润为动机的营销活动那么容易。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://sproutsocial.com/insights/data/brands-creating-change/&quot;>;关于社会问题的品牌传播研究&lt;/a>;发现，消费者认为品牌最适合采取当涉及到品牌价值观、影响业务或影响品牌员工或消费者时，您应采取何种立场。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;面向未来的 LGBTQ+ 包容性需要积极主动地了解 LGBTQ+ 群体的需求，以及您的 LGBTQ+ 群体的需求。非 LGBTQ+ 客户以及客户对 LGBTQ+ 问题的看法。然后，您需要了解您的运营如何影响 LGBTQ+ 社区，以找到独特的重叠部分和采取行动的机会。如果您有 LGBTQ+ 客户，您可能会开发满足他们需求的产品。如果您与 LGBTQ+ 内容创作者或艺术家合作，您可能会利用他们的才能实现互惠互利。如果您有 LGBTQ+ 用户或客户，您可能会征求他们的反馈以开发更具包容性的产品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了锁定这些努力，您需要根据组织根深蒂固的使命、目的来重新构建它们和值。如果您的组织坚定地致力于维护尊严，您可以将 LGBTQ+ 包容性作为保护所有客户和员工尊严的重要组成部分。如果您的组织坚定地致力于勇敢，您可以将 LGBTQ+ 包容性定义为承认勇敢反对迫害，并作为一个组织勇敢地发言。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;总而言之，这意味着组织能够&lt;a href= &quot;https://www.deloitte.com/global/en/about/people/social-responsibility/lgbt-inclusion.html&quot;>;明确阐述&lt;/a>; LGBTQ+ 包容性的地位，因为它与其核心目的、价值相关主张和价值观将为他们的努力奠定坚实的基础，当政治风向转变时，这种基础不太可能动摇。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.协作设计有利于 LGBTQ+ 社区的举措。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;尽管品牌的骄傲月活动已经变得无处不在，但仅仅将产品交给 LGBTQ+ 影响者并让他们阅读剧本并不能特别引起 LGBTQ+ 人群的共鸣。如果做得不好，它可能会被认为是一种肤浅的宣传噱头，旨在从 LGBTQ+ 群体中获利，但却没有给他们带来真正的好处。此外，当这些举措似乎与组织的目的或价值主张脱节时，您的非 LGBTQ+ 选民可能会觉得您的社会立场是武断的——这为那些可能对 LGBTQ+ 人群存有偏见的人批评您的立场“打开了大门”。告诉他们应该怎么想。”&lt;span>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你可以实际解决的问题&lt;em>;不是&lt;/em>;消费者、员工或其他人持有的信念范围而是社会事业、组织目的和选民需求的一致性。当举措或合作伙伴关系同时​​满足这三个方面时（例如，由客户需求驱动并根据客户意见设计的骄傲月举措，旨在解决与企业核心服务相关的未满足需求），即使选民不属于直接以社区为中心的社区，他们可能会支持这一举措，或者在最坏的情况下，对这一举措持中立态度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;顾问在 30 分钟的头脑风暴中吐出的机会主义营销策略已经过时了。设计&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/lucianapaulise/2022/10/11/how-to-promote-inclusion--virgin-atlantic-removes-gendered-uniforms/?sh=74cb1f3355dd&quot;在这方面>;成功的举措&lt;/a>;需要与 LGBTQ+ 社区内外的成员进行深入合作，以确保该举措为目标社区创造价值，使其与组织的宗旨和身份保持一致，并测试它是否能够实现以预期的方式登陆观众。越多的三方成员能够推动并告知这一过程（无论是通过顾问委员会、焦点小组还是其他参与方法），这些举措就越有可能成功满足未满足的需求、创造价值并引起共鸣。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;强>;3。采取有目的的立场并捍卫它。 &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一旦您了解了社区的需求以及您的组织可获得的机会，就可以在您的品牌的全力支持下采取果断且有目的的行动。对于您发起的每一项倡议和活动，请讲述一个故事，说明并加强您所倡导的社会事业、组织的宗旨和选民的需求之间的联系。我们的目标是让任何熟悉您品牌的人都会说：“当然，他们会支持这一事业。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您的支持 LGBTQ+ 的举措遭到批评者的攻击，无论是反对者，该怎么办？通过抵制、社交媒体活动，甚至当面恐吓？执行将包容性举措与组织的宗旨、价值主张、核心价值观和选民需求保持一致的步骤并不是为了防止批评，而是为了为此做好准备。以这种方式准备，为领导者提供了面对批评时坚强站起来并做出回应所需的一切：“我们在与全球客户和员工社区的对话中设计了这一举措，并相信它不仅庆祝骄傲月，而且体现了我们坚定的信念并进一步推进了我们的核心使命。我们很自豪能够产生这种影响，并邀请您详细了解为什么这一举措对我们很重要。虽然如果您觉得我们没有达到目标，我们会提出尊重的不同意见，但我们不会容忍针对我们的团队成员或其他客户的骚扰或暴力。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，组织仍然有可能犯错并撤回他们的倡议并道歉。但如果他们这样做了，那是因为他们在与自己的目的、价值主张和价值观保持一致、了解其选民和满足他们的需求的过程中犯了错误，而不是因为他们受到暴力威胁的压力。&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;使用此方法作为试金石。随着社会格局的变化，品牌、组织和领导者面临的期望也会发生变化。今天的“最佳实践”很可能在十年、五年甚至一年后变得无效，甚至适得其反。您的 DEI、ESG 和其他与社会问题相关的举措应该与时俱进，但您的承诺力度不应与时俱进。为了保持和加强员工、客户和其他成员对组织的信任，请使用这种目的和价值驱动的方法作为创建、重新审视和修改您的计划的试金石。在行动中，所需要做的就是回答以下问题：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;这个问题如何影响我们现有的目标以及我们服务的选民？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;对此的立场如何issue strengthen our purpose for existing, and benefit our constituents?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How do our constituents want us to act on this issue that centers our purpose and creates value for them?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p >;One consequence of answering these questions is that your organization &lt;em>;will not &lt;/em>;end up taking stances on every social issue, nor will it engage to the same degree on every cause or current event. It might even receive critique for its inaction in these cases. But when it does take a stance, it will be in strong alignment with its purpose, its value proposition, its values, and its employees, customers, and other constituents. When it acts, it will be with the full weight of its organizational identity and resources, without wavering even in the face of pushback.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This latest wave of anti-LGBTQ+ hostility is alarming, but if your organization holds steady to its purpose, operations, and the people it serves, you&#39;ll hold true to your commitment to LGBTQ+ inclusion every month out of the year.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Your Company Have an India Strategy?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/does-your-company-have-an-india-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1336468982.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/anand purohit/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;The price-to-book ratios of Indian subsidiaries of multinationals far exceeds those of their parent companies. That suggests the subsidiaries have better growth prospects, which makes sense given India&amp;#8217;s rapidly growing middle class. At this point, any multinational without an India strategy is missing out on a major opportunity for growth and profitability. But tailoring your strategy for India requires customizing your products and services and tapping into the &amp;#8220;India stack.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/does-your-company-have-an-india-strategy?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/does-your-company-have-an-india-strategy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;At the end of financial year 2022, the price-to-book (P/B) ratio for the European consumer products giant Unilever PLC stood at six. The same number for its subsidiary in India, Hindustan Unilever, was twice that, at twelve. This difference is not because the Indian subsidiary is a young or small company — on the contrary, the Indian subsidiary is a 90-year-old company with a market cap of $76 billion. Nor is this an isolated instance.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Nestle SA, the world&#39;s largest food and beverage company giant based out of Switzerland, has a P/B ratio of six, while its subsidiary in India has a whopping 82; 3M USA has a P/B of 4.2, its Indian subsidiary has a P/B of 12.7; the German parent of BASF, a global leader in speciality chemicals, has a P/B ratio of just one, its Indian subsidiary has four; the German parent of Siemens, a heavy industry leader, has a P/B ratio of two, its Indian subsidiary has ten. These differences are so vast that in some cases the Indian subsidiary may be valued more than the parent on a standalone basis. &lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Why is there such a chasm in P/Bs of parent companies and their Indian subsidiaries? Because Indian firms have better growth prospects, higher profitability, and more efficient asset utilization, all the while when the parent languishes in its home market. That&#39;s why every multinational must have an India strategy, or else it will miss out on one of the most promising market opportunities in the world today.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;P/B ratio represents how a company&#39;s assets are priced by the markets. It is higher for companies with better growth prospects (measured by revenue growth), more profitable operations (measured by profits to sales ratio), more efficient utilization of assets (measured by sales to assets ratio), and lower cost of capital. Lower cost of capital could not be the reason for higher P/B ratios for Indian subsidiaries. A company&#39;s cost of capital is limited by its country&#39;s sovereign rating. India&#39;s credit rating at BBB- is much inferior to the AAA rating of USA, Germany, and Switzerland. So, it is unlikely that all else held equal, an Indian subsidiary has a lower cost of capital than its parent located in a G7 country. Therefore, its higher P/B ratio must be related to better profitability and/or growth prospects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Over the last five years, the Compounded Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) in revenues for Unilever India was 9.6%, which is four times faster than that of 2.2% of Unilever parent. Note that parent&#39;s growth rate includes that of the Indian subsidiary, without which, its growth rate would be even lower. Turning to profitability, return on assets for the Indian subsidiary is 11% against 8% of the parent. What is surprising is that the higher profit margin for the Indian subsidiary, of 17%, against 13% of the parent. It is surprising because Unilever&#39;s products are priced cheaper in the India market, because of lower purchasing power of its target segment. Higher profits could be due to higher market concentration and pricing power, but that seems unlikely because of fierce competition from several sources including other multinationals such as Colgate, innovative local competitors like &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Patanjali Ayurved&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, and the availability of numerous cheaper alternatives addressing the same market, including from the informal sector. The higher margin is therefore most likely because the cost of production and distribution is lower in India, which is indeed the case. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The same story plays out for other multinationals. Nestle India earned a profit margin of 14.2% as against that of its parent of 9.8% and did so while generating sales-to-assets ratio of 196% as against just 69% for its parent. Siemens India had a profit margin of 10.6% against 4.8% for its parent, and a sales-to-assets ratio of 91% as against 51% for its parent.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;These numbers show that almost on all fronts &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;— &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;that is, market growth, asset utilization, and profitability &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;— &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;the Indian market offers more attractive prospects than the home market for the multinational. &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;The Growing Indian Market&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;India enjoys a fast-growing segment of urban middle class for consumer products. &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2019/01/india-urbanization-why-the-world-should-watch/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;The World Economic Forum&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; summarizes it well: “In terms of sheer numbers, the largest urban transformation of the 21st century is … happening in India.” The &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/middle-class-nearly-1/3rd-of-indias-population-to-be-2/3rds-by-2047-report/articleshow/95239621.cms&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;share of middle class&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; in India increased from 14% in 2005 to 31% in 2021, and is expected to further increase to 63% by 2047. Similar estimates come from &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://store.frost.com/indias-macroeconomic-opportunities-2030.html&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, which estimates that the share of people in India who are poor will continue to dwindle, and while the middle class grows, doubling its percentage from 28.5% in 2019 to 53.8% in 2030.  Middle class is defined as Indian households earning between $6,700 to $40,000, measured in 2020 US Dollars, which adjusted for purchasing power parity, equates to $22,700 to $136,000 in the US. Even a small change in the percentage change of middle class means a lot because of the India&#39;s large population base. At &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.un.org/en/desa/india-overtake-china-world-most-populous-country-april-2023-united-nations-projects#:~:text=24%20April%202023%20%2D%20China%20will,the%20population%20of%20mainland%20China.&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;1.43 billion&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, it is now the most populous country in the world and is about twice the size of US and EU populations put together. (The populations of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/popclock/&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;US&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; and &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://european-union.europa.eu/principles-countries-history/key-facts-and-figures/life-eu_en&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;EU&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; are 334 million and 447 million, respectively.) Roughly 25 percentage point change, from 28.5% to 53.8%, even at the current population base, means 350 million people, which is more than the EU&#39;s population.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;The increase in urban middle class in India is a combination of three factors: rapid urbanization of smaller towns, the movement of people from rural to urban areas in search of better employment opportunities, and a progression of people from subsistence income levels to those with substantial disposable income and aspirational lifestyle. &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/middle-class-nearly-1/3rd-of-indias-population-to-be-2/3rds-by-2047-report/articleshow/95239621.cms&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Small cities&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; with population between 1.0 and 2.5 million are growing at astronomical rates, touching 10% per year.&amp;nbsp; Sixteen towns have been labelled as boomtowns given their rapid increase of the young population. Within those cities, the share of middle class is expanding, turbo charging the growth rates of the urban middle class. Super metros such as Mumbai, Delhi, and Bangalore, with populations exceeding 10 million each, are contributing to growth in another way. They are showing almost 10% annual increase in the population of super rich, those who can afford fancy cars, luxury homes, and vacations in international hotspots. No multinational can afford to overlook this urban growth.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;It would be good to compare India&#39;s numbers with other countries. A report by &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/global_20170228_global-middle-class.pdf&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Brookings&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; projected that 1.06 billion people around the world entered middle class from 2015 to 2022. India&#39;s contribution was estimated at 380 million, or about one third of the total, surpassing even China&#39;s contribution of 350 million people. No other country reaches even half of these numbers. Interesting, in 2030, the total consumption of US middle class is expected to be $4.7 trillion in purchasing power parity terms (in 2011 dollars), about the same as in 2015. The most astounding and consequential global growth in consumption of middle class will come from India, from $2.1 trillion in 2015 (less than half of US) to $10.7 trillion in 2030 (more than twice that of US), both in 2011 dollars. China is expected to become the world&#39;s largest middle class, with a consumption of $14.3 trillion. Another growth center will be Indonesia, which is expected to become the fourth largest middle-class consumption center after China, India, and US. But at $2.4 trillion, it would be about one-fourth the size of India&#39;s.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;These data are also consistent with data on national aggregate growth rates. &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/gs-research/the-path-to-2075-slower-global-growth-but-convergence-remains-intact/report.pdf&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Goldman Sachs&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; calculated India&#39;s real GDP growth rate during 2010-2019 at 6.9%, second fastest among all major economies in the world, and more than three times as fast as that of developed countries. During the decade of 2020-2029, India&#39;s growth rate is expected to be the highest in the world, followed by China, Philippines, Turkey, and Egypt. No developed country would come even half as close as India in terms of growth rate. By 2050, India&#39;s real GDP will cross the consolidated GDP of the EU in raw numbers. Adjusted for &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oecd-ilibrary.org/finance-and-investment/purchasing-power-parities-ppp/indicator/english_1290ee5a-en&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;purchasing power parity&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, India&#39;s GDP would easily be three times that of EU. By 2075, China, India, and USA are expected to be the largest economies in the world, in that order. No other countries would be close to that number, though Indonesia, Nigeria, Pakistan, and Egypt could join the top 10, with each of them being less than a third of each of the top three.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Lessons for Multinationals&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In light of the data on India&#39;s overall growth and growing middle class, it&#39;s not a surprise that multinationals&#39; subsidiaries are highly valued for their own growth opportunities. Every multinational now needs an India strategy to benefit from its fast-growing urban middle class. They will succeed provided they follow three recommendations:&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;o&quot; data-font=&quot;Courier New&quot; data-listid=&quot;1&quot; data-list-defn-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;335552541&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559682&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559684&amp;quot;:-2,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:1440,&amp;quot;335559991&amp;quot;:360,&amp;quot;469769226&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469769242&amp;quot;:[9675],&amp;quot;469777803&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;left&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777804&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;o&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777815&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;hybridMultilevel&amp;quot;}&quot; aria-setsize=&quot;-1&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;1&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Make significant resource commitments to India. This requires localizing product design, manufacturing, and marketing capabilities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;o&quot; data-font=&quot;Courier New&quot; data-listid=&quot;1&quot; data-list-defn-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;335552541&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559682&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559684&amp;quot;:-2,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:1440,&amp;quot;335559991&amp;quot;:360,&amp;quot;469769226&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469769242&amp;quot;:[9675],&amp;quot;469777803&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;left&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777804&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;o&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777815&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;hybridMultilevel&amp;quot;}&quot; aria-setsize=&quot;-1&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;2&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;Customize products and services&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; by understanding the culture, values, norms, usage habits, extreme heat and paucity of air conditioning, plethora of languages, and multiplicity of local laws. Notably, despite being a single country, India means a multitude of cultures and languages. There are more than &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Languages_of_India&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;780 languages written in 66 different scripts&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;, of which 22 languages are considered “official,” each with its own script.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:1434,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259,&amp;quot;335559991&amp;quot;:357}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;o&quot; data-font=&quot;Courier New&quot; data-listid=&quot;1&quot; data-list-defn-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;335552541&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559682&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559684&amp;quot;:-2,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:1440,&amp;quot;335559991&amp;quot;:360,&amp;quot;469769226&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Courier New&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469769242&amp;quot;:[9675],&amp;quot;469777803&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;left&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777804&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;o&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;469777815&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;hybridMultilevel&amp;quot;}&quot; aria-setsize=&quot;-1&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;1&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;Leverage the “&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India_Stack&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;India Stack&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;,”&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; the world&#39;s largest &lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;unified software and digital infrastructure platform, that aims to bring India&#39;s population into the digital age of presence-less, paperless, and cashless service delivery&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;. Its scale can be judged from the fact that from 2010, when almost no person had a unique identity like social security number in the US, now, over 1.2 billion people in India have unique digital identities, linked to their bank accounts, through biometrics. A custom-developed unified payment interface now widely used in India, implies that almost everyone now uses a smart phone, to pay from, and receive money to, a digitally connected bank account. &amp;nbsp;This &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/companies/indias-e-commerce-market-projected-to-touch-150-b-in-2026-report/article66653508.ece&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;growing e-commerce&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; infrastructure and capabilities are&amp;nbsp;facilitated by almost every &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2016/12/doing-business-in-india-requires-a-mobile-first-strategy&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;middle-class person&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; carrying a smart phone, connected on internet with world&#39;s cheapest bandwidth. The logistics, payment, and distribution systems created using &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/05/the-ups-and-downs-of-indias-digital-transformation&quot;>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;none&quot;>;digital technology&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>; in India, is now miles ahead of that in the West, and is now the envy of the world.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:1434,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259,&amp;quot;335559991&amp;quot;:357}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;>;In summary, the high P/B ratios of multinationals&#39; subsidiaries in India demonstrate the value of what will soon be the world&#39;s largest consumer market. Every B2C company must take notice and must have an India strategy. The strategy must entail a suitable plan to enter the market, while doing so with high profitability and efficient utilization of capital. Importantly, it means going back to the drawing board, creating products made for Indian markets, producing them in India, using India-sourced raw materials, and distributing them using local channels and digitally enabled infrastructure. A wholesale copying of what worked in a developed country and applying it to India is unlikely to work.&lt;/span>;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559731&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:259}&quot;>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Marketing When Budgets Are Down]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_27_523536254.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;大卫·扎伊茨/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;企业财务的一般规则是，营销预算一有麻烦就会像石头一样下降，而一旦环境恶化，营销预算就会像羽毛一样上升解决了。到 2023 年中期，我们距离稳定状态还很远——西方市场预计的 GDP 增长令人沮丧地持平，事实证明通货膨胀相当顽固，而且这些干扰仍在不断发生。短期内很难看到营销预算大幅增加。 Gartner 对数百名 CMO 进行的年度调查绘制了近期营销支出的演变情况，为企业领导者如何在更短的时间内交付成果并建立推动增长的能力提供了指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span >; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/marketing-when-budgets-are-down?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;营销的数字化转型带来了前所未有的增长，无论是功能范围还是消费能力。新渠道、新技术、新能力需要新水平的投资。但美好时光不可能永远持续下去，随着预算的减少，大流行迎来了一个新的、更加严峻的时代。这使得&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing&quot;>;首席营销官 (CMO)&lt;/a>; 面临着减少其投资组合中以前神圣不可侵犯的部分（例如营销技术）的支出的压力。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/495785/1158365?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBCMOSPENDSURVEY&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;Gartner 年度调查&lt;/数百名 CMO 绘制了近期营销支出的演变图，为企业领导者如何在更短的时间内交付成果并建立推动增长的能力提供指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;无人知晓因在更多数字化和技术上花费而被解雇&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您什么时候第一次成为数字化的？ 20 年前，我得到的第一份工作的标题中就包含“数字”一词，我想这让我成为了一名数字营销老手。当时，我构建业务案例的时间几乎与激活活动的时间一样长。这很容易被忘记，但在 2000 年代中期从线下转向数字化绝非易事。数字营销领导者总是渴望更多 - 更多的预算、更多的技术、更多的数据、更多的人员、领导团队的更多关注。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实上，这就是这个时期的开始更多。数字化对营销造成了沉重打击，而与消费者和客户互动、联系和交易的可能性创造了巨大的机会。它还创建了&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/leadership-vision-chief-marketing-officer?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_CMOVISION2022&amp;amp ;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;首席营销官面临的挑战&lt;/a>;，他们努力平衡勇敢的数字营销领导者与非数字领导者的预算需求。前者提出了一个令人信服的论点：我们不断赞扬数字化的优点，认为它是具有成本效益、可衡量和可优化的选择。相比之下，任何线下的东西都显得古板、过时，而且是模拟的。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;没有人因为在数字和技术上花费（甚至更多）而被解雇&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;更多的时期持续了相当长的一段时间。毕竟，数字化是一头饥饿的野兽，拥有看似无穷无尽的诱人工具、技术、人才和渠道。早在 2016 年初，我就成为了一名营销分析师，当时营销技术和数字渠道占据了营销总预算的很大一部分。届时，我们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/495785/1158365?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBCMOSPENDSURVEY&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;年度 CMO 支出和策略调查&lt;据报道，企业平均营销预算高达公司收入的 12.1%。 2016 年，超过四分之一的营销总预算分配给了技术，而且支出排名前三位的渠道都是数字渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然 2016 年的营销总预算可能达到了一个高水位线。 ，这当然不是异常值 - 事实上，技术支出占营销预算总额的比例在 2018 年达到峰值，几乎占营销预算的三分之一 (29.2%)。2016 年至 2020 年间，营销预算平均占公司收入的 11.2%，令人印象深刻.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;更少，但更多&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当我们在 2020 年初、大流行封锁之前对 CMO 进行调查时，CMO 无法预料到疫情的全面规模Covid-19 的影响：营销预算被削减，客户旅程被打乱。但这场大流行也为数字和技术带来了另一个推动力。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/digital-iq-index-genius-brands?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_GENIUSBRANDSEBOOK&amp;amp;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;品牌&lt;/a >; 以前落后于同行的企业现在别无选择，只能转向数字渠道来与锁定的受众进行互动和交易。已经在数字化方面投入巨资的品牌别无选择，只能进一步加快投资。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，即使投入较少，也会有更多。更多电子商务、&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/multichannel-marketing-survey?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_MULTICHANNELMKTG&amp;amp;utm_term=ebook&quot;>;更多数字渠道&lt;/a>;，以及更多技术。当我们在 2020 年对 CMO 进行调查时，他们表示，与付费媒体或代理机构等资源组合中的其他要素相比，他们更有可能保护对技术的投资，因为他们相信技术将是帮助他们在未来发展的重要工具。大流行——当我们进入“新常态”时。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;疫情后的漫长回升&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;就像一根棍子上挂着的胡萝卜令人沮丧的是，过去几年“新常态”一直遥不可及。世界卫生组织可能已经宣布 Covid-19 全球卫生紧急状态结束，但我们距离正常状态还很远。从最近大型银行的倒闭到各种社交媒体平台的波动，这些问题都困扰着整个最高管理层，无论他们受到影响的程度如何。这一系列看似永无止境的破坏导致了企业增长的许多锚点：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;更高的利率&lt;/strong>;影响新投资的投资回报率潜力。在当前&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/recession-playbook-marketing-leaders?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_GMLRECESSIONPLAYBOOK&amp;amp;utm_term= ebook&quot;>;宏观经济环境&lt;/a>;，投资者优先考虑当前的利润和现金流，而不是等待未来的增长。较高的利率也削弱了经济需求，抑制了增长。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人才市场依然困难&lt;/strong>;，员工流动率较高，对战略性重要职位的竞争加剧，员工信任度降低管理方面的问题，以及混合和远程工作方面的紧张局势。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;数字化转型滞后&lt;/strong>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/ press-releases/2022-10-19-gartner-says-89-percent-of-board-directors-say-digital-is-embedded-in-all-business-growth-strategies&quot;>;2023 年 Gartner 董事会调查&lt; /a>; 报告称，81% 的董事会尚未在实现数字业务转型目标方面取得进展或实现。此外，2022 年 Gartner 的一项调查发现，67% 的 CFO 认为过去三年的数字化支出没有达到企业预期。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;虽然可以方便地在前后构建近期企业历史记录——疫情方面，另一个拐点也可能已经出现。企业已经从集中投资支持数字化增长的工具和能力的时期转向这些投资需要开始回报的时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当技术投资和数字营销不再酷炫和与众不同时，它们是&lt;em>;主流&lt;/em>;。用 Gartner 的话来说，此类投资已经从&lt;em>;创新系统&lt;/em>;（变革性、颠覆性且很大程度上未经证实）转变为&lt;em>;记录系统&lt;/em>;（其中占主导地位的战略力量） &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/455982/1074604?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGOPERATIONS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;运营效率&lt;/a>; ，并且企业期望可预测性、可靠性和稳定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;我们（不需要）需要更大的船&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这让我们到了 2023 年Gartner 5 月底发布的年度 CMO 支出和战略调查数据表明，“更多”时代已经结束。首先（也是最明显的），它表明我们调查的 400 多家北美和欧洲 CMO 的营销预算尚未恢复到新冠疫情前的峰值。事实上，2022 年调查报告的收益有所下滑，平均预算从 2022 年公司收入的 9.5% 降至 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2023-05 -22-gartner-survey-reveals-71%的cmos相信他们缺乏足够的预算来在2023年全面执行他们的战略&quot;>;2023年将达到9.1%&lt;/a>; .&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许比高层预算趋势更令人担忧的是营销支出能力明显受到挤压。 （人才和数字媒体）成本的增加和（营销技术利用率）收益的下降造成了一场营销生活成本危机，类似于过去 18 个月许多市场的消费者所经历的危机。简而言之，每营销一美元购买的东西就会减少。因此，实际上，我们已经从“多”时代转向了“少”时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“少”时代对财务和心理的影响可以从对此的反应中清晰地听到。年的调查。超过 70% 的受访者表示，他们的企业缺乏足够的预算或资源来成功实施 2023 年的营销策略。75% 的受访者表示，他们的企业要求他们用更少的资源做更多的事情，86% 的受访者表示，他们“他们面临着对营销方式进行重大改变以实现可持续成果的压力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今年调查中最令人惊讶的发现可能与企业对技术投资越来越不耐烦有关。四分之三的受访者表示，他们面临着企业削减 Martech 投资的压力——这在几年前是不可想象的。更重要的是：数字媒体看似势不可挡的崛起已经陷入停滞。当我们看看分配给数字渠道和线下渠道的媒体支出比例时，会发现到 2023 年，这一比例下降了 1 个百分点，达到 55%。到 2023 年，完全有可能因为在数字和技术上投入更多而被解雇。错误引用 1975 年经典电影《大白鲨》：我们不需要更大的船；我们需要的是更大的船。我们需要一个更高效的电影。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;适应更少的时代&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;关于 70 年代经典电影的主题，弗朗西斯·福特·科波拉 (Francis Ford Copolla)在谈到他 1979 年的代表作《现代启示录》时，他曾说过一句名言：“我们人太多了，我们拥有太多的钱、太多的设备，但渐渐地我们都发疯了。”这并不是说首席营销官经历了科波拉所说的那种过剩，但他确实提到了更多的主要挑战之一：有时更多实际上带来的效果更少。或者，反过来说，有时你可以用更少的钱获得更多的东西。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，用更少的钱提供更多的东西是那些可怕的陈词滥调之一 - 说起来容易，但实现起来却非常困难。这具有挑战性，因为“更多”是大多数企业领导者的首选状态。多年来，在我与首席营销官和营销领导者进行的数千次对话中，相当一部分内容涉及“如何构建业务案例来增加营销预算？”这一主题的变化。另一个合理的块？ “我如何定义我可以削减的东西和我不能失去的东西？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些基本问题的答案无法在闪亮的新技术中找到；相反，这是吃蔬菜的战略版本。作为领导者，您需要有一个坚定的计划来定义营销范围，并清楚地了解该职能的范围如何逐步实现企业目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，您的计划必须立足于近期和未来的目标。长期行动将提供使今天保持活力的销售线索和销售，以及有助于明天实现差异化和增长的投资。这需要一个细致入微的故事来阐述&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/ Three-techniques-to-prove-the-value-of-marketing?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp; utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_PROVEMKTGVALUE2023&quot;>;营销的价值&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/ Three-techniques-to-prove-the-value-of-marketing?utm_source= press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_PROVEMKTGVALUE2023&quot;>;向企业提出的建议&lt;/a>; — 营销如何实现&lt;em>;目标回报&lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;投资回报&lt;/em>;。它需要接受这样一个事实：构建这个价值故事的工作不是计量经济学模型或归因分析；而是关于构建价值故事的工作。这些是达到目的的手段，而不是目的本身。这是关于与利益相关者就营销如何创造价值达成相互理解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这也是关于拥抱和探索大量的不确定性，并使用情景规划和敏感性分析的核心战略工具来了解当前存在的问题。是成功的关键，使您的团队能够制定适当响应的战略选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过回归健全战略管理的首要原则，营销人员将制定一个计划，摆脱无关的东西，从而实现&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487268/1142263?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGSYMTAKEAWAYS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;关注右侧&lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot; https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487268/1142263?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGSYMTAKEAWAYS&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;&lt;em>;更少&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;最有可能支持目标的实现。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了以稍微不同的方式来阐述这一点，在 Gartner，我们讨论 CMO 如何将自己从 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/ newsroom/press-releases/2023-05-22-gartner-says-catalytic-marketing-allows-cmos-to-drive-profit-growth-amid-macroeconomic-stress&quot;>;暴政更多&lt;/a>;通过关注三个主要领导特质：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;清晰。&lt;/strong>; 精挑细选很重要。 CMO 必须就战略生命周期内将支持和不支持哪些内容做出清晰的决定。应该对那些未通过的举措给予同等的思考和考虑，并明确原因。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;勇气。领导者必须有勇气向团队提出难题。它识别虚假假设、战略感伤和有害的文化规范。例如，首席营销官必须消除“仅仅因为我们在一个项目上花费了 10 万美元，并不意味着我们应该多花 10 万美元”的沉没成本偏见。同样，首席营销官必须与历史性的价值假设作斗争：仅仅因为一项投资在三年前有意义，并不意味着业务案例会逐年滚动。所有重大投资都应该能够根据对未来目标（而不是过去目标）的可衡量贡献来证明自己的合理性。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;联系。&lt;/strong>;成功几乎总是如此一种协作努力。成功合作的开始是沟通和理解。 CMO 必须与 CFO、CSO、CIO 等合作，对营销计划如何实现业务目标有明确的定义和共同的理解。同样，他们必须了解营销与价值创造过程中其他职能的交叉点。抛弃市场营销所喜爱的晦涩指标和三个字母的缩写。将品牌话语转化为商业话语，以揭开营销的神秘面纱并增加联系。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;等等，但是人工智能呢？&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您可能会问“人工智能肯定会改变一切吗？”也许&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/how-should-cmos-respond-to-chatgpt-today?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_YOY_GML_NPP_PR1_RECHATGPT&quot;>;变革力量人工智能&lt;/a>;将迎来数字投资的新时代。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但由于几个原因，现实很复杂。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;首先，人工智能对于营销 - 它已经存在，隐藏在您的技术堆栈（以及您的合作伙伴和代理机构的技术堆栈）中多年。其次，虽然&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/webinar/487667/1143179?utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_WBMKTGGENERATIVEAI&amp;amp;utm_term=wb&quot;>;生成式人工智能&lt;/a>;的承诺激发兴趣和热情，这一切都发生在技术利用率大幅下降的时期。 Gartner 的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/marketing-technology-survey-2022?utm_source=press-release&amp;amp;utm_medium=press-release&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GML_GB_2023_GML_NPP_PR1_MARTECHSURVEY22&amp;amp;utm_term=gi&quot; >;2022年营销技术调查&lt;/a>;报告称，martech的使用率仅为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2022-10-03-gartner-survey -发现营销人员只利用了他们的营销技术堆栈功能的 42%&quot;>;42%&lt;/a>;。因此，您在营销技术上花费的每一美元，您所利用的还不到投资的一半。鉴于营销技术一直占总营销预算的四分之一以上，这种收益水平不仅仅是技术风险，而是财务风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种水平的财务风险并不能阻止 CMO通过寻找新技术解决方案。但这应该让他们在一头扎进新的承诺之前认真思考。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;还会有更多&lt;em>;更多&lt;/em>;吗？ &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;企业财务的一般规则是，一旦出现麻烦，营销预算就会像石头一样下降，而一旦环境稳定下来，营销预算就会像羽毛一样上升。到 2023 年中期，我们还远未达到稳定的状态——西方市场的 GDP 增长预计将持平，令人沮丧，通货膨胀被证明相当顽固，而这些干扰只会不断出现。短期内很难看到营销预算大幅增加。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，情况有些复杂。平均值掩盖了差异，而且不同行业和地区的预算差异很大。如果您是营销消费品的 CMO，那么您 2023 年的预算很可能比金融服务领域的同行健康得多。如果您在德国，您的预算很可能不如您在英国的同事。然而，在我们 2023 年调查的所有行业和市场中，预算都落后于大流行前的水平。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2024 年会怎样？预测未来一直是一件愚蠢的事。也许我们将再次看到另一个更多的时代，新技术、体验和渠道为营销开辟了新的机会。也许我们会从更少的时代学到宝贵的经验教训，即使资金增加，营销也会变得精益和高效。 Perhaps.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Managing Anxiety When There&rsquo;s No Room for Error]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jul23_27_57363406.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;fStop 图片 - Brian Cassie/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close &quot;>; &lt;span>;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当您的工作岗位必须不惜一切代价避免错误时 &amp;#8212;想想医疗、安全、金融和运输行业——人们很容易害怕制作一个。但有一些方法可以建设性地降低潜在错误的风险并减少您的焦虑。首先，区分严重和不太严重的潜在错误，并重点关注前者。然后采用系统和习惯来减轻这些威胁。获得他人的支持来解决您的弱点，同时找到发挥您优势的解决方案。与关注相同问题的其他人合作。解决任何自我破坏行为，例如不寻求帮助。通过消除大部分小错误的小行动，减少因小错误担忧而造成的干扰。最后，考虑一种你可以犯一些无后果错误的爱好。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/managing-anxiety-when-theres-no-room-for-error?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-anxiety-when-theres -no-room-for-error?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在某些领域，错误是正常的，而且代价也不是很高。如果设计师在制作精美的封面图片之前多次重新开始，发明家在找到可行的原型之前尝试了一百个原型，或者企业家从一个想法转向另一个想法，那么这并不重要。关于客户的反馈。在这些角色中，失败是成功之路的一部分。在其他情况下，风险可能会受到一个人较低级别的责任的限制。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是那些期望完美的角色呢？没有人希望他们的神经外科医生犯错误，或者他们的刑事辩护律师休息一天。会计师不能向美国国税局、美国证券交易委员会或任何其他监管机构提交有缺陷的财务报表。一些安全角色专注于监视潜在威胁，成功意味着永远不会错过任何威胁。你的工作可能属于这一类。或者，也许工作中出错的后果并不那么严重，但你觉得这是因为老板刻薄、裁员迫在眉睫或根深蒂固的焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你如何应对这种感觉你根本就不能搞砸吗？我的建议是使用策略来减少犯严重错误的机会，同时减少对此的担忧。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;焦虑的基础知识&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;让我们从焦虑如何产生的一些基本背景开始。首先，过度思考并不能解决问题。它让我们陷入瘫痪，而不是让我们动员起来。其次，人们常常沉迷于一种特定类型的错误或威胁，而忽视其他类型的错误或威胁，因为恐惧会缩小我们的注意力。最后， &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/gretchenrubin_one-of-my-aphorisms-is-action-is-an-antidote-activity-6651614263683137537-w-8Y?trk=posts_directory&quot;>;行动是焦虑的解药&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;错误代价高昂或危险的工作（例如医学、会计、工程或安全）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse. com/books/316156/the-anxiety-toolkit-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;有时会吸引天生认真负责、勤奋且善于把事​​情做好的人。但对于已经具有这种性格类型的人来说，时刻保持谨慎可能会很困难。这有点像父母“小心”的告诫会让本来就谨慎或焦虑的孩子变得更加紧张。如果您的培训或机构专注于消除错误，这可能会加剧您的完美主义和焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是您可以采取的措施来减轻紧张感。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;区分大和小小错误&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;如果你考虑一下你可能犯的每一个错误，它会让你分心，忽略那些你最应该害怕的错误。如果你经常采取行动来减少犯最严重错误的风险，你的精神负担就会减轻。要确定要优先考虑哪些风险，请考虑那些容易想到的风险以及经常被忽视的风险，例如机会成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;还有其他一些人们看不到的、有些相关的主要风险类别。一是前国务卿唐纳德·拉姆斯菲尔德所说的“未知的未知”：来自意想不到的情况的风险，以至于不会被考虑。另一个是“你不知道你不知道什么”，指的是你没有意识到的盲点，或者&lt;a href=&quot;/2012/05/discover-what-you-need-to-know ”当您认为自己完全理解某件事，但实际上没有理解时&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建立适当的机制来减轻这些风险。例如，每月安排一次与同事的会议，讨论您如何处理困难案例，以此发现您遗漏的任何潜在风险。在你的日历上安排一个定期会议，并期望你将讨论复杂的决策，将确保这一切得以完成。考虑一些例子，并询问您在自己的角色中可能会遇到哪些类似情况：也许您不知道学生可能会以与您预期不同的方式解释指令，从而导致您的实验室出现危险情况。您不知道手术室中的巡回护士会使用他们熟悉的程序，而不是您经常使用的程序，从而导致混乱或错过重要步骤。您不知道软件提供商会在重要截止日期的前一天推出有缺陷的更新并破坏您所依赖的系统。您现在可以做什么来确保不犯这些错误？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;谨慎的人可以重新训练自己寻找并规避最严重的风险。但这需要一种超越他人通常做法的心理能力，并能够容忍不确定性。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;采用降低风险的系统和习惯&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;而不是思考通过意志力减少错误，永远不会有糟糕的一天，创建不依赖于那种不切实际的机器人完美的系统。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有证据表明，诸如 &lt;a href=&quot;/podcast/2010 /01/using-checklists-to-prevent-fa.html&quot;>;例如，清单可以减少错误&lt;/a>;，但&lt;a href=&quot;/2010/02/draftwhat-sort-of-checklist-sh&quot; >;在特定领域未得到充分利用&lt;/a>;。如果您正在寻找灵感，请考虑如何调整在其他行业或角色中采取的行动。例如，心脏监护仪和呼吸机等医疗设备通常包含冗余传感器和警报器，以检测故障并提供及时警报。您的角色如何才能更早地收到或自动重复警告信号？航空等行业对未遂事件有严格的报告要求。如果一篇文章因重大事实错误而即将付印，或者一个项目在工作人员通宵达旦后才勉强按时完成，您是否应该这样做？什么是最有用的并且真正专注于学习而不是指责？ &lt;a href=&quot;https://toddkashdan.com/the-art-of-insubordination/&quot;>;自学科学&lt;/a>;如何建立多元化的团队，分享相反的观点，勇敢地表达担忧，并进行健康的辩论。创建一种奖励人们征求和积极强化不寻常观点的文化。当有人指出您不知道的事情时，请特别注意鼓励他们将来继续这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;获得支持来解决您的弱点&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当我还是一名治疗师时，我的弱点始终是记录保存。我讨厌记录。我的大脑运转得很快，感觉录音一直在拖慢我的速度。我更喜欢将所有精力投入到与客户面对面的互动中。如果我再次担任这个角色，我将不再尝试自己在该领域进行改进，并接受我需要一个支持人员来让我保持记录的正轨。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，如果您&#39;如果你是唯一知道如何扮演关键角色的人，而你又不擅长将你的流程系统化，那么你可能会得到帮助来做到这一点。如果你不是最好的沟通者，但正在向客户或老板做一个必须获胜的推销，你可以请导师、朋友，甚至是具有更多这些技能的人工智能聊天机器人来帮助你更有说服力吗？同样，如果冲突管理不是强项，但团队内斗可能会导致关键项目脱轨，也许您可​​以聘请一位顾问，您可以根据需要提供建议，甚至可能实施建议。或者，如果您凌乱的办公室确实存在丢失文件的风险，那么请专业的组织者进来，每隔几个月就给您一个新的开始。请记住，帮助您避免错误的不仅仅是您自己的意志力和勤奋。您可以招募一群同事 - 甚至朋友、家人和技术 - 来帮助您。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;发挥您的优势&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;I &lt;a href =&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/645534/stress-free-productivity-by-alice-boyes-phd/&quot;>;经常争论&lt;/a>;利用你的优势来减轻你的劣势，这可以延伸到如何避免错误。例如，如果你在视觉上有创造力，你可以创建视觉提醒，或者如果幽默是一种优势，那么幽默的。只需谷歌“有趣的航空公司安全视频”即可找到如何让人们注意严肃的安全建议的示例。如果你善于交际并且善于与人相处，你会如何利用这种天赋来获取其他人通常保守秘密的信息，比如告诉你为什么你可能不想与某个特定的个人或团体合作？相比之下，如果你比较内向，你如何利用你的自然倾向去倾听和观察而不是说话，以注意到迫在眉睫的问题，或者让人们更有可能足够信任你，揭露你的担忧或错误，而不用担心你会告诉你其他的？考虑一下您的最大优势如何帮助您解决特定问题。 One question you can ask yourself to identify your uncommon strengths is: What are you willing to do that 95% of other people aren&#39;t?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Address self-sabotaging behaviors&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When we&#39;re very anxious about something, we often self-sabotage in ways that increase the chances of the feared thing happening. For example, you know you&#39;ve got a weakness, but you don&#39;t seek mentors or supervisors who could help you address it because you don&#39;t want to draw attention to it. Or you don&#39;t ask for an accommodation for your depression due to embarrassment and stigma or a belief you should tough it out, but that increases the chances of making a mistake on a bad day. Or you hate wasting money, so you don&#39;t try an option that might solve the problem but isn&#39;t guaranteed. Or you&#39;re a perfectionist so you don&#39;t seek to solve a problem where improvements are possible but perfect seems impossible. Get creative about overcoming your self-sabotage, and &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/be-kinder-to-yourself&quot;>;talk to yourself compassionately about it&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Collaborate with others focused on the same issues&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When you think about mistakes, you may mostly do so on a personal or team level. “How can I prevent myself or a colleague from getting this important thing wrong?” But to seek out better solutions — and the camaraderie of a group that shares your fears — consider getting involved in larger efforts to reduce mistakes in your field, like sitting on a committee for complaints and disciplinary actions or one establishing new guidelines for people in your role. Teaching also usually improves our own practice, so consider finding opportunities to teach others about how your work is done in a way that minimizes or eliminates mistakes. Write a talk on this for an industry conference or host a panel.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Reduce small-threat distraction by taking simple actions to mitigate those risks&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Though most of your focus should be on the biggest threats, some simple strategies can lessen the risk of small mistakes so they won&#39;t distract you from that focus. You&#39;ll want to take simple actions that help reduce the frequency of minor problems, and then accept that you can&#39;t eliminate all of them. Pick the low-hanging fruit. For example, if a doctor is worried about forgetting names of patients and family members, they might write the names down on the top of each page as they&#39;re taking notes during interactions. Address minor potential mistakes to the extent that they free up your mental capacity to think about and prevent larger ones.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Consider a hobby that allows you to make mistakes&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;To add some balance to your life, you might want to take up an activity in which mistakes and false starts aren&#39;t at all costly. For example, I&#39;ve recently taken up vegetable gardening, and it&#39;s refreshing to partake in an interest in which a low rate of success is perfectly acceptable. After all, a packet of a hundred seeds costs only a few dollars. A friend of a friend is an avid surfer, content to miss or bail out on dozens of waves to eventually get few good rides, which is a great antidote to his day job as a startup CFO trying to make sure the company doesn&#39;t run out of money.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When perfection is expected and mistakes are costly, it&#39;s easy to become terrified of making one. You might lose sleep over it or avoid leadership and increased responsibility. But there are ways to constructively reduce the risk of potential mistakes and reduce your anxiety.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Manage Your Team&rsquo;s Workload After Layoffs]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_98413121-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Susanne Walstrom/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;All too often in the case of layoffs, the people who survive it are expected to pick up the work that their terminated colleagues left behind. Meanwhile, these layoff survivors are often struggling with survivor guilt, anxiety, and low morale. In short, after a layoff, more is being asked of people who have less to give. This is a recipe for disaster when it comes to burnout and retention of key talent. In this piece, the authors outline four strategies for right sizing the workload on your &lt;span data-markjs=&quot;true&quot;>;team.&amp;#160;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-to-manage-your-teams-workload-after-layoffs?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Facing economic uncertainty and slowing revenue growth, companies continue to announce layoffs affecting thousands of workers. These downsizings, which have shifted beyond the tech industry to multiple&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-companies-conducting-layoffs-in-2023-heres-the-list-11673288386&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;other sectors&lt;/a>;, are undeniably tragic for layoff victims. But they&#39;re also terrible for the workers left behind. Layoff survivors often struggle with psychological impacts from the downsizing, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bizreport.com/layoff-aftermath-survey-2022/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;guilt, anxiety, and depression&lt;/a>;. In a state of diminished&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/12/what-companies-still-get-wrong-about-layoffs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;trust and morale&lt;/a>;, they also remain on edge as they fearfully await another round of cuts. And all too often, layoff survivors are expected to pick up the work their terminated colleagues left behind.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In short, companies often ask even more of their people at a time when they have less to give. This dynamic is a recipe for disaster when it comes to burnout, retention of key talent, and the long-term success of your team. For the health and performance of your team, it&#39;s essential to evaluate your team&#39;s capacity after a layoff and to take significant steps to right-size your team&#39;s workload. Here&#39;s how:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Identify projects and initiatives to postpone&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In a state of overload, it&#39;s a natural stress response to put your nose to the grindstone to make a dent in the volume of work. However, it is critical to step back and identify where your team should invest its precious time and energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Start by creating a comprehensive list with your team of all ongoing initiatives and projects and discussing what each one solves, creates, or improves.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Next, rank these initiatives based on their expected impact and each project&#39;s potential benefits to the organization.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Finally, identify which initiatives can be postponed but easily resumed later versus those where temporarily pausing might be consequential and difficult to reverse.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Due to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/07/how-susceptible-are-you-to-the-sunk-cost-fallacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;sunk cost fallacy&lt;/a>;, we are reluctant to abandon a strategy or course of action that we have already invested in. However, many projects can be put on hold and resumed easily at a moment&#39;s notice. Acknowledging this distinction will allow you and your team to override this fallacy and make decisions more swiftly so you can focus on the most critical work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As you choose projects to postpone, however, ensure you retain one or more future-focused projects. These projects often serve as a source of inspiration and motivation for the team, infusing energy into their work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Align with your boss to manage your “shelf space”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Supermarkets and retail stores are naturally constrained by their shelf space, unable to add a new product unless they remove an existing one. Leaders should apply a similar principle in managing their team&#39;s workload, but rarely do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The next time your boss requests something from your team, ask whether the new request requires immediate attention. If it does, ask your manager to help you prioritize the request among your team&#39;s other assignments. For example, you might say, “The team is also working on these three other initiatives. Are there any that can be dropped or postponed to make room for this one?” Giving your boss a choice gives them a &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33400628/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;sense of control&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;and is more effective than flatly pushing back.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Also, get in the habit of proactively sharing the estimated resource requirements for any requests. Most leaders are unaware of the effort and expense teams expend to fulfill their demands. When you proactively communicate resource requirements with your boss, they become more discerning in their inquiries, significantly reducing your team&#39;s workload.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Uncover your team&#39;s full set of talents&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Teams are often unaware of the complete set of skills, knowledge, and abilities within their ranks. This talent goes untapped to the detriment of team productivity and performance precisely when you need it most.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address this issue and unlock your team&#39;s potential, schedule a meeting to uncover all the talent resident on your team. Give team members 10 minutes to reflect and write down their talents and skills. Next, ask each team member to share their list with the team. As they do so, encourage the team to add additional talents or skills they recognize in their colleague that they didn&#39;t mention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This simple exercise is a profound eye-opener, revealing hidden talents and helping teams identify their go-to colleagues when they need help. It also serves as an energizing experience for all participants, as colleagues rarely discuss and acknowledge each other&#39;s talents and skills in a direct and focused manner. In our experience facilitating this exercise with over 30 teams and hundreds of participants, every participant has had the uplifting experience of having talents that they were unaware of or took for granted added by their colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This simple exercise can deliver a significant boost in both engagement and productivity on teams.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Simplify, simplify, simplify&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the face of overwhelming workloads, teams often overlook opportunities for simplification.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://webinar.gartner.com/463005/agenda/session/1092611&quot;>;Gartner data&lt;/a>;, 27% of employees and 38% of managers feel overwhelmed by the ever-mounting burden of information. Discuss with your team how to simplify communication and information overload. For instance, it can be helpful to agree to limit any write-ups, such as proposals or meeting pre-reads, to a one-page summary that clearly highlights its relevance in the present context. Additionally, in meetings or chats — where opinions often overflow and unnecessary complexity arises — encourage participants to distill their ideas to their essence. Prompt team members to get to the crux by asking, “Can you summarize the essence of your suggestion in two sentences?” And as you discuss any workstream or product with your team, consistently challenge yourselves to simplify by asking, “How can we shorten or simplify this?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A second frequently neglected area is to seek input from your internal customers on what can be simplified in the solutions or services you offer them. Surprisingly, their perspectives can illuminate unnecessary complexity that your team may have overlooked. For example, the Dutch company AFAS Software regularly holds meetings with its clients solely dedicated to discussing what features or elements they should remove from their software solution. This proactive approach ensures that their software remains up-to-date and free from needless complexity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Layoffs are difficult and stressful for everyone involved. But by implementing the strategies above, you can help shield your team from the damaging effects of work overload. Your efforts will help eliminate depleting low-value work, ensure your team can focus on the most critical work, and boost their morale and engagement.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Out for These 3 Gender Biases in Performance Reviews]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_26_AnjaSusanj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Anja Sušanj&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Three kinds of bias often creep into the performance-review process, in ways that disproportionately affect women, especially when they choose to take advantage of the flexibility offered by hybrid and remote work. These biases are &lt;em>;experience bias&lt;/em>;, which leads reviewers to overvalue tasks that are easy to define; &lt;em>;proximity bias&lt;/em>;, which leads them to think that people in their immediate orbit do the most important work; and i&lt;em>;n-group/out-group bias, &lt;/em>;which leads them to give preferential treatment to people they feel belong to a group they identify with. This article, based on the author&amp;#8217;s study of a large multinational consulting group, explains the nature of these biases and offers suggestions for how to combat them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/watch-out-for-these-3-gender-biases-in-performance-reviews?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Because women continue to bear most of the burdens of caregiving, many have benefitted from the flexibility of hybrid and remote work, which has allowed them to remain part of the full-time workforce while spending more time at home. In theory, this is good news, because full-time employees tend to be promoted more often and let go less often — but &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/women-face-a-double-disadvantage-in-the-hybrid-workplace&quot;>;in practice&lt;/a>; that&#39;s not what&#39;s happening.为什么？ Because when women take advantage of hybrid and remote work options today, they become subject to &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/6-ways-to-make-performance-reviews-more-fair&quot;>;biases&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;that creep into the performance-review process and cause them to be &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/04/how-gender-bias-corrupts-performance-reviews-and-what-to-do-about-it&quot;>;judged unfairly&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I witnessed this problem firsthand during a consulting project I did recently for a global company with hundreds of thousands of employees worldwide. During the project, which took place as the company (which I&#39;ll call HAPI&amp;nbsp; Consulting, to preserve its anonymity) was in the midst of a large reorganization, I was reporting to the CEO, his executive, and the board. With their support, I gathered and analyzed data on performance reviews given in a hybrid work environment (pre- and post-pandemic), and in that context I identified three specific kinds of bias that were hurting women and their career prospects. I&#39;ll explore them in turn below.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Experience bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first bias I observed was what we call &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/05/fooled-by-experience&quot;>;&lt;em>;experience bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; one aspect of which is overvaluing tasks that are easy to define.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This form of bias, I found, was prevalent in performance reviews at HAPI Consulting — where, because of the reorganization, many employees had been forced to put their routine work on hold. During that period, reviewers had judged employees instead on how they had chosen to refocus their energies. Men, on the whole, had chosen work that was much easier to recognize. They spent more time on highly visible external tasks, such as speaking at industry conferences and giving interviews to journalists, bloggers, and podcasters. These tasks were straightforward to review when it came to short-term measures of success. Meanwhile, &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/research-women-took-on-even-more-invisible-work-during-the-pandemic&quot;>;women&lt;/a>; spent more time on much less visible internal tasks, such as boosting team cohesion to help get projects back on track and providing psychologically safe spaces for team members to ask questions and process elements of the reorganization that were taking place at the company. These tasks had longer timelines and were harder to evaluate in the short term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These choices lent themselves to experience bias. It&#39;s easy to understand, for example, how somebody who has presented at a major conference (probably a man) might have immediately provided a measurable benefit to the company. In fact, men were three times more likely than women to speak at outside events. But how easy is it to measure and evaluate the work that somebody (probably a woman) has begun to do in a long-term effort to repair team dynamics or prevent deep-rooted problems that might ultimately affect hundreds or thousands of employees? Needless to say, given the nature of experience bias, reviewers at HAPI Consulting praised the men more regularly in their performance reviews for having succeeded in their work. More specifically, men who reviewed other men assessed them 12% higher than women, on average, as compared to when women reviewed both men and other women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With the support of leadership, I tested several interventions designed to help reviewers at the company correct this bias. While some interventions failed, two had a statistically significant chance (with a 95% confidence interval or above) of reducing biases at this company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first was for managers to help employees set individualized goals with tailored metrics and then ask them to track what they had done every week — and to do it on a virtual whiteboard that the rest of the team and the directors up the chain could see. In this way, people who had contributed to less-easily-defined outcomes, such as team cohesion, could still point to a record of their efforts over time for all to see. This whiteboard could record important work even if it wasn&#39;t easily described in terms of traditional goals and metrics. This was helpful come performance review time. Even if employees had failed to reach the goals laid out for them in their last performance review, there was still a record of all their efforts and achievements, which, according to the post-survey results, helped reviewers better grasp the value of the more ambiguous, internal work that (mostly) women were performing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The second was designed to help employees become better at describing their own efforts. At the beginning of the week, for each project they were working on, employees were asked to provide two different estimates on their virtual whiteboard: how long each task would take to accomplish and its level of difficulty (high, medium, or low). For example, an employee might identify the three projects they&#39;re working on for the week and allocate the amount of time they plan to spend on each, based on the type of task and estimated difficulty. At the end of each week, employees were asked to revisit their estimates, note how their time was actually allocated and how difficult the task ended up being, and reflect on the reasons for the differences between their forecasts and “actuals.” This practice allowed employees to look back on their recorded predictions, reflect on what the record showed in comparison to their perceptions, and fine-tune their ability to paint an accurate picture of their efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Initially, the data showed that women were more accurate in their estimations of the time a task would take, although they often overestimated the difficulty of tasks. Meanwhile, men underestimated both the time a task would take and its difficulty. Following the intervention, the likelihood of women accurately identifying the difficulty of the task increased by a factor of 28, while men were 12.5 times more likely to do so. Additionally, men became 7 times more likely to accurately estimate the time required for a task, whereas there was no significant difference in this aspect for women.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Proximity bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;An other form of bias I observed was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/employee-relations/pages/preventing-proximity-bias-in-a-hybrid-workplace.aspx&quot;>;&lt;em>;proximity bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; or the tendency to think that people who are in your physical orbit do the most important work. A hybrid work environment exacerbates this bias and was penalizing women at HAPI Consulting, where men were more likely than women to come into the office. Reviewers tended to express skepticism, or at least confusion, about what women did when they worked remotely, whereas they tended to give men the benefit of the doubt and assume that they were more focused and productive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even when women came into the office as often as men, reviewers assigned them achievement levels that were a statistically significant 3% lower than those they assigned to the men. And when women came into the office more than men, reviewers seemed to believe that they were doing so only because they were looking out for themselves and wanted to “have a seat at the table” to defend their position in the reorganization of the company. Conversely, when men came into the office an above-average amount, they were seen as strong leaders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To address this problem of proximity bias, I administered a survey to employees to gauge their preferences among several choices: more online gatherings, an “anchor day” when everybody was expected to be in the office, or more offsite team-building opportunities. The employees&#39; preference was that the company create an anchor day, which it did. This intervention led to a statistically significant drop in proximity bias that was observable in the next performance-review cycle. In addition to having employees post their current projects on a virtual whiteboard each week, teams were also asked to hold weekly meetings during which they would discuss three achievements from the previous week, their goals for the current week, and three challenges they were facing in trying to achieve them. By drawing more equal attention to the work that everybody was doing, no matter where they did it, these meetings helped the company resist proximity bias.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;In-group/out-group bias&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The third form of bias that was creeping into remote-work performance evaluations was &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2000-08465-006&quot;>;&lt;em>;in-group/out-group bias&lt;/em>;,&lt;/a>; or giving preferential treatment to people you feel belong to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11752497/&quot;>;group you identify with&lt;/a>;. Not surprisingly, employees who were working remotely, and particularly those who had moved away from the office and across state lines, were increasingly seen as members of the out-group — and they had annual performance review scores that were lower by an average of 20%. Benefits would accrue to those in the in-group, including vertical promotions, horizontal promotions (providing employees with new opportunities to learn new skills and take on more prized tasks that would position them well for vertical promotions), and bonuses, such as equity shares in the company. Both men and women were subject to this form of bias, but because men tend to be seen more readily as leaders, they were more easily able to join the in-group than women.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To increase a sense of belonging, the company launched a campaign called “I am HAPI Consulting, We are HAPI Consulting.” One element of the campaign asked employees to answer simple, sometimes silly questions so that teams could come to know the commonalities among them. For example, when providing updates at meetings, employees might also have to tack on the answer to the question, “Dog or cat?” or “What is on your bucket list this year?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Questions like these provided some memorable moments that everyone could share, no matter whether they worked in the office or remotely, and they allowed more people to experience in-group moments. Strikingly, this practice led to a 14% increase in feelings of belonging to the in-group, and a 17% increase in employees&#39; perceptions of which &lt;em>;other&lt;/em>; employees belong to the in-group. At performance-review time, reviewers were also asked to recall one thing they had in common with the person they were about to review. We found that this simple intervention, which meant that reviews began from a point of commonality, decreased the gender discrimination in the company&#39;s performance reviews by several percentage points.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Men and women often experience the workplace differently, whether in-person or virtually. To include and support the best talent for your company in a dynamic environment, it&#39;s important to take a careful look at the data, be alert to the three kinds of biases discussed in this article, and identify practices that are leading you to overvalue the efforts of certain groups. The insights you gain from doing so will not only help you treat women more fairly but also will lead to fewer predictable surprises, more productive work hours, and increased efficiency in smoothly leading teams — and your company — to success.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[28 Questions to Ask Your Boss in Your One-on-Ones]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1398880959.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;NicoElNino/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Good one-on-one meetings between managers and their direct reports address the practical and personal needs of the employee, benefitting their performance, growth, and well-being, as well as the success of their team and the broader organization. However, since managers are typically the ones who run these meetings, the employee&amp;#8217;s needs are often forgotten. Then it&amp;#8217;s up to the employee to ask questions to get the attention they need. The authors&amp;#8217; research points to twenty-eight questions that can drive the best conversations.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When she started a new role, Brianna was told she would be having regular one-on-one meetings (1:1s) with her manager, Jayden. She welcomed this news; she saw it as a great opportunity to get aligned with and supported and mentored by her new boss. But her hopes were quickly dashed. In their initial meeting, Jayden focused only on project updates and then assigned her a few additional tasks. This pattern continued over the weeks and Brianna routinely left their meetings feeling both micro-managed and unsupported in her development.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This story is, sadly, a composite of many we have heard from employees in our research on 1:1s between managers and their direct reports. As one of us (Steve) described in a new book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Glad-Met-Art-Science-Meetings/dp/0197641873&quot;>;&lt;em>;Glad We Met: The Art and Science of 1:1 Meetings&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;,&lt;/em>; a good one-on-one meeting addresses both the practical and personal needs of the employee (practical: information, instruction, alignment; personal: the need to be treated with consideration, respect, trust, and support). As such, these meetings are a critical source of growth and support for the employee and promote the thriving and success of teams and the broader organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But these benefits are only realized when the meeting includes frequent conversations that &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/11/make-the-most-of-your-one-on-one-meetings&quot;>;address those employee needs&lt;/a>;. And as 1:1s are typically facilitated by managers, they often devolve into addressing what is front of mind for them, rather than the employee. That&#39;s especially true because it is very rare for managers to receive training on how to run these meetings well, so they often simply recycle dysfunctional practices they themselves have experienced.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you are in Brianna&#39;s position — if your boss&#39;s approach to your 1:1s has left you feeling unsupported and unheard — you should feel empowered to direct the conversation toward your needs yourself. You can do this by asking smart questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Questions to Ask&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Based on published research as well as data we collected from nearly 200 employees on important topics to broach in a 1:1, we have identified 28 key questions in seven broad categories to help you get the most value from your check-ins with your boss. You can use, adapt, and put these into your own voice as you see fit.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Ask for Guidance and Input&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Use these questions to get help from your manager on any tasks or projects you are having difficulty with, or to express your need for additional resources, input, or support.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;I am having some challenges and struggles with X. Can you help me think about how to navigate and address X successfully?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Could you suggest any ideas and thoughts around how I could get more support (people, time, funding) to help with Y?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What do you think of my idea Z? Do you have any suggestions for how to improve it? Or, might you have an alternative idea I should consider?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Clarify Priorities and Expectations&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To be sure you are on track and working efficiently, make sure you and your manager are on the same page. Ask for clarification on what tasks need your most focused attention from their point of view.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;4&quot;>; &lt;li>;Given what is on my plate, what should I be prioritizing right now, and can you help me understand why?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you review my workload, am I taking on on the right projects and tasks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Am I on track for meeting my goals and your expectations from your perspective? Is any any refocusing necessary?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there any context I might be missing about the projects I am working on? For example, what is the reasoning for doing project X?&lt;strong>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Align with the Organization and Its Strategy&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Ask questions to understand how your role relates to the broader strategic goals of the organization and the way its leaders are thinking about the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;8&quot;>; &lt;li>;What is going on further up the tree (or in other parts of the organization) that would be helpful for me to know as I work on my key tasks?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To better help me understand the big picture, how does the work I&#39;m doing or the assignment you just gave me fit into the broader goals and strategy?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything that the management team is working on or considering that you think I should know about at present given its potential impact on my role?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is new in our strategic priorities as a company that you feel I should know about, if anything?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Seek Growth Opportunities and Career Advancement&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Come to the meeting with your thinking (however inchoate) around your professional short-term and long-term goals and ask your manager what steps you should take to get there.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;12&quot;>; &lt;li>;I would value your counsel. What can I do to prepare myself for greater opportunities or to pursue X interest of mine?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you reflect on where the organization is going, do you have any thoughts on how I should improve and develop to best align?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What strengths do you think I have and how might they be helpful in the future?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;From your perspective, what should I be targeting as my next career move and why do you recommend that position?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How can we make sure that my skillset is put to the best use to support the team and the organization?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How can we make sure that my full potential is achieved?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Get Feedback on Your Performance&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Check in with your manager to see how you are doing, performance-wise. You shouldn&#39;t make every meeting into an official performance evaluation, but it is important to periodically check in and calibrate if your manager isn&#39;t doing that themselves.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;18&quot;>; &lt;li>;Am I meeting your expectations? I would relish learning your perspective on my work performance.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What feedback might you be able to share with me about how I&#39;m doing at X or Y task?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Do you feel I have any spots I&#39;m overlooking when it comes to A or B?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;As you reflect on what I do at work, what should I start, stop, or continue doing?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Build a Relationship&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Your 1:1 is a critical place for you to build and nurture your relationship with your manager. Allocate time at the beginning or end of the meeting to connect with your manager personally.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;22&quot;>; &lt;li>;How is your day going?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How are things going for you overall? Are you doing ok?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What is something you are excited about outside of work?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything you would like to know about me? (If needed, be prepared to say “I don&#39;t feel comfortable sharing that, but here&#39;s something else you should know about me.”)&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h3>;Offer Support&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Consider ways in which you can help your manager achieve their goals and fulfill their role. Managers need assistance, reassurance, and support to optimize their efficiency and performance. Just like you&#39;d expect your manager to support you, see how you can lend them a hand. This will also increase the chances of you getting what you need in the 1:1.&lt;/p>; &lt;ol start=&quot;26&quot;>; &lt;li>;What are your priorities over the next X days? What can I do to help you with this?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Where can I offer you support?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Is there anything keeping you up at night that I can help with?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;How to Use the Questions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;For each 1:1 meeting, pick a category or two to focus on. You can&#39;t address them all in every meeting, so you will need to rotate or pick the most relevant at a given time. Likewise, choose sparingly from among the questions — no need to ask them all at one time. You&#39;ll simply want to sample from all categories over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Don&#39;t hesitate to follow up on your manager&#39;s responses to your questions. A great follow-up is often simply “why?” You&#39;ll glean strategic insights into the rationale, motives, assumptions, and big picture behind your day-to-day work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Good 1:1 meetings with your manager are critical for your success and the success of your team and organization. Asking the right questions to make sure those meetings give you what you need can have a huge impact on your work experience — helping you stay engaged, developing your understanding of your role and place in the organization, and improving your relationship with your manager — not to mention enhancing your well-being.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies That Replace People with AI Will Get Left Behind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1300035600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;piranka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Companies are integrating AI into their operations so quickly that job losses are likely to mount before the gains arrive. White-collar workers might be especially vulnerable in the short-term.The speed of this adoption presents an opportunity for companies to step up their pace of innovation, however &amp;#8212; and if enough companies to go on offensive, then we won&amp;#8217;t have to worry about AI unemployment. Adopting a bias for boldness and a startup mentality will help companies find the agility to make the most of this moment, and protect jobs as a result.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;After much discussion, the debate over job displacement from artificial intelligence is settling into a consensus. Historically, we&#39;ve never experienced macro-level unemployment from new technologies, so AI is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/long-run-ai-job-creator-destroyer-babak-pahlavan%3FtrackingId=6uoHh%252F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%253D%253D/?trackingId=6uoHh%2F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%3D%3D&quot;>;unlikely to make&lt;/a>; many people jobless in the long term — &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/05/24/artificial-intelligence-ai-eric-schmidt-demographic-crisis-babies-labor-shortage/&quot;>;especially since&lt;/a>; most advanced countries are now seeing their working-age populations decline. However, because companies are adopting ChatGPT and other generative AI remarkably fast, we may see &lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/podcast/ripple-effect/rise-of-ai-are-robots-taking-our-jobs-lynn-wu/&quot;>;substantial job displacement in the short term&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Compare AI with the rise of electricity around the turn of the twentieth&amp;nbsp;century. It took factories decades to switch from steam-powered central driveshafts to electric motors for each machine. They had to reorganize their layout in order to take advantage of the new electric technology. The process happened slowly enough that the economy had time to adjust, only new factories adopting the motors at first. As electricity created new jobs, laid-off workers in steam-powered factories could move over. Greater wealth created entirely new industries to engage workers, along with higher expectations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Something similar happened with the spread of computing in the middle of the twentieth century. It went at a faster pace than electrification, but was still slow enough to prevent mass unemployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI is different because companies are integrating it into their operations so quickly that job losses are likely to mount before the gains arrive. White-collar workers might be especially vulnerable in the short-term. Indeed, commentators are describing an “AI gold rush” rather than a bubble, powered by advanced chipmakers such as Nvidia. Goldman Sachs &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65102150&quot;>;recently predicted&lt;/a>; that companies would use it to eliminate a quarter of all current work tasks in the United States and Europe. That probably means tens of millions of people out of work — especially people who thought their specialized knowledge &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-negative-impact-middle-class-white-collar-workers-2023-5?utm_medium=newsletter&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Insider%20Today%2C%20June%202%2C%202023&amp;amp;utm_term=INSIDER%20TODAY%20SEND%20LIST%20-%20ALL%20ENGAGED&quot;>;gave them job security&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That leaves two possibilities to mitigate this risk. The first is that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/23/business/jobs-protections-artificial-intelligence.html&quot;>;governments step in&lt;/a>;, either to slow down the commercial adoption of AI (highly unlikely), or to offer special welfare programs to support and retrain the newly unemployed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But there&#39;s another, often neglected possibility that comes without the unintended consequences of governmental intervention. Some companies are rapidly integrating generative AI into their systems, not just to automate tasks, but to empower employees to do more than they could before — ie, making them more productive. A &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-ai-is-helping-companies-redesign-processes&quot;>;radical redesign&lt;/a>; of corporate processes could spark all sorts of new value creation. If many companies do this, then as a society we&#39;ll generate enough new jobs to escape the short-term displacement trap.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But will they? Even the least aggressive company tends to be pretty good about cutting costs. Innovation, however, is another matter. We didn&#39;t worry about this in the past, because we had enough time for a few aggressive companies to gradually change industries. They innovated over time to make up for the slow loss of displaced jobs. That innovation created new jobs and kept unemployment low. But macroeconomically speaking, we don&#39;t have the luxury of time with the AI transition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So the alternative to relying on the government is to have many companies innovating fast enough to create new jobs at the same pace that the economy as a whole eliminates existing ones. Generative AI is spreading fast in business and society, but that speed also means an opportunity for companies to step up their pace of innovation. If we get enough companies to go on offense in this way, then we won&#39;t have to worry about AI unemployment.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, companies won&#39;t — and shouldn&#39;t — lean into AI in order to solve macroeconomic problems. But fortunately they have good business reasons to do so. The companies that create opportunities from AI will also position themselves to thrive in the long run.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Going on the Offensive with AI&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Already we can point to aggressive companies looking to innovate in AI. Having become a trailblazer in reusable rockets and electric cars, Elon Musk is now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/twitter-elon-musk-linda-yaccarino-spacex-244f0125?mod=series_elonmuskcompanies&quot;>;promising to make&lt;/a>; Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-wants-to-see-an-ai-rival-to-google-microsoft-a299e27f?mod=hp_lista_pos1&quot;>;as much of a leader&lt;/a>; in AI as Microsoft and Google. Musk, however, is &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/does-elon-musk-have-a-strategy&quot;>;a famous outlier&lt;/a>; and the jury is still out on Twitter. So what does it mean for a company to go on offense with AI?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To answer this question, let&#39;s look at what makes companies adept at navigating the kinds of changes we&#39;re seeing now. One of us (Tabrizi) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Going-Offense-Playbook-Perpetual-Innovation/dp/1646871375/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679313&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;>;assembled a team&lt;/a>; of researchers to study 26 sizable companies with good data from 2006–2022. The team divided the companies into groups of high, medium, and low agility and innovation over time, with comparable data and case studies of each.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What set the agile, innovative companies apart from those who remained neutral or defensive? The team narrowed the differentiators down to eight drivers of agile innovation: existential purpose, obsession with what customers want, a Pygmalion-style influence over colleagues, a startup mindset even after scaling up, a bias for boldness, radical collaboration, the readiness to control tempo, and operating bimodally. Most leaders praise those attributes, but it turns out it&#39;s remarkably hard for big organizations to sustain any of them over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tabrizi has written &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/how-microsoft-became-innovative-again&quot;>;elsewhere&lt;/a>; about how Microsoft went on offense to become a corporate leader by overhauling its hierarchy and pursuing partnerships such as with Open AI. But other companies have done something similar with AI as a result of those drivers. Let&#39;s focus on two of the most important drivers here — the bias for boldness and the startup mentality. Getting those drivers in place can take a company far into agile innovation, because these force changes throughout the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Bias for Boldness&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Any company that invests in AI in the near future is likely to make money from it. Yet mere investment is likely to offer only incremental gains. The numbers might look good, especially in cutting costs. But the company will miss the opportunity for big gains by creating substantial value — or a defensible future niche. Cautious investment won&#39;t protect you in the long run from competition, and certainly won&#39;t help us with the macroeconomic challenge we&#39;re facing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That&#39;s the problem with any new technology: You can proceed cautiously and probably do just fine. Big companies hate risk, &lt;a href=&quot;/2000/03/meeting-the-challenge-of-disruptive-change&quot;>;which is why&lt;/a>; they operate as well-oiled machines churning out reliable products at an affordable cost. That&#39;s also why many of them outsource their innovation by acquiring startups — and even that approach often leads to timid improvements. All successful organizations, especially at size, prefer to minimize risk and daring. But as Brené Brown &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Rising-Strong-Reckoning-Rumble-Revolution/dp/0812995821/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679119&amp;amp;sr=1-7&quot;>;points out&lt;/a>;, “You can choose courage, or you can choose comfort, but you cannot choose both.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boldness has become a corporate cliché, with leaders protesting too much, but with AI we need companies to really mean it — to embrace rather than minimize risk. Take Adobe, whose Photoshop program has long held the largest share of the photographic design market. Adobe could have played it safe as generative AI emerged, adopting it in small areas while waiting to see how the technology worked out. That&#39;s what Kodak did with digital photography, and what Motorola did with digital telephony. But instead, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/search/results/content/?fromMember=%5B%22ACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ%22%5D&amp;amp;heroEntityKey=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_profile%3AACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ&amp;amp;keywords=jj%20delgado%F0%9F%A4%99&amp;amp;position=0&amp;amp;searchId=a8067e47-50fe-43fd-a269-0d80da62e1f5&amp;amp;sid=8k2&amp;amp;update=urn%3Ali%3Afs_updateV2%3A(urn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A7066792598446743552%2CBLENDED_SEARCH_FEED%2CEMPTY%2CDEFAULT%2Cfalse)&quot;>;Adobe has pushed&lt;/a>; generative AI deeply into Photoshop, to the point that ordinary users can create all sorts of videos they couldn&#39;t before. Adobe could have seen AI as a threat or distraction, and it has continued to improve Photoshop without AI. But its leaders had the courage to invest aggressively in AI to elevate what users can do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deeper in the technology, Nvidia, the chipmaker, has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2023-06-03/chips-inside-nvidia-s-30-year-ride-to-overnight-ai-success?sref=bsFVYL6k&quot;>;getting headlines&lt;/a>; for offering the best semiconductor chips for AI. To outsiders, the company might just seem lucky, with the right technology at the right time. But Nvidia&#39;s current success is no accident: In the past decade, it aggressively acquired and developed expertise in AI, including creating customized chips and software. We can expect that aggressiveness to continue, enabling not only higher-value offerings for Nvidia, but better uses for AI than simple cost-cutting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Boldness won&#39;t work every time. But a bias for boldness is essential to overcome the deep-seated risk aversion in corporate hierarchies.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A Startup Mentality&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Similar to boldness, and equally important for successful AI, is adopting the mentality of a startup company, no matter your company&#39;s age or size. Startups excel in looking widely at markets and pivoting quickly to what customers are wanting now. Big companies have the resources to apply to those opportunities, but they usually move so slowly, with so many barriers (and lack of boldness), that startups get to markets faster. Open AI, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johanmoreno/2022/12/29/openai-positioned-itself-as-the-ai--leader-in-2022-but-could-google-supersede-it-in-23/?sh=b69aaa953216&quot;>;beat out&lt;/a>; Google with ChatGPT, had the best of both worlds: a startup mentality free of the hesitations that hampered Google, but with ample resources supplied by Microsoft and other investors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The startup mindset is not just about courage and flexibility; it also involves a ferocious commitment to big achievement, a kind of hero&#39;s journey to address a great challenge. Instead of predictability churning out good products at scale — though that&#39;s a perfectly worthwhile goal — startups want to create something extraordinary. So they put a premium on looking around, flexibly partnering with others. They dispense with existing structures and biases, no matter how old and respected, in order to get done what needs to be done.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Amazon, the e-commerce giant, demonstrated a startup mentality in its embrace of AI. As the technology developed over a decade ago, the company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/how-amazon-made-alexa-smarter/&quot;>;saw an opportunity&lt;/a>; in creating a “smart speaker” as a new interface to the web. Amazon had no expertise in AI, but it picked up what it needed through hiring, acquisition, and internal development. The result was the Echo speaker and Alexa digital assistant, which did far more than simply help people order more items for purchase. It opened a new channel for adding value (and jobs) in many areas. Amazon has gone on to invest aggressively in AI beyond Alexa, with CEO Andy Jassy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/amazons-alexa-head-defends-companys-work-on-ai-amid-chatgpt-boom.html&quot;>;saying&lt;/a>; the technology promises to “transform and improve virtually every customer experience.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;• • •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies can&#39;t adopt these drivers overnight, but they can start moving toward a point of serious commitment to new possibilities. Most of those drivers also work at the level of individuals looking for purpose and achievement in their own careers. They can embrace boldness, adopt a startup mentality, and other imperatives. Like companies, employees can invest aggressively in AI by acquiring the requisite skills and experience — thereby not just protecting their careers, but adding value &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-boom-share-profits-workers-productivity-wages-2023-5?inline-endstory-related-recommendations=&quot;>;at a higher level&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Much of corporate life has quite properly been about churning out reliable products at low cost. What we need now, to prevent mass unemployment, is for many firms to break out of this discipline and speed up the AI future. The great danger is that most companies will play it safe, make the easy investments, and do fine in the short term.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Humanity never thrives when it fears innovation. Imagine if the first humans feared fire; yes, they got burned sometimes, but without harnessing the power of it, we might have gone extinct. We think the same applies to AI. Rather than fear it, we need to harness its power. We must put it in the hands of every human being, so we collectively can achieve and live at this higher level.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Your New Leadership Role with the End in Mind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_22_Carlo_Cadenas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Illustration by Carlo Cadenas&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;To successfully step into a new role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance &amp;#8220;now-forward&amp;#8221; planning with &amp;#8220;future-back&amp;#8221; visioning. That is, you must start with the end in mind, envisioning what you want to accomplish during this era of your leadership and what needs to happen before for can take the next step. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;When taking on a new leadership role, it&#39;s&amp;nbsp;natural to focus on the immediate challenges of making a successful transition, including accelerating your learning, building relationship with stakeholders, and securing early wins. However, it is essential to complement this “now-forward” planning with “future-back” thinking about your desired destination and what it will take to get there. As Stephen Covey expressed in his best-selling book, &lt;em>;The Seven Habits of Highly Effective People&lt;/em>;, you want to “start with the end in mind.” This means envisioning what you want to accomplish in the new role so you will be ready to move beyond it and then working backward to map out how you will get there. In so doing, you can shape your early actions to lay the foundation for long-term success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The starting point is to engage in what Dan Ciampa, the noted executive coach, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.danciampa.com/more-designated-successors.php&quot;>;defined as “era planning&lt;/a>;.” Your era is the anticipated duration of time you think you will be in the new position. Of course, you may end up staying longer or leaving earlier, but try to make a rough guess about when you will have accomplished enough to be “done.” You&#39;ll want to ask yourself two key questions: “As I wrap up this job, what will be true?” and “What will be possible?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Envisioning &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Your Leadership Legacy &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The first question — “What will be true?”&amp;nbsp;— asks you to outline the legacy you aspire to create and the story you will tell about your achievements. Focus on what you want to be remembered for in your new position and what you want your team and peers to say about your leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Consider key areas such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Performance outcomes:&lt;/strong>; What are the tangible results — for example, in terms of increased productivity or profitability — you will achieve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Organizational transformation:&lt;/strong>; How will you reshape the team and its culture?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Innovation:&lt;/strong>; What will you do to foster creativity and develop new areas for growth?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Talent development:&lt;/strong>; How will you hire and train people to take the organization into the future?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Distill these into a concise, written personal narrative. Then, think about what you need to do, starting now, to realize this legacy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Creating&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>; Future Possibilities &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The second question — “What will be possible?” — encourages you to envision futures beyond your current role and strategize the steps you&#39;ll take to turn them into viable options. This process involves identifying multiple potential paths forward and pinpointing the skills you&#39;ll need to acquire and the connections you&#39;ll need to establish over the course of this era to make those viable options. By exploring different scenarios and actively planning your development, you&#39;ll be better equipped to adapt and seize emerging opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Take these steps:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Create a list of potential futures, considering logical next steps in your organization and your industry, as well as less conventional but still attractive options that would take you in different directions.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Assess whether there are skill gaps you need to close to achieve some or all of those futures by reflecting on your existing strengths and areas for improvement.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Identify the bridges — the steps and connections — that would allow you to transition from your current role to your desired future options. These might include expanding your professional network, deepening your industry knowledge, or engaging in what Ken Banta and Orlan Boston &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/the-strategic-side-gig&quot;>;described as “strategic side gigs&lt;/a>;,” such as teaching or working on boards of directors.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Develop a plan for how you&#39;ll acquire the skills and build the bridges to make the potential futures you have identified realistic options, setting specific goals and holding yourself accountable for achieving them.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As Peter Drucker said, “The best way to predict the future is to create it.” By imagining multiple potential futures and working toward them, you&#39;ll create real options for yourself when you&#39;re ready to move on from your current role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To successfully step into a new leadership role and set yourself up for long-term success, you must balance “now-forward” planning with “future-back” visioning. This mindset will empower you to make early decisions that will accelerate your transition, pave the way for long-term impact in the new role, and contribute to your continued career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>