<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/<item><title><![CDATA[Companies That Replace People with AI Will Get Left Behind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_23_1300035600.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;piranka/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司将人工智能融入其运营的速度如此之快，以至于在收益到来之前失业人数可能会增加。白领工人在短期内可能尤其容易受到影响。这种采用的速度为公司提供了加快创新步伐的机会，但是＆#8212;如果有足够多的公司继续进攻，那么我们就不必担心人工智能失业。采用大胆的偏见和创业心态将有助于公司找到充分利用这一时刻的敏捷性，从而保护就业机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/companies-that-replace-people-with-ai-will-get-left-behind?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;之后经过一番讨论，关于人工智能取代工作岗位的争论正在形成共识。从历史上看，我们从未经历过新技术带来的宏观失业，因此人工智能&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/long-run-ai-job-creator-destroyer-babak-pahlavan %3FtrackingId=6uoHh%252F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%253D%253D/?trackingId=6uoHh%2F4yS9uf2vTJPHE1vA%3D%3D&quot;>;从长远来看不太可能让&lt;/a>;许多人失业 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com /2023/05/24/artificial-intelligence-ai-eric-schmidt-demographic-crisis-babies-labor-shortage/&quot;>;尤其是&lt;/a>;大多数发达国家的劳动年龄人口正在下降。然而，由于公司正在以非常快的速度采用 ChatGPT 和其他生成式人工智能，我们可能会看到 &lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/podcast/ripple-effect/rise-of-ai-are-robots- take-our-jobs-lynn-wu/&quot;>;短期内会导致大量工作岗位流失&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将人工智能与二十世纪初电力的兴起进行比较。工厂花了几十年的时间才将每台机器的蒸汽动力中央传动轴转换为电动机。他们必须重新组织布局才能利用新的电力技术。这个过程发生得很慢，以至于经济有时间进行调整，只有新工厂首先采用电机。随着电力创造新的就业机会，蒸汽动力工厂的下岗工人可以转移。更多的财富创造了全新的行业来吸引工人，同时也带来了更高的期望。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;二十世纪中叶计算机的传播也发生了类似的情况。它的发展速度比电气化更快，但仍然足够慢，足以防止大规模失业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能不同，因为公司将其整合到运营中的速度如此之快，以至于在收益到来之前失业可能会增加。白领工人在短期内可能尤其容易受到伤害。事实上，评论员正在描述由英伟达等先进芯片制造商推动的“人工智能淘金热”，而不是泡沫。高盛&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65102150&quot;>;最近预测&lt;/a>;公司将使用它来消除美国和欧洲当前所有工作任务的四分之一。这可能意味着数以千万计的人失业——尤其是那些认为自己的专业知识&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-negative-impact-middle-class-white- Collar-workers-2023-5?utm_medium=newsletter&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Insider%20Today%2C%20June%202%2C%202023&amp;amp;utm_term=INSIDER%20TODAY%20SEND%20LIST%20-%20ALL%20ENGAGED&quot;>;给了他们工作保障&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这留下了两种降低这种风险的可能性。首先是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/23/business/jobs-protections-artificial-intelligence.html&quot;>;政府介入&lt;/a>;，要么放慢速度人工智能的商业应用（极不可能），或者提供特殊福利计划来支持和再培训新失业者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是还有另一种经常被忽视的可能性，这种可能性不会因政府干预而产生意想不到的后果。一些公司正在迅速将生成式人工智能集成到他们的系统中，不仅是为了自动化任务，而且是为了让员工能够做比以前更多的事情，即提高他们的工作效率。对企业流程进行&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-ai-is-helping-companies-redesign-processes&quot;>;彻底的重新设计&lt;/a>;可能会激发各种新的价值创造。如果许多公司都这样做，那么作为一个社会，我们将创造足够的新就业机会来摆脱短期失业陷阱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是他们会吗？即使是最不积极进取的公司也往往很擅长削减成本。然而，创新是另一回事。过去我们不担心这个，因为我们有足够的时间让一些激进的公司逐步改变行业。随着时间的推移，他们不断创新，以弥补失业的缓慢损失。这项创新创造了新的就业机会并保持了较低的失业率。但从宏观经济角度来看，我们没有足够的时间来进行人工智能转型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，依赖政府的替代方案是让许多公司以足够快的速度进行创新，以与人工智能相同的速度创造新的就业机会。整个经济消除了现有的经济。生成式人工智能正在商业和社会中快速传播，但这种速度也意味着企业加快创新步伐的机会。如果我们有足够多的公司以这种方式进攻，那么我们就不必担心人工智能失业。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，公司不会——也不应该——为了秩序而倾向于人工智能。解决宏观经济问题。但幸运的是，他们有充分的商业理由这样做。从人工智能中创造机会的公司也将实现长期繁荣。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;利用人工智能发起攻势&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们已经可以指出那些寻求人工智能创新的积极进取的公司。埃隆·马斯克 (Elon Musk) 已成为可重复使用火箭和电动汽车领域的开拓者，现在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/twitter-elon-musk-linda-yaccarino-spacex-244f0125?mod=series_elonmuskcompanies&quot; >;承诺制作&lt;/a>; Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-wants-to-see-an-ai-rival-to-google-microsoft-a299e27f? mod=hp_lista_pos1&quot;>;与微软和谷歌一样是人工智能领域的领导者&lt;/a>;。然而，马斯克是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/does-elon-musk-have-a-strategy&quot;>;一个著名的异常者&lt;/a>;，并且 Twitter 上的评判还没有定论。那么，对于一家公司来说，进攻人工智能意味着什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了回答这个问题，让我们看看是什么让公司能够善于应对我们现在所看到的各种变化。我们中的一员 (Tabrizi) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Going-Offense-Playbook-Perpetual-Innovation/dp/1646871375/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679313&amp;amp;sr=1 -1&quot;>;组建了一个研究团队&lt;/a>;，对2006年至2022年间拥有良好数据的26家规模较大的公司进行了研究。随着时间的推移，团队将公司分为高、中、低敏捷性和创新性组，并对每个组进行可比较的数据和案例研究。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;是什么让敏捷、创新的公司与那些保持中立或创新的公司区分开来。防守？该团队将敏捷创新的差异化因素缩小为八个驱动因素：存在的目的、对客户需求的痴迷、对同事的皮格马利翁式影响、即使扩大规模后的创业心态、大胆的偏见、激进的协作、控制的准备节奏，并双峰运行。大多数领导者都赞扬这些属性，但事实证明，随着时间的推移，大型组织很难维持其中任何一个属性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Tabrizi 写道&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/how-microsoft-became-再次创新>;其他地方&lt;/a>;讲述了微软如何通过彻底改革其层级结构并寻求与 Open AI 等合作伙伴关系，成为企业领导者。但由于这些驱动因素，其他公司也对人工智能做了类似的事情。让我们重点关注两个最重要的驱动因素——大胆的偏见和创业心态。将这些驱动因素落实到位可以使公司深入敏捷创新，因为这些力量会在整个组织中发生变化。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;大胆的偏见&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;任何在不久的将来投资人工智能的公司很可能会从中赚钱。然而，单纯的投资可能只能带来增量收益。这些数字可能看起来不错，尤其是在削减成本方面。但该公司将错过通过创造巨大价值或可防御的未来利基市场来获得巨大收益的机会。从长远来看，谨慎投资并不能保护您免受竞争，当然也无法帮助我们应对所面临的宏观经济挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是任何新技术的问题：您可以谨慎行事，也许做得很好。大公司讨厌风险，&lt;a href=&quot;/2000/03/meeting-the-challenge-of-disruptive-change&quot;>;这就是为什么&lt;/a>;他们像运转良好的机器一样以可承受的成本生产可靠的产品。这也是为什么他们中的许多人通过收购初创公司来外包创新的原因——即使这种方法也常常会带来胆怯的改进。所有成功的组织，尤其是规模较大的组织，都倾向于将风险和勇气降至最低。但正如 Brené Brown &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Rising-Strong-Reckoning-Rumble-Revolution/dp/0812995821/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1686679119&amp;amp;sr=1-7 &quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;，“你可以选择勇气，也可以选择舒适，但你不能两者都选择。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大胆已经成为企业的陈词滥调，领导者抗议太多，但我们需要企业真正认真地对待人工智能——拥抱风险，而不是最小化风险。以 Adob​​e 为例，其 Photoshop 程序长期以来一直占据摄影设计市场的最大份额。随着生成式人工智能的出现，Adobe 本可以谨慎行事，在小范围内采用它，同时等待看看该技术的效果如何。这就是柯达在数码摄影方面所做的事情，以及摩托罗拉在数字电话方面所做的事情。相反，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/search/results/content/?fromMember=%5B%22ACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH6erPefJ5euQ%22%5D&amp;amp;heroEntityKey=urn%3Ali%3Afsd_profile%3AACoAAAFFnEEBmgB0scn3E8AJ0XdH 6erPefJ5euQ&amp;关键字=jj% 20delgado%F0%9F%A4%99&amp;amp;position=0&amp;amp;searchId=a8067e47-50fe-43fd-a269-0d80da62e1f5&amp;amp;sid=8k2&amp;amp;update=urn%3Ali%3Afs_updateV2%3A(urn%3Ali%3Aactivity%3A70667925984 46743552%2CBLENDED_SEARCH_FEED% 2CEMPTY%2CDEFAULT%2Cfalse)&quot;>;Adobe 已将&lt;/a>;生成式 AI 深入 Photoshop 中，普通用户可以创建以前无法创建的各种视频。 Adobe 可能将 AI 视为一种威胁或干扰，但它在没有 AI 的情况下继续改进 Photoshop。但其领导者有勇气积极投资人工智能，以提升用户的能力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在技术的更深层次上，芯片制造商 Nvidia 一直在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg. com/opinion/articles/2023-06-03/chips-inside-nvidia-s-30-year-ride-to-overnight-ai-success?sref=bsFVYL6k&quot;>;因提供最佳半导体而成为头条新闻&lt;/a>;人工智能芯片。在外人看来，该公司可能看起来很幸运，在正确的时间拥有了正确的技术。但英伟达目前的成功并非偶然：在过去十年中，它积极获取和开发人工智能领域的专业知识，包括创建定制芯片和软件。我们预计这种进取精神将继续下去，不仅为 Nvidia 提供更高价值的产品，而且比简单的成本削减更好地利用人工智能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;大胆并非每次都有效。但是，对于克服企业层级中根深蒂固的风险厌恶情绪，大胆的偏见至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;创业心态&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与大胆类似，对于成功的人工智能同样重要的是，采用初创公司的心态，无论您的公司成立时间或规模如何。初创公司擅长广泛关注市场并快速满足客户当前的需求。大公司拥有资源来利用这些机会，但它们通常行动缓慢，障碍众多（而且缺乏勇气），因此初创企业能够更快地进入市场。开放人工智能，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johanmoreno/2022/12/29/openai-positioned-itself-as-the-ai--leader-in-2022-but- can-google-supersede-it-in-23/?sh=b69aaa953216&quot;>;用 ChatGPT 击败&lt;/a>; Google，两全其美：创业心态摆脱了阻碍 Google 的犹豫，但拥有充足的资源由微软和其他投资者提供。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;创业心态不仅仅在于勇气和灵活性；还在于勇气和灵活性。它还涉及对伟大成就的坚定承诺，这是一种应对巨大挑战的英雄之旅。初创公司想要创造一些非凡的东西，而不是按照可预测性大规模生产出优质产品（尽管这是一个完全值得的目标）。因此，他们非常重视环顾四周，灵活地与他人合作。他们摒弃现有的结构和偏见，无论历史有多长、受人尊敬，以便完成需要做的事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;电子商务巨头亚马逊在拥抱人工智能方面展现了创业心态。随着十多年前技术的发展，该公司&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/how-amazon-made-alexa-smarter/&quot;>;看到了创建一个机会&lt;/a>; “智能扬声器”作为网络的新界面。亚马逊在人工智能方面没有专业知识，但它通过招聘、收购和内部开发获得了所需的知识。结果是 Echo 扬声器和 Alexa 数字助理，它的作用远远超出了简单地帮助人们订购更多商品。它为许多领域的增值（和就业）开辟了新的渠道。亚马逊继续在 Alexa 之外积极投资人工智能，首席执行官 Andy Jassy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/amazons-alexa-head-defends-companys-work-on -ai-amid-chatgpt-boom.html&quot;>;说&lt;/a>;该技术承诺“改变和改善几乎所有客户体验。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•• •&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司不可能一夜之间采用这些驱动因素，但他们可以开始认真致力于新的可能性。这些驱动力中的大多数人也在为自己的职业生涯寻找目标和成就的个人层面上工作。他们可以拥抱大胆、采取创业心态和其他必要条件。与公司一样，员工可以通过获得必要的技能和经验来积极投资人工智能，从而不仅可以保护他们的职业生涯，还可以增加价值&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/ai-boom-share-profits- Workers-productivity-wages-2023-5?inline-endstory-lated-recommendations=&quot;>;在更高的水平&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;企业生活的大部分内容都是在生产可靠的产品低成本。为了防止大规模失业，我们现在需要的是许多公司打破这一规则，加速人工智能的未来发展。最大的危险在于，大多数公司都会谨慎行事，进行轻松的投资，并在短期内表现出色。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当人类害怕创新时，它就永远不会繁荣。想象一下，如果第一批人类害怕火，那会是什么样子？是的，它们有时会被烧伤，但如果不利用它的力量，我们可能已经灭绝了。我们认为这同样适用于人工智能。我们不需要害怕它，而是需要利用它的力量。我们必须将它交到每个人的手中，这样我们才能共同实现并生活在这个更高的水平上。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Your New Leadership Role with the End in Mind]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_22_Carlo_Cadenas.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;卡洛·卡德纳斯 (Carlo Cadenas) 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;要成功担任新角色并为长期成功做好准备，您必须在“现在与未来”之间取得平衡。规划“未来”愿景。也就是说，你必须从目的开始，设想在你的领导时代你想要完成什么，以及之前需要发生什么才能采取下一步。这种心态将使您能够尽早做出决定，从而加速您的过渡，为在新角色中产生长期影响铺平道路，并为您的持续职业发展做出贡献。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/start-your-new-leadership-role-with-the-end-in-mind?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;p>;担任新的领导角色时，很自然地会关注成功过渡所面临的直接挑战，包括加快学习速度、与利益相关者建立关系以及确保早期胜利。然而，必须用“未来”思考来补充这种“现在向前”的计划，考虑您想要的目的地以及到达那里需要做什么。正如史蒂芬·柯维在他的畅销书《高效人士的七个习惯》中所表达的那样，你要“以终为始”。这意味着设想你想要在新角色中完成什么，这样你就准备好超越它，然后向后工作以规划你将如何实现这一目标。通过这样做，您可以制定早期行动，为长期成功奠定基础。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;起点是参与著名高管教练 Dan Ciampa 的&lt;a href=&quot;http: //www.danciampa.com/more-designated-successors.php&quot;>;定义为“时代规划&lt;/a>;”。您的时代是您认为自己将处于新职位的预期持续时间。当然，你最终可能会停留更长时间或更早离开，但请尝试粗略地猜测一下你何时会完成足够的“完成”。你需要问自己两个关键问题：“当我完成这份工作时，事实会怎样？”和“什么将是可能的？”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;设想&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;你的领导力遗产&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第一个问题——“什么将会是真实的？ ”——要求您概述您渴望创造的遗产以及您将讲述的关于您的成就的故事。重点关注您希望在新职位上被记住的方面，以及您希望您的团队和同事如何评价您的领导力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;考虑以下关键领域：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>; &lt;strong>;绩效成果：&lt;/strong>;您将实现哪些切实成果（例如，提高生产力或盈利能力）？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;组织转型：&lt;/strong>;将如何实现您重塑团队及其文化？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;创新：&lt;/strong>;您将采取哪些措施来培养创造力并开发新的增长领域？&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人才发展：&lt;/strong>;您将如何雇用和培训人员来带领组织走向未来？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;将这些提炼成简洁的书面个人叙述。然后，思考一下从现在开始，您需要做什么来实现这一遗产。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;创造&lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;未来的可能性&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;第二个问题——“什么是可能的？” — 鼓励您展望当前角色之外的未来，并制定战略，将其转变为可行的选择。这个过程包括确定多种潜在的前进道路，并确定您需要获得的技能以及您在这个时代的过程中需要建立的联系，以做出这些可行的选择。通过探索不同的场景并积极规划您的发展，您将能够更好地适应和抓住新兴机遇。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;采取以下步骤：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;创建潜在未来清单，考虑您的组织和行业中合乎逻辑的后续步骤，以及不太传统但仍然有吸引力的选择，这些选择将带您走向不同的方向。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;评估您是否需要弥补技能差距才能实现某些目标或目标通过反思您现有的优势和需要改进的领域，您可以实现所有这些未来。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;确定桥梁（步骤和联系），使您能够从当前的角色过渡到您想要的未来选择。这些可能包括扩展您的专业网络、加深您的行业知识，或参与 Ken Banta 和 Orlan Boston &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/the-strategic-side-gig&quot;>;所描述的“战略性副业&lt;/a” >;”，例如教学或在董事会工作。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;制定计划，说明如何获得技能并建立桥梁，使您已确定的潜在未来成为现实的选择，设定具体目标和让自己对实现这些目标负责。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;正如彼得·德鲁克所说，“预测未来的最好方法就是创造未来。”通过想象多种潜在的未来并为之努力，当您准备好离开当前的角色时，您将为自己创造真正的选择。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;成功地进入新的领导角色并为自己做好准备为了取得长期成功，您必须平衡“当前”规划与“未来”愿景。这种心态将使您能够尽早做出决定，从而加速您的过渡，为在新角色中产生长期影响铺平道路，并为您的持续职业发展做出贡献。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https ://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Roles Could Generative AI Play on Your Team?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_22_1273134318.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Normform/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;ChatGPT 的最新进展只是新人工智能技术的首次应用。因此，公司和领导者需要考虑此处概述的各种应用程序，并使用本文中描述的框架为您自己的公司或组织开发应用程序。在此过程中，他们将发现新型 GPT。通过根据对企业的潜在价值和开发成本对这些不同的 GPT 进行分类，以单个人发起或参与交互（GroupGPT、CoachGPT）开始的应用程序可能是最容易构建的，并且应该产生巨大的商业价值，使他们成为完美的初始候选人。相比之下，涉及多个实体或由机器（AutoGPT、BossGPT 和 ImperialGPT）发起的交互的应用程序可能更难实现，并且具有更棘手的道德和法律影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/what-roles-could-generative-ai-play-on-your-team?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;围绕大型语言模型 (LLM) 和其他类型的生成人工智能 (GenAI) 推出的狂热不会很快消退。 GenAI 的用户正在为他们的业务和个人发现和推荐新的、有趣的用例 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/04/14/upshot/up-ai-uses.html&quot; >;生活&lt;/a>;。许多建议都是从 GenAI 需要人工提示的假设开始的。事实上，《时代》杂志最近宣称“即时工程”将成为下一个热门工作，&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/6272103/ai-prompt-engineer-job/&quot;>;薪资达到 335,000 美元&lt;/a>;。技术论坛和教育网站都专注于即时工程，Udemy 已经提供&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.udemy.com/course/master-prompt-engineering-with-chatgpt&quot;>;有关该主题的课程&lt;/ a>;，并且与我们合作的几个组织现在开始投入大量资源来培训员工如何最好地使用 ChatGPT。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，可能值得停下来考虑与 GPT 技术交互的其他方式，这些可能很快就会出现。我们提出了一种直观的方式来思考这个问题，该方式基于我们自己对 GenAI 开发的调查，并结合与寻求开发某些版本的公司的对话。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;GPT 交互框架&lt; /h2>; &lt;p>;一个好的起点是区分谁&lt;em>;参与交互&lt;/em>;（个人、群体或另一台机器）以及&lt;em>;谁发起交互，&lt;/em>; >; 人或机器。这导致了六种不同类型的 GenAI 用途，如下所示。 ChatGPT 是由一个人发起与机器的交互，这一点已经众所周知。我们现在描述其他每个 GPT 并概述它们的潜力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;CoachGPT&lt;/strong>;&amp;nbsp;是一个私人助理，可为您提供一系列有关管理日常生活的建议。这些建议不是基于您的明确提示，而是基于对您所做的事情和环境的观察。例如，它可以观察您作为一名高管，并注意到您发现很难在团队中建立信任；然后它可以建议精确的行动来克服这个盲点。它还可以就发展选择甚至薪资谈判提出个性化建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CoachGPT 随后会查看您采纳或未采纳哪些建议，哪些对您有利，哪些对您没有帮助，从而改善其绩效随着时间的推移提供建议。随着时间的推移，您将获得高度个性化的人工智能顾问、教练或咨询师。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;组织可以采用 CoachGPT 为客户提供有关如何使用产品的建议，无论建筑公司是否提供 CoachGPT 来为最终用户提供如何使用产品的建议最好使用其设备，或者会计师事务所就如何最好地对一组交易进行会计提供实时建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了使 CoachGPT 有效，个人和组织必须允许它在后台，监控线上和线下活动。显然，在我们将内心的想法托付给系统之前，需要先解决严重的隐私问题。然而，在私人生活和职业生活中取得积极成果的潜力是巨大的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;GroupGPT &lt;/strong>;将是一个真正的团体成员，可以观察团体成员之间的互动并为讨论做出贡献。例如，它可以进行事实检查，提供对话摘要，建议下一步讨论什么，扮演魔鬼代言人的角色，提供竞争对手的观点，对想法进行压力测试，甚至提出一个创造性的解决方案来解决问题&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些请求可能来自各个小组成员或团队的老板，他们不需要参与团队互动，而只是寻求管理、激励和评估小组成员。贡献可以交付给整个团体或特定个人，并根据该人的角色、技能或个性进行调整。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;上述隐私问题也适用于 GroupGPT，但是，如果得到解决，组织可以利用 GroupGPT 进行项目管理，尤其是涉及跨不同部门或地区的相对较大团队的长期且复杂的项目。由于 GroupGPT 将克服人类在信息存储和处理能力方面的限制，因此非常适合支持复杂且分散的团队。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;BossGPT&lt;/strong>; &amp;nbsp;在为团队提供建议方面发挥着积极作用。人们在没有提示的情况下知道他们可以或应该做什么。它可以向团队成员提供个人建议，但当它开始协调团队成员的工作，告诉他们作为一个团队谁应该做什么以使团队产出最大化时，它的真正价值就显现出来了。随着项目和团队动态的发展，BossGPT 还可以介入提供个人指导和进一步的建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;BossGPT 工作所需的算法会复杂得多，因为他们必须考虑一些不可预测的个人和团队对机器指令的反应，但它可以有广泛的用途。例如：更换工作的高管可以要求获得她对第一个组织的 BossGPT 指令的反应副本，然后可以使用该副本来评估她如何适应新组织以及新组织特定的 BossGPT。&lt;/p>; &lt;在组织层面，公司可以部署 BossGPT 来管理人员，从而增强——甚至可能取代——现有的管理者。同样，BossGPT 在协调跨组织工作以及管理复杂的供应链或多个供应商方面拥有巨大的应用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;公司可以将 BossGPT 变成一种产品，为客户提供人工智能解决方案，帮助他们管理业务。这些解决方案可以是前面描述的 CoachGPT 示例的自然扩展。例如，一家销售建筑设备的公司可以提供 BossGPT 来协调建筑工地上的许多最终用户，而会计师事务所可以提供它来协调其客户的许多员工的工作，以最有效的方式运行会计功能。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;AutoGPT&lt;/strong>; &amp;nbsp;需要人类向一台机器发出请求或提示，然后机器再让其他机器完成任务。最简单的形式是，人类可能会指示机器完成一项任务，但机器意识到它缺少特定的软件来执行它，因此它会在谷歌上搜索缺少的软件，然后下载并安装它，然后使用它&lt;a href=&quot;https://autogpt.net/auto-gpt-vs-chatgpt-how-do-they-differ-and-everything-you-need-to-know/&quot;>;完成请求&lt;/a >;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在更复杂的版本中，人类可以给 AutoGPT 一个目标（例如创建最好的病毒式 YouTube 视频），并指示它与另一个 GenAI 交互，以迭代地提出最佳的 ChatGPT 提示来实现目标。然后，机器将通过向另一台机器提出提示来启动该过程，然后评估结果，并调整提示以越来越接近最终目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在最复杂的版本中，AutoGPT 可以绘制关于上述其他 GPT 的功能。 For example, a team leader could task a machine with maximizing both the effectiveness and job satisfaction of her team members. AutoGPT could then switch between coaching individuals through CoachGPT, providing them with suggestions for smoother team interactions through GroupGPT, while at the same time issuing specific instructions on what needs to be done through BossGPT. AutoGPT could subsequently collect feedback from each activity and adjust all the other activities to reach the given goal.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unlike the above versions, which are still to be created, a version of AutoGPT has been developed and was rolled out in April 2023, and it&#39;s quickly gaining broad acceptance. The technology is still not perfect and requires improvements, but it is already evident that AutoGPT is able to complete a set of jobs that requires the completion of several tasks one after the other.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We see its biggest applications in complex tasks, such as supply chain coordination, but also in fields such as cybersecurity. For example, organizations could prompt AutoGPT to continually address any cybersecurity vulnerabilities, which would entail looking for them — which already happens — but then instead of simply flagging them, AutoGPT would search for solutions to the threats or write its own patches to counter them. A human might still be in the loop, but since the system is self-generative within these limits, we believe that AutoGPT&#39;s response is likely to be faster and more efficient.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ImperialGPT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong>;is the most abstract GenAI — and perhaps the most transformational — in which two or more machines would interact with each other, direct each other, and ultimately direct humans to engage in a course of action. This type of GPT worries most AI analysts, who fear losing control of AI and AI “going rogue.” We concur with these concerns, particularly if — as now — there are no strict guardrails on what AI is allowed to do.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the same time, if ImperialGPT is allowed to come up with ideas and share them with humans, but its ability to act on the ideas is restricted, we believe that this could generate extremely interesting creative solutions especially for “unknown unknowns,” where human knowledge and creativity fall short. They could then easily envision and game out multiple black swan events and worst-case scenarios, complete with potential costs and outcomes, to provide possible solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the potential dangers of ImperialGPT, and the need for tight regulation, we believe that ImperialGPT will be slow to take off, at least commercially. We do anticipate, however, that governments, intelligence services, and the military will be interested in deploying ImperialGPT under strictly controlled conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Implications for your Business&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;So, what does our framework mean for companies and organizations around the world? First and foremost, we encourage you to step back and see the recent advances in ChatGPT as merely the first application of new AI technologies. Second, we urge you to think about the various applications outlined here and use our framework to develop applications for your own company or organization. In the process, we are sure you will discover new types of GPTs that we have not mentioned. Third, we suggest you classify these different GPTs in terms of potential value to your business, and the cost of developing them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We believe that applications that begin with a single human initiating or participating in the interaction (GroupGPT, CoachGPT) will probably be the easiest to build and should generate substantial business value, making them the perfect initial candidates. In contrast, applications with interactions involving multiple entities or those initiated by machines (AutoGPT, BossGPT, and ImperialGPT) may be harder to implement, with trickier ethical and legal implications.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You might also want to start thinking about the complex ethical, legal, and regulatory concerns that will arise with each GPT type. Failure to do so exposes you and your company to both legal liabilities and — perhaps more importantly — an unintended negative effect on humanity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our next set of recommendations depends on your company type. A tech company or startup, or one that has ample resources to invest in these technologies, should start working on developing one or more of the GPTs discussed above. This is clearly a high-risk, high-reward strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In contrast, if your competitive strength is not in GenAI or if you lack resources, you might be better off adopting a “wait and see” approach. This means you will be slow to adopt the current technology, but you will not waste valuable resources on what may turn out to be only an interim version of a product. Instead, you can begin preparing your internal systems to better capture and store data as well as readying your organization to embrace these new GPTs, in terms of both work processes and culture.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The launch and rapid adoption of GenAIs is rightly being considered as the next level in the evolution of AI and a potentially epochal moment for humanity in general. Although GenAIs represent breakthroughs in solving fundamental engineering and computer science problems, they do not automatically guarantee value creation for all organizations. Rather, smart companies will need to invest in modifying and adapting the core technology before figuring out the best way to monetize the innovations. Firms that do this right may indeed strike it rich in the GenAI goldrush.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Leadership Teams Navigate Uncertain Times]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_21_816813440.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;While we don&amp;#8217;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&amp;#8217;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&amp;#8217;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand &amp;#8212; and reward &amp;#8212; high-performing leadership teams. Based on his conversations with more than 100 clients across industries, PWC US Chair and Senior Partner Tim Ryan has identified seven factors that set these teams apart: 1) They create a &amp;#8220;company-first&amp;#8221; culture; 2) They think and act across the enterprise; 3) They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business; 4) They free up the right people for the hard stuff; 5) They&amp;#8217;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills; 6) They encourage healthy debate, but avoid undermining fellow leaders; and 7) They strive to be humble and objective.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-leadership-teams-navigate-uncertain-times?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Whether it&#39;s inflation, rising interest rates, supply-chain disruptions, geopolitical tensions — there is a lot happening in the global economy. And on top of those forces, consumer expectations are increasing, competition is intense and investors are raising the bar. There&#39;s never been a more challenging time to be a CEO or member of senior management.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Given the complexities, it is no surprise that some companies are performing exceptionally well, a lot are doing just ok and there are others struggling to keep up. Based on my latest discussions with more than 100 clients across industries, what I&#39;ve seen is that the outperforming companies have leadership teams with the following seven factors in common:&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They create a “company-first” culture.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Senior leadership teams are typically made up of individuals who are highly skilled in their domain — but what&#39;s different at high-performing companies is these leaders embrace a company-first culture. This means doing what&#39;s right for the business and your people, instead of driving individual agendas or objectives. One CEO of a high-performing industrial company shared that being part of his leadership team is like being on a sports team: “The team comes first, not the star individual.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They think and act across the enterprise&lt;/strong>;.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-performing teams recognize that their role extends beyond the individual unit they manage, and they operate across silos. One CEO of a leading digital bank shared with me that his team&#39;s enterprise-focused mindset drove a reimagined customer experience resulting in industry-leading efficiency ratios. They achieved this by sharing data across the enterprise and committing to one set of data governance rules.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They maintain a relentless focus on reinventing the business.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Too often CEOs and senior leadership focus the majority of their time on running the business, while the portfolio and business-model reinvention takes a back seat. Strong companies are putting the bold reimagining of their business at the top of the agenda.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bold actions include running the business with unparalleled discipline, managing costs, simplifying wherever you can, and pulling on every lever to win. Taking bold action also involves reshaping portfolios while reinventing the back, middle and front offices—with a sense of urgency.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One CEO of a pharmaceutical company, who was looking to innovate and disrupt their industry, implemented a bold new business model powered by a cutting-edge commerce and marketplace platform in a matter of months. This resulted in a direct, better way to reach customers, increased margins, and greater trust and transparency across their entire value chain.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They free up the right people for the hard stuff. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Reinventing your business is a full-time job and needs dedicated minds who aren&#39;t also focused on managing other day jobs. High-performing leadership teams find the time to focus on the hard stuff and delegate the day-to-day operations to others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A CEO of a major energy company put one of his top business leaders in charge of their enterprise-wide business model transformation to both enable its success and send a clear message to all stakeholders of the importance of the transformation. While it&#39;s difficult to have a leader step away from the work they are doing to take on a transformation effort, the dedicated focus makes all the difference. The energy company&#39;s transformation leader has since positioned the company for significant value accretion and cost optimization through standardization and simplification, all while driving leadership commitment, organizational readiness and business outcome sustainability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They&#39;re inclusive of different backgrounds and skills. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;High-quality teams are inclusive in all ways. This means inclusive of genders and ethnicities, but also of diverse views, backgrounds, and skill sets. It&#39;s critical to have a breadth of leaders in your C-suite that bring forth differentiated expertise and perspectives to enable an organization to innovate more robustly and accelerate transformations. It&#39;s why top leadership teams have a chief technology officer, chief people officer and chief communications officer at the table.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In one instance, a CEO of a major technology company shared with me that too many companies lack a diversity of skills in the C-suite, particularly when it comes to technology. As a result, senior management might not be able to identify what the “art of the possible” is when transforming their business and how different tools, like emerging technologies, could help. In these cases, leadership teams focus on building a “faster horse and buggy”&#39; rather than reimagining what&#39;s next.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They encourage healthy debate but avoid undermining fellow leaders. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Good teams have healthy debates, transparently talk about pros and cons and explore alternatives together. Before transformation efforts begin, they spend a lot of time agreeing on the desired outcomes and business requirements of the effort.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Getting leadership teams to engage in open, honest discussions is critical. One CEO of a major industrial company shared with me that she never imagined the amount of time she needed to spend helping her team “get along.” What I took from her comment is that leadership is about coaching the team to share their various points of view, challenge each other with healthy debate, and come together once a decision is made to row in the same direction.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;They strive to be humble and objective. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Humility is critical at the CEO and senior levels of any company because it filters down to every level of the organization. It helps fight complacency. Most companies have a lot to be proud of, but if the focus is always on the success of the past instead of the opportunity for the future, other companies will quickly pass you by.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Similarly, some leaders struggle with objectively assessing their current performance and where their company and results truly stand. Leading companies are constantly challenging themselves and use objectivity to both drive performance, keep the competition in the rearview mirror and shareholder activists at bay.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I recently spoke with a CEO from a consumer technology company about the importance of having the right people on your company&#39;s board and the critical role the board plays in bringing an outside-in perspective. Board members are in the advantageous position to help the C-suite look around corners, prepare for potential challenges, and discover blind spots.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;While we don&#39;t know what the rest of the year will bring, it&#39;s reasonable to assume that the headwinds we&#39;re experiencing will continue. This is an environment that will demand — and reward — high-performing leadership teams. They&#39;ll drive outsized growth, increase shareholder value, and likely have a little more fun along the way — working together and sharing the successes of a team that is creating more value for their customers, employees, and communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How the Best Brand-Influencer Partnerships Reach Gen Z]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_14_1479691532.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;关闭&quot;>; &lt;span >;总结。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;真实性是 Z 世代最重要的价值观之一。他们觉得自己有能力在各种社交论坛上就任何话题提出和回答自己的问题&amp;#8212;从美容到健康再到家居装修再到技术再到科学。他们对权威的看法已经从学术机构或知名编辑的声音等传统来源扩展到感知影响力。作者为想要进入这个影响者时代并与 Z 世代建立真正联系的品牌提供了五个教训。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 06/how-the-best-brand-influencer-partnerships-reach-gen-z?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;如果您还没有听说过 Alix Earle，它可能只是时间问题。这位刚从迈阿密大学毕业的年轻影响者在 TikTok 上拥有超过 500 万粉丝，最近与 United Talent Agency (UTA) 签约，该公司是全球媒体和娱乐生态系统中代表人才的三大公司之一。她利用自己的个人品牌与 Tarte 和 Rare Beauty 等美容公司合作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在线观看无数的 Alix Earle 视频让她的公式非常清晰。她拥有模特般的美貌，勾选了纯粹的美感。她完善了“与我一起准备”(GRWM) 格式（以及其他格式），这是一个简短的视频，其中她从自然美到完美无瑕，展示了专业但可复制的化妆技术和产品使用。当她在“自拍”视频中应用自己的造型时，她在一段快速、轻松的独白中提供了讲故事、幽默、脆弱、抱负、相关性和产品提及的混合体。她觉得平易近人，足以成为一名普通大学生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种平易近人正是 Earle 与 Z 世代产生如此多共鸣的原因。真实性是这一代人最重要的价值观之一。作为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/board-matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-knowhttps:/www.ey.com/en_us/board -matters/why-gen-z-matters-and-what-boards-should-know&quot;>;安永最近的研究亮点&lt;/a>;：“在假新闻和过滤照片呈现‘完美生活’的时代之后，Z 世代结束了。他们觉得自己有能力在各种社交论坛上就任何主题提出和回答自己的问题——从美容到健康到家居装修再到技术再到科学。他们对权威的看法已经从传统来源（如学术机构或知名编辑的声音）扩展到感知影响力——正如 Earle 的迅速崛起所证明的那样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;研究 Alix Earle 的成功为品牌营销人员提供了五个重要的教训，告诉他们如何进入这个有影响力的时代——并与 Z 世代建立真正的联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.为您的品牌找到合适的影响者&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;简单地对顶级影响者列表进行强制排名并不是解决问题的办法。品牌希望找到能够触及目标受众的人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一旦品牌定义了他们竞争的类别，营销人员就可以寻找参与度最高、声音和风格最有影响力的人与品牌产生共鸣。人工智能和其他分析数据的工具可以帮助您解决这个问题——例如，数据分析可以揭示影响者和品牌之间的追随者、创意方法和共同社区。还有一些公司，例如 Gallery Media 和领先的人才代理机构，负责策划有影响力的人并管理更复杂的品牌关系和执行。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.为移动消费创造品牌故事&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Z 世代通过在手机上滚动浏览由算法驱动的个性化“为您”提供的照片、视频和表情包来填补他们的空闲时间。理想情况下，品牌应该授权与他们合作的有影响力的人创作简短、引人入胜且适合移动设备的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;拥抱脆弱和开放，就像厄尔在一到三分钟的短故事中所做的那样，使品牌以与个人相关且真实的方式与年轻一代建立联系。然而，品牌必须明白，这不是一个 30 秒的电视广告，影响者会按照他们自己选择的方向来讲述故事。这是对其他品牌故事的补充，而不是替代。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.激励消费者制作自己的品牌内容&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;与前几代人不同，Z 世代不会将他们的帖子“广播”到社交网络上。他们更频繁地通过“私人故事”与更少的人分享。由于这些帖子的发布频率和亲密度，参与度要高得多，并且随着这种转变，我们还看到 Z 世代不再像上一代那样在社交媒体帐户上广泛传播他们的快乐时刻，而是分享更多原始时刻，例如个人危机&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个年轻人在 TikTok 上 Earle 的 GRWM 视频中看到美容产品，随后在 Snap 上的私人故事中与他们的朋友组认可该产品就是一个例子，说明如何品牌之旅从高调的社交媒体影响力到深刻的个人影响力。品牌必须赢得进入这个神圣空间的权利，并且必须了解这些更私密场所的不透明性和新风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4.跨越界限脱颖而出&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;随着生成式和对话式 AI 大规模应用于创意环境，需要新的灵感和创造力来源才能脱颖而出。由于所有影响者现在都可以使用相同的技术来推动研究、增强创意和加速生产，因此具有前瞻性思维的品牌将寻求通过人的独创性或真正的名人来实现差异化。真正创造力的门槛只会越来越高，需要不同寻常的品牌并置或新邀请消费者共同创造。我们目前对影响力的定义可能会迅速改变，因为 AI 会同时操纵目标和驱动算法的创意。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5.避免克隆文化&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;作为营销人员，我们可能会珍惜机会，不惜一切代价通过工程趋势来推动消费，从而通过有影响力的人获得速度。但是，如果我们在这一切的科学上取得了太多成功，我们是否正在创建与我们对多样性和包容性的承诺相矛盾的趋势回声室，或者在某些社会原型中克隆重复行为？如果影响力至少依赖于原创性的表象，那么随着每个人都使用类似的 AI 驱动的见解，它会变得更难吗？品牌利用创造力和数据（或艺术和科学）的结合精确地推动他们的商业野心，但他们可能会越来越多地寻求拓宽战略以寻找新的受众、声音和灵感，从而使他们的消费者和想法基础多样化。” p>; &lt;p>;创作者经济正在蓬勃发展、富有创造力且有价值，尤其是在技术支持的经济模式激励强大的人才使其成为真正的专业人士的情况下。利用其新动力创造价值的品牌将脱颖而出并推动&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_us/cmo?WT.mc_id=14001454&amp;amp;AA.tsrc=pr&quot;>;指数级增长&lt;/一个>;。成功的关键是深入了解最新的影响力来源以及所有最新的风险和回报动态。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;本文反映的观点是作者的观点，不一定反映 Ernst &amp;amp; 的观点Young LLP or other members of the global EY organization.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI Can Help Stressed-Out Managers Be Better Coaches]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_21_1433543804.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;SvetaZi/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;更多&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;对管理者评估和指导员工的期望&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;绩效有所提高，代际更替和远程工作加剧了这一趋势。员工需要频繁、个性化、一对一的指导，但经理们却被他们本已沉重的负担所束缚。新的人工智能工具有望提高管理培训的效率和有效性——但首先，必须克服恐惧和不信任的共同根源。基于研究和案例研究，作者提出了五个步骤，以确保使用 AI 辅助教练改善管理者和员工的生活。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/how-ai-can-help-stressed-out-managers-be-better-coaches?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;中间经理们正承受来自领导者的压力，要求他们&lt;a href=&quot;https://workforceinstitute.org/our-2023-workplace-predictions/&quot;>;花更多时间培养和指导&lt;/a>;他们的直接下属。压力也来自下层，因为员工&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/all-things-work/pages/performance-management-evolves.aspx&quot;>;期望有rise&lt;/a>; 获得实时、个性化的反馈，尤其是在职业生涯早期或远程入职的人中。面临的挑战是在不导致更高水平的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup.com/workplace/357404/manager-burnout-getting-worse.aspx&quot;>;中层经理倦怠和压力&lt;/a的情况下满足这些需求>;。根据我们的研究和咨询工作，我们预见到新的 AI 工具可以让管理者更轻松、更高效地提供高质量的指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;员工需要更多指导，但管理者能力不足&lt;/h2>; &lt; p>;OC Tanner 的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octanner.com/global-culture-report/2023/leadership-at-risk.html&quot;>;2023 年全球文化调查&lt;/a>;发现，承担监督责任的领导者- 包括培训员工 - 在过去一年中增加了 21% 的焦虑率，这使倦怠的几率增加了惊人的 520%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;尽管可能会超负荷，但经理们通常希望教练他们的员工，因为他们知道这是有益的。事实上，管理培训已被证明可以提高&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/01492063211003951&quot;>;工作满意度&lt;/a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https:// bpspsychub.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/joop.12402&quot;>;知识共享&lt;/a>;，以及&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/hrdq。 21175&quot;>;绩效&lt;/a>; — 组织（和管理者！）想要的所有结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;AI 机会&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们对该领域的回顾表明，基于 AI 的管理教练是尚不普遍，因此我们提供两个案例来说明它如何在您的组织中发挥作用：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Eleos Health&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Eleos Health 是一家行为健康技术公司，Katherine 曾深入研究过她的民族志&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyt.2022.990370/full&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;的一部分。 Eleos 平台使用符合 HIPAA 标准的软件来记录和分析治疗师与客户之间的对话。除了为治疗师节省做笔记的时间外，该平台的人工智能还可以自动识别相关的循证技术，并总结治疗师与客户对话中的关键时刻。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一位治疗师解释说：“每次会议结束后， Eleos 平台分析了我使用的咨询技术并提供了有用的总结。这让我很清楚我在那个病人身上停下来的地方，以及下次我应该使用什么干预措施来最好地帮助他们。”通过这种方式，AI 平台使治疗师能够在工作中进行自主改进，而不必过于依赖主管的指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，AI 平台可以促进治疗师和治疗师之间更有用的检查点他们的主管在他们确实需要见面时。例如，它可用于在讨论复杂案例时快速合成或提取相关的客户端会话数据，减少对记忆或笔记的依赖。正如一位主管告诉凯瑟琳的那样，“新的治疗师经常有问题...... Eleos 的分析让我能够在他们的会议访问中的关键时刻归零，或者治疗师使用的技术，以及随着时间的推移患者的进步，所以我们的辅导时间&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Gong&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;第二个例子来自 Gong，它为销售团队开发了一个 AI 平台。 Gong 的平台不引人注意地捕捉了代理人和潜在客户之间的实时互动。在对话展开的同时，人工智能正在后台处理数据，检查速度、主题、语气和轮流等变量与该公司的最佳实践相比如何。这些数据用于为销售人员实时提供见解和建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，Gong 的 AI 可以自动创建一个高质量的销售对话记录示例库，作为自主学习的资源。人们发现这对新员工特别有帮助，他们可以按照自己的节奏聆听模范销售电话，而不是依赖他人的直接培训。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;确定基本的入职培训内容并为销售代表提供真实的培训销售电话中的时间建议节省了经理数小时的时间，这些时间过去常常花在听新员工的电话上，以帮助他们了解在销售过程中哪些有效，哪些无效。结果是有效的知识转移。正如一位 Gong 用户告诉我们的那样，“该平台使我能够提高自己的技能并与其他销售代表分享最佳实践。我发现通过反馈和指标进行基于 AI 的知识共享可以使整个团队不断改进。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;了解潜在的挑战&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;我们不认可任何特定的工具或公司，但我们确实鼓励人力资源和人事经理寻找可以增强其组织管理培训的人工智能选项。该领域的其他公司包括 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/aclk?sa=l&amp;amp;ai=DChcSEwiTpMbD1r3-AhUv5uMHHSv6CJkYABABGgJ5bQ&amp;amp;sig=AOD64_22a36n60RhrD3gwoHexVSlB_b0HA&amp;amp;q&amp;amp;adurl&amp;amp;ved=2ahUK Ewiy477D1r3-AhXXkYkEHSXLCgYQ0Qx6BAgIEAE&quot;>;Beamery&lt; /a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.humu.com/&quot;>;Humu&lt;/a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultureamp.com/?_gl=1*td4rop*_up *MQ..&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwi46iBhDyARIsAE3nVrY95mViC1V0iVh7byxvuAVNebyAoaKUOfSTaQAgP1hJzXQFE0X73XUaAhsGEALw_wcB&quot;>;文化放大器&lt;/a>;，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterup.com/platform &quot;>;BetterUp&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.skillsoft.com/meet-skillsoft-percipio&quot;>;Skillsoft&lt;/a>;，以及 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/ibm-transforms-人力资源-ai.aspx&quot;>;IBM&lt;/a>;。我们预计新产品将不断涌现，包括那些嵌入生成式 AI 功能的产品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当您货比三家时，评估您的员工是否准备好采用 AI 辅助教练系统。请记住，评估某人的工作并尝试改进它已经&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90753495/how-to-manage-the-anxiety-of-giving-negative-feedback&quot;>;充满情绪的过程&lt;/a>;；在组合中加入技术会加剧焦虑。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个有据可查的现象是“&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bdm.2155&quot;>;算法厌恶&lt;/a>;”：人们不愿或不愿相信算法胜过相信人的判断。当算法判断员工的&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;效能&lt;/a>;时，这可能会更有效。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;此外，引入一个新的评估来源可能会在管理者和员工之间造成社交距离，尤其是在存在偏见、透明度和隐私问题的情况下。例如，&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1002/smj.3322&quot;>;一项研究&lt;/a>;表明，员工讨厌基于 AI 的反馈，即使它在客观上有帮助，如果他们没有被告知提前他们的经理正在使用它。这项研究说明了在评估 AI 辅助教练工具时不仅要考虑成本、准确性和时间等因素的重要性，还要考虑可能影响其成功或失败的人为因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;五个步骤成功的 AI 辅助教练&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为确保 AI 辅助教练计划为员工和管理者带来最佳结果，我们建议采取以下步骤：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;建立心理安全和信任&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;数十年的研究表明，各方之间基于信任的关系对于有效的反馈和指导至关重要。这是BchVrOz9BtWnrw&quot;>;在处理 AI 的“黑匣子”时更为重要&lt;/a>;-生成的评估。例如，在一项新研究中，员工认为他们的-skills&quot;>;经理们将他们的最大利益放在心上&lt;/a>;更愿意接受人工智能生成的建议——即使是他们最初并不同意的建议。经理可以&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/make-it-safe-for-employees-to-speak-up-especially-in-risky-times&quot;>;建立心理安全感&lt;/a>;并信任该工具阐明 AI 集成的基本原理，就如何使用员工数据提供保证，并鼓励人们就问题或疑问发表意见。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;让员工参与设计和实施&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;为了获得最好的质量和最多的支持，&lt;a href=&quot;https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/ai-on-the-front-lines/&quot;>;在整个过程中包容员工至关重要探索和采用过程&lt;/a>;。 Microsoft 在最近的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/four-ways-leaders-can-empower-people-for-how-work-gets-done&quot;>;调查中发现的 4,500 名全球高管&lt;/a>;认为，让人们在技术计划中有发言权对于让他们对这些工具感到满意和参与有很大帮助。理想情况下，员工将参与到&lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3411764.3445304&quot;>;确定绩效指标&lt;/a>;和将由AI。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;让员工对其数据和参与有一定的控制权&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;让员工自主决定他们如何使用 AI 辅助教练系统有助于减轻审查和隐私问题。例如，Eleos Health 的平台允许临床医生选择不使用该平台进行特定的患者治疗。另一种推荐的方法是形成一个包容员工的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/technology/pages/hr-gets-help-vetting-ai-tools.aspx&quot;>; AI 治理委员会&lt;/a>;，以确保收集哪些数据、如何使用这些数据以及采取哪些保护措施来保护员工隐私的透明度。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;简化和自定义输出&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;通常，AI 工具允许管理人员自定义生成的数据显示和分析；我们建议组织充分利用这些功能。例如，在推出之初，将输出重点放在几个性能指标上可能会有所帮助，直到人们对工具感到更满意为止。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;经理还可以自定义反馈的质量，以反映特定的员工需求——例如，通过让输出提供operations-performance&quot;>;在员工入职期间提供更令人鼓舞的反馈&lt;/a>;。在一项&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0022242920956676&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;中，AI 辅导工具被发现对中等技能的员工最有效，因为技能较低的员工有时会发现反馈太多（建议太多），而技能更高的员工有时会发现反馈缺乏细微差别。员工需要的是个性化指导，因此选择一种足够灵活的 AI 工具以适应组织中的各种人员和情况非常重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;集中培训管理人员&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;许多管理人员可以受益于&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/most-managers-dont-know-how-to-coach-people-but-they-can-learn&quot;>;有效教练的基础培训&lt;/a>;，包括如何在这个过程中嵌入真正的同理心和同情心。集成人工智能工具将需要额外的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/technology-skills-employees-should-have-fdc6c0ba&quot;>;管理人员技能提升&lt;/a>;。他们不仅应该接受技术知识方面的培训，还应该接受如何灵敏且胜任地将人工智能生成的数据翻译给员工的培训。通过提供实践案例和其他形式的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogs.yu.edu/facultynews/wp-content/uploads/sites/13/2022/05/Flaherty_2022_J -of-SW-Education.pdf&quot;>;体验式学习&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;人工智能工具特别有望在不增加管理人员负担的情况下提高教练的频率、个性化和准确性。但是，无法保证这些收益。 To be successful, it&#39;s critical to integrate AI technology in a way that leads to a better &lt;em>;human&lt;/em>; experience for both managers and employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Where Religious Identity Fits into Your DEI Strategy]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄形象>; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/05/Jun23_03_1383510658.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;哈佛商业评论员工/golero/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot; >; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司通常避免在工作中承认宗教差异，因为他们担心这样做会带来法律风险。这是短视的。人们的宗教身份是多样性的一种形式，因此宗教必须成为任何公司 DEI 战略的一部分。这七个最佳实践将帮助公司拥抱宗教多样性。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious- identity-fits-into-your-dei-strategy?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/where-religious-identity-fits-into-your-dei -strategy?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;现在是公司树立信仰的时候了。即使多元化工作在企业文化中变得普遍，宗教身份也经常被排除在外。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;对财富 100 强&lt;/a>;公司的审查表明，只有极少数公司将宗教或跨信仰参与纳入其实现多元化的方法中。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多公司出于对法律纠纷的恐惧，或者担心它可能会打开传教和分歧的闸门，而回避这种参与。但是，将宗教纳入您的 DEI 工作可以在员工之间建立归属感，并帮助他们更好地服务于更广泛的客户。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;最近的研究&lt;/a>;和实践表明，尊重宗教身份不仅可以提高员工敬业度，而且还能带来员工以外的好处&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是公司应采用的七个最佳实践，以积极参与工作场所的宗教多样性并从中受益。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;将您的心态从“宗教是一种风险”转变为“宗教是一种资产。”&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gallup-international.bg/en/36009/religion-prevails-in-the-world/&quot;>;62%世人自称有宗教信仰&lt;/a>;，更有人说信神。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgespan.org/getmedia/0952bd65-31a2-4d9a-97b0-5926ef1f48e6/elevating-the-role-of-faith-inspired-impact-in-the-social-sector-jan -2021.pdf&quot;>;77% 的美国人表示宗教在他们的生活中非常重要或有些重要&lt;/a>;。大约 30% -sector-jan-2021.pdf&quot;>;美国的社会部门组织有信仰&lt;/a>;，并为所有宗教或非宗教背景的人提供重要服务。与此同时，由于&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justice.gov/crs/highlights/2021-hate-crime-statistics&quot;>;全国范围内与宗教相关的仇恨犯罪呈上升趋势&lt;/a>;，许多美国人认为宗教是一个不适合工作场所的话题，认为人际冲突、同事之间的紧张关系、安全问题和法律冲突是可能的结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，公开承认宗教多样性并将其视为一种资产的公司，可以增强团队凝聚力，提高绩效。例如，根据 &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/redi-index-2023&quot;>;2023 年宗教股权多元化和包容性报告，埃森哲被指定为全球 500 强“对信仰友好的公司” (REDI) Index&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;.&lt;/u>; Accenture 提供包容性假期政策和宗教扫盲培训等标志。在第一届年度 &lt;a href=&quot;https://marriott.byu.edu/event/faithatworkcomp/speakers&quot;>;Faith &amp;amp; Belief @ Work 案例竞赛&lt;/a>;，2 月在杨百翰大学举行，埃森哲全球变革管理负责人 Sumreen Ahmed，&lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/2/post/2023/02/ four-areas-where-the-impact-of-faith-in-systems-cannot-be-ignored.html&quot;>;谈到参与宗教多样性的力量&lt;/a>;：“如果领导者想要创造一个环境，让人们他们不仅受到激励来工作，而且为了更大的利益而茁壮成长，他们需要从了解最重要的事情开始。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将宗教视为一种资产并给予员工许可 &lt;a href= &quot;/2022/09/how-to-talk-about-religion-at-work&quot;>;在工作中谈论宗教&lt;/a>;是利用宗教多样性力量的第一步。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;阐明在公司内部促进宗教多元化的明确指导方针。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;美国人说他们&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prri.org/spotlight/corporate-america-leads-in-exposing-americans- to-diversity/&quot;>;在工作中遇到宗教多样性&lt;/a>;比在他们生活的任何其他领域都多。正如我们在此讨论的那样，工作场所中的不同身份和观点&lt;em>;可以&lt;/em>;带来更强大的团队和更好的成果，但如果参与不当，它们也会导致误解和冲突。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;工作中的宗教包容必须尊重所有员工的尊严：选择表达其宗教身份的员工、声称没有宗教身份的员工以及选择不公开其宗教身份的员工。制定一套详细说明公司如何参与宗教活动的原则，可以减轻反宗教或宗教间的偏见，防止潜在的人际紧张局势升级，并鼓励以创新方式激活宗教多样性，造福所有人。创建框架的技巧包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;将框架与现有的公司价值观联系起来&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;强调宗教认同和多样性的积极贡献&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;承认支持在工作场所表达宗教身份&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;建立护栏以确保不同群体之间的平等待遇&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;鼓励跨宗教、精神和世俗身份的合作机会&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;提升为员工提供专业发展资源，以加深对不同宗教传统的了解&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Intuit 的 DEI ERG 负责人 Cecilia Persson-Ramos 去年夏天主动采用了一套原则来指导公司的 &lt;a href =&quot;https://www.intuit.com/blog/life-at-intuit/building-inclusion-empowering-confidence-through-religious-accommodations/&quot;>;基于信仰的 ERG&lt;/a>;。这些原则包括对每个 ERG 的支持，因为它遵守其特定的宗教习俗，同时还鼓励 ERG 在协作活动中相互合作。 “我们已经开始看到影响，”她告诉我们。 “成员感到自己被看到和听到，并且为了整个社区的利益而加强合作。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;培养宗教素养以承认宗教多样性。&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;公司可以通过培养眼光来发展业务与宗教表达有关的问题。问问 Martha Moore，她开发了 &lt;a href=&quot;https://about.nike.com/en/newsroom/releases/nike-victory-swim-collection-official-images-and-release-date&quot;>;Nike Victory Swim收集&lt;/a>; 在注意到穆斯林妇女在海滩度假时坐在岸边而不是下水之后。她&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/culture/on-and-off-the-avenue/nike-takes-the-plunge-into-modest-swimwear&quot;>;发现了一个市场&lt;/a>;通过关注为全球数亿穆斯林女性购买适度的泳装，并因此为耐克创造了数百万美元的收入。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;满足特定宗教社区的需求也可以提升品牌知名度并在一部分客户中建立忠诚度。例如，Google 提供了一个&lt;a href=&quot;https://qiblafinder.withgoogle.com/intl/en/desktop/finder&quot;>;qibla finder&lt;/a>; 来帮助世界各地的穆斯林&lt;a href=&quot;https ://www.whyislam.org/kaba/&quot;>;前往沙特阿拉伯的天房&lt;/a>;，因为他们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/uae/why-do- muslims-pray-five-times-a-day-and-what-does-it-signify/articleshow/94053372.cms?from=mdr&quot;>;每日五次祈祷&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在同时，忽视承认工作中的宗教表达会导致法律后果。 In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/faces-eeoc-samantha-elauf&quot;>;EEOC v. Abercrombie&lt;/a>;, the Supreme Court ruled 8–1 in favor of Samantha Elauf, the young Muslim woman who wasn&#39;t offered a job at an Abercrombie store in Tulsa, OK because &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/02/us/supreme-court-rules-in-samantha-elauf-abercrombie-fitch-case.html&quot;>;her hijab didn&#39;t comply with Abercrombie&#39;s “look policy&lt;/a>;.”&amp;nbsp;In the majority opinion, &lt;a href=&quot;https://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/575/14-86/#tab-opinion-3413626&quot;>;Justice Scalia held&lt;/a>; that it is incumbent upon the employer to know when an article of clothing is related to religious expression.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies are responsible, under the law, for equipping team members with the skills to effectively recognize and accommodate religious identity in the workplace. More than that, having an eye for religious diversity can lead to new product development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Know the law — but not for the reasons you think.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Risk is frequently cited as one of the biggest barriers to religious engagement for C-suite leaders. However, not engaging religious identity as part of corporate culture is the riskier choice. Provided that is pursued in a respectful and equitable manner, the benefits for a company in openly engaging religious identity at work outweigh the risks of breaking what some see as a &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.vanderbilt.edu/handle/1803/17502&quot;>;“church-state” firewall&lt;/a>;, or the secular tone of the corporate setting&lt;strong>;. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Andrea Lucas, a commissioner at the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/eeoc-commissioner-andrea-lucas&quot;>;is an outspoken advocate&lt;/a>; for engaging religious identity in the workplace as the best way to avoid a lawsuit. The EEOC&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/laws/guidance/section-12-religious-discrimination&quot;>;Compliance Manual on Religious Discrimination&lt;/a>; offers up-to-date guidelines and practical case studies to support business leaders as they navigate tricky issues related to religion at work. According to Lucas, it&#39;s companies that avoid religious identity that end up in challenging positions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies should advocate for education around legal risks and remedies and seek ways that religious inclusion can be a brand builder, not a risk minefield.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Provide meaningful and flexible accommodations for employees&#39; diverse religious practices.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many aspects of religious expression intersect with company policies, like time off and scheduling. Here&#39;s how some companies have provided accommodations:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Holidays:&lt;/strong>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/are-non-christian-employees-represented-in-your-holiday-policies&quot;>;When creating time off policies&lt;/a>;, companies can offer floating holidays, giving employees the flexibility to choose which holidays are meaningful to them, whether religious or secular. &lt;a href=&quot;https://static.googleusercontent.com/media/about.google/en/belonging/diversity-annual-report/2023/static/pdfs/google_2023_diversity_annual_report.pdf?cachebust=d0bd616&quot;>;Google took it one step further&lt;/a>; and made an inclusive scheduling guide for employees on accommodating diverse religious practices.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Dietary restrictions:&lt;/strong>; Adherence to different religious traditions often includes dietary restrictions: Some Hindus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/07/08/eight-in-ten-indians-limit-meat-in-their-diets-and-four-in-ten-consider-themselves-vegetarian/#:~:text=For%20example%2C%20Hindu%20texts%20often,teachings%2C%20meanwhile%2C%20prohibit%20pork&quot;>;do not eat beef&lt;/a>;, some Muslims and Jews &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sun-sentinel.com/2016/07/07/halal-or-kosher-no-pork-muslims-and-jews-have-common-ground/&quot;>;do not eat pork&lt;/a>;, some Mormons &lt;a href=&quot;https://pacific.churchofjesuschrist.org/why-mormons-dont-drink-alcohol-tea-and-coffee#:~:text=In%20the%20Word%20of%20Wisdom,see%20D%26C%2089%3A8).&quot;>;do not drink caffeine or alcohol&lt;/a>;, and some Buddhists &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/buddhist-diet&quot;>;are vegetarian&lt;/a>;. At Interfaith America, we gather dietary restrictions during the onboarding process, which are then populated into a shared document available to all managers who order food for work events.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Spaces for observance:&lt;/strong>; Companies can provide a designated prayer or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workitdaily.com/things-didnt-know-working-nike/3-you-re-given-summer-fridays&quot;>;meditation space&lt;/a>; in the office for employees of any faith or tradition to pray or reflect. For example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ibtimes.com/keep-faith-work-3685588&quot;>;Texas Instruments provides 24/7 access to serenity rooms&lt;/a>; at several of their campuses.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;Offer ongoing religious diversity skill-building opportunities for all employees.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Rev. David Keck, chaplain at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University in Daytona Beach, Florida, tells the story of a fellow faculty member who, when he was a commercial pilot, was alerted by his crew before takeoff to a man who was moving his body rhythmically and speaking a foreign language. Rather than succumb to knee-jerk racial profiling and/or anti-religious bias, the pilot drew on his religious literacy to ascertain that the man was simply praying with his whole body, as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.myjewishlearning.com/article/physical-movement-in-jewish-prayer/&quot;>;Orthodox Jews &lt;/a>;(and many others!) do daily. The pilot reassured his crew and the flight took off as scheduled. Keck prompts the students in his Religion, Conflict, and Peace class to imagine how the story would have turned out differently — and likely led to unfavorable news headlines — had the pilot not been familiar with Jewish prayer practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From interns to senior executives, employees across every sector need skills and knowledge to engage religious diversity to be successful in their roles. Sixty percent of companies in North America &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benefitscanada.com/news/bencan/68-of-north-american-employers-have-a-formal-dei-program-survey/#:~:text=More%20than%20two%2Dthirds%20(68,surveys%20by%20Leger%20Marketing%20Inc.&quot;>;offer regular diversity &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benefitscanada.com/news/bencan/68-of-north-american-employers-have-a-formal-dei-program-survey/#:~:text=More%20than%20two%2Dthirds%20(68,surveys%20by%20Leger%20Marketing%20Inc.&quot;>;trainings&lt;/a>; for their employees, but few include a robust focus on religion. Best practice pedagogy from Interfaith America&#39;s 20-year history of training and equipping leaders to engage religious diversity includes case studies, storytelling, and practical application to inspire and equip team members for success.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Upskilling a company&#39;s workforce to meaningfully engage religious diversity in a nuanced and constructive way will pay dividends across the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Support interfaith ERGs and other employee-led efforts to engage religious diversity.&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.interfaithbusinessnetwork.com/podcast/episode-2&quot;>;Interfaith Employee Resource Groups (ERGs&lt;/a>;&lt;u>;)&lt;/u>; are one important tool for creating an inclusive workplace culture. According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://religiousfreedomandbusiness.org/redi-index-2023&quot;>;2023 REDI Index&lt;/a>;, only 8.6% of Fortune 500 companies publicly report having faith-oriented ERGs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salesforce&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.salesforce.com/company/equality/equality-groups/#eq-sf-fh&quot;>;Faithforce&lt;/a>; is one example of a best-in-class employee-led interfaith effort to build belonging across diverse identities. From the beginning, Faithforce leadership made it clear that their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.salesforce.com/blog/faith-inclusion-workplace/&quot;>;goal was not proselytizing or politics&lt;/a>;, but focused instead on engaging religion as part of the company&#39;s diversity efforts. Farah Siddiqui, cofounder and global president of Faithforce from 2017 to 2021 (and now supporting faith inclusion at Google) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.interfaithamerica.org/religion-at-work-how-to-get-dei-right/&quot;>;shares lessons learned&lt;/a>; with leaders looking to jumpstart interfaith engagement in their workplaces.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Hallmarks of high-impact interfaith ERGs include:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;A clear charter naming what it is and is not appropriate behavior&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.equinix.com/blog/2023/05/05/equinix-faithconnect-welcomes-those-from-all-beliefs/&quot;>;Celebrations of religious holidays&lt;/a>; to support team members and educate others&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Events focused on &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.aa.com/american-stories/american-stories-details/2017/Faith-and-Love-Religious-diversity-groups-find-common-message-during-roundtable-discussion/default.aspx&quot;>;exploring shared values&lt;/a>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Resources explaining diverse religious traditions&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Community collaborations &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/729586950?embedded=true&amp;amp;source=vimeo_logo&amp;amp;owner=56118460&quot;>;in response to a humanitarian crisis&lt;/a>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;American corporations have long sought to avoid religious engagement in the workplace, fearing legal risks and the unfamiliar terrain of engaging the multiplicity of religious traditions in an ever-increasingly diverse workforce. By proactively engaging religious diversity at work, companies prevent crises, broaden brand loyalty, strengthen company culture, and increase team cohesion and effectiveness.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You Frustrated with Your Team&rsquo;s Ability to Solve Problems?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/are-you-frustrated-with-your-teams-ability-to-solve-problems]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/June23_21_200116808.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Yellow Dog Productions/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Often when you feel like your team isn&amp;#8217;t working together to effectively problem solve, it&amp;#8217;s because you don&amp;#8217;t understand various team member&amp;#8217;s problem-solving styles. The author, who has studied how people make decisions for 30 years, has identified five archetypes she calls problem-solving profiles. Adventurers are optimistic, confident and tend to go with their gut reactions. Detectives like to follow the data. Listeners are more collaborative and want to solicit others&amp;#8217; input. Thinkers are cautious and like to identify multiple paths forward. Visionaries pride themselves on seeing pathways that other&amp;#8217;s don&amp;#8217;t. Understanding your team&amp;#8217;s problem-solving profiles will help identify tensions you may be feeling, reduce friction and modify behavior to get your decision-making back on track.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/are-you-frustrated-with-your-teams-ability-to-solve-problems?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/are-you-frustrated-with-your-teams-ability-to-solve-problems?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Evelyn, the chief executive of an eco-conscious hospitality company, had flown with her senior leadership team to visit their Costa Rica operations. A hotel that could give the company access to a more upscale market was up for sale, and the head of the local office wanted to move quickly on the opportunity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, once the team was assembled on location, it quickly became apparent that the Costa Rica branch had some puzzling financial data that the Denver-based headquarters team hadn&#39;t been fully aware of. Sitting with her chief financial officer, head of retail, and head of new business development, Evelyn wanted to move quickly through the financials so that they could jump on this exciting new opportunity — and she was frustrated that she was the only one talking. She wanted to hear from the team, but they were keeping quiet. The team needed clarity before they could move ahead with a significant financial purchase, and Evelyn felt that her team wasn&#39;t effectively working together to solve the problem.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s not uncommon for managers to find themselves in a situation similar to Evelyn&#39;s. This often results from team members&#39; conflicting decision-making styles. We tend to like to work with people who think – and problem-solve – like we do, reinforcing our own cognitive biases and blind spots, and unwittingly discouraging true, creative problem solving.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I&#39;ve spent 30 years studying how people make decisions and have identified&lt;a href=&quot;https://app.areamethod.com/&quot;>; five different decision-making archetypes&lt;/a>;, which I call problem solver profiles (PSPs). As I describe in my book&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Problem-Solver-Maximizing-Strengths-Publications/dp/1501768034/ref=sr_1_1?crid=1TZOS4HMW4TL5&amp;amp;keywords=cheryl+strauss+einhorn+problem+solver&amp;amp;qid=1657549920&amp;amp;sprefix=cheryl+strauss+einhorn%2Caps%2C67&amp;amp;sr=8-1&quot;>; &lt;em>;Problem Solver: Maximizing Your Strengths to Make Better Decisions&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;, these PSPs are personal approaches built from our individual strengths and weaknesses. Once we gain awareness of our own and our team members&#39; profiles, we can take steps to become more dynamic, flexible decision-makers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Five Problem-Solver Profiles&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We tend to see the strengths of our own decision-making patterns and the weaknesses of others&#39;. But every problem solver profile has unique strengths and weaknesses; these cognitive biases are two-sides of the same coin. Of course, many of us can be more than one type of problem solver, but in almost all cases we lean on one dominant approach. Below are the five problem solver profiles and how a few of their cognitive biases can help or hurt their decision performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Adventurers&lt;/strong>; tend to go with their gut reactions. This optimistic and confident decision-maker often finds the future more interesting than the present. Their optimism bias helps their ability to quickly make many decisions — but it can also skew their assessment of the quality of the decision they face.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Detectives&lt;/strong>; like to follow the data. This evidence-based decision-maker intrepidly searches out the data so that it will lead them somewhere. Yet, their draw to research and facts can also lead them to a confirmation bias that the data is the most important criteria in their current decision. For example, focused on the data, they may miss out on collaborating well with others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Listeners&lt;/strong>; want to solicit others&#39; input. This collaborative and trusting decision-maker works well with their colleagues. However, they often suffer from a liking bias that can make it difficult to tune into their own opinion or to express a viewpoint that might be at odds with others.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Thinkers&lt;/strong>; thrive on identifying multiple paths and outcomes. This thoughtful, cautious decision-maker likes to know their options. Their desire to understand the “why” behind a decision can impede their ability to evaluate each option individually as they may fall victim to a frame blindness that limits how they see and understand the problem they are solving.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Visionaries&lt;/strong>; pride themselves on seeing pathways that others don&#39;t. This creative, original decision-maker has a big vision, but they may fall prey to scarcity bias, preferring to seek out a unique solution rather than the obvious solution right before him.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From this very brief overview, you can see how various combinations of PSPs will interact differently. For example, a thinker and an adventurer may effectively counter each others&#39; cognitive biases, but they might also experience friction in the ways they go about problem solving. A team of visionaries or detectives, on the other hand, may be comfortable working together, but may also amplify each other&#39;s weaknesses. Visionaries are great at coming up with new ideas, but struggle to vet these ideas, while detectives may find a lot of evidence to test their assumptions; once they have the data, however, they are ready to move forward without bringing in the other stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Since Evelyn and her team had just completed a professional development workshop, each had identified their PSP. Evelyn knew that she is an adventurer, full of ideas, always thinking ahead, and ready to move forward quickly. But she remembered that morning in Costa Rica that her CFO was a thinker, and the retail leader, new business development chief, and head of Costa Rica&#39;s operations were all listeners. Together they formed a thoughtful and collaborative team — but one that moved relatively slowly, wanting to have time to explore different options and their implications and to come to a consensus-driven decision.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Evelyn realized that her team had fallen into a pattern where she spoke first, offering her favored decision and looking for confirmation from her team — adventurers feel comfortable getting started. She expected the others to behave like adventurers too, moving quickly based on their own skill sets. But when the team was faced with a situation where they needed to drill down into the data, Evelyn&#39;s gut reaction came into conflict with the slower and more methodical decision-making of the thinker and listeners on her team.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Evelyn decided to modify her own behavior, holding back on being the first to speak in order to uplift her team&#39;s ability to work well together. The result: They surfaced questions about the financials that Evelyn hadn&#39;t thought to ask.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Evelyn had started out feeling frustrated, and thinking that her team was the problem. By taking the time to apply her knowledge of problem solver profiles, she was able to identify the causes of the tension she was feeling, and recognized that her decision-making approach had been a barrier to effective problem solving. She could then reframe the problem, thereby reducing the friction and get decision making on track in a way that all team members could contribute positively. Ultimately, the company decided not to pursue a new purchase, but instead to focus on getting the Costa Rica branch on a more solid financial footing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Evelyn had been selected for her job &lt;em>;because&lt;/em>; of her adventurer characteristics; they are part of her personality as someone who gets things done. But she needed to stop expecting that her management team would behave exactly like her. By stepping back and seeing her team&#39;s strengths rather than their weaknesses, she was able to more effectively lead the company.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many managers face this same challenge. Reframing — as Evelyn did — can improve your team, your work relationships, and your leadership. Using PSPs to understand different decision-making patterns will help you examine your own decision-making approach, as well as the diversity of decision-making styles and dynamics that arise in your team&#39;s decision-making. With this foundation, you can adjust your approach to more effectively work with others to make better big decisions together.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:25:05 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Collaboration Technology Is the Key to Better Planning and Sourcing - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM WORKDAY]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/06/collaboration-technology-is-the-key-to-better-planning-and-sourcing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-359057&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/HBRSourcingAds-CollaborativeTechnology-Hero-1200x675-1.png&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Collaboration Technology: The Key to Better Planning and Sourcing&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Financial planning and analysis (FP&amp;amp;A) and sourcing teams across industry sectors are struggling to deal with a global supply chain disrupted by a triple whammy of ongoing challenges from the pandemic, rising energy costs, and stubbornly high inflation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Supply chain volatility and economic uncertainty have magnified the need for enterprises to deploy collaboration tools that eliminate operational silos and streamline procurement. Many future-focused organizations are adopting cloud-based sourcing and planning software to facilitate real-time planning, budgeting, and stakeholder collaboration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Overcoming operational constraints&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The inability of internal and external stakeholders to collaborate on a shared data set is a primary reason for the misalignment of operational and financial planning and sourcing. Many organizations use legacy solutions that rely on manual and inefficient processes for planning and sourcing, which can result in siloed information systems that impede growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bridging these data gaps can help facilitate cross-disciplinary cooperation and can drive positive outcomes. In a recent &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/pdfs/comm/workday/OptimizingTheSupplyChainByAligningThePlanningAndSourcingFunctions.pdf&quot;>;Harvard Business Review (HBR) Analytic Services survey&lt;/a>; of financial planning and procurement executives, 51% of respondents said better data integration results in more accurate budget forecasting and reduces overspending.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Siloed organizational information systems are significant hurdles to collaboration between FP&amp;amp;A and sourcing teams. In addition to needing integrated technology platforms, the organizational structures themselves may need realignment, as having the planning and sourcing teams report to different department heads inhibits collaboration, 47% of survey respondents said.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Collaboration bottlenecks can hurt an organization&#39;s supply chain resilience. In service industries, accurate forecasting of employment levels directly affects the sourcing of office space and equipment. For manufacturers and retailers, disconnects between planning and sourcing can result in overspending on inventory or getting the wrong inventory to the wrong place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Updating legacy solutions&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Planning and sourcing teams need cloud-based technology in place of cumbersome legacy supply chain management tools, such as manually updated spreadsheets and email chains.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Automation can enable sourcing departments to ensure that operations teams have the information they need for purchases that reflect negotiated savings and price caps. Real-time procurement data can also help FP&amp;amp;A teams update their plans and budgets to reflect constantly changing market conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Among the survey respondents from high-performing organizations, 42% said their planning and sourcing functions share real-time access to the same data. The organizations that best facilitate their collaboration have made strategic commitments to using the best available technology solutions. “They really put their money where their mouth is in terms of gaining visibility across their operations,” says &lt;a href=&quot;https://haslam.utk.edu/people/profile/chad-autry/&quot;>;Chad Autry&lt;/a>;, professor of supply chain management at the University of Tennessee.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Solutions designed to enable stakeholder engagement and cooperation can pay big dividends. Many companies that invest in collaboration-enabling technology are gaining a competitive advantage, as facilitating seamless data sharing improves their efficiency and reduces their costs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;Helping companies solve real-world problems&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Organizations can customize their cloud-native sourcing and planning platforms for specific customer needs and scale them up or down as needed. Easily configurable frameworks enable organizations to deploy and manage their own platforms—so they can make changes without rewriting code or starting over.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Enterprises investing in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workday.com/en-us/products/spend-management/strategic-sourcing.html?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIjenVtPTb_gIVkxJlCh37yQ2-EAAYAiAAEgKmOvD_BwE&amp;amp;eid=enus_ppc_gg_gg_spmgt_fileat_web_20.1975&amp;amp;utm_medium=ppc&amp;amp;utm_source=gg&amp;amp;productfocus=spmgt&amp;amp;aud=fileat&amp;amp;assettype=web&amp;amp;assetid=20.1975&amp;amp;pblr=gg&amp;amp;ef_id=EAIaIQobChMIjenVtPTb_gIVkxJlCh37yQ2-EAAYAiAAEgKmOvD_BwE:G:s&amp;amp;s_kwcid=AL!8892!3!599852364149!b!!g!!strategic%20sourcing&amp;amp;_bt=599852364149&amp;amp;_bk=strategic%20sourcing&amp;amp;_bm=b&amp;amp;_bn=g&amp;amp;_bg=142252694332&quot;>;strategic sourcing&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workday.com/en-us/products/adaptive-planning/overview.html&quot;>;planning&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a>;solutions need a platform that is open, extensible, and interoperable, enabling connectivity with other productivity applications and collaboration tools. It&#39;s also important to implement technology that uses machine learning to optimize workflows and analyze real-time data for actionable business insights.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At any organization, the optimal technology should reflect its unique supply chain needs and processes and should be easy to implement and use. Successful automation reflects an enterprise&#39;s planning, sourcing, and financial processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workday.com/en-us/customer-stories/ip/ntt-global-sourcing-data-insights-meet-stakeholders-needs.html&quot;>;NTT Global Sourcing&lt;/a>; replaced its legacy workflow processes with strategic sourcing software that facilitates a source-to-contract system to provide real-time insights into projected savings. The platform streamlines collaboration with internal and external stakeholders, enables shared workflows using a common data set, and provides a dependable audit trail.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Improving collaboration between planning and sourcing teams leads to improved supply chain resilience and better efficiency. Organizations may know when new technology is working when their planning and sourcing groups no longer rely on traditional manual methods of communicating and collaborating.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“When planning and sourcing are well integrated and working from the same data, good things happen,” says &lt;a href=&quot;https://gufaculty360.georgetown.edu/s/contact/0031Q000027S70cQAC/linda-dunn&quot;>;Linda Dunn&lt;/a>;, assistant professor of supply chain management at Georgetown University. “You have a stronger understanding of your suppliers, facilitating good supplier relationship management.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Improving the alignment between your organization&#39;s planning and sourcing teams can help you improve your operational efficiency and reduce your costs. Better supply chain risk management capabilities can also help your FP&amp;amp;A and strategic sourcing teams act faster and more efficiently, enabling more efficient sourcing, production, and distribution—as well as growth and leadership in your sector during a fast-evolving economic climate.&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;For more detailed insights on the benefits of strategic sourcing and collaboration technology, download the HBR–Analytic Services research report “&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;a href=&quot;/resources/pdfs/comm/workday/OptimizingTheSupplyChainByAligningThePlanningAndSourcingFunctions.pdf&quot;>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;Optimizing the Supply Chain by Aligning the Planning and Sourcing Functions&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/a>;&lt;strong>;&lt;em>;.”&lt;/em>;&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Are You Ready to Become a Manager?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_1094310820.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Rawpixel/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;When you&amp;#8217;re working toward a promotion to a management position, proving that you&amp;#8217;re ready is just one part of the process. To be a strong manager, you need to be a problem-solver at the highest level. It&amp;#8217;s essential to uncover what you don&amp;#8217;t know yet. In addition to assembling tangible examples that demonstrate your managerial credentials, take an objective assessment of the gaps in your experience, knowledge, and management skills. To determine which skills and knowledge you need to improve or develop to become an effective first-time manager, ask yourself these 10 questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/are-you-ready-to-become-a-manager?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Transitioning into management for the first time is a significant career milestone. I can still remember the precise moment when I learned that I would lead a team. I had patiently, but persistently, pursued my promotion. I strategically changed jobs to put myself on an expedited track to management at a large firm with a great reputation. I was convinced I was ready. After I celebrated the announcement of my ascent to management, I quickly discovered that I had a lot to learn.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My decision to pursue a promotion began with analyzing the leadership landscape at my workplace. I started mentally comparing my own strengths and accomplishments with theirs.&amp;nbsp;I found myself thinking about occasions when I&#39;d been publicly praised by someone important about the impact of my work, or of moments when someone thanked me privately for completing a significant task.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a career coach, I hear similar stories from the professionals I support who are actively pursuing promotions. Your results, abilities, and external validations matter. But to become an effective manager, it&#39;s essential to uncover what you don&#39;t know yet. In addition to assembling tangible examples that demonstrate your managerial credentials, take an objective assessment of the gaps in your experience, knowledge, and management skills.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I say this with emphasis, not to hold you back, but to propel you forward. To be a strong manager, you need to be a problem-solver at the highest level. As you prepare for your next step, I want you to think beyond proving you&#39;re ready for a promotion. I want you to be proactive in creating a career-growth plan that will enable you to navigate the transition and continue to learn in your promoted role.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;My work as a career coach is centered on asking questions, reflecting on the responses, identifying gaps and weaknesses, and coming up with steps to address them. As a first step, the self-assessment questions I draw upon in coaching sessions can start to ignite ideas and illuminate challenges. To determine which skills and knowledge you need to improve or develop to become an effective first-time manager, ask yourself these 10 questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Management Skills&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;What&#39;s my leadership style?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Your leadership style derives from a mix of your strengths, personality, and values coupled with your vision and goals. Reflect on each of these components and then decide what you want to be known for. Remember, you can adapt your approach over time as you continue to learn and advance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How can I help my team develop?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Understanding how to measure performance and assess gaps and growth opportunities on your team will be essential in your role as a manager. Take time to think about how your promotion may impact team structures and dynamics. Brainstorm potential opportunities to play a key role in developing the team.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How will I prioritize and delegate work effectively?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;I&#39;m frequently asked to support managers who are struggling to meet competing demands. Learning how to prioritize and delegate effectively will make or break your success as a team leader. This will take time to figure out. As you do, continue to ask yourself questions like: What will I need to stop doing? What will I need to do more of? What will I need to maintain? How will I provide oversight and accountability?&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Am I a good public speaker, and can I lead meetings?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;How you communicate as a manager is a key driver for how you assign work, drive engagement, and share information with multiple stakeholders. This is often done via meetings. As you prepare to take the next step into management, do an honest appraisal of your communication skills and assess your comfort level when it comes to leading meetings and presenting to larger groups.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How do I deliver constructive feedback and resolve conflict?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Providing guidance, addressing performance gaps, and solving problems are important managerial responsibilities. Consider issues you may have witnessed with coworkers regarding processes, projects, or interpersonal dynamics. What did you learn from what you observed? What skills will you need to manage performance and resolve conflict if the need arises?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Knowledge&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;What are your company&#39;s policies for health, safety, and regulatory requirements?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Your company&#39;s HR team will take the lead in ensuring employees undergo necessary training on company policies, but now&#39;s a great time to familiarize yourself with your employee handbook and HR resources. As a manager, your team members will come to you with questions, and you&#39;ll be responsible for helping ensure company-wide compliance with protocols and policies.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Am I familiar with state and federal employment legislation?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Again, your HR team will be responsible for employment law guidance that impacts how you work, and it&#39;s smart to familiarize yourself with company guides and to keep up to date with any relevant news or discussions of legislative changes. A prime example of rapidly changing regulations occurred during the pandemic when the US federal, state, and local governments introduced new Covid-19 workplace protections to safeguard the health and safety of workers.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;How will I handle queries related to the company&#39;s compensation strategy, profit sharing, benefits, and equity planning?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As an employee, understanding the composition of your paycheck is important. As a manager who&#39;s responsible for a team, you&#39;ll likely receive queries from team members related to compensation, benefits, and time policies. Following your promotion to a management role, you&#39;ll need to be prepared for confidential conversations that may include eligibility for overtime pay for exempt and nonexempt employees, financial data from fiscal year cycles, open enrollment periods for benefits, and company protocols for compensation decisions.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Have I participated in the full recruitment process?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;As a manager, you&#39;ll be required to participate in the execution of staffing plans. The full cycle of recruitment ranges from assessing needs and creating job descriptions to selecting candidates, extending offers, and onboarding new hires. If a promotion will signal your first time participating in the recruitment process, be prepared to ask your HR team for guidance on procedures and best practices.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Do I know the latest diversity, equity, and inclusion best practices?&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Understanding if your organization has DEI guidelines or resources will help you answer questions or clarify processes you&#39;ll oversee in your role. In addition, you can continue to track broader DEI developments and news that may impact your new responsibilities. A current example is the rollout of new salary transparency laws to address pay equity in an increasing number of states, including Rhode Island, Washington, New York, and California.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Pursuing a promotion effectively is about more than just landing a new title. It&#39;s a valuable opportunity to consider the strengths, traits, expertise, and knowledge that will support you, as well as the weaknesses, skills gaps, and lack of exposure that could make you less effective in the long run. With an objective assessment, you can create actionable next steps to set you up for future managerial success.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Chief Data and AI Officers Are Set Up to Fail]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/06/why-chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/06/Jun23_20_107253611.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Paseika/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;With the explosion of generative AI and other powerful new data tools, chief data and artificial intelligence officers (CDAIOs) are more important than ever as companies navigate this new landscape. Too many, however, are set up to fail by poor alignment, lack of trust, not enough focus on business opportunities, and how their job is understood internally. There are five steps companies can take to better set their CDAIOs up for success: 1) make data everyone&amp;#8217;s business, 2) make business leaders data champions, 3) review all data and AI investments to make sure the money is well spent, 4) shift to an ecosystem mindset, and 5) proceed with caution.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/why-chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/why-chief-data-and-ai-officers-are-set-up-to-fail?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;This year, the already tenuous roles of the chief data, analytics, and AI officer (CDO/CDAO/CDAIO) have become even more precarious. Many companies have seen departures and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/cios-meet-your-new-colleagues-chief-data-analytics-and-ai-officers-af6b58b9&quot;>;recalibration&lt;/a>; of corporate data and AI leadership responsibilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These roles are still relatively new. The CDO job was established at big banks in response to the financial crises of 2008–2009, and was subsequently extended to industries as diverse as pharmaceuticals, health care, consumer goods, entertainment, and the Federal government. Between 2012 and 2023, &lt;a href=&quot;https://static1.squarespace.com/static/62adf3ca029a6808a6c5be30/t/63a477e23d7f9162b7771d6b/1671722982363/WAVESTONE+NVP--+Data+%26+Analytics+Executive+Leadership+2023--Survey+Findings.pdf&quot;>;according to survey data&lt;/a>;, companies having appointed a CDO grew from just 12.0% to 82.6%, with an expansion of responsibilities over time to include analytics (CDAO) and AI (CDAIO). However, only 35.5% of major companies report that the role is successful and well established, and just 40.5% say that the CDAIO role is well understood within their company. Clearly, something is not working.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For some data and analytics leaders, 2023 has felt like a return to the earliest unglamorous days of the role: financial turbulence and the explosion of generative AI has forced them to focus on defensive risk and regulatory tasks rather than forward-looking initiatives focused on growth, customer acquisition, and the creation of new products and services. Corporate leadership is placing demands on CDAIOs to deploy the potentially transformative capabilities of GenAI while avoiding harm — a high-pressure balancing act with a technology that offers huge risks and opportunities.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a moment when more companies want and need CDAIOs, the role is as challenging as ever — and often set up for failure. Here are five steps companies can take to fix it.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What&#39;s Wrong with the CDAIO Job?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As coauthors we have been firsthand witnesses of and participants in the rise and evolution of the CDAIO role. Randy has served as an advisor to leading companies on the use of data and analytics for over two decades. Allison served as an industry CDO for five years and is currently advising CDAIOs and companies on how to deliver business value. While we both agree that the role can feel impossible, we also believe the current iterations include the foundations for a better, more effective version of the job.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The first generation of chief data officers were often hired into large companies in regulated industries such as health care and finance. Initially, the role was understood as a defensive one that focused on control and risk rather than a business one, even though both functions use the same data and analytical skills. Transaction data used by banks to detect fraud patterns is also used to uncover existing or latent customer needs, but companies invested in the former and not the latter. As the focus shifted to commercialization of data, companies too often viewed this as a technical and talent problem, rather than as a business problem. They invested heavily in technology and people, building out data infrastructures and teams of data engineers and data scientists, but didn&#39;t focus enough on the importance of business relationships and the most critical business questions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As a result, companies didn&#39;t end up getting what they wanted from their data programs. While 91.9% of companies report that they have achieved some measurable value from their investments in data and analytics, just a dismal 23.9% say they have created a data-driven organization, and an even more paltry 20.6% of firms report having established a data culture. The CDAIO has been left on the hook for major projects that require huge investment and reach into all corners of the company, but often fail to deliver measurable benefit. Even when they&#39;ve done exactly what was asked of them, it can be hard to argue they&#39;ve succeeded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We believe that two factors largely led to this situation: the wrong focus and a lack of trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Rather than technology and infrastructure problems, the focus of the role should have been on business outcomes: Identifying the problem that you are trying to solve for your customers, prioritizing use cases with the highest business return, and cross-pollinating capabilities, whether the goal is commercial, risk control, or both. “The hardest part of the job is knowing what problem you are trying to solve for your customers,” says Cassie Kozyrkov, chief decision scientist at Google, and a pioneer in the field of decision intelligence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Lack of trust has been an equivalent factor. Business leaders need to trust that the investments that they are making in data, analytics, and AI are delivering a business return — that they&#39;re money well spent. If business value isn&#39;t clearly being delivered, that trust erodes and business leaders will be reluctant to make further investments. CDAIOs, especially in large companies, have built out governance infrastructure of people, policy, processes, and stewardship models in efforts to federate ownership of trust in data throughout the organization. These efforts are complicated, often unpopular, and the benefits are difficult to quantify. Since virtually every problem in a digital economy can be described as a data problem, victory is hard to achieve unless there are agreed-upon metrics against which progress can be measured.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How to Fix It&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Progress in any new era of innovation comes in fits and starts and can be hard to measure. It is fair to argue that data and business strategy have been misaligned, have not been a C-level and board priority, that governance efforts have been too clunky for widespread adoption and measurement, and that discipline has been incomplete. The emergence of generative AI has magnified these issues, and raised new issues of trust, quality, and ethics that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/science/annals-of-artificial-intelligence/can-we-stop-the-singularity&quot;>;in the news&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/05/20/ai-existential-risk-debate/&quot;>;are commanding executive and board attention&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies can and must fix how they manage data, analytics, and AI, and set the CDAIO role up for success. This requirement will only expand, especially when &lt;a href=&quot;https://static1.squarespace.com/static/62adf3ca029a6808a6c5be30/t/63a477e23d7f9162b7771d6b/1671722982363/WAVESTONE+NVP--+Data+%26+Analytics+Executive+Leadership+2023--Survey+Findings.pdf&quot;>;83.9% of companies&lt;/a>; plan to increase their investments in data, analytics, and AI next year. Here are a few concrete recommendations companies can undertake today to repair the CDAIO role and deliver business value from their data, analytics, and AI investments:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Make data everyone&#39;s business.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While CDAIOs have long been promoting the importance of data literacy, there has been inconsistent adoption of practices such as strong governance, policies, and standards. The areas with the most maturity and discipline in data are typically the finance and compliance-related functions. Success in these areas, reinforced with C-level and board involvement, can serve as models for the enterprise.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At Schneider Electric, a global energy management and digital automation leader, Philippe Rambach, chief artificial intelligence officer, speaks of how Schneider has built a corporate culture that&#39;s everyone&#39;s business:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Being serious about data management requires a dedicated organization. To support this ambition, we decided to carve out data from IT, focusing data on a governance, business, and performance agenda across the company. We then decided to create two roles of chief data officer and chief AI officer. What&#39;s key in the data-focused journey is to strive to have a single source of truth in the company, and to make high-quality data easily accessible across the company to all decision makers.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h3>;Make business leaders champions for data projects.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Business leaders need to become the champions and advocates for investment in data and analytics. Successful data leaders are critical partners to business leaders, who come to rely on them as righthand lieutenants providing critical data and decision-points that can drive successful business outcomes. CDAIOs should not seek to impose an agenda (“data and AI are great; we should be doing so much more”), no matter how well intentioned. Seek out business leaders who are ready to champion data and AI within their business lines and become trusted partners through results that build credibility.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Review all data and AI investments to make sure funds are well spent.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Distinguish between “nice to have” versus “need to have” investments. Continue only with those that are delivering measurable business value to the organization today or can demonstrate a quick path to value in the near term. Companies must refocus their investments on those capabilities that are essential and are needed to grow and compete. Data analytics and AI leadership requires time, attention, clear and effective communication, and the storytelling skills to articulate the need, establish realistic expectations, and elicit buy-in.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Shift to an ecosystem mindset.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;To make the most of data and AI, cultivating partnerships and collaboration with vendors, universities, and other partners is important. Schneider&#39;s Rambach adds:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;The new nature of competition is really not about technology; AI technology moves too fast for that. It&#39;s about the value you deliver to customers. And whatever value you deliver, it can be augmented through partnerships. We open up our IoT platform for third-party innovations so partners can use our software development kits to develop new applications to innovate for better efficiency and sustainability of buildings.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;h3>;Proceed with caution.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While generative AI offers game-changing opportunities, Rambach reiterates the importance of understanding risks and proceeding with caution, as these models:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;…expose companies to new types of vulnerabilities, notably by giving easier and faster access to larger quantities and diversity of data to more users. Now is the time to establish data governance and cybersecurity measures to use these new capabilities responsibly. Companies and users should always approach generative AI with caution and focus on confidentiality, like users should not upload any confidential information on publicly accessible AI chatbot platforms. Secured/private versions of LLMs should be preferred.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;Many CDAIOs lead enterprise committees with leaders from risk, finance, technology, cybersecurity, legal/ethics, privacy, HR, and the business lines. These teams need heightened stature and accountability. Companies should also add data, analytics, and AI expertise to their corporate boards. Just 23.8% say that the industry is doing enough to address data and AI ethics. Issues of AI and data privacy, governance, and ethics will pose a threat to companies if not managed responsibly and effectively.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At a time when many companies are taking a hard look at the CDAIO function, now is the time when data and AI leaders must step forward to show how they are contributing to the business value of the company. Those companies that have a clear vision for how they will deliver business value from their data and AI investments will be the companies that are most likely to prevail in the coming decade and beyond.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jun 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>