<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How to Be a Purpose-Driven Leader Without Burning Out]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-be-a-purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1298982699.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;丹尼尔·格里泽尔吉/盖蒂图片社&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;仆人式领导理念 &amp;#8212;将团队的需求置于自己的需求之上为我们带来了一个更加富有同情心、以人为本的工作环境。但在当今的环境下，这会导致倦怠。相反，作者提出了一种更具影响力的哲学，称为“崇高目标领导力”。它将领导者和团队成员联系起来，共同追求对选民产生积极影响的共同目标。在仆人式领导中，传达的信息是：你的角色是服务他人，这使得你很容易专注于取悦他人，而很难拒绝。在崇高目标的领导力中，传达的信息是：你有责任发挥影响力。这需要更多的战略思考来决定你的努力应该放在哪里。作者提出了三个领域，管理者可以将目光转向崇高目标的领导力。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/how-to-be-a- Purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to -be-a- Purpose-driven-leader-without-burning-out? language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当罗伯特·格林利夫 (Robert Greenleaf) 创造了短语“&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.greenleaf.org/what-is-servant-leadership/&quot;>;仆人式领导&lt;/a>;”在 1970 年一篇开创性的文章中指出，这是对传统命令与控制领导模式的急需改进。盛行了几个世纪。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“仆人式领导首先是仆人。它始于人们想要服务的自然感觉。然后有意识的选择就会让人渴望成为领导者，”格林利夫写道。 “这个人与首先成为领导者的人截然不同，也许是因为需要缓解不寻常的权力驱动力或获得物质财富。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有据可查的研究告诉我们，组织和个人&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-humble-leadership-really-works&quot;>;当领导者关注团队而不是自己时，表现会更好&lt;/a>;。在个人层面上，仆人式领导&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.regent.edu/journal/emerging-leadership-journeys/impact-of-servant-leadership/&quot;>;增加&lt;/a>;追随者的信任和忠诚度，以及对领导者的满意度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，自格林利夫最初的文章发表以来的 50 年里，特别是在过去三年里，发生了很大的变化。仆人式领导背后的叙述越来越平淡，这是有充分理由的：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;严重的倦怠。&lt;/strong>;在当今的环境中，当领导者感到疲倦、过度劳累和压力时，服务可以感觉就像从空杯子里倒水一样。我们告诉经理，“你来这里是为了为你的团队服务。”我们告诉面向客户的团队，“你是来为客户服务的。”总而言之，这让人筋疲力尽。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;人们更加忙碌&lt;/strong>;。当格林利夫最初引入仆人式领导时，典型的经理可能会监督一个小型职能团队。他们没有自己的可交付成果，没有参与多个跨职能计划，也没有在一天开始时回复大量隔夜电子邮件。如今，随着中层管理人员的不断精简，领导者通常会&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/people-and-organizational-performance/our-insights/how-to-identify-组织的控制权范围&quot;>;11 至 15 名直接下属&lt;/a>;以及他们自己的高风险交付成果。这些疲惫不堪的管理者常常觉得自己没有时间投入到奴役之中。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;工作场所的等级制度已经变得不那么严格了&lt;/strong>;。如今的组织结构图通常更像攀登架，而不是&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/stop-offering-career-ladders-start-offering-career-portfolios&quot;>;梯子&lt;/a>;。没有正式权威的领导正在兴起，并引发了一个问题：谁是仆人，谁被服务？&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;仆人式领导是进入更加人性化的工作世界的重要踏脚石。但下一个演变即将到来。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/to-retain-employees-give-them-a-sense-of- Purpose-and-community&quot;>;工作场所数据&lt;/a>;（以及我们自己的经验）告诉我们，我们正处于拐点。我们正处于这样一个时刻，正式和非正式的领导者都必须朝着更有目的的领导风格迈进，重点关注组织的工作对现实生活中的人类的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们将这种影响力驱动的理念称为“崇高目标的领导力”。当领导者和团队成员共同追求比他们自己（他们的团队、他们的客户、他们的社区）更大的事业时，他们的目标是积极影响他们的选民（而不是为他们服务）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是这是一种微妙但又明显的转变。在仆人驱动型领导中，信息的核心是：&lt;em>;你的职责是为他人服务&lt;/em>;。这使得很难拒绝，并且领导者（及其团队）很容易做出反应，试图取悦所有人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在崇高目标的领导中，核心信息是：&lt;em>;您的职责是产生影响&lt;/em>;。这需要更多的战略思考来决定你的努力方向。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你的北极星是一个共同的目标时，领导者在这件事上有更多的选择；你不觉得需要取悦所有人。在我们的咨询实践中，我们看到了第一手证据，表明崇高目标的领导力可以有效地推动绩效提升，同时保持服务文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是管理者可以在以下三个领域进行的工作：将他们的镜头转向崇高目标的领导力：&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1.员工互动&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;经理们经常被教导要向员工提出这样的问题：我能做些什么来帮助你取得成功？您需要我提供什么样的支持？虽然这些都是很好的问题（而且肯定会比咆哮命令得到更好的结果），但善意的领导者发现自己在这些互动中留下了一份令人筋疲力尽的行动项目清单。经过几次这样的经历后，劳累过度的管理者往往会发现，甚至不去询问团队需要什么样的帮助就变得更容易了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与其放弃提供支持的想法，管理者可以创造一种微妙的、通过调整到更高的目标，并提出以下问题来实现强大的转变：&lt;em>;您&lt;/em>;需要什么才能成功实现我们的目标？您需要获得什么帮助？&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;这种微小的语言变化重塑了情感动态。领导者不必独自负责支持员工，而是询问员工他们需要什么才能成功，从而创造一种共同的责任感。领导者有目的地将自己定位为对员工的成果产生积极影响，但他们并不承担支持员工的唯一责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是我们的客户的前后对比。一位副总裁，面对 12 名直接下属和无数的自己的交付成果，已经捉襟见肘。作为仆人式领导感到疲惫不堪且不可能。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;副总裁开始询问他们的项目经理，“鉴于我们的目标是积极影响我们的客户，您需要什么样的支持才能按时做好这件事？”项目经理很快确定他们需要其他部门的资源和支持才能按时完成任务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;副总裁是否坚持传统的“你需要我做什么？”双方都会遭受损失。副总裁的工作量超出了他们的能力范围，而项目经理也不会与其他部门合作。着眼于共同目标（成功完成改善客户生活的项目），领导者及其团队成员都会变得更加强大和高效。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2.决策&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当你的主要关注点是服务时，你就会很容易把注意力集中在取悦他人上&lt;em>; - &lt;/em>;这是一种永无休止且常常徒劳的努力。无论领导者做什么，工作中的许多要素，例如紧迫的期限和具有挑战性的反馈，本质上都是令人不快的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当领导者仅通过试图提供帮助和支持的角度来制定决策时对他们的选民来说，这会导致倦怠。最坏的情况是，它滋生了权利，员工认为领导者的工作就是让他们快乐，什么也不做。这种情绪混乱的总和可能会阻止领导者做出艰难（但正确）的决定。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，领导者可以围绕目标制定决策。例如，在会议中，不要问：你对此有何看法？这对你有用吗？领导们可以问：这会产生什么影响？这将如何影响我们的员工或客户？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;凯瑟琳是一家医疗器械公司的客户成功主管，她利用这种模型将她的团队从抱怨转向采取行动。该团队的部分职能是让客户及时了解交货时间。这包括当客户的订单延迟时给他们打电话。在经历了特别令人沮丧的一天之后，她的团队向凯瑟琳提出了一个请求：他们不想再拨打这些电话。她的团队感叹“有些客户甚至没有注意到他们的订单是否被延迟了！”&lt;/em>;其他人则蜂拥而至，&lt;em>;“我们无法加快送货卡车的速度！打电话有什么意义？如果他们担心，他们就会打电话给我们。”&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个仅仅想取悦团队的领导者可能会想让团队停止打电话，或者他们可能会接听电话他们自己。相反，凯瑟琳用问题来重新调整团队以实现更高的目标。她问道：“如果我们的顾客措手不及，不知道订单会延迟，会对他们产生什么影响？如果我们停止主动而只是被动，这会对我们的声誉产生怎样的影响？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种看似简单的视角转变促使团队思考他们的工作如何影响组织的总体目标。这改变了他们的思维过程：他们不再关注自己的反应，而是开始考虑对团队的影响，并将自己视为更大整体的一部分。团队决定继续拨打电话，但轮换职责，这样每个人就不必每天都拨打电话。重新调整团队以实现更高的目标，减轻领导者的压力并增加团队的支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3.辅导&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;任何领导者的主要职能都是&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;辅导团队&lt;/a>;。然而，当在可交付成果的基础上添加辅导时，领导者可能很难投入时间来培养员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最近，在我们为酒店行业的一组销售经理举办的辅导计划中，参与者坦言感到不知所措。该组织拥有卓越的文化，管理者通常希望领导他们的团队做好工作。然而，随着旅游业开始蓬勃发展，他们增加了更多的销售人员，经理们发现自己捉襟见肘。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们问经理们：“你们指导谁？”他们的答案几乎是一致的：表现最差的人。然而，销售经理们感叹，尽管他们进行了大量的培训投资，但表现不佳的员工充其量也只表现出了边际进步。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然后，我们将视角从仆人式领导转向崇高目的领导。我们建议管理者不要问谁最需要辅导，而是问自己：我的辅导时间在哪些方面会产生最大的影响？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;管理者开始从不同的角度看待他们的团队：谁是最值得辅导的？谁学得快？谁与客户关系最密切？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;项目结束后，这些经理开始将更多时间投入到高绩效和中等绩效员工身上。他们亲自指导高绩效员工如何获得最高价值的机会。他们通过团体辅导圈和同伴角色扮演给予中层表现更多的关注。他们并没有放弃对底层的辅导，而是没有花费数小时的辅导时间，而是通过点播课程、自学等方式指导表现较差的人拥有更多的学习成果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;结果很快就出来了：高绩效者变得更好，中等绩效者也得到了改善。同样有趣的是，表现不佳的人做了以下三件事之一：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;努力成为表现中等的人&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;坚持到底，取得与他们在开始时相同的边际进步他们几乎占用了经理所有的辅导时间&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;或者，当面临在自己的发展中拥有一定自主权的挑战时，他们会自我选择退出——这个过程比经理发生得更快、更少的挫败感花费数小时的时间试图指导一名不想提高的球员。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;总体而言，团队创造了创纪录的收入，而且他们对此感到更加满足。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;仆人式领导给我们带来了一个更加富有同情心、以人为本的工作环境。现在是我们进行下一次飞跃的时候了。在当今的环境中，精疲力竭的领导者无休止地试图服务，将难以推动未来增长所需的创新、韧性和意义感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;将镜头提升到崇高目标的领导力有能力团结起来员工和管理者追求有所作为。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Overcoming Your Fear of Giving Tough Feedback]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_26_1379555.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;胡安·莫亚诺/Stocksy&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;缺乏建设性反馈对您的团队有害，剥夺他们的指导和成长机会。沟通不畅和期望不明确的工作场所是低信任和脱离的滋生地。提供反馈对于成为有效的领导者至关重要。在本文中，作者提供了五种方法来克服您对提供反馈的恐惧。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/ 07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving-tough-feedback?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/overcoming-your-fear-of-giving -tough-feedback?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“我感觉我要吐了，”Filip在我们的教练课程中向我坦白了。 “提供反馈是领导者每天应该不费吹灰之力就能做到的事情，”他说。 “但对我来说，这感觉就像世界末日。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Filip 是一家公司的项目管理总监为全球流媒体内容提供商提供翻译服务的公司。 Filip 工作勤奋（有时甚至会犯错），是处理多个优先事项、跨时区、语言和文化协调译员、质量控制专家和客户联络的专家。他有一种在模糊性中蓬勃发展的诀窍，专注于战略目标，而又不会迷失在细节中。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;菲利普也感到自豪他自己始终为团队提供支持，即使这需要承受愤怒的高管的压力。但当向他的直接下属提供反馈时，菲利普坚韧的外表崩溃了。他会担心自己辛辛苦苦建立起来的关系会遭到破坏。他会花好几个小时思考该说些什么&lt;/span>;——&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;有时甚至几天。一想到说出“我有一些反馈给你”这句话，他就感到恶心。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;当- 由 Filip 最聪明的团队成员之一 Angelique 牵头的 stakes 项目失败了，这让他对提供反馈的恐惧成为焦点。两周以来，菲利普一直感觉到有些不对劲。球队的士气低落和表现迟缓让他感到担忧，但他告诉自己安琪莉可最终会振作起来。他从未表达过自己的担忧，而代价是毁灭性的。他们最大的客户现在将转向另一个可以提供更好服务的提供商。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“我本可以阻止这种情况。我应该说出来的。”菲利普告诉我的。他的故事呼应了我从许多高管教练客户那里听到的一个挣扎：我如何克服对提供反馈的恐惧？&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您是否担心会造成紧张、消极情绪厌恶冲突是一种常见特征，管理者也不能幸免。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400; “避免冲突并不能帮任何人忙。当问题得不到解决或被掩盖时，每个人都会受苦，包括你。缺乏建设性的反馈也不利于您的团队，剥夺他们的指导和成长机会。沟通不畅和期望不明确的工作场所是低信任度和脱离感的滋生地。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;以下是如何应对不适感和疏离感的方法。困难对话带来的忧虑，因此您可以说出需要说的话。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;挑战二元思维。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;许多避免对抗的领导者都持有诸如“没有人喜欢事无巨细”或“提出这个问题会破坏我们的工作关系”之类的假设。虽然这些信念可能源于过去被拒绝和失败的经历，但它们反映了不准确的二元思维。事实上，既不会破坏人际关系，也不会赢得“难管的经理”的名声，既自信又直接，这是可能的。&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; >;相反，应该关注通过畅所欲言可以获得什么以及清晰沟通的潜在回报。说出您的想法不仅可以帮助您感到更加自信，而且：&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您的输入可能正是推动完成一项具有挑战性的任务所需要的&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-重量：400；” aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您对同事的破坏性行为做出的坦诚评论可能会带来更加和平、高效的工作环境。&lt;/span>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/ li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您的建设性批评可以帮助团队成员在自己的角色中发展和成长，开辟新的职业机会&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt; /ul>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;当你仔细观察时，你会发现表达你的想法、感受和意见远比把它们埋藏起来并承受后果要有益得多.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;将反馈视为一种工具。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;尽管您也许您会相信，您的团队渴望有意义、坦诚的反馈。而 72% 的员工&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbswk.hbs.edu/item/why-people-crave-feedback-and-why-were-afraid-to-give-it&quot;>;&lt; span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;评价&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“提供关键反馈的经理”对他们的职业发展很重要，只有 5 % 相信管理者会提供此类反馈。同样，当团队成员认为他们的老板不擅长提供诚实的反馈时，他们的敬业度得分&lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/overcoming-feedback-phobia-take-the-first-step&quot;>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;通常&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;会急剧下降。但另一方面，在提供诚实反馈方面排名前 10% 的领导者所创建的团队在参与度方面排名前 23%。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;剥夺您的团队成长所需的信息是不公平的。当你将冲突重新定义为领导力中健康、规范的一部分时，你在与他人讨论困难话题时可能会感到的预期焦虑就会减轻。下次你必须提供反馈时，深呼吸并记住，你不是在制造冲突，而是在引导你的员工走向成长。你不是在批评；而是在批评。你在养育。你当然不是一个恶棍；您正在成为他们需要的领导者。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;预测可能发生的情况。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;对未知事物的恐惧或想知道接受者会如何反应可能会阻碍许多领导者发声。如果你的直接下属变得具有防御性并猛烈攻击你怎么办？如果他们开始哭泣怎么办？&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;您可以使用最坏情况/最好情况/最有可能来平息焦虑并处理不确定性工具。考虑可能发生的最坏情况。例如，如果你的员工哭了，你会如何处理？也许你会抽出时间。然后考虑可能发生的最好情况，以培养更多的乐观情绪。最后，考虑最有可能发生的情况，通常介于两个极端之间。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;强势开始。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span 风格=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;你还可以通过规划你的开场白来缓解你的思绪旋风。从一开始就掌控一切可以增强信心，并让你在谈话中树立尊重的基调。一旦菲利普意识到他需要与安吉丽克正面解决这个问题，他走近她说：“我很欣赏你的奉献精神和创造力。我想谈论的是一种士气低落的模式，我想了解是否有任何障碍我们可以共同解决。”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;尽可能使用“我”的陈述有助于确保您直接沟通，而不会仅仅因为害怕而犹豫不决或最小化您的担忧。具体也很重要。与其说“你又搞砸了”，不如说“我担心今天的客户会议没有及时拿到文件。”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b >;让反馈成为流程的一部分。&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;反馈应该是一种定期的仪式，而不是偶尔的爆发。让反馈成为一种习惯，可以确保你内心的微小烦恼和挫败感不会演变成重大冲突。另外，逐渐让自己暴露在可怕的情况下是克服它们的最好方法。作为您角色的一部分，您越多练习在低风险的日常场景中提供反馈，您就会变得越擅长。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font- Weight: 400;&quot;>;系统化反馈的一个好方法是定期&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/28-questions-to-ask-your-boss-in-your-one-on-ones&quot;>;一-与您的团队合作&lt;/a>;。您还可以安排项目汇报，以便团队成员进行反思，或者安排事前剖析，以便人们可以提前讨论任何风险、潜在问题，并详细说明他们将如何相互合作。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;创建积极的反馈文化将使您有机会展示新发现的自信技能，同时加强与团队的融洽和信任。作为领导者，这是您可以期待的最好的事情之一。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div >;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt; a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:55:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways Our Brains Undermine Our Ability to Be a Good Leader]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_1464364780.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Orla/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; 关闭-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;神经领导力研究所的研究人员发现，要取得成功，我们必须在卓越领导力的三个核心领域表现出色：着眼未来、与人友善以及能够推动结果。然而，当我们成长为领导者时，我们的大脑的进化方式会挑战我们在这些领域表现出色的能力。该团队分析了大型组织使用的数十个领导力发展计划，发现它们往往无法为所有三个领域的领导者提供装备。好消息是，一旦我们了解了大脑为何与我们作对，我们就可以学会如何对抗这些倾向。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-ways-our-brains-undermine-our-ability-to-be-a-good-leader?language=es&quot;>;学习西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-我们的大脑如何破坏我们成为优秀领导者的能力？ language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;罗宾，一位常年取得优异成绩的人，刚刚晋升为她的第一个领导职位。但她入职的头几个月比预想的要艰难：她的同事不再和她开玩笑，她被拉向不同的方向，而且她不断地灭火。当一位表现最好的员工突然离开去寻找另一个机会时，罗宾意识到她的团队资源不足。压力造成了影响，罗宾开始害怕周一早上。也许她不适合成为一名领导者？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;罗宾的故事很熟悉。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90452760/first-time-leaders-need-to-stick-to-these-4-truths-to-succeed&quot;>;百分之六十&lt;/a>;的新经理在前 24 个月内失败了。这不仅仅是新任经理面临的问题：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescoachescouncil/2020/03/13/why-most-new-executives-fail-and-four-things-companies-can-do-about-it/?sh=6abf27d76730&quot;>;50% 到 70%&lt;/a>; 的新任高管也会在前 18 个月内失败。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了取得成功，我们在神经领导力研究所的研究发现，我们必须在卓越领导力的三个核心领域表现出色：着眼未来、与人友善以及能够推动结果。然而，当我们成长为领导者时，我们的大脑的进化方式会挑战我们在这些领域表现出色的能力。我们分析了大型组织使用的数十个领导力发展计划，发现它们往往无法为所有三个领域的领导者提供装备。好消息是，一旦我们了解了为什么我们的大脑会与我们作对，我们就可以学会如何对抗这些倾向。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;着眼于未来&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导者不能只做今天的工作，而必须不断地审视下一步，并确保他们的团队做好准备。这与我们的大脑如何进化来重视眼前和短期的未来是不一致的。事实上，在一项研究中，&lt;a href=&quot;https://legacy.iftf.org/americanfuturegap/&quot;>;27%&lt;/a>; 的美国人表示，他们很少或从未考虑过未来五年会发生什么。这是一个令人担忧的问题，因为预测行业趋势、未来技能要求和客户需求等因素是领导者成功的核心。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据管理顾问 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/10938&quot;>;Elliott Jaques&lt;/a>; 的说法，你在组织中的职位越高，你需要思考得越远。虽然直线经理可能必须维持一个季度的计划，但首席执行官需要考虑 10 年后业务的发展状况。雅克将这个概念称为“时间跨度”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当然，挑战在于，即使在最好的时期，思考未来也是困难的。人们思考的越多，就越难注意到可以提供有关可能的未来的见解的安静信号。我们的大脑还必须与&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strategy-business.com/article/00345&quot;>;距离偏见&lt;/a>;作斗争，这导致我们优先考虑时间较近的想法和决策，而不是未来更远的事情。此外，我们研究的高管领导力项目中，只有 16% 的成果致力于思考未来，而中级领导者项目和首次领导者项目的比例更低，分别为 4% 和 6%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幸运的是，研究表明思考和预测未来的习惯是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;可以学习的&lt;/ a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xap-0000040.pdf&quot;>;技能&lt;/a>;，这是领导者可以而且应该作为领导力培训的一部分学习的众多认知技能之一。一种开始方法是每月划出时间，并为您希望团队在三到六个月内达到的“未来状态”制定计划。利用这一愿景，然后逆向工作，确定您需要做什么才能让您的团队在接下来的六个月内达到目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;您的员工就是一切&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导者都是杂耍者，而他们杂耍的事情往往是不一致的。以领导者的总体责任为例：制定能够创造成功成果的业务战略。然而，他们还必须善于与员工沟通并激励员工。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这两项任务常常是矛盾的，因为人们常常因为技术能力而晋升到领导职位&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/05/transform-your-technical-expertise-into-leadership&quot;>;因为技术能力&lt;/a>;，而不是个人魅力。社会神经科学家马修·利伯曼&lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/should-leaders-focus-on-results-or-on-people&quot;>;指出&lt;/a>;，技术能力强且风度翩翩的领导者在某种程度上是独角兽。他引用了一项研究，其中一位被视为注重结果的领导者（结合了强大的分析能力和前进和解决问题的强烈动力）只有 14% 的机会被视为伟大的领导者。如果领导者仅在社交技能（如沟通和同理心等属性）方面表现出色，那么他们被视为伟大领导者的几率就更低，只有 12%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，对于在结果和社交技能方面都很强的领导者，被视为伟大领导者的可能性飙升至 72%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;那么，这样的独角兽有多少呢？我们中的一员（大卫）与管理研究集团首席执行官 Tricia Naddaff 一起&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/your-brain-at-work/201310/find-out-how-many-leaders-are-both-goal-and-people-focused&quot;>;分析了&lt;/a>;来自数千名员工的数据，在这些数据中，人们对老板的目标关注度和人员关注度进行了评价。只有不到 1% 的领导者在这两个方面都获得了较高的评价。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;事实证明，这是有神经学原因的。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;神经影像学研究&lt;/a>;表明，负责目标聚焦和人员聚焦的不同大脑中心存在一种跷跷板效应：当一个中心向上拨动时，另一个向下拨动。更重要的是，&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0146167207301011&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，随着个人力量的增强，大脑的目标聚焦网络将占据主导地位。这个过程是适应性的，因为作为领导者要做出有效的决策，必须经常脱离每个人的需求，并将他们视为棋子而不是人类。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在目标和人员关注点之间取得适当的平衡是关键。但根据我们的研究，只有 58% 的高管领导力项目关注人员成果，其中中层领导者和初次领导者分别占 64% 和 51%。了解这一点，领导者就可以通过更有意识地向员工发出他们受到关心的信号来培养正确的平衡。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;推动现实的结果&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导力的最大难题之一是我们的大脑感知权力的方式。随着&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ejsp.324&quot;>;个人认为自己&lt;/a>;变得更强大，他们往往会变得更加乐观。这通常会导致不切实际的目标和过高的期望，从而导致领导者和负责繁重工作的直接下属之间的脱节。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;结果是领导者变得更加“&lt;a href=&quot;https://membership.neuroleadership.com/material/how-power-affects-behavior-and-decision-making/&quot;>;以愿景为中心&lt;/a>;”，而不太关心细节。拥有权力感会积极地触发我们的大脑，让我们感觉良好，就像赢得金钱或获得奖励一样。一旦大脑以这种方式被触发，它就会通过将我们的行为引导到有力量回报的活动来寻求激活更多的奖励，比如思考大局或追求目标而不是关注细节。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;好消息是，通过了解大脑变得不那么注重细节和更有远见的倾向，你可以通过寻求其他观点来抵消这种冲动，以对当前保持现实并设定更多&lt;a href=&quot;https://neuroleadership.com/your-brain-at-work/putting-people -first&quot;>;以人为本的目标&lt;/a>;，与他人的福祉息息相关。例如，如果您正在着手一个新项目，并认为需要三周时间才能完成，请询问将执行日常任务的其他人的观点，以确保交付优质产品所需的时间一致，然后在可能的情况下愿意改变您的时间表。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对 Robin 来说幸运的是，她的公司投资了一个精心设计的领导力计划，该计划可以平衡所有三种具有挑战性的能力。在接下来的六个月里，她获得了深刻的见解，使她能够更好地了解是什么让她的团队运转，同时学习如何提前思考并平衡领导力的各个方面与日常的战术需求。尽管大脑可能并非天生适合领导力，但通过正确的基于科学的培训和习惯形成，各级领导者都可以度过艰难的星期一，甚至更久。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/p>; div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https ://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Skills Provide a Development Path for Sub-Saharan Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_25_996888296.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;wilpunt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;撒哈拉以南非洲地区正在城市化，大规模农村人口向城市迁移。但与西方世界的城市化不同，撒哈拉以南非洲缺少一个关键组成部分：工业化城市。因此，这些城市地区变得人满为患，住房质量不合格，基础设施严重不足，无法应对计划外的人口增长。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幸运的是，解决这一问题的新发展手册已经在制定，其基础是撒哈拉以南非洲地区拥有先进数字技能的年轻人。这些年轻工人精通数字技术、富有创造力，可以引领巨大的变革——如果他们有能力并得到支持来释放他们的潜力。他们可以通过互联网通过“数字工作”提供的无限和不受限制的机会，向西欧、美国和亚洲输出数字技能。从音乐到软件开发再到提示工程。但为了扩大规模并取得成功，必须在政策层面和实施过程中考虑优质数字教育、税务条约和协调以及以外包为重点的初创企业等领域的变化。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/digital-skills-provide-a-development-path-for-sub-saharan-africa?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;撒哈拉以南非洲地区正在城市化，大规模农村人口向城市迁移。但与数十年和数百年前西方世界的城市化不同，撒哈拉以南非洲地区缺少一个关键组成部分：工业化城市。换句话说，与工业化先于城市化的西方世界不同，撒哈拉以南非洲的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/documents/africas-urbanizes-dynamics-2022-economic-power-africas-cities&quot;>;城市&lt;/a>;正在随着边际制造业产出和工业能力的增长而发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其影响是巨大的，因为这些城市地区已经变得过于拥挤，住房质量不合格，基础设施严重不足，无法应对计划外的人口增长。 。由于税收有限，正在城市化的撒哈拉以南非洲城市资金不足，可能会面临医疗保健服务和整体社会福利方面的严峻挑战。随着气候变化影响&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/pidgin/articles/c97je2gzdlwo&quot;>;拉各斯&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.africanews.com/2023/05/07/kenya-residents-on-a-mission-to-reduce-flooding-damage/&quot;>;内罗毕&lt;/a>;等主要城市，非洲大陆需要紧急解决方案。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据Statista 表示，平均而言，2021 年撒哈拉以南非洲城市化率约为 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/805657/urbanization-in-sub-saharan-africa/&quot;>;41.83%&lt;/a>;，即使该大陆仅占 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2016/11/23/figures-of- the-week-africa-induscialization-day/#:~:text=%20average%20share%20of%20manufacturing,at%20just%20under%202%20percent.&quot;>;全球制造业产出的 2%&lt;/a>;。这意味着那些搬到城市地区寻找经济机会的人却找不到经济机会，这导致了高失业率，尤其是年轻人的失业率。布鲁金斯学会估计非洲青年失业率&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brookings.edu/blog/africa-in-focus/2021/12/08/the-case-for-job-creation-hubs-to-reduce-youth-unemployment-in-africa/&quot;>;约 60%&lt;/a>;，而联合国贸易和发展会议 (UNCTAD) 则将&lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/press- material/facts-and-figures-7&quot;>;大多数国家的贫困率超过50%&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;许多因素加剧了这种快速的“工业化之前的城市化”带来的挑战，其中包括落后的工业化政策。多年来，撒哈拉以南非洲领导人一直在制定一项模仿中国的战略，该战略依赖于这样的预期：一旦中国的工资变得相对昂贵，西方世界就会将低水平的工厂工作外包给撒哈拉以南非洲，以刺激制造业的活跃。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是，&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/09/why-africas-induscialization-wont-look-like-chinas&quot;>;正如我之前指出的&lt;/a>;，这将是一个巨大的挑战如果非洲试图推行中国的战略，那就错了。随着人工智能和机器人技术的进步，对中国有效的做法已经失效，西欧和美国几乎不可能将一些低水平工作转移到境外。机器人会做家里的工作。相反，撒哈拉以南非洲的政策制定者必须制定一套新的发展手册，考虑到该地区目前的现实状况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;幸运的是，这一新的发展手册已经在不断发展，并且以撒哈拉以南非洲众多的年轻人为基础。过去几年，在运营早期风险基金 Tekedia Capital 和拥有数千名学生的商学院 Tekedia Institute 的过程中，我收集了有关行业、核心经济指标、自由职业、离岸工作等因素的大量数据。根据数据集，我认为非洲大陆的发展之路是通过拥有先进数字技能的年轻人来实现的。撒哈拉以南非洲的年轻人精通数字技术，富有创造力，如果他们有能力并得到支持来释放他们的潜力，不仅是在区域范围内，而且在全球范围内，他们可以领导一场巨大的变革。这些年轻人可以通过互联网提供的无限和不受限制的机会向西欧、美国和亚洲输出数字技能。换句话说，西方国家在将工厂工作外包给中国的同时，很快就会以多种方式将“&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/12/the-most-and-least-digital-jobs-and-how-well-ey-pay&quot;>;数字工作&lt;/a>;”外包给撒哈拉以南非洲地区。这些数字工作多种多样，从音乐到软件开发再到&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/the-hottest-job-in-tech-right-now-is-in-prompt-engineering/&quot;>;即时工程&lt;/a>;。对于日本和韩国等出生率仍然较低的国家来说，撒哈拉以南非洲地区提供了现成的人才基础，可以远程支持其经济。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;随着撒哈拉以南非洲地区的宽带普及率不断加深，一些有利的基础设施已经存在。随着地面宽带的不断扩张，SpaceX Starlink 卫星宽带的到来为城市和农村地区的连接带来了许多希望。随着利用太阳能提供能源服务的可再生能源初创公司的出现，年轻的技术人员正在克服基础设施方面的挑战，使他们更容易参与全球数字经济。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些转变使年轻的撒哈拉以南工人能够在他们所在的地方赚取收入，一旦收入被进口，他们就有能力大规模贡献和改变当地经济。事实上，一些数字专家在为国际组织工作赚钱后，决定创办自己的公司，并在此过程中培养其他年轻人才。非洲大陆拥有&lt;a href=&quot;https://guardian.ng/technology/nigeria-products- Five-of-seven-unicorns-in-africa/&quot;>;至少七家独角兽&lt;/a>;——估值至少10亿美元的初创企业——当它们在公开证券交易所上市、被大型跨国公司收购或成长为有能力支付丰厚股息时，所创造的财富将用于加速发展。更重要的是，由于他们工作的数字化性质，甚至不需要留在城市地区；例如，Andela 是一家数字技能外包初创公司，它从撒哈拉以南非洲的任何地方雇用工人，只要他们有良好的互联网服务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但要扩大这一规模并取得成功，必须在政策层面和实施过程中考虑以下因素：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;高质量数字教育：&lt;/strong>;Covid-19 大流行表明，许多撒哈拉以南非洲国家的数字化准备程度仍然很低。虽然中国、美国和欧洲的许多大学能够过渡到远程学习，但许多撒哈拉以南非洲的大学却不能。建设支持未来知识经济的基础设施对于撒哈拉以南非洲地区释放年轻人的巨大潜力至关重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;税收协定和协调：&lt;/strong>;在尼日利亚、加纳和肯尼亚等撒哈拉以南非洲地区的主要经济体中，大多数年轻人为欧洲、美国和加拿大的一些领先公司工作。撒哈拉以南非洲地区的政策制定者必须确保这些工人得到公平的报酬，并确保他们依法缴纳当地税款。一项使跨国公司更容易雇用和培养这些人才的明确政策应该成为该地区发展优先事项的一部分。同样重要的是确保繁重的税收不会削弱年轻工人的积极性。这就需要有效实施和协调税收协定。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;以外包为重点的初创企业&lt;/strong>;：应制定区域和国家政策，以深化以外包为重点的数字公司的能力。像 Andela 这样的公司估值超过 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tekedia.com/andela-becomes-a-unicorn-raises-200-million-at-1-5-billion-valuation/&quot;>;15 亿美元&lt;/a>;，培训年轻人，然后将他们的数字技能输出到世界各地，而他们则留在非洲大陆。非洲驻欧洲、亚洲和北美的大使馆和使团可以支持他们与主要客户建立联系，提供雇用非洲青年服务的渠道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;撒哈拉以南非洲拥有年轻人来推动知识经济。 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.un.org/ohrls/news/young-people%E2%80%99s-pottial-key-africa%E2%80%99s-sustainable-development&quot;>;根据联合国的说法&lt;/a>;，“非洲是世界上人口最年轻的国家，撒哈拉以南非洲地区 70% 的人口年龄在 30 岁以下。”如果非洲大陆对他们进行更高水平的数字技能教育和培训，撒哈拉以南非洲将在几十年内实现发展，并将经历其独特的工业化版本。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Journey to Cloud Smart: Executives Share Their Perspectives - SPONSOR CONTENT FROM VMWARE]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/sponsored/2023/07/the-journey-to-cloud-smart-executives-share-their-perspectives]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;html>; &lt;head>;&lt;/head>; &lt;body>; &lt;figure>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-0&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/hero-1024x682.jpg&quot; >; &lt;/figure>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;最近多年来，越来越多的组织转向多个公共云提供商来运营其业务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在某些情况下，这种情况是无意中出现的，因为不同的团队更喜欢不同的平台。有时，这是渴望获得多云竞争和经济优势的组织战略决策的结果。这些包括更高的灵活性、更低的成本、更大的数据货币化能力以及法规遵从性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，采用多云的过程可能是漫长而痛苦的。在此过程中，许多企业可能会面临复杂性和成本的飙升，更不用说安全问题了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;释放多云方法的真正潜力（变得“云智能”）需要有针对性和战略性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;与多云复杂性的斗争&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;多云挑战可能会让企业领导者措手不及。公有云“在纸面上看起来真的非常非常好”，ice挪威的云和基础设施架构师 William Brown 说道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fiserv 的高级副总裁兼杰出工程师 Tom Eck 表示：“在最初的兴奋爆发之后，出现了幻灭的阶段，事情没有按预期进行。”&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) google tag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos3&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;对于 T-Systems（德国电信股份公司旗下）云平台高级副总裁 Christoph Rode 来说，多云的采用带来了多个方面的挑战。 “即使你进行了成本控制，你也会意识到成本正在螺旋式上升，”他说。 “我需要控制成本。我需要控制安全性、合规性，并且需要帮助。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些经历并不是独一无二的。 VMware 委托 Vanson Bourne 最近对近 6,000 名 IT 领导者进行的一项调查显示，70% 的人表示他们正在努力应对多云挑战。很少有企业能够达到&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.vmware.com/reaching-multicloud-tipping-point&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;临界点&lt;/a>;，即多云的战略优势超过其复杂性：70% 的公司尚未在多云采用之旅中达到高级阶段。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;经历这些挑战的组织正在错失围绕多云收入、盈利能力和数据的关键机遇可以带来竞争优势的货币化。他们也无法享受多云数据主权和数据安全优势，从而保持客户和员工的忠诚度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;“云智能”的优势&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有更好的方法来采用多云。报告中调查的五分之一的组织可以被视为“云智能”，或者其多云方法成熟。他们正在采取有计划的战略方法来实现数字化转型和多云实施。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;“对我来说，应用程序的安全性、应用程序在世界各地的可访问性以及如何使用这些应用程序才是云智能的真正开始。”Quality Bicycle Products 的系统架构师 Joe Van Ert 说道。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些关键因素是将云智能组织与那些面临多云采用挑战的组织区分开来的：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;应用程序创新&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Vi灵活性和云支出&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;云安全&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;数据管理文化和团队&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div id=&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;>; &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;>;if (isAdobeSync()) googletag.cmd.push(function() { googletag.display(&quot;DFP_IC_pos4&quot;); });&lt;/script>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;无论企业处于云采用之路的哪个阶段，它都可以采用云智能思维方式。采用这种方法并利用正确技术的组织可以降低复杂性并减轻处理多个云带来的挑战。充分利用可用的云平台，使企业能够最大限度地提高收入和盈利能力，安全地跨境管理数据，并通过指尖将数据货币化。&lt;/p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;详细了解&lt;a href=&quot;http://vmware.com/multi-cloud&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;成为云智能组织&lt;/a>;。&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;/body>; &lt;/html>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:55:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Questions Sales Teams Should Ask After Losing (or Winning) a Deal]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-winning-a-deal]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_DanielCreel.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Daniel Creel 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close- Caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;当销售人员失去一笔交易时，大多数人更愿意继续前进，而不是徘徊在损失的具体细节上。同样，当他们赢得一笔交易时，大多数人都会很快庆祝。但很少有人花时间评估他们为何赢得业务。在作者的书中，在领导和指导销售团队的经验中，他们发现有证据表明，简短、针对性强的销售回顾可以显着提高团队未来的获胜率，在回顾中你可以揭示胜利或失败背后的原因。除了为销售团队带来明显的好处之外，对于谁来说，该流程可以帮助确定未来使用的最佳消息传递和行为——分析胜利和损失还可以为产品、营销和财务团队提供宝贵的见解。团队应该问三个问题：1）客户将如何阐明他们选择的价值？ 2) 谁是房间内外最有影响力的声音？ 3) 除了价格之外，客户做出决定的关键决定因素是什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-having-a-deal?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/0 7/3-questions-sales-teams-should-ask-after-losing-or-wining-a-deal?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;当他读到这封电子邮件时，“我们决定朝另一个方向前进”，这就像打在肚子上的一记重拳。布伦特低下头试图吸收损失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;布伦特是一家金融科技公司的客户经理，他非常确信这笔交易将会完成，因此他将其放在了本季度结束的预测中。他甚至已经在精神上花掉了他的佣金。当他接受自己失去这笔交易的现实时，他意识到有一些迹象表明客户没有完全投入。现在，他们要使用其他人了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;布伦特知道他必须告诉他的老板。但他最不想做的就是召开一次会议来揭露自己的失败。也许他可以在他们交谈之前再做一笔交易，从而避免他确信会是一场痛苦的谈话。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当销售人员失去一笔交易时，大多数人更愿意继续前进，而不是在损失的具体细节上徘徊。同样，当他们赢得一笔交易时，大多数人都会很快庆祝。但很少有人花时间评估他们为什么赢得业务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据我们领导和指导销售团队的经验，我们看到证据表明，简短、针对性强的销售回顾可以揭示成功或失败背后的原因，可以显着提高团队未来的获胜率。除了为销售团队带来明显的好处（该流程可以帮助他们确定未来使用的最佳信息和行为）之外，分析胜利和损失还可以为产品、营销和财务团队提供宝贵的见解。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;领导者和销售人员面临的挑战是深入挖掘定价和功能的传统竞争分析，以揭示影响客户购买决策的细微差别因素。虽然销售人员可能会因为拿放大镜观察后视镜而抱怨，尤其是在可能仍然令人痛苦的损失时，但我们发现，即使只花 10 分钟进行回顾也会带来巨大的回报。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以下是组织和个人可以在销售回顾中使用的三个问题。无论球队赢得还是输掉交易，这些问题都有效。它们旨在帮助团队了解推动客户购买决策的真正问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;客户如何阐明他们选择的价值？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;领导者可以在交易完成或失败后向团队提出问题。该过程首先要求团队超越解决方案本身。相反，重点关注客户如何阐明实施他们选择的解决方案（无论是您的解决方案还是您竞争对手的解决方案）的效果。例如，该解决方案可能会影响客户的其他部门，超出销售人员传统上接触的初始用户组，或者它可能会帮助客户完成其他内部优先事项。超越明显的产品用户可以帮助团队了解他们更大的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你输掉了这笔交易，通过这个镜头更深入地挖掘将帮助你制定自己的定位，以便下次创造更多的紧迫感。如果您赢得了交易，这些信息将帮助您采取行动，确保从客户的角度实现高价值的实施。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在上述金融科技公司中，销售回顾显示客户对一些产品功能给予了高度重视，他们认为这些功能是其内部团队的必备功能。客户认为竞争对手的产品在这些领域更加强大。在回顾期间变得具体，促使布伦特公司的产品团队进行了一些小调整，使它们处于同等水平。营销人员还收集了有关如何调整材料以突出变化的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;揭示损失通常有助于发现机会。但赢得胜利也有好处。询问相关销售人员客户如何阐明您的解决方案的价值，为整个团队创造了共同的胜利。在经济紧缩的情况下，夸大胜利而不是仅仅解决损失，会提醒您的销售团队，客户发现您的解决方案很有价值，并且许多人仍在购买。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;谁是房间内外最有影响力的声音？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;通常，关键决策者、影响者和主题专家直到交易决定后才会被透露。了解您赢得的交易中的这些人是谁，可以为您的实施做好准备。了解当您失去一笔交易时谁的声音具有重要影响力，可以帮助销售团队在未来的销售过程中尽早解决这些影响者的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过查看参与者和价值故事更全面地揭示损失，可以帮助销售团队摆脱拒绝的痛苦。值得注意的是，羞耻和责备的环境很少能产生伟大的洞察力。相反，应该关注他们下次可以采取哪些不同的做法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当金融科技公司更仔细地观察决策者时，很明显，首席信息官已经做出了最终决定。虽然大多数销售拜访都是针对用户组的，但正是 CIO 确定了必须具备的功能，从而导致团队付出了代价。了解这一点促使销售支持部门创建额外的培训，以帮助销售团队更熟练地拜访首席信息官。营销团队开发了一个新的平台，展示他们的产品如何应对典型的 CIO 挑战，财务团队开发了模型来展示其随着时间的推移产生的净积极影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;除了价格之外，客户决策的关键决定因素是什么？&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当团队失去一笔交易时，很容易将其归咎于定价。要求团队思考为什么客户会出于价格以外的原因做出决策，这将使他们能够反思解决方案的全部价值。它还将使他们能够更广泛地审视自己的产品在竞争格局中的表现。当你失去一笔交易时，这个问题将帮助你的团队通过更加适应未来的细微差别来提高他们的技能。相反，当你获胜时，除了定价之外，解释你获胜的原因会增强团队的信心，这有助于你保持未来的利润。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;询问买家自己还有哪些其他因素影响了决策，这也很有帮助。他们甚至可能没有意识到推动他们思考的微妙因素，直到他们被要求拆开包装。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;失败后，金融科技团队回到客户那里询问他们为什么选择竞争对手，从而使团队能够获得有关感知到的产品差异的更详细信息。保持对话中立，而不试图重新推销，创造了一个客户愿意分享的环境。损失仍然令人痛苦，但他们直接从客户那里获得的深刻见解帮助团队调整了未来的产品。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;虽然销售回顾的好处是显而易见的，但挑战往往在于评估何时使用销售回顾。组织可能在一个季度内完成数百或数千笔交易，但并非所有交易都值得反思。人们倾向于限制对季度末未完成的大型交易进行回顾。然而，根据我们的经验，当时的情绪非常高涨，因此回顾的效用通常很低。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相反，我们发现销售领导每季度为每位客户经理至少举行一次回顾会很有帮助。这使得团队能够收集对公司多个职能部门有价值的信息。也许最重要的是，这种方法将训练销售团队独立思考为什么他们实际上获胜或失败，而与回顾无关。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论领导者选择讨论哪项交易，从不进行回顾到进行几次回顾都将是一项相当大的成就，并提供可能改变进入市场策略的见解。通过进行更深入的销售回顾，这家金融科技公司能够调整他们的产品，提高销售团队的技能，并在关键买家中建立更强大的影响力。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于大多数领导者来说，需要时间才能产生与案例研究中所取得的效果类似的影响，但在此过程中，客户主管会感到被倾听，销售将更加有效，并且进入市场的团队将能够更好地支持销售。最终，这使领导者能够将小损失转化为大胜利。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 22:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[When Your Employee Isn&rsquo;t Reaching Their Full Potential]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potential]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_24_56660878.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jeanette Martin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; 关闭-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;感觉您的员工没有主动发挥自己的才能，这可能会令人沮丧。作为他们的经理，你甚至可能想知道这是否是知识或意志力的问题：他们是否不明白如何才能发挥最佳表现？或者他们只是没有动力？在本文中，作者探讨了员工可能无法充分发挥潜力的三个主要原因：个人挑战、人际关系问题和领导力问题。考虑到这一点确实令人不快，但请记住，至少 30% 的员工认为自己的工作是有问题的。绩效是管理方式的产物，这意味着您的领导力可以在决定人们是否发挥潜力方面发挥重要作用。尽管你打算支持和培养你的员工，但你可能会通过微观管理、过于宽松的监督或目标沟通不畅等管理罪恶来压制他们的才能。关于这一可能令人震惊的启示的好消息是，它是一个完全在您控制范围内的领域。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-potial?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot; /2023/07/when-your-employee-isnt-reaching-their-full-pottial?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;您已经在您的员工身上看到了真正能力的闪光，甚至可能是偶尔的才华。那么，为什么他们未能发挥这种潜力呢？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;作为一个关心培养员工技能、能力和职业发展轨迹的领导者，如果他们没有主动发挥自己的才能，会感到非常沮丧。有时，您甚至可能想知道这是知识还是意志力的问题：他们是否不明白如何才能发挥最佳表现？还是&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/4-reasons-good-employees-lose-their-motivation&quot;>;他们只是没有动力&lt;/a>;？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;显然，您认为员工的“典型表现”（他们通常做的事情）不如他们的“最大表现”或能力（他们能做到的最好水平）是有原因的 - 因此，作为第一步，重要的是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tand fonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/08959280701333289&quot;>;澄清并量化&lt;/a>;这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;也许您正在考虑他们巅峰表现的具体示例，例如在高风险情况下发表引人注目的演讲，或者在他们展示宝贵技能的特定时刻，例如&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10. 1111/1467-8721.ep10768746?journalCode=cdpa&quot;>;智力&lt;/a>;（识别重要的隐藏模式，化混乱和复杂为秩序，学习新事物），&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1745691611421204?journalCode=ppsa&quot;>;好奇心&lt;/a >;（提出真正有洞察力的问题），或&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10400419.2015.1030293&quot;>;创造力&lt;/a>;（提供意想不到的见解，产生原创且有用的新想法）。如果他们曾经做过一次，那么他们显然有能力达到这个水平，更不用说多次了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，缩小员工可能无法充分发挥潜力的原因至关重要。我们发现了三个主要类别要检查：个人挑战，人际关系问题或您自己的领导。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; &lt;strong>;个人挑战&lt;/strong>; &lt;/strong>; &lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;人们无法充分发挥自己的潜力的一个原因是，很少有人知道他们的&lt;a a href =“ “>;实际潜力&lt;/a>;首先。考虑一下，在任何专业知识、才能或绩效领域，人们的优秀程度和他们认为自己的优秀程度之间的重叠度通常小于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2011-29559-001&quot;>;10%&lt;/a>;。作为领导者，您可以向您领导和管理的团队成员赠送一份强大的礼物：了解他们的能力，有时甚至在他们行动之前，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Talk-Three-Powerful-Feedback/dp/1912555093&quot;>;举起一面镜子&lt;/a>;。事实上，反馈是员工绩效的关键催化剂，但&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/buy/1996-02773-003&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，三分之二的情况下，反馈要么无法使他人变得更好，甚至使他们&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/03/the-feedback-fallacy&quot;>;变得更糟&lt;/a>;！&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;确保您特别赞扬了员工在其工作中的表现最好，这样他们就知道什么是“优秀”，并让他们参与讨论他们在那些时刻为成功所做的事情。他们之所以能成功演讲是因为他们花了时间练习和准备吗？他们是否事先采访了观众以便他们引用相关例子？帮助他们深入挖掘成功背后的原因有助于向他们展示如何复制成功。换句话说，将自己视为&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-leader-as-coach&quot;>;作为教练&lt;/a>;，而不是老板。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们未能发挥潜力的另一个主要驱动因素就是&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2010-06019-003&quot;>;动机&lt;/a>;。如果您过去看到您的员工表现出色，那么显然能力不是问题所在，因此他们当前的积极性值得调查。您可以与您的团队成员联系，了解发生了什么情况，尤其是在发生突然变化的情况下。也许他们正在经历&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/how-to-manage-an-employee-whos-having-a-personal-crisis&quot;>;个人生活中的挑战&lt;/a>;，或者正在走向&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/do-you-know-burnout-when-you-see-it&quot;>;倦怠&lt;/a>;，需要休息一下。或者，也许&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/how-to-lose-your-best-employees&quot;>;他们在自己的角色中感到停滞&lt;/a>;，需要新的挑战，包括延伸目标，您可以&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/02/give-your-employees-specific-goals-and-the-freedom-to-figure-out-how-to-reach-them&quot;>;帮助他们制定&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong >;人际问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;有时，员工的表现不佳来自于他们周围的环境——即其他人。正如鲍里斯·格罗伊斯伯格和他的同事&lt;a href=&quot;/2004/05/the-risky-business-of-hiring-stars&quot;>;所表明的&lt;/a>;，迁移到新公司的明星员工往往无法复制他们的成功，因为帮助推动他们崛起的支持因素（例如公司特定的知识或网络）不再存在。事实上，尽管组织通常为外部聘用的员工支付的费用高于内部晋升的员工，但外部聘用通常无法像内部候选人那样&lt;a href=&quot;https://knowledge.wharton.upenn.edu/article/why-external-hires-get-paid-more-and-perform-worse-than-internal-staff/&quot;>;带来更多价值&lt;/a>;，尤其是因为许多以前使他们成功的条件可能不再存在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，您的员工可能会由于新的团队动态（可能是在同事离开或加入团队后）、角色或职责的改变、或感觉缺乏认可或地位变化（其他人获得晋升或奖金）而陷入停滞状态。您员工的才能可能没有改变，但他们的执行能力却没有改变。如果是这种情况，您需要诚实地讨论动态并找到重新构建或调解冲突的机会，或者将他们转移到更有可能成功的新角色。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;领导力问题&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;考虑起来令人不愉快，但请记住&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Why-Many-Incompetent-Become-Leaders/dp/163 3696324&quot;>;至少 30% 的员工绩效&lt;/a>;是其管理方式的结果，这意味着您的领导力可以在决定人们是否发挥潜力方面发挥重要作用。尽管您打算支持和培养您的员工，但您可能会通过&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/11/signs-that-youre-a-micromanager&quot;>;微观管理&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;/2015/06/get-what-you-need-from-your-hands-off-boss&quot;>;过于宽松的监管&lt;/a>;或糟糕的&lt;a href=&quot;/2011/02/making-sure-your -employees-suc&quot;>;传达目标&lt;/a>;，以及其他管理上的过失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关于这一可能令人震惊的揭露的好消息是，这是一个完全在您控制范围内的领域。通过围绕如何与员工沟通、提供反馈、授权他们和管理他们的&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/06/a-refresher-on-ab-testing&quot;>;A/B 测试&lt;/a>;策略，您可以直接检查您提供的指导的结果，并评估他们表现不佳的主要原因是否确实是 。 。 .&amp;nbsp;你。测试过去对他们有效的策略以及那些已被其他员工证明有效的策略很有用。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有人都是独一无二的，没有一种策略适合所有人。话虽如此，通常情况下，当您花更多时间与与您有信任关系的员工相处并给予他们更多反馈（包括建设性批评、值得称赞、认可和资源）时，他们将更有可能发挥自己的潜力，而不是相反。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后，请记住，人都是人，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Human-Automation-Quest-Reclaim-Unique-ebook/dp/B099KQ V3ZJ&quot;>;人不是机器&lt;/a>;。这意味着您不应该期望每个人都能始终发挥出最大水平或全部能力。事实上，地球上最有创造力和才华的人——在任何领域——他们的表现可能会非常不一致，因为&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2003-02410-016&quot;>;灵感是结果的强大驱动力&lt;/a>;，也是创新和卓越工作的主要动力。放宽员工的要求，尊重他们的自然周期，当然还要酌情&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/hold-your-team-accountable-with-compassion-not-fear&quot;>;让他们承担责任&lt;/a>;，这就是优秀管理者所做的事情。顺便说一句，支撑工作绩效的不一致或不稳定因素也可能适用于您 - 因此检查您是否正在发挥自己的潜力以及可能阻止您这样做的因素可能会有所帮助。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;了解员工绩效（也许还有您自己）的绩效差距是一种深思熟虑和同理心的练习。通过检查上述可能性，您将能够更好地帮助指导您的团队更频繁地发挥最佳状态。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Effectively &mdash; and Legally &mdash; Use Racial Data for DEI]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/how-to-effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_24_RacialData.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Ngadi Smart 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption =&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;美国最高法院最近裁决反对高等教育中的平权行动后，领导者可能会担心他们的 DEI 举措和计划将面临更多审查和法律挑战。虽然减少责任是一种负责任的举措，但作者警告不要让这些努力导致因恐惧而放弃有效的 DEI 做法。为了在这段时间内保持 DEI 的进展，企业应重点关注减少法律风险最大的种族数据的使用，同时采取果断行动，继续使用种族数据来消除歧视、消除偏见并创造更公平的工作场所。作者阐述了如何减少这种风险，确定了数据使用的五个目标（识别差异、消除普遍障碍、纠正歧视、设计公平流程以及展示 DEI 进展），并为希望维持 DEI 进展的公司提供了注意事项。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to- effectively-and-legally-use- race-data-for-dei?language=es&quot;>;西班牙语阅读&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/how-to- effectively-and-legally-use-racial-data-for-dei?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;继美国最高法院裁定取消高等教育中具有种族意识的招生之后，一些企业领导者可能会担心，除了减少招聘中本已较低的多样性之外，管道，该裁决可能会导致他们的多元化、公平和包容性 (DEI) 举措和计划面临更多审查和法律挑战。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然减少责任是一项负责任的举措，但领导者应注意确保他们防范法律风险的努力不会变成因恐惧而放弃有效的 DEI 实践。在这个动荡的时期保持 DEI 进步和承诺的关键在于有意识地采取行动：减少对最具法律风险的种族数据的使用，同时采取果断行动继续使用种族数据来消除歧视、消除偏见并创造更公平的工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;减少法律风险&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;要了解如何在这个复杂的主题上采取最佳行动，重要的是从法律基础开始。根据&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ftc.gov/policy-notices/no-fear-act/protections-against-discrimination&quot;>;《民权法案》第七章&lt;/a>;，在任何雇佣决策中考虑任何单一候选人或员工的种族都是违法的，即使是为了打造一支更加多元化、公平或包容的劳动力队伍。雇主无法制定事实上的招聘配额（例如，“该部门雇用的员工中 50% 必须是女性”），或为某些群体的员工“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wilmerhale.com/en/insights/blogs/esg-epicenter/20220524-california-court-strikes-down-law-on-board-diversity&quot;>;预留席位&lt;/a>;”，即使是为了多元化。&lt;/p >; &lt;p>;根据法律，即使在最高法院最近做出裁决之后，性别意识或种族意识的招聘做法也是允许的&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;，但仅作为有限、临时和高度结构化的一部分&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cov.com/en/news-and-insights/insights/2023/07/considerations-for-employers-following-the-eeocs-response-to-the-supreme-courts -ruling-on-race-thought-college-admissions?utm_source=pardot&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=clientalerts&amp;amp;sc_camp=2D3D522D49CB4CE599B743213715F288&quot;>;自愿平权行动计划&lt;/a>;，仅在雇主发现全公司或全行业招聘歧视的证据时才采取，只是为了纠正最初的不平衡，以及只要不对非目标群体成员造成“不当伤害”（意味着雇主不能解雇白人工人来雇用有色人种工人）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;只要遵循这些指导方针，雇主和 DEI 从业者都不需要惊慌。删除“多元化”这个词，发誓在工作中不提及种族，或者关闭与种族相关的亲和团体，都是有害的过度反应，并不能反映出真正的法律风险。就目前情况而言，绝大多数工作场所 DEI 计划&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/2023/06/29/legal-experts-supremecourt-affirmative-action/&quot;>;受到法律先例的强烈支持&lt;/a>;，并且不太可能受到最高法院裁决的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果做得正确，DEI 计划可以&lt;a href=&quot;https://ajg.com/us/news-and-insights/2021 /sep/diversity-equity-and-inclusion-an-important-loss-prevention-tool/&quot;>;减少&lt;/a>;就业歧视和敌对工作环境索赔的风险，并可以降低整个组织的风险。然而，雇主仍然可以通过审核现有计划来降低风险，以确保它们不会违反现行法律。法律不允许指导招聘经理利用个人种族作为个人候选人的“决胜局”或“加分”的政策。为特定社会群体的成员留出具体数量或百分比的角色或席位也同样存在风险。避免诸如禁止不属于特定种族的员工加入员工资源团体或指示招聘人员由符合特定人口统计标准的人来填补职位之类的硬性规定（例如，“您必须由有色人种女性来担任此职位。”）从本质上讲，如果一项政策、流程或做法需要了解个人的种族特征才能做出影响其就业的决定，您可能需要对其进行审查。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;收集种族数据以识别差异&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一些领导者可能会阅读上一段并假设降低风险的简单方法就是根本不收集任何种族数据。然而，做出这样的结论将是把婴儿和洗澡水一起倒掉，并可能使公司的 DEI 进展面临风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然使用个人的种族数据来影响招聘决定是非法的，但汇总整个候选人库的种族数据来确定与种族相关的整体差异是完全合理的。结合员工敬业度调查收集人口统计数据可能会揭示会议参与方面的种族差距，值得仔细研究。结合人力资源数据收集人口统计数据可能会揭示值得干预的营业额中的种族差距。换句话说，收集人口数据（包括种族）可以揭示现有做法、先前的歧视性做法或劳动力池的历史限制所造成的不利影响，这些标准均由平等就业机会委员会的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.constangy.com/affirmative-action-alert/increase-diversity-without-violating-the-law&quot;>;自愿平权行动指南&lt;/a>;专门列出。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种数据驱动的方法不仅符合规定符合当前雇主指南，但它在确保 DEI 举措产生可衡量的影响方面也非常有效。具有社会意识的投资者、员工和客户希望雇主超越公开的承诺声明，采取具体行动来纠正组织、行业和社会中真正的不平等现象。收集种族数据以获取有关您的组织、行业甚至社会中不平等现象的信息，是您作为领导者可以采取的最有价值的 DEI 相关行动之一，并确保您在采取行动时，心中有明确的目标，有目的地工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据消除普遍障碍&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;对 DEI 举措的一个常见误解是这样的假设：如果发现种族差异，DEI 举措会通过给予边缘化群体来纠正这种差异。群体的优惠待遇——所谓的“反向歧视”。例如，一些管理者可能会认为，如果分析揭示了种族招聘歧视，DEI 举措将寻求以牺牲白人员工为代价来“为边缘化人群提供工作机会”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种粗暴和零和的做法不仅是公然非法的，而且还可能会损害白人员工的利益。这也与 DEI 工作的现实相去甚远。最有效的 DEI 计划使用种族数据来识别在工作场所损害公平和精英管理的歧视性障碍，并制定为每个人消除这些障碍的举措。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，如果使用种族数据的分析发现，由于缺乏标准的晋升流程和候选人的较高准入门槛，黑人、亚洲人、拉丁裔和土著经理候选人面临不成比例的障碍，那么 DEI 举措可能会与所有领导者合作制定标准化的晋升流程，培训领导者如何使用它以及如何消除偏见，并自动考虑所有员工在任职三年后晋升。这些举措还有一个额外的好处，那就是减少经理的偏袒、裙带关系和其他可能对任何背景的员工产生负面影响的不道德行为。大多数 DEI 举措都遵循这种模式：他们收集边缘群体的数据，以设计更适合每个人的工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据纠正歧视&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;当雇主寻求&lt;a href=&quot;/2020/11/how-to-identify-and-fix-pay-inequality-at-your-company&quot;>;薪酬公平审计&lt;/a>;时，他们会了解不同背景的员工是否在同工同酬中得到公平的报酬。如果答案是否定的，那么负责任的雇主可能会主动向受影响的员工提供欠薪，以纠正不平等现象。额外的工资不会像零和游戏那样从未受影响的员工身上“拿走”；雇主提供的信息是为了把事情做对：做大蛋糕，而不是争夺蛋糕。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，如果雇主使用种族数据来确定白人经理正在获得更多的机会来承担具有挑战性的项目、建立人际网络并接受高级领导者的指导，那么除了消除普遍的机会障碍之外，他们可能会主动创造更多的机会，为边缘化群体的成员提供具有挑战性的项目、人际网络和指导。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;以这种方式使用数据的令人惊讶的好处之一是它可以帮助您的员工了解 DEI 计划背后的基本原理。因为大多数人都认为工作场所本质上是公平的，或者是精英管理的，除非事实证明并非如此，所以 DEI 举措（例如，成立一个员工资源小组，主要针对拉丁裔员工进行活动规划）可能会遭到那些对优惠待遇感到焦虑的人的冷漠或强烈反对。通过将 DEI 工作建立在数据基础上（例如，通过分析显示与白人员工相比，拉丁裔员工相对缺乏社区、支持和归属感），您可以帮助您的员工了解 DEI 计划的重要性，并为您支持员工的承诺感到自豪。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据设计公平流程&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;您不能使用个人的种族信息来让他们比其他候选人提高 30% 的分数。除了遵循上述指导方针的高度限制的自愿平权行动计划之外，您不能将 30% 的职位分配给边缘化种族群体的成员。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但是&lt;em>;，&lt;/em>;您可以规定招聘流程的每个阶段都由至少 30% 合格的有色人种候选人组成，然后再继续（这种做法称为&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.diversitylab.com/pilot-projects/mansfield-overview/&quot;>;曼斯菲尔德规则&lt;/a>;，或&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclusocal.org/en/inclusion-targets-whats-legal&quot;>;包容附加条款&lt;/a>;）。虽然这些做法通常旨在纠正全行业的歧视或有限的劳动力资源，但没有一位候选人的被雇用几率高于或低于下一位候选人。雇主只需在继续之前花额外的时间有意扩大候选人库即可。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;类似的流程可以与其他消除偏见的做法结合起来，以进一步确保公平。例如，您可以明确表示任何自愿共享的种族数据都不会与个人的候选资格相关联。您甚至可能要求处理候选人库多样性种族数据的个人与做出就业决定的人分开工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;使用种族数据来展示 DEI 进展&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;一些领导者可能出于值得称赞的最初理由而投资 DEI 举措和计划，因为他们“显然”需要支持劳动力。然而，当这些举措顺利进行时，这些领导者可能会不确定下一步该做什么。当形势好的时候，这些 DEI 举措被视为成功、以人为本的工作场所的标志。但是，当组织面临财务压力、面临业务挑战并且必须兼顾相互竞争的优先事项时，由于缺乏充分的理由，DEI 可能会使其成为&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/protecting-dei-progress-when-budgets-are-tight&quot;>;预算削减的首要目标&lt;/a>;。既无法证明 DEI 计划存在的基于证据的理由，也无法对 DEI 计划的有效性进行基于证据的评估的组织将永远无法将其 DEI 努力与短暂的趋势和时尚脱钩。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于&lt;em>;&lt;/em>;使用显示种族差异或未满足需求的数据启动 DEI 计划的组织来说，种族数据可能是证明其持续存在合理性的最有力工具。如果您的&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/to-understand-whether-your-company-is-inclusive-map-how-your-employees-interact&quot;>;网络分析&lt;/a>;或&lt;a href=&quot;https ://www.cultureamp.com/blog/employee-belonging&quot;>;归属感调查&lt;/a>;量化了参与决策过程的种族差距，您可以使用这些调查结果作为设计新决策过程的基本原理，创建咨询委员会向领导者通报情况，并依靠员工资源小组与有色人种员工分享有关他们的意见正在被征求的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;通过再次运行相同的分析并比较您收到的数据，您&#39;您将能够对您的计划的成功或失败做出强有力的推论，并利用这些发现进一步改进您的 DEI 计划。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;要记住的原则&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;不要：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;恐慌、放弃 DEI 努力或出于毫无根据的恐惧而损害有效举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;为依赖于了解他们的种族或民族，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;向种族群体成员分配或保留一定比例的理想资源（例如，晋升、职位、任务） ，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;使用人们的种族数据在任何决定中给予他们提升或贬低，没有事先分析显示差异，也没有首先与法律顾问交谈法律顾问。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;表达对任何角色或职位的种族偏好、标准或限制，无需事先分析显示差异，也无需先与法律顾问交谈。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;应该：&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;使用种族数据为招聘工作提供信息并使候选人库多样化（例如，通过使用曼斯菲尔德规则）。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;汇总种族数据以保持匿名而不失去群体-级别洞察力。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;利用种族数据来识别组织中的种族不平等和差异。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;引用种族数据来设计消除障碍和纠正歧视的 DEI 工作和举措。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>; li>; &lt;li>;参考纵向种族数据来显示 DEI 进展、交流 DEI 计划的功效并庆祝您的胜利。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/to-drive-diversity- works-dont-tiptoe-around-your-legal-risk&quot;>;尽早与律师和法律专家合作&lt;/a>;，设计并沟通合法且有效的 DEI 计划。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p >;DEI 的工作不会消失，领导者也知道这一点：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bain.com/about/media-center/press-releases/2023/bain--company-study-shows- 85 的企业领导人将社会问题视为其公司的紧急关注点/&quot;>;根据最近的一项调查，85%&lt;/a>; 将社会问题视为“紧急”问题。员工和消费者仍然期望组织不仅承诺做得更好，而且&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/to-make-having-progress-on-dei-measure-outcomes&quot;>;实现可衡量的成果&lt;/a >; 这可以证明他们的言论并非空话。这样做需要基于证据的 DEI 工作——需要合法有效地收集和使用种族数据以及其他人口统计数据——成为这项工作的新标准。如果做得好，您将能够同时支撑您的法律风险，并加速您的组织向您的选民期望从其 DEI 计划中获得更高的透明度、问责制和有效性标准的过渡。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这只是DEI 的下一步发展是在 1964 年《民权法案》的基础上，为争取工作中更大的多样性、公平性和包容性而进行的长期斗争，并得到了数十年的广泛支持。您的组织如何满足当前的需求将决定您如何适应 DEI 旅程的下一阶段。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>; &lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br >;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Research: A Little Nature in the Office Boosts Morale and Productivity]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/research-a-little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/Jul23_19_MaryHaasdykVooys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;玛丽·哈斯戴克·沃伊斯 (Mary Haasdyk Vooys) 插图&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;综述。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;“微观自然”研究&amp;#8212;将小型、经济实惠的自然元素融入工作场所——展示了其对员工绩效和福祉的积极影响。研究表明，在工作中接触大自然可以提高生产力、乐于助人和创造力，而且没有证据表明存在负面影响。建议包括真实的和人造的自然，延伸到办公环境之外，利用未充分利用的空间，并鼓励工作时间之外接触自然。工作场所与自然的融合可提高整体业务绩效。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a- Little-nature-in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/research-a-little-nature -in-the-office-boosts-morale-and-productivity?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;位于金丝雀码头，这个繁华的地区是许多全球企业的伦敦基地企业、开发商正在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.architectsjournal.co.uk/news/glenn-howells-and-eden-project-to-give-canary-wharf-a-green-revamp&quot;>;构建一个“绿色脊柱”&lt;/a>;很快就会蜿蜒穿过摩天大楼，让工人们在工作日可以随时进入绿色空间。在城镇另一边正在建设中的 Google 英国总部，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/6/1/15723642/google-london-office-pictures-headquarters-kings-cross&quot;>;300大楼顶部有一米长的屋顶公园&lt;/a>;，种植了 250 多棵树，为员工提供了逃离办公室和下面城市环境的自然场所。在大西洋的另一边，零售商 LL Bean 将其中一个仓库的中间切掉，将空间变成一个庭院，以便每个人&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90908239/ll- bean-new-headquarters&quot;>;在他们的新家庭办公室&lt;/a>;在工作时可以欣赏到大自然的景色。 These real-world examples of incorporating nature into commercial spaces are part of a growing trend to design places where employees can be immersed in nature during their workdays.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Increasing nature in the work environment certainly aligns with many companies&#39; sustainability initiatives. However, the motive also stems from nature&#39;s effect on humans — it is well established that nature makes us feel better. Our emotions, our thinking, our connection to others, and our physical well-being &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amr.2017.0177&quot;>;are all enhanced by being in and around nature&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the connection between contact with nature and our well-being, large investments in bringing nature into the workplace raise some thorny issues. First, in a time of economic headwinds and cost-cutting, is there a business case for incorporating nature into employees&#39; surroundings? Second, what about those workplaces where it is not feasible or sensible to incorporate a green spine or a rooftop garden?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Answering these questions requires first understanding whether nature has effects on metrics that matter to organizations&#39; bottom lines (eg, employee satisfaction and performance) and if so whether less-extreme doses of nature are meaningful enough to elicit these gains. Thus, we set out to test the effects (if any) of what we call &lt;em>;micro-nature &lt;/em>;— small, affordable, seemingly innocuous ways of incorporating nature into the workplace — on how employees feel at work, and how they perform.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Research&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;We measured or manipulated contact with nature at work in different ways across multiple studies, with workers in the US, Canada, China, New Zealand, and Indonesia. In experiments, working adults were simply shown images of workplaces suffused with natural elements or matching images without nature. We then asked them to imagine they worked in these spaces and report how it would make them feel and perform. We also conducted more complex studies in real-world work settings. For instance, we assessed employees&#39; actual contact with nature during a week at work (eg, working near plants, natural views, or the sound of running water), and then measured their feelings and objective job performance. Finally, in a field experiment in an accounting firm, we went into the offices at night and placed potted plants at some employees&#39; desks and similar pots, only filled with office supplies, at other desks. We then measured the attitudes and job performance of the two groups and compared them.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The results were largely consistent across these studies: Experiencing even small doses of nature at work improved the way employees felt in ways that fueled &lt;a href=&quot;https://discovery.ucl.ac.uk/id/eprint/10166977/1/Tang%20et%20al%20final%20prepublished.pdf&quot;>;higher task performance, increased helping&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063231172182&quot;>;enhanced creativity&lt;/a>;. These findings indicate that incorporating micro-nature into work settings can contribute to worker well-being and performance in a meaningful way.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also looked into whether there were differences between employees that shaped how nature affected them at work — factors such as how much individuals appreciate nature in general, and the extent to which they are drawn to novel experiences. Our findings showed that some people are especially prone to experiencing the benefits of nature. However, we found no evidence that any employees were negatively impacted by nature exposure at work; thus, micro-nature seems to hold considerable promise for employees with little downsides.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bearing these findings in mind, we believe that nature should be accessible to as many employees as possible, not just those lucky enough to work below a green roof or alongside a park. Companies should provide employees with micro-nature experiences. Below, we offer suggestions for incorporating micro-nature into the workplace, while also encouraging managers to take liberties and get creative in their specific organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Capitalizing on Micro-Nature&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;Real is best, but artificial works too.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Giving employees opportunities to access “the real thing” is ideal when it comes to nature: indoor water features, windows with views of nature or that open to let in natural sounds like birdsong. But just because it&#39;s not the real thing does not mean that employees will not benefit from nature. Research shows that even depictions of nature, such as murals and artificial flowers, can give employees a natural boost.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Think beyond the office…&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It goes without saying that it is not just office workers who benefit from nature. Employees in settings where the work environment feels especially removed from nature — think warehousing or manufacturing — are especially likely to notice a dash of the outdoors brought inside and be positively impacted by it because of how different it is from their status quo.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;…and beyond the workplace.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The benefits of nature extend beyond employees&#39; work lives. Some of our research looked at the work-related benefits of spending time outdoors in the evening, after the workday. We found that employees &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/01492063221106430&quot;>;were more productive the next day&lt;/a>; when they spent time outdoors the prior evening. Especially for hybrid and remote workers, the implications are clear: The benefits of being around nature at home carry over into work. So even incentivizing employees to take an evening walk can help them be more productive the next day.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Utilize unused or underused spaces.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;By definition, micro-nature is small, and can be as simple as painting a wall with natural tones, adding flowers to the break room, or landscaping the area outside employees&#39; windows. We encourage managers to keep an eye out for the unused or underused spaces around their workplace that can be easily and cheaply turned into natural features. For instance, adding more landscaping to an overly industrial parking lot may boost employees&#39; morale.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Overall, our findings indicate that the benefits of connecting employees to nature at work extend beyond sustainability, and include positive effects on employees&#39; well-being and how they perform their jobs. As such, we view contact with nature as a valuable supplement to well-designed jobs that already include meaningful work, fair compensation, and respectful treatment. For firms that provide these things and are looking for more ways to enhance the environment in which their employees work, micro-nature offers considerable promise.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Companies Need to Prove They Can Be Trusted with Technology]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1282056839.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Hiroshi Watanabe/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Trust in technology &amp;#8212; and the companies that use it &amp;#8212; has taken a hit over the past few years. Transgressions against individuals&amp;#8217; privacy, calcification of corporate or individual biases into life-altering algorithms, constant threats that new tech erodes their ability to make a living, and beta testing unsecured or faulty connected devices or vehicles on an unsuspecting populace have encouraged healthy skepticism. To rebuild digital trust, companies need to pursue three broad goals: security and reliability, accountability and oversight, and inclusive, responsible, ethical use. Practically, this requires three steps: 1) define a vision for digital trust, 2) plan to act in more trustworthy ways, and 3) recruit people who will help earn trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/companies-need-to-prove-they-can-be-trusted-with-technology?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Technological solutionism — the idea that tech developers can be trusted to innovate or code our way out of problems, and into prosperity — is on its way out. Individuals&#39; trust in tech and the companies who develop it has been eroded by innumerable failures. For businesses, it&#39;s no longer acceptable to use technology without taking steps to ensure it&#39;s trustworthy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regular people — and, increasingly, legislators and regulators — have reasonably been made skeptical by recent transgressions against individuals&#39; privacy, calcification of corporate or individual biases into life-altering algorithms, constant threats that new tech erodes their ability to make a living, and beta testing unsecured or faulty connected devices or vehicles on an unsuspecting populace. Looking at the near future, with generative AI and virtual worlds being implemented faster than we can track, the trust problem is only getting worse.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;More tech isn&#39;t going to solve this problem. Customers are looking at the choices that company leaders make and assessing whether those choices match individual consumers and citizens&#39; values — and whether they put people first. And because every company uses some form of digital technology in its operations and relationships with customers and partners, every company needs to worry about digital trust. “Digital trust programs are a necessity, and when done right, can be both a differentiator and enabler for a business. As demands rise for companies to show they are trustworthy, organizations should strive to build a digital trust strategy that meets or exceeds their customers&#39; expectations, not just what&#39;s legally required,” according to Vikram Rao, Salesforce&#39;s Chief Trust Officer and a member of the World Economic Forum Digital Trust Steering Committee.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Some companies may look at the problem and hope they can buy or hire their way out of it. In some cases, a new role, like a Chief Trust Officer or Chief Digital Trust Officer may help. But before CEOs and boards rush into creating a c-suite role as a panacea, they need to take a hard look at what exactly trustworthy technology looks like in the 21st century, how companies earn digital trust, and what changes and investments they need to make to do that.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What makes technology trustworthy?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;No technology is inherently trustworthy or untrustworthy. After all, technologies have no agency in themselves; instead, as a character in the Afrofuturist film &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://greatergood.berkeley.edu/article/item/twelve_new_films_that_highlight_the_best_in_humanity&quot;>;Neptune Frost&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; puts it, “technology is only a reflection of us.” Trust in technology is a reflection of the decisions people make when they develop the tech, use it, and implement it. While there are many ways to think about trust, when the World Economic Forum convened business, government, and civil society leaders in the field of trustworthy tech, the assembled group &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;reached this consensus&lt;/a>;: “Digital trust is individuals&#39; expectation that digital technologies and services — and the organizations providing them — will protect all stakeholders&#39; interests and uphold societal expectations and values.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this work, the Forum&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/community&quot;>;Digital Trust Community&lt;/a>; realized that the most important question to ask with regard to technology is not “how do you get people to trust technology?” Rather it&#39;s “what do we need to do — as technology developers, owners, and users — to respect people&#39;s values and expectations?” With the right mindset and the right goals, it&#39;s possible to develop an effective and trustworthy strategy for the use of digital technology. At its heart, such a trustworthy tech strategy comes from consideration for the individuals subjected to new technologies (regardless of the technology in question).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With respect for individual rights and expectations in mind, a trustworthy digital technology strategy should identify the right goals. The World Economic Forum&#39;s digital trust community offered three broad sets of goals:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Security and Reliability&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Accountability and Oversight, and&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Inclusive, Ethical, and Responsible Use&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;As Julie Brill, Microsoft&#39;s Chief Privacy Officer and a member of the Forum&#39;s Digital Trust Steering Committee said at the time, “the goals of any developer of AI or other technologies should mirror the goals of the organizations and individuals who use or encounter that technology. Shared goals of inclusivity and responsible use, strong privacy and security protections, and effective oversight are the foundational elements to building a trustworthy relationship between developers, their customers, and individuals who use the technology.” Users and consumers can better rely on technologies that protect them, that include their needs and match their values, and that have good governance practices baked in, to remediate any inadvertent harms.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do you invest in digital trust?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Earning digital trust isn&#39;t simple, and it can&#39;t be automated. Rather it requires a series of judgment calls, investments, and organizational changes that reflect the totality of a technology&#39;s likely impact on individuals. These shifts, encompassing the whole business, can only be orchestrated by company leaders. As Keith Enright, Chief Privacy Officer at Google and Digital Trust Steering Committee member, said, “decisions companies are making now about preparedness determine where they will be down the line in terms of trust.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Becoming prepared to start earning back trust requires CEOs and Boards of Directors to do at least three things:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Define a vision for digital trust&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Plan to act in more trustworthy ways&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Recruit people who will help earn trust&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The first investment leaders need to make is to take the time and energy to truly understand the impact of the technologies they create or deploy. Developing a realistic and comprehensive vision for how an organization uses technology in service of its goals and those of the people who rely on it determines how an organization will invest in digital trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders should approach decisions involving technology with a clear sense of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_World_Economic_Forum_Digital_Trust_Initiative_2023.pdf&quot;>;how those technologies reflect and impact core organizational values&lt;/a>; and the values of the society in which the business operates. Their vision for creating or adopting new technologies must consider both the benefits to the business and society alongside a clear and responsible assessment of the potential harms new technologies might impose on potential customers or other stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a business adopting generative AI must assess how the technology might increase efficiencies (a benefit to the business), unlock new solutions to pressing challenges (a benefit to society) while also developing a plan to prevent &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/managing-the-risks-of-generative-ai&quot;>;expected harms&lt;/a>;, for example, to democratic processes from AI “hallucinations” or misinformation and to workers displaced by these advanced technologies. Only a vision that responsibly considers both the benefits and the risk of new technology can truly be considered trustworthy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;After deciding on a vision that includes trustworthy goals, organizations need a plan to act for digital trust. This plan requires leaders to invest in the internal structures and teams that best support digital trust. For all applications of digital technology, the Forum&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://initiatives.weforum.org/digital-trust/framework&quot;>;work&lt;/a>; identified eight dimensions where positive action can help achieve an organization&#39;s goals — both trust goals and overall financial or strategic goals. Those dimensions are cybersecurity, safety, transparency, interoperability, auditability, redressability, fairness and privacy. (As with the Digital Trust Goals, these dimensions are defined and explored in the Forum&#39;s Insight Report, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/reports/earning-digital-trust-decision-making-for-trustworthy-technologies&quot;>;&lt;em>;Earning Digital Trust: Decision-making for Trustworthy Technologies&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In most organizations, these areas likely fall to different departments and leaders, which means optimizing them requires an interdisciplinary approach — and possibly some structural change — in order to support the careful decision-making required to earn trust from users and other stakeholders. However, the realities of a given industry or company may mean it&#39;s not possible to maximize every one of the dimensions described. For example, greater transparency may not be possible for companies who work in highly-sensitive industries (eg, national security), so their accountability and security would have to supplement. Similarly, some dimensions of trustworthiness (perhaps most noticeably privacy) vary between jurisdictions and geographies. People&#39;s expectations and values are the litmus test for what makes technology trustworthy. Trust, itself, may be highly region and industry specific.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The third big initial investment is in the people who can help the business earn digital trust. Making technology trustworthy is a multi-faceted effort conducted on an organizational (or societal) scale — which means that ultimate responsibility for trustworthiness falls to the CEO. This general duty of trustworthy technology decision-making doesn&#39;t mean, however, that the business shouldn&#39;t invest in recruiting experts (maybe even on the c-suite), who can help establish the right strategy, and the right structures, to support digital trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This leader, possibly a Chief Trust Officer — but just as likely to be the Chief Privacy Officer, General Counsel, CISO, or another executive — must be both an expert in stakeholder management and a trusted counselor to the CEO and the board. Stakeholder management comes into play where companies already have cybersecurity, privacy, compliance, and even ethics functions. The leads for each of those roles has a stake in the overall trustworthiness of the digital strategy of a company — in both building it and benefiting from it. In order to be a counselor on digital trust, this individual must also be able to think systemically — bridging between these disciplines in order to help leaders make the best judgement call on how, where, and toward what ends new technologies should be applied.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In order to be most effective, an officer responsible for digital trust can&#39;t be an expert on every technology and every facet of trust, rather they have to be able to understand the strategy for the company and the values of affected individuals, workers, and customers. They support development of a trustworthy vision by conveying a system-wide picture of what the technology landscape looks like to CEOs and boards and helping build a strategy that supports trust rather than erodes it. They also help oversee the myriad and interdepending actions that, taken together, earn trust from users, partners, and other stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;CEOs must understand that trust in the technology that underlies and enables virtually every business can&#39;t be bought, but by investing in the time it takes to make the right decisions, establish a trustworthy vision, and recruit effective supporters, it can be earned.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 21:25:04 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What Happens After the U.S. Economy&rsquo;s Soft Landing?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-u-s-economys-soft-landing]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/July23_20_1427804800.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;baona/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;A year ago, a recession was seen as a foregone conclusion &amp;#8212; and yet the Fed appears to have successfully lowered inflation without triggering a recession. Many of the negative forecasts followed a pattern of underestimating the US economy&amp;#8217;s resilience, typically because they were based on historical models and precedent, not situational and idiosyncratic context. While the soft landing may be progressing with promise, it won&amp;#8217;t be an end state &amp;#8212; a new disequilibrium will emerge. Leaders can&amp;#8217;t wait for macroeconomic certainty or stability. Instead, they must recognize that the macroeconomy will remain untamed by models &amp;#8212; and that what matters is judgment.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/07/what-happens-after-the-us-economys-soft-landing?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The US economy has defied the doomsayers once again. More than a year has passed since a recession was seen as a foregone conclusion and a “soft landing” pronounced near impossible. But today, the soft landing is well advanced, even if not complete: The Fed has found success in lowering inflation without triggering a recession. The labor market, the only reliable evidence that the economy is in recession, has cooled without pushing up the unemployment rate.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though this is welcome news, the protracted uncertainty surrounding the economy has confounded many leaders — and came at a cost for those who hunkered down prematurely in anticipation of recession. This uncertainty will persist. What comes after the soft landing (if in fact it can be completed)? To answer this question, we look at why the recession calls were wrong and what lies ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Recession Prophecies, Unfulfilled&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As in the pandemic, when doomsayers predicted a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.project-syndicate.org/commentary/coronavirus-greater-great-depression-by-nouriel-roubini-2020-03&quot;>;Greater Depression&lt;/a>;,” much negativity dominated public discourse of the last year and a half. Some leaders predicted a “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/06/01/jamie-dimon-says-brace-yourself-for-an-economic-hurricane-caused-by-the-fed-and-ukraine-war.html&quot;>;hurricane&lt;/a>;” would hit the economy shortly; others &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@alex.domash/can-job-vacancies-fall-without-an-increase-in-unemployment-1031fe19c635&quot;>;dismissed even the possibility&lt;/a>; of a soft landing.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But as the below graphic illustrates, that is exactly what has played out over the last 16 months. Job openings have come off their highs as firms feel under less strain, and quit rates have fallen as workers feel less enticed to jump ship — all while hiring (“payrolls”) continues at a robust pace. As the unemployment rate remains near its 60-year low there is no sign of recession.&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-describedby=&quot;caption-attachment-360940&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/07/W230719_SZLEZAK_SOFT_LANDING_360.png&quot; >; &quot; title=&quot;US Labor Market&#39;s Progress Toward a Soft Landing.&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;1592&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;See more HBR charts in Data &amp;amp; Visuals &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;What went wrong, or, more appropriately, what went right?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many of the negative forecasts followed a pattern of underestimating the US economy&#39;s resilience, typically because they were based on historical models and precedent – not situational and idiosyncratic context. Consider the following four displays of resilience:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Labor market resilience.&lt;/strong>; The widespread assumption was that monetary policy would push labor demand collectively under water. Instead we have seen pockets of weakness, covered by aggregate strength. Significant layoffs happened where hiring had overshot (eg, tech) but in other sectors (eg, services) hiring was still catching up and remained strong. Laid-off workers found new jobs. Resilience was found in the unusual economic diversification of recessionary sectors with booming ones.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Consumer resilience.&lt;/strong>; Growing layoffs, inflation eating away at household budgets, and falling portfolios weakening balance sheets led to predictions of a collapse in spending. But the context mattered. Balance sheets had buffers, including cash. And while individual budgets were squeezed, the total number of incomes continued to grow rapidly as hiring persisted, providing consumer strength. The aggregate downdraft has not happened.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Housing resilience.&lt;/strong>; A common fear has been that rising interest rates would kneecap the housing market — delaying construction activity, pushing down prices, or even, as some doomsayers predicted, causing another housing-centered recession. But these narratives overlooked the fact that activity remains precisely because &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/08/09/real-estate-housing-market-falling-prices-economic-risk/&quot;>;housing inventory is low&lt;/a>;. As a result, higher rates have tamped down — rather than choked — housing activity. Housing starts and prices dipped, and transactions fell, but they have stabilized and are rising again.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Financial system resilience.&lt;/strong>; Another common fear was that the Fed will hike until something breaks. The idea that the financial system would be the collateral damage of higher rates is not unreasonable as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/03/15/svb-collapse-financial-instability-fed-inflation-recession-finance-banks-economy-carlsson-szlezak-swartz/&quot;>;collapse of SVB demonstrated&lt;/a>;. But the risk of contagion was overestimated, while the ability of policy-makers to avert it was underestimated.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;The better-than-expected outcomes share a pattern. Each concern had merit but was considered too narrowly. The idiosyncratic, contextual, and situational drivers mattered more than what historical relationships — and the models that are based on them — said about these sectors.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lesson that cannot be learned often enough, it seems, is that trust in macroeconomic models remains too strong. The idiosyncrasies of the cycle call for judgment rather than precise forecasts. Meanwhile, the doomsaying is routinely amplified as the microphone is reliably passed to the gloomiest voices.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;The Path Ahead&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Economics often unhelpfully frames the economic cycle as “moving to equilibrium.” (The aviation analogy of a “soft landing” is similarly guilty.) In reality, we are always moving from one idiosyncratic disequilibrium to another, meaning &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/business-forecasts-are-reliably-wrong-yet-still-valuable&quot;>;executives cannot rely on forecasts&lt;/a>;. New idiosyncratic drivers will always deliver new situations that models won&#39;t readily pick up on.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, what could the new disequilibrium be?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Though the first stages of the soft landing are a success, ruling out a recession would be a mistake. It remains a possible, even plausible, outcome (and over time an inevitability). Monetary policy still has a foot on the brake. Real shocks can always end a cycle, particularly when growth is already slow and the economy thus more vulnerable, and financial stressors, such as bank failures, can pop up unexpectedly. Considering the &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/03/assessing-the-current-risks-to-the-us-economy&quot;>;three types of recession&lt;/a>; risk remains indispensable, but we still view recession risk in the near term as much lower than consensus.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A re-acceleration is more likely, as a resilient economy successfully weathers this period of weak (but non-recessionary) growth. Yet, such a re-acceleration could play out in different ways – some are welcome, others are not.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 1: A Re-run of the Overshooting Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If demand picks up strongly and outstrips the economy&#39;s capacity (think available labor, capital, and known processes), another bout of inflation is likely. This would necessitate a fresh round of monetary tightening with all the risks we discussed above.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Even so, it would &lt;em>;not&lt;/em>; immediately point to an “inflation regime break” — the mistaken narrative of the last two years that the US economy was seeing a structural return of inflation. It would mean another bout of cyclical inflation that comes (and goes) with a mismatch of demand and supply.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 2: A Just-Right Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;If demand grows in line with the economy&#39;s capacity, the expansion can plod along at acceptable growth rates without renewed inflation pressures. Monetary policy could ease from its very tight stance toward a more neutral stance — until a shift toward a new disequilibrium arises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;strong>;Scenario 3: A Better-Than-Good Economy&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;We know this has arrived when the economy&#39;s capacity grows considerably faster than demand, facilitating rapid growth without concomitant cyclical inflation. While strong capital formation and strong labor participation can help facilitate this scenario to a degree, it&#39;s crux would be an acceleration of productivity growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Can this happen and is it likely?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many are eager to pencil in much higher growth courtesy of ChatGPT and other applications of AI — but not so fast. The mere availability of labor does not guarantee faster productivity growth; think of tech as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/08/the-secret-of-productivity-growth-is-not-technology/&quot;>;just the fuel&lt;/a>;. The &lt;em>;spark&lt;/em>; typically comes in the form of tight labor markets. When firms are forced to substitute capital for labor, they tend to do more of it. When they can&#39;t hire the next worker, they transform their processes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such sustained labor market tightness and its benefits are a realistic prospect. Still, leaders should remain prudent about size and speed of such gains. Big productivity gains at the macroeconomic level come gradually, not abruptly, and their size is often overestimated — as we saw in the pandemic, when analysts rushed to pencil in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/10/how-to-be-realistic-about-covids-impact-on-productivity-growth/&quot;>;an extra 1 percentage point of growth&lt;/a>; that did not materialize.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The benefits of such a scenario would be broader than just somewhat higher growth. Tight labor markets create real wage growth across the income distribution, and the biggest winners tend to be at the bottom of the distribution. This creates opportunities for career advancement and job creation for those who have had fewer opportunities or struggled to get on the job ladder, and it pulls into the labor market those who may have otherwise exited.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While the soft landing may be progressing with promise, it won&#39;t be an end state — a new disequilibrium will emerge. Leaders can&#39;t wait for macroeconomic certainty or stability. Instead, they must recognize that the macroeconomy will remain untamed by models — and that what matters is judgment. Gloomy headlines will persist, and economic models will offer a flat view of the world that misses out on critical context. Leaders must apply the same skills they employ each day to lead their firms through uncertainty to navigating the macroeconomy. They must avoid both overreacting to the latest piece of data and preparing for only one unchanging view the future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For firms, the &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/why-firms-are-struggling-with-the-us-economys-soft-landing&quot;>;challenges of a tight economy&lt;/a>;, including margin pressure, as well as higher, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/06/07/inflation-interest-rates-higher-but-healthy-bcg/&quot;>;healthy interest rates&lt;/a>;, are likely here to stay — but they are preferable to the alternative of recession. Meeting these challenges head on means more capital for labor substitution, more reinvention, and more technological absorption. Each of these form the foundation of the better-than-good economic scenario.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>