<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[Businesses Need to Bring Younger Employees into Their Leadership Ranks]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/businesses-need-to-bring-younger-employees-into-their-leadership-ranks]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_12_864707740.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;RichVintage/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;企业在应对气候变化等当今时代的挑战方面发挥着至关重要的作用。为了提高他们在这个领域的效率，他们必须对开发我们所需的创新更加好奇，并且更加渴望相应地调整他们的行为。如今，老化的领导结构可能会阻碍这一点。努力实现代际领导力是克服这些问题并通过增强企业实力来释放竞争优势的关键。续订容量。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;PGI0xetTRG9lQhkv18mrb+ZIgXb2YEiFYp+QigILXQ7R8PFtEc7XfkmhYu2wB6Z6&quot; data- index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW4uuNinQXO5tM3CarXyYyK30Lp5WXHCShyRMFY+FvxhXw==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; data-page-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;10&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;businesses-need -to-bring-younger-employees-into-their-leadership-ranks&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;寻址气候变化和生物多样性丧失等挑战需要技术创新。因此，对发现新方法的强烈好奇心是关键。但同样重要的是，我们愿意，甚至渴望相应地改变我们的信念和行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 23:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Project Management Strategies for a Hybrid Workplace]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/3-project-management-strategies-for-a-hybrid-workplace]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_12_1202264382.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jorg Greuel/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;在混合项目中，沟通和协调变得更加关键和更具挑战性。数字工具和会议可能是一些团队成员保持联系的&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;唯一&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;方式。 &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;根据作者运行数十个 Web 开发和内容项目的经验，混合项目经理需要考虑三个关键领域：如何规划和实施以合适的人员和期望启动项目，如何设置工具以便每个人都可以使用它们，以及如何有效地使用会议。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;/div>; &lt;content js-target=&quot;article-content&quot; data-key=&quot;Uuz5WyKxJ3W9Beyw0/F0vpbaWtA7hBNK8xxq3pD2LZMSHDJHly6HCdYY5e8JUFsm&quot; data-index=&quot;BM5l29iJY6Ee+8B2yfNlrdgbvN4VLOJhHh/T44P8lW4uuN inQXO5tM3CarXyYyK3QISJNZ1dzXD7p+tTIRvFOw==&quot; data-waiver=&quot;false&quot; 数据页-year=&quot;2023&quot; data-page-month=&quot;10&quot; data-page-seo-title=&quot;3-project-management-strategies-for-a-hybrid-workplace&quot; data-page-adUnit-locations=&quot;&quot; data-page-slug=&quot;article&quot; data-piano-verified=&quot;false&quot; >; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;混合团队工作可能会放大任何项目固有的风险。每个项目都取决于组建合适的团队、确保每个人都清楚自己要交付的内容、建立沟通规范以及管理好会议，但在混合项目中，这些事情变得更加关键和更具挑战性。你可能很难让每个人都达成共识。您可能从未见过他们中的一些人。数字工具和会议可能是&lt;/span>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;唯一的&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;方式一些团队成员可以保持联系。&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/content>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Business Case for Love]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/the-business-case-for-love]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_12_1140416930.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;费尔南多·特拉班科摄影/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;虽然人工智能改变了游戏规则，但它远非当今商业领域最强大的力量。作者花了几十年的时间研究最敬业的团队“以及最忠实的客户——已经确定了一种强有力地驱动消费者和员工行为的力量：爱。当有人说他们“爱”时在进行某项活动时，他的研究发现，这并不是粗心的夸大其词。这意味着在做这项活动时，这个人正在蓬勃发展。热爱自己所做的事情的员工会感到轻松、掌控、全神贯注于自己正在做的事情，并且工作效率更高。喜爱产品的顾客不仅是忠诚的，而且是忠诚的。他们很可能成为某个品牌的拥护者。然而，大多数企业并没有研究人们为什么喜欢他们的产品或喜欢为他们工作，也没有释放它的策略。本文提供了组织如何将爱融入其产品的示例。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/the -business-case-for-love?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/the-business-case-for-love?language=pt&quot;>;阅读em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;人工智能火车在铁轨上疾驰，让我们害怕，让我们兴奋，还发出一阵喧闹声。它可以写诗、检测气候变化的天气模式以及准翻译鲸鱼的歌曲。皮尤有 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/07/26/which-us-workers-are-more-expose-to-ai-on-their-jobs/&quot; >;预测&lt;/a>;近五分之一的美国工人从事的工作极有可能被人工智能改变。它是一个游戏规则改变者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但人工智能并不是商业中最强大的力量——绝对不是。在快速生成模式方面，人工智能是无与伦比的。当谈到驱动客户和员工的行为时，人工智能是无用的。而且永远都是这样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我的职业生涯一直在研究卓越，早在 1990 年就开始了盖洛普对华特迪士尼世界最优秀管家的研究。我一直在寻找世界上最优秀的经理、领导者、教师和销售人员的共同点，并且研究了是什么推动了最敬业的团队和最忠诚的客户。在数千个这样的定性焦点小组和访谈中，有一种力量最有力地驱动客户和员工的行为。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种力量就是爱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们回避这个词，依赖于相反，使用更适合企业的短语，例如“员工敬业度”或“客户忠诚度”。我们很乐意谈论“关怀文化”或“热情服务”或“客户满意度”。但我们避开了爱。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今天，企业界的大部分人都被人工智能的前景所迷惑和分心，是时候审视爱了，这是所有感情中最人性化的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我与数十万高绩效员工的对话中，他们都谈到了工作中他们喜欢的特定时刻或活动。他们不会说“喜欢”或“享受”。他们说“爱”。当他们说“爱”时，这意味着他们想继续回到这项活动并寻找机会做更多的事情。当他们从事自己喜欢的活动时，他们的工作会更加流畅，压力也会更小。我的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.loveandwork.org/&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，在自己所做的事情中找到热爱的员工更有可能留在自己的工作岗位上，并宣传自己的公司一个很棒的地方。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这同样适用于客户。我认识一位电影制片厂高管，他说，当他对最新电影进行试镜时，他听到的不是“我真的很喜欢”或“我认为这很棒”。他只注意有多少次听到有人自发地说：“我喜欢它！”因为只有这样，他才能确定这个人会告诉其他人去看电影——甚至自己会回去看多次。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对于所有产品的所有客户来说都是如此。只有当你成功地做到了如此引人注目、如此深刻、如此真诚、如此感人的事情时，客户才会说：“我喜欢这种体验！”您能够预测他们随后的行为。与此形成鲜明对比的是，“喜欢”或“真正享受”或“满意”实际上并不能告诉我们任何有关一个人未来行为的信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;用数字衡量爱情&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;我们可以在数据中定量地看到这一点。让顾客、员工或电影观众对他们的体验的某些方面进行评分，评分范围为 1-5，其中 5 分表示非常积极。传统观点认为，这些感受会驱动人们的行为，例如客户的忠诚度、拥护度和支出，或者员工的生产力、质量和保留率。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;传统观点还认为，体验被评为 3 驱动力4 号人的这些期望行为略少，而 4 号人的驾驶量也比 5 号人稍少。正是这种想法导致我们将 4 分和 5 分归为“前两名”评分，或“好评百分比”分数，然后让我们的团队集中精力，努力将尽可能多的人纳入这一类别 -实际上，将 2 移至 3，并将 3 移至 4/5 类别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，这种想法没有得到数据支持。从 2 到 3、从 3 到 4 对期望的客户或员工行为几乎没有什么推动作用 - 从 2 到 3 到 4 的界限也可能是平坦的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;只有当员工或客户评价他们的体验时才会这样做作为一个极端的积极因素——5——我们看到人们对某种经历的感受与其随后的行为之间的联系。从这个意义上说，4 比 5 更像 3。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从该数据可以得出两个结论。首先，任何有效的领导者都不应该在员工或客户调查中取得“前两名”的分数。这是将苹果与橙子混为一谈，从而模糊了员工或客户的真实情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这也意味着 5 分（那些对自己的体验评价非常积极的人）不仅仅是向前迈出了一步从 4 开始。它们完全是另一回事。当有人自发地使用“爱”这个词来描述他们的经历时，这不仅仅是“很多很多的喜欢”，或者“关怀达到11”，或者“超级热情”。导致某人说“我&lt;em>;喜欢&lt;/em>;”的感觉完全属于不同的类别。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，想要推动员工和客户高效行为的领导者必须深入审视这个“爱”范畴。只有认真对待“爱”作为一种独立且独特的体验，领导者才能定义如何让人们感受到爱。一旦他们定义了它，他们将能够有意地将其设计到员工和客户体验的各个方面。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;是什么让一个人说“我喜欢那个！”&lt;/strong >;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在过去的四分之一个世纪里，我对 5 进行了数十万次采访和调查。如果你今天问我：当人们说他们“喜欢”某样东西时，他们真正的意思是什么？我会给你这样的定义：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;爱是&lt;/em>; &lt;em>;对人类繁荣的深刻而坚定的承诺&lt;/em>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这这是一种深刻的感受，但你可以在人们对看似肤浅的经历的描述中找到它。当你说：“我喜欢那部电影！”你使用“爱”这个词并不是对你觉得有趣的事情的粗心夸大。我的采访显示，你选择“爱”这个词是因为电影中的某些东西让你感动，让你感觉自己更强大，与他人联系更紧密，更多的你，更多的人看到，甚至更聪明。你喜欢它，因为它触动了你。以某种可识别的方式，这部电影帮助你蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你说你“喜欢”做某项活动时，我的研究发现你致力于这个词，因为当你做这项活动时，你会觉得与自己融为一体，轻松自在，掌控一切，全神贯注于自己正在做的事情。你正在蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当你说你爱这位老师，或者这位医生，或者这个团队，或者这个经理，那是因为，通过显性和隐性的信号，你已经得出这样的结论：他们深深地爱着他们。并坚定不移地致力于帮助您蓬勃发展。他们不认为你是“人数”。他们看到&lt;em>;你&lt;/em>;。当你感受到这一点时，你就会感受到爱。你可以根据自己的感受来称呼它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这个定义揭示了为什么人工智能解决方案总是不那么可爱。无论他们处理多少数据，或者他们的大型语言模型有多大，我们都知道这个算法并不真正希望我们蓬勃发展。它甚至不知道什么是繁荣。它永远不可能，也永远不会。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;如何设计爱&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在人工智能时代，最优秀的人才将希望为以下组织工作：承诺在所做的一切事情上充满爱心。这并不意味着这些组织会软弱或无精打采——严厉的爱仍然是爱。这意味着最优秀的人才将对组织是否充满爱心地做事非常敏感，而不仅仅是高效或具有成本效益。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;同样，最挑剔的客户只会忠诚于组织那些有意将爱融入每个接触点的公司。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了将爱融入其中，我们可以首先对“爱”和“不爱”做出清晰的区分。注意：在下面的示例中，我将挑选出特定的接触点来帮助您区分爱与不爱。我提到这些接触点并不一定意味着整个公司是有爱心的还是没有爱心的。充满爱心的公司一次建立一个接触点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;充满爱心的公司告诉员工和客户它代表什么，并且不害怕采取行动来强化其道德立场。 Chick-Fil-A 拒绝周日营业是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chick-fil-a.com/about/who-we-are&quot;>;其价值观&lt;/a>;的明确信号 —它希望员工每周至少有一天在社区中与家人团聚，除了他们认为这是正确的事情之外，没有任何良好的商业原因。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个例子是 In-n- Out Burger 致力于只为顾客提供最新鲜的食物。几年前，当我问公司高管为什么他们不提供早餐时，他们告诉我，他们知道自己无法保持食材足够新鲜，无法兑现对顾客的承诺。所以，没有早餐。对新鲜度的承诺也是 In-n-Out Burger 的得来速窗户直接通向厨房的原因。顾客可以看到货架上摆满了新鲜的土豆、西红柿和生菜，而其他快餐店却隐藏了“香肠”的制作过程。该公司以一种充满爱的方式设计了他们的客户产品和体验，这表明了其对其价值观和客户繁荣的承诺。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;相比之下，没有爱心的公司是不道德的和交易性的，总是并且只评估如何最大化利润或收入。例如，达美航空最近对其常旅客计划的改变就很不受欢迎。达美航空过去常常通过更便宜的机票和升舱来奖励最忠实的客户。根据新规定，乘客在达美航空的信誉不再取决于他们乘坐飞机的频率，而是更多地取决于他们在达美信用卡上的消费金额——它现在是一项常客计划。这种变化在纯粹的交易世界中是有意义的。但这会让乘客混淆达美航空的身份，让他们迷失方向——这对你所服务的人来说是一件没有爱心的事情。也许是意识到了这一点，达美航空首席执行官最近宣布计划&lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/delta-loyalty-program-frequent-flyers-24d9620b38fd6493e6b85d52b95bf7f1&quot;>;回滚其中一些更改&lt;/a>;。&lt; /p>; &lt;p>;充满爱心的公司对其语言深思熟虑。例如，家得宝将其总部称为“商店支持中心”，以强化其对每天为客户提供服务的地点的承诺。第一资本的代理人介绍自己的名字、实际位置，并承诺“今天我将成为你的顾问”。通过这样做，他们不仅向您（客户）个性化自己，而且还提醒您他们打算如何在通话中为您提供服务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这与那些通过事务性绰号“全职当量”或 FTE。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;充满爱心的公司围绕小团队设计工作，因为只有当团队领导者和团队成员频繁关注时，人类才能蓬勃发展。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这家不友善的公司设计围绕资产负债表上有意义的事情进行。经理与直接下属比例为 1 比 70 的呼叫中心并不受欢迎。可悲且讽刺的是，医院也是如此。正如一个大型医疗保健系统的 CHRO 与我分享的那样，他们的护士主管与护士的比例也是 1 比 70。按照这些比例，我们出现如此倦怠危机和护理短缺就不足为奇了。这就好像医院对护士在工作中需要什么来获得营养视而不见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这家充满爱心的公司拥有强大的校友计划。毕竟，如果友善地对待你的员工就是坚定不移地致力于他们的繁荣，那么即使在这个人离开后，这种承诺也会持续存在。没有爱心的公司将每个人仅仅视为达到目的的手段，因此，一旦员工离开，就好像他们从未存在过一样。他们的名字很少在会议上被提及，他们的贡献，无论他们可能是什么，很快就会被纳入更广泛的公司的努力之下。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有爱心的公司不会使用绩效评级，因为他们看到每个员工不仅仅是一个数字。他们也没有高潜力计划，因为他们相信每个工人都有学习和成长的空间，因此机会和优势不应该保留给少数有“潜力”的人。&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;这家充满爱心的公司非常注重转变。例如，一些有远见的医院最近采取的一项爱心举措是设立住院医生角色。这是您入院时指派给您的医生，他的工作有双重：首先向您解释其他医疗专家正在为您做什么以及为什么这样做，其次向您解释您的需求、恐惧和常规。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在没有爱心的医院里，你被从一名护士移交给另一名护士、一名医生、另一名医生、一名管理人员，并且必须重新向他们解释自己。每一个。在没有爱心的医院里，你感觉自己只剩下症状——你就是 302 房间的胆囊。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;爱是最有力地驱动客户和员工行为的力量 - 奇怪的是，当今的企业并不重视它。他们不研究它。他们甚至没有释放它的策略。对于传统的大多数人来说，这是多么遗憾的事，而对于明智的少数商界领袖来说，这是多么巨大的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;谁不想被热情地招募呢？还是深情地入住酒店？或者亲切地提供金融服务？谁不想享受一顿充满爱的外出就餐、作为乘客的一次充满爱的飞行体验、以及得到精心处理的保险索赔？我们都会的。正如数据显示的那样，如果我们获得更多充满爱的体验，我们的行为就会更加高效——员工表现出更高的绩效，客户表现出更高的忠诚度，并且两者都会成为您品牌的拥护者。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人工智能机车几乎肯定会从我们的生活中分流爱情。人工智能可以大规模模仿，但它永远不会致力于帮助任何一个人类繁荣发展。我们希望人工智能能够被高效、无害地部署。但由于它对我们的立场是不道德的，因此它永远无法被善意地运用。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Types of Manipulators at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/5-types-of-manipulators-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Oct23_12_538061812.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;SvetaZi/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;很多变量都会影响我们的日常决策&amp;#8212;尽管也许没有什么比其他人的态度和偏好更有效的了。人类寻求与他人归属感的本能有助于我们合作并建立系统和社会。但这也给居心不良的人提供了误导、麻痹甚至强迫我们服务&lt;em>;他们&lt;/em>;利益而不是我们自己利益的机会。作者称之为“同伴压力操纵”。直接针对我们的集体本能。五种操纵策略尤其会导致决策者犯下错误，例如选择可疑的合作伙伴或投资、雇用不合格的机构、为考虑不周的内部活动开绿灯以及支持普遍糟糕的想法。一旦您能够识别五种常见的操纵策略，您就可以在任何时候感觉产品、想法、投资或行动方案可能不真实时进行保护性心理练习。&lt;/p>; &lt;/ span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/5-types-of-manipulators-at-work?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt; /a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/5-types-of-manipulators-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;你还记得吗您曾尝试过哪个大肆宣传的广告公司，但最终却表现平平？或者是你对不幸的营销计划有不好的预感，但无论如何还是支持你的团队成员？或者新的合作伙伴或员工声称与您有共同的价值观，但却引发了麻烦？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在某种程度上，您可能已经预见到每个错误的出现。那么，发生了什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;很多变量都会影响我们的日常决策 - 尽管可能没有更多&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/文章/PMC3695714/&quot;>;比其他人的态度和偏好更有力&lt;/a>;。人类寻求与他人归属感的本能有助于我们合作并建立系统和社会。但这也给居心不良的人提供了误导、麻痹甚至强迫我们服务&lt;em>;他们&lt;/em>;利益而不是我们自己利益的机会。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我所说的“同侪压力操纵”直接针对我们的集体本能。五种操纵策略尤其会导致决策者犯下错误，例如选择可疑的合作伙伴或投资、雇用不合格的机构、为考虑不周的内部活动开绿灯以及支持普遍糟糕的想法。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在这里，我们将讨论如何捍卫您的利益你自己和你的团队的决策是通过同侪压力操纵做出的。一旦您能够识别五种常见的操纵策略，您就可以在任何时候感觉产品、想法、投资或行动方案可能不真实时进行保护性心理练习。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;如何同伴压力操纵有效吗？​​&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;操纵者需要你接受三个假设为真——即使它们没有明确说明。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些想法构成了同伴压力操纵的基础。学会注意并评估何时有人希望您相信这三个“事实”：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;相关的&lt;em>;其他&lt;/em>;人相信操纵者告诉您他们相信的事情。&lt;/li >; &lt;li>;其他人的意见不仅是真实的，而且与&lt;em>;您的&lt;/em>;相关&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;您的&lt;em>;个人&lt;/em>;最佳利益在决策中受到威胁蔑视或附和他人的观点。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;当您了解五种操纵策略以及如何扭转每一种策略时，请记住这个框架。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>; 5 种操纵策略&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;这些场景的灵感来自于我与不同领域的决策者的对话，并综合到现实世界的例子中。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.他们窃取了可信度。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;莎拉是一位科技会议主席，她需要为她的活动再预订一位发言人。一位营销专家要求提供这个位置。他说他曾与亚马逊、PayPal、Stripe 和其他主要品牌合作过。他还提到了一个“科技股”非营利组织的名字，称他希望为边缘群体的创始人提供帮助。莎拉印象深刻，给他预订了。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但在他讲话几分钟后，她就后悔了。这位专家没有向观众提供任何营销建议。相反，他向他们推销自己的服务。他甚至提供了“特别的一次性折扣”，一位与会者称这是“令人畏缩”的举动。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;失败后，莎拉更详细地研究了这位专家，看看她错过了他的哪些方面。她了解到，他的客户实际上是亚马逊、PayPal、Stripe 等公司的现任或前任员工，而不是他所代表的公司本身。她也找不到他参与他声称支持的事业的任何历史。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;看起来莎拉的专家不真实地将自己与他知道会给她留下深刻印象的品牌名称和事业联系在一起，选择了 &lt;他们对自己的可信度。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当某人的推销严重依赖于他们的联想时，请审查他们的真实性。询问有关这些关系的问题。这个人与这些人或品牌到底有什么联系？他们是否在这些事业上投入了时间？他们采取了哪些行动来践行他们声称持有的价值观？&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2.他们利用共同的威胁来赢得您的信任。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;虽然我们经常因共同利益而与人建立联系，但我们往往会立即喜欢的人是那些&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary .wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1475-6811.2006.00109.x&quot;>;分享我们的&lt;em>;负面&lt;/em>;意见&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;与格温有同样挫败感的人与首席财务官合作更有可能说服她接受他们的建议。与本一样担心这笔交易会伤害他们的人更有可能赢得他的信任。共同的负面情绪可以使人们团结起来，但它也可以帮助操纵者使人们与他们的议程保持一致。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;仔细审查任何引发共同敌人或共同威胁以建立融洽关系的宣传。如果有人谈论你们对灾难性结果或即将发生的事件的恐惧，或者如果他们声称分享你对某个人、情况或品牌的愤怒——请注意。他们如何利用这一共同威胁很重要。他们提到它是因为这是他们想要解决的真正问题吗？或者，这种共同的威胁除了帮助他们与你建立联系之外没有其他任何目的吗？如果有人煽动你的愤怒或恐惧只是为了表明志同道合，他们会促使你接受他们接下来所说的一切。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最终，没有必要怀疑每个与你有共同恐惧的人。但您正在考虑的产品或计划应该因其提供的功能而引人注目，而不是其所反对的内容。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.他们伪造了市场验证。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;在品牌合作伙伴关系未能推动销售后，营销主管乔丹重新阅读了合作伙伴品牌的案例研究，以调查出了什么问题。他注意到他之前错过的一些奇怪的事情：案例研究是假设的，没有提及实际客户的名字。该品牌还拥有大量社交媒体受众，但参与度较低，这表明可能存在“机器人”追随者。事实证明，该品牌网站上的媒体徽标代表的是付费广告，而不是文章或新闻。乔丹开始认为该品牌伪造了他们的受众规模，甚至可能还伪造了他们过去的作品。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;伪造市场验证对于操纵者来说是轻而易举的事情。他们明白，强大的观众的出现会激发我们寻求同伴认可和归属感的本能。他们指望我们从表面上看这些指标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;用外表来代替现实是很诱人的。但请花点时间询问能够揭示受众规模和情绪的市场洞察来源。 NPS 分数、使用统计数据、网络分析和社交参与度等量化数据比关注者数量更能直接表明情绪。获取参考文献和案例研究主题的名称，并询问模糊的启发式信息，例如网站上的媒体徽标。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;4.他们试图抹黑竞争对手。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;迈克尔是一家营养饮料品牌的销售总监，他希望与当地经销商合作。但竞争品牌也是如此——只有其中一个能够赢得独家协议。于是迈克尔发起了战斗：他告诉经销商，选择其他品牌将是一个冒险的选择。迈克尔表示，他们的产品在营养科学界并不可信，许多人认为它“不安全”。迈克尔暗示，与他们合作会损害经销商的声誉，甚至可能带来责任。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;批评竞争产品的质量或适合度并没有什么不妥的。但试图通过将它们描绘成有污点、不合法或禁忌的方式来抹黑它们，是一种操纵策略，如果人们敢于做出错误的选择，就会害怕被联想到耻辱。在迈克尔的案例中，他援引了社会最大的耻辱之一来抹黑他的竞争对手：忽视安全。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你有一种令人不安的感觉，即一个人向你推销某样东西想要抹黑或污蔑竞争对手的选择，那么你就会感到不安。首先需要从特征中解析事实。深入研究“人们的想法”或“社区相信”的说法，找出&lt;em>;谁&lt;/em>;实际上说了&lt;em>;什么&lt;/em>;。他们的具体用词是什么？他们是否使用了“不安全”这个词，或者这是一种表征？不同的利益相关者如何解释来自来源的信息，他们有什么动机？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您得出结论，这些特征毕竟有优点，请采取下一步。评估推介的好处，而不考虑其他选择。拒绝错误的二分法，即仅仅因为选项 A 不好，选项 B 就一定是好的。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;5.他们分而治之。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;凯德是一位雄心勃勃的物流经理，但他并没有得到同事的充分信任，因为他似乎总是渴望更多的权威。他请求副总裁允许组建并主持一个监管监督委员会。该委员会表面上会保护公司免受事故影响，但它也会让凯德访问其他经理的私人项目日志。副总裁并不相信，但告诉凯德，如果团队的其他成员都参与其中，他会考虑这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，凯德向部门负责人请愿。他告诉他们，他已经得到了副总统的支持。部门领导不想惹恼别人，所以就同意了。然后，凯德告诉经理们，他们的部门主管已经同意了，而经理们也很不情愿地签字同意。人们对给予凯德监督持谨慎态度。 But they didn&#39;t want to challenge their bosses and peers, so no one spoke up. Thus Cade showed his VP what looked like “unanimous support” from the team and received permission to form the committee that, privately, no one wanted.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This tactic of dividing and conquering is known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simplypsychology.org/pluralistic-ignorance.html&quot;>;pluralistic ignorance&lt;/a>;. It works by inducing a fear among group members of opposing a bad idea because they&#39;ve been (wrongly) led to believe they&#39;re alone in their opposition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you find yourself pressured to adopt a consensus view you&#39;re unsure of, investigate whether it has actual &lt;em>;support&lt;/em>; — or just compliance. Ask colleagues what they like about the idea and how they see it helping. Watch for their tone. Are they evangelizing, or just going along? Create an opening for candid feedback by sharing your own uncertainty: “I don&#39;t know how I feel about X. Are you convinced it&#39;s the right move?” Anonymous surveys can also open the door for discussion by uncovering that team members aren&#39;t sharing their actual views.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Peer pressure manipulators don&#39;t use the strongest arguments to persuade us. They just tap into our need for approval and connection, or exploit our fear of losing standing in the group.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The good news is, we don&#39;t need to stop caring what other people think of us to resist this manipulation. We just need to spot the sleights of hand, simplistic leaps, and false assumptions that prop it up. So ask questions and test claims. Manipulation topples when you challenge its foundation. And more often than not, other people will thank you for pushing back.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 12 Oct 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[New Technologies Arrive in Clusters. What Does That Mean for AI?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/new-technologies-arrive-in-clusters-what-does-that-mean-for-ai]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_06_1648864214.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Historically, technology arrives in clusters. With electrification came dynamos, generators, switch gears and power distribution system. With the printing press came the technologies to make large quantities of cheap paper and ink. Looking at these past clusters can help us understand the moment we&amp;#8217;re in now, and what the future of AI &amp;#8212; especially GenAI &amp;#8212; might really look like. For now, leaders should assess the state of their data quality and work to build organizational muscle to complete data projects. They should also look for proprietary data that they own, which can give them a competitive advantage, and beef up their change management capabilities.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/new-technologies-arrive-in-clusters-what-does-that-mean-for-ai?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/new-technologies-arrive-in-clusters-what-does-that-mean-for-ai?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The potential — and hype — surrounding machine learning, artificial intelligence, and especially generative AI is everywhere. Some are predicting a full suite of “this changes everything” advances in all industries, for all professions, and for people in their public and private lives. This technology is unmatched at recognizing patterns in data, and its proponents argue it has the potential to be an enormous research laboratory that never stops working, a paradigm-buster that unlocks human creativity, an accelerator for human ingenuity, and a window into reality that is currently beyond reach. Sundar Pichai, of Google likens it potential to fire and electricity.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I too am genuinely excited, if somewhat more reservedly. Today, AI offers opportunities to improve productivity, which has&lt;a title=&quot;https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2022/08/28/the-missing-pandemic-innovation-boom&quot; href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2022/08/28/the-missing-pandemic-innovation-boom&quot;>; remained flat&lt;/a>; for a long time, and to tackle &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2023/09/13/how-scientists-are-using-artificial-intelligence&quot;>;heretofore intractable problems&lt;/a>;, such as the search for antibiotic-resistant drugs, an understanding of how proteins fold, and finding materials with properties needed to build better batteries. Impressive successes ranging from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lineate.com/blog/3-ways-amazon-uses-ai-to-make-product-recommendations&quot;>;Amazon&#39;s recommendation engine&lt;/a>;, to Callaway Golf&#39;s design of its next generation drivers, to PepsiCo&#39;s efforts to manufacture &lt;a title=&quot;https://blogs.microsoft.com/ai-for-business/pepsico-perfect-cheetos/&quot; href=&quot;https://blogs.microsoft.com/ai-for-business/pepsico-perfect-cheetos/&quot;>;more consistent Cheetos&lt;/a>; help justify the excitement.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But I also think that progress will take longer and prove far tougher than most expect, especially in commercial settings. As I&#39;ll explain, success with AI demands concerted efforts that extend far beyond the technology. Thus, they demand the full commitment of a company&#39;s most senior leadership.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It is important to note that AI has generated considerable excitement in the past, quelled by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AI_winter#:~:text=There%20were%20two%20major%20winters,single%2Dlayer%20artificial%20neural%20networks)&quot;>;AI winters&lt;/a>; in the mid 1970s and early 1990s. And just three years ago, in 2020, &lt;em>;The Economist&lt;/em>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/technology-quarterly/2020/06/11/an-understanding-of-ais-limitations-is-starting-to-sink-in&quot;>;noted&lt;/a>; that “Another full-blown winter is unlikely. But an autumnal breeze is picking up.” As one example, self-driving cars benefited from considerable investment, and always seem to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://universe.byu.edu/2016/01/15/self-driving-cars-are-just-around-the-corner/&quot;>;“just around the corner,”&lt;/a>; but &lt;a href=&quot;https://umdearborn.edu/news/why-your-first-driverless-car-decades-not-years-away&quot;>;are more probably decades away.&lt;/a>; Further, during the pandemic, when insights were are a premium, none of the hundreds of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/07/30/1030329/machine-learning-ai-failed-covid-hospital-diagnosis-pandemic/&quot;>;AI tools built to catch Covid&lt;/a>; have passed muster. Indeed, the failure rate of AI projects appears to be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2023/04/10/why-most-machine-learning-applications-fail-to-deploy/?sh=6dee0b08736d&quot;>;north of 80%&lt;/a>;. Finally, a recent study by Meta (formerly Facebook) researchers under controlled conditions suggest that large language models don&#39;t get the facts right &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2308.10168.pdf&quot;>;two-thirds of the time&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Still, I&#39;m less concerned about the technology per se and more concerned about the other advances that must accompany AI. For history suggests it takes wide range of related technologies, organizational innovations, and accommodations between the new technologies and society for any new technology to flower. I&#39;ll use electrification and the printing press to illustrate these points, then explore how they apply to AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As the Austrian political economist Joseph Schumpeter &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ebusinessforum.gr/old/content/downloads/IstheInformationRevolutionDead&quot;>;pointed out&lt;/a>;, successful technologies tend to arrive in clusters. With electrification came dynamos, generators, switch gears, and power-distribution systems. With the printing press came the technologies to make large quantities of cheap paper and ink. And, though not a technology per se, new materials other than the Bible and other classics were needed to fuel demand for printed materials.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A single missing component can impede the adoption of the new technology. Today, for example, the lack of enough fast-charging stations is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2021/12/11/the-tricky-business-of-charging-electric-cars?utm_medium=cpc.adword.pd&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;ppccampaignID=17210591673&amp;amp;ppcadID=&amp;amp;utm_campaign=a.22brand_pmax&amp;amp;utm_content=conversion.direct-response.anonymous&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwx5qoBhDyARIsAPbMagCl_gWXBuyeFVRJoNK_eIISY6YEQW5LjFFp3SrF2o1C8jTc-M6JfDAaAl26EALw_wcB&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&quot;>;slowing the advance of electric cars&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Next, new technologies require new organizational capabilities. While the benefits of electricity and electric motors were easy to see, they required that factories be redesigned. It took 40 years of learning, experimentation, and investment along multiple fronts to fully electrify the factory. Similarly, it took about that long for a publishing industry, which helped match supply, demand, and price, to emerge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Sooner or later, new technologies and societies must come to accommodate one another. In the beginning, electricity was dangerous — mistakenly touching a live wire could prove fatal! Over time, standard sockets and plugs helped ease that concern. Few people could read when the printing press was invented. But as societies became increasingly literate, the benefits of the printing press grew. Looking at these past clusters can help us understand the moment we&#39;re in now, and what the future of AI might really look like.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Barriers to the Adoption of AI&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Each of these areas presents formidable barriers for the widespread adoption of AI. (In using the term artificial intelligence, or AI, I am casting a wide net, including machine learning, deep learning, computer vision, natural language processing, robotics, expert systems, fuzzy logic, and other areas of tasks typically associated with human intelligence.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, consider the technologies related to AI. The two most important are massive computing power and large quantities of high-quality data. Increasingly sophisticated models require more computing power, which, as predicted by Moore&#39;s Law, appears to be growing apace. Probably not fast enough for those on the leading edge, but plenty fast for most commercial uses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The situation is more complex when it comes to “large quantities of high-quality data.” In teaching an AI to play chess, for example, researchers provided algorithm the rules and instructed it to play games against itself, obviating real-world quality issues. In contrast, poor data quality sunk IBM&#39;s Watson&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statnews.com/2017/09/05/watson-ibm-cancer/&quot;>;initial entry into health care&lt;/a>;. To further underscore the importance of high-quality data, researchers generally acknowledge that today&#39;s AI models would not be possible without the highly-curated, trusted data &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/18/magazine/wikipedia-ai-chatgpt.html?searchResultPosition=3&quot;>;scraped from Wikipedia&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;All this stands to reason: Even a technology as remarkable as AI can produce results no better than its inputs. And in most commercial settings, &lt;a href=&quot;/2017/09/only-3-of-companies-data-meets-basic-quality-standards&quot;>;quality issues&lt;/a>; resemble Watson far more closely than the pristine circumstances of chess. The &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/if-your-data-is-bad-your-machine-learning-tools-are-useless&quot;>;quality requirements&lt;/a>; for training, updating, and operating AI models are broad, deep, and, in some cases, poorly understood. For example, while it appears that Microsoft&#39;s Tay chatbot was well trained in normal discourse, user-generated content &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tay_(chatbot)#:~:text=Tay%20was%20an%20artificial%20intelligence,only%2016%20hours%20after%20its&quot;>;quickly taught it to mimic hate speech&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Exacerbating this, many companies&#39; data and systems architectures are increasingly messy and chaotic. This makes getting the data in shape to apply AI tools much harder, compounding quality issues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;I find this situation paradoxical. As best I can tell, everyone involved understands the importance of high-quality data. Some practitioners privately admit data is the most important part of any AI project. But companies haven&#39;t even put someone in charge, never mind sorted out the complete program they&#39;ll need to ensure they have the high-quality data they need. Perhaps, as Google researchers &lt;a href=&quot;https://research.google/pubs/pub49953/&quot;>;note&lt;/a>;, “Everyone wants to do the model work, not the data work.” But until that data work gets done, it&#39;s hard to see good models emerging and AI succeeding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Now consider the issues associated with organizational capabilities needed to put AI to work. These may well prove as difficult as the quality issues. I find the penetration of basic, though powerful, analytical techniques broadly instructive here because both it and AI depend so heavily on data. Such tools have been around for at least two generations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But other than basic reporting, most organization still don&#39;t use them very much or well. And these tools are far easier to understand than AI models. The unfortunate reality is that &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/06/your-data-strategy-needs-to-include-everyone&quot;>;analytics is bolted onto, rather than built into, organizations,&lt;/a>; practically guaranteeing a perpetual fight for relevance. It is hard to see a bright future for AI until this structural issue is resolved.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The second big organizational issue is that employees resist innovations that threaten their jobs. And while AI can reduce the drudgery in work, make employees more productive, and lead to a growth in employment, most are right to be concerned. After all, a drudge job beats no job when it helps feed a family. So, how will employees and AI work together? Should employees be expected to help create an AI that will replace them? To explain and or clean up training data? In situations where AI replaces them, how should they be compensated? In situations for where AI makes people more effective and/or efficient, should people receive higher compensation? There are no easy answers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One final point regarding staff. Even as generative AI is easy to use, developing and deploying most AI requires top talent. Yet too many data scientists feel their talents are wasted. As one veteran put it, “I find that most data scientists are incredibly frustrated that they aren&#39;t having much impact.” No surprise! Finding something novel that the business actually uses and deploying a model in practice is incredibly difficult. Even worse is dealing with bureaucracy, quality issues, and the fears of those impacted by their work. Companies hoping to attract and retain top talent must address these frustrations.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, and lastly, consider issues of humans/society and AI coming to accommodate one another. As noted above, some believe AI will elevate humanity while others believe the AI threatens civilization. So, these issues are already generating enormous attention, though so far little agreement, on national and international levels. Though only a few companies will have much influence at those levels, most will find they have to take a stand on some, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;What are the standards against which companies should compare their AIs? There are numerous reports of deaths caused by self-driving cars. But people are far from perfect drivers and their mistakes also kill lots of people. Is “zero accidents” or “fewer accidents” the objective?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Should companies compensate individuals for providing their data? Should they pay more for data guaranteed correct?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How should national security issues, such as the competition between US and China impact companies&#39; plans?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;AI is much like a “black box” — it does not give good explanations for the ways it reached its conclusions. Thus, companies should begin to think through how they will address legitimate questions such as “Why did you deny my loan?”&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;What to do?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;This is probably a good time to take stock. Is your company fully embracing the data, organization, and societal challenges that AI requires and is your senior leadership fully committed? If so, you&#39;ve raised your chances of success. Good luck!&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Or, does the vast majority of your work focus on the technology, perhaps led by your chief analytics officer and/or your tech group? If so, ask yourself if you&#39;re up for the full range of work on the data, organization, and society/people issues needed to earn significant business results. If not, best to keep your powder dry. If so, the really hard and important work still lies ahead. You simply must get your more senior leadership invested in the effort. There is no set script for doing so.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You must also begin work on the data and organizational issues describe above. I recommend two steps to help you get started:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;For data quality, make some measurements so you know where you stand. Then &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/02/to-improve-data-quality-start-at-the-source&quot;>;make some improvements&lt;/a>; by finding and eliminating the root causes of error.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;To build the organizational muscle you need, &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/10/most-analytics-projects-dont-require-much-data&quot;>;complete several “small data projects,”&lt;/a>; involving teams of people focused on improving their own work processes.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;I also recommend two further steps, anticipating a decision to plunge headlong into the effort:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;Scour the company for proprietary data, stuff you have that others cannot match. This is important because you&#39;re unlikely to create sustained advantage with data your competitors can also access.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Beef up your change management capabilities. No matter what works best, putting AI to work will require massive change. Start to build the professional help you will need.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h2>;AI Isn&#39;t Easy&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The hype surrounding AI makes it seem much easier than it is. Don&#39;t get sucked in! It is easy to “play” in the AI sandbox. But actually making it pay off, at scale, across the company requires serious work, top to bottom and across the company. The technology is almost certainly the most manageable of the required efforts. You also need high-quality data and some tough organizational changes, all against a backdrop of societal acceptance. AI is only for those in it for the long haul!&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 23:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Team Caught in the Solution Fixation Trap?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/is-your-team-caught-in-the-solution-fixation-trap]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_11_1501194045.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;MirageC/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span >;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;面对不断升级的复杂性，组织越来越依赖团队来解决这些错综复杂的问题并推动关键的组织决策。为了从团队动力中获取最大价值，领导者必须时刻注意可能影响团队动力的潜在偏见，并积极引导和微调团队流程。具体来说，作者敦促领导者解决他们称之为解决方案固定陷阱的决策偏差，当团队在完全理解手头的问题之前急于讨论可能的解决方案时，就会出现这种偏差。作者讨论了帮助他们发现这种偏见的研究，解释了解决方案固定陷阱是什么样的，并讨论了领导者可以采取哪些措施来保护他们的团队免受这种偏见的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt; div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/is-your-team-caught-in-the-solution-fixation-trap?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt; br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/is-your-team-caught-in-the-solution-fixation-trap?language=pt&quot;>;葡萄牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;有您是否曾发现您的团队来回寻找问题的良好解决方案却没有取得进展？或者，您可能在会议结束后对所选解决方案感到不确定，想知道您的团队是否忽略了重要信息。为了帮助您的团队更自信地做出更好的决策，您需要解决决策偏差，我们称之为&lt;em>;解决方案固定陷阱&lt;/em>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当团队急于解决问题时，就会出现解决方案固定陷阱。在完全理解手头的问题之前讨论可能的解决方案。例如，负责解决销售下降问题的营销团队可能会匆忙建议对现有营销活动进行修改，而没有花足够的时间来充分了解销售下降的根本原因。同样，负责增强求职者人口多样性的招聘工作组可能会在没有充分分析可能的抑制因素的情况下匆忙提出新的招聘策略。这不仅使团队难以找到他们有信心的解决方案，而且使他们面临采取错误行动方针的风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在本文中，我们分享了对我们有帮助的研究发现这种偏见，解释解决方案固定陷阱是什么样的，并讨论您可以采取哪些措施来保护您的团队免受其影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;可视化团队的展开决策行为&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;为了更好为了解释解决方案固定陷阱是什么样子，我们开发了一种方法来可视化和分析团队的决策行为。当我们与周围的世界（例如其他团队成员）互动时，我们的每一种行为（言语或非言语）都有其作用。例如，分享一条信息或询问信息都是专注于信息处理的行为。对阶段图的仔细分析——突出显示团队参与具有共同功能的行为的时间段的插图——帮助我们回答了有关团队动态的重要问题，并揭示了解决方案固定陷阱等现象。阶段映射技术的重点是识别具有共同功能的行为簇，我们将其标记为阶段类型。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;169 名 MBA 学生参与了这项研究。参与者组成 28 个小组，参加了涉及一系列问题解决任务的学习模拟。 （披露：&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbsp.harvard.edu/product/7000-HTM-ENG&quot;>;领导力和团队模拟：Everest V2&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;是哈佛商业出版社的产品。）我们录制了每个团队参与模拟时的音频和视频。然后，我们逐字转录团队沟通，并根据其功能为每个语句分配一个代码。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/hcr/article等学者的先前研究-abstract/15/4/549/4584138?redirectedFrom=fulltext&quot;>;马歇尔·普尔、乔内尔·罗斯&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1952-03911-001&quot; >;Robert Bales&lt;/a>;认为，负责解决问题的团队的行为可以分为四个阶段类型：1）信息处理，2）解决方案探索，3）确认，4）执行行动。下图显示了塑造每个阶段的行为示例。当团队随着时间的推移处理一项任务时，它会经历这些阶段。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-364976&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023 /09/W230913_SOHRAB_DECISION_MAKING_BEHAVIOR_360.png&quot; >; 信息处理，显示为橙色：分享他人可能不知道的内容、询问信息、回答问题。&lt;br />; 解决方案探索，绿色：提出解决方案、评估提出的解决方案，以及扩展提议的解决方案。&lt;br />;确认，黄色：要求确认和确认。&lt;br />;执行行动，蓝色：确保每个人都可以访问所需的文件，完成所需的文书工作，并讨论有关流程的指南。 &lt;br />; 无组织期，灰色：无组织的行动，不专注于一种行为。栏的左侧标记为“任务开始”，右侧标记为“任务结束”。每个块的长度对应于一个阶段所花费的时间量。第一个块最长，大约占任务栏的三分之一，表示信息处理阶段。然后两个较小的块显示切换到解决方案探索阶段并返回到信息处理阶段，接下来是任务栏上第二长的块，这是解决方案探索所花费的另一个阶段。条形的最后四分之一显示确认阶段的一小段，并以执行行动阶段的最后一个区块达到高潮。来源：Serena G. Sohrab、Mary J. Waller、Sjir Uitdewilligen。&lt;br />; &quot; title= “假设团队决策行为的阶段图。” width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;649&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data -visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;在数据和视觉效果中查看更多 HBR 图表 &lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The上图还描述了假设团队在成员处理问题解决任务时的交互，每个块代表一个专注于特定类型行为的时间段。团队首先讨论可用信息（第一个橙色块）。一旦成员确信每个人都有机会分享他们所知道的内容，团队转而考虑可能的解决方案（绿色块）。然后，团队在参与之前返回讨论信息以更好地告知其决策（第二个橙色块）对潜在解决方案的长时间讨论并对其进行评估（第二个绿色块）。此阶段之后，团队寻求每个人的口头确认（黄色块）。团队通过确保正确记录和记录决策（蓝色块）来结束任务。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;虽然这种行为似乎与我们大多数人在做出决策时期望团队中发生的情况一致，大多数团队的行为轨迹实际上看起来更像下图，阶段之间的切换更加频繁，并且存在一些无组织的时期（以灰色块表示）。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment -364975&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/W230913_SOHRAB_DECISION_MAKING_BEHAVIOR_PHASES_360.png&quot; >; &quot; title=&quot;典型团队决策行为的阶段图。&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;369&quot;>; &lt; /figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和视觉中的更多 HBR 图表&lt;i >;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;h2>;解决方案固定陷阱&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在我们的研究中，我们检查了 28 个团队的阶段图通过分析他们在任务期间的互动，我们能够发现一种作为关键绩效指标的行为模式，区分找到最佳解决方案的高绩效团队和选择最佳解决方案的低绩效团队最糟糕的解决方案。下图显示了五个高绩效团队和五个低绩效团队的阶段图。&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;figure>; &lt;img aria-scribedby=&quot;caption-attachment-365163&quot; src=&quot;/resources/images/ Article_assets/2023/09/W230913_SOHRAB_DECISION_MAKING_BEHAVIOR_TEAMS_360_V2.png&quot; >; 第二组任务被标记为“低绩效团队”。所有五个任务栏都包含更多的解决方案探索块，这表明低绩效团队的讨论主要是解决方案探索和评估，而不是收集和分析达成良好解决方案所需的信息。来源：Serena G. Sohrab 、Mary J. Waller、Sjir Uitdewilligen。&quot; title=&quot;五个高绩效团队和五个低绩效团队的阶段图比较。&quot; width=&quot;360&quot; height=&quot;872&quot;>; &lt;/figure>; &lt;p>;&lt;span>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hbr.org/data-visuals&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;>;查看数据和视觉中的更多 HBR 图表&lt;i>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>; &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;从这些地图中可以明显看出，表现不佳的团队的讨论主要是解决方案探索和评估，而不是收集和分析达成良好解决方案所需的信息。有趣的是，高绩效团队和低绩效团队在开始任务时都会讨论他们对问题的了解。然而，不久之后，低绩效团队开始专注于提出他们应该做什么的建议，并开始生成各种解决方案。一旦发生这种情况，他们就无法在任何持续的时间内返回信息分析。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们还发现，当这些低绩效团队专注于解决方案探索时，他们不太可能寻求信息来解决问题。回答出现的问题。如果团队成员问：“我们对 X 了解多少？”，低绩效者通常会忽略这个问题，并继续讨论潜在的解决方案而不证实它们。这种对辩论解决方案的执着限制了低绩效者揭示和充分评估他们可以获得的所有信息的能力，这反过来又导致了糟糕的决策结果。有趣的是，这些似乎急于讨论解决方案的团队并没有比高绩效团队更快地完成整体任务。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;保护您的团队免受解决方案固定陷阱&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;那又怎样？管理者可以做些什么来防止他们的团队陷入这种解决方案固定陷阱？以下是基于我们研究的一些易于实施的策略：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;通过查看所有可用信息来开始会议。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;绕过桌子并鼓励人们分享他们的内容了解（而不是他们的意见）当前的情况或问题。一旦每个人都有机会分享他们所知道的内容，询问房间里的人是否知道任何未讨论的信息。这是至关重要的，因为超过三十年的研究提供了确凿的证据，证明所有团队成员不知道的信息是在团队讨论中提及的可能性显着降低。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;留意不成熟的解决方案建议。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;会议几乎不是任何人最喜欢的活动，因为大多数人认为会议浪费时间，&lt;a href=&quot;/2017/07/stop-the-meeting-madness&quot;>;压倒性的，甚至是吸魂痛苦的&lt;/a>;。因此，当你召集人们开会解决问题或做出决定时，你可能会遇到那些有意无意地试图匆忙讨论并尽快结束会议的人。他们可以通过对时间做出明确的评论或更微妙的方式来做到这一点，例如直接讨论可能的解决方案。当您注意到不成熟的解决方案建议时，可以通过这样的话来标记它：“感谢您的建议 - 当我们确定我们已经发现了所有相关信息时，让我们回到这个建议。”然后，将讨论带回信息共享和分析。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;在整个过程中鼓励基于证据的决策。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;当出现问题时，引导团队根据问题进行回答。现有信息，而不是他们的意见或粗略猜测。您可能会说，“听起来我们需要回去进一步深入研究这个问题。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;使用可视化工具来组织所讨论的信息和解决方案。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;一些我们的其他&lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/job.2301&quot;>;研究&lt;/a>;表明，筛选和共享复杂信息的团队可以从使用集体显示，例如干擦板或电子白板。在共享显示器上写入信息当然可以帮助将信息与讨论的可能解决方案联系起来。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;。 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;面对组织面临的不断升级的复杂性，对团队解决这些复杂问题和推动关键组织决策的依赖正在增加。为了从团队动力中获取最大价值，至关重要的是要时刻注意可能影响团队动力的潜在偏见，并积极引导和微调团队流程。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/分区>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[What&rsquo;s Lost When Data Systems Don&rsquo;t Communicate]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/whats-lost-when-data-systems-dont-communicate]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_11_6551-000359-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Raimund Koch/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot; close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;在每个行业，许多大公司都拥有帮助桥接过时、断开连接的系统和数据库的团队。没有它们，公司就无法在不中断运营的情况下升级技术。问题在于，在断开连接或几乎不修补的系统上运行公司会影响各个级别的员工。要了解断开连接的系统给公司带来的成本是什么？ “断网债务” &amp;#8212;作者测量了由于断开连接的系统而产生的信息孤岛对公司 100 多个团队的业务成果的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/whats-lost-when-data-systems-dont-communicate?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/whats-lost -when-data-systems-dont-communicate?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;想象一个场景。凯利是一家大型医院网络的一名敬业员工，她准备好迎接新一天处理心烦意乱的顾客的情况。作为消费者关系团队的成员，她处理了多次被转接的患者的升级电话。她当天的挑战涉及一位潜在的阿尔茨海默病患者从不同的医院网络寻求第二意见。不幸的是，这位患者被告知凯利的网络无法以电子方式传输医疗记录，因此可能需要花费 90 分钟来收集 CD 上的记录。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在通话的压力下，凯利认为根本原因是内部系统内的同步问题。她采取了主动行动，浏览了各种系统，包括电子健康记录系统、档案、健康交换和健康信息服务提供商系统。 Kelly 手动解决了同步问题并确保记录发送完毕，赢得了患者的感激。这种服务行为特别有意义，因为她自己有年迈的父母，给凯利带来了巨大的快乐。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;每天，像凯利这样的几位超级倡导者在医院网络中工作，解决众多会员问题，这些问题主要源于现代化进程已经成熟，或者不同的系统需要相互通信。事实上，在每个行业，许多大公司都有这样的团队，他们帮助弥合过时、脱节的系统和数据库。没有它们，公司就无法在不中断运营的情况下升级技术。这种情况虽然是想象出来的，但在现实中在公司和行业中普遍存在。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;问题在于，在断开连接或几乎不拼凑在一起的系统上运行公司会影响各个级别的员工。在另一个真实的案例中，一位《财富》500 强企业的首席财务官每个季度都在努力整合来自 50 家子公司的 70 多个系统的财务数据。该团队必须精心提取、协调、集成和验证来自这些系统的数据，这是一个耗时且危险的过程，容易出现错误。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight =&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作的未来&quot; dek=&quot;您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black ;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;工作的未来&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？ &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;每个季度财务团队和 IT 团队都会争论&lt;em>;相同&lt;/em>;问题：&lt;em>;为什么我们有大量不同的系统？为什么这些系统不互相通信？我们可以做些什么来消除这些造成更多风险、延误和工作量的数据孤岛？ &lt;/em>;&lt;em>;我们如何拆除这些导致风险、延迟和额外工作的数据孤岛？&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;像 Kelly、财务和 IT 团队以及 CFO 一样，大多数人无论从事什么工作、部门或行业，员工都熟悉这些挫败感的某些形式。他们花费数小时将数据从一个系统移动到另一个系统，对不兼容的应用程序进行故障排除，并且经常将这种功能障碍视为工作中不可避免的摩擦。但大多数公司并不知道问题有多严重，因为他们没有花时间来量化这种断开连接对业务成果的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;了解断开连接的系统给公司造成的损失 - 我们称之为“断网债务”——我们衡量了因断网系统而产生的信息孤岛对公司 100 多个团队的业务成果的影响。以下是公司需要了解的有关此问题的信息以及如何解决该问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;断开连接债务：业务中断开连接的系统的成本&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;在理想的世界中，所有系统都处于一个组织将在后端通过 API 相互集成，并无缝地相互通信。对于用户（即员工）而言，这意味着避免从多个来源复制或提取信息的重复性手动工作。相反，理想情况下，用户应该利用他们的经验、判断和培训，根据系统提供的信息做出决策或建议，系统负责从多个来源收集信息的繁琐工作。 &amp;nbsp;但这种情况很少发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;存在断开连接的系统，因为每个系统都是为了满足组织在特定时间点的需求而构建的。但随着时间的推移，随着业务需求和工作流程的发展，这些系统的设计方式与不断变化的业务需求之间存在着差距。例如，云系统不与大型机系统通信。今天的新系统很可能是明天断开连接的遗留系统。当组织认为这是一个不可避免的问题时，他们就隐含地接受了长期成本：客户或最终消费者遇到的低效率、错误、延迟，以及收入风险、扩展障碍、客户体验、客户流失等方面的业务风险。 ，或市场份额的损失。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了弥合这些差距，所有组织都倾向于“让人员解决问题”：员工手动从多个系统中提取数据，做出决策，然后将数据输入回相关系统系统。这些员工充当不同系统之间的人类粘合剂，承担“转椅”的角色。当然，这会带来与&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/08/how-much-time-and-energy-do-we-waste-toggling- Between-applications&quot;>;在众多应用程序之间切换相关的认知和生产力成本&lt;/a>;。但这只是总成本的一部分。断开连接的系统会产生信息孤岛，导致大量的手动工作和执行过程中的过度延迟。最终，这些缺点凸显了脱节债务的真正成本：对组织成果和关键绩效指标持续产生负面影响，从而加剧风险。组织需要在很长一段时间内支付这些成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了了解断开连接的系统的拖累给公司带来了多大的损失，我们研究了超过 103 个团队，他们在 13 个关键领域的 1,000 多个实例中参与了超过 42 个流程。业务涵盖 10 家财富 500 强企业和 8 家中小企业。我们使用工作图（组织中团队如何工作的数字地图）来确定这些成本的产生地点和方式，并根据成本、客户体验、员工体验、收入和风险对它们进行排序。我们研究的公司涵盖银行、零售、电信、生命科学和消费品。为了估计断开连接的系统对业务成果的唯一影响，我们忽略了团队支付的切换税。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们发现断开连接的系统对业务成果的影响存在很大差异。在某些情况下，团队将多达 60% 的工作日时间花在此类系统产生的活动上——从多个系统提取信息、将数据输入其他系统等。这种低效的工作利用导致了“断网债务”——组织付出了高昂的代价下表总结了我们在各个职能部门和团队中发现的结果及其对业务成果的影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;! -- table start -- 断开债务 -- ajrp 2023 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;div>; &lt;h4>;断开债务&lt;/h4>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;企业断开系统的成本。&lt;/p>; &lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;5&quot; cellpadding=&quot;5&quot;>; &lt;thead>; &lt;tr>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;函数&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;流程&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot;>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/th>; &lt;th valign=&quot;top&quot; width=&quot; 25%&quot;>;业务维度&lt;/th>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;/thead>; &lt;tbody>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;供应链&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td >; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;订单管理&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class= &quot;&quot;>;订单创建和处理延迟了 11%&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;收入&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr >; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;供应链&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;规划&lt;/p >; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开系统的估计平均影响（断开债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;所有规划工作延迟 10%，影响季度收入&lt;/p>; &lt;/td >; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;成本&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;供应链&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;退货&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;估计平均影响（断网债务）断开连接的系统&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户退货延迟了 12%–18%，导致糟糕的客户体验和保留挑战&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/ p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;客户服务&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;计费&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class =&quot;&quot;>;客户账单处理速度慢了 7%，导致客户保留率较差&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户体验&lt;/p>; &lt; /td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;客户服务&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot; &quot;>;客户加入&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户加入速度慢 5%，可能导致客户数量减少满意度 (CSAT) 分数和较低的市场份额&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;客户服务&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;订单履行&lt;/p >; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户订单处理速度减慢 15%，可能导致 CSAT 分数降低&lt;/p>; &lt; /td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;收入/客户体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;客户服务&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;服务保证&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;预计断开连接的系统的平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;客户服务速度比预期慢 34%，导致 CSAT 分数较差&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt; /p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;成本/客户体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;财务&lt;/p>; &lt;/ td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;应收账款&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开系统的估计平均影响（断开债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;由于应收账款延迟 16%，营运资金减少&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务规模&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;成本/风险&lt;/p >; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;功能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;财务&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class= &quot;&quot;>;应付账款&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开系统的估计平均影响（断开债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;供应商付款比预期慢 20%，可能领先更高的供应商流失率&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;成本&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人力资源&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;录用信&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt; td>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;新员工收到录用通知书慢了 8%&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;员工体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人力资源&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class= &quot;&quot;>;员工入职&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开系统的估计平均影响（断开债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;新员工在入职期间面临 11% 的延迟&lt; /p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;员工体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人力资源&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;招聘&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;招聘流程慢了 14%&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class =&quot;&quot;>;成本/员工经验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/tr>; &lt;tr>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;职能&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人力资源&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;流程&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;培训&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;断开连接的系统的估计平均影响（断开连接债务）&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; >;培训相关功能运行速度慢8%&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;td>; &lt;p>;业务维度&lt;/p>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>;成本/员工体验&lt;/p>; &lt;/td>; &lt;/ tr>; &lt;/tbody>; &lt;/table>; &lt;div>; &lt;p class=&quot;&quot;>; &lt;!-- 来源：此处 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>; &lt;!-- table end -- 断线债务 -- ajrp 2023 -->;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论公司规模如何，我们发现断线债务会导致执行速度变慢、手动工作过多以及出现更多错误。对业务成果的最终影响可能有多种可能性，包括收入增长放缓、成本增加、风险增加以及客户和员工体验较差。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;例如，在上表中，断开连接的系统导致了总部位于美国的快速消费品零售商每年向分销渠道销售价值 3 亿美元的产品时，会额外延迟 10%（相当于额外几天）。同样，一家 F500 生命科学公司的 6,000 多名新员工在完成入职手续时又延迟了四个星期。最后，在一个例子中，注册新银行账户的客户在获得批准方面经历了几天的延迟。在此过程中，由于后端系统整合得不好，该组织与客户反复沟通，要求他们填写额外的表格和详细信息。而且内部流程缓慢，需要将多个系统的数据汇集在一起​​，然后将它们拼接在一起。所有这些不仅导致糟糕的客户体验，而且管理层担心他们可能会在竞争中失去潜在客户，因为竞争提供了更简化的注册体验。我们尚未研究的组织的其他领域也将遭受类似的断开系统成本。在团队没有遭受断线债务的少数情况下，我们发现他们要么在一个系统内执行所有工作，要么主要根据一个系统的数据参与决策。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;领导者可以做什么&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;随着业务需求的发展，由断开的系统产生的信息孤岛及其对业务成果造成的风险将继续成为现实。此问题会影响组织的所有部分，并给企业带来风险。因此，处理这个问题需要列入组织中所有领导者的议程。董事会中的首席执行官和风险委员会必须设定季度目标和指标，以积极跟踪和减轻因断开连接的系统而产生的风险。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从本质上讲，组织需要采用产品管理生命周期方法来管理断开连接的系统，并始终保持在线状态&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;优先考虑哪些领域需要进一步调查和改进的经验法则 - 业务关键部分的团队花费超过 5% 的工作日从至少 2-3 个离线的地方提取信息系统。因此，首先，领导者的首要任务应该是获得可见性——找到可能损害业务的孤岛并减轻其影响。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;1.了解断开连接的系统的存在及其对业务成果的影响&lt;/h3>; &lt;h3>;找到您的“Kellys”：&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;找到通常在一线的同事，对因断开连接而造成的客户挫败感有第一手的见解系统。培养一种文化，让他们可以公开与高层领导分享摩擦点，生成客户挑战的热图。通过社交倾听和高级领导者直接接触遇险电话来补充这一点。一些公司采取了“&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbsp.harvard.edu/product/115006-PDF-ENG&quot;>;零距离&lt;/a>;”方法，努力理解一线问题并系统地解决它们。&lt; /p>; &lt;h3>;为您的系统和流程创建遥测：&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;使用当今的工具，您可以绘制和测量系统交互，&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/do-you-know-how -your-teams-get-work-done&quot;>;创建“工作图”，即您的团队如何完成工作的地图&lt;/a>;。这有助于识别和量化断点，尤其是部门和系统之间的断点。因此，它允许您列出流程中最繁忙的断点的优先级列表。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;查找“Kellys”和工作图的组合为您提供了短期和长期攻击的优先级列表修复。 “Kellys”和工作图表测量中突出显示的重叠断点或摩擦点会产生您可以坚定地解决的优先事项。将此作为公司的每周纪律。根据这种可见性创建指标和目标，并将其一路发送给董事会的风险委员会。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;2.短期修复可以赢得时间。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;这些问题有短期修复，其功能更像是创可贴解决方案，容易受到业务变化的影响，包括收购、监管变化、流程变化、等等。但他们可以改善情况并为长期变革赢得更多时间。解决方案包括：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;构建单窗格应用程序：它们的唯一目的是从多个系统收集数据并将它们聚合到单个视图中。因此，用户不会花费精力从多个系统手动提取数据，而是专注于 &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/wellarchitected/latest/sap-lens/best-practice-1- 7.html&quot;>;单一应用程序窗口&lt;/a>;。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;自动化任务：从多个系统提取数据、预填充应用程序中的字段以及将数据写回到系统中。然而，这个解决方案是暂时的，因为它不能解决根本问题，并且可能只会导致在断开连接的解决方案之上激增更多的自动化解决方案。&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;利用计算领域的最新进展：LLM 以及其他工具可能是对于从多个系统中提取非结构化信息、减少手动工作并将其标准化为结构化格式非常有用。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;这些解决方案将从断开连接的系统中提取信息的机械手动工作从人类转移到了软件。这种方法降低了脱节的风险，并为企业领导者提供了解决根本问题的空间。例如，尽管建立了自动化，但过时且缓慢的系统仍然会减慢整个航空公司预订流程和客户体验。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;3.长期修复。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;可持续的长期解决方案成本高昂且难以实施。通常，它们可能涉及：&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;利用更新的技术从根本上重新设计系统：这些举措需要 18-36 个月的时间，并且通常涉及需要大量纪律的更大规模的变革管理工作。&lt;/li >; &lt;li>;要求构建更多更快、更可扩展且更安全的 API 和适配器。随着业务需求的发展和新工作流程的创建，这些 API 和接口将需要更新。&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;但是这些类型的变化并不是离散事件，因为业务需求不断发展，因此这些新的变化也不是孤立的事件。工程系统也很快就会过时。因此，组织需要一种不断迭代的策略——了解离线系统对业务目标的当前影响，短期修复以赢得一些时间和空间，以及长期更深入的修复。然后从头开始再次迭代。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Ways to Determine What Your Customer Really Values]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/3-ways-to-determine-what-your-customer-really-values]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_11_1219096552.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Klaus Vedfelt/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;公司经常陷入麻烦，因为他们对利益相关者的价值做出了错误的假设。避免这个陷阱的一个好方法是反映您的公司在这三个尺度上的位置，您应该按照提供的顺序进行操作：商品化与定制化；理性与感性；可评估与不可知。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/3-ways-to-define-what -your-customer-really-values?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/3-ways-to-define-what-your-customer-really- value?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;创造价值是商业战略和竞争优势的核心。例如，这就是新加坡航空&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com.au/Airline_Review-d8729151-Reviews-Singapore-Airlines&quot;>;始终跻身顶级航空公司名单&lt;/a>;的原因例如，为什么丰田是 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/martyswant/2021/12/16/why-toyota-is-the-top-auto-brand-in-the- halo-100/?sh=7ed923e16171&quot;>;在同行中评价如此之高&lt;/a>;。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但“价值”这个术语却令人惊讶地被误用和误解。在“创造价值”方面，由于对利益相关者有价值的错误假设，有很多地方会绊倒和跌倒。避免这个陷阱的一个好方法是反映您的公司在这三个尺度上的位置，您应该按照提供的顺序进行操作。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1.商品化与定制化&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;几年前，我为一群来自不同行业的经理举办了战略研讨会。我指出，价值是由许多因素创造的，我告诉大家，为了获得竞争优势而降低价格通常是错误的，因为价格不等于价值。澳大利亚最大矿业公司 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bhp.com/&quot;>;BHP&lt;/a>; 的高管特雷弗 (Trevor) 尖声说道：“如果你是价格接受者而不是价格制定者怎么办？ ?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;必和必拓在全球销售铁矿石、冶金煤、铜和其他矿物。特雷弗指的是必和必拓销售“商品”的事实。我就其他可能的差异化领域提出了建议，例如准时交货和客户服务。但对于中国公司的买家来说，这些并不是选择的主要推动因素。他们倾向于认为这些事情是理所当然的。即使产品的质量也不是区别因素，因为煤炭、铁矿石和其他矿物都是按照规格分级的。换句话说，Trevor 是对的，当所有其他&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the-volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;战略因素&lt;/ a>; 在购买决策中是平等的，这在商品中经常发生。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但我也是对的。许多其他产品和服务是定制的而不是商品化的，在这些情况下，价格不等于价值。例如，史蒂夫是一家专门从事大型和昂贵住宅的厨房设计和安装公司的首席执行官。当他的询问减少时，他立即认为自己“太贵了”。于是，他开始了一轮降价。但成本真的是问题吗？为了找到答案，我们采访了他的一些选择竞争对手的客户。一个典型的例子是珍娜。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;她为她的大房子的厨房寻求了三份报价。 “自然，它们的价格不同，”她说。 “我本可以按照提供的价格购买一辆新车。”她解释说，她选择的厨房承包商并不是最便宜的。对珍娜来说更重要的是其他四个因素：创新设计（她花了很多时间与每个承包商一起寻找最佳的设计解决方案）、工作质量（以前的客户对厨房装修的建议）、客户服务（易于处理和良好的倾听技巧）以及内含物的质量（推荐洗碗机、水槽和水龙头的品牌）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;她说，最后一个因素是“信任”。这“非常重要，因为她不会每天都在那里检查管道和电气配件的安装。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;您在商品化与定制化规模上的地位取决于独特价值的多少你为你的产品做出了贡献，这就是为什么你需要从这个规模开始。如果您从事供应原材料的业务，那么您可能不会增加太多价值。这意味着降低价格是增加竞争优势的唯一选择。但大多数企业的情况并非如此。您的“增值”可以包括从客户对您的服务的体验到您的材料质量的各种因素。这些是客户愿意支付更多费用的价值因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;下一个量表可帮助您了解您提供的价值类型。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2.理性与感性&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;几年前，我是一家制造房屋桁架和框架的公司的首席执行官。这些是在我们的工厂预制的，装载到卡车上，然后拖到客户的建筑工地。我们为建筑商提供了建造房屋骨架所需的一切。我的任务是让公司扭亏为盈。这要求我们获得竞争优势。因此，我们需要充分了解客户判断“价值”的标准。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;建筑商的价值是通过权衡价格与其他&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/05/dialing-up-the -volume-on-strategic-innovation&quot;>;战略因素。&lt;/a>;其中包括产品质量（产品必须符合规格并在安装过程中保持在一起）、交付（准时很重要，延误会产生金钱）和客户服务（技术建议和处理任何问题）。对于建筑商、我们的客户来说，购买决定是非常理性的，涉及仔细评估的成本和收益。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2015/01/when-to-sell-with-facts-and-figures -and-when-to-appeal-to-emotions&quot;>;但并非所有产品和服务都能以如此理性的方式增加价值&lt;/a>;。 Angeline是一家国际知名化妆品公司的产品经理。其产品主要通过大型零售百货商店销售。我问她对于她的消费者（即化妆品的使用者）的“价值”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;她回答说，“这个决定并不纯粹是理性的，因为形象非常重要。消费者与品牌产生情感联系。”她补充道，“这就是我们将我们的产品与知名名人联系起来的原因。”她还指出，在线影响者变得越来越重要：“他们可以成就或毁掉一个产品。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在理性与感性的尺度上找到自己的位置需要仔细审查客户的决策过程。他们是否受到情绪因素的影响，或者是否能够完全抛开情绪，采取务实、理性的态度？许多消费者的决定都包含情感成分，而相关公司的广告就完全泄露了信息。想想我们看到的汽车、旅行或软饮料等产品的广告。这些广告通过品牌和形象来定位产品，以最大化非理性价值因素，例如名人代言和高端形象。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这将我们带到了第三个尺度，这有助于阐明客户如何选择你.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3.可评估与不可知&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;想象一下。朱莉下班开车回家，她意识到自己需要牛奶、面包和大米。她不想在超市排队，所以她去了当地的便利店。在做出这个决定时，她会评估价格（她会比在超市支付更多费用）、客户服务（快速而愉快）、位置（方便，在回家的路上）、产品范围（他们有她想要的东西）、营业时间（它们是开放的）和商店展示（干净且组织良好）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有这些对她来说都是非常重要的，她决定进入当地的便利店而不是繁忙的地下停车场在超市。与她的决定相关的标准是已知的，并且可以由她进行评估。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但在其他情况下，情况并非如此。以我的朋友吉姆为例，他最近做了膝关节置换手术。我问他是如何选择他的外科医生的。 “他是我当地医生推荐的，”他说。 “看来他的名声不错。但是，天哪，他很贵。”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;吉姆的决定并不是基于价格。事实上，我还没有听到有人说他们刚刚被“镇上最便宜的外科医生”替换了髋关节或膝盖。那么，它是基于什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;吉姆没有评估价值的专业知识和技术知识。他对价值的看法是基于声誉和口碑。他认为这些因素会反映在价格中 - 因此价格越高，价值就越高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果您从事向没有背景的客户销售产品或服务的业务要准确了解它们是如何工作的，您需要弄清楚您在可评估与不可知范围内的位置。在这些地区进行购买的客户被迫依赖其他信息来源来做出购买决定。您必须确保您在其他来源中表现出色。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是为什么吉姆的专家在他向患者提供的小册子中参考了著名教学医院的大量最新研究成果。网站和亲自。他还详细描述了他使用的尖端技术，以证明他是最新的。最后，他收录了许多前患者的感言，用他们自己的话讲述他们的故事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;•••&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有很多方法可以帮助您在弄清楚客户的价值时会感到困惑。但是，思考您在三个价值尺度上的立场将帮助您确定您提供的独特价值（无论是有形的还是无形的），以及您的客户如何认可它。这就是您如何建立真正的、可持续的竞争优势。&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- 引用 -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 11 Oct 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Future of Mental Health at Work Is Safety, Community, and a Healthy Organizational Culture]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/the-future-of-mental-health-at-work-is-safety-community-and-a-healthy-organizational-culture]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_10_1446656906.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label= &quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Alexandr Dubynin/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt; span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;一项探索不断变化的员工格局的新研究&amp;#8217关于心理健康、耻辱和工作的经验和观点揭示了有关工作场所心理健康在大流行之前、期间和之后如何变化的新见解。研究结果表明，美国的心理健康状况并未改善，但也出现了一些新的亮点。工人们对工作中的心理健康表现出越来越高的认识，并超越传统福利和最新技术。他们越来越想要的是研究一直显示有效的东西：心理更健康的文化。作者详细分析了员工的需求以及“员工的需求”。越来越期待&amp;#8212;在心理健康支持方面，来自雇主的建议，并为领导者提供多种策略，以培养可持续的心理健康文化。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt; a href=&quot;/2023/10/the-future-of-mental-health-at-work-is-safety-community-and-a-healthy-organizational-culture?language=es&quot;>;西班牙语阅读&lt;/a >; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/the-future-of-mental-health-at-work-is-safety-community-and-a-healthy-organizational-culture?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;在过去四年中，全球流行病、种族正义清算和其他宏观挑战加速了工作场所心理健康状况发生了巨大变化。自那时以来，雇主通过提供扩大的福利、冥想应用程序、正念计划、心理健康日和宣传活动，取得了显着的进展。然而，这些投资本身还不够。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2019 年，Mind Share Partners 与 Qualtrics 合作开始了两年一次的工作中心理健康报告，以探索员工经验和观点不断变化的格局围绕心理健康、耻辱和工作。每份报告都收集了 1,500 名全职美国工人的全国代表性样本。每份报告还包括来自历史上边缘化人群的统计显着样本：女性、有色人种、LGBTQ+ 工人等。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;今年，我们的 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/mentalhealthatworkreport -2023&quot;>;第三项研究&lt;/a>;揭示了有关大流行之前、期间和之后工作场所心理健康如何变化的新见解。以下是我们发现的关于员工在工作中心理健康方面的愿望和需求的信息，以及雇主如何提供这些信息。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;工作场所心理健康的变化格局&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In Mind Share Partners 的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/mentalhealthatworkreport-2019&quot;>;2019 年首份报告&lt;/a>;中，我们将心理健康描述为工作场所幸福感、敬业度、和生产力，以及多样性、公平和包容性。尽管心理健康挑战的比例不断增加，但大多数雇主在有效的心理健康支持方面仅仅触及表面。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/mentalhealthatworkreport -2021&quot;>;2021 年报告&lt;/a>;，我们将工作场所心理健康描述为&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/10/its-a-new-era-for-mental-health-at-work&quot;>;催化时间点&lt;/a>;。在大流行期间，心理健康挑战的普遍性激增，工作本身对心理健康造成了更大的压力。与此同时，我们对心理健康的集体意识也增强了。我们更多地谈论这个问题，雇主正在投资更多的心理健康支持，例如福利、冥想应用程序和心理健康日。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight -center&quot; title=&quot;工作的未来&quot; dek=&quot;您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-future-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black ;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;工作的未来&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 您的公司会适应还是被抛在后面？ &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;2023 年，工作精神本身正在经历转变。随着世界摆脱大流行，工人们&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/sections/money/2022/09/13/1122059402/the-economics-behind-quiet-quitting-and-what -我们应该称之为“重新评估”什么对他们来说真正重要，从而导致更广泛的趋势，例如安静退出、“伟大的辞职”等等。与此同时，雇主投资继续发生变化。一些公司继续创新和改善工作场所体验，例如提高基本工资、试行四天工作周以及给予员工更大的工作地点和工作方式自主权。其他人则缩减了规模，希望实现“大流行前的正常状态”。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Mind Share Partners 2023 年工作心理健康报告的主要发现&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;今年的研究表明，心理健康美国的情况并没有改善，但也出现了一些新的亮点。工人们对工作中的心理健康表现出越来越高的认识，并超越传统福利和最新技术。他们越来越想要的是研究一直显示有效的东西：心理更健康的文化。我们的发现如下：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;员工正在从危机转向萎靡不振。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;从 2019 年到 2021 年，心理健康症状激增，员工对心理健康的总体看法下降。 2023 年，我们发现报告任何症状的人数下降了 20%，这是一个充满希望的趋势。但当被要求对过去一年的整体心理健康状况进行评分（满分 10 分）时，工人的评分持续下降。 2019 年，78% 的人给出了 7 到 10 的评分。2021 年，67% 的人给出了评分。 2023 年，61% 的评分在 7 到 10 之间，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/organizational-and-employee-development/pages/financial-strain-impacts-workers -mental-health.aspx&quot;>;据报道，财务&lt;/a>;和工作本身对心理健康的负面影响最大。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;心理健康状况如何看似同时改善和恶化？心理健康包括各种各样的经历，从可诊断的状况和症状到悲伤、倦怠和压力等挑战。摆脱大流行的许多危机缓解了当时许多心理健康挑战的严重性。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;但工人们进入了一个充满挑战的新世界：通货膨胀、增长&lt;a href=&quot;https:// time.com/5888024/50-trillion-venue-inequality-america/&quot;>;收入不平等&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/newsroom/press-releases/2023/venue- Poor-health-insurance-coverage.html&quot;>;贫困率&lt;/a>;、裁员、&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/companies-making-workers-employees-return-to-office-rto -wfh-hybrid-2023-1&quot;>;强制返回办公室&lt;/a>;，雇主加倍努力&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/31/google-ceo-to- Employees-productivity-and-focus-must-improve.html&quot;>;生产力&lt;/a>;和&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/recode/22841490/work-remote-wages-labor-force -participation-great-resignation-unions-quits&quot;>;在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/09/03/business”浪潮中，雇主和工人之间的紧张关系日益加剧&lt;/a>; /economy/strikes-union-sag-uaw.html&quot;>;工会化&lt;/a>;。这些问题本质上是社会、政治和经济问题。虽然治疗和冥想肯定可以帮助个体工人应对，但从根本上解决这些问题需要系统干预。许多人，比如年轻人，仍在应对&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/07/science/pandemic-adolescents-depression-anxiety.html&quot;>;危机&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;因此，许多人陷入了一种压倒性的感觉，嗯，“废话”，或者正如著名组织心理学家 Adam Grant 在 2021 年创造的那样，他们“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes” .com/2021/04/19/well/mind/covid-mental-health-languishing.html&quot;>;陷入困境&lt;/a>;。”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;投资组织文化胜过治疗和自我保健。&lt; /h3>; &lt;p>;从历史上看，雇主提供的心理健康支持主要集中在产品化、个性化的方法上——治疗、应用程序、休假。这为员工提供了在工作之外的业余时间自我管理心理健康的资源。同时，这也意味着应该私下处理此事。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，在过去几年中，&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/business- news/poor-working-conditions-can-impact-your-mental-health/450455&quot;>;围绕心理健康与工作本身之间相互依赖性的研究继续变得更加有力。 &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/12/burnout-is-about-your-workplace-not-your-people&quot;>;职业倦怠&lt;/a>;尤其是&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/ news/item/28-05-2019-倦怠-职业现象-国际-分类-疾病&quot;>;世界卫生组织定义&lt;/a>;从根本上根源于管理不善的工作场所压力。同样，顶尖的倦怠研究专家克里斯蒂娜·马斯拉赫 (Christina Maslach) 指出了&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/02/beyond-burned-out&quot;>;导致倦怠的六大主要原因&lt;/a>;：不可持续的工作量、感觉缺乏控制、努力奖励不足、缺乏支持性社区、缺乏公平以及价值观和技能不匹配——所有这些都是工作场所因素。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;为了更好地了解工人的需求，我们要求今年的受访者评价以下因素对他们心理健康的帮助程度：&lt; /p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;心理健康治疗&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;心理健康的自我保健资源&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;有利于心理健康的安全和支持性文化&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;健康的文化和可持续的工作文化&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;在所有受访者中，健康和可持续的文化成为明显的赢家，78％的人认为它有中等、非常或极其有帮助。当按照性别、代际、LGBTQ+ 身份、种族和族裔、照顾者状况和资历水平对结果进行细分时，这一点仍然成立。其次是有利于心理健康的安全和支持性文化（67%），其次是心理健康治疗（64%）和自我保健资源（60%）。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;员工对心理健康的认识也不断提高。更好地了解什么样的支持才是真正有帮助的——不仅仅是应付工作。员工们将心理健康视为工作场所的集体责任，而不是个人的责任。支持工作中的心理健康越来越意味着从根本上重新调整组织文化与人类福祉。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;心理安全感有所下降。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;从我们 2019 年至 2021 年的研究中，员工变得更加愿意交谈了解心理健康，并对心理健康和患有心理健康问题的人形成更健康的信念。两者都表明心理健康耻辱感有所减少。随着雇主增加对心理健康资源的投资，更多的工人也表示感受到了支持。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;然而，进入 2023 年，一个悖论出现了。工人的个人信仰继续反映了对心理健康的更大认识和理解。然而，他们也觉得在工作中谈论心理健康不太安全，不太可能这样做，而且今年在心理健康方面得到雇主的支持较少——而且这些下降接近大流行前的水平。事实上，员工对向高层领导谈论心理健康的满意度几乎下降了一半，从 2021 年的 37% 降至 2023 年的 19%。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不幸的是，这并不奇怪。尽管许多雇主在心理健康方面进行了投资，但许多雇主也“重返业务”&lt;a href=&quot;https://about.fb.com/news/2023/03/mark-zuckerberg-meta-year-of-效率/&quot;>;生产力&lt;/a>;、&lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/06/01/marc-benioff-salesforce-performance-culture-earnings-call/&quot;>;绩效&lt;/a>; , &lt;a href=&quot;https://tech.co/news/heres-what-google-meta-and-co-have-cut-to-save-costs&quot;>;底线成本&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/01/10/resistance-attrition-quiet-quitting-drop-diversity-forced-return-to-office-gleb-tsipursky/&quot;>;返回办公室计划&lt;/a >; 和&lt;a href=&quot;https://abcnews.go.com/US/corporate-america-slashing-dei-workers-amid-backlash-diversity/story?id=100477952&quot;>;对 DEI 的投资&lt;/a>; - 同时仍然鼓励灵活性和工作与生活的平衡，尽管工作的现实使其更加难以实现。在复杂的信号中，尽管个人层面的意识有所提高，信念更加健康，但员工在组织内的心理安全感却恶化了。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;对 DEI 的投资正在改善心理健康和参与度。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>; Mind Share Partners 自 2019 年以来与 Qualtrics 合作进行的所有三项研究都表明，来自边缘化身份群体的人在心理健康和工作方面面临着不成比例的挑战。今年，女性、Z 世代、黑人、拉丁裔和 LGBTQ+ 受访者的心理健康状况往往比同龄人更差；当他们谈论工作中的心理健康时，不太可能得到支持性回应；总体而言，他们对工作满意度、信任、自豪感和留在雇主的意愿的参与程度较低。这些结果代表了文化和制度的持续存在，这些文化和制度不仅导致了公然的歧视行为，而且还导致了招聘、发展和支持流程中嵌入的偏见。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;好的一面是什么？雇主的努力得到了回报，并为工人的经历带来了有意义的改变。感觉雇主支持其身份的受访者在心理健康以及工作对心理健康的影响方面表现出更好的结果，并且总体上与那些感觉不支持的受访者相比，他们对雇主更加投入和忠诚。&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;返回办公室问题的答案是自主权。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;关于混合工作的争论持续升温&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/newsletters/archive/2023/07/远程工作返回办公室政策/674736/&quot;>;有争议&lt;/a>;。在今年的研究中，我们询问参与者是否亲自工作、混合工作或完全远程工作。此外，我们还询问他们这样做是出于选择还是雇主强制要求的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在比较不同工作情况的关键结果时，没有出现一致的主题。然而，可以自由决定工作地点的混合型员工的心理健康症状持续时间较短，工作对心理健康的积极影响更大，在工作中谈论心理健康更舒适，因心理健康原因离职的可能性更低，以及更大的自豪感和在当前雇主工作两年或更长时间的意愿。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;没有、也永远不会有一种明确“更好”或“更差”的单一、普遍的工作方式” 比另一个。 （还记得&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/the-truth-about-open-offices&quot;>;开放式办公室&lt;/a>;吗？）好处总是会因公司、职能、行业、地区、文化而异，&lt; a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/in-the-office-it-is-all-about-moments-that-matter&quot;>;员工生命周期的阶段&lt;/a >;、团队成员个人的需求和偏好等等。然而，对工作地点的关注分散了工作的许多其他方面，例如我们的工作时间或沟通方式。更重要的是，它掩盖了一个更基本的问题：个人的能力选择&lt;/a>;适合他们的方式。&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;雇主可以做什么&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;自 2017 年成立以来，Mind Share Partners 一直与跨行业、跨规模和跨地区的全球组织合作。随着我们继续加强雇主内部的培训、战略咨询和实施工作以及更广泛的运动建设和宣传举措，我们根据今年的调查结果为组织提供了五项关键战略：&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;共同重新设想一个心理健康的工作场所。&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;对于心理健康的工作场所，永远不会有一个一刀切的愿景。要实现这一目标，需要根据组织的规模、阶段、行业、地区、个人角色等，集体重新设想工作场所心理健康对组织中的每个人（领导者和员工）意味着什么。首先要了解您的组织、组织内部的心理健康状况，以及最终您的员工的需求。 This means &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/post/5-workplace-mental-health-questions-to-include-in-employee-pulse-and-employee-engagement-surveys&quot;>;measuring&lt;/a>; mental health and workplace factors, asking about workers&#39; perspectives on a regular basis, and enacting real, meaningful change tailored to the needs of your people. Further embedding these efforts into your organization&#39;s culture, systems, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/post/prioritizing-mental-health-throughout-employee-journey-mapping&quot;>;employee life cycle&lt;/a>;, and business strategy ensures that well-being is built into the business itself, not simply relegated to an HR &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/08/what-wellness-programs-dont-do-for-workers&quot;>;wellness program&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Enable culture change from top down and bottom up.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This year&#39;s study showed that workers want safer and more supportive cultures for mental health and healthier and more sustainable work cultures in general. Inevitably, this kind of culture change requires both top-down and bottom-up approaches.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From the top, leaders can tell their own &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/leaders-sharing-your-own-mental-health-story-can-help-you-become-a-better-ally&quot;>;mental health story&lt;/a>; within their organization or turn outward and share publicly like in Mind Share Partners&#39; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/leadersgofirst&quot;>;Leaders Go First &lt;/a>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/leadersgofirst&quot;>;campaign&lt;/a>;. This normalizes mental health and helps others feel comfortable talking about it at work if they want to. They can also model healthy work practices and, specifically as leaders, resource teams and individuals to maintain healthy and sustainable ways of working.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;From the bottom-up, employers and individual workers alike can explore forums for conversation, such as &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/05/how-to-form-a-mental-health-employee-resource-group&quot;>;employee resource groups&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/peerlisteningprograms&quot;>;peer listening programs&lt;/a>;, a cross-functional mental health working group, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/casestudy-pgim&quot;>;mental health champion networks&lt;/a>;. These conversations can be about mental health, but they can also take place within teams to establish work norms, explore &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/the-radical-promise-of-truly-flexible-work&quot;>;inclusive flexibility&lt;/a>;, and empower individuals to decide how they work best.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One natural step forward is to equip your people to lead this change. This typically happens through training across levels, taking a proactive, preventive approach with a management and equity lens that goes beyond simply “noticing the warning signs.” Workers and leaders alike need the strategies to create psychological safety and sustainable work cultures. Upskilling your people can also include &lt;a href=&quot;/2020/08/8-ways-managers-can-support-employees-mental-health&quot;>;manager programs&lt;/a>;, leadership coaching, mentorship, and more.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Explore root-cause solutions alongside wellness perks.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;When managing any strategy or budget, it&#39;s easy to fall into the trap of investing in “quick fix” programs and products without critically evaluating their purpose. For instance, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/mindsharepartners/2019/10/10/the-futility-of-mental-health-days/&quot;>;mental health days&lt;/a>; allege benefits of rest and rejuvenation and are often accompanied by optimistic awareness slogans like “It&#39;s OK not to be OK!” This can accomplish commendable intentions: giving rest, raising awareness, and sparking a broader dialogue. But what comes after? Well, in many cases, it&#39;s back to the same churn and burn(out). Even worse, it enables employers to continue “not okay” (ie, unsustainable) business practices under the guise of personal resilience.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Leaders need to offer ways to cope &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;solve for root causes. There&#39;s an ever-growing number of players in the space — &lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/6308096/therapy-mental-health-worse-us/&quot;>;health care providers&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/08/what-wellness-programs-dont-do-for-workers&quot;>;wellness programs&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/the-unbearable-irony-of-meditation-apps/&quot;>;meditation apps&lt;/a>; — each with its own philosophy, approach, product, and business objective. All have their unique benefits often steeped in scientific literature, but when workers are asking for a healthy and sustainable culture of work, these approaches &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eidCHlP8_bQ&quot;>;may not solve the right problem&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Recommit to the foundations of work itself.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;While every organization is different, there are still core foundations every workplace must meaningfully address in order to cultivate a mentally healthy workforce:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Safety:&lt;/strong>; This includes physical and psychological safety, financial stability, as well as balance and sustainability in the long term.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Autonomy: &lt;/strong>;This includes the time, bandwidth, and resources to do one&#39;s job; control, flexibility, and predictability over one&#39;s work; and having a voice.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;strong>;Belonging: &lt;/strong>;This includes the ability to show up authentically to work, make meaningful connections and be supported, and feel a holistic sense of community with others.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;These are core human needs that, unfortunately, tend to be overlooked as employers pursue wellness perks without addressing the fundamentals. For a deeper dive, explore the US Surgeon General&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hhs.gov/surgeongeneral/priorities/workplace-well-being/index.html&quot;>;recently launched framework&lt;/a>; on workplace mental health and well-being, which Mind Share Partners collaborated on.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Stay the course on DEI.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Employers&#39; place in solving the inequities of the world has been heavily debated, to say the least. But let&#39;s look even more simply at what&#39;s well within the realm of their control: the workplace. Organizations not only have the ethical responsibility to avoid perpetuating inequity but also the opportunity to help employees flourish from human diversity, camaraderie, and shared purpose. This year&#39;s data shows that when social identities are supported, workers have better mental health and engagement outcomes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Mental health and DEI are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/diversityinclusion&quot;>;intrinsically tied&lt;/a>;. Historically marginalized groups face added cultural and structural barriers both at work and when &lt;a href=&quot;https://steinberginstitute.org/bipoc-mental-health-month-common-barriers-to-mental-health-services/&quot;>;seeking&lt;/a>; mental health support. Mental health is also a category within DEI given the prevailing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/stigma-and-discrimination&quot;>;stigma and marginalization&lt;/a>; of those navigating mental health challenges or living with conditions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ultimately, DEI is about making the work work for everyone. Of course, like any visionary goal, this requires people power, budget, strategic planning, and cross-functional investment. Unfortunately, some employers have &lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/it-shouldn-t-be-this-easy-for-companies-to-walk-back-th-1850686363&quot;>;shied away&lt;/a>; from DEI amid the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/06/30/business/economy/hiring-affirmative-action.html&quot;>;rollback&lt;/a>; of affirmative action. Others remain steadfast and committed, in part as a business imperative. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mindsharepartners.org/post/mind-share-partners-to-corporate-america-stay-the-course-on-dei&quot;>;Our message&lt;/a>;? Stay the course.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;What would typically take decades for a social movement, the workplace mental health movement achieved in a matter of years.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As we look to the future, the workplace mental health movement will ultimately need to go “back to basics.” Workers no longer want frivolous perks to distract them from work. They want stable employment to mitigate financial anxiety, recognition to know they matter, sustainable workloads to prevent burnout, a supportive community to find belonging, the flexibility to decide how work works for them, and the autonomy and voice to feel respect, agency, and ownership over their work and their lives.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The future of mental health at work won&#39;t be an emerging technological renaissance or a transformation of hybrid work. The future will be a recommitment to core human needs. It will be safety, community, and a healthy organizational culture. It will be sustainable work rooted in equity and workers&#39; voices. The future of workplace mental health will start with exactly that: work itself.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 23:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Your Organization Should Use Salary Benchmarking]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/why-your-organization-should-use-salary-benchmarking]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_09_1372212398.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Jorg Greuel/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In a growing number of states and countries, employers are not allowed to ask job candidates&amp;#8217; salary history or even their salary expectations. That means employers must find new ways to determine appropriate compensation. A key solution lies in salary benchmarking &amp;#8212; using aggregated market data to establish competitive pay rates. Recent research in collaboration with a leading US payroll processing company revealed that access to robust benchmarking tools doubled the probability of firms setting the &amp;#8220;right&amp;#8221; salary. Data sources vary from government-released data to crowdsourced information on platforms like Glassdoor. Despite the availability of various tools, ensuring that salary decisions align with market trends is crucial, not just for compliance but also for retaining talent. As pay transparency grows, leveraging high-quality benchmarking sources effectively can optimize employer&amp;#8217;s wage expenses and bolster employee retention.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/why-your-organization-should-use-salary-benchmarking?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/why-your-organization-should-use-salary-benchmarking?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Recent transparency policies across several US states, like salary history bans that prevent employers from requiring candidates to report their compensation or even their salary expectations, have heightened the focus on fair salary practices in the workplace. As a result, there&#39;s an increased demand for strategies to determine appropriate compensation. A key solution lies in salary benchmarking: using aggregated market data to establish competitive pay rates.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Setting salaries is a balancing act: you do not want to offer salaries that are too high relative to the market, because that&#39;d be wasteful; but offering salaries that are below market may make it difficult to attract, retain and motivate your employees. How do employers find their sweet spot?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nber.org/papers/w30570&quot;>;recent study&lt;/a>;, we developed a theoretical model to shed light on the demand for salary benchmarking. In our model, firms know exactly how much value the job candidate would bring to the table. The firm would like to offer the candidate below that value to keep some of the value as profit. However, how much lower should the offer be? The lower the offer, the better the savings. On the other hand, if the offer is too low, the firm risks losing the job candidate to another firm — they may turn down the offer, or accept the offer and leave shortly thereafter.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;So, whether the company wants to make a more or less aggressive offer depends critically on what the firm believes is the market value of the job candidate: ie, how much &lt;em>;other firms&lt;/em>; are willing to pay for the job candidate. That&#39;s where salary benchmarking comes in: firms can use data on the offers accepted by similar employees (eg, with the same position title and industry) to make sure that their offer is not too low, or too high, relative to the market benchmark.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our research also provides empirical evidence that access to salary benchmarks has a significant effect on the salaries that firms set. We conducted it in collaboration with the largest US payroll processing company, ADP, serving 650,000 firms and processing paychecks for 20 million Americans. In addition to the payroll services, the company aggregates the salary data from their payroll records in the form of salary benchmarks. Clients can then &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adp.com/what-we-offer/products/adp-datacloud.aspx&quot;>;search&lt;/a>; for any job title they want in a user-friendly way. It is one of the most advanced benchmark tools and is being used by many prominent firms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our data covers the roll-out of the tool when it was first introduced to the market, late 2015, through the start of the pandemic in 2020. Our sample includes 584 “treatment” firms that gained access to the tool and 1,431 “control” firms that did not gain access to the tool but were selected because they shared similar characteristics to the treatment firms. We studied the evolution of salaries in the treatment firms shortly before and after they gained access to the benchmarking tool, and we compared that to the corresponding evolution of salaries in the control firms.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Here&#39;s what we found: let&#39;s say that a firm sets the “right” salary when they choose a salary that is in a narrow (5%) band of the median salary for the same position, industry, and state. Prior to gaining access to the benchmarking tool, there was an 11.6% probability that a firm sets the “right” salary. After gaining access to the benchmarking tool, the probability of setting the “right” salary increased two-fold, to 22.1%. This is compelling evidence that these salary benchmarks are truly influencing pay-setting, and causing position-level salaries to converge across companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also found that the effects of salary benchmarking are quite symmetric. After looking up the benchmark, firms are less likely to pay significantly above-market, presumably because it would be wasteful; but firms are also less likely to pay significantly below-market, presumably because it would be costly in terms of attracting, retaining and motivating employees.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For standardized positions, such as bank teller and receptionist, we found some evidence of a modest increase in the average salary. If employers are choosing to raise salaries for this group, it must be because they expect to get something in return, right? For instance, bumping salaries up to market may allow employers to retain their employees and save those pesky turnover costs. Our research shows that, indeed, benchmarking improves retention. Among employees in these roles, the gain of about 6% in average salary was followed by an increase of about 16% in the retention rate over the following 12 months.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How can I use salary benchmarking?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The payroll data show that high quality salary benchmarks sway employers to set pay closer to the marketplace median pay, and that benchmark users benefit from a boost in employee retention. But how exactly does one go about sourcing and using a salary benchmark?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Salary benchmarks are wide ranging; some are created by the government and others exclusive to the clients of consulting firms. Still others are crowdsourced data from anonymous employees. For example, the US government reports average earnings at the six-digit occupation code, within industry and state, each year using surveys of businesses and households. These data are highly representative, but are released infrequently and at a higher level of aggregation than the sought after position level information. Meanwhile, several large consulting firms offer exclusive access to the aggregated earnings of their clients, often using proprietary standardized corporate titles. Most recently, firms that collect salary information as part of their core businesses, like ADP, have added user interfaces that make these data accessible as benchmarks. And platforms like Glassdoor have encouraged millions of users to volunteer their salary information anonymously in exchange for seeing the average inputs of others at the position level.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To better understand how firms use salary benchmarking, we also conducted a survey with the members of the Society for Human Resource Management Research Institute (SHRM). We collected responses from a large sample of 2,085 HR managers in charge of pay-setting. This sample spans organizations of every size, state and industry, including both public and private sectors. To complement this data, we conducted an additional survey with a sample of clients from ADP, in which we obtained responses from 720 HR managers in charge of pay-setting.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Employers use salary benchmarking for a wide range of purposes. For instance, 54% of respondents use benchmarking when setting the pay of new hires. Other popular uses include salary negotiations (53%), setting ranges for specific job titles (90%), and setting the salary for a job advertisement (41%). Employers also vary in terms of how frequently they consult salary benchmarks. For instance, while some employers do benchmarking for every single new hire (37% of respondents), the rest prefer to do it for some specific new hires or for some specific positions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our survey data indicates that employers differ in which data sources they use. The most popular option is to use industry surveys, chosen by 68% of respondents, but hiring a consulting firm to conduct these surveys can be quite expensive, and there is no guarantee that the survey data will live up to the expectations. If you do not have a big budget, you may also want to try the second most popular option: free online data sources (58% of respondents) such as Glassdoor.com. More recently, payroll service companies have gained popularity (used by 23% of respondents and the fastest growing source), which may give the best bang for your buck in terms of data quality. Most employers, however, use a combination of data sources. While the majority look at free online sources, on a scale of 1-5, HR professionals report that other sources are twice as trustworthy as free online sources.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Labor market trends can sometimes change rapidly, especially in the post-pandemic world. You do not need to check the benchmarks on a daily basis, but try to at least do it from time to time — remember that information, too, has an expiration date. Likewise, you may not have time to sit down to study market trends for every position in which you hire. However, make sure to at least do due diligence for the positions that are most critical for your business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When using a benchmarking tool, you may feel information overload. Some tools provide not only the median pay, but also the mean, 10th percentile, 25th percentile, and so on and so forth. And some tools allow you to filter by industry, state, and other criteria. There are trade-offs. For instance, filters can allow you to focus on peer employers, but at the cost of smaller sample sizes and thus statistically imprecise benchmarks. While the right approach depends on the context at hand, according to our survey, there are some clear favorites: most firms (89%) prefer to look at the median market pay or the average market pay, and the most popular filters are by industry (87%) and state (84%).&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We also gave the survey respondents an opportunity to share their own tips and advice for salary benchmarking. Some recommended not relying on job title information alone, but rather to pay attention to the job description to ensure it&#39;s a good match. Another manager suggested that, to the extent possible, you should review the benchmarks regularly to stay in sync with the latest trends in the job market. In the same spirit, one manager recommends being proactive — do not wait until employees are unhappy about low pay and reach out to you, or you risk higher turnover.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In sum, the pay transparency revolution extends to firms knowing much more about what their competitors are offering. New high-quality sources have changed pay-setting practices. According to our latest study, keeping up with pay in the marketplace, and knowing how to use those sources, can affect your bottom-line retention and payroll costs. And from a societal perspective, this is closing the gap between pay across firms.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 22:25:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[10 Reasons Why Inclusion Is a Competitive Advantage]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/10/10-reasons-why-inclusion-is-a-competitive-advantage]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/10/Oct23_10_457893079.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Michael H/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;In their new book, &lt;em>;Move Fast and Fix Things&lt;/em>;, Frances Frei and Anne Morriss outline five strategies to help leaders tackle their hardest problems and quickly make change. Their third strategy is creating an inclusive environment that allows all employees to thrive. Although it can be hard to measure a complex outcome like inclusion, researchers are working to identify and quantify the many effects of inclusion on firm performance, and the insights they&amp;#8217;re generating are persuasive.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/10-reasons-why-inclusion-is-a-competitive-advantage?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/10-reasons-why-inclusion-is-a-competitive-advantage?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;Facebook made “Move fast and break things” an informal company motto. But leadership experts Frances Frei and Anne Morriss argue that this belief is deeply flawed — and that it keeps leaders from building a great company. &lt;/em>;&lt;em>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;The best leaders move fast and fix things — they solve hard problems while making their organizations stronger. In their new book &lt;/em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://store.hbr.org/product/move-fast-and-fix-things-the-trusted-leader-s-guide-to-solving-hard-problems/10546&quot;>;Move Fast and Fix Things&lt;/a>;&lt;em>; (Harvard Business Review Press), Frei and Morriss outline five strategies to help leaders tackle their hardest problems and quickly make change:&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Identify your real problem. (See &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/10-signs-your-company-is-resistant-to-change&quot;>;10 Signs Your Company Is Resistant to Change&lt;/a>;)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Build — or rebuild — trust with your stakeholders. (See &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/10/10-pitfalls-that-destroy-organizational-trust&quot;>;10 Pitfalls That Destroy Organizational Trust&lt;/a>;)&lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Create inclusive conditions that allow your whole team to thrive. &lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Tell a compelling story about the change you need to make. &lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;&lt;em>;Execute your plan with a sense of urgency. &lt;/em>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;This month, we&#39;ll be publishing a series of excerpts that correspond to each strategy. Today&#39;s excerpt is about inclusion, which Frei and Morriss define as the act of creating conditions that allow other people to thrive — not in spite of their differences as complex, multidimensional humans, but precisely because of those differences.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Although it can be hard to measure a complex outcome like inclusion, researchers are getting better at it. Serious people are working to identify and quantify the many effects of inclusion on firm performance, and the insights they&#39;re generating are persuasive. Below is a list of some of our favorite findings, many of which remain generally underappreciated.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1. Inclusion helps you recruit good people. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Inclusion is now a tell for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.glassdoor.com/employers/blog/diversity/&quot;>;all kinds of talented people&lt;/a>; — not only the underrepresented — that you&#39;ve built a healthy workplace and understand what it takes to collectively excel. Expect candidates to look for evidence of inclusiveness in everything from where you recruit to the fine print of your benefits package. For example, they may not need those same-sex fertility benefits or veteran mentorship services, but they&#39;ll still see them as a sign that you appreciate difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2. Inclusion helps you retain good people.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It turns out that those same candidates &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/12/to-retain-employees-focus-on-inclusion-not-just-diversity&quot;>;will stick around as employees&lt;/a>; if you truly walk the talk on inclusion. Inclusion drives &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jstor.org/stable/25067557&quot;>;higher rates of retention&lt;/a>; at all levels of the organization, and some employee segments (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shrm.org/foundation/ourwork/initiatives/engaging-and-integrating-military-veterans/Documents/13056-G-01_SHRMF_WhyHireVet.pdf&quot;>;military veterans top the list&lt;/a>;) will reward your ability to value their unique contribution with industry-leading loyalty.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3. Inclusion increases the engagement of your people. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Engagement scores are consistently higher for companies labeled “inclusive,” and we now have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshbersin/2015/12/06/why-diversity-and-inclusion-will-be-a-top-priority-for-2016/?sh=fc0a6632ed5b&quot;>;some interesting data&lt;/a>; that helps to explain these numbers. Inclusive companies are &lt;em>;also &lt;/em>;almost three times better at coaching people for improved performance and four times better at identifying and building leaders. Making people better is the key to their engagement, and inclusion seems to give you an advantage.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4. &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Inclusion makes you more resilient.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When different types of people are thriving in your organization, &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;you&#39;re better at navigating crises&lt;/a>; and (our favorite business euphemism) “turbulent times” in general. You&#39;re more adaptable, more comfortable with change, and better at dealing with personnel problems. One fun fact: while the S&amp;amp;P saw a 35% decline in stock performance between 2007 and 2009 (remember that ride?), the shares of inclusive companies went in the other direction, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/mursalhedayat/2020/06/24/diversity-in-the-workplace-is-now-more-critical-than-ever/?sh=5172eb6e60aa&quot;>;gaining over 14% in value&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5. &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Inclusion grows your marketplace.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Inclusive teams are &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/how-diversity-can-drive-innovation&quot;>;better at identifying and cultivating new markets&lt;/a>; because they expand a firm&#39;s peripheral vision and help eliminate its blind spots. &lt;a href=&quot;/2004/09/diversity-as-strategy&quot;>;More women in decision-making roles&lt;/a>;, for example, improves a company&#39;s ability to solve problems for female clients. And this is before we even get to the macro implications of &lt;em>;economic &lt;/em>;inclusion. For example, the US GDP could get &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.accenture.com/_acnmedia/pdf-89/accenture-disability-inclusion-research-report.pdf&quot;>;a boost of up to $25 billion&lt;/a>; if just 1% more of persons with disabilities joined the labor force. What percentage of that boost would represent new customers for your business?&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6. &lt;/strong>;&lt;strong>;Inclusion makes you more innovative.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Inclusion creates a healthier meritocracy for new ideas &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/04/research-adding-women-to-the-c-suite-changes-how-companies-think&quot;>;where out-of-the-box thinking is more likely to break through&lt;/a>;. This happens in part because people in inclusive organizations are more likely to surface and hear the &lt;em>;what &lt;/em>;of a good idea rather than allow that idea to be diluted or buried by an unexpected &lt;em>;who&lt;/em>;. How much of an innovation bump does true inclusion buy you? Depending on your starting place, estimates range from &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/01/how-and-where-diversity-drives-financial-performance&quot;>;roughly 20%&lt;/a>; all the way &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/how-diversity-can-drive-innovation&quot;>;up to 70%&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;7. Inclusion turns you into better decision-makers. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Decision quality goes up when a range of voices are &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/11/why-diverse-teams-are-smarter&quot;>;not only present but also integrated&lt;/a>;. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/eriklarson/2017/09/21/new-research-diversity-inclusion-better-decision-making-at-work/?sh=627907124cbf&quot;>;one delightful study&lt;/a>;, all-male teams beat individuals nearly 60% of the time, but gender-diverse teams outperformed individuals almost 75% of the time. Teams that were gender diverse, geographically diverse, and had at least one age gap of more than 20 years made better decisions than that lone individual &lt;em>;87% of the time&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;8. Inclusion helps you manage risk.&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In the wreckage of the 2008 financial crisis, a serious “Lehman Sisters” argument emerged positing that the story would have played out differently if more women had been in the room for the most consequential decisions. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0148296315002143&quot;>;Subsequent&lt;/a>; &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.aom.org/doi/abs/10.5465/amj.2018.1039?journalCode=amj&quot;>;studies&lt;/a>; have since explored this argument, concluding that gender inclusion in the C-suite and boardroom is associated with a healthier firm relationship to risk—neither overly risk-averse nor risk-seeking—and better overall performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;9. Inclusion improves your stock price. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Estimated bumps to shareholder returns range &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.catalyst.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/The_Bottom_Line_Connecting_Corporate_Performance_and_Gender_Diversity.pdf&quot;>;from 10% to over 30%&lt;/a>; (seriously) when you get inclusion right. This may be why Goldman Sachs &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/article/bc-finreg-unlocking-diversity-inclusion/unlocking-diversitys-promise-psychological-safety-trust-and-inclusion-idUSKBN2C01N2&quot;>;recently announced&lt;/a>; that it would no longer take any company public where the board is made up exclusively of straight, white men. Whatever your organization&#39;s own return on inclusion may end up being, the question we often ask companies is, “What else are you doing to chase those kinds of returns?”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;10. Inclusion makes you more money. &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;For all the reasons we&#39;ve covered in entries one through nine, inclusion ends up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/diversity-and-inclusion/diversity-wins-how-inclusion-matters&quot;>;boosting both your top line and bottom line&lt;/a>;. Your talented, engaged teams will drive higher revenues through better innovation and smarter market development, while allowing you to spend capital more efficiently through better decision-making, higher retention, and higher productivity. And when you hit some turbulence along the way, you&#39;re more likely to land the plane safely. We hope to live in a world where inclusion is an organizational given. Until we get there, we know of no other distinction that can deliver these kinds of advantages.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;em>;This excerpt has been lightly edited.&lt;/em>;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>