<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>哈佛商业评论</title><description>哈佛商业评论全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link/> https://hbr.org/ <item><title><![CDATA[How to Think Strategically About a Career Transition]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a-career-transition]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;英雄图像 >; &lt;div>; &lt;div js-target=&quot;video-player-page&quot; data-props=&quot;{&quot;name&quot;:&quot;6336768663112&quot;}&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div >; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;div>;&lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;span>;加载中... &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt; /div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;script src=&quot;//players.brightcove.net/2071817190001/default_default/index.min.js&quot;>;&lt;/script>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption= &quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;摘要。&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;职业转型是艰难的。我们中的许多人很难想象一个与我们现有的角色截然不同的新角色。而一旦行动起来，就很难顺利进行。 Herminia Ibarra 随时为您提供帮助。这位伦敦商学院教授开始意识到职业变动是多么具有挑战性，并且她对如何提高成功率有一些想法。伊瓦拉是我们哈佛商业评论《工作新世界》一集的嘉宾。她是古巴人，在耶鲁大学获得硕士和博士学位。在担任伦敦商学院组织行为学教授之前，她曾是哈佛商学院和欧洲工商管理学院 (INSEAD) 的教员。谈话的重点是职业转型，她认为，当人们对他们是有策略的。还讨论了：网络和她对“真实性”的有些争议的看法。在工作场所。&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a -career-transition?language=es&quot;>;阅读西班牙语&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-think-strategically-about-a-career-transition?language=pt&quot; >;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;对于我们大多数人来说，重塑我们的职业生涯和我们自己是一项极其艰巨的任务。正如伦敦商学院教授 Herminia Ibarra 指出的那样，您可能知道您不想再做什么，但不确定下一步您实际上想要做什么。她说，人们“当他们不确切知道自己在搜索什么时，就不知道如何搜索”。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;比试图找出下一步职业更重要的是更广泛地思考关于你可能的自我，然后同时探索其中几个可能的自我。这就是拥有多元化网络有很大帮助的地方。虽然我们大多数人讨厌社交，但伊瓦拉也提供了如何在这方面做得更好的建议。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;在我们的视频系列“工作新世界”的这一集中，《哈佛商业评论》主编 Adi Ignatius 坐下来与多产作家、职业转型专家 Ibarra 一起讨论：&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;如何顺利、成功地从一种职业过渡到另一种职业&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;在工作场所保持真实，不限制自己的成长和发展&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;如何突破孤立的网络，真正与那些能够为您带来新机会的人建立联系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Ibarra 的两本书将于下个月推出更新版本：&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https: //www.amazon.com/Working-Identity-Updated-Preface-Unconventional-ebook/dp/B0BTMQ97ZG/&quot;>;工作身份：重塑职业生涯的非常规策略&lt;/a>; &lt;/em>;和&lt;em>;&lt;a href =&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Leader-Updated-Global-Bestseller-Preface-ebook/dp/B0BTMQN19H/&quot;>;像领导者一样行动，像领导者一样思考&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;。&lt;/ p>; &lt;hr>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;赫米尼亚，欢迎。&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight =&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;工作新世界&quot; dek=&quot;前几集&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt; a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-world-of-work&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 洞察中心集合 &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The新工作世界&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; 前几集 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA： &lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;非常感谢。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想谈谈很多关于职业转变的事情，但我想先介绍一下背景，我知道你的观点是，这是一个职业不断重塑的时代。您认为为什么会这样？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我研究职业重塑已有 20 多年了。第一版&lt;em>;工作身份&lt;/em>;已经是 20 年前的事了，而且这一趋势还在不断加速。如果说有什么不同的话，那就是我们正在重塑自己，并进一步重塑我们的职业生涯。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;有四件事促成了这一点。我们的寿命越来越长，随着我们寿命的延长，我们不想从 40 岁开始一直滑下去，因为我们很容易再工作 40 年。我们希望充分利用它。这是一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;二是技术。我不必对此多说，但它正在改变一切。它正在扰乱工作。它正在创造新的就业机会。它使我们能够在任何地方工作。它为能够重塑自己创造了一个非常有趣的环境。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第三个是我们的公司、组织、我们的工作场所：它们也不断受到干扰。这创造了机遇，但也带来了挑战。例如，我们最近在科技界看到了大规模的裁员浪潮。现在，金融行业的人们正在努力应对高利率以及这对他们的产品意味着什么，这样的例子不胜枚举。我们不再像以前那样长时间呆在工作岗位上，无论是出于选择还是被迫，因为我们被要求离开工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第四个趋势，这个趋势已经持续了很长时间，我们对工作的期望发生了很大变化。它曾经提供稳定的生活。 [现在]我们想要从工作中得到一切。我们想要激情，我们想要目标。我们想要自我实现。我们想要灵活性。我们对他们的要求太多，而且越来越不耐烦，如果得不到这些东西，我们就想继续前进。&lt;/p>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;newsletter&quot; name=&quot;The New World of Work&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;follow-subscribe data-name=&quot;hbpnewworldofwork&quot; data-activity=&quot;newsletter&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div style=&quot;color: #000000&quot;>; &lt;svg>; &lt;use xlink:href=&quot;/ resources/css/images/hbr-icons.svg#the-new-world-of-work&quot;>;&lt;/use>; &lt;/svg>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 订阅我们的每周通讯 &lt; /div>; &lt;div>; 工作新世界 &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 关于人才、技术和商业未来的坦诚对话。为订阅者准备的特别电子邮件系列。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; js-target=&quot;subscribe-for-newsletter-tout&quot; data-method=&quot;subscribe&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/ div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/sign-in&quot; js-target=&quot;sign-in-this&quot;>;注册&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;>;登录向上&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; 感谢您注册，&lt;span js-target=&quot;newsletter-success-firstname&quot;>; &lt;/span>;！ &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; 您可以查看我们的&lt;a href=&quot;/email-newsletters&quot;>;其他简讯&lt;/a>;或通过管理您的&lt;a href=&quot;/my-library/preferences&quot;>;随时选择退出电子邮件首选项&lt;/a>;。 &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/follow-subscribe>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果职业重塑，如果重塑的需求是当代商业世界的一个标准方面，为什么我们在尝试实现它时遇到这么多麻烦？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是我学到的一件事，这真的很难。这真的很难，比人们想象的要花更长的时间。有几件事。一是大多数人知道他们不想再做什么，但他们并不确切知道他们想做什么。因为他们没有答案，我会回过头来讨论这个问题，所以他们不知道该怎么办。当他们不确切知道自己在搜索什么时，他们就不知道如何搜索。这就是其中之一。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;另一个是，我们所做的就是我们是谁。这是一种非常重要的感觉，它是我们身份的一部分。即使失去一份我们不喜欢的工作也是一个巨大的损失，因为这是我们所做的事情，是与我们共度时光的人，是我们的时间的结构。我们已经做到了这一点。我们对此进行了投资。心理失落感是一个很大的障碍。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;最后一点是，尤其是从职业生涯中期开始，当我们改变职业时，我们就会转向不同的领域。它不是线性的，在更高层次上更加相似。这是不同的东西。我将这些转变称为制度化不足。我的意思是步骤不明确，你不知道需要多长时间。你没有和其他人步调一致地做这件事。目前还不清楚谁是榜样。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你想成为律师事务所的合伙人，你就知道步骤是什么。这可能很困难，但您知道步骤是什么和时间表。如果你是一名律师，想成为一名艺术企业家，那么这还没有制度化。没有什么特别的教育项目可供您参加。不同的人以不同的方式进入这个领域。目前还不清楚。这更加未知。目前还不清楚如何解决。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所以我想回到你谈到的第一点，那就是我们我们不太擅长弄清楚我们的可能性是什么。我认同这一点。我做过的大部分工作，都会有人来找我说，你愿意做 X 吗？即使是职业转变，我也没有想到，是其他人想到的。一切顺利，我热爱我的工作。但我认为很多人都觉得缺乏能动性，无法控制我在工作生活和职业生涯中想做的事情。有关于如何清晰思考下一步可能采取的建议吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我有很多建议。其中一件事是，我们必须摆脱这样的想法：如果你不知道答案，如果你不知道目标或目标职业，你应该等待并反思，直到你找到答案在你的脑海中。实际上我们并不是这么想的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当人们向你提出建议时，这真是太棒了。这也可能很危险，因为有时这些事情与你已经在做的事情太接近了。如果你确实想做出改变，它们可能不是最合适的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;比试图弄清楚更重要的是尝试。不要思考“对我来说最理想的工作是什么？”，[问]“可能是 10 个，或者可能是 6 个组织，或者可能是我可以采取的 5 条不同的途径？”并开始并行、同时地探索它们。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你边走边学。有时候，你以为自己想要的东西并没有实现。或者，例如，你梦想它们是这样的。有时会更困难并且需要更长的时间。你必须同时做一些其他事情。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;第一个明确的建议和成功做到这一点的方法是列出一系列可能性。我称他们为“可能的自己”。并开始并行地探索一个、两个，最好是多个。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我曾经与一位猎头进行过交谈，他们问我的工作情况。我告诉他们这符合我所有的要求。我对此感觉很好。我感觉我正在做一件重要的事情。我说：“每个人都有这样的感觉，对吧？”那个人说没有人有这种感觉。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;如果你处于这样的情况，那你就非常幸运了。我对人们对自己的工作感到满意的程度感兴趣。我们对工作的满意度有多少？这是工作，虽然它是生活的一部分，但不一定是我们的生活。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;根据您的经验和研究，我们中有多少人对自己的工作总体感到满意？这是常态还是我们必须接受一些较少的东西？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一般调查显示很多不满。这种情况来来去去，有时期，也有部门。重要的是要认识到工作并不是单一的。我热爱我的工作，它也符合我的所有要求，但我的工作中有些部分我真的不喜欢，感觉像是苦差事。有些部分是我喜欢的，每项工作都是如此。这是一个比例问题。总的来说，你主要是在做你觉得有成就感的事情吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;外面有很多人不满意。他们可能曾经是，但随着时间的推移，要么他们已经改变，要么他们的组织已经改变，或者与他们一起工作的人已经改变，他们不再对这些因素感到满意。他们不觉得受到挑战。他们不喜欢也不尊重与他们一起工作的人。它们与组织的使命不一致。所有这些都会造成不满。通过与我的学生交谈和进行研究，我的感觉是，今天有很多人不满意。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想在此基础上提出鹿特丹哈萨姆提出的问题。在一个日益由混合工作模式主导的世界中，您如何看待“员工体验”的演变？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我没有一个水晶球。我不知道。我所知道的是，组织仍在试图解决这个问题。他们仍在尝试不同的方式并试图了解员工的体验。但这是一个我无法回答的问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;好吧，这是另一个问题，这是来自瑞士的Ellie。我们应该如何考虑平衡？如果你转换职业，你就会危及你所积累的一些资历以及你所获得的好处和积极的一面。我们如何避免这种情况，或者我们如何考虑这种权衡？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这是另一个大问题，我是否必须这样做从底部开始？或者有办法不这样做吗？这取决于你下一步要做什么，对吧？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;过去几年我广泛采访过的一个人是她所在组织的首席合规官，她已经成为一名纪录片制片人。她必须从最底层做起，从一名学徒开始。这取决于情况。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;其他人会进入更邻近的领域，也许会更具创业精神。他们不必这样做，他们可以真正利用他们所拥有的技能和经验，尽管角色和环境截然不同。这取决于很多。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们试图通过重返学校来解决这个问题，这对你的淘汰有很大帮助。但每个人都忘记了，事情并不总是向上的。所以你会看到，“好吧，我在这里。如果我做出改变，我就会留在这里。而我可以继续升职，”情况很可能并非如此。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;世界在变化，工作岗位正在消失，如果你对所做的事情感到不快乐和富有成效，曲线很可能也在下降，你必须考虑到这一点。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;似乎正在讨论的另一个主题每个人的头脑都是人工智能。我们总是想知道技术是否会取代我们的工作。有时确实如此。对于生成式人工智能，我们都怀着高度的担忧来询问它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你是否在思考这个问题，它如何改变或加速你正在思考的一切？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>; &lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们正在将其视为伦敦商学院的一个机构。我正在尝试尽可能多地使用它。我感兴趣的是它如何改变人们的工作。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;从我的角度来看，我感兴趣的是它将如何改变人们的合作方式。谁做了什么？出现了哪些组织？我们不知道这些问题的答案。我们知道我们需要提出关于价值观一致性的重大问题。我们知道，从整个数字化转型浪潮来看，有技术部分，但还有整个其他部分，这就是它的使用方式。组织能够使用它吗？人们能够适应并充分利用它吗？所有这些还有待观察。但当然，它值得尝试、关注、研究、提出好问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所以这是一个问题与技术相关。这是来自班加罗尔的巴斯卡兰。 Bhaskaran 表示，在人力资源部门工作了 21 年之后，他们决定跳槽到一个较小的组织，希望它能够灵活、敏捷等等。结果证明它有剧毒。巴斯卡兰渴望新的角色和组织，但始终担心不确定性。当一个人考虑采取行动时，如何应对这种不可避免的对不确定性的恐惧？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;完全可以理解。不幸的是，转行的过程往往会前进一步，后退两步。现在你已经学到了一些东西，我认为你学到的部分内容是你需要真正更仔细地研究你将要接触的背景，并尽可能多地了解它们。现在你已经学会了更多地询问文化、与人们交谈、研究组织。所有这些都非常重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这就是为什么在我所做的研究中，经常出现“我不知道我想要什么，我不知道这需要多长时间”的不确定性的原因之一。将会采取”开始攻击人们。然后突然出现了一个选择，一个要约，与这家更小、更灵活的公司合作，它就是救世主。所以他们接受了它，因为否则他们仍然会陷入“我要做什么？”的痛苦之中，而没有尽可能多地进行研究。没有真正问“什么对我来说重要？”为此腾出时间非常重要。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论如何，你都得离开那里了。因此，您必然要应对不确定性，但也许要更仔细地研究一下。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们谈论两件事。一是如何思考职业转型时刻，如何积极主动、聪明应对。但好吧，你已经采取了行动。您如何成功过渡到这个新角色？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我很想听您多谈谈这一点。我们已经从 A 公司跳槽到 B 公司。我们应该给自己多长时间？我们应该对自己有多严厉？我们应该阅读&lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/First-90-Days-Strategies-Expanded/dp/1422188612&quot;>;前 90 天&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>;吗？我们如何成功过渡？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;前 90 天仍然是该主题的圣经。他首先说的（这也涉及到前一个问题）是，前 90 天实际上很早就开始了，包括做功课、与人们交谈并找出利益相关者。有一个可爱的想法，我认为这是你需要能够与你的老板或你的主要利益相关者进行五次对话，讨论关于如何衡量你的期望，关于关键主题，所以您将认识到您的成功与组织中其他人的成功之间的相互依赖关系。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;让我们换个话题来谈谈关于真实性，这是您研究并撰写了大量文章的另一个主题。我关于领导力的大多数对话在某些时候都会演变成关于工作中需要完全真实的对话。我的感觉是你对这一切的看法更加复杂。领导者应该如何考虑真实性问题？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这种完全真实性的东西让我抓狂。什么是完全真实性？是不是想到什么就说什么？是像周日在家去公园散步时穿的那样吗？这意味着什么？我认为这一切都有很多废话。真实性的定义是什么？这是一种特质吗？这是一个结果，一个了解自己并尽力成为自己的过程吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我不认为这是一种特质。我认为这是一个学习的过程。我们想要真实。没有人喜欢假货。没有人追随假货。这对你的心理健康有害。我完全赞成。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我问的问题是，你如何定义真实性，而不会让你像以前一样？我们成长，我们进化。我们是多重的。我们有不同的方面，我们是谁的不同方面表现出来。我们需要能够表达这种复杂性，并问自己：“当我学习时，真实意味着什么？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;当它成为习惯行为时，那就太好了。你知道该怎么做。但是当你学习的时候，你还没有弄清楚。人们往往会将习惯性行为与真实性混为一谈。当他们走出舒适区的那一刻，“哦，那不是真正的我。我没那么正宗。”通常的评论是：“那不是我。”好吧，现在不是你，你还没有尝试过。有时尝试这些有助于学习的东西，却感觉不真实。如果这就是学习的代价，我认为这是非常值得的。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;br>;当有些人谈论在工作中保持真实时，我认为他们想要公开他们是谁、他们的个人生活，也许还有他们的性取向。如果他们有一种古怪的幽默感，他们希望能够带来这种幽默感。一方面，你绝对需要学习新技能、软技能和硬技能。但人们觉得，如果他们能够以我所说的方式在工作中保持“真实”，他们就会获得深深的幸福感。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;对我来说，这更多的是一种归属感，以及能够弄清楚，“我属于这里还是我必须隐藏对我来说重要的事情才能在这里发挥作用？”&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;回到全身心投入工作的话题：职场关系就是关系。在人际关系中，人们会互相了解。当你见到某人的那一刻，你不会告诉他们关于你的一切，你的个人生活、职业生活、优势、疑虑、痛苦，所有这些。你不这样做。你可以认识人。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们以这种方式对待真实性，这一点非常重要。我们正在建立关系。当我们建立关系时，我们希望能够披露。自我表露是建立关系的基础。这确实很重要，但这并不是说每时每刻都能够以不尊重工作中建立关系的方式传播有关自己的一切。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>; &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我认为其中一些是世代相传的。我们这一代人倾向于不广播所有内容。我认为后代中的一些人对此更加满意，期望如此，并且对此感到满意。代际工作场所动态的一部分是我们所有人都对此感到满意。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关于复杂性的另一件事是，在工作场所，我们也会互相评估彼此的潜力。谁会做得好，谁会进步？我们在能够表现出脆弱性和表达脆弱性的背景下谈论了很多关于真实性。但是，当男性与女性表达脆弱性时，其编码方式并不相同；或者当黑人与白人表达自信时，其编码方式也不同。所有这些复杂性都会发挥作用，我们确实需要考虑到这一点，因为我们每个人都希望尽自己最大的努力，并能够在我们工作的组织内实现我们的目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>; ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;2023 年领导者的理想形象是什么？您认为最重要的技能或经验是什么？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;《哈佛商业评论》的你们已经发布了这方面的头条新闻，并且有这是一种非常常见的鼓点，并且已经流行了一段时间，这说明了软技能和人际交往能力的重要性。我们已经讨论这个问题很长时间了。这场流行病加速了这一点，实际上也加速了当今领导的所有复杂性，因为最终我们深刻地看到的是组织面临的问题，它们是大问题。它们是适应性问题。这意味着这些问题没有一个简单的解决方案，你需要调动每个人的精力、大脑和心灵来解决这些问题。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你真的必须能够让人们参与进来，让他们参与进来告诉你他们的想法，让他们在自己的舒适区之外工作，所有这一切都需要一套人际交往能力，而当今大多数成功并达到顶峰的管理者不一定具备这些技能，因为他们因交付而获得了奖励任何方式都会产生结果。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;交付结果仍然很重要。最终发生的事情是，当人们变得更高级并且开始看起来有前途时，他们会得到很多推动，也就是说，现在真的是时候考虑如何培养另一面了，这与你如何联系有关与人相处时，如何发挥他们最好的一面，如何创造一个心理安全的环境。所有这些都变得更加重要，不是因为拥有它有多好，而是因为我们组织中的学习要求变得如此之高。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/ p>; &lt;p>;根据您的研究，您认为许多领导者都具备这些技能还是很少有人具备这些技能？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我&#39;我们对此有几个不同的知识基础。其中之一是我所教的高管。他们都会说，“我很擅长承担责任和推动结果，但我有点事必躬亲，我的辅导技巧不太好。”这是我最常见的个人资料。您可能知道，我们与 Spencer Stuart 的几位同事一起研究了这个问题，并于去年发表了一篇文章，&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-leadership-odyssey&quot;>;“领导力奥德赛”&lt;/ a>; 在《哈佛商业评论》中，我们能够使用斯宾塞·斯图尔特 (Spencer Stuart) 的首席高管招聘数据。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们的框架方式是，继任流程中的大多数高管、候选人在当这涉及到这些人际交往能力。我们最终了解了他们如何认识到，如果他们不发展这些技能，这将真正阻碍他们想要实现的目标，以及他们如何实现这一目标。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想确保我们谈论的一个主题是网络。网络看似很简单，但我们很多人甚至很难开始建立有效且有意义的网络。您对如何做得更好有什么想法吗？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;快速广告：&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the -challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive&quot;>;《哈佛商业评论》昨天发表了一篇关于作为高管的网络挑战的全新文章&lt;/a>;。是什么让那些有自己的挑战的高级人士特别难以建立人际网络？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;无论如何，这个话题对我来说有着无尽的吸引力，Adi，因为我在 80 年代开始研究这个问题，当时我我正在做我的博士研究，从那以后就一直在关注它。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;标题是我们大多数人都不擅长。我们大多数人都不擅长。有些人非常好，但我们大多数人都很坏，你可以通过社会心理学来解释其中的大部分原因。很大一部分原因在于我们的构建方式，我们会自发地与与我们相似的人建立关系，并且我们经常会遇到他们，因为他们的办公室就在隔壁。&lt;/p>; &lt;p >;我总结的方式是机制相似和接近。这就是我们建立网络的原因。我们既自恋又懒惰。我们喜欢像我们这样的人。与他们交谈更容易，而且由于我们没有太多时间，我们将去认识那些容易认识的人，因为他们就在隔壁。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这意味着我们的网络是孤立的。他们不好。他们不帮助我们找到新工作。它们并不能帮助我们晋升到更大的角色。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我们必须为此努力，但为此努力也确实令人厌恶，而您已经发表了一些关于其运作方式的出色研究。当我们以更具战略性的方式建立关系时，利用他人会让我们感觉有点肮脏、有点不诚实、有点功利。它妨碍了我们的精英意识。它妨碍了我们的自力更生意识，但从我的研究中我们知道，许多其他人对于找到工作、改变职业以及作为领导者在你已经担任的角色上发挥高效和创新至关重要。 &lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;关于如何建立一个与你旁边隔间里的人无关的网络，有什么建议吗？&lt;/p>; &lt; p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;这些技巧都非常简单。努力、加入项目、参加课程、参加课外活动、进行推荐、与人联系、在活动中发言。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;不要同时做所有这些，而是​​选择一些东西。问题是我们没有腾出时间，因为就像你的例子一样，你在等待东西来找你。这些都是你需要采取主动的事情，但这很容易。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;一个很好的方法就是选择一些你失去联系的人，与他们联系，给他们写信，比如，“嘿，我正在考虑这个问题。很高兴能与您联系并就此进行对话。这个怎么样？”很容易做到。只是我们不这样做。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;我想回到你谈到的一件事，那就是不断学习、不断学习适应。我认为我们中的很多人都接受过培训，以获得下一份工作，然后我们得到了它，我们带着过去的自己。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;你说我们需要不断发展，而且我认为这很有趣从这个意义上说，真实性是一个有弹性的概念。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;好吧，我们的角色是领导者、中层管理者等等。我们如何适应？我们如何进化？我们怎样才能不陷入从第一天起就养成的习惯呢？我们如何不断发展？&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA：&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;所有这一切都有一个生命周期。我要说的一件事是你刚刚开始了一个新角色。我不会担心重塑自己。你是因为你的身份而被聘用的。利用这一点并确保与利益相关者和其他一切建立联系，但你并不打算在这里重塑自己。您确实希望充分利用您为该职位带来的一切。&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;人们忘记的是，对您的期望变化很快，环境也变化很快。危险点实际上更像是一年、两年或三年，这取决于你的情况变化有多快，当你认为你已经解决了，但人们对你的期望提高了，或者环境已经改变了lot.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;What becomes really important here, the main thing I say to people is, think about how you&#39;re defining your job, where you&#39;re spending your time, what you&#39;re allocating time to, and can you think of it more as a portfolio in which some slivers of your time you&#39;re going to spend learning new things, exploring new things, getting involved in projects that give you a more strategic view of the organization, something adjacent to what you normally do, but something that really allows you to keep expanding the frontier as opposed to settling into a comfort zone that&#39;s going to make you much more vulnerable to the what-got-you-here-won&#39;t-get-you-there phenomenon.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Working your network, people get comfortable. There&#39;s a set of usual suspects that you keep turning to, no fresh blood, and you become very insular in your views.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;ADI IGNATIUS:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Herminia, we&#39;re out of time, but I want to really thank you for being on the show. It&#39;s great to see you again and great to connect.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;HERMINIA IBARRA:&lt;/strong>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Thank you so much, Adi.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:55:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How Black Police Officers Combat Systemic Racism at Work]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Aug23_25_73979724.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Darrin Klimek/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;If you&amp;#8217;re a member of an historically marginalized group, enacting change in an organization can be challenging. This is likely even more difficult if your organization is known for bias and even violence against your own group. This is the position many Black police officers are in, and researchers wanted to better understand the strategies they use to advocate for anti-racism despite the numerous roadblocks. This article looks at why Black police officers choose the job, how they challenge racism, and how they sustain their efforts. It also offers suggestions for employees in other fields can continue to fight for change in their own companies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-black-police-officers-combat-systemic-racism-at-work?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;The 2014 shooting death of Black teenager &lt;a href=&quot;https://rfkhumanrights.org/michael-brown-case-urges-justice-reform&quot;>;Michael Brown&lt;/a>; by a white police officer in Ferguson, Missouri, was an early event that propelled the Black Lives Matter movement to national prominence and elevated discussions of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/identities/2019/8/9/20798921/michael-brown-ferguson-uprising-police-violence-reform&quot;>;race and policing&lt;/a>; in the United States. In the summer of 2020, the murder of George Floyd sparked a racial reckoning &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2020/12/30/950053607/in-2020-protests-spread-across-the-globe-with-a-similar-message-black-lives-matt&quot;>;in the US and around the world&lt;/a>; that further magnified calls for police reform. Consequently, police departments around the country have begun to adopt anti-racist organizational policies, like offering &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/03/training-police-departments-to-be-less-biased&quot;>;diversity training&lt;/a>; and increasing recruitment of officers who are members of &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/04/simple-changes-to-job-ads-can-help-recruit-more-police-officers-of-color&quot;>;racial minority groups&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Unfortunately, relying solely on &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/06/are-your-organizations-dei-efforts-superficial-or-structural&quot;>;top-down strategies&lt;/a>; like these is not adequate to effectively combat systemic racism in policing. This is complicated by the fact that individuals from marginalized groups (for example, Black individuals or women) can &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1467-9221.2004.00402.x?casa_token=s9Iz78o8iXYAAAAA:8raiiLrqWip9SvhixeLcUgoMB_o2FMC6_qVx4GV_bFGYFPHKRGFtCqE7KzJsoudY6UFewQR_IGkPFUDC&quot;>;hold biases against members of their own group&lt;/a>; and may be socialized to &lt;a href=&quot;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1540-6210.2008.00905.x?casa_token=EfotWb6z5jEAAAAA:xC_ZxCBpnKSckZY2VRAEJc65udbL8AiZUeDAF9YjWKFdqIUf_LE1nGRsKHIOo8MjerFqJouVEk3Rlg&quot;>;reinforce systems of discrimination and inequity&lt;/a>; — a point which is particularly pertinent when considering the &lt;a href=&quot;https://abcnews.go.com/US/tyre-nichols-case-diversity-policing-address-police-brutality/story?id=96768457&quot;>;killing of Tyre Nichols&lt;/a>; that involved five Black officers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In light of this, our author team wanted to better understand the bottom-up strategies that officers may use to combat systemic racism. In particular, we were curious about the experiences of Black police officers who, instead of going with the status quo, actively seek to combat racism within policing. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2023-21994-001&quot;>;recent work&lt;/a>;, published in the Journal of Applied Psychology, aimed to deeply understand the anti-racism efforts of Black law enforcement officers who chose to be champions of reform within an institution that has a reputation for &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12111-013-9246-5&quot;>;perpetuating racism against Black communities&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Our research draws on insights gleaned from 48 interviews with Black police officers who are at the fore of anti-racism. We learned why they joined &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/11/why-so-many-organizations-stay-white&quot;>;law enforcement&lt;/a>;, how they challenged racism as police officers, and how they sustained their anti-racism efforts in the face of continuous racial discrimination both within their organizations and society writ large. Based on our findings, we also outline guidelines for employees in other industries who are motivated to engage in such social change efforts. Although not reflective of the experiences or actions of all Black police officers, our study shows how their anti-racism efforts can foster lasting change for both police organizations and Black communities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Why do Black police officers join law enforcement?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When organizations or occupations are known for being an unwelcome — often dangerous — place to work for members of a marginalized group, it follows that members of these groups would attempt to avoid experiences of racism by choosing not to work in that organization or occupation. Yet, the officers in our study intentionally chose to join and fight racism within exactly these types of environments — why?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Officers explained that they chose to challenge racism from within policing because it is one of the most prominent societal institutions that continues to perpetuate race-based discrimination against Black individuals. Indeed, numerous officers in our study explained a direct connection between their first- or secondhand experiences of racism from police and their choice to enter law enforcement. As Chief Williams explained, “I made the decision to become a police officer because I was a victim of police brutality when I was 14 … [I told myself], &#39;I&#39;m going to try and stop those kinds of things from happening to anyone, regardless of who they were&#39; … I knew I had to do something to make a difference.” (All names of participants have been changed to protect their identities.)&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As this example shows, the direct or indirect encounters with racism in policing that would presumably deter Black individuals from joining police organizations actually motivated many of our participants to enter law enforcement, with the goal of driving change.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do Black police officers challenge racism?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Fueled by the motivation to combat racism in policing from the inside out, officers leveraged their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cpr.org/2020/10/02/black-and-latino-officers-bring-their-own-experiences-with-racism-to-the-job/&quot;>;unique position&lt;/a>; as members in both law enforcement and the Black community, simultaneously working to reduce racism in policing &lt;em>;and&lt;/em>; remediate the effects of racism in the Black community. This dual approach enabled officers in our study to more holistically combat racism by tackling multiple facets of the system.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Three combinations of organizational and community focused anti-racism strategies emerged in our data as especially impactful in policing.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Educating within and across police organizations and communities.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;First, we found that many Black officers believed racism in law enforcement could be attributed to white officers&#39; lack of knowledge about the Black community. As such, several officers in our study attempted to remedy this knowledge gap by sharing the cultural values and norms of Black communities with their white colleagues.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At times, these efforts were reactive — in response to racist incidents they witnessed or experienced themselves. For example, Sergeant Scott recalled witnessing a white colleague become defensive after misinterpreting the mannerisms of a Black community member as aggression. This was the impetus to educate his colleague about communication norms in the community and positively reshaped how the white colleague interacted with Black community members thereafter. Sergeant Scott explained, “Today if you talk to the Black families that he deals with, they love him. He&#39;s very empathetic … [The white officer told me] &#39;I wasn&#39;t always like this. I didn&#39;t understand. It took somebody else to explain it to me for me to understand.&#39;”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At other times, efforts to educate white colleagues were proactive. For example, Lieutenant Allen initiated changes to the police academy curriculum, explaining, “I&#39;ve taken out 40 hours of things that were not necessary and added 40 hours of cultural diversity training … [because] we need to figure out how to communicate and connect with people that are different from us.” These examples speak to the importance of educating colleagues in police organizations — both proactively and reactively — about the Black community.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition to educating white officers, participants in our study described how important it was to demystify law enforcement by sharing strategies and principles that underlie law enforcement policies and decisions with community members. Senior Police Officer Richardson made himself available to community members as a resource because “a lot of the people in the community do not know the laws [such as] traffic laws [or] penal codes.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Promoting and demonstrating respect for Black community members.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Across nearly every interview, officers emphasized the importance of promoting respect for Black individuals within law enforcement and in the Black community. For example, participants frequently described encountering racism in their day-to-day work. In these instances, holding white officers accountable for their racist behavior was critical. Officer Edwards overheard white officers disparaging the lifestyles of Black community members and reported it to his supervisor, saying, “I went to the lieutenant, my lieutenant went to their lieutenant. I brought it up like, &#39;They&#39;re over there talking about Black people,&#39;” and consequently, the group of white officers was reprimanded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Regarding their interactions with Black community members, law enforcement officers in our study took extra care to demonstrate &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/07/do-your-employees-feel-respected&quot;>;respect&lt;/a>; through behaviors they viewed as humanizing and dignifying. They shared examples of showing the respect that they felt was owed to each community member. As Officer Miller said, “I feel like I can be nice and still arrest you … I don&#39;t have to be mean or treat you as less than a person to enforce the law.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Uplifting Black individuals in the police organization and the community.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Finally, the officers we spoke with often described how one of the most powerful and rewarding strategies to combat racism in their workplace was to support Black individuals at work — via recruiting, promoting, and mentoring other Black officers — and in the community by going above and beyond for Black community members.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, Officer Baker recognized that her Black junior colleagues were likely experiencing challenges during the George Floyd protests, such as being suddenly ostracized by white officers, that were unique to being a Black officer. She intentionally reached out to mentor them, saying, “I was able to be supportive … let them know that there is nothing wrong with them and that how they&#39;re being treated by our white partners … has nothing to do with us Black officers.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Within the Black community, officers often reported also going above and beyond in their service to support the community members. Officer Pierce told us that he stops to help citizens with flat tires whenever he can because this shapes community members&#39; perceptions of police: “Now that woman has a totally different attitude about police officers … she didn&#39;t really like police officers in light of everything that&#39;s been going on. I threw off her game because she wanted to hate us.” These efforts not only helped Black community members have a greater sense of trust in law enforcement, but also created a sense of reciprocity wherein these community members were willing to help officers do their jobs more effectively by, for example, sharing information that could help solve an investigation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In all, these efforts were especially effective in officers&#39; eyes because they performed two simultaneous and necessary functions: They moved toward fostering police officers&#39; respect for Black community members and toward repairing the Black community&#39;s trust in law enforcement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;How do Black police officers sustain their anti-racism efforts?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Unsurprisingly, Black officers encountered significant roadblocks and backlash for their efforts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, by virtue of entering an organization that has a history of perpetuating racism, Black officers were likely to suffer through the negative consequences of racism while also working to combat it. Officers reported racial slurs from colleagues, getting left on the side of the road in dangerous weather by white officers, and being informally prohibited from sitting with the white officers at mealtimes.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, officers described that by entering law enforcement, they experienced stigma from Black individuals given the institution&#39;s reputation for being deeply devastating to the Black community. For example, officers remembered being called a “traitor” or a “sellout” by Black community members because of their profession.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, officers experienced retaliation for their anti-racism efforts in both overt and subtle forms such as explicit acts of bullying — like having tires slashed — or career advancement opportunities that were inexplicably delayed. These challenges tended to be particularly pronounced in the wake of police-related &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/supporting-employees-after-violence-against-their-community&quot;>;mega-threats&lt;/a>; (negative events that are both related to an identity and command significant media attention, like the murder of George Floyd) that brought police brutality toward Black community members to the forefront of national attention.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The combination of being rejected at work &lt;em>;and &lt;/em>;in the community was extremely troubling, with officers experiencing significant stress, isolation, and even suicidal thoughts. In fact, many endured periods of time when they seriously considered quitting. This raises the question: How did these employees persevere and continue combatting racism in law enforcement?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There were two key factors. The first, counterintuitively, was the very racism that was causing the stress. Officers explained how these experiences highlighted that their efforts were very much still needed. As Detective Coates explained, “I know that I&#39;m needed … I know that I can&#39;t change a lot of these people&#39;s minds, but I can change [some] through my actions.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The second factor was seeing glimpses of evidence that their anti-racism efforts were making a positive impact. For instance, Officer Pierce successfully advocated to recruit new officers from Historical Black Colleges and Universities (HBCUs); Chief Davis described receiving an apology email from a white officer who had said something offensive to him in the past; and Lieutenant Allen wrote an open letter to a racist officer and shared it within his department, causing the officer to resign. As Senior Police Officer King noted, “I stay motivated and encouraged seeing change being made for the better. I&#39;ll stay motivated and encouraged knowing the fact that a simple thank you, a simple gesture, a simple conversation is changing someone&#39;s life for the better.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Beyond the changes taking place in law enforcement, the officers also described instances of positive change in their communities. Senior Corporal Adams bought lunch for a Black citizen who was nervous interacting with a police officer, explaining, “It totally took his guard down … He was talking about fishing and hunting and all that stuff after that.” Detective Coates shared how citizens would share tips and information when they trusted that the information would be dealt with fairly. In a particularly poignant example, one officer responded to a call for a young Black woman experiencing a mental health crisis, and after he and his partner stayed in touch with her, she eventually invited them to her high school graduation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For these officers, combating racism drove their entry into law enforcement, shaped their choices each day, and led to glimpses of transformation that provided them with a better understanding of their impact — this played a critical role in sustaining the anti-racism motivation needed to continue this work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;What can we learn from Black police officers?&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Policing is, of course, different from other work settings in many ways, and not every experience or lesson will transfer. Yet, we believe that some of the strategies that motivate Black officers to engage in and sustain anti-racism efforts within policing can help other historically underrepresented employees and their allies fight for change in their own organizations. Although it is incumbent on organizations to address racism and other systemic issues at the policy level, we see three key ways that their strategies can be especially useful to those aiming to drive change in other work settings.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Clarify your “why.”&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The officers in our study had a clear purpose, which not only guided their choice of policing as an occupation, but sparked motivation during challenging periods. This clarity of purpose is likely to be similarly powerful across occupations for those passionate about driving social change, meaning that a sharp focus on such motivation — “Why is this meaningful to me personally? Why is this important for society more broadly?” — is a worthwhile starting point and a critical touchpoint as the work continues.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Leverage your unique set of identities.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Our research participants recognized how being both Black and a police officer uniquely positioned them to drive change in ways that others could not. Though at times contentious, their simultaneous membership in the Black community and the police organization prompted others&#39; receptivity to their actions. Having a footing in each of these worlds also enabled officers to address the problematic behavior and support those most impacted by it. Carefully considering one&#39;s unique position and access to stakeholders may similarly unlock effectiveness in other occupations.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Anticipate setbacks and celebrate progress.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It was clear to officers that there are significant roadblocks to enacting change. They described sustaining their anti-racism by having a plan in place to navigate roadblocks, reframing mega-threats as indications that their work is greatly needed, and celebrating glimpses of the changes they were aiming to create. Anticipating the backlash and envisioning what small steps toward success will look like may similarly enable those driving for social change in any occupation to sustain engagement in the face of challenges and setbacks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In recalling his efforts to educate colleagues about the Black community, Deputy Chief Taylor described the moments that sustained his anti-racism motivation: “When you see the light go on, it&#39;s a wonderful thing because now it opens up [white officers&#39;] eyes to a whole other world out there that they didn&#39;t think previously existed.” The anti-racism strategies and challenges that emerged in our research highlight the day-to-day, often unrecognized anti-racism work that employees like Deputy Chief Taylor shoulder above and beyond the demands of their formal work roles. Importantly, our research shows that employees do not need to have discretion over policies or be in a formal leadership role to combat racism; they can make an impact through their anti-racist actions each day at work.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Smaller Companies Must Embrace Risk Management]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_08_125412697.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Caroline Purser/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;SMEs do not have the same regulatory pressures that can lead larger companies to measure and mitigate their risks, but they also have fewer buffer resources to resist unexpected shocks. They are one large potential incident away from bankruptcy. That&amp;#8217;s why SMEs can benefit from taking three actions: designing controls proportionate to the risks at stake, analyzing the lessons from success (not only from failures), and using risk management to boost and protect business performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/smaller-companies-must-embrace-risk-management?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;There&#39;s an unfortunate stereotype that risk management is boring. Risk managers are pessimistic clerks. Compliance officers are scaremongers. Too many managers think this way. As a result, risk management is an unloved and misunderstood discipline. Until disaster strikes, risk management is, for most, a painstaking and costly chore.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In an increasingly volatile world, however, risk management has never been so important. Nonetheless, risk managers struggle to make their voice heard in the face of more immediate and commercial pressures. This is especially true in small- and medium-sized companies — organizations with entrepreneurial cultures, fewer regulatory demands, and more resource constraints. These businesses tend to view risk management as an expensive luxury — and they may be more exposed to risks as a result.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This article presents a more enlightened approach to risk management based on two decades of applying, researching, and teaching risk management to academic and professional audiences. It will help managers — including those at SMEs — to better understand risks and apply effective, positive risk management techniques. It&#39;s a framework that relies on three actions: designing controls proportionate to the risks at stake, analyzing the lessons from success (not only from failures), and using risk management to boost and protect business performance.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management is proportionate &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Proportionality means that small risks require small fuss; big risks demand big focus. Daily risks are acceptable, such as: forgetting an email attachment, double paying a modest invoice, missing a deadline on an internal report. Errors and slips like these simply show how busy we are. They are understandable oversights in fast-moving enterprises, especially SMEs where teams are lean and resources scarce.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;Conversely, extreme risks deserve greater care: a phishing link starting a cyber-attack, the loss of key intellectual property in an innovative start-up, a bacterial infection in the water supply of a care home. Neglecting real dangers costs millions, heartaches, and lives — and that&#39;s when we regret not being more vigilant, more careful, more &lt;em>;boring&lt;/em>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Yet, organizations often miscalculate risks. Smaller incidents are the most frequent; they raise attention but do not matter. From a &lt;a href=&quot;https://orx.org/download/annual-operational-risk-loss-reports-2022&quot;>;sample&lt;/a>; of 500,000 operational losses in banks over the years, data show that incidents from the smallest size category are the most frequent (61%) but the least damaging overall (6% of the total loss severity). The real damage comes from largest, rarest incidents: each year, the top 0.3% of incidents cause on average 63% of the total losses. Despite this imbalance, risk managers and businesses dedicate more time and attention to the small issues, rather than preventing serious damage.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Risk management is costly when over-applied. For example, excessive cyber protections slow down computers and logins, and double checks of every single payment and transactions wastes time that could be better used for creative activities. Credibility comes from restraint. Risk managers are respected when they show pragmatism in their calls for prudence. Competent risk managers prepare for severe and plausible scenarios while tolerating limited mishaps.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Proportionate risk management reduces the inefficiencies arising from either too much control or too little control. Being too cautious leads to slowness, rigidities, and opportunity costs. Carelessness causes accidents, instability, and remediation costs. Non-financial risks have a risk-return trade-off &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.semanticscholar.org/paper/Measuring-and-Managing-Operational-Risk-in-the-An-Chapelle-Crama/5920d87080830026d615a39cb9e63ba143fe5ef4&quot;>;like their financial equivalents&lt;/a>;. Saving costs by lifting some operational controls to increase productivity is a reward for operational risks. Effective risk managers and astute business leaders have a clear view of how much risk they are prepared to accept, and for which benefits. The concept is widely referred to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bis.org/review/r151023i.htm&quot;>;risk appetite&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management celebrates success &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;It is a good risk management practice to dissect the root causes of accidents, especially those with the largest potential damage. However, when focusing on past losses and future mistakes only, risk managers fail to recognize and reinforce the causes of success. Looking back to the causes of failures is valuable, but it can create resistance through implied criticism.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, a senior risk officer of a clearing house in London stormed out of a workshop when some of the causes of the loss discussed were identified as a consequence of his management style. He vetoed further exercises and was let go six months later, for other reasons. The firm in question has now closed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Reflecting on success stories is inspiring. “&lt;em>;Why did we win?”&lt;/em>; creates more enthusiasm for analysis than “&lt;em>;Why did we lose?&lt;/em>;” Dissecting past achievements is encouraging and insightful. Successes are there, but often overlooked: on Monday morning, no one notices the IT migration that ran smoothly over the weekend, nor praises the absence of customer complaints, thanks to the efficient performance of staff. The &lt;em>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psycnet.apa.org/record/1998-12834-004&quot;>;negativity bias&lt;/a>;&lt;/em>; of the human brain means that negative experiences imprint on our memory more quickly and last longer than positive ones. Deliberate reflection on past victories is a welcome counterbalance to the common risk management focus on what went wrong.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are accepted rules for effective risk management: vigilance is key, and rapid intervention reduces impact. “&lt;em>;If you see something, say something&lt;/em>;” is the New York City Subway&#39;s motto to prevent terrorist attacks. “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btp.police.uk/police-forces/british-transport-police/areas/campaigns/see-it-say-it-sorted/&quot;>;&lt;em>;See it, say it, sorted&lt;/em>;&lt;/a>;” is the equivalent for the London Underground.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For SMEs, discipline and vigilance are also essential for success. Start-ups need more than great ideas to thrive; they depend on the relentless attention of their founders, who must continually monitor performance and be alert on what could go wrong. The international expansion of a nascent brand requires rigorous planning, market knowledge, thorough due diligence, and competent managers who can fix a myriad of potential issues before they turn into disasters. Such as in personal life, the early detection of a theft, a fire, or an illness can make all the difference between a fright and a tragedy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Praising good risk management practices reinforces winning behaviors and avoids undue criticism, and positive risk managers become mentors, not doomsayers. Welcome and accepted, risk management becomes an ingredient of achievement.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Positive risk management protects performance &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Managing risks is inseparable from managing performance. Positive risk management aims to capture the upside of uncertainty, and to prevent the downside as much as possible.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Dream big, risk big: taking risks is necessary, even desirable. But it takes method. Stunt actors are great risk managers, otherwise they would not survive their first movie. Entrepreneurs must balance dare with caution, or they are destined to fail. Firms and governments must watch and respond to threats, or they will create havoc for themselves and others, as we have witnessed too many times. When risk management fails, organizations go down. The Great Financial Crisis, Covid-19, or the recent collapse of Silicon Valley Bank all find their source in the failure of risk management.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Risk management is a condition for ambition: the more ambitious the objective, the more important risk management is to achieve it. Hotels and resorts require flawless processes for a satisfactory customer experience; fintech banks must be first-class cybersecurity experts to operate; healthcare providers need impeccable patient safety procedures to survive.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Particularly for smaller firms, growth comes with risks, and fast-growing start-ups generate operational risks faster than revenues, as complexity increases more rapidly than size. Only those with sound risk management systems will become the Google, Amazon, Disney, or McDonald&#39;s of tomorrow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With the growing focus on climate change, financial regulators and investors such a BlackRock &lt;a href=&quot;tcfd:%20https://www.fsb-tcfd.org&quot;>;expect&lt;/a>; organizations to understand, assess and communicate their exposure to climate-related risks. However, what is now required for climate-related risks is valid for all types of business exposures: to protect its business model and performance, managers need to oversee all the relevant changes to their operating environment. For instance, blockchain innovations and cryptocurrencies are most relevant to payment platform providers, while the mining conditions of cobalt and the availability of rare earth elements are essential to monitor for lithium-ion battery producers. Generative AI scares many, but used wisely (with proper risk management), this tool can be a fantastic productivity booster to be embraced rather than fought.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Conclusion&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;SMEs do not have the same regulatory pressures that can lead larger companies to measure and mitigate their risks, but they also have fewer buffer resources to resist unexpected shocks. They are one large potential incident away from bankruptcy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;By being positive about risk management, professionals can bring an inspiring narrative to their discipline, recognizing the value of taking risks and the necessity of protecting performance. A constructive dialogue between optimists and pessimists, between those who dare and those who prefer caution, powerful engine for business growth without booms and busts. In the pursuit of success and happiness, we need to decide what we can gamble on, and what we cannot afford to lose.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[4 Skills the Next Generation of Data Scientists Needs to Develop]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sept23_08_1298126402.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Westend61/Getty Images; Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;As reliance on data and analytics continues to expand across industries from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source=prnewswire&amp;#38;utm_medium=referral&amp;#38;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;agriculture&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/&quot;>;manufacturing&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed-data-network-partnerships&quot;>;health care&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial-services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot;>;financial services&lt;/a>;, it stands to reason that the next generation of data leaders will have far-reaching roles that impact strategy, decision-making, operations, and countless other functions.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/4-skills-the-next-generation-of-data-scientists-needs-to-develop?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Once a year, I teach a course to aspiring data scientists. At the beginning of the first class, I ask my students what they hope to learn. Often, their answers are “analyze data” or “build good models.” Compare those responses to the workshops I run with practicing data scientists who speak in different terms when discussing what they do. They call it “solving problems” — a step in the right direction — but even that is too narrow.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As reliance on data and analytics continues to expand across industries from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/agriculture-analytics-market-255757945.html?utm_source=prnewswire&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=paidpr&quot;>;agriculture&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/09/manufacturing-data-advanced-analytics/&quot;>;manufacturing&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://healthitanalytics.com/news/mayo-clinic-platform-expands-distributed-data-network-partnerships&quot;>;health care&lt;/a>; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/risk-and-resilience/our-insights/scaling-analytics-across-financial-services-understanding-the-value-of-model-life-cycle-transformations&quot;>;financial services&lt;/a>;, it stands to reason that the next generation of data leaders will have far-reaching roles that impact strategy, decision-making, operations, and countless other functions. To help prepare this new talent, I have developed a framework composed of four key areas of skills and capabilities that will help current and future data scientists hone their abilities to add maximum value to a business. This is done by ensuring that data science work is seen as important and indispensable by their business-function counterparts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Using this framework, and with greater understanding of what each area of business entails, today&#39;s data scientists and those entering this field can see how their knowledge and experiences stack up — and where they need more development.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;1. Problem Spotting: Seeing the real issue&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;As they delve into analytics across the business, data leaders have a front row seat to nearly every operation and function. This provides them with a unique vantage point for both solving problems and identifying new ones. Here&#39;s a real-world example. The head of guest relations for a mid-range hotel chain was getting flak from upper management for low ratings on their check-in process. Surveys revealed that guests thought check-in was poorly managed, took too long, and didn&#39;t provide the results they wanted — specifically, a seamless and pleasurable experience. Management also found that people who rated check-in poorly had a lower rate of returning to the hotel.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The guest relations department reached out to the data analytics team to figure out the root of the check-in problem. Even when they looked at customer demographics, the kinds of rooms they wanted, and whether they checked in at the front desk, at a kiosk, or on their phone — plus time of day, time of year, and whether customers were in the loyalty program — the data team couldn&#39;t put their finger on the underlying cause.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Then an employee suggested they look at customer surveys that had been collected on a rolling basis. Some natural language text analytics teased out some themes — namely, the hotel infrastructure was not optimal. Guests would have problems with the Wi-Fi, room keys occasionally wouldn&#39;t work, furniture was broken, or rooms weren&#39;t clean when they arrived. These problems were not directly related to check-in, but guests attributed them to the check-in process because that&#39;s what they remembered. Bottom line — the problem was with how the hotel was being managed, not the check-in process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Solving the problem that is in front of you can mean missing out on opportunities to help the business improve in other ways. Those who work with data often have access to deep, unique insights into numerous aspects of the business. To become adept at problem-spotting, data leaders need to embrace that big-picture view and gain deeper insights, with greater transparency around what matters most to business leaders. In this way, data leaders can add value by identifying problems that otherwise escape notice.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;2. Problem Scoping: Gaining clarity and specificity&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once a problem has been spotted, the next step is determining its scope — that is, gaining clarity into the nature of the problem and how analytics can help solve it. This is especially important if a business leader has approached the data team with a vague concern or challenge.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In my classes and my workshops, we practice scoping with an exercise. I assume the role of a product or strategy or marketing leader with a well-defined problem in my head. For instance, perhaps I manage customers, and want to be able to identify which customers are at risk of giving low net promoter score (NPS) ratings so that we can intervene and improve their experience. Any reasonable data scientist would know how to select the right data and data science techniques to solve this problem. But business leaders rarely speak like this. And so I scope the problem using exaggerated jargon and overly general terms. It goes something like this: “We&#39;re struggling to hit our customer sat targets — we need to zero in on our go-to-market strategies. It could be a pipeline issue, but we just don&#39;t have alignment. I think we&#39;re playing in the right sandboxes, now we just need to know the who and the why. Sound good?”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A student, in the role of the data scientist, practices asking clarifying questions — perhaps starting with, “What do you mean by &#39;alignment?&#39;” and “How are we measuring customer sat targets?” and “What measures indicate that we&#39;ve been successful (or not)?” What ensues is an iterative process of extracting information to help craft a well-defined problem that can be solved with data analytic tools and concepts.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In my Chief Analytics Officer work with clients, one of the most important (and challenging) parts of my job is to take what&#39;s in a business leader&#39;s head and turn it into a well-scoped business problem. I have a checklist of probing questions that I ask, such as:&lt;/p>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li>;What, precisely, is the problem we&#39;re trying to solve?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What outcomes, if improved, would indicate that the problem has actually been solved?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;What data would ideally be available to solve the problem, and what data are actually available?&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;How will the analysis lead to a solution?&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;p>;Answering the last question is arguably the most important part, as it will determine the appropriate analytic technique — eg, some simple insights or a more formal predictive or causal inference model. Here, I run through many “what-if” scenarios with the business team; for example, “What if the results show this, or that? How will that help you make a better decision?” Often, business leaders try to push this question off, suggesting we can consider actions once analytic results are available. That&#39;s a mistake — knowing how the analysis will translate into a solution is a key part of formulating the analytic plan.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;To excel at problem-scoping, data leaders need good communication skills to talk through the problem with the business leader to arrive at the requisite specificity that will enable data analytics tools and concepts to meaningfully contribute to the business. Only then can the problem be turned over to the data team for analysis.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;3. Problem Shepherding: Getting updates, gathering feedback&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once the problem is identified and scoped out, many data analysts go into isolation and only emerge when they have found a solution. This approach is highly problematic. To be most effective, the process requires a great deal of information sharing and setting of expectations — or what I call problem shepherding.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For data leaders, this means empowering their team to get more comfortable with providing &lt;em>;preliminary&lt;/em>; results to the business team. Each exchange then becomes an opportunity to gather feedback. For example, “Are these initial results of interest to the business team?” and “Are we defining terms correctly?” From one update to the next, the results come together with sequential updates until the project is concluded.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This approach runs counter to how some data scientists prefer to work. Sometimes they get enamored with their models and their creative problem-solving techniques, and they can&#39;t wait for the big reveal. But “big reveals” are a bad practice — in danger of backfiring. Too much surprise in a final presentation can put the audience on the defensive. The reason? Surprising results often prompt people to start questioning the underlying data and methods.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Every data model requires assumptions (eg, what to do with missing data, how to treat outliers, etc.). If data teams actively working on analyses don&#39;t disclose and discuss their assumptions ahead of time — and, instead, wait until the end — the business team is going to pile on the questions and nitpick the weaknesses. However, by bringing the business team into decision-making along the way, they will buy into the results and commit their trust.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many business leaders have shared with me that the best final data deliverables are those in which there are no surprises. They&#39;ve been working closely with the data team all along, and the final deliverable or presentation is simply a culmination of their work to date. This is how problem-shepherding gets buy-in through collaboration, exposing the difficult choices that data scientists need to make.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Problem-shepherding sets up a process of providing regular updates and gathering feedback from the business team. Data scientists and team leaders who are strong in this area are able to encourage and facilitate candid discussions that ensure the final deliverable hits the mark with the business team — with no surprises.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;4. Solution Translating: Speaking in the language of the audience&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;At this point, we transition from problem to solution, the success of which depends on how well data leaders and their teams have executed on the first three steps. More than determining a final answer, the data team must also deliver a solution that&#39;s understandable and, therefore, actionable.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This isn&#39;t just about putting the data in a chart or another visual display. Rather, the solution — whether data insights or a new course of action recommended by the model — must be conveyed in language the business team can understand. One tool I&#39;ve recommended is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-go-from-awful-awesome-presenting-data-analytics-joel-shapiro/&quot;>;two-page data analytics memo&lt;/a>;, which highlights the most important elements of the problem to be solved. While two pages may seem highly condensed, especially compared to the hefty reports that data teams often generate, brevity is the power behind this secret weapon.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The two-page limit can avoid the temptation to go on and on about details of the data analysis and encourage focus on the recommendations being made and the evidence for them. I&#39;m certainly not alone in advocating for shorter memos. Amazon founder Jeff Bezos required executives to present their ideas in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/04/23/what-jeff-bezos-learned-from-requiring-6-page-memos-at-amazon.html&quot;>;six-page memos&lt;/a>; (versus a PowerPoint presentation) that could be easily digested and discussed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;strong>;The Takeaway: &lt;/strong>;Solution translation requires data leaders to step back and consider how to make the most impact with their analyses and recommendations. By using simple language, while not compromising the complexity, data leaders who excel in this area can deliver the equivalent of an elevator speech to engage business leaders with compelling and understandable solutions.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As data and analytics become increasingly embedded in business decision-making and solutions, data teams must move well beyond merely solving the problems they&#39;ve been assigned. Data leaders and their teams must focus instead on the terms “collaboration and communication.” This means becoming more adept at broader roles that help them spot the real problem, scope out its nature and importance, shepherd the process with periodic updates, and deliver and translate solutions that will truly make an impact.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Inside PepsiCo&rsquo;s Effort to Reach Net Zero Emissions]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1316393475.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Andriy Onufriyenko/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;For corporations like PepsiCo, most greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions originate in the supply chain, which is challenging to manage. PepsiCo believes three elements &amp;#8212; expectations, economics, and enablement &amp;#8212; are essential for effective supply-chain engagement and action. Clear expectations guide supplier partners, while understanding the economic realities aids in creating profitable GHG reductions. Lastly, enabling suppliers through support and resources can facilitate a smoother transition towards shared net-zero goals. PepsiCo&amp;#8217;s plan reflects these principles, forging a path toward a sustainable and resilient future.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/inside-pepsicos-effort-to-reach-net-zero-emissions?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Setting a net-zero goal is just the start of a climate strategy. The pressure is now on to deliver substantive progress. For many companies, the vast bulk of greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions lie outside the walls of their businesses in their supply chain – called “Scope 3” emissions. Having visibility to, quantifying, and ultimately managing these emissions is difficult. While these impacts lie outside of a company&#39;s direct control, stakeholder expectations, reporting frameworks and business demands require large corporations to activate their partners and deliver progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The reward is high, if you can get it right. It&#39;s not just about delivering a reduced planetary impact but also building a value chain that enables our future growth and is resilient in the face of climate change. The global climate crisis was the catalyst to launch our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pepsico.com/who-we-are/our-commitments/pepsico-positive&quot;>;PepsiCo Positive (pep+) &lt;/a>;transformation and set a goal to become net zero by 2040. Since then, PepsiCo has taken supply-chain relationships to new levels of collaboration and built a range of strategies designed to bring supplier partners along on our journey.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fundamentally, PepsiCo&#39;s business is rooted in agriculture. Climate change will affect crops, and it will impact farmers and the yields they can deliver. We must have a clear strategy for the business to both manage our impact on the climate and make our company more resilient and competitive going forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Internally, we are constantly working to embed net-zero thinking into our teams. For example, PepsiCo incentivizes progress by making Scope 1 and 2 emissions reductions part of the compensation review process for the top 200 executives at the company, and we are working toward being able to more accurately quantify Scope 3 emissions so that we can include that metric in the future as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;article-promo>; &lt;hbr-component type=&quot;promo&quot; is-insight=&quot;insight-center&quot; title=&quot;The New Age of Operations&quot; dek=&quot;Improving efficiency and increasing resilience.&quot; cta-text=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/insight-center/the-new-age-of-operations&quot; style=&quot;color:black;text-decoration:none&quot;>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; Insight Center Collection &lt;/div>; &lt;h3>;The New Age of Operations&lt;/h3>; &lt;div>; Improving efficiency and increasing resilience. &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hbr-component>; &lt;/article-promo>; &lt;p>;In our value chain, with more than 100,000 suppliers of varying sizes and capabilities, a one-size-fits-all approach will not achieve the needed impact towards net zero.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are many approaches to take, and we have learned lessons along the way. But we believe there are three fundamental elements – expectations, economics and enablement – that you must get right in order to have successful supply-chain-partner engagement and, more importantly, supply-chain-partner action.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Expectations&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Setting clear and consistent expectations with supply-chain partners is the foundation for success. Companies must let suppliers know emissions reductions are important, particularly when it is something that will be measured over time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In our agricultural supply chain, for example, farmers have different levels of understanding around emissions. Some are aware of climate change and its impacts, while for others, it isn&#39;t even on their radar screens. As leaders, we must provide clear and consistent guidelines for our suppliers and other supply-chain partners, so they can understand their role in our journey now and into the future. We set out these expectations at our annual Global Supplier Summit and are asking our partners to take four specific, near-term actions:&lt;/p>; &lt;ol>; &lt;li>;Report Scope 1 &amp;amp; 2 emissions to us by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Set, or commit to setting, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sciencebasedtargets.org/how-it-works&quot;>;a science-based target (SBT)&lt;/a>; by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;Convert PepsiCo&#39;s portion of electrical load to renewable electricity, where available, by the end of 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;li>;For agricultural suppliers, collaborate with us to develop an action plan for sustainable ingredients and to build regenerative agriculture acres by the end 2023.&lt;/li>; &lt;/ol>; &lt;p>;Setting an SBT for emissions reductions provides a clear structure and framework. Tracking data across the value chain is vital to understanding the breadth and pace of progress.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This is a big shift for some of our suppliers&#39; operations. In some cases, this is not just about investment but also about making changes in the way they operate. More than ever, supplier relationships need to move from transactional to partnership. That&#39;s where companies can use their scale and knowledge to help suppliers&#39; transition – acting as partners and providing support along the way.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Economics&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When engaging supply-chain partners, companies often make the mistake of supporting them only with financial incentives (or disincentives). While economics are certainly critical, they come into play only after the foundation and expectations have been set.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One of the most powerful things to do is clarify for suppliers the economic realities and tradeoffs that come with GHG reductions. Decarbonization can be expensive, but the reality is it won&#39;t always cost more. Reducing inputs, such as water and fertilizer, minimizing plastic use, and investing in renewable energy can all save money. Companies can help their suppliers do the math and understand the concrete ways they can come out ahead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies must also consider how to better structure partnerships to lead toward a sustainable transition. Long-term agreements that incentivize and support sustainable transformation can be a great catalyst. PepsiCo signed a seven-and-a-half-year strategic commercial agreement with ADM to share costs and resources and closely collaborate on projects that aim to significantly expand regenerative agriculture by up to 2 million acres by 2030 across our shared North American supply chains. The length of the contract helps to instill confidence to invest in sustainable practices as well as achieving carbon reduction goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Enablement&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;When it comes to net zero, the challenges are too complex and interconnected to leave implementation up to chance. As partners, we have offered guidance to help enable our suppliers as they navigate the interplay of strategies so that they can more easily make progress against our shared goals.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;For example, we&#39;ve created programs to guide on setting SBTs and have provided resources that outline different options for emissions reductions, particularly in moving to renewable electricity, as this can vary based on each supplier&#39;s situation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Companies, like PepsiCo, can also help solve sustainability challenges by using their scale and networks to invest in, and scale-up, promising start-ups and leverage relationships with some of the largest companies in the world.&amp;nbsp; In doing so, making them more cost-efficient and accessible to our partners. For agriculture technologies, we are doing trials of promising solutions on demonstration farms around the world and investing in suppliers that we believe can make a real impact. For farmers, proven approaches are key to achieving buy-in and implementing solutions quickly and effectively. Through our pep+ REnew program, we are also working towards helping our supply-chain partners with aggregated buys of renewable energy to create scale and cost efficiencies that individual suppliers cannot achieve on their own.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Creating a sustainable value chain is difficult, but with the right approach, it is a powerful means to meet sustainability goals, create a more resilient organization and fuel improved business performance. At PepsiCo, that&#39;s our end game, and the three fundamental elements – expectations, economics and enablement – will set us, as well as our supply chain partners, on the path to truly sustainable growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop Overworking After Vacation]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_07_1438950079.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;master1305/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;After a vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for &amp;#8220;lost&amp;#8221; time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&amp;#8217;re still valuable to the organization. Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? The authors offer several strategies.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/stop-overworking-after-vacation?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;As summer winds down and many of our coaching clients and research participants are returning from vacation, we&#39;re seeing increased levels of return-to-work anxiety. As one client, “Leslie,” put it:&lt;/p>; &lt;blockquote>; &lt;p>;Coming back from vacation almost makes [it] seem not worth it. For me, it&#39;s like psychologically accelerating from a cruising pace of 30 mph to a speed of 80 so I can get through my inbox, catch up on all the meetings I missed, and reconnect with my neglected clients. And that&#39;s on top of the guilt I&#39;ve been feeling about overburdening my team while they&#39;ve been covering for me.&lt;/p>; &lt;/blockquote>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s easy to respond to these intense feelings like Leslie did, by throwing yourself into &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/08/why-we-glorify-overwork-and-refuse-to-rest&quot;>;overworking&lt;/a>;, overcompensating, and overachieving the minute you disable your out of office responder — especially in work cultures that don&#39;t exactly encourage time off in the first place.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;However, there&#39;s a healthier, more balanced approach that can help you ease back into your routine without losing all the stress-reducing and performance-enhancing benefits of unplugging from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Time Off Is Essential&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;First, let&#39;s be clear that taking periodic breaks in order to reset and recover from work stress (what researchers refer to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;work recovery&lt;/a>;) isn&#39;t a “nice to have” — it&#39;s essential for sustained performance and growth. Just as athletes engage in regular periods of rest and recovery in order to perform at their best and avoid injury, workers need periods of time away from their jobs to recuperate from the strain of work and replenish their physical and mental energy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualreviews.org/doi/pdf/10.1146/annurev-orgpsych-012420-091355&quot;>;Research&lt;/a>; shows that those who don&#39;t take the opportunity to rest, recharge, and recover are at higher risk of exhaustion, low motivation, poor performance, and burnout, while those who engage in regular periods of work recovery enjoy better sleep, higher job satisfaction, more engagement, and higher job performance. Human bodies and brains simply aren&#39;t built to endure chronic stress, and there&#39;s plenty of evidence showing how disconnecting from the strains and demands of work not only lowers stress, but increases &lt;a href=&quot;https://kops.uni-konstanz.de/server/api/core/bitstreams/63f6ae78-86f7-47fc-96b1-17654a0d2bf6/content&quot;>;productivity&lt;/a>; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8733151/&quot;>;boosts creativity&lt;/a>;. Even &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9432722/&quot;>;micro-breaks&lt;/a>; taken throughout the workday, such as stretching, doing some deep breathing exercises, or stepping outside for some fresh air, can halt the stress cycle and return you to baseline.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Despite the clear benefits of time away, however, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/social-trends/2023/03/30/how-americans-view-their-jobs&quot;>;nearly half&lt;/a>; of American workers don&#39;t take all the paid time off their employer offers. Chief among their reasons are worries that they&#39;ll fall behind, or that time off will hurt their chances for advancement or even increase their risk of losing their job, as well as guilt over coworkers having to take on additional work.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;These are sentiments we hear often, including from our senior executive clients, who frequently express a fear of losing momentum if they step away. Part of our role as executive coaches is empowering clients to invest in themselves and their performance with the practice of regular work recovery.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Resisting the Urge to Overwork After Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Post-vacation, it can be tempting to double down on work in an attempt to make up for “lost” time, or to try to hurry through the time it takes to get back up to speed. Other times, the urge to overwork stems from a well-meaning effort to relieve team members of the extra work they were covering for you, or a desire to demonstrate that even though you were away, your commitment remains high and you&#39;re still valuable to the organization.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Whatever the motivation behind post-vacation overwork, it can leave you boomeranging from one extreme to the other, which increases stress and actually undermines your efforts to catch up. So how can you retain all the benefits of work recovery and resist jumping right back into the grind? Here are some strategies that have worked for our research participants and clients:&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Shift to a performance mindset.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;High performance and sufficient recovery were never meant to function separately, yet in the corporate world, performance tends to be overemphasized while recovery is overlooked. Rather than treating time away as a last resort only &lt;em>;after&lt;/em>; you&#39;re depleted and unproductive, or as a special reward when your to-do list is finally done, take a cue from top athletes and include work recovery as &lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/how-to-recover-from-work-stress-according-to-science&quot;>;an essential component&lt;/a>; of a high-performance strategy. Work recovery works best when it&#39;s practiced regularly and consistently.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Prevent or ease “reentry shock.”&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;“Reentry shock” refers to the discombobulation you feel when you transition from a place of calm and equilibrium to one that pulls you into the frazzle and fray. You can prevent this by using buffers. Schedule a free day between your return from vacation and your return to work so you can mentally and physically prepare for the change in environment. Keep your calendar light just after your return, which will give you a chance to reacclimate and avoid overwork. For example, one of our clients has a two-day “no meetings” buffer after his return.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Bring some vacation magic home with you.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;What exactly was it during your period of recovery that helped you decompress and feel more like yourself? Was it exercise? Reconnecting with loved ones? An artistic pursuit or hobby that&#39;s neglected during the work week? Simply enjoying some unscheduled leisure time? As much as possible, build these activities and conditions into your normal weekly routine. Remember, even small doses of downtime make a difference.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Before saying yes to new requests when you return to work, consider what&#39;s getting in your way of saying no.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Are you concerned about not being recognized, rewarded, or promoted? If so, stop, breathe, and check your assumptions. It may be possible to get the recognition and rewards you&#39;re looking for without overcommitting yourself and sacrificing your health and well-being. If you can&#39;t identify the problem areas — or if you need help figuring out what to do about them — consider working with a coach.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Review, communicate, and maintain your boundaries.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Returning from a recovery period is a great time to review and refresh your work boundaries. Let everyone know when you will and will not be available for work, and if work demands begin to creep past your role or your comfort level, speak with leadership about shifting responsibilities, or see if you can delegate. Boundaries should help define others&#39; expectations of your role, and they should protect your downtime and allow you to mentally detach from work.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Leave a toxic work environment that discourages time away or that rewards employees for excessive hours and self-sacrifice.&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;This kind of unhealthy work environment will leave you ripe for exhaustion and burnout. If you can&#39;t leave right away, start creating an exit strategy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Preventing the Urge to Overwork Before Time Off&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Next time you&#39;re planning to take time off, try in advance to make things easier for future you. Weeks before you leave, arrange for who&#39;s covering your responsibilities during your absence, and include their contact information in your out-of-office message. Set clear expectations for when/if you should be contacted during vacation. Structure a reentry routine ahead of time so you can plug into an existing process and more easily get back into work mode. Finally, consider conducting a premortem before finalizing your plans. What specific challenges or failures&amp;nbsp;might you expect or imagine?&amp;nbsp;What were their main causes? What was not yet accounted for? And ultimately, what additional preventive steps can you take now? This simple but powerful process helps further refine your pre–time off planning, which can prevent most reentry problems.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Periodic time away from work is one of the best ways to ensure that you&#39;ll be able to sustain your energy and productivity. With some planning before your time away and some sensible guardrails after your return, you can bring all the stress-lowering benefits of work recovery back with you.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Accelerating Digital Integration in Africa]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_06_16aIvW0lxOk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff; Unsplash; A Mokhtari/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Regional integration, similar to the European Union&amp;#8217;s, has been cited as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration. Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate Africa&amp;#8217;s digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/accelerating-digital-integration-in-africa?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 2021, the combined &lt;a href=&quot;https://statisticstimes.com/economy/africa-gdp.php#:~:text=GDP%20of%20Africa&amp;amp;text=The%20African%20economy%2C%20comprising%2054,largest%20economy%20in%20the%20world.&quot;>;GDP of Africa&#39;s 54 countries&lt;/a>; was less than 15% of the United States&#39; GDP. The continent consists of many relatively small countries, economies, and markets, which is a disadvantage on the world stage, where countries with huge populations and GDPs wield the most influence.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Deeper economic integration in Africa offers a pathway to shared prosperity and increased global influence. Regional integration, similar to the European Union&#39;s, has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afdb.org/en/news-and-events/importance-of-regional-and-continental-integration-for-africas-development-18773&quot;>;been cited&lt;/a>; as a key to creating stability, growing economies, improving market efficiency, sharing the costs of large infrastructure projects, and addressing peace and security. And since the world is becoming more digital every day, digital integration is vital to successful regional integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In this context, “digital integration” refers to creating shared systems and standard rules for digitalization across Africa. It entails digital cooperation, particularly in finance, governance, and security. In practice, digital integration will feature concepts such as a harmonized digital financial system, consistent continent-wide laws for digital activities, and shared regulatory technology like identity verification, electronic taxation, and business registration systems. Among other things, digital integration will facilitate optimal trade, resulting in cost savings, better information flow for improved participation in global commerce, and greater market access, particularly for small businesses, which &lt;a href=&quot;https://unctad.org/edar2022&quot;>;dominate trade in Africa&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Private sector partnerships, building interoperable systems, and focusing on the infrastructure for power and the internet are three key ideas that could help accelerate this digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Private Sector Collaboration&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Many private African organizations have successfully established themselves across national boundaries, driven by profit-making ambitions and unrestricted by bureaucracy or politics. Despite inherent challenges, corporations like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/organizations/naspers-limited&quot;>;Naspers&lt;/a>;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtn.com/about/&quot;>;MTN Group&lt;/a>;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ecobank.com/group/about-us/history&quot;>;Ecobank&lt;/a>;, for example, have found ways to expand across national borders. They can serve as reference points and potential partners for the digital integration of Africa&#39;s economies.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Fostering digital integration requires collaborations between these private players, governments, and regional bodies. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://papss.com/&quot;>;Pan-African Payment and Settlement System&lt;/a>; (PAPSS) demonstrates that this approach is feasible. While PAPSS is the product of a partnership between the African Union and the African Export-Import Bank, it depends on a network of some of Africa&#39;s largest private commercial banks.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A centralized payment and settlement system for intra-African commerce, officially introduced in January 2022, PAPSS facilitates continental commerce and deeper economic integration. It enables payments for intra-African trade transactions in local currencies (Africa has roughly 42 currencies), reducing expenses and accelerating trade settlement and payment. Before PAPSS, the typical payment route between two African countries required that an African currency be first exchanged for dollars, pounds, or euros and then swapped a second time for a different African currency. This raises the cost of intra-African currency transactions by an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/fandd/issues/2022/09/Digital-Journeys-Africa-freeing-foreign-exchange-wellisz&quot;>;estimated $5 billion&lt;/a>; each year.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Building for Interoperability&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Building continent-wide digital systems will take time and significant resources, but immediately prioritizing interoperability could create the foundation for digital integration. Thus, public digital systems being built in African countries should be interoperable — that is, have capabilities for the exchange and use of information with other similar systems in other countries. Inevitably, some economies and sectors move faster than others with digitalization. Therefore, building with interoperability in mind will allow for easy integration in the near future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With identity systems, for example, an ideal scenario would be for ID obtained in Nigeria to be easily digitally verifiable by a bank in Namibia. This would be possible if Nigeria&#39;s digital identity system had the capacity for interoperability. Moreover, interoperable ID systems across the continent would allow for continent-wide know-your-customer systems, enabling access to financial services anywhere in Africa and thus making intra-African commerce easier.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Of course, interoperable public systems require significant policy and regulatory interventions. Governments and regional bodies must address challenges such as harmonizing standards, enhancing current legal frameworks, and adopting cybersecurity, consumer, and data protection regulations to facilitate successful interoperability.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Power and Internet&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Digital integration has no chance if digital services are only accessible to a fraction of the population, as in many African countries. While physical infrastructure like roads, rails, and ports connecting the continent is critical to Africa&#39;s physical integration, power and the internet will determine the success of digital integration.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many African countries still have less than half of their population as internet users, with countries such as Burundi and the Central African Republic having &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1124283/internet-penetration-in-africa-by-country/&quot;>;less than 15%&lt;/a>; internet penetration. Similarly, 600 million people, or&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/reports/africa-energy-outlook-2022/key-findings&quot;>; 43% of the entire African population&lt;/a>;, do not have access to electricity, with the majority living in sub-Saharan Africa. Therefore, accelerating universal access to power and the internet should become a priority.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Africa desperately needs digital integration, but it&#39;s critical to recognize its inherent difficulties — for example, concerns about sovereignty and divergent national objectives. What&#39;s more, active steps toward digital integration require deliberate government commitment, which requires governments to recognize their importance and have the resources to pursue them.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Thu, 07 Sep 2023 20:25:01 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Negotiate Your Salary in the Age of Pay Transparency Laws]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/09/Sep23_06_7aWvQdR36Y0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&amp;#8217;s possible. But how should you negotiate for yourself when a pay band is exceptionally large? In this article, the author shares insights from two experts on compensation and negotiation. They recommend not focusing on &amp;#8220;fairness&amp;#8221; &lt;/span>;when making your case, but rather &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400&quot;>;focusing the conversation on yours and the employer&amp;#8217;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/how-to-negotiate-your-salary-in-the-age-of-pay-transparency-laws?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Having more information to gauge your worth should, in theory, give you more leverage in salary negotiations. But the reality is complicated. Companies could be less willing to stray from their set ranges, and you might feel hesitant to push for fear of looking unreasonable. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;How should you approach salary conversations in this new era of pay transparency laws? What&#39;s the best way to advocate for yourself when the pay band is exceptionally large? And is it better to be direct or subtle? &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;What the Experts Say&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/04/3-new-us-employment-regulations-that-companies-should-prepare-for-now&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pay transparency laws&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; vary from state to state,&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; but in a nutshell, they require employers to disclose information about pay, such as salary ranges, in job postings or in offers to candidates. The aim is to create more visibility in pay practices and &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/01/how-salary-transparency-can-help-you-and-your-workplace&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;help close gender and racial wage gaps&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For job seekers, the upshot is more agency in salary negotiations, says D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;avid Buckmaster, the author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Fair-Pay-Raise-Stronger-Businesses/dp/1665098317&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Fair Pay&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, who&#39;s worked on employee compensation projects for companies including Nike and Starbucks&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. Before these laws existed, Buckmaster says that compensation was like a mysterious black box. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Job candidates&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; were in the dark about what comparable employees made and how the company benchmarked salaries to the rest of the market,” he says. “Now, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;having a pay range takes away some of those unknowns.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The downside is that it can cause job seekers to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;hyper-fixate on salary&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, rather than the &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/01/negotiating-your-next-job&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;big picture of an employment offer&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, according to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Victoria Medvec, a professor at the Kellogg School of Management at Northwestern and author of &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Negotiate-without-Fear-Strategies-Maximize/dp/1119719097&quot;>;&lt;i>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiate Without Fear&lt;/span>;&lt;/i>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Your pay is a piece of it, but there are other aspects of the job to consider like your role, responsibilities, benefits, and flexibility,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Here are some tips to help you navigate the conversation and get the compensation you deserve.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Appreciate your newfound power.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2023/03/how-to-ask-for-what-you-want-and-get-it&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating your salary&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; requires information, tact, confidence — and the right mindset, says &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec.&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; “Knowledge is power, and&lt;/span>; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;y&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ou now have an advantage because you know what&#39;s possible.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While some salary bands might seem too broad to be useful, they underscore the power of negotiation, she says. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;The range exists because &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiation is a dynamic interaction between the employee and employer and &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;some people do it more effectively.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;After all, she says, it&#39;s not &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/how-women-can-get-what-they-want-in-a-negotiation&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;just about being willing to ask for more&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, it&#39;s also about having the information and self-assurance to make your case.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Don&#39;t get in your own head and don&#39;t be intimidated or discouraged — even if a certain number feels out of reach, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;adds Buckmaster. For example, if you make $70,000 and you&#39;re being offered a comparable job with a listed range of $100,000-$150,000, you might feel as if you can&#39;t ask for the top of the range. But the fact is, your current salary has little bearing on what another company is willing to pay you, he says: “What you made before &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;doesn&#39;t matter.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do your research.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Your goal is to go into the negotiation with an objective, realistic understanding of how the employer views your market value. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This requires some homework to figure out where you might land within the company&#39;s published&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; compensation &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;bands: at the top, in the middle, or toward the bottom. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Before pay transparency laws existed, people may have assumed that HR has been randomly throwing darts at a dartboard to determine what people got paid, but there&#39;s rigor behind the numbers,” says Buckmaster. He says that behind the listed range lies an “approval matrix” that&#39;s invisible to candidates. “Every company has a trigger point that requires extra approvals to justify placing someone at the very top of the range.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;D&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;on&#39;t be disheartened; rather, use that &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/10/work-speak-the-right-way-to-negotiate&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;knowledge to make a compelling case&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; for yourself. Visit j&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ob search websites and databases, such as Glassdoor, Ladders, and Salary.com, and talk to recruiters and industry colleagues. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Take a good, hard look at your experience and qualifications and be honest about your work history. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Evaluate your actual job level and the scope of your past responsibilities. De-emphasize titles. Being a director at a startup is not the same as being one at a large company,” Buckmaster says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Be savvy about the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Many, but not all, &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/04/15-rules-for-negotiating-a-job-offer&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;salary negotiations take place&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; after the company has extended an offer. But you might consider signaling your salary expectations earlier in the process if you think your pay ought to be on the high-end of the range, says Buckmaster. He suggests saying something along the lines of, “I&#39;m looking forward to seeing the offer and trust that my starting position in your pay range will align with my significant experience doing this work at XYZ company.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Once the company has made an offer, the opportunity to negotiate for more is usually quite narrow, so Buckmaster advises making your case wisely. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;“Don&#39;t go back multiple times, otherwise it might affect your reputation on the way in,” he says. “You don&#39;t want to come across as being challenging to work with.” Make your argument concise, crisp, and reasonable. “Most companies don&#39;t want to have custom, complicated negotiations with everyone who comes in.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;State your case…&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Negotiating a higher salary requires clearly articulating why you&#39;re worth more. Medvec recommends&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; focusing on your &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;differentiators: your background, skill set, and special abilities that match the company&#39;s needs. You&#39;ve &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2022/07/5-ways-to-stand-out-in-your-next-job-interview&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;already outlined your past achievements&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; in the hiring process&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;, of course. Now it&#39;s time to talk about how you&#39;ll add value in the future — and how that should be reflected in your pay. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec suggests laying out how you&#39;ll help the company generate new lines of revenue, cut costs, attract talent, or enter new markets. “Talk about your exact role and responsibilities, including what specifically you&#39;ll be doing,” she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Pinpointing how &lt;/span>;&lt;a href=&quot;/2018/10/to-land-a-great-job-talk-about-why-you-love-your-work&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;you&#39;re going to tackle their challenges&lt;/span>;&lt;/a>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; puts you in a stronger position, she says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Bear in mind that approval matrix, adds Buckmaster. “&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Help the recruiter tell your story internally,” he says. “Make their job easier with solid arguments oriented around the business. Otherwise they&#39;re going to have a hard time getting it approved.”&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;… and bring your A-game if you&#39;re aiming extra high.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;While it&#39;s possible to &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;negotiate above the stated pay range, your case has to be bulletproof. Many companies are comfortable with roughly 5% of their employees being paid over the maximum, according to Buckmaster. Pay bands are not an exact science and “sometimes people break the system and end up with higher salaries,” he says. This can happen for many reasons. Perhaps the new hire is joining a smaller company, or maybe their manager is more like a peer, or maybe the new employee is taking on a specialized role, or perhaps they know esoteric coding language that the company needs. “Or it could be that they&#39;re uniquely gifted and hard to get,” he says. &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;A word of warning though: If you&#39;re paid over the maximum, you might be ineligible for salary increases in the future, so be sure to inquire about the company&#39;s policies. &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For senior roles, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Medvec&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>; recommends booking a half hour with an employment lawyer in the city where the company is based. “Find out not just how much others ask for, but also what&#39;s in their contracts, like stock, equity, and employment guarantees,” she says. “It will be an expensive 30 minutes, but well worth it for senior-level jobs.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t focus on “fairness,” but rather mutual interests.&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;P&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ay-transparency laws were created to help ensure equitable compensation, but it&#39;s not a good idea to frame your individual negotiation around fairness, &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;according to Medvec. “Don&#39;t create a rationale based on what&#39;s right or what&#39;s fair,” she says. Instead, “reference information about what others earn to anchor your request, but keep the conversation focused on the employer&#39;s interests.” &lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;For example, Medvec recommends saying something along the lines of: “I know from publicly available information that this role pays up to $190,000. I believe I&#39;m at the top end of that pay range because I&#39;m uniquely positioned to do XYZ, and I&#39;m confident in what I bring to the table. But I&#39;m also comfortable getting a base salary of $160,00 with a $50,000 annual bonus when I achieve the objectives that are important to you.” &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;This way, you&#39;re making strategic compromises that benefit both you and the organization.&lt;/span>;&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;b>;Principles to Remember&lt;/b>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Do&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Appreciate your newfound advantage. Pay transparency empowers you with information about what&#39;s possible.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Carve out time to do your homework so you can build a strong argument for the salary you want.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Make sure the recruiter can tell your story to the decision-makers by framing your argument in terms of the business.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;h3>;&lt;b>;Don&#39;t&lt;/b>;&lt;/h3>; &lt;ul>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Doubt yourself even if a certain number feels out of reach. If you think you&#39;re worth it, make a strong, rational case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;Belabor what&#39;s fair or what&#39;s right; &lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;rather, focus the conversation on yours and the employer&#39;s mutual interests.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; aria-level=&quot;1&quot;>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;M&lt;/span>;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;>;ake the mistake of assuming you can negotiate indefinitely; companies usually have a clear process and don&#39;t want a drawn-out back-and-forth.&lt;/span>;&lt;/li>; &lt;/ul>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is India the World&rsquo;s Next Great Economic Power?]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_05_638755428.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/anand purohit/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Is India&amp;#8217;s economic rise inevitable? There&amp;#8217;s good reason to think that this latest round of Indo-optimism might be different than previous iterations, but the country still has major challenges to address to make good on this promise. In terms of drivers, demand &amp;#8212; in the form of a consumer boom, context appropriate innovation, and a green transition &amp;#8212; and supply &amp;#8212; in the form of a demographic dividend, access to finance, and major infrastructure upgrades &amp;#8212; are helping to push the country forward. This is facilitated by policy reforms, geopolitical positioning, and a diaspora dividend. Even so, the country faces barriers to success, including unbalanced growth, unrealized demographic potential, and unrealized ease-of-business and innovation potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/is-india-the-worlds-next-great-economic-power?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;In 2002, India&#39;s government launched a ubiquitous international tourism campaign known as “Incredible India.” Were it to launch a similar campaign today, it might as well be called “Inevitable India.” Not just enthusiasts within the country, but a chorus of global analysts, have declared India as the next great economic power: Goldman Sachs has predicted it will become the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html&quot;>;world&#39;s second-largest economy by 2075,&lt;/a>; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/c9de715e-2e29-4a7f-880b-1509c04bf11b&quot;>;FT&#39;s Martin Wolf suggests&lt;/a>; that by 2050, its purchasing power will be 30% larger than that of the US&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have been through similar surges of Indo-optimism before. But the on-the-ground reality has continued to frustrate even the most ardent of India&#39;s champions. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/04/28/india-revolutions-economy-growth-future/&quot;>;bold predictions&lt;/a>; that it would overtake China (an economy still five times larger than India&#39;s), to McKinsey&#39;s 2007 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/asia-pacific/the-bird-of-gold&quot;>;“bird of gold”&lt;/a>; promise of the Indian consumer that never quite panned out, to deregulation followed by policy reversals and crises of confidence in doing business with India, to devastating periods through the pandemic, the country&#39;s promised inevitable rise has remained elusive. What&#39;s different now?&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are several positive trends converging, from different sides of the Indian business ecosystem: demand, supply, and the system-wide facilitating factors; in combination, they can transcend economic cycles, macro shocks, and policy reversals. Some are new, and the older ones are reaching critical mass and they can finally reinforce each other to create a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jimcollins.com/concepts/the-flywheel.html&quot;>;growth flywheel&lt;/a>;. But as with all flywheels, it is important to remain vigilant about rattling noises and burning smells, and in India&#39;s case, these exist in abundance. It&#39;s essential for both business and government leaders to pay attention and act before the flywheel breaks.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Demand&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Three forces are converging on the demand side to fuel India&#39;s economic growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Consumer boom&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;The starting point for any discussion of India&#39;s promise is, invariably, the promise of the Indian consumer. With 1.4 billion people and myriad unmet needs, India&#39;s growth is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html&quot;>;driven mainly&lt;/a>; by domestic consumption and investments. Real wages are expected to grow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/01/apac-salary-asia-leads-2023-real-wage-growth-jumps-in-india-china.html&quot;>;at 4.6%,&lt;/a>; whereas disposable income will continue to grow in excess of &lt;a href=&quot;https://tradingeconomics.com/india/disposable-personal-income&quot;>;15%&lt;/a>;. Industries that are mature in the West are fast-growing in India: Private health insurance, for example, has almost &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/advisor/in/health-insurance/health-insurance-statistics/&quot;>;tripled between 2015 and 2021&lt;/a>;, while consumer durables were expected to grow between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisil.com/en/home/newsroom/press-releases/2022/09/volume-vault-to-lift-consumer-durables-revenue-15-18-percent.html&quot;>;15% and 18%&lt;/a>; this year.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Context-appropriate innovation&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;International companies have struggled to grasp what constitutes India&#39;s “middle class” and craft the appropriate value propositions. While &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/middle-class-nearly-1/3rd-of-indias-population-to-be-2/3rds-by-2047-report/articleshow/95239621.cms&quot;>;some analysts&lt;/a>; argue that one out of every three Indians is “middle class,” only &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrinks-and-poverty-spreads-while-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;66 million&lt;/a>; are genuinely “middle income” by global standards, while a whopping &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2021/03/18/in-the-pandemic-indias-middle-class-shrinks-and-poverty-spreads-while-china-sees-smaller-changes/&quot;>;1.16 billion&lt;/a>; are low income. However, many in this second group constitute a vast &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/be53790c-ea16-4e5c-9410-bac189fb2636&quot;>;aspirational consuming class&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This has many implications. For one, competing in India means selling at much lower price points, which in turn requires reconfiguring activities, production, and supply chains in ways that are hard for competitors to mimic. India&#39;s best-selling car is Wagon R, priced at $7,000 and made by Japan&#39;s Suzuki, a company whose &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/10/31/business/corporate-business/suzuki-india-market-share/&quot;>;41% market share&lt;/a>; in India is an outlier in the auto industry globally.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That said, as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.firstpost.com/entertainment/explained-why-netflix-is-failing-big-time-in-india-10580421.html&quot;>;Netflix discovered&lt;/a>; through its stumbles in the country, it takes more than low prices to win in India. Localizing the content, working in multiple Indian languages, and leveraging synergies across products that Indian consumers want, as Amazon or Disney can do, is essential. In a very different sector, McDonald&#39;s, has incorporated vegetarian options, Indian snacks, and menus for multi-generational families, building a contextualized value proposition.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Those that can crack the code of the Indian consumer are handsomely rewarded: Many McDonald&#39;s franchisees in India are billionaires. The home appliances manufacturer Havells introduced a product line with “India-friendly” offerings such as water purifiers and compressor-less air coolers, relevant to both the Indian consumers&#39; needs and affordability. Since its listing 30 years ago, &lt;a href=&quot;https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/havells-india-ltd/stocks/companyid-10507.cms&quot;>;Havells&#39;&lt;/a>; profits have grown 826 times, and its market cap has jumped 5,800 times.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Green transition&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A burgeoning new source of demand growth comes from India&#39;s urgent need for a green transition. The scale of its economic potential means that its energy demand will be enormous. As the third-largest energy-consuming nation, it is already &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investindia.gov.in/sector/renewable-energy#:~:text=India&#39;s%20installed%20renewable%20energy%20capacity,additions%20of%209.83%25%20in%202022.&quot;>;4th in the world&lt;/a>; in renewable energy installed capacity. The country has set &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iea.org/commentaries/india-s-clean-energy-transition-is-rapidly-underway-benefiting-the-entire-world&quot;>;ambitious targets&lt;/a>;: installing 500 gigawatts of renewable energy capacity, producing 5 million tons of green hydrogen annually, cutting emissions by 45%, along with a billion tons of CO2 — all by 2030. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Mission_2070_A_Green_New_Deal_for_a_Net_Zero_India_2021.pdf&quot;>;2021 report&lt;/a>;&amp;nbsp;by the World Economic Forum projects 50 million net new “green economy” jobs in India — which means more consumers — and $15 trillion in economic opportunity by 2070, with $1 trillion by 2030.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;Supply&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;There are several positive forces converging on the supply side as well.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Demographic dividend&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;One part of the supply-side story is old news: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.com/en_in/india-at-100/reaping-the-demographic-dividend&quot;>;By 2030&lt;/a>;, India&#39;s working-age population is expected to be 1.04 billion with a dependency ratio to be the lowest in its history at 31.2%, contributing just under a quarter of the incremental global workforce. The working-age population bulge is expected to last till 2055.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The “Asian Miracle” was built on harnessing this trend: Japan entered this sweet spot in 1964, South Korea in 1967 and China in 1994. Additionally, India also has the largest pool of English-speaking STEM graduates in the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Access to finance&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;India&#39;s financial markets are in a better state than ever before. With the China opportunities cooling, investors need alternatives, and India comes closest. The MSCI India Index is up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/india-investing-china-stocks-growth-exports-demographics-31252a80&quot;>;12%&lt;/a>; this year, compared to 2% for the MSCI Emerging Markets Index.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Bank balance sheets are &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/with-stronger-balance-sheets-indias-banking-sector-at-an-inflection-point/articleshow/96702845.cms&quot;>;stronger&lt;/a>; and credit markets are functioning well. It&#39;s telling that many Indian banks are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/finance/banks/news/indian-banks-better-placed-than-their-us-peers-due-to-attractive-valuations-and-stickier-deposits/articleshow/98859627.cms&quot;>;valued higher&lt;/a>; than US peers. &amp;nbsp;HDFC Bank — which merged with its parent, mortgage lender HDFC — has a market capitalization of $171 billion, making it the 4&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 13.3333px;&quot;>;th &lt;/span>;largest financial company in the world. Even before the merger, the 29-year-old upstart was more valuable than the 154-year-old Goldman Sachs.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The change can be seen even in the traditionally underfinanced informal sector, comprising over 86% of India&#39;s workforce. Avendus, a leading Indian investment bank, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avendus.com/crypted_pdf_path/msme-lending-report-formattedvf-img-642a719b97ccc-.pdf&quot;>;calculated&lt;/a>; that Indian small-and-medium-enterprise sector&#39;s total demand for debt is $1.5 trillion. Of this, $725 billion is unaddressable because of lack of collateral, and formal credit is only available to the tune of $289 billion. This is motivating lenders to deepen their offerings. New-to-credit customers are at 34% up from 9% of customers for small business lenders in 2017. Loans by small business lenders have jumped 43% annually in the past two years.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Infrastructure upgrades, both physical and digital&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;A critical barrier that sticks in the mind of anyone who has visited India is its lagging infrastructure. Historically, &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/programmes/from_our_own_correspondent/9483756.stm&quot;>;investing in handouts&lt;/a>; may have been more politically expedient, but the current administration&#39;s popularity gives it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/modi-should-focus-on-people-not-just-big-projects/2023/02/06/ceb85dc4-a66b-11ed-b2a3-edb05ee0e313_story.html&quot;>;greater leeway&lt;/a>; to invest in infrastructure. Capital expenditure as a percentage of total government expenditure has increased from 11% in 2010 to a projected 22% this year. Infrastructure expenditure this year will see a 33% hike to $122 billion.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The outcomes have been striking. India has been adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;10,000 km of highway&lt;/a>; annually. Since 2014, the number of Indian airports has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;doubled&lt;/a>; and an upgraded train system will have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/03/13/india-is-getting-an-eye-wateringly-big-transport-upgrade&quot;>;new high efficiency “freight corridors&lt;/a>;” connecting the economic centers of India.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In addition, one of most distinctive changes has been in the digital infrastructure. With &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/info-tech/indias-internet-subscribers-increased-to-88125-million-as-of-march-end-trai-report/article67219636.ece&quot;>;881.25 million&lt;/a>; internet subscribers, India has the second-highest internet-enabled population in the world behind China&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://english.scio.gov.cn/m/pressroom/2022-11/07/content_78506468.htm&quot;>;1.05 billion&lt;/a>;. Riding on this access, there is a &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/05/the-case-for-investing-in-digital-public-infrastructure&quot;>;digital public infrastructure&lt;/a>; — a model being studied by other countries — that combines a population-scale unique identity system, a payments interface that makes digital payments seamless, and a data management system, whereby citizens can access essential documents online, such as tax documents, vaccination certificates, etc. All of this helps make public services and credit more easily accessible to a wider swath of the population.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;As an indicator of the resulting change, India has &lt;a href=&quot;https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/gadgets-news/india-tops-world-ranking-in-digital-payments-beats-china-by-huge-margin-report/articleshow/100944643.cms&quot;>;topped the list&lt;/a>; for digital payments beating China by a huge margin. Interestingly, India&#39;s payments are more than the digital payments made in the next four leading countries combined.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Facilitators&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;On top of these forces in motion, there are several system-wide facilitators in the mix.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Domestic policy reforms&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Many &lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/india/1734728/india-may-soon-achieve-modis-ease-of-doing-business-goal&quot;>;regulatory and policy reforms&lt;/a>; have been put in place, from implementation of the 2016 Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code to the elimination of more than 39,000 regulations to foster ease of doing business.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Many other reforms, such as construction permits and power connections, are the domain of state governments and there is a drive towards change at these levels as well. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/asia/2023/05/11/how-indias-states-compete-for-investment&quot;>;State governments are competing&lt;/a>; by helping speed up the process of setting up businesses, providing incentives for investment and even attracting clusters of competing companies, which enables more business-friendly environments in more regions across the country.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Geopolitical sweet spot&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Another transformation is a more distinctive geopolitical positioning for India, triggered, most significantly, by the growing rift between China and Western economies, particularly the US This is translating into new business opportunities for India, most visibly — the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-65784719&quot;>;manufacturing of Apple&#39;s smartphones&lt;/a>;. With a goal of producing 20 million iPhones a year, 50,000 new jobs will be created by one such project alone. In addition, when it comes to military-grade technology used for space launches, there is greater confidence in India as a host than China and there is already a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/04/business/india-space-startups.html&quot;>;thriving ecosystem&lt;/a>; in place. India has hosted &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_foreign_satellites_launched_by_India&quot;>;111 international space launches&lt;/a>; since 2020, and successfully &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2023/science/india-moon-landing-photos.html&quot;>;landed a rover on the moon&lt;/a>; in late August.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To consider another prominent example, chipmaker, Micron Technology, &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.micron.com/news-releases/news-release-details/micron-announces-new-semiconductor-assembly-and-test-facility&quot;>;announced&lt;/a>; plans to build a new assembly and test facility, as part of moves to diversify beyond China. In fact, the new president of the World Bank has suggested that there is a narrow window for India to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-should-cash-china-plus-one-strategy-world-bank-chief-2023-07-19/#:~:text=In%20recent%20years%2C%20many%20companies,World%20Bank%20chief%20last%20month.&quot;>;“cash in”&lt;/a>; on the growing trend behind companies seeking to diversify their supply chain and manufacturing beyond a massive dependence on China.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Diaspora dividend&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;It is interesting to note that both the CEO of Micron Technology and the World Bank chief are Indian-born, which brings us to the third key facilitator: the Indian diaspora, now the world&#39;s largest and influential in ways that it had never been before. In the business world alone it is telling that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/06/12/indias-diaspora-is-bigger-and-more-influential-than-any-in-history&quot;>;25 of S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a>; company CEOs are Indian-born. Beyond this, senior management ranks of numerous companies are populated by Indians. It&#39;s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://m.economictimes.com/tech/startups/indians-are-driving-the-us-startup-story-nfap-study/india-is-the-leading-country-of-origin-for-immigrant-founders-of-us-unicorns/slideshow/93165270.cms&quot;>;leading country of origin&lt;/a>; for immigrant founders of US unicorns. These connections help build global connectivity to Indian business and facilitate India&#39;s integration into global value chains.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Barriers&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;While these factors reinforce each other, many barriers remain – and they could cause the multiplier effect to stall. Consider three major bumps in the road and the actions needed.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unbalanced growth&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Despite impressive growth numbers at the national level, the economic benefits have been highly unequal. The top 10% of Indians hold &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;77%&lt;/a>; of the national wealth. Almost &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oxfam.org/en/india-extreme-inequality-numbers&quot;>;2 people every second&lt;/a>; are pushed into poverty because of health care costs alone. India&#39;s population density — amongst the highest in the world — exacerbates the zero-sum nature of resource allocation and environmental stresses. Regional imbalances — southern and western India growing 12% faster than northern and eastern India — will magnify over time. Superimpose on this linguistic fault-lines, new inter-regional tensions could surface. Handling these will require deft management of the political economy.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Other imbalances are growing because of divisive politics. An increasingly assertive form of &lt;a href=&quot;https://frontline.thehindu.com/columns/india-this-side-ganesh-devy-putting-the-useless-to-use-the-divisive-politics-of-the-word-hindutva/article67045226.ece&quot;>;Hindutva ideology&lt;/a>; is overshadowing core issues such as job-creation, enhancing productivity and shared economic benefits. The root cause of this problem was a belief in large sections of society that what started as affirmative action projects in a newly independent India should have had sunset clauses leading to discontent over minority appeasement by political leaders. The pendulum has now swung in the other direction creating new challenges of exclusion and identity politics. For many India-watchers it hasn&#39;t helped that India has declined in its position on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://rsf.org/en/index&quot;>;World Press Freedom Index&lt;/a>;. Consequently, potentially, bottled-up sentiments in large sections of the disaffected and minority segments of the population can explode, triggering a downward spiral. Such developments can undermine objectives of shared prosperity. For international investors and trade partners, this can add a risk premium of majoritarianism in a country with as much religious, linguistic and socio-cultural diversity as India. More significantly, these developments exhaust political capital, which can otherwise be leveraged for social and economic transformation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;There are at least two solutions to these challenges. One is of political parties moving away from identity politics to inclusive growth and job-creation as the most reliable means of winning over the widest swath of the country&#39;s vast population. Two, India sees a constant flow of state-level elections, which distorts public dialogue by skewing it away from longer-term economic growth-oriented perspectives. Streamlining and bunching elections will give breathing space to public discourse and push political leadership and voters toward longer-term horizons.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unrealized demographic potential&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/india/despite-world-beating-growth-indias-lack-jobs-threatens-its-young-2023-05-30/&quot;>;Less than half&lt;/a>; of urban workers have full-time jobs, while far too much of India&#39;s employment is in under-productive informal sectors. Education, skill-building, and health care are grossly inadequate. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://do3n1uzkew47z.cloudfront.net/siteassets/pdf/ISR_Report_2023.pdf&quot;>;India Skills Report 2023&lt;/a>;&lt;em>;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em>;found only half of young Indians are employable. Even the “crown jewels” technology services sector is vulnerable; demand for outsourcing is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2023/06/29/ai-why-india-risks-falling-behind-in-the-tech-race/d8236bc2-16bb-11ee-9de3-ba1fa29e9bec_story.html&quot;>;falling&lt;/a>; and the labor-cost arbitrage model will be disrupted by secular shifts towards cloud computing and AI for coding and routine functions. Alarmingly, India&#39;s female labor participation rate has been in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/SL.TLF.CACT.FE.ZS?locations=IN&quot;>;steady decline&lt;/a>;, having dropped from 32% in 2005 to 19% in 2021.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Emulating, say, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.rmresults.com/a-spotlight-on-vietnams-transformation-in-education&quot;>;Vietnam&lt;/a>;, public and private investment in upskilling must be prioritized, which could add &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dw.com/en/india-youth-lack-skills/a-56879385&quot;>;$570 billion&lt;/a>; to the Indian economy. A major handicap has been manufacturing — a key jobs creator in comparable economies — which has plateaued at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot;>;13.3% of GDP&lt;/a>;. The current infrastructure thrust, policy reforms, geopolitical drivers and capital influx could help unlock Indian manufacturing, but the barriers discussed here must be removed.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In emerging sectors, the surge of potential in AI could be an opportunity for India to take leadership in a cutting-edge area, given the &lt;a href=&quot;/2021/12/50-global-hubs-for-top-ai-talent&quot;>;emergent AI talent hubs&lt;/a>; in the country that can be massively expanded, paired with the &lt;a href=&quot;/2019/01/which-countries-are-leading-the-data-economy&quot;>;vast pools of data&lt;/a>; that accumulate in India. Cultural and organizational changes are needed to create on-ramps for women in the workforce and retain them. Such projects have long gestation periods, so a focused and disciplined long-term plan is required.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3>;Unrealized ease-of-business and innovation potential&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;Doing business in India has improved, but many challenges remain. Land acquisition can stall construction projects and the courts are slow-moving institutions. Land records may be non-existing or outdated and environmental clearances have created additional barriers. On top of this, contract enforcement remains challenging. According to an index created by The Economist, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/international/2023/05/02/the-2023-crony-capitalism-index&quot;>;India ranks 10th&lt;/a>; in the prevalence of crony capitalism, in spite of the large-scale liberalization of the past three decades. A legacy of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/08/17/india-must-abandon-protectionism&quot;>;protectionism&lt;/a>; still persists.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;India&#39;s state capacity needs change. Contrary to popular perception, the Indian state is not big and bungling, but weak and waning. Institutions — from regulators to civic bodies to the judiciary — often juggle conflicting demands and are playing catch-up to market and social realities. Many important decisions are made with a crisis as a frame of reference and India&#39;s story of victories is often of individual heroism amidst institutional failure. Making India&#39;s state machinery cutting-edge may well be India&#39;s pivotal project.&lt;/p>; &lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;. 。 .&lt;/h3>; &lt;p>;In sum, while barriers remain, the positive forces can, indeed, create a domino effect: “Inevitable India” is within reach. India&#39;s greatest challenge will be to make its inevitability tangible and believable to the many constituencies that wish to see India succeed. To get from “Incredible India” — aimed at tourists — to now bring the global economy to its door, India next campaign ought to be “Credible India.”&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;br>;&lt;hr>;&lt;div>;获取更多RSS：&lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.net&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.net&lt;/a>; &lt;br>;&lt;a href=&quot;https://feedx.best&quot; style=&quot;color:orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>;https://feedx.best&lt;/a>;&lt;br>;&lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[AI and the New Digital Cold War]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war]]><description> &lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_02_792DVvbiBBo-scaled.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;HBR Staff/Unsplash&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Globalization is not dead, but it is changing. The United States and China are creating two separate spheres for technology, and artificial intelligence is on the front lines of this new &amp;#8220;Digital Cold War.&amp;#8221; If democracies want to succeed in this new era of &amp;#8220;re-globalization&amp;#8221; they will need to coordinate across governments and between the private and public sectors. AI is coming, whether we like it or not. We are at a fork in the road and all segments of society will need to pitch in to build AI systems that contribute to a just and democratic future where humans can thrive.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/ai-and-the-new-digital-cold-war?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;We are entering a new world order, one marked by increased nationalism and greater geopolitical competition. While countries are not going to undo all of the global economic systems that took shape under American unipolarity for the past three decades, certain critical sectors will become decoupled in a process we have previously referred to as &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/02/geopolitics-are-changing-venture-capital-must-too&quot;>;“re-globalization.”&lt;/a>;&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Most significantly, the technology ecosystem will be split largely into two spheres dictated by the world&#39;s two economic powerhouses, the United States and China. Other states will need to decide which sphere they want to be part of, putting pressure on the United States and China to outpace the other and establish their technological dominance. Unfolding before us is a heightened form of economic competition we understand as the “Digital Cold War.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The Digital Cold War will be an economic war, with technological innovations increasingly determining geopolitical prowess. Artificial intelligence (AI), with its capacity to rapidly and radically transform society, will be the most decisive technology in this arena. AI feeds on information, and its most powerful use cases will emerge through its applications across public and private sectors. For the democratic world to pull ahead, companies and countries need to adopt a new approach that prioritizes collaboration and transformation over competition and disruption.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;A New Era of Democratic Coordination&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Everywhere we are seeing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/24/business/dealbook/globalization-fink-marks.html&quot;>;claims&lt;/a>; that “globalization is dead.” Such declarations are fundamentally misguided. The system we are moving toward is more complicated than a reversion of global interconnection. In many cases, trade is simply being rerouted rather than shut down. Most commercial industries will remain open and global, but certain critical sectors will turn inward, toward localized supply chains.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;This trend began not with the United States and its policies but rather with Xi Jinping and his &lt;a href=&quot;http://english.www.gov.cn/policies/latest_releases/2015/05/19/content_281475110703534.htm&quot;>;2015 Made in China plan&lt;/a>;, which made clear that the Chinese government had begun prioritizing national resilience over market efficiency. Xi laid out a plan to outcompete the United States and other global powers in the commanding areas of the economy, most of all high technology. Indeed, China continues to march towards its goal of 70% self-sufficiency in critical technology by 2025. Since then, the United States has responded with its own series of ambitious measures to retain technological supremacy. This reality leads us into a bipolar high technology future.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When it comes to AI — arguably the most decisive technology in this global contestation — we are heading toward two hermetically sealed ecosystems: one that supports open systems but is also associated with democracy, privacy, and individual rights, versus one that supports state control, information-flow restriction, and politically imposed limits on openness. As much as we might hope that China&#39;s political model will evolve and that its technology will be subject to democratic feedback, we should not be naïve: That is not the trajectory that it is on. For a future to prevail that prizes openness and individual rights, democratic nations need to be market leaders in AI. The only way to ensure this is by promoting international collaboration, especially between democracies and other defenders of the rules-based order.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the previous era, the United States could innovate on a technology and other countries would simply adopt it. When American technology leaders made groundbreaking advancements with personal computers and the internet, they operated under the assumption that American companies could work in isolation and spread their technologies across the world in a top-down fashion. The cloud revolution amplified this further, with Amazon, Microsoft, and Google owning 65% of the global market for cloud computing. This strategy may have worked when technologies were intended for pure disruption. AI, however, is geared for societal transformation. This requires a new kind of collaboration across stakeholders.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Along with computing capabilities, the power of AI is based on the amount of aggregated data that is fed to it. This means that the United States, or any country, working in isolation with restricted data flows will fail to maximize the potential of its technology — and yet data localization policies &lt;a href=&quot;https://itif.org/publications/2021/07/19/how-barriers-cross-border-data-flows-are-spreading-globally-what-they-cost/&quot;>;doubled worldwide&lt;/a>; from 2017 to 2021, further obstructing cross-border collaboration. The summation of human knowledge and capabilities is not siloed in any one country or culture. Even Wikipedia&#39;s knowledge base is only 11% in the English language. For AI to thrive in its ability to help us solve our hardest problems, we have to unlock the world&#39;s capacity — from French nuclear scientists to Korean philosophers, from Indian researchers to Kenyan artists, and indeed to Chinese researchers who choose to leave China and work and live in the West.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Plus, the capital requirements for investments in the sector are so large at present that very few national markets are big enough to succeed with AI on their own. For example, consider investment in semiconductors — a key input into AI progress. The UK&#39;s recently announced 100 million GBP &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gov.uk/government/news/initial-100-million-for-expert-taskforce-to-help-uk-build-and-adopt-next-generation-of-safe-ai&quot;>;AI plan&lt;/a>; and 1 billion GBP &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gov.uk/government/news/new-1-billion-strategy-for-uks-semiconductor-sector&quot;>;semiconductor investment&lt;/a>; pale in comparison to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/senate-approves-280-billion-bill-to-boost-us-science-chip-production-11658942295&quot;>;US&#39;s&lt;/a>; $280 billion and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-25/eu-enacts-43-billion-chips-act-in-bid-to-boost-production&quot;>;EU&#39;s&lt;/a>; 43 billion EUR chips packages — and even these packages are constrained compared to the scale of the investment required to fully develop these technologies. Certainly, few investors globally can support fundraising rounds for startups like the one-year-old Inflection AI&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/inflection-ai-raises-13-bln-funding-microsoft-others-2023-06-29/&quot;>;$1.3 billion round&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;At the center of this all, a disjointed approach with various patchworks of regulatory frameworks across the West will harm any ability to compete and win against Chinese AI systems. It is not just a function of population, but a function of data points. Chinese society,&amp;nbsp;with a population more than &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.visualcapitalist.com/the-population-of-china-compared-with-the-rest-of-the-world/&quot;>;four times larger&lt;/a>; than the US&#39;s, &amp;nbsp;has become so digitized with data freely shared between its government and domestic technology champions. Soon their models, based largely on American and foreign research, can leapfrog the capabilities of those in the West.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;With its size, centralized government, and inroads in other countries, China has the potential to develop one comprehensive AI model that outcompetes the multiplicity of models coming out of democratic nations if there is no international coordination. While the United States is still the AI leader — with the companies that are doing the most cutting-edge research — and while AI seems to have a bias toward open systems with unfettered access to information, the United States risks losing its edge if it fails to coalesce around a uniform strategy with other democratic nations. If this were to happen, Chinese companies could bring their technology to Western markets, influencing democratic politics and signaling to the world China&#39;s economic dominance — and its broader colonization of digital infrastructure around the world.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;AI is becoming an increasingly critical part of this global infrastructure, and the West must act swiftly and in a unified fashion to ensure the technology remains open and democratically controlled. To develop the most powerful AI models across sectors, the United States will need to collaborate with other allied countries — to name a few, India, Singapore, Japan, South Korea, and European nations — by adopting data-sharing policies and encouraging the co-creation of technological innovations. Much can be gleaned from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.european-data-governance-act.com/#:~:text=What%20is%20the%20European%20Data,of%20EU%20citizens%20and%20businesses.&quot;>;European Data Governance Act&lt;/a>; approved by the EU in 2022, which facilitates data-sharing across member countries to maximize benefits for its citizens and businesses.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Failure to course correct will severely limit the impact of AI. For models tackling climate change, siloed data is an immediate death sentence. Medical and healthcare data and innovations are not limited to any one country, nor any one research institution. Industrial AI powering global supply chains cannot be effective without the constant flow of interconnected data. In consumer applications, varying copyright frameworks would stymie cultural relevance and influence, favoring those with free access to data over others. Moreover, piecemeal data regulation and sovereignty requirements raise compliance costs and complexity, harming the innovation economy&#39;s ability to succeed.&amp;nbsp;This is not to suggest that governments should abstain from regulating AI, but rather that they should work together to establish uniform standards and practices across countries. Coordination among democratic nations will empower each country to individually feel resilient when it comes to AI, but also elevate the West as a bloc to be the leader in AI.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;Responsible Innovation for AI Transformation&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;In addition to collaborating across states, if Western companies want to become true market leaders, they will also need to collaborate within states, namely with governmental institutions and civil society. While most of the current discourse surrounding AI focuses on large language models and other generative capabilities, AI&#39;s most significant long-term impacts will come from the ways in which it transforms industries and society as a whole. And genuine transformation cannot come about if private actors are disconnected from the wider society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Already we are seeing AI&#39;s transformative potential beginning to take shape. AI has the capacity to massively level the playing field for who has access to information and insights. In the classroom, AI can give&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;A lot of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/30/tech/ai-industry-statement-extinction-risk-warning/index.html&quot;>;recent attention&lt;/a>; has fixated on the existential threat AI could pose to humanity in the somewhat distant future. But AI is also destabilizing democratic systems in the here and now, providing new avenues for mis- and dis-information through sophisticated bots and realistic deep-fakes. AI will also throw into question the value of democracy itself. What happens when authoritarian systems, augmented by AI, can outperform their democratic counterparts, for instance by massively reducing crime with expanded surveillance? Or by providing vastly better healthcare because of access to centralized information with no restrictions for privacy? Undemocratic alternatives will only become more tempting as AI develops, and these possibilities are not too far off.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We are at a fork in the road when it comes to AI. We can go down the path that leads to automation and destruction, replacing human work and meaning, or we can go down the path that leads to copiloting and enablement, making us more productive, helping us live more balanced lives, and becoming greater masters of our craft. Unlike the social media revolution, which, if regulators really wanted to, they could have slowed or redirected, the AI revolution can only charge forward. Unlike previous &lt;em>;platform&lt;/em>; revolutions, this is a &lt;em>;technological&lt;/em>; revolution, and its mantle has already been picked up by stakeholders across society.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The most successful companies will be those that embrace this forward-looking vision and build to endure, by centering a core set of values that align with society and abide by self-regulatory mechanisms. Taking the further step of partnering with the public sector and incumbent ecosystems is also crucial. We cannot risk AI going awry and putting democracies off track in this competitive race. Since the impacts of AI will be felt across every sector of society, accounting for broad stakeholder interests is both a moral responsibility and the only way to bring about sustainable transformation. In the age of AI, companies will need to pursue an agenda of responsible innovation, working outside of the usual technological silos.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To win the Digital Cold War, the United States and its allies must be the market leaders in AI. And to build the best AI companies, they need to prioritize international collaboration and engender a new mindset — one that aims to innovate responsibly and unleash human potential.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:25:03 +0800</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Challenges of Networking as an Executive]]></title><link/><![CDATA[https://hbr.org/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive]]><description>&lt;div>; &lt;hero-image >; &lt;div>; &lt;img src=&quot;https://hbr.org/resources/images/article_assets/2023/08/Sep23_02_200428479-007.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;&quot; aria-label=&quot;&quot; >; &lt;div>; &lt;span>;Martin Barraud/Getty Images&lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;/hero-image>; &lt;div more-caption=&quot;more&quot; close-caption=&quot;close&quot;>; &lt;span>;Summary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>; &lt;span>;&lt;p>;Networking is critical for senior executives who are making job and career transitions, but it&amp;#8217;s hard to find advice on how best to manage the process. In this article, the authors &amp;#8212; who have decades of experience working with executives during periods of transition &amp;#8212; identify six networking hurdles that executives often encounter, and they provide guidance on how to get over them.&lt;/p>; &lt;/span>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;div>; &lt;/div>; &lt;div>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive?language=es&quot;>;Leer en español&lt;/a>; &lt;br>; &lt;a href=&quot;/2023/09/the-challenges-of-networking-as-an-executive?language=pt&quot;>;Ler em português&lt;/a>; &lt;/div>; &lt;p>;Look online at any of the thousands of articles available on the challenges of networking for a job, and you&#39;ll find that 100% of them give advice on how relatively junior professionals can network “up.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;But surprisingly little advice is available for senior executives, who experience a different but equally challenging set of networking hurdles. That&#39;s a problem, because knowing how to reap networking&#39;s full benefits is crucial for people at the top of the pyramid, especially a time when CEO turnover is at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2023/04/27/ceo-turnover-high-pandemic/&quot;>;record high&lt;/a>;.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We have decades of experience working with and studying senior executives who are making career changes. In this article, we&#39;ll identify six common hurdles that that they often struggle with when it comes to career networking, and we&#39;ll provide some guidance on how to get over them.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;1) Reluctance to ask for help&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Networking for a next role means asking for help. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0749597897927461&quot;>;Research in social psychology&lt;/a>; shows that people with high status are more apt to feel pressure to maintain an image of strength and competence and to value self-reliance, all of which can make them reluctant to seek assistance. They fear rejection and worry that asking for help might expose perceived weaknesses, potentially undermining their status, position, or reputation. This is ego-driven reluctance, and we see it frequently. As one of Herminia&#39;s students put it, “I give help — I don&#39;t ask for it.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;One way around this tendency, which is a natural one, is to start your networking process by reaching out to lower-risk (and lower-yield) contacts — ideally, executives who you know well, who have done their own networking, and who can share not only how they approached others for help but also what they got out of asking for it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;You can probably do this with more people than you realize: As the Stanford social psychologist Xuan Zhao has found, people regularly &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/09567976221097615?journalCode=pssa&quot;>;underestimate&lt;/a>; others&#39; willingness to help, because they don&#39;t realize how happy it makes those others to do so. Low-risk warm-ups and rehearsal practice — what Spish calls “hearing the dreaded words come out of your mouth” — will help you fine-tune your message, defuse your emotions, and experience success. And having a few positive experiences under your belt will make your later, more-challenging calls and emails easier.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;2) &amp;nbsp;Prioritizing secrecy &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;The more senior an executive, the more likely they are to want secrecy, especially if they&#39;ve been laid off. One of Spish&#39;s clients, for example, asked: “How do I go out into the market without letting the market know that I&#39;m looking? I&#39;d like to reach out to people, but I don&#39;t want them to know that I&#39;m interested in looking.”&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Such worries limit your exposure to others, which is a problem in its own right. But they also force you to be secretive as you work on networking and career change — a process, according to Herminia&#39;s research, that often takes far longer than people expect. That burden of secrecy, carried for a long time, can exact a significant psychological toll.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Limiting your exposure to others can be especially pernicious when it keeps you from stepping back and exploring broadly what you would really like to do next. And try as you might, you won&#39;t fool people by obfuscating. At senior levels, it&#39;s a small world: The people you talk to can figure out what you&#39;re up to, perhaps by making a call to a source in their own network, or perhaps just by doing a search online. If you do succeed in concealing your story, it&#39;s likely to tax your nerves and cost you a lot of energy to get the same result that just speaking honestly and directly would have gotten you. With rare exceptions, honesty is the best policy.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;3) &amp;nbsp;Unrealistic expectations &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Because they&#39;re reluctant to ask for help and don&#39;t want word to get out that they are in the market for a new role, senior executives typically want to get their networking done fast. Or they simply assume that because they&#39;re senior, the process won&#39;t take very long. Unfortunately, the more senior you are, the more time you&#39;re likely to need to find and align on the right fit. In Spish&#39;s experience, the shortest possible search is about three months, and the longer ones can take as much as 18 months.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Not only does effective networking take a long time, it also involves a great deal of work, stamina, efficiency, and patience. There are three primary reasons for this.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;First, as both of us have found, only a small percentage of people looking for their next role know exactly which handful of companies they&#39;d like to work for. Because they don&#39;t know enough about the market or what they really want to be able to come up with a targeted search, they have to start with research and very general exploratory networking. That all takes time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Second, what you want and are best suited for may not actually be available to you. Both of us have seen highly qualified and experienced people take an excruciatingly long time to find their next role. &lt;span>;O&lt;/span>;ne executive that Herminia recently observed thought, given his past experience, that he&#39;d be an ideal candidate for the audit committee of a big corporate board, but as the selection criteria shifted to include a greater diversity of professional profiles, he found himself waiting to get a nod.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Third, most companies today have elaborate, time-consuming, and unpredictable vetting processes, which can often add months at the tail end of the hiring process.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the senior-executive job market, it helps to recognize that in the messy meeting of supply and demand you have surprisingly little control. A great proactive tactic that can help you compensate for that as you do your networking is to fill your calendar with stimulating, parallel activities (community work, pro-bono consulting, short-term advising, adjunct teaching) in which you can have a more immediate impact and receive a more gratifying response. This compensates for the tedium, if not burden, of asking and waiting for help. It also provides battered egos with positive, if provisional, identities.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;4) Not wanting to put in the work &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Executives who are used to having things done for them often balk at devoting time to tedious work that they can&#39;t delegate. But to network successfully, you need to treat the task as fully worth your time and energy — and you need to be methodical and organized about it.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;To help with that, Spish has developed a networking process that consists of identifying and then contacting three kinds of contacts: information givers, door openers, and decision makers. Information givers are people who can tell you about the market, companies, and hiring trends; they can help you get smart and get over your fear of networking. Door openers are typically people you&#39;ve worked with in the past. They&#39;re responsive, and because they know you and your work style, they&#39;re willing to vouch for you and can introduce you to the decision makers.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;If you&#39;d like to use this process, the best way to start is by first making a list of all your employers, clients, and customers, and then by writing down the names of the people you met in those roles. You might find you easily come up with 100 names.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;No matter what approach you use to organizing, targeting, and segmenting your search, you&#39;ll always need to start by generating a long list of people you&#39;ve worked with and then methodically following a system for reaching out to them. Because it&#39;s a learning process, you can&#39;t plan it all out in advance; you&#39;re better off adopting a “snowball” approach” in which you ask each contact who else you should meet. This is especially true if you&#39;re looking in markets that are unfamiliar to you. In that case, you&#39;ll need to network in what Spish calls “the valleys below the clouds.” There are lots of opportunities in these valleys, but they unfamiliar and require exploration. If you don&#39;t explore them, you limit your options and can hurt your career growth.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;It&#39;s a high-cost, high-yield game, but it pays off. Spish has found that once you&#39;ve reached out to 50 or more contacts on your list, the network will start to reach out to you, at which point you can let the process carry you forward.&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;5) Overly focusing on “the narrative” &lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Once you&#39;ve made a contact, there is the important matter of what to say. All too often, executives spend the bulk of a networking conversation in small talk about shared contacts or experiences without getting to the point (that they need a new job) until the very end of the conversation. This is especially common when they feel they need to conceal the reality of what&#39;s going on — that they don&#39;t get along with their boss, say, or that they&#39;ve been fired. When that happens, they often enter into the conversation already on the defensive, they speak evasively, and they devote their energy to protecting their public image instead of learning all they can. The end result is that they waste a lot of their — and their contacts&#39; — time.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;Another unproductive tack is to spend 80% of your time trying to explain why you&#39;re unhappy, or leaving, or got fired — a negative approach that anchors your conversation in the past when it should be positive and focused on the future. You&#39;re much better off spending 20% of your allotted time explaining your situation and focusing the remaining 80% on what you&#39;re looking for instead.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;The best practice in networking conversations is to be direct, succinct, and positive. People want to know why you&#39;re calling them and what you want from them, and the more senior they are, the more likely they&#39;ll be to expect a brief, executive summary of this sort: “This is why I&#39;m calling you. This is what I want from you. I hope that there&#39;s enough in these two points for us to have a 10-minute conversation.”&lt;/p>; &lt;h2>;&lt;strong>;6) &amp;nbsp;Failing to tailor your story&lt;/strong>;&lt;/h2>; &lt;p>;Executives looking to make a transition often spend inordinate amounts of time perfecting a single script — the fabled “elevator pitch” about their “core skills and abilities.” They do this assuming that this script will make them universally relevant, but almost invariably what they end up with just isn&#39;t satisfactorily tailored to the needs of the receiver.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;We&#39;ve seen a lot of executives try to approach networking the way they would work with head-hunters: They write a generic email, just changing the name and one or two sentences, attach their resume, and send it out to a bunch of people. Likewise, many walk into a meeting and robotically state their one-minute pitch even if it doesn&#39;t fit the unique circumstances and requirements of the person who&#39;s listening.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;That just doesn&#39;t work. Yes, figuring out your core storyline (Who am I, and why am I here?) is important. But you can&#39;t assume that you&#39;re going to be saying the same thing about yourself to every person you meet. Nor can you assume that every listener is capable of translating your pitch into their own business context.&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;In the end, here&#39;s what you need to remember: It&#39;s not about you. If you hope to clinch a role for which you&#39;re truly well suited, you need to figure out how to make the switch from talking about yourself to talking knowledgeably about the company and its problems — and then to articulating how well equipped you are to solve those problems. As Spish has found, that&#39;s how you create opportunities for yourself: A large percentage of the most senior executives he&#39;s coached have ended up moving into roles that didn&#39;t even exist before they had their conversation.&lt;/p>; &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>;* * *&lt;/p>; &lt;p>;When you&#39;re a senior executive, networking is a delicate, complex, and time-consuming task. Ego and impatience, left unchecked, will sabotage your success. The best approach is to think of networking as an opportunity not just to scout out your next role but also to strengthen or deepen relationships you already have — and, even better, to add new relationships that will help you be a better professional in your new job and the others that come after it.&lt;/p>; &lt;!-- citation -->; &lt;/div>; &lt;/div>;</description><pubDate> Tue, 05 Sep 2023 21:25:02 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>