<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title><![CDATA[LessWrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community blog devoted to refining the art of rationality]]></description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com<image/><url> https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/v1497915096/favicon_lncumn.ico</url><title>少错</title><link/>https://www.lesswrong.com<generator>节点的 RSS</generator><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 11 月 8 日星期三 10:12:59 GMT </lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/feed.xml?view=rss&amp;karmaThreshold=2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[Thinking By The Clock]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 7:40 AM GMT<br/><br/><h2>我。</h2><p>我确信《哈利·波特与理性之道》教会了我一些它所要教的显而易见的事情。然而，在我第一次读到这本书十年后回想起来，最让我印象深刻的往往是故事情节中间的简短、随意的片段。</p><blockquote><p>弗雷德和乔治忧心忡忡地交换了眼色。</p><p> “我想不出任何办法，”乔治说。</p><p> “我也不能，”弗雷德说。 “对不起。”</p><p>哈利盯着他们。</p><p>然后哈利开始解释你是如何思考事情的。</p><p>哈利说，众所周知，这需要超过两秒钟的时间。</p><p> <a href="https://hpmor.com/chapter/25">-《哈利·波特与理性方法》，第 25 章</a>。</p></blockquote><p>这是LessWrong式理性的第一堂课，实际上，由于我接触了HPMoR和序列，我开始尝试刻意自学。这实际上是“按时钟思考”的强大技巧。</p><p>我曾经将其称为“思考五分钟”，但这个技术名称用词不当。这实际上是对孩子的谎言。有时我思考的时间要少得多，大约三十秒。有时我会思考更多的时间，比如几天。尽管如此，当你第一次学习武术时，你可能会以一种尴尬、僵硬的姿势站立，不能转身或迈步，所以我首先学会了以五分钟为增量按时钟思考。</p><h2>二.</h2><p>当我第一次去健身房举重时，我和一个朋友一起做的。我认为这不会很好地发挥作用（我是一个很瘦的人），但我想取悦他们。我在他们指给我的长凳上坐下，紧紧抓住他们要我抓住的重物，把它上下举了一会儿。当他们说停止时，我就停止了。 “这似乎有点快，”我记得当时说道，“我们完成了吗？”亲爱的读者，我们还没有完成。当我第一次开始和另一个朋友慢跑时，这种模式又重复了。我不知何故期望整个跑步过程会持续下去，你知道，直到我们感到无聊，这很快就发生了。</p><p> （如果我可以说一句话来为年轻的我辩护的话，他真的没有听起来那么不健康。<i>足球</i>很有趣，我经常踢球。堆放干草堆给了我报酬，我很愿意只要有人告诉我，我就可以拿钱搬重物。）</p><p>因此，当我第一次遇到一项既不有趣也不立即有利可图的艰巨智力任务时，我可能会感到惊讶，我有点退缩了。根据记忆，那可能是微积分。我讨厌微积分。我会坐在桌旁做作业或为考试而学习，然后发现自己读了几遍问题，然后瞥了一眼时钟或渴望地看着电路理论教科书。 （我对“娱乐”的定义让很多人感到惊讶。）然而，当助教问起时，我会说我学了几个小时的微积分。我坐在桌子旁，不是吗？</p><p>就像坐在干草棚<span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefes9664i8v1r"><sup><a href="#fnes9664i8v1r">[1]</a></sup></span>的谷仓凳子上一样，无论你做了多久，都完全无法将草捆堆放好，坐在办公桌前盯着时钟也完全无法让衍生品的想法进入我的脑海。</p><h2>三．</h2><p>但你知道，这并不完全是上面引文中弗雷德和乔治遇到的问题，不是吗？他们大概在那两秒钟里正在思考。那么让我来谈谈文化人类学的一些巧妙的知识。</p><p>当两个人说话时，一个人说完和另一个人接电话之间会存在一段间隙。由于他们事先都不知道什么时候能说完，而且句号实际上也不会发音，所以听者必须等待一小会儿才能开始说话。如果听者等待的时间不够长，他们就会打断对方并与对方交谈。如果听者等待太久，你可能会陷入尴尬的沉默。</p><p>我以前真的不知道要等多久。有人告诉我，当我还是个孩子的时候，有人问我怎么样，然后必须等待半分钟（整整三十秒！）或更长时间才能开始说话，这并不罕见。当我说话时，我所说的话会是经过深思熟虑的、出人意料的。我认为发生的事情是，我不知道你应该在来回的谈话中快速做出回应。</p><p>我必须学会这一点，刻意强迫自己加快语速。有一段时间，我充分利用了不置可否的开场白，例如“你知道，我正在考虑这个问题……”，这让我获得了额外的宝贵时间来弄清楚接下来我想说的话。最终，尽管我的技巧得到了不错的提高，但现在我发现这种沉默和大多数人一样尴尬。对我来说，通常很容易根据对话的语气来匹配一个浅薄的、足够准确的评论，然后直接说出来。如果我这样做，那么谈话通常会顺利进行。耶，成功了！</p><p>然后，在一些有趣的哈利·波特同人小说中的这种简单的交流让我意识到，如果我在谈话中，我已经学会在一秒钟左右后切断我的想法，这有时会让我说出<i>非常愚蠢的事情。</i>一旦你意识到这一点，有时你可以通过设置稍微太快的谈话节奏并温和地引导他们停止思考，让人们自己说蠢话。</p><p>我有说过这是你可以对其他人做的事情吗？好吧，你猜怎么着——人们也可以这样对你。</p><p>也许我使用“按时钟思考”技巧的最戏剧性的场合是在工作面试期间。这是一次与多个不同人的多轮面试，此时我正在与人力资源部门交谈。我们进行了很好的交谈，讨论了我对办公室布局的看法，我对什么样的工作感到兴奋，然后他们问我，没有任何迹象表明这是一个不同类型的问题，我想要什么样的薪水。</p><p>读者，我可以看到明显的、足够准确的回应，这将使这场友好的对话继续下去。在到达面试之前我已经对此进行了一些思考，我可以快速取出缓存的号码，然后我们就可以继续交谈。我正要这么做。我已经练习了足够多的保持对话流畅的技巧。不过幸运的是，我还练习了注意到一个我不应该轻率地继续过去的重要问题的技巧。我并没有完全停止谈话，但我确实说了一个变体，“这是一个重要的问题，如果我们认为我们很合适，那么我不认为这会成为障碍。让我仔细考虑一下，我“会回复你吗？我很好奇你的想法是什么。” <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnreftgpq1onoglq"><sup><a href="#fntgpq1onoglq">[2]</a></sup></span> <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref9r1vrg46s4i"><sup><a href="#fn9r1vrg46s4i">[3]</a></sup></span>他们退缩了一点，我确实停止了谈话三十秒来真正思考我的答案。</p><p>在一个普通人的生活中，有很多时候，你会在谈话中被问到一个需要你思考的问题。对话流程的规范建议您最多思考几秒钟。当谈论天气或孩子们的表现时，这些规范很可爱，并且它们与如何最好地实现长期项目或如何解决难题的问题相反。</p><p>我在工作会议中使用了按时钟思考。 （Adam：“我们如何将此功能添加到 UI 中？” Bella：“作为侧边栏怎么样？” Adam：“太好了，听起来不错。” 我：“我有一个想法。让我们每个人都考虑一下花两分钟写下我们的想法，然后我们分享这些想法？”）</p><p>我在与女朋友的讨论中使用了“按时钟思考”。 （不，我不是在这里给你一个例子。如果你很好奇我的浪漫生活是如何运作的，我是多面体，请随时约我约会。）</p><p>实际上，你并不<i>需要</i>对话间隙的社会压力来使这成为一种有用的技术。这就是我看到人们最常犯这个错误的地方。不过，由于选择偏差，显然我没有看到其他人在独处时会犯那么多错误。</p><p>练习的技巧是发现你只是试图快速思考，并检查这是否是你想要更多考虑的决定。你想要训练的技巧是那一刻的注意，小小的警钟告诉你应该给出你的答复，否则当那个警钟充满<i>谎言时，这将是一个尴尬的沉默。</i>如果这是理性武术中型的一个动作，那么该动作将从提出一个问题开始，让你张开嘴快速给出答案，然后再抓住自己并花时间真正按时钟思考。</p><p>从五分钟开始。训练自己如何利用时间。然后练习较小的增量。不要让自己偷懒或分心。</p><h2>四．</h2><p>所有这些都是因为思考太快而需要放慢速度。那另一个方向呢？</p><p>有时我听到有人说他们已经思考一个难题数周、数月甚至数年。有时候那个人就是我！有人多年来一直在思考这个问题，而且好的想法正在发生，这可能都是事实，但我经常对此表示怀疑。</p><p>当我十三岁左右的时候，我妈妈给了我一把便宜的吉他作为节日礼物。我发现这个乐器很有趣，我尝试着玩它，看看它能发出什么声音。我当然听过吉他音乐，但我的家人或直接圈子里没有人演奏。在接下来的十五年里，我一直带着吉他，把它从衣柜里、宿舍床下或汽车后备箱里拿出来，摸索着调音，拨动几根琴弦，查找一两个和弦。 ，并享受它充满房间的声音。</p><p>你可以说我弹了很多年吉他，这确实是<i>事实</i>，但它会极具误导性。在最初的十年里，如果我有一百多个小时把吉他放在腿上，我会感到惊讶，而其中只有十几个小时是在教练或老师指导我该怎么做的情况下进行的。去年，我决定真正能够用吉他演奏一些音乐，上个月我花在积极练习上的时间可能比我拥有它的第二年花在触摸乐器上的时间还要多。</p><p>在我读到《HPMoR》中的这些台词之前，我经常会思考一些事情很多年，也就是说，我会把这个想法从后柜里拿出来，仔细思考一下，然后再收起来。有时我仍然会使用这样的语言，但现在当我真正想找到答案或用我的想法做一些事情时，我有了额外的版本。</p><p>想象一下这个问题，就像你正在练习吉他一样，你需要为下个月的世俗至日制作音乐。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref0a3qbk9pfb3"><sup><a href="#fn0a3qbk9pfb3">[4]</a></sup></span></p><p>如果你像我一样，这会让一些事情变得更加清晰。</p><p>心烦意乱的时候就别想这些了。采取某种方式记笔记或将信息带到下一次会议中。您需要清楚地了解“足够好”是什么样子，才能知道自己是否达到了目标。毫不留情地丢弃那些不会实现目标的路线，但也不要不断地用头撞在没有取得进展的同一堵砖墙上。当你盯着令人着迷的电路理论教科书时，不要对自己说你正在研究它，其中充满了基尔霍夫定律和戴维宁定理（微积分最终迫使我进行适当的战斗）等秘密，只是在等待你流浪。</p><p>这就是我在三十多岁时做出疯狂职业转变的想法。这是我在决定是否离开我的家乡搬到大城市时使用的方法。我选择了几个周末，尽可能让这些周末不受干扰，并使用秒表积极地工作整整两天。我期望能够取得真正的进展，即使这种进展是以排除某些事情或消除死胡同的形式出现的，而且我一直在努力。</p><p>从五分钟开始。训练自己如何利用时间。然后练习更大的增量。留出时间休息和维持生活，但不要将做饭与专注于问题混为一谈。</p><h2>五、</h2><p> 《按时钟思考》是最明显的心理动作之一，我可以明确地将其归因于尤德科夫斯基的写作。我希望我能向自己描述年轻时如何做到这一点，因为我会从这项技术中受益。由于缺乏时间旅行，我能做的下一个最好的事情就是用比尤德科斯基使用的更多的文字来解释它，以防有人仅仅通过阅读哈利和韦斯莱之间的对话就无法吸收核心思想并生成训练其反应的步骤双胞胎。<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Q924oPJzK92FifuFg/write-a-thousand-roads-to-rome">写下通往罗马的一千条路</a>，也许当所有其他路都失败时，其中一条会引导某人到达那里。</p><p>我认为这是最困难的部分。不是仅仅吸收这个想法，不是意识到它的重要性，而是练习这个动作，直到你在顶着社会压力或在思考其他事情时做到了为止。我最好、最喜欢的老师曾经给我讲过一个故事，他早上检查邮箱时在冰上滑倒，然后发现自己完美地向后摔倒。我相信，这就是正确的理性武术所要达到的根深蒂固的使用水平。</p><p>能够按时钟思考，即使在早上喝完咖啡之前感到惊讶。这就是我所渴望的。 Ars Longa——艺术是漫长的！ <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/DoLQN5ryZ9XkZjq5h/tsuyoku-naritai-i-want-to-become-stronger">Tsuyoku Naritai</a> – 我想变得更强！</p><blockquote><p>哈利说，你<i>永远不会</i>认为<i>任何</i>问题都是不可能的，直到你拿起一个真正的时钟，通过分针的运动思考它五分钟。不是比喻意义上的五分钟，而是物理时钟上的五分钟。</p><p> <a href="https://hpmor.com/chapter/25">-HPMoR，第 25 章</a></p></blockquote><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnes9664i8v1r"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefes9664i8v1r">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> 。 。好吧，如果有人指出这一点，这就是一个不准确的地方，这会让我烦恼。不，干草棚里通常没有凳子。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fntgpq1onoglq"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnreftgpq1onoglq">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>为了避免这听起来太老练，我承认我也排练过这个答案，这要感谢帕特里克·麦肯齐的<a href="https://www.kalzumeus.com/2012/01/23/salary-negotiation/">薪资谈判</a>建议。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn9r1vrg46s4i"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref9r1vrg46s4i">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>事实上，我对自己很恼火，因为我在上次面试时没有这样做。我看到了这个时刻，我标记了要考虑的事情，但我没有这样做，因为我非常重视对方的时间，而且因为我认为我们比典型的工作面试更加合作。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn0a3qbk9pfb3"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref0a3qbk9pfb3">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>对于波士顿和纽约市来说幸运的是，我不是这两个城市世俗夏至的主要音乐家。对于我能在波士顿的 Solstice 打球的情况，我既充满希望，又目前还没有做好准备。如果您碰巧来访，请随时打个招呼！</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/WJtq4DoyT9ovPyHjH/thinking-by-the-clock#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/WJtq4DoyT9ovPyHjH/thinking-by-the-clock<guid ispermalink="false"> WJtq4DoyT9ovPyHjH</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Screwtape]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 07:40:59 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Impressions from base-GPT-4?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 5:43 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>我想知道这里的一些人是否有机会使用 base-GPT-4（出于研究目的而非常有选择地提供访问权限）并且不介意分享他们的一些印象？</p><p>我知道有些人一直在玩它，但我从未见过关于印象和教训的讨论。我知道访问这个模型是非常重要的，但是给予了一些访问权限。</p><p>我想对于这里的很多人来说，听到这样的对话会非常有趣......</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/tbJdxJMAiehewGpq2/impressions-from-base-gpt-4#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/tbJdxJMAiehewGpq2/impressions-from-base-gpt-4<guid ispermalink="false"> tbJdxJMAiehewGpq2</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[mishka]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:43:23 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Quantopian contest, but for food intake and weight]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 5:41 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>十二年前，我每天摄入约 1200 卡路里热量，体重减轻了约 100 磅。残酷地令人不快和分解代谢，但大多是成功的。它正在悄悄回来。没有像糖水、快餐、外出就餐这样容易实现的目标。 </p><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/tcjcn2a8pa3fvuvuvya8" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/qjzgekq384xq6veejsrv 150w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/quuq13e9mignu8sxsshq 300w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/meqkpy9i9h5in1io5j6r 450w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/brl4w3bkwshixoz5s6wg 600w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/wgzjnd1pkjqedus3mgfj 750w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/gi9bmfrni3aw6vbucwvv 900w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/hfxon7g0p4g6htuv4vio 1050w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/jblrvixsnvxsjcyfi1js 1200w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/tgf4yoszh4o0n9nvxaea 1350w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/zs5lbaemlcyppmv3dvr2 1423w"></figure><p>从那时起，我<a href="https://www.myfitnesspal.com/food/diary/Lucent?date=2023-11-07">记录了每天吃的每一口食物</a>，无论是周末禁食时喝的 10 卡路里肉汤，还是暴饮暴食我最喜欢的深盘<a href="https://lucent.pizza/">“lucent”披萨</a>4000 卡路里，一切都使用食物秤，而不是一次不假思索地将油倒入其中。食谱或盲目地将花生酱涂在三明治上。这培养了超人的卡路里估算能力。 “你说这个是280大卡？尝起来有350大卡，我看一下菜谱……原来如此，<a href="https://www.kroger.com/product/images/large/back/1007426500157">食品标签上的酥油少了一半</a>。”我经常称重，拥有阻抗身体成分数据、来自间接热量计（<a href="https://twitter.com/Lucent/status/1721306149259981060">我现在拥有的</a>）的定期 RMR 数据、睡眠-觉醒时间、所有健身课程和每日步数。</p><p>直到去年，我还认为 CICO 是原因而不是结果。不管出于什么原因，我更饿了，或者意志力更弱，所以我必须忍受痛苦才能达到健康的体重。从那以后，我的信念转向了一个由未知的稳态控制的蜿蜒设定点。无论是<a href="https://slimemoldtimemold.com/">污染</a>、欧米伽比率、<a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1800033115">重力调节器</a>还是某种组合，我都非常想弄清楚。</p><p>理想情况下，庞大的纵向数据集包含数十或数百个重叠的微观实验（数月的生酮、周末禁食、低蛋白、土豆、一波又一波的单调膳食），这些实验加起来超过了在实验室测试单个假设数周的统计显着性。如果肥胖问题的答案需要复杂的重叠或条件序列，那么它可能隐藏在数据挖掘中并首先通过数据挖掘发现，而不是由聪明的假设者发明整套。您将很难找到更多或更好的数据来挖掘。</p><p>我今年 41 岁，<a href="https://ptable.com/">基本上</a><a href="https://flightaware.com/">已经退休</a>，<a href="https://github.com/Lucent/health-data/blob/main/background.md">没有处方药或真正的健康问题</a>，没有压力源，甚至没有重大的起伏。我有预算和时间来准备符合任何规格的食物，但不能（出于<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/vegetarian/35d7iq/">恶心/厌恶</a>）食用动物（35 岁）或鸡蛋（~5 岁）。乳制品我仍然可以接受，所以不要发送任何工厂化农场视频并毁掉它们。除非它是具有明显优势的基本补充剂，可以替代牛磺酸或镁等缺失的（动物）营养素，否则我不太喜欢补充剂。</p><p>回想起<a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20170805125439/https://www.quantopian.com/open">Quantopian 编写最佳股市预测算法竞赛</a>的乐趣，我想提供相同的内容，只是包含摄入量和体重数据。我建立了一个<a href="https://fitcast.com/sample.html">简单的拟合来使用摄入量和体重来预测 RMR</a> 。随着时间的推移，它会发生显着的变化，或者使用<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protein_leverage_hypothesis">蛋白质杠杆</a>来最大限度地减少总摄入量，减肥将是一个微不足道的练习。看起来更像是<strong>我的设定点只有在满足某些条件时才会向上或向下移动</strong>，并且我想<a href="https://slimemoldtimemold.com/2022/03/15/control-and-correlation/">找到正在工作的控制系统</a>。举个例子，纯粹是出于奇思妙想：</p><pre> <code>RMR_rolling = 2500 RMR_today = RMR_rolling if (trailing_average(omega-6:3, 30 days) >; 10:1) { if (yesterday_protein >; 50g) RMR_today = RMR_rolling - 500 } else RMR_today += min(max(intake - RMR_rolling, 0), 500) if (steps_today * weight_current >; 1,000,000 ft-lbs) set_point -= 0.1 lbs</code></pre><p>如果这么简单，也许我可以构建或外包它，但我正在寻找一位有兴趣和创造力的统计学家来设计<a href="https://github.com/Lucent/health-data/blob/main/theories.md">我无法想象的</a>控制系统。</p><p>就赏金而言，一个控制系统描述和测试它的代码（在统计上不会过度拟合）至少价值 2,500 美元。诊断要排除或增加的食物子集、要采取的行动及其精确值（步行 3 英里，将设定值降低 4 盎司），或可持续的、非悲惨的见解（只吃土豆？尝试了三次，数据就在那里）价值 5,000 美元。如果我能成功地将其付诸实践 6 个月而不会遭受任何痛苦（高度主观），并且它使我的设定点下降了超过 30 磅，那么至少价值 10,000 美元。如果在回溯测试中它可以根据当前体重、设定点、最近的宏观数据等预测今天的摄入量，那就太棒了。</p><p>我的幻想？模型会询问：您在 2020 年夏季散步时是否穿着加重背心，因为重力调节器低估了损失。或者，您这个月是否在高海拔地区度假？这些赏金是平庸的、技术上正确的结论的最低限度。为了真正改变生活的洞察力，让我可以随意生活，我愿意花六位数。我可以买潮药，但我首先想在出厂设置上尝试取得胜利。</p><p>我有<a href="https://github.com/Lucent?tab=repositories">技术能力</a>，并将尽我所能提供帮助。如果这种数据分析是您的驾驶室，并且此类游戏不适合您，那么我只会满足您的小时费率。如果您希望解决问题的一部分，例如将数据导入数据库或提取 PUFA 比率，则同样如此。</p><h2><a href="https://github.com/Lucent/health-data">摄入量、体重、步数、RMR、睡眠、锻炼的存储库</a></h2><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/quantopian-contest-but-for-food-intake-and-weight#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/v2LazrqH5odiYucaG/quantopian-contest-but-for-food-intake-and-weight<guid ispermalink="false"> v2LazrqH5odiYucaG</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Lucent]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:41:35 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How I Think, Part Two: Distrusting Individuals]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 4:06 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>我之前谈过电影，所以我想我会继续说下去。我与一个似乎不信任决定哪些电影赢得奥斯卡金像奖的人进行了交谈（在撰写本文时，这是一个由 7,000 多人组成的团体，他们必须拥有电影学分，并根据董事会的邀请加入投票池）维基<a href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Academy_Awards#Voters">百科</a>）。现在，我认为那些人并不总是正确的。我记得在<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rocky#:~:text=they%20would%20award%20the%201977%20Oscar">维基百科</a>上读到，他们中的一些人说，如果他们能回到过去，他们会投票给《总统班底》而不是《洛基》来赢得最佳影片。如果这是真的，显然<i>有人</i>错了。所以我不会对他们所说的话投入<i>太多</i>的精力。但我仍然相信，这可能是评判好电影的最佳方式之一：它们赢得了多少奥斯卡奖。</p><p>其他人都疯了。我疯了。我曾经对我面对面遇到的人所说的话投入了大量的精力。如果有人说某部电影是他们最喜欢的电影，我就认为这部电影可能不错。如果有人说某部电影不值得一看，我就相信他们。现在我只是点头微笑，让他们所说的大部分内容从我身边溜走并忽略它。这听起来很粗鲁。我想我可能会说“我会检查一下”之类的话。如果这个人更详细地描述了他们喜欢这部电影的哪些方面，比如它是如何成为最伟大的动作片，因为它对枪支的工作方式非常真实，或者其他什么，我会把它记在脑子里，稍后再查。</p><p>不要相信个人。尤其是当面交谈时。首先，这个过程中的步骤太多，很容易出现乱码。也许这个人只是有奇怪或不寻常的品味。他们也总有可能在撒谎或夸大其词之类的。当然，他们也可能记错了电影的名字，或者单独说错了。你可能<i>听错了</i>电影的名字，或者后来又记错了。这就是六种潜在的出错方式，而且还必须有大约五十种。</p><p>这样想吧。您可以轻松访问数十种不同的电影评级系统，在其中您可以了解数十万其他人对电影的感受。为什么您只选择其中一篇评论并相信<i>该评论</i>而不是该组的平均值？</p><p>现在，我认为当有人推荐一部电影时写下来是很有趣的，然后，如果我最终观看了它，请回去告诉那个人我看过它并且（希望）喜欢它。</p><p>好吧，电影就是这样。事实更糟。我认为人们对电影的感受可能是错误的（也许他们只是真的<i>想</i>喜欢它或其他什么，我不知道）。但在大多数情况下，人们应该被信任知道他们对某事的感受。但是当他们报道的不是自己的感受而是事实时呢？根据不同的人，他们有百分之五十的可能性是完全错误的。我曾多次对某人在谈话后所说的话进行事实核查，但他们坚决主张的内容根本没有事实依据。那么，即使他们明白了什么，他们正确记住并说出所有内容的可能性有多大？我的意思是，你稍后在大英百科全书或维基百科上查找它，并且它所说的与那个人所说的几乎完全相同的机会有多大？我想说相当低。即使他们所说的一切都是真的，总体信息也可能不是真的。他们强调部分信息重要性的方式可能有问题或者其他原因。</p><p>当然，你不能相信我，因为我只是一个人。我认为相信某人<i>写的</i>比相信他们<i>说的要好一点。</i>但也好不了多少。使用书写时，一些容易出错的步骤消失了，但肯定不是全部，甚至不是最重要的步骤。</p><p>有些主题的准确性可能与个人可以与受信任的网站相媲美。有些事情互联网根本无法做到（没有人工智能），比如量身定制的建议。获得不同人对政治问题或其他问题的意见可能是重要且有价值的。我不确定政治观点的选择偏见在网上还是在面对面的情况下更严重。</p><p>我想我信任别人就像我信任 Chat GPT 一样。如果他们说了一些有趣的话，我就会查阅并验证。他们可能听起来对此非常有信心。他们可能附加了所有这些细节，使其看起来更有可能是真的。他们甚至可能会引用他们的消息来源。但我的意思是，它们只是一种吐出信息的黑匣子。除非他们实际上是在您面前阅读网站上的信息，否则存在太多未知因素。</p><p>也许信任个人最糟糕的事情是它会像滚雪球一样越滚越大，人们开始重复他们听到<i>别人</i>说的话。也许最糟糕的是，当你真正相信某人时，后来发现他们完全错误可能会损害你们的关系。或者也许<i>不</i>信任别人是比疾病更糟糕的治疗方法。但我不这么认为。我仍然与一些我真正信任的人进行了一些非常有意义的对话，除了准确地报告自己的感受之外，我不相信他们会做任何事情。有时我会从人们那里学到一些有趣的事情，在查阅资料后发现这些事情都是真实的。这确实使得与某人进行广泛的事实讨论变得困难。我的意思是，我只是经常说“嗯，有趣”，或者“如果这是真的，我想知道这对 X 意味着什么”。有时我可以拿出手机并开始验证声明，这让我更轻松地提出自己的声明，总体而言让我更多地参与讨论。不过，这可能会让对方变得不那么有趣。或不。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FcZDnhot7cJSKK3ym/how-i-think-part-two-distrusting-individuals#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FcZDnhot7cJSKK3ym/how-i-think-part-two-distrusting-individuals<guid ispermalink="false"> FcZDnhot7cJSKK3ym</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Henage]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 04:06:13 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How I Think, Part One: Investing in Fun]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 4:00 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>首先，这些博客文章只是我大脑的转储页面。我不会担心编辑它们或确保它们对阅读它们的人有用。我会尽量不关心使用专业语言或类似的东西。好的，我们开始吧。</p><p>不久前（大约一年前）我改变了我的乐趣哲学。由于我的两个人生目标之一是体验世界上最好的地方（另一个目标是让世界变得更美好），“乐趣”是其中的重要组成部分。但我意识到，就像金钱一样，获得乐趣的最好方法不是仅仅找到一项有效的活动并一遍又一遍地进行它。</p><p>当你赚钱的时候，无论你在十二岁的时候能找到什么工作，都可能不如培养获得更好工作的技能对你有帮助（我猜，培养这些技能的一个好方法就是先做一份糟糕的工作） 。无论如何，比这更好的是复利投资。一份糟糕的工作（保姆）可能每小时赚 5 美元。一份好工作（会计之类的，我不知道）每小时可以挣 50 美元。但要找到一份每小时 500 美元的工作需要付出<i>很大</i>的努力。做一份会计工作，然后将大部分钱投资于标准普尔 500 指数要容易得多，这可以在你生命结束时带来 x32 利润（每年获得 12%，减去通货膨胀，十年内大约会翻倍，尽管我想我没有考虑复利。五年内每十年翻一番意味着x32）。因此，一名将所有资金用于投资的会计师每小时可以赚 1500 美元。这些数字都不是真实的（不过我认为 12% 已经很接近了），但这并不重要。回到投资乐趣。</p><p>嗯，我意识到，更重要的是，不是让我<i>现在</i>正在做的活动变得有趣，而是让我回顾它时变得有趣。我意识到我通常为了好玩而做的事情：玩电子游戏，在钢琴上弹我喜欢的歌曲，现在看来并不是那么有趣。所以我改变了策略。现在这就是我做事的方式：</p><p>我列出了一些事情，当我一天结束时回顾它们时，我很高兴我做了这些事情。还有一些更多基于努力的事情，比如“编写一个我最终完成的游戏”。但清单上仍然有很多“有趣”的事情，比如阅读、看一部好电影，或者和家人一起做一些有趣的事情。我将这个清单命名为“内省令人满意的事情清单”。即使是为了“有趣” “上面的东西，对他们来说有一个新的水平。当读一本书或看一部电影时，如果它具有影响力或具有文化意义，那就更令人满意。当与家人共度时光时，如果我们实际上是在互相交流，而不是，就像，都玩同一个视频游戏，但很少在游戏中见面，几乎从不说话。我还能够在列表中添加一些我确实喜欢但尚未被接受的东西我以前喜欢做“有趣”的事情，比如在 YouTube 上观看速成课程系列。</p><p>但投资不仅仅应该在一天结束时获得回报。希望这将在我的余生中得到回报。就像，我开始注意到我看的电影越具有文化意义，观看的其他电影就越有趣。我的意思是，每当一部电影提到《低俗小说》或《2001：太空漫游》时，我都会因为看过它而感到一点点快乐，而在回去看老的著名电影之前，我只会得到一点点快乐当电影引用那些老歌时，我感到困惑和感觉错过了一些东西。这是一个小例子。到目前为止，投资的大部分是能够与其他看过电影的人交谈，回想观看电影的情况，向尚未看过电影的人展示电影，通过每天提醒这部电影经历，以及很多只是对生活感到更快乐，因为我觉得其中有美好的东西，我经历过的事情（也许最后一个包括一点不健康的势利，比如“哈哈，我有精致的品味，喜欢电影”比其他人喜欢的电影更好”）。</p><p>我变得更加有意识地寻找优质媒体。以下是我所看到的三个层次：</p><p>糟糕：滚动浏览 Netflix，观看一部看起来不错的电影（有很酷的标题 + 封面图片 + 预览视频）。</p><p>好的：浏览 Netflix，观看一部看起来不错的电影，而且这部电影也被列为赢得了奥斯卡金像奖或在 IMDB 或其他网站上评价很高。</p><p>太棒了：访问<a href="https://www.imdb.com/chart/top">https://www.imdb.com/chart/top</a>并查看有序的电影列表，直到找到一部您尚未看过但也在 Netflix 上看过的电影（并且属于您喜欢的类型） ，最好）。类似的方法可以通过按获得最多学院奖项的维基百科页面进行排序来实现： <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Academy_Award-winning_films">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Academy_Award-writing_films</a></p><p>我和几个人谈论过我如何找到我想看的电影（我说的是“我用烂番茄来寻找评论家和观众评价很好的电影”），而且其中不止一个人纷纷表示“观众的评价或许更重要吧？” I think they are very slightly right (I would rather watch a movie with a 95% audience score and a 10% critics score than vice-versa. Actually, I&#39;m second-guessing myself now. Third-guessing myself? Maybe I <i>would</i> rather watch one hated by audiences and loved by critics.) but I think that the critics score highly impacts how I will feel about the movie a year from now if nothing else.</p><p> Of course, watching movies in this way will usually also make my immediate experience better (a couple of exceptions would be very old movies like Metropolis or old-and-interpretive movies like Persona, both of which I felt good about watching afterward but were kind of a struggle to get through).</p><p> I think maybe even looking back on movies that I&#39;d seen before beginning to use this strategy is better through this lens. That&#39;s just a hypothesis, though. Like, maybe the fact that I now put more time into remembering watching the Princess Bride than National Treasure improves my happiness?</p><p> At first I was worried about using up all the good movies right away. But I realized a few things. First, although it would be feasible to run out of the highest tier of greatest movies, it takes much longer to watch TV shows or read books, which I can fall back on if the movie quality starts dropping. And second, it&#39;s good to watch these movies now so that I have longer to attach positive memories to them. The movies I really like, I can have fun watching them again just a few years from now, even without showing them to someone new. I think that&#39;s the real investment. I&#39;m not all that old, so I was watching the Lord of the Rings trilogy from a pretty young age, and I feel like those movies are a part of me. I first watched the Star Wars movies later, so it&#39;s taken a few watch-throughs to start to feel like I really like them. I watched the Indiana Jones movies just recently, and although I liked them, I expect it will take a few more times until I <i>really</i> like them. I imagine it kind of like planting seeds that I hope will someday grow into big trees if I keep watering them.</p><p> I think this definition of long-term fun planting is easy enough to do <i>all</i> the time, aside from like paid work and sleep (even when eating, exercising, or driving you can listen to a worthwhile book). When I first made my list of Introspectively Satisfying Things, I decided to just never do anything that wasn&#39;t on the list. If I got tired of doing the hardish ones like programming, I would just switch to reading or watching crash course YouTube videos. I&#39;ve slipped a little on this. I probably spend most of my wasted time reading unimportant Wikipedia pages and things like that. But why should I settle for playing in the dirt when I can be planting seeds?</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/CYqFScdQKiyfeENSh/how-i-think-part-one-investing-in-fun#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/CYqFScdQKiyfeENSh/how-i-think-part-one-investing-in-fun<guid ispermalink="false"> CYqFScdQKiyfeENSh</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Richard Henage]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 04:00:27 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Concrete positive visions for a future without AGI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 3:12 AM GMT<br/><br/><blockquote><p> <i>&quot;There was a threshold crossed somewhere,&quot; said the Confessor, &quot;without a single apocalypse to mark it.  Fewer wars.  Less starvation.  Better technology.  The economy kept growing.  People had more resource to spare for charity, and the altruists had fewer and fewer causes to choose from.  They came even to me, in my time, and rescued me.  Earth cleaned itself up, and whenever something threatened to go drastically wrong again, the whole attention of the planet turned in that direction and took care of it.  Humanity finally got its act together.&quot;</i></p></blockquote><p> — Eliezer Yudkowsky, <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/HawFh7RvDM4RyoJ2d/three-worlds-collide-0-8">Three Worlds Collide</a></p><hr><p> A common sentiment among people worried about AI x-risk is that our world is on track to stagnate, collapse, or otherwise come to a bad end without (aligned) AGI to save the day.</p><p> <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/pause-for-thought-the-ai-pause-debate">Scott Alexander</a> :</p><blockquote><p> [I]f we never get AI, I expect the future to be short and grim. Most likely we kill ourselves with synthetic biology. If not, some combination of <a href="https://slatestarcodex.com/2018/11/26/is-science-slowing-down-2/">technological</a> and <a href="https://slatestarcodex.com/2017/02/09/considerations-on-cost-disease/">economic</a> stagnation, rising <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/bad-definitions-of-democracy-and">totalitarianism</a> + <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/theses-on-the-current-moment">illiberalism</a> <a href="https://www.theintrinsicperspective.com/p/the-gossip-trap">+</a> <a href="https://slatestarcodex.com/2019/06/07/addendum-to-enormous-nutshell-competing-selectors/">mobocracy</a> , <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/slightly-against-underpopulation">fertility collapse and dysgenics</a> will impoverish the world and accelerate its decaying institutional quality.</p></blockquote><p> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/users/disturbance?mention=user">@disturbance</a> in aa recent <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/A22bTHYLDdkeqFsLd/saying-the-quiet-part-out-loud-trading-off-x-risk-for">LW post</a> that got lots of comments:</p><blockquote><p> <i><strong>Statement:</strong></i> <i>I want to deliberately balance the caution and the recklessness in developing AGI, such that it gets created in the last possible moment so that I and my close ones do not die.</i></p></blockquote><p><br> A seemingly straightforward implication of this view is that we should therefore be willing to take on some amount of risk in order to build towards AGI faster than we would in a world where we had the luxury to take our time.</p><p> I think some of these sentiments and their implications are based on a mistaken view of the relative difficulty of particular technical and social challenges, but here I want to focus on a totally different point: there are lots of ways that things could go well without AGI (at least for a while).</p><p> Even if positive scenarios without AGI are unlikely or unrealistic given our current circumstances and trajectory, it&#39;s useful to have a concrete vision of what a good medium-term future without AGI could look like. I think it&#39;s especially important to take a moment to reflect on these possible good futures because recent preliminary governance wins, even if they succeed without qualification, are mainly focused on restriction and avoidance of bad outcomes rather than on building towards particular positive outcomes.</p><p> The rest of this post is a collection of examples of technologies, ideas, projects, and trends unrelated to AGI that give me hope and joy when I see them being worked on or talked about. It&#39;s not meant to be exhaustive in any sense - mostly it is just a list of areas that I personally enjoy reading about, and would consider professional opportunities related to them.</p><p> Most of them involve solving hard technological and social problems. Some are quite speculative, and likely to be intractable or extremely unlikely to come to pass in isolation. But making incremental progress on any one is probably robustly positive for the world and lucrative and fulfilling for the people working on them <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref4o93wh13dw3"><sup><a href="#fn4o93wh13dw3">[1]</a></sup></span> . And progress tends to snowball, as long as there&#39;s no catastrophe to stop it.</p><p> As you read through the list, try to set aside your own views and probabilities on AGI, other x-risks, and fizzle or stagnation scenarios. Imagine a world where it is simply a given that humanity has time and space to flourish unimpeded for a time. Visualize what such a world might look like, where solutions are permitted to snowball without the threat of everything being cut short or falling to pieces. The purpose of this post is not to argue that any such world is particularly likely to be actualized; it is intended to serve as a concrete reminder that there are things worth working towards, and concrete ways to do so.</p><hr><h2> Energy abundance; solar and nuclear energy </h2><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/rsTwJGdPqipt7PJs3/cl5ddygtfr1kzymxdhj4" alt="图像"><figcaption> From <a href="https://twitter.com/AukeHoekstra/status/1507047932226375688/photo/1">AukeHoekstra</a> on Twitter; global solar capacity added vs. forecasts</figcaption></figure><p> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/y4kYmFhqmA6gxsu9Y/radical-energy-abundance">Energy abundance</a> has the potential to revolutionize many aspects of civilization, and there are fewer and fewer technological barriers holding it back. Regulatory barriers (eg to nuclear power, and to all kinds of construction and growth generally) may remain, but in a hypothetical world free of unrelated obstacles, energy abundance is looking more and more like a case of &quot;when&quot; and &quot;how,&quot; rather than &quot;if&quot;.</p><h2> Prediction markets</h2><p> Robin Hanson has been talking about the benefits of prediction markets since 1988, but it feels like with the recent growth of <a href="https://manifold.markets/home">Manifold</a> and the continued operation of real-money prediction markets (PredictIt, Kalshi, Polymarket) things are starting to snowball.</p><p> I&#39;m most excited about the future of real-money policy prediction markets on all sorts of legal and governance issues. The possibility of such markets might seem distant given the current regulatory climate around prediction markets themselves, but that seems like the kind of thing that could change rapidly under the right circumstances. Imagine if, instead of a years-long slog through the FDA, the process for getting a new drug approved was a matter of simply convincing a prediction market that the efficacy and harms met certain objective risk thresholds, with private insurers competing to backstop the liability.</p><p> Assorted links:</p><ul><li> Scott Alexander&#39;s <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/archive?sort=search&amp;search=mantic">posts</a> on prediction and forecasting</li><li> <a href="https://www.baseratetimes.com/">The Base Rate Times</a></li><li> <a href="https://news.manifold.markets/">Manifold&#39;s blog</a></li></ul><h2> Space travel and space tech</h2><p> Kinda self-explanatory. <a href="https://www.starlink.com/">Starlink</a> and <a href="https://www.spacex.com/">SpaceX</a> seem to be leading the way at the moment, but I&#39;m excited to follow other private and national space efforts.</p><h2> Life extension</h2><p> <a href="https://twitter.com/bryan_johnson">Bryan Johnson</a> is all over Twitter these days, documenting his self-experimentation in a quest to extend his own lifespan, ideally indefinitely. This is also a <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/tag/life-extension">favorite topic</a> of OG transhumanists on LessWrong and elsewhere, and it&#39;s nice to see it get some attention from someone with serious resources.</p><p> I haven&#39;t looked too closely into the specifics of the &quot; <a href="https://blueprint.bryanjohnson.com/">Blueprint protocol</a> &quot;, but from a distance it strikes me as about the right mix of correctly combining and synthesizing a bunch of existing science in an evidence-based way, and mad experimentation of his own design.</p><h2> Occupational licensing reform</h2><p> A lot of <a href="https://www.cato.org/publications/facilitating-personal-improvement-occupational-licensing">occupational licensing</a> in the US and around the world is mostly about rent-seeking. Reform efforts have <a href="https://www.rstreet.org/commentary/occupational-licensing-reform-is-having-a-moment/">enjoyed some success</a> in recent years, and it&#39;s nice to see some feel-good / commonsense wins in US politics, even if they&#39;re probably relatively minor in the grand scheme of things. <a href="https://twitter.com/senatorshoshana">Shoshana Weissmann</a> is a great Twitter follow on this issue. More generally, efforts to reduce <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Educational_inflation">credentialism</a> seem like a promising avenue towards incremental reclamation of territory ceded to <a href="https://slatestarcodex.com/2014/07/30/meditations-on-moloch/">Moloch</a> .</p><h2> Automation of all kinds</h2><p> I think efforts to combine software, robotics, logistics, mechanical engineering, and the AI we already have to reduce the amount of labor that humans do, especially grunt work, is very cool and likely to lead to large and real productivity gains.</p><p> Self-driving cars and trucks are perhaps the flashiest example of this kind of automation, but I expect more gradual automation in restaurants, factories, cleaning, maintenance, and other areas of the economy that currently rely on a lot of relatively low-skill, low-paying human labor to unlock a lot of human capital. Avoiding squandering that unlocked potential or ceding it right back to Moloch will be a challenge, but it&#39;s a challenge that looks a bit more solvable with a lot more collective wealth.<br><br> Semi-related: <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/P98i7kAN2uWuy7mhD/ai-summer-harvest">AI Summer Harvest</a></p><h2> Charter cities</h2><p> Scott Alexander&#39;s <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/archive?sort=search&amp;search=model%20city">posts</a> on this topic are always a treat. More so than any specific project or proposal, what excites me about charter cities is the abstract appeal of starting from scratch. In software, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Legacy_system">legacy systems</a> often complicate and slow development of new features, and I think the same dynamic exists in many traditional cities. Beneath the streets of New York City are <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/08/18/nyregion/new-york-101-streets-repair-and-maintenance.html">layers and layers</a> of utilities and pipes, some over a century old. Charter cities offer an opportunity to start fresh: literal <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greenfield_project">greenfield projects</a> .</p><h2> Genetic engineering and biohacking</h2><p> In humans, plants, and animals. There&#39;s too much cool stuff here to talk about or even list, so I&#39;ll just dump a few links:</p><ul><li> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/yT22RcWrxZcXyGjsA/how-to-have-polygenically-screened-children">How to have Polygenically Screened Children</a></li><li> Gene drives to eliminate malaria or mosquitoes altogether: <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/gjs3q83hA4giubaAw/will-no-one-rid-me-of-this-turbulent-pest">Will no one rid me of this turbulent pest?</a></li><li> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/cLr6TJj2qRrBa3Wmu/intelligence-enhancement-monthly-thread-13-oct-2023?commentId=yLJvn42im5QiEf2uq">human intelligence enhancement!?</a></li><li> <a href="https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/sPnNyG79CcSZq9avo/lab-grown-meat-is-cleared-for-sale-in-the-united-states">Lab-grown meat</a></li></ul><h2> Rationality</h2><p> The original <a href="https://www.readthesequences.com/">sequences</a> hold up amazingly well, and modern LessWrong is still pretty great. I think there is a lot more room to grow, whether it is by writing and re-writing key ideas with better (or just different) <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@RationalAnimations">presentation</a> , spreading such ideas more widely, or developing more CFAR-style curriculum and teaching it to people of all ages.</p><p> Some of my own favorite recent rationality writing is buried in Eliezer&#39;s <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/SA9hDewwsYgnuscae/projectlawful-com-eliezer-s-latest-story-past-1m-words">million word collaborative BDSM fiction</a> , and could really use a more accessible presentation. (Though some of it, eg <a href=" https://glowfic.com/posts/5826">on Bayesian statistics and that practice of science</a> , already stands pretty well on its own, despite the obscure format.)</p><h2> Effective altruism</h2><p> Also pretty great. I could <a href="https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/8hvmvrgcxJJ2pYR4X/announcing-a-contest-ea-criticism-and-red-teaming">criticize</a> a lot of things about EA, but my overall feelings are pretty well-captured by adapting a classic Churchill quote: &quot;EA is the worst form of altruism except for all those other forms that have been tried from time to time...&quot;</p><p> I think an EA that was free from the threat of AGI x-risk for a while has the potential to be even more amazing. In such a world, my guess is that EA would succeed at directing a sizable fraction of the wealth and productivity gains unlocked by other areas in this list towards tackling a lot of big problems (global poverty, global health, animal welfare, non-AGI x-risks, etc.) much faster than those problems would get addressed in a world without EA.</p><h2> Cryonics</h2><p> A <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/A22bTHYLDdkeqFsLd/saying-the-quiet-part-out-loud-trading-off-x-risk-for#comments">common view</a> is that current cyronics tech is speculative, and a hard sell to friends and family. Another worry is that civilization hardly seems stable enough to keep you well-preserved and on-track to advance to a point where they will reliably bring you back as yourself, into a world you&#39;re happy to be brought back into.</p><p> Those concerns might be valid, but they look like problems on which it is possible to make incremental progress. If you mainly care about immortality for yourself and your loved ones, my guess is your best bet is to push hard for cryonics research and adoption, as well as overall civilizational stability and adequacy. Incremental progress in any of those areas seems far more likely to increase the likelihood you are eventually brought back, compared to pushing towards AGI as fast as possible. <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefpaj4dtv7wxe"><sup><a href="#fnpaj4dtv7wxe">[2]</a></sup></span><br>链接：</p><ul><li> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/2cYebKxNp47PapHTL/cryonics-signup-guide-1-overview">Cryonics signup guide #1: Overview</a></li><li> Cryosphere discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/ngtdNWeJCv">https://discord.gg/ngtdNWeJCv</a></li></ul><h2> Georgism</h2><p> Georgism and land value taxes are an elegant idea for aligning incentives, funding public goods, and combating rent-seeking. I think land value taxes are simple enough that there is some hope of incremental adoption in some form or jurisdiction in the relatively near future. A decent introduction and source for further reading is <a href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/does-georgism-work-is-land-really">this winner</a> from Scott&#39;s book review contest a couple of years ago.</p><h2> Balsa Research</h2><p> <a href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/announcing-balsa-research">Zvi&#39;s thing</a> , focused on addressing <a href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/repeal-the-foreign-dredge-act-of">low-hanging fruit</a> and finding achievable, shovel-ready wins through public policy. Whether Balsa in particular succeeds at its mission or not, I think it is an exciting model for how rationalists can enter the space of public policy-making and politics in an effective and robustly positive way.</p><h2> dath ilan</h2><p> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/tag/dath-ilan">dath ilan</a> is Eliezer&#39;s fictional medianworld. The defining characteristic is that the real Eliezer&#39;s most important personality traits are the median among the entire planet&#39;s population. Because Eliezer himself is unusually smart, kind, and honorable compared to the average earthling, the population of dath ilan is much smarter, kinder, and better coordinated as a whole compared to Earth.</p><p> Many details and features of dath ilan would probably look pretty strange to an average earthling. Some of this strangeness is due to Eliezer&#39;s <i>other</i> unusual-for-Earth traits and personal preferences, but the deeper lesson of dath ilan is that many of their systems of governance, coordination mechanisms, <a href="https://glowfic.com/posts/5826">methods of doing science</a> , and modes of thought are actually derived from a combination of reasoning from first principles and relatively few assumptions about human nature and behavior.</p><p> It&#39;s not that there&#39;s a particular &quot;dath ilani&quot; way of aggregating information or resolving conflicts or running an economy. Rather, the <i>desire</i> to flourish, cooperate, build, and enjoy the benefits of technological civilization and other nice things is common among a very wide distribution of possible humans. It might take a certain baseline level of population-level intelligence, coordination ability, and lucky history to actually achieve all those nice things, but civilizations which do manage the feat will probably share some commonalities with each other and with dath ilan that Earth currently lacks.</p><p> dath ilan is currently getting along pretty well without AGI, making it an inspiring picture of what one possible future of Earth without AGI could look like. In worlds where Earth succeeds in the long-term, I expect that it will share many features with dath ilan. But I think a more interesting and exciting question involves thinking about ways that the best versions of Earth and dath ilan will still be different.</p><hr><p> When I imagine a world that manages to solve problems or make significant progress in even a few of the areas above, I feel a lot more optimistic about the possibility of such a world confronting the challenge of building an AGI safely, eventually. And even if we still fail at that ultimate challenge, such a world would be a nicer place to live in the meantime.</p><p> If you&#39;re feeling despair about recent AI progress, consider turning some of your attention or professional efforts elsewhere. There are lots of opportunities in research, startups, and established companies that have nothing to do with pushing the frontier of AI capabilities <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefnh1xh2mnyvr"><sup><a href="#fnnh1xh2mnyvr">[3]</a></sup></span> , and lots of ways to have fun, build meaning, and enjoy life that don&#39;t involve thinking about AGI at all. </p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn4o93wh13dw3"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref4o93wh13dw3">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> Also, none of them come with the moral hazards, uncertainties, and<br> x-risks associated with working directly towards AGI.</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnpaj4dtv7wxe"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefpaj4dtv7wxe">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> My guess is that reconstructing a well-preserved brain and developing indefinite life extension technology for biological humans are probably about equally hard (ie both trivial) for a superintelligence.</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnnh1xh2mnyvr"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefnh1xh2mnyvr">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p> Even startups that are focused on applying current AI in service of automating and improving existing business processes in diverse industries are probably net-positive for the world under a wide variety of progress models, and likely to be personally lucrative if you choose wisely.<br><br> Though for both short-term viability and moral hazard reasons, you probably want to be careful to avoid pure &quot;wrapper&quot; startups whose business model depends on continued access to current and future third-party frontier models. But automating business processes or building integrations using current AI at established companies seems positive or at least non-harmful, as long as you&#39;re confident in your ability not to depend on or contribute to &quot;hype&quot; around future advances.</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/rsTwJGdPqipt7PJs3/concrete-positive-visions-for-a-future-without-agi#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/rsTwJGdPqipt7PJs3/concrete-positive-visions-for-a-future-without-agi<guid ispermalink="false"> rsTwJGdPqipt7PJs3</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Max H]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:12:42 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[South Bay ACX/LW/EA Meetup & Vegansgiving Potluck]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 2:30 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> Ilmarin House is hosting an ACX/LW/EA meetup and plant-based potluck. These are sort of parallel events; the meetup will take place as usual (ie unstructured conversation) except those who want to are invited to join us at the dinner table at five.</p><p> If you can&#39;t bring a dish (though that&#39;s encouraged), you&#39;re still welcome to have dinner with us. Either way, please let us know you&#39;re coming and what dish you&#39;ll bring (if any). If you do bring something (thanks!), please make sure it doesn&#39;t contain animal products and enter it <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1MYVK_plNVxHk_3RNLurUzYBa4H1qE2PgW-nBWORnkJ0/edit?usp=sharing">in the spreadsheet</a> .</p><p> As always, kids are welcome! Bring some friends if you think they&#39;d have fun. If you have questions or comments, please let us know at svmeetup@protonmail.com.</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/events/Df5mLGpnyyQkH7mwR/south-bay-acx-lw-ea-meetup-and-vegansgiving-potluck#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/events/Df5mLGpnyyQkH7mwR/south-bay-acx-lw-ea-meetup-and-vegansgiving-potluck<guid ispermalink="false"> Df5mLGpnyyQkH7mwR</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[IS]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 02:30:55 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Progress links digest, 2023-11-07: Techno-optimism and more]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 8, 2023 2:05 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> Again I&#39;ve been delayed in putting this out by travel etc., so it&#39;s a longer one with links from the last month or so:</p><h2> <strong>On the Progress Forum</strong></h2><ul><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/y4kYmFhqmA6gxsu9Y/radical-energy-abundance">Radical Energy Abundance</a> , by Casey Handmer</li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/qHmfwzbyKThD7sFye/faa-s-safety-philosophy-and-progress-in-personal-aviation">FAA&#39;s safety philosophy and progress in personal aviation</a> , by Eli Dourado</li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/oTrktskpBncRkpPFa/where-i-have-landed-on-ideas-getting-harder-to-find-in-a">Where I have landed on “ideas getting harder to find”, in a nutshell</a> , by me</li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/49tFxpkaxkQ748BAu/working-draft-of-getting-the-conditions-right-progress-in">Getting the Conditions Right: Progress in Weather Forecasting</a> , by Jeremy</li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/qamKuYPfYXgWjrE6C/something-is-getting-harder-to-find-but-it-s-not-ideas">Something Is Getting Harder To Find But It&#39;s Not Ideas</a> , by Maxwell and Connor Tabarrok. (“Clever, wonderful, and entertaining presentation of our paper,” says <a href="https://twitter.com/ChadJonesEcon/status/1712254915903738064">@ChadJonesEcon</a> .) Also, <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/5QpeG9tscYL5bJQef/did-medieval-peasants-have-more-vacation-time-than-us">Did Medieval Peasants Have More Vacation Time Than Us?</a></li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/wnfZPfs6ZXQx7AsaT/today-s-backwater-tomorrow-s-superstar">Today&#39;s backwater, tomorrow&#39;s superstar</a> , by Connor O&#39;Brien. Also, <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/WySpftT3vZiPARTyz">How does a society hedge its bets?</a> and <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/YW3pLDe7yJPnLCbje/industrial-policy-needs-immigration-reform">Industrial policy needs immigration reform</a></li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/tGP2TYNJQ6FXv6h7d/schadenfreude-versus-optimism-in-drug-development">Schadenfreude versus optimism in drug development</a> , by Alex Telford. Also, <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/Fby9MzPFo6XYKmmBA/should-the-uk-embrace-its-role-as-an-exporter-of-talent-and">Should the UK embrace its role as an exporter of talent and ideas?</a></li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/BbHx7zQ9WkFizyMEj/health-insurance-pricing-battling-the-snake-heads-of-hydra">Health Insurance Pricing: Battling the snake-heads of Hydra</a> , by Tina Marsh Dalton</li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/xJ5T9dGq3atfEWKhK/address-to-a-unitarian-universalist-congregation-on-my">Address to a Unitarian Universalist congregation on my Heritage</a> , by Matt Ritter</li></ul><h2> <strong>Other work from the Roots of Progress fellows</strong></h2><ul><li> <a href="https://kinetic.reviews/p/american-power-was-built-on-cost">American Power Was Built on Cost Overruns</a> , by <a href="https://twitter.com/Madeline_Zimm/status/1717327696361886046">@Madeline_Zimm</a> . (IMO, the biggest risk of running over schedule/budget is that your project will get canceled. If it doesn&#39;t, people will judge it based on what it accomplished and not care about anything else. <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1717389815446999204">Lots of great things were delivered late and over budget</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://www.palladiummag.com/2023/04/04/the-golden-age-of-aerospace/">The Golden Age of Aerospace</a> , by Brian Balkus</li><li> <a href="https://maximumprogress.substack.com/p/how-to-imbue-the-basic-models-of">How to Imbue the Basic Models of Biology With a Positive Vision of the Future</a> , by <a href="https://twitter.com/MTabarrok/status/1714623811826368980">@MTabarrok</a></li><li> <a href="https://atelfo.github.io/2023/10/11/progress-and-concepts-of-health-and-disease.html">Concepts of health and disease as a barrier to progress</a> , by <a href="https://twitter.com/Atelfo/status/1712233356790739436">@Atelfo</a></li></ul><p> Follow all the ROP fellow Twitter accounts via <a href="https://twitter.com/i/lists/1712437542530789529">this list</a> .</p><h2><strong>机会</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://arcinstitute.org/programs/coordinated-search-stanford-biomedical-data-science">Arc Institute announces a new call for applications for Core Investigators</a> , “scientific leaders who are empowered to tackle curiosity driven research” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/arcinstitute/status/1708969505953841564">@arcinstitute</a> ). Their new building <a href="https://twitter.com/patrickc/status/1715464343314448531">officially opened recently</a></li><li> Speculative Technologies launches the <a href="https://spec.tech/brains">“Brains” Coordinated Research Accelerator</a> “to help people with ambitious research ideas refine them and find a place to execute on them in government organizations, nonprofits, and beyond” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/Spec__Tech/status/1714304105529663814">@Spec__Tech</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://jobs.lever.co/convergentresearch/e9285aad-502f-4a63-9c80-df8015828278?lever-origin=applied&amp;lever-source%5B%5D=X">Convergent Research is hiring a Launch Manager</a> to “work closely with each new FRO as it starts as well as the whole CR team” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/AGamick/status/1715378776442364034">@AGamick</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://worldsfair.notion.site/Chief-of-Staff-02fd225cad8b41f1bcb30a7ce83ed573">The World&#39;s Fair Co. is hiring a Chief of Staff</a> to help scale their projects (via <a href="https://twitter.com/camwiese/status/1717197070577045984">@camwiese</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/gdb/status/1717597476088422485">OpenAI is hiring</a> for “a new quantitative &amp; evidence-driven approach to AI safety.” Related, <a href="https://openai.com/blog/frontier-model-forum-updates">their $10M AI Safety fund</a></li><li> <a href="https://ourworldindata.org/communications-outreach-manager-q4-2023">Our World in Data is hiring a Communications &amp; Outreach Manager</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/MaxCRoser/status/1712073238153437620">@MaxCRoser</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://www.consciousrepository.com/p/a-little-ship-called-weird-biology">A new biology lab in St. Louis</a> for any “renegade scientist who wants to find a way to just <i>do the science</i> without starting a company” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/BenAnderson421/status/1715770301148016697">@BenAnderson421</a> )</li></ul><h2> <strong>Announcements</strong></h2><ul><li> <a href="https://scrollprize.org/firstletters">The Vesuvius Challenge has read the first word from an unopened Herculaneum scroll</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/natfriedman/status/1712470683207532906">@natfriedman</a> ). The word is “πορφυρας” which means “purple dye” or “cloths of purple.” (Why would purple be a topic of interest? In the ancient world, purple dye was made from mollusk mucus. <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1712555634879828326">It took roughly <i>9,000</i> mollusks per <i>gram</i> of this dye, making it labor-intensive, and therefore expensive, and therefore high-status—reserved only for royalty.</a> )</li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8Pnao7bUAANEgr.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/qsxg4ra34m37rj8vy3on" alt=""></a></p><ul><li> <a href="https://experiment.com/programs/climate-biotech-garden-proteins">Homeworld publishes over 50 proposals</a> from a program focused on protein engineering (via <a href="https://twitter.com/HomeworldBio/status/1717631733422575847">@HomeworldBio</a> )</li><li> A student team at Berkeley <a href="https://twitter.com/LanderChallenge/status/1711473632025759877">won the first Lander Challenge prize</a> for reusable rockets</li></ul><h2><strong>消息</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/first-malaria-vaccine-slashes-early-childhood-deaths">First malaria vaccine slashes early childhood mortality</a> : Huge analysis of RTS,S in Africa shows it <strong>decreased toddler deaths by 13%</strong> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/michael_nielsen/status/1717199823131295922">@michael_nielsen</a> ). Related, Alex Tabarrok makes <a href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/10/what-is-an-emergency-the-case-of-rapid-malaria-vaccination.html">the case for rapid malaria vaccination</a></li><li> <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/news-release/nasas-bennu-asteroid-sample-contains-carbon-water/">More carbon than expected and an abundance of water were found in the 4.5-billion-year-old asteroid sample returned to Earth by OSIRIS-REx</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/NASA/status/1712140634952282306">@NASA</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://nbcbayarea.com/investigations/googles-waymo-safety-study-on-driverless-cars/3311188">Swiss Re says that “Waymo&#39;s driverless vehicles file 76% fewer property damage claims compared to human-driven cars”</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/devonzuegel/status/1716905985175101627">@devonzuegel</a> ). And <a href="https://getcruise.com/news/blog/2023/human-ridehail-crash-rate-benchmark/">Cruise publishes a white paper</a> claiming their AVs “outperform humans in a comparable driving environment” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/kvogt/status/1707103740879405440">@kvogt</a> ). After this was published, however, <a href="https://getcruise.com/news/blog/2023/a-detailed-review-of-the-recent-sf-hit-and-run-incident/">a Cruise car was involved in an accident in SF</a> ; California suspended Cruise&#39;s license, and then Cruise decided to pause operations nationwide. I don&#39;t know whether AVs are truly safer than human drivers yet, but I am confident they will get there, because every time we solve a problem like this, we can solve it <i>for good</i> . AVs never forget their training, while every day first-time human drivers are out on the road.</li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/NobelPrize/status/1711317572287611223">Claudia Goldin won the economics Nobel</a> “for having advanced our understanding of women&#39;s labour market outcomes.” Her work “showed that female participation in the labour market did not have an upward trend over a 200 year period, but instead forms a U-shaped curve” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/NobelPrize/status/1711317803267948617">@NobelPrize</a> )</li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F7_SdXxW8AAEe6Q.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/nrsatc0uv2a55xcm6uzh" alt=""></a></p><h2> <strong>Techno-optimism</strong></h2><ul><li> <a href="https://a16z.com/the-techno-optimist-manifesto/">Marc Andreessen publishes “The Techno-Optimist Manifesto”</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/pmarca/status/1713930459779129358">@pmarca</a> )</li><li> Stewart Brand calls it <a href="https://twitter.com/stewartbrand/status/1713975757012385826">“clarifying and self-consistent” but “incomplete”</a></li><li> Ben Reinhardt <a href="https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/ws58tgsksp9550i0iucz0/The-Techno-Optimist-Manifesto-Andreessen-Horowitz.pdf?rlkey=1xgf2nrd8iicwd9ek4v6of0uq&amp;dl=0">responds with an annotated copy</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/Ben_Reinhardt/status/1714462378346090514">@Ben_Reinhardt</a> )</li><li> Virginia Postrel <a href="https://vpostrel.substack.com/p/an-english-major-reads-the-techno">calls it a Rorschach test</a></li><li> Matt Yglesias says <a href="https://www.slowboring.com/p/the-techno-optimists-fallacy">it commits a fallacy</a></li><li> Ezra Klein <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/10/26/opinion/marc-andreessen-reactionary-futurism.html">calls it “reactionary futurism”</a></li><li> Jim Pethokoukis says it&#39;s <a href="https://fasterplease.substack.com/p/critics-of-marc-andreessens-techno">basic economics</a></li><li> Noah Smith <a href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/thoughts-on-techno-optimism">gives his thoughts</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/chrisalbon/status/1715780020877304198">Chris Albon tries to explain</a> why Andreessen mentioned “tech ethics” in a section titled “The Enemy”</li></ul><p> <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1714046087248453786">More discussion on the Progress Forum</a> . I have not written a response yet, but see my previous writing on <a href="https://rootsofprogress.org/%7B%20post_url%202020-07-25-descriptive-vs-prescriptive-optimism%20%%7D">different forms of optimism</a> and on <a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/07/13/1028295/proud-solutionist-history-technology-industry/">“solutionism” as a third way</a> between complacent optimism and defeatist pessimism.</p><h2><strong>文件</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31803">An Economic View of Corporate Social Impact</a> : “We find that consumer surplus is the primary component of social impact (dwarfing profits, worker surplus, and externalities)” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/dylanmatt/status/1717017823505989754">@dylanmatt</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31758">One Giant Leap: Emancipation and Aggregate Economic Gains</a> : “We re-characterize American slavery as inefficient, whereby emancipation generated substantial aggregate economic gains” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/Rick__Hornbeck/status/1712541669525172605">@Rick__Hornbeck</a> )</li></ul><h2> <strong>Podcasts</strong></h2><ul><li> <a href="https://www.notboring.co/p/age-of-miracles">Introducing: Age of Miracles</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/packyM/status/1712813829585813618">@packyM</a> ). “Each season, we&#39;re diving into one frontier industry that will shape our superabundant future.” Season 1 is on nuclear, with <a href="https://twitter.com/juliadewahl/status/1717899129454833824">@juliadewahl</a> (who was inspired in part by <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7tYlXY19I3c&amp;ab_channel=SalemCenterforPolicy">my nuclear talk</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hata-Z6G8lE&amp;ab_channel=EnergyImpactCenter">Bret Kugelmass interiews Eli Dourado for Titans of Nuclear</a> , self-recommending (via <a href="https://twitter.com/elidourado/status/1711402001014091785">@elidourado</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://hearthisidea.com/episodes/dattani/">Saloni Dattani on “Hear This Idea” talking about the history of malaria</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/salonium/status/1715086279417684343">@salonium</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://chartercitiesinstitute.org/podcast/charter-cities-podcast-episode-59-lant-pritchett-on-economic-growth-charter-cities-and-state-capability/">Lant Pritchett on economic growth, charter cities, labor mobility, and state capability with the Charter Cities Institute</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/kurtislockhart/status/1717233490452730197">@kurtislockhart</a> )</li><li> <a href="https://www.dwarkeshpatel.com/p/grant-sanderson">Dwarkesh interviews Grant Sanderson of 3blue1brown</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/dwarkesh_sp/status/1712471643514458464">@dwarkesh_sp</a> )</li></ul><h2><strong>文章</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://www.ageofinvention.xyz/p/age-of-invention-lessons-from-the">Lessons from the Rise of Coal</a> (by <a href="https://twitter.com/antonhowes/status/1717252635214885195">@antonhowes</a> )</li><li> Ben Southwood says <a href="https://www.bensouthwood.co.uk/p/why-induced-demand-is-fake">induced demand is fake</a> but also <a href="https://www.bensouthwood.co.uk/p/when-roads-are-bad">sometimes roads are bad</a></li><li> “Unlike other antivenom treatments which are specific to a type of snake, varespladib methyl is capable of curing a broad spectrum of bites from different snake species. This means that the infamous line found in older first-aid manuals for treating snake bites (&#39;If possible, catch the snake…&#39; – so that the doctors can identify which antivenom to give), can now thankfully be ignored.” <a href="https://www.chm.bris.ac.uk/motm/varespladib-methyl/varespladib-methylh.htm">Varespladib methyl is the molecule of the month</a></li><li> <a href="https://henrysward.medium.com/what-i-tell-employees-about-negative-press-7c134e7a601c">Carreyou&#39;s work on Theranos “changed everything for tech reporters. Their career path changed from reporting interesting technology trends to exposing corruption in tech companies”</a></li></ul><h2> <strong>Micro-essays from me</strong></h2><ul><li> “What is progress?” I don&#39;t think there&#39;s much difficulty in the concept of “progress,” it just means a movement forward along some path. The difficulty is in: which path, toward what end? There&#39;s also not much difficulty in understanding what progress means in science, technology, or the economy: it is an advance in our knowledge and capabilities, our ability to understand and manipulate/control the world. The difficulty is in defining <i>human</i> progress, and understanding how it relates to the other forms. In general, I would say that human progress is anything that helps people live better lives: longer, healthier, happier lives; lives with more choice and opportunity; lives of thriving and flourishing. ( <a href="https://www.threads.net/@jasoncrawford/post/Cy91uDoslQS">Threads</a> )</li><li> When we think about “state capacity”, we should make a distinction between state <i>effectiveness</i> and state <i>scope</i> . If a given function (building infrastructure, responding to pandemics, etc.) is a government function, then it is a government <i>responsibility</i> , and it&#39;s important for government to be good and effective at that thing, and not be interfered with. But separately we can debate which functions are good ones to give to the government and which are better private. I find that the concept of “capacity” can blur these distinctions. ( <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1712108974479204565">Twitter</a> , <a href="https://www.threads.net/@jasoncrawford/post/CyQu_3UL6Ld">Threads</a> )</li></ul><h2><strong>查询</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1712873776843502079">John Carmack&#39;s book challenge</a> : “I appreciate that there are many people who roll their eyes at my optimistic-libertarian-technological-triumphalist take on things … suggest a book for me to read that you think will challenge my worldview”</li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/Ben_Reinhardt/status/1711752246239662509">Historical examples of technological bottlenecks and key risks?</a> Related, <a href="https://twitter.com/Ben_Reinhardt/status/1717928053391679559">examples of small differences making the difference in a technology&#39;s ability to get out of R&amp;D and into the real world?</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/michael_nielsen/status/1716591706668425279">How efficient is CRISPR editing in vivo? How far are we from being able to edit every cell in a complex organism?</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1715332984461472221">How much of “we don&#39;t build beautiful buildings anymore” comes down to local building restrictions?</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/maryrosemilkovi/status/1714633811273867599">Is there a case for suing NEPA a la Held v. Montana?</a></li><li> <a href="https://progressforum.org/posts/KJJiGjqsDs5XeNmPz/solved-and-unsolved-externality-problems">Well-known examples of externalities (positive and negative, solved and unsolved)?</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/kenshirriff/status/1711809521260318772">Can anyone identify this vintage computer?</a></li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8GRjjjbgAMHcjx.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/spywdi2u0mona1sa6fvz" alt=""></a></p><h2><strong>社交媒体</strong></h2><ul><li><a href="https://twitter.com/peterhartree/status/1711674136022409494">Cheap, nimble robots are coming soon</a> . Related, <a href="https://twitter.com/MorningBrew/status/1715377844413415862">Amazon has started testing these human-like robots in one of its Washington-based warehouses</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/timd_ca/status/1713729441342603746">Zooming around a bacteria cell</a></li><li> “Starlink satellites orbit at around 550 km of altitude. What if we could build satellites that could orbit at half that altitude? Cutting transmission distance in half would mean cutting power requirements for handsets by a factor of 4. There&#39;s enough atmospheric drag at 250 km that satellites there will deorbit within days. How do you build a satellite that can stay there indefinitely? Air-breathing propulsion” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/elidourado/status/1712499736802902498">@elidourado</a> )</li><li> “Most things with a combustion engine will be replaced with a battery in years to come. … Tipping point economics will be different for each use case. <a href="https://twitter.com/TimMLatimer/status/1714295272258572624">Currently: lawnmowers</a> ”</li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/culturaltutor/status/1715530213444964543">When pineapples represented the height of luxury</a> . “ <a href="https://twitter.com/culturaltutor/status/1715530250874995012">We are surrounded by things … which have become normal or even boring but which, to people in the past, were miraculous and delightful</a> ”</li><li> “22% of the children born in 1950 died before they were five years old. Since then, child mortality has fallen to 3.7%. Our animation shows this wasn&#39;t just due to progress in a few countries. People around the world have achieved improvements” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/MaxCRoser/status/1711290064074940641">@MaxCRoser</a> )</li><li> “Went to the pharmacy—naturally many people are coughing in the queue. But there&#39;s no airflow from outside, no air filtration system, &amp; no air purifiers on the ground cleaning the air so people don&#39;t infect one another. Future generations will look back and think we were mad!” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/robertwiblin/status/1716923155871416403">@robertwiblin</a> ) Like 19th-century hospitals, where you were more likely to catch something than to be cured. Related, “ <a href="https://twitter.com/robertwiblin/status/1712828006434005370">every cold and flu is a policy failure! If we were smart we could scale up far-UVC lamps and put an end to respiratory disease</a> ”</li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/vpostrel/status/1717313853950984485">Virginia Postrel clarifies some points about looms and Luddites</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/DrPhiltill/status/1714487581012820391">“You <i>can</i> work safely” is a better motto than “Safety is our top priority”</a></li><li> Related, <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1714325489513271443">good illustration of how un-safety-conscious people were 100 years ago</a></li><li> “Homelessness” is the most serious problem according to San Franciscans, and “too much construction” is the least. <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1715317366605705456">Does that give anybody any ideas?</a></li><li> <a href="https://twitter.com/nathancofnas/status/1717945088712618006">Large-scale immigration to Japan was spearheaded by Abe to make up for the low birth rate</a></li><li> “There should be a test like the series 65 that just gives you permission to access any pharmaceuticals you want. <strong>Accredited ingestor status</strong> ” (via <a href="https://twitter.com/devonzuegel/status/1712614663349776471">@devonzuegel</a> )</li><li> “In the 19th Century, the only planning requirement infrastructure had to go through was a committee of five MPs, who couldn&#39;t own land in the route, represent a constituency there, or have shares in a railway proposal they considered” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/bswud/status/1717510189744583130">@bswud</a> ) Related: “If we tried to build the Panama Canal today the plan would never pass an environmental impact review process” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/rasheedguo/status/1718267555926737185">@rasheedguo</a> )</li><li> “In America&#39;s history, we see celebration of competent, principled and strong men. Not only did we cherish it, we invested heavily in enabling more” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/codyaims/status/1712244726353863126">@codyaims</a> )</li><li> “When Bell Labs announced the transistor – arguably the most important invention of the modern age – the New York Times buried the story on page 46. Don&#39;t get discouraged if people don&#39;t understand the value of what you&#39;re working on” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/sethbannon/status/1712077475054858469">@sethbannon</a> )</li><li> “The Roman Empire produced several million square meters of polished marble slabs, this was possible because it invented and used water-powered stone-cutting machines” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lefineder/status/1718645162677621068">@lefineder</a> )</li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F9nXPVbWQAAljp6.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/eckrscf9wrpj9ph7vndz" alt=""></a></p><ul><li> “Computer vision has been solved” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/_vztu/status/1712682819800224011">@_vztu</a> )</li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8SrodnbEAARe2e.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/qd00ucvw5buf8g5fsfpu" alt=""></a></p><ul><li> The record for fastest train speed in the US was achieved by mounting two jet engines from a B-36 bomber to a diesel railcar (via <a href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1714286732416598047">@AlecStapp</a> )</li></ul><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8pd4Y9asAAZBH4.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/zqfyoi88pehyzigdgbmc" alt=""></a></p><ul><li> “If we solve immortality by, say, 2050, then nearly all of us, anyone still alive by then, are effectively children. We might live 1000 years. Meet our great^20 grandchildren. Journey to the stars.” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/CJHandmer/status/1712339219111370918">@CJHandmer</a> )</li></ul><h2> <strong>Quotes</strong></h2><p> From <i>Whole Earth Discipline</i> by <a href="https://twitter.com/stewartbrand/status/1714319540749013034">@stewartbrand</a> :</p><blockquote><p> Science is the only news.</p><p> When you scan through a newspaper or magazine, all the human interest stuff is the same old he-said-she-said, the politics and economics the same sorry cyclic dramas, the fashions a pathetic illusion of newness, and even the technology is predictable if you know the science.</p><p> Human nature doesn&#39;t change much; science does, and the change accrues, altering the world irreversibly.</p></blockquote><p> <a href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1712226726808342954">“Peanut butter killed formal rulemaking”</a></p><blockquote><p> The United States Department of Agriculture tried this when it was about to issue a rule regarding the minimum peanut content in peanut butter. Advocates wanted it to be at least 90 percent peanuts, manufacturers wanted to require only 87 percent peanuts, and adjudicating that 3 percent difference under the formal rulemaking process took the Food and Drug Administration twelve years of the 1960s and 1970s. The case went almost all the way to the Supreme Court, and the oral hearing alone took twenty weeks and produced a 7736-page transcript. (The advocates ultimately prevailed.) Since then, when Congress writes laws, it usually avoids the words “on the record” when it comes to rulemaking, leaving agencies the option to choose the informal “notice and comment” process. Unsurprisingly, it&#39;s chosen every time. Peanut butter killed formal rulemaking.</p></blockquote><p> (Although <a href="https://twitter.com/JamesBroughel/status/1712428822220468383">@JamesBroughel comments</a> : “Actually, the real reason agencies don&#39;t use formal rulemaking is a Supreme Court case called United States v. Florida East Coast Railway, where the court ruled agencies may use informal notice-and-comment rulemaking in all but a very limited set of circumstances.”)</p><p> <a href="https://law.justia.com/cases/federal/appellate-courts/F2/449/1109/240994/">Calvert Cliffs&#39; Coordinating Committee, Inc. v. US Atomic Energy Commission, 1971</a> :</p><blockquote><p> These cases are only the beginning of what promises to become a flood of new litigation — litigation seeking judicial assistance in protecting our natural environment. Several recently enacted statutes attest to the commitment of the Government to control, at long last, the destructive engine of material “progress.”</p></blockquote><p> ( <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1714333365980070080">Brought back to mind</a> via Jim Pethokoukis via <a href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/10/the-calverts-cliff-decision.html">Alex Tabarrok</a> .)</p><p> “The leadership of Operation Warp Speed made a lot of personal sacrifices to deliver a safe and effective vaccine in record time. And they get almost no credit” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1712576296218145016">@AlecStapp</a> ):</p><blockquote><p> When Slaoui had his job interview on May 11, he minced no words. “All I want to do is make a vaccine that helps our country and the world, he said. “I&#39;m not going to be afraid to break things. I have no political ambition.” If he had to hold meetings just to placate people, he was out. And if there was any political interference, he would resign on the spot. The other five candidates all expressed doubt about having a vaccine by the end of 2020. Slaoui alone said he could do it. He got the job. <strong>He resigned from Moderna&#39;s board and sold all his stock in the company, knowing that he was likely forfeiting a fortune. He also decided he wouldn&#39;t take a paycheck for overseeing the project.</strong></p></blockquote><p> <a href="https://twitter.com/stuartbuck1/status/1714069034822455576">Policies as “organizational scar tissue”</a> (from <a href="https://m.signalvnoise.com/dont-scar-on-the-first-cut/">Jason Fried</a> ):</p><blockquote><p> Many policies are organizational scar tissue-codified overreactions to situations that are unlikely to happen again.</p><p> The second something goes wrong, the natural tendency is to create a policy. “Someone&#39;s wearing shorts!? We need a dress code!” No, you don&#39;t. You just need to tell John not to wear shorts again.</p><p> Policies are organizational scar tissue. They are codified overreactions to situations that are unlikely to happen again. They are collective punishment for the misdeeds of an individual.</p><p> This is how bureaucracies are born. No one sets out to create a bureaucracy. They sneak up on companies slowly. They are created one policy -one scar -at a time.</p><p> So don&#39;t scar on the first cut. Don&#39;t create a policy because one person did something wrong once. Policies are only meant for situations that come up over and over again.</p></blockquote><p> “I think about this list from @elidourado a lot. Progress is a policy choice.” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1717591968253895062">@AlecStapp</a> , originally from <a href="https://www.city-journal.org/article/remove-barriers-to-productivity">City Journal</a> ):</p><blockquote><p> If we can&#39;t counterbalance the supply shock in every granular manifestation, we can at least take action to boost productivity and aggregate supply. Macroeconomic textbooks don&#39;t focus on this policy lever because they assume that the supply side of the economy is already optimized. Yet it is manifestly evident that American society is not maximizing its productivity. If we wanted to raise American productivity, for example, we could simplify <a href="https://www.thecgo.org/benchmark/the-biggest-no-brainer-in-all-of-energy-policy">geothermal permitting</a> , deregulate advanced <a href="https://www.nei.org/advocacy/build-new-reactors/advanced-nuclear">meltdown-proof nuclear reactors</a> , make it easier to build <a href="https://www.niskanencenter.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Reed-Transmission-Brief-April-2021-2.pdf">transmission lines</a> , figure out why high-speed rail is <a href="https://twitter.com/elidourado/status/1486535716410638340">so expensive</a> , fix <a href="https://www.thecgo.org/benchmark/why-are-we-so-slow-today">permitting</a> generally, abolish <a href="https://rollcall.com/2022/03/08/us-shipping-rules-complicate-bid-to-ban-russian-oil-and-gas">the Jones Act</a> , <a href="https://www.cato.org/commentary/americas-ports-problem-decades-making">automate</a> our ports, allow drones to <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/us-law-week/faa-needs-to-unleash-the-commercial-potential-of-drones">operate autonomously</a> , legalize <a href="https://www.mercatus.org/system/files/mercatus-dourado-supersonic-transport-v1.pdf">supersonic flight over land</a> , reduce <a href="https://www.brookings.edu/research/how-occupational-licensing-matters-for-wages-and-careers">occupational-licensing requirements</a> , train more <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/02/why-does-the-us-make-it-so-hard-to-be-a-doctor/622065">medical workers</a> , <a href="https://www.mercatus.org/system/files/Stratmann-CON-Barriers-to-Entry.pdf">build more hospitals</a> , revamp our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIzT-IlJsts">pandemic-response institutions</a> , simplify <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1536-7150.2008.00597.x">drug approvals</a> , <a href="https://www.thecgo.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Regulation_and_Economic_Opportunity_Blueprints_for_Reform_Chapter_9.pdf">deregulate land use</a> to allow denser housing and mixed-use neighborhoods, allow<a href="https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/636499/one-billion-americans-by-matthew-yglesias">more immigration</a> , cancel <a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2022/03/nasa-inspector-general-says-sls-costs-are-unsustainable">inefficient programs</a> , restrict <a href="https://www.thecgo.org/benchmark/a-2006-nasa-program-shows-how-government-can-move-at-the-speed-of-startups">cost-plus procurement contracts</a> in favor of more effective methods, end <a href="https://www.f35.com/f35/about/economic-impact.html">appropriations based on job creation</a> , avoid <a href="https://progress.institute/curing-alzheimers-by-investing-in-aging-research">political direction of scientific research</a> , and instill <a href="https://future.a16z.com/what-we-learned-doing-fast-grants">urgency in grantmaking</a> .</p></blockquote><h2><strong>图表</strong></h2><p>The original chart that inspired Steve Jobs to liken the computer to “a bicycle for the mind” (via <a href="https://heikelarson.substack.com/p/ride-a-bike-worship-on-wheels">Heike Larson</a> ):</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8mmj8IXYAA2evX.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/u9bu5vlft7kyohk64fzg" alt=""></a></p><p> “In late 17th century England the professional class was almost wholly literate, the latter spread of literacy was just a matter of all the other classes joining them” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/lefineder/status/1717282569467617718">@lefineder</a> ). Note in particular the growth of literacy among <i>artisans</i> ~1600–1700s. Part of what made the Industrial Revolution was the combination of abstract knowledge and craft skill. George Stephenson learned to read so that he could study steam engines, then invented the locomotive:</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F9UBx32X0AAJpyW.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/f65wgf3hneao3x2tp2ry" alt=""></a></p><p> <a href="https://humanprogress.org/dataset/arable-land-needed-to-produce-a-fixed-quantity-of-crops/?countries=167&amp;regions=2189&amp;view=selected&amp;y-axis-start=0">Agricultural land efficiency</a> (via <a href="https://twitter.com/HumanProgress/status/1712259816809255271">@HumanProgress</a> ):</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8MqFJgW8AAboZQ.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/c5wr8g4manqszpeolvf3" alt=""></a></p><p> “The classic urbanist story is that cars have become safer for passengers by becoming more deadly (bigger/heavier) for pedestrians. This data cuts strongly against that story. I presume the urbanist response is mostly that sprawl/car culture have decreased pedestrian exposure?” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/atrembath/status/1714693362618630511">@atrembath</a> )</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8vLr-hbcAAdYfv.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/jlydl1yt2xf6uywv3ins" alt=""></a></p><h2> <strong>Aesthetics/culture</strong></h2><p> “Serving human progress through photography.” TIME Magazine, Aug. 20, 1945 (h/t Laura London) ( <a href="https://www.threads.net/@jasoncrawford/post/CyO8H3mrkEK">Threads</a> , <a href="https://twitter.com/jasoncrawford/status/1711855132571259219">Twitter</a> ):</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8G6_f2WYAAX-Az.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/nwh1hn8se6vhkdzcfqkh" alt=""></a></p><h2><strong>乐趣</strong></h2><p>“On one hand, AI is going to be incredibly disruptive for visual artists, but on the other hand: Jean-Jacquet Rousseau” ( <a href="https://twitter.com/kendrictonn/status/1712047084143251673">@kendrictonn</a> )</p><p> <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/F8JnEleaEAABzwG.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/lovffcg0akw64m2kj9nc" alt=""></a></p><p></p><p><br></p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/progress-links-digest-2023-11-07-techno-optimism-and-more#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb/progress-links-digest-2023-11-07-techno-optimism-and-more<guid ispermalink="false"> qgfBuaKe8fhWjkGvb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jasoncrawford]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Wed, 08 Nov 2023 02:05:31 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Announcing Athena - Women in AI Alignment Research]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 7, 2023 9:46 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> Athena is a new research mentorship program fostering diversity of ideas in AI safety research. We aim to get more women and marginalized genders into technical research and offer the support needed to thrive in this space.</p><p></p><p> Applications for scholars are open until December 3rd, 2023</p><p> Apply as a scholar: <a href="https://forms.gle/HVZ4L6FeeBQc9yWd8"><u>here</u></a></p><p> Apply as a mentor or speaker: <a href="https://forms.gle/nF6u7qTgpSgk6KAWA"><u>here</u></a></p><p> Financial aid is available for travel expenses for the in-person retreat to those otherwise unable to attend without it</p><p> <strong><img style="width:77.22%" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/pJ9qWeBRRuvPvnoNK/ir6viglg8bsblwytib32"></strong></p><h3><strong>程序结构</strong></h3><p>A 2-month hybrid mentorship program for women looking to strengthen their research skills and network in technical AI safety research beginning in January 2024.</p><p> This includes 1-week in-person retreat in Oxford, UK followed by a 2-month remote mentorship by established researchers in the field, with networking and weekly research talks.</p><p></p><p> Athena aims to equip women with the knowledge, skills, and network they need to thrive in AI safety research. We believe that diversity is a strength, and hope to see this program as a stepping stone towards a more diverse and inclusive AI safety research field.</p><p> This program is designed to offer mentorship opportunities to technically qualified women who are early in their AI safety research careers or looking to transition into the field by connecting them with experienced mentors, resources to upskill, networking, and a supportive community.</p><p></p><h3> <strong>Who should apply?</strong></h3><p> Women and people of other <a href="https://wit.abcd.harvard.edu/mission#:~:text=What%20do%20we%20mean%20by,many%20other%20marginalized%20gender%20identities."><u>marginalized genders</u></a> that have some research or technical industry experience, and are interested in transitioning to AI Alignment research or have a bit of experience in the Alignment field but are looking for more support. We encourage those with a non-traditional background to apply and welcome interdisciplinary work in this field.</p><p></p><h3> <strong>Application process</strong></h3><p> Submit the online application questions - <a href="https://forms.gle/HVZ4L6FeeBQc9yWd8"><u>here</u></a></p><p> Complete an interview with the founder and one other AI safety researcher</p><p> Additional possible interviews with mentor</p><p></p><h3><strong>问题？</strong></h3><p> Email: claire@researchathena.org</p><p></p><h3> <strong>Why are we doing this</strong></h3><p> <strong>The current culture requires a shift to retain a diverse set of qualified researchers</strong></p><p> Athena aims to increase the number of women pursuing careers in AI alignment, which is currently a male-dominated field with a very specific culture that can initially come across as unwelcoming to those that aren&#39;t traditionally represented here. Women may have different hurdles to cross than their male counterparts such as implicit and explicit bias, different family and home obligations, unwanted approaches for romantic relationships by male colleagues, isolation, and a lack of representation.</p><p> We want to take steps to shift the current culture to one that values diversity and inclusivity through recruiting qualified women into the field through extended outreach, providing technical mentorship with an experienced researcher, creating a targeted support structure during the program, and continued role and grant placement support after the program. There are also opportunities for networking and collaboration within the larger research ecosystem.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Having diverse research teams and ideas is valuable for AI Alignment research</strong></p><p> Research has consistently shown that diverse teams produce more innovative solutions. When we have a diverse group of people, including women, working on AI alignment, we are more likely to come up with comprehensive and holistic solutions that consider a wide range of perspectives and people. When more women participate in traditionally male-dominated fields like the sciences, the breadth of knowledge in that area usually grows, a surge in female involvement directly correlates with advancements in understanding [ <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/culture/article/141107-gender-studies-women-scientific-research-feminist"><u>1</u></a> ]. Since there is a lack of women in this field, Athena aims to prepare women to join a research team or position after the program, where that team will benefit from this.</p><p></p><p> <strong>Research suggests that all-women programming can provide benefits to women</strong></p><p> Cox &amp; Fisher (2008) found that women in a single-sex environment in a software engineering course reported higher levels of enjoyment, fairness, motivation, support, and comfort and allowed them to perform at a level that exceeded that of the all-male groups in the class [ <a href="https://www.informingscience.org/Publications/175?Source=%2FJournals%2FJITEResearch%2FArticles%3FVolume%3D0-0"><u>1</u></a> ].</p><p> Kahveci (2008) explored a program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering and found that it helped marginalized women move towards legitimate participation in these fields and enhanced a sense of community and mutual engagement [ <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/pdfdirect/10.1002/sce.20234"><u>2</u></a> ].</p><p></p><p> <strong>Creating more representation for future policy advisors and makers</strong></p><p> As government awareness and sense of urgency grows for AI-related decision-making and legislation, we need a diverse range of experts in the field to help policy makers make informed decisions. If we only have a specific type of person in this position, the policies will reflect that, maybe to our detriment. Women&#39;s participation in decision-making is highly beneficial and their role in designing and applying public policies has a positive impact on people&#39;s lives</p><p> “It is not about men against women, but there is evidence to show through research that when you have more women in public decision-making, you get policies that benefit women, children and families in general. When women are in sufficient numbers in parliaments they promote women&#39;s rights legislation, children&#39;s rights and they tend to speak up more for the interests of communities, local communities, because of their close involvement in community life. [ <a href="https://ourworld.unu.edu/en/everyone-benefits-from-more-women-in-power"><u>2</u></a> ]<br></p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/pJ9qWeBRRuvPvnoNK/announcing-athena-women-in-ai-alignment-research#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/pJ9qWeBRRuvPvnoNK/announcing-athena-women-in-ai-alignment-research<guid ispermalink="false"> pJ9qWeBRRuvPvnoNK</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Claire Short]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:46:42 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Vote on Interesting Disagreements]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on November 7, 2023 9:35 PM GMT<br/><br/><div><style>

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .InlineReactSelectionWrapper-root {
  flex: 1 1 70%;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemDate-root {
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .AgreementVoteAxis-agreementSection {
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItem-body {
  display: flex;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemMeta-root {
  order: 2;
  margin-left: auto;
  margin-right: 0px;
  flex-wrap: wrap;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemMeta-rightSection {
  position: inherit;
  top: 0px;
  right: 0px;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemMeta-username {
  text-align: center;
  word-wrap: break-word;
  max-width: 100px;
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemMeta-collapse {
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentBody-commentStyling {
  margin-bottom: 8px;
  order: 1;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node {
  margin-bottom: 0px !important;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .comments-item-reply-link {
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .NamesAttachedReactionsCommentBottom-addReactionButton {

}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .CommentOutdatedWarning-outdatedWarning {
  display: none!important;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .NamesAttachedReactionsCommentBottom-footerReactions
 {
  display: flex;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node span:has(img[src*="/reactionImages/nounproject/x.svg"]) {
  order: 2;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node span:has(img[src*="/reactionImages/nounproject/check.svg"]) {
  order: 1;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node span:has(> .NamesAttachedReactionsCommentBottom-addReactionButton) {
  order: 3;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .NamesAttachedReactionsCommentBottom-overviewButton {
  display: none;
}

.InlineReactSelectionWrapper-button {
  display: none;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .CommentsItem-replyLink {
  font-size: 0px;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL a.comments-item-reply-link.CommentsItem-replyLink:before {
    content: "Add Poll Option";
    font-size: 16px;
    padding: 10px;
    border: 1px solid;
    border-radius: 5px;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .CommentsItem-bottom {
  margin-top: 20px;
  margin-bottom: 15px;
}

#NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItem-bottom {
  margin-top: 0px!important;
  margin-bottom: 0px!important;
}

@media (min-width: 768px) {
  #NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItemMeta-root {
    flex-wrap: nowrap!important;
  }
}

@media (max-width: 768px) {
 #NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL .comments-node .CommentsItem-body {
  display: flex;
  flex-direction: row;
  flex-wrap: wrap;
 }
}

</style><p>Do you have a question you&#39;d like to see argued about? Would you like to indicate your position and <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/dialogues">discuss</a> it with someone who disagrees?</p><p> Add poll options to <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hc9nMipTXy2sm3tJb/disagreements-elicitation-thread?commentId=NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL">the thread below</a> to find questions with lots of interest and disagreement.</p><h2> How to use the poll </h2><figure class="image"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/vo1evlhtxxz0q94oryxv" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/vbk76agmvcdtoiemfp4m 140w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/d23zwglivx84bl0auug1 280w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/qnfr09uhe32sksbrfhgy 420w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/obchknfv9slnt1ej6jen 560w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/lixbfnxp0z8xsg50n1ey 700w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/nyekulxfyuxinxds9xtz 840w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/gs9orbjbfh1zzibyjmz0 980w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/snyjmzczvni0plmthsxr 1120w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/awphk3r6jq9guer5jjlp 1260w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NtsPs9wcwrpeK6KYL/mppvptu0sxm78f1zrinx 1392w"></figure><ol><li> <strong>Reacts:</strong> Click on the <strong>agree/disagree reacts</strong> to help people see how much disagreement there is on the topic.</li><li> <strong>Karma:</strong> Upvote positions that <strong>you&#39;d like to read dialogues</strong> about.</li><li> <strong>New Poll Option:</strong> Add new positions for people to take sides on. <strong>Please add the agree/disagree reacts</strong> to new poll options you make.</li></ol><p> The goal is to show people where a lot of interesting disagreement lies. This can be used to find discussion and <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/dialogues">dialogue</a> topics in the future.</p></div><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hc9nMipTXy2sm3tJb/vote-on-interesting-disagreements#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hc9nMipTXy2sm3tJb/vote-on-interesting-disagreements<guid ispermalink="false"> hc9nMipTXy2sm3tJb</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben Pace]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>