<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title><![CDATA[LessWrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community blog devoted to refining the art of rationality]]></description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com<image/><url> https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/v1497915096/favicon_lncumn.ico</url><title>少错</title><link/>https://www.lesswrong.com<generator>节点的 RSS</generator><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 10 月 10 日，星期二 20:11:19 GMT </lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/feed.xml?view=rss&amp;karmaThreshold=2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[Announcing MIRI’s new CEO and leadership team]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 7:22 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> 2023 年，MIRI 将重点转向广泛的公众交流——例如，请参阅我们<a href="https://www.ted.com/talks/eliezer_yudkowsky_will_superintelligent_ai_end_the_world?language=en">最近的 TED 演讲</a>，以及我们在《时代》杂志上发表的文章“ <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oM9pEezyCb4dCsuKq/pausing-ai-developments-isn-t-enough-we-need-to-shut-it-all-1">暂停人工智能开发还不够”。我们需要将其全部关闭</a>”，以及我们在各种播客上的露面。虽然我们继续支持 MIRI 的各种技术研究项目，但这不再是我们的<i>首要</i>任务，至少在可预见的未来是如此。</p><p>与这种重点转移相一致的是，MIRI 在过去几个月中也发生了许多组织变化，我们有点迟到了公开宣布这些变化。主要变化如下。</p><ul><li><strong>马洛·布尔贡：首席执行官（CEO）</strong><ul><li> Malo Bourgon 是 MIRI 中仅次于 Eliezer Yudkowsky 的最资深团队成员，他已从首席运营官转任为 MIRI 的高级领导职务。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefifgd2ta9j58"><sup><a href="#fnifgd2ta9j58">[1]</a></sup></span>我们从 2 月份开始试行这一变革，并于 6 月份正式实施。</li><li>这在一定程度上是为了更好地反映 MIRI 的长期现实。内特（Nate）多年来一直专注于高层战略和研究，而马洛（Malo）则负责组织的大部分日常运营。</li><li>这一变化也反映出马洛正在承担更多的决策权和更大的领导组织的责任。</li></ul></li><li><strong>内特·苏亚雷斯：总统</strong><ul><li>此前担任 MIRI 高级领导职务（执行董事）的 Nate 已调任总裁这一新职位。</li><li>作为总裁（以及董事会成员），Nate 将继续在指导 MIRI 和制定我们的愿景和战略方面发挥核心作用。</li></ul></li><li><strong>埃利泽·尤德科夫斯基：董事会主席</strong><ul><li>Eliezer 是 MIRI 的联合创始人兼高级研究员，此前已经是 MIRI 董事会成员。</li><li>我们现在任命 Eliezer 为董事会主席，以便更好地反映事实，即他的观点在 MIRI 战略方向中占有重要地位。</li><li>董事会前任主席埃德温·埃文斯 (Edwin Evans) 仍留在 MIRI 董事会。</li><li> Eliezer、Nate 和 Malo 对于哪些技术研究方向最有前途有着不同的看法。为了平衡他们的不同观点，除了整个组织资助的研究之外，董事会目前还为 Eliezer、Nate 和 Malo 各自提供了预算，用于资助不同的技术研究。</li></ul></li><li><strong>亚历克斯·维米尔：首席运营官 (COO)</strong><ul><li>亚历克斯已接替马洛担任首席运营官。</li><li>作为首席运营官，Alex 负责运营/监督运营团队，正如他已经这样做了一段时间一样，他将继续与 Malo 密切合作（正如他十多年来所做的那样），以帮助找出我们的目标核心约束是，并找出如何打破它们。</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Jimmy Rintjema：首席财务官 (CFO)</strong><ul><li> Jimmy 自 2015 年以来一直在 MIRI 工作。多年来，Jimmy 逐渐承担起越来越多的管理 MIRI 业务运营的责任，包括人力资源和财务。</li><li>作为这一转变的一部分，吉米在这个领域承担了更多的责任和权力，这次头衔的变化就是为了反映这一点。</li></ul></li></ul><p> Nate 分享了以下关于将 MIRI 的领导角色移交给 Malo 的信息：</p><blockquote><p>这种变化在很大程度上是对现状的维护。多年来，马洛在 MIRI 的日常运营方面一直表现出色（包括为所有在新冠疫情期间想要避开城市的员工购买乡村住宅，以及让该场地顺利运营等壮举）。近年来，士气低落，至少我没有看到我们面前有多少充满希望的道路。在过去一年左右的时间里，这种情况发生了一些变化，随着人们对人工智能的全面认识的提高，开辟了新的社会和政治可能性。我认为马洛比我更有能力利用其中的许多优势。我还希望，既然他担任了首席执行官，他就能够取得更令人印象深刻的成就（并且更频繁地）。</p></blockquote><p>除了这些变化之外，我们还聘用了两名新的高级员工，以更好地管理、协调和支持 MIRI 在两个主要重点领域的工作：</p><ul><li><strong>丽莎蒂尔加特：研究经理</strong><ul><li>Lisa 将管理 MIRI 的研究人员和项目。她的工作包括制定新的研究策略、管理现有项目、改进研究流程以及发展和支持（新）研究团队。</li><li> Lisa 是来自 TUM 和佐治亚理工学院的计算机科学家，拥有学术和行业 ML 研究背景以及 CDTM 和 Entrepreneur First 的技术管理和创业培训背景。她在 ML 研究实验室和初创公司工作了几年，并花了 8 个月在 SERI MATS 进行对齐研究。她过去的工作包括<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.10248">模型内部结构</a>、机器人 RLHF 以及神经技术/全脑仿真项目。</li><li>丽莎还是远见联盟基金的资助顾问。</li></ul></li><li> <strong>Gretta Duleba：通讯经理</strong><ul><li>我（Gretta）将领导 MIRI 的沟通团队，与 Rob Bensinger、Colm Ó Riain、Nate、Eliezer 和其他员工合作，创建简洁、有效的方法来解释比人类更聪明的人工智能所带来的极端风险以及什么我们认为应该解决这个问题。</li><li>在转行担任独立关系顾问之前，我曾担任 Google 的高级软件工程经理，领导 Google 地图和 Google Analytics 的大型团队。</li></ul></li></ul><p>经过这些变化，我们的组织结构现在如下所示：</p><p> <a href="https://intelligence.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/MIRI-Org-Structure.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/rgf3zvjohzuryqkkiwnc" alt="MIRI 的组织结构图。" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/rgf3zvjohzuryqkkiwnc 1051w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/ol7nhjkpgscq83dbmro0 300w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/q41qjy7cknua1etblfjl 1024w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/admkblfizbjfpmz7hn6b 768w"></a></p><p>我们希望这种新的组织结构将使我们能够更有效地执行我们的优先事项，并且如果运气好的话，能够彻底解决人工智能带来的生存风险。</p><p>关于我们的新（且仍在不断发展）的战略，以及我们对世界（通常非常严峻）形势的总体思考，我们希望有更多的内容。但我不希望这些公告进一步延迟分享上述更新，因此我已将 2023 年战略更新纳入多篇文章中，从这篇文章开始。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnreft1zb6ysqgd"><sup><a href="#fnt1zb6ysqgd">[2]</a></sup></span> </p><p></p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnifgd2ta9j58"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefifgd2ta9j58">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>美国非营利组织的首席执行官通常拥有“执行董事”的头衔。然而，在 MIRI，我们希望我们的头衔具有明确的含义，“董事”一词也用于指代董事会成员。因此，我们只希望在某人实际上是 MIRI 董事会成员的情况下在其头衔中包含“董事”。在担任我们的首席执行官期间，Nate 也是 MIRI 董事会的成员（并且在这次交接后仍然是），因此“执行董事”这一头衔似乎很合适。然而，由于 Malo 并非 MIRI 董事会成员，因此他将使用“首席执行官”的头衔。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnt1zb6ysqgd"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnreft1zb6ysqgd">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>感谢 Rob Bensinger 和 Malo Bourgon 帮助撰写和编辑这篇文章。</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/announcing-miri-s-new-ceo-and-leadership-team#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY/announcing-miri-s-new-ceo-and-leadership-team<guid ispermalink="false"> NjtHt55nFbw3gehzY</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Gretta Duleba]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 19:22:11 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Documenting Journey Into AI Safety]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 6:30 PM GMT<br/><br/><h2><strong>概括</strong></h2><p>最近，我注意到许多人因为在人工智能安全领域的尝试似乎缺乏进展而变得灰心丧气。在我看来，<i>人工智能安全管道职业生涯的</i>一个关键瓶颈是获得导师。</p><p><strong>可能有助于解决这种指导需求的一种方法是让经历此过程的个人记录他们的路径，重点关注同行和导师的反馈</strong><i><strong>。</strong></i> <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnrefsi3tgce3y8r"><sup><a href="#fnsi3tgce3y8r">[1]</a></sup></span>虽然此内容不会针对每个特定的听众量身定制，但我的直觉是，向个人提供的许多反馈对于尚未能够自己找到导师的其他人来说仍然很有价值。这样的系列可以成为新人的资源，并且可以显着增加<i>可以</i>参与该领域的人数。</p><p><strong>如果您有时间，我将非常感谢您对我的思考过程和这项努力提供任何反馈。</strong>查看反馈请求部分以获取更多信息。</p><hr><h2><strong>反馈请求</strong></h2><p>我优先考虑尽快解决这个问题，而不是我的最终计划，因为我相信我们可以比我自己更有效地取得更好的结果。因此，如果某些事情看起来非常明显，而我没有提及或考虑到它，请告诉我！当您阅读这篇针对不同人群的文章时，需要考虑以下一些问题：</p><ul><li>如果您对人工智能安全不熟悉，这样的系列会对您有帮助吗？您是否想确保尽早涵盖任何内容（如果可能）？</li><li>场地建设者们，我是在场地建设方面失礼了，还是这样的事情对你们来说有意义？我有什么办法可以改进吗？</li><li>人工智能安全资深人士，我是否错过了一个明显的机会或角度？您认为在这样的系列中，有什么事情是非常值得讨论的吗？</li></ul><h2><strong>简介</strong></h2><p>我叫雅各布·海姆斯，住在美国科罗拉多州博尔德郊外。我拥有计算建模硕士学位。在空闲时间我喜欢玩各种游戏，尤其是TTRPG。</p><h2><strong>检查情况</strong></h2><p>当我开始考虑转行进入人工智能安全领域时，我看到了两个选择：提升技能并申请职位，或者申请博士学位（目的是专注于人工智能安全，完成该项目后进入该领域） ）。经过与多位人士讨论后，我决定选择前者，原因如下：</p><ul><li>人们似乎一致认为，当个人确切地知道他们计划研究什么利基/问题时，博士学位是最有效的——我没有。</li><li>人工智能安全领域目前相对较小，但正在不断增长，这意味着现在所做的工作可能会产生更大的影响（因为它可能会影响未来的工作和/或实践）。</li><li> TAI/AGI 的时间表可能足够短，我们需要尽可能多的人尽快致力于人工智能安全。</li></ul><p>在这些相同的对话中，我会询问其他人发现哪些资源和方法最有帮助。最常见的建议是这样的：“课程在某种程度上是有帮助的，但我发现实际上为研究和/或项目工作做出贡献会更有效。”当询问去哪里为这些努力做出贡献时，我得到了一些 Discord 服务器、机会委员会、研究小组、赠款、组织，甚至一些初创企业和公司，这些公司更多地是为了<i>职业资本</i>而不是实际价值添加到我将生成的人工智能安全性中。</p><p>不幸的是，大多数招聘启事并不是在寻找新人，而是包含诸如“必须在相关领域工作 5 年以上”或“需要硕士，博士优先”之类的陈述。为了进一步限制人才库，很大一部分接受初学者的职位需要搬迁到华盛顿特区、旧金山湾区或伦敦，而这些职位的竞争都非常激烈。人们经常重复的“我们需要更多对人工智能安全感兴趣的人”的想法似乎并不完全准确。更真实的版本是“我们需要对人工智能安全感兴趣的更有<i>经验、有资质的</i>人”。 <span class="footnote-reference" role="doc-noteref" id="fnref1thyj3pkzdd"><sup><a href="#fn1thyj3pkzdd">[2]</a></sup></span></p><h3><strong>不一致之处</strong></h3><p>据我所知，到目前为止，我的故事是一个相对常见的故事，这意味着我们发现了一个经常发生的不一致之处：当人们开始考虑进入人工智能安全领域时，他们不鼓励攻读博士学位，但一旦他们知道得足够多，理论上能够做出贡献，那么对于具有他们经验水平的个人来说，机会就很少了。</p><p>博士学位的价值，除了拥有 3-5 年相对稳定的薪水之外，还在于在拥有更多知识和实践的人的指导和监督下获得（在您的研究领域）研究的经验。至少从理论上来说，这种关系并不是高等教育所垄断的；相反，指导受到导师数量的限制。由于该领域正在快速发展（良好的工作领域建设者），我们现有的人工智能安全专家不可能有能力指导所有新人，继续推进自己的工作，并实现健康的工作与生活平衡。</p><h3><strong>可能有帮助的事情</strong></h3><p>为了解决这个问题，我们需要一种方法来加强正在进行的指导。我认为我可以通过记录/记录我向人工智能安全职业生涯的过渡来协助这项工作，包括我与同行/导师的对话、我能够进入的课程的进展（在协调员的许可下） ），以及随着我了解更多，我的观点如何改变。这不如直接与自己的导师交谈那么好，但应该为那些发现很难知道下一步该做什么以及如何做的个人提供额外的资源。</p><h3><strong>关于利益冲突</strong></h3><p>当我写这篇文章时，我意识到这篇文章可能被认为主要是自私的。这种观点将我视为一个尚未找到导师的人，并试图在帮助他人的幌子下寻找最好的导师。也许你没有想到这一点，但如果我自己注意到这一点，我认为这可能值得解决。</p><p>我致力于人工智能安全领域的工作，目前我有一份稳定的兼职工作。正因为如此，我相信在某个时候我会找到出色的导师。我不想从别人那里挖导师，所以我提出了一个由两部分组成的解决方案：</p><ol><li>一旦我具备了技能和经验，我就会致力于指导他人。</li><li>在权衡您是否会联系我和/或提供指导时，不应考虑拟议的系列。</li></ol><p>如果您有时间担任导师，请这样做。</p><h2><strong>系列结构</strong></h2><p>在收到我之前提到的资源后，我把自己放在 Discord 上，向个人和渠道发送有关我可以贡献的机会的信息，并申请了我可以获得的所有其他机会。即便如此，我还是没有找到动力，所以我开始尝试为自己创造机会。</p><p>通过与人工智能治理团队中的其他人建立联系，我最终能够与另一位愿意合作进行机械可解释性研究的研究人员建立联系，并开始与他合作。我还一直密切关注论坛和招聘网站以寻找新的机会，这让我看到了 Linda Linsefors 的<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/mw8X3wCdcHipdTicv/apply-to-lead-a-project-during-the-next-virtual-ai-safety">帖子</a>，内容涉及申请成为即将举行的人工智能安全营的研究负责人。虽然一开始我不确定自己是否符合这个职位的要求，但我还是联系了她，并与她确认我可能很适合。从那时起，我对我的正式研究计划（实际上是 AISC 的申请）进行了多次迭代，并且在这样做的过程中我学到了很多东西。</p><p>考虑到这一点，该系列很可能是一个播客（主要），目的是在情况特别有利时制作额外的内容（视频、文档）。播客的第一集将是对我迄今为止的道路的总结，包括最有价值的资源和经验。在此之后（可以重新审视其他人特别感兴趣的任何内容），播客将变成一本关于我目前正在从事的两个项目（AISC 研究计划和机械解释性研究）以及任何随着时间的推移我会发现。我每周都会与我在整个课程中建立的联系进行多次会议，并且我也会（在获得许可的情况下）录制这些会议的音频。之后，我将对其进行编辑，以重点关注最重要的部分，这应该有助于吸引听众的注意力。此外，我很乐意创建帖子，表达我对特定资源为何以及如何对我有帮助的想法。</p><p>展望未来，我将继续申请项目/课程（<i>例如</i>SERI-MATS），目的是在安全的情况下分享尽可能多的内容（我可以看到存在一些边缘情况，研究需要更多的安全措施，尽管我怀疑我是否能够在一段时间内为此类项目做出贡献）。</p><h2><strong>致谢</strong></h2><p>特别感谢 Linda Linsefors、Peter Gebauer 和 Chris Lonsberry 对本文和我们的讨论的反馈。如果没有<a href="https://aisafety.quest/#calls"><u>AI Safety Quest 的导航呼叫</u></a>、 <a href="https://80000hours.org/speak-with-us/?int_campaign=2021-08__primary-navigation"><u>80,000 小时 1-1 建议</u></a>或<a href="https://www.bluedotimpact.org/ai/"><u>BlueDot Impact 的 AI 课程的</u></a>帮助，我也不会发表这篇文章。</p><p>我还要感谢那些花时间阅读这篇文章并提供反馈的人。 <br></p><ol class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fnsi3tgce3y8r"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnrefsi3tgce3y8r">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>完全归功于 Peter Gebauer 在我们的一次讨论中提出了这个想法。</p></div></li><li class="footnote-item" role="doc-endnote" id="fn1thyj3pkzdd"> <span class="footnote-back-link"><sup><strong><a href="#fnref1thyj3pkzdd">^</a></strong></sup></span><div class="footnote-content"><p>我什至发现了一篇相对较新的文章（2023 年 3 月下旬），声称 OpenAI 愿意雇用更多研究人员，只要有任何<i>优秀的</i>研究人员愿意从事对齐工作即可。</p></div></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg/documenting-journey-into-ai-safety#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg/documenting-journey-into-ai-safety<guid ispermalink="false"> ozDWnEChJwuB5L5wg</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jacobhaimes]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 18:37:14 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Childhood Roundup #3]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 2:30 PM GMT<br/><br/><p>又到了总结自上一篇此类帖子以来我注意到的所有与童年相关的故事的时候了，这些故事不适合其他地方。</p><p>除了标准职位之外，我还有一个个人说明，不幸的是我们目前的保姆的健康状况不允许她继续，因此我们正在为我们的三个孩子寻找和面试新的全职保姆在曼哈顿这里。我希望在本周末有人就位。如果您是或认识我们应该考虑的人，请立即与我联系并提供相关信息。您可以在 Twitter 上私信我，在 LesssWrong 上私信我，或者通过 substack 给我发电子邮件（或者直接发电子邮件，如果您知道的话）。提前致谢。</p><span id="more-23555"></span><h4>我们都需要一个朋友</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Austen/status/1678031280183840775">抱歉，你被欺负了，这里有一些金子吗？</a>在本例中，由于某种原因，一个四处寻求交朋友的孩子筹集了 4 万美元。但没有朋友。</p><blockquote><p>赵伊文：非凡的超级反派起源故事</p></blockquote><p>我感受到他的痛苦。为我的孩子们寻找朋友也很困难——如果有人在曼哈顿下城附近有 10 岁或以下的孩子，并且想尝试安排一起玩耍的约会带孩子们过来，请联系我们。</p><h4>花在孩子身上的时间在历史上是反常的</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/devonzuegel/status/1675247814647873539">提醒您的是，如今的职业母亲花在照顾孩子上的时间比 20 世纪 60 年代的家庭主妇还要多</a>。质量时间很棒，但数量时间已经失控。</p><p>布莱恩·卡普兰（Bryan Caplan）在<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://thezvi.substack.com/p/more-dakka">我的旧帖子《更多达卡》（More Dakka）</a>的版本中<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://betonit.substack.com/p/do-ten-times-as-much">指出了</a>另一种假设，该假设也解释了所有“父母不重要”的衡量标准。</p><blockquote><p>以育儿为例。大多数读者将我的<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/046501867X?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=bryacaplwebp-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;creativeASIN=046501867X"><em>《生养更多孩子的自私理由》</em></a>总结为“养育孩子并不重要”。但这只是对双胞胎和收养数据的一种可能的解释。然而，这些数据也与大多数父母几乎没有试图取得成果的理论相一致——至少在许多相关方面是这样。在开始在家教育孩子之前，我<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.econlib.org/archives/2015/09/why_im_homescho.html">深入思考了这个问题</a>。我总是对那些未能教导孩子了解供求关系的经济学家感到震惊。我所有的孩子都知道这些神圣的图表。他们的孩子和我的孩子有什么区别？我做了十倍。</p></blockquote><p>是的。我以类似的方式解释“父母不重要”的统计数据。如果你在多种可能失败的方式中的一种或多种失败，就会造成很大的损害。</p><p>然后你可以做得比基线好得多，但这需要你投入异常更多的工作或异常聪明的工作，或两者兼而有之。这种情况发生的频率不够高，无法在统计数据中显示出来。仍然有很大的空间对利润率产生重大影响，但也没有足够系统性地体现在统计数据中。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41539-023-00173-y">声称双胞胎研究高估了环境对教育程度的影响</a>，重新分析将 43% 的影响降低到 26%。</p><p>我确实担心有些人会把这些事情看得太过分。我仍然不相信所有的说法，即什么都不重要，或者无关紧要，或者重要的是不要做一些非常愚蠢或有害的事情。我认为此类研究确实未能捕获重要的输入和输出，也无法比较非常相似的环境。可以简单地说，在足够不同的环境下，你可以解释任意大的教育程度差异。</p><h4>让您的孩子玩耍</h4><p>乔恩·海特和彼得·格雷提出了一个看似合理的假设： <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jonathanhaidt.substack.com/p/the-play-deficit?utm_source=post-email-title&amp;publication_id=1221094&amp;post_id=135441845&amp;isFreemail=true&amp;utm_medium=email">玩耍剥夺是青少年心理健康危机的主要原因</a>。毫无疑问，在过去的几十年里，随着电子产品作为替代品的兴起，以及我们在儿童进行体育活动时对他们的过度保护，现实世界的游戏在范围和质量上都急剧下降。在美国，这种剥夺玩耍的行为尤其糟糕，因此这也可以解释为什么我们有特别严重的心理健康问题，而智能手机假说本身无法解释这一问题。</p><p>还要注意的是，要算作游戏，它必须超出成人的控制范围，而这正是我们经常坚决反对的。</p><blockquote><p> [研究]表明，玩耍是孩子们快乐的直接源泉。当孩子们被要求描绘或描述让他们快乐的活动时，他们会描绘或描述玩耍的场景。还有研究表明，当孩子们被允许多一点玩耍时——比如学校提供多一点的课间休息时间——孩子们会变得更快乐。研究还表明，孩子们认为游戏是他们自己发起和控制的活动。如果是大人在指挥，那就不是游戏了。玩耍的乐趣是摆脱成人控制的自由的乐趣。</p><p> ……</p><p>研究表明，各个年龄段的人，如果拥有强大的<em>内部控制点</em>（内部LOC），即强烈地意识到自己能够解决自己的问题并掌控自己的生活，那么他们患焦虑症的可能性就会小得多。与内部 LOC 较弱的人相比，抑郁程度更高。</p><p> ……</p><p>此外，两项针对成年人的回顾性研究表明，从各种指标来看，那些在童年时回忆起更多独立玩耍经历的人，在成年后比那些回忆起较少独立性的人更快乐、更成功。</p></blockquote><p>我发现这至少是这个难题的主要部分，这一点令人信服。</p><p>好消息：现在有<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/FreeRangeKids/status/1669515733712216064">五个州</a>制定了“合理儿童独立”法律，预计今年还会有两项法律。这创造了安全港，有望避免像“<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://letgrow.org/cops-stop-6-year-old/">密歇根州父母让 6 岁的孩子步行去商店，两名警察出现</a>”这样的头条新闻。</p><blockquote><p> “他们说，‘她还不够大，’我记得我当时想，‘那是你个人的信念。你根本不了解我的孩子！但我记得我当时想，‘我需要让自己冷静下来。’”</p><p>他的谨慎得到了回报。 “警察说，‘我们不想让儿童保护服务介入其中，’”这表明，如果推动的话，他们当然可以。于是汤姆给了他们他的名字和身份证明，并承诺：“警官，我会确保她以后在我们的房子里。”</p><p>这就是他和他的妻子所做的。他们改变了养育方式，不是因为实际的危险，而是因为其他人的看法。</p><p>这反过来又改变了他们的女儿。在这次受挫的步行之后，“她几乎想立即再次尝试，”汤姆说。 “但我们不允许她这样做。因为如果她再次尝试并且他们再次找到她，他们肯定会向我们求助儿童保护服务。”</p><p>精神抖擞的小姑娘又问了几遍。然后……她不再问了。</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://reason.com/2023/06/17/confused-tiktok-mom-asks-for-help-when-random-child-comes-over-to-play-with-her-kid/">父母常常不帮忙，是的，这是 TikTok 精心挑选的，但仍然</a>：</p><blockquote><p> Lenore Skenazy：当随机的孩子过来和她的孩子一起玩时，困惑的 TikTok 妈妈寻求帮助</p><p>“我不认识这个孩子，我不认识他的妈妈，我不知道他住在哪里，”她在一段疯传的视频中说道。</p><p>一位妈妈在 TikTok 上寻求建议：“我的孩子在外面，另一个孩子在外面的某个地方散步，然后他们停下来开始一起玩。”</p><p>她很困惑。</p><p>妈妈接着解释说，那个不知名的孩子已经8岁了。他很有礼貌，看上去受到了很好的照顾。他和她的儿子一起进了屋，他们整个下午都在玩电子游戏。那个彬彬有礼、无名的男孩六个半小时都没有离开。</p><p>这就是问题所在。</p><p>这位妈妈不明白一个孩子怎么能结交新朋友、过来玩、而不让他的妈妈或爸爸惊慌失措地寻找他。她补充说，如果她自己的儿子失踪六个小时，她就会报警。</p><p> ……</p><p>她报告说，男孩的父母“一点也不担心。这对我来说太疯狂了！”</p><p>奇怪的是，一个能干的孩子自己出去玩，在宵禁前回到家，并没有发生什么不好的事情——这还被认为是新闻。</p></blockquote><p>大多数情况下，这实际上是个好消息。这位妈妈很困惑，为什么其他孩子的父母没有吓坏，而不是自己吓坏或不让孩子们玩。她承认这很好。</p><p>对陌生人或邻居向您求助儿童保护服务 (CPS) 的恐惧<a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/OctoAbbi/status/1709203485386817646">并不是对此类行为安全性的幻影恐惧的反映</a>。这是一种高度合理的恐惧，而且基础率很高。</p><blockquote><p>耶路撒冷：这是……一个疯狂的统计数据。 37% 的美国儿童是 CPS 报告的对象（28% 的白人儿童和 53% 的黑人儿童在 18 岁生日之前经历过 CPS 参与）。</p><p>阿比盖尔：我的邻居威胁要打电话给警察局，因为我让我的孩子在我的全围栏后院玩耍，而我却在里面观看。她走过来，敲我的门，当着那个孩子的面威胁我。现在的人们无缘无故地打电话。每个人都害怕它。根据我的经历，妈妈们经常谈论恐惧。</p></blockquote><p>其中一些 CPS 报告是粗略的，例如作为预防措施由某些伤害自动触发的报告。许多其他人则不然。举报率如此之高，每个人都争先恐后地避免成为目标，这使得其他人不得不更加争先恐后，等等。</p><p>或者，另一种选择：</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Chris_arnade/status/1678033467987357696">克里斯·阿马德</a>：六岁的孩子独自放学回家是世界其他地方认为正常的事情之一，但美国认为这是犯罪行为</p></blockquote><figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F0de4c13b-388f-40cb-b7f8-9c782d55d41d_680x460.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/vhfx5v5xbqmcud9g2dtu" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AlmostMedia/status/1693064029454086490">朱莉·弗雷德里克森总结道</a>。</p><blockquote><p>朱莉·弗雷德里克森：所有危险行为都减少了，每个人都很痛苦。</p><p>德里克·汤普森：青少年中悲伤、绝望和自杀念头的激增与其他行为趋势同时发生： – 吸烟报告下降 – 吸毒和饮酒下降 – 性行为也下降 – 欺凌行为并未增加。</p><p>这似乎也很重要：疾病预防控制中心报告称，“出于安全考虑”，缺课的青少年（尤其是黑人青少年）显着增加。</p></blockquote><p>嗯，是。为什么你认为所有的孩子都很痛苦？因为我们把当孩子定义为太冒险，把一切都放在严格的护栏上，不让我们的孩子成为孩子。这不是“尽管”的情况，而是“因为”的情况。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1703525305200382156">Mason 和 RFH 的观点也很明确</a>。</p><blockquote><p> RFH：如今，女性与孩子相处的时间是历史上前所未有的，这让女性和孩子都变得疯狂。</p><p>今天的职业妈妈在育儿上花费的时间比 50 年代的家庭主妇还要多，似乎没有人认为这是一个严重的问题，并且可能导致女性不再想成为妈妈，工作量和做母亲的压力已经失控。</p><p>女人越来越迷失母性，孩子也无法形成独立的人格，大家都变得狂躁、无形。</p><p>孩子们需要独处的时间来感到无聊并学习自我指导，妈妈们需要时间与其他成年人交谈并满足自己的需求。当我看到父母在操场上跟着他们八岁的孩子时，我感到不舒服，让他们自己解决并认识其他孩子！</p><p>梅森：孩子们需要父母/照顾者*可用，*而不是无所不在 这对于婴儿和 12 岁的孩子来说看起来非常不同，但我认为这个原则对两者都适用 现在很难提供这一点，主要是因为概念蠕动回复：“忽视”。</p><p>假设，技工应该比任何人都更了解这一点（我认为他们经常这样做）。那些不了解这一点的人就是那些重视女性/母亲痛苦并专门选择自己的道路来为自己创造更多工作的人。</p></blockquote><p>如果这是因为额外的时间带来了快乐，那就有道理了。 <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinhanson/status/1706741404876390529">这不是</a>（ <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31712?utm_campaign=ntwh&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=ntwg24">纸上的</a>），至少不是母亲受过大学教育时发生的额外时间。</p><blockquote><p>受过大学教育的母亲比受教育程度较低的母亲花在集中育儿上的时间要多得多，尽管她们的时间机会成本更高，工作时间也更长。</p><p> ……</p><p>我们发现，在所有母亲中，与花在其他活动上的时间相比，花在育儿上的时间会带来更高的积极情绪。</p><p>然而，受过大学教育的母亲在集中育儿过程中所经历的积极情绪并不比其他母亲多，负面情绪也不少。</p><p>此外，受过大学教育的母亲对花在管理活动上的时间的积极感受要少得多，而对花在与孩子的教育活动上的时间的消极感受要多得多。</p></blockquote><p>这很直观。你有两种输入：一种义务感和一种花时间的真正愿望，因为花时间是快乐的或有用的。高产出是否与幸福感相关，取决于哪种效应在驱动。</p><h4>安全错觉</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/education/2023/08/17/school-clear-backpacks/">出于对枪支的无数恐惧，学校开始要求透明背包</a>。我不敢想象如果我对背包里的东西的隐私为零的话会是什么样子。我仍然会接受定期的主动射击训练，这似乎稍微不那么造成创伤。</p><p>帖子以完美的野外观察结束，“这就是某事，因此我们必须这样做”。</p><blockquote><p> “我觉得这不会起到多大作用，”谢尼曼说。 “但无论我们能做什么，我都会做。”</p></blockquote><p>提醒大家，奇怪的绑架并不是一回事。他们可能会被忽视。</p><blockquote><p>致命性 Jane：在美国，陌生人绑架事件仅占儿童失踪案件的不到 0.1%。大多数失踪儿童案件都是离家出走。就绑架而言，绝大多数是非监护父母所为。人们总是担心错误的事情。</p><p>我经常在 Facebook 上看到有人说人们不能将购物车归还畜栏，因为如果有人绑架了他们的孩子怎么办？伙计们，当你花 60 秒归还购物车时，没有武装民兵伺机闯入你上锁的汽车。</p><p>当陌生人绑架事件确实发生时，通常是孩子独自在外面玩耍。人们在杂货店从购物车里抢走婴儿并逃跑的现象并不常见。</p></blockquote><p>当陌生人绑架事件确实发生时，通常是因为陌生人打电话报警，报告一个没有受到充分直接监管的孩子，然后一件事引发了另一件事，来自该州的陌生人绑架了您的孩子。</p><h4>社交媒体的名字不好</h4><p><a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/04/17/social-media-contagion/">米奇·丹尼尔斯 (Mitch Daniels) 也加入了对儿童和社交媒体发出警告的行列。</a>从这篇文章的框架和执行可以看出，这个人有政治天赋。我很遗憾他没有将帽子扔进拳击场。当然，作为一名优秀的政治家，他没有提出具体的建议或可行的解决方案。</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/reality__gamer/status/1648407913159958530">社交媒体对孩子有害的理论正是因为我们不会让他们在没有媒体的情况下进行社交</a>。</p><blockquote><p> Conservatards fail to understand that if the damn kids are on their phones too much it is because they have created an RLHF torture chamber of arrested development for adolescents, in which the only possible vector for creative growth is talking to strange people online.</p><p> We need to abandon with prejudice the idea that teenagers are “children”. Once you turn like thirteen you&#39;re a person capable and desiring to take creative strategic actions in the world. The problem is if you do this with no oversight at this point you&#39;ll fuck up and get hurt.</p><p> What teenagers should be doing – useful labor in apprenticeship roles in guilds (repeal child labor laws) – doing prosocial work and exploration in scouts-type programs guided by older peers – artistic and cultural clubs – making remix art in Discords and grinding for clout</p><p> What teenagers are doing – 8 hours of sitting in class – 3 hours of homework (demoralization therapy to assimilate one to bureaucracy) – 2 hours of sports, “fun” in which you are yelled at by a man as defective if you don&#39;t put yourself through more pain – psychiatric therapy</p><p> Conservative freaks respond to zoomer culture by saying that suburban America should be even more of a Hitlero-Stalinist RLHF Black Iron Prison Rome than it already is, fifty years ago you could let eight year olds run around outside the house, today 12 year olds have babysitters.</p></blockquote><p> The theory continues along similar lines. The core insight here seems right to me. If you do not want kids lives to be dominated by screens, they will at minimum need to not be physically prevented from engaging in real world physical activities.</p><p> The same applies to phones in school, where children are even more held prisoner.</p><blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/DavidDeutschOxf/status/1708401155502403783">Jonathan Haidt</a> : Adolescents get 237 notifications per day (median). 97% of them use their phones during the school day. There is not much attention left over for everything else. This is madness. Schools can give them all 7 hours off, 5 days a week. Go phone free.</p><p> David Deutsch: They&#39;re forbidden real-life conversation. When they briefly escape the crushing boredom you call “everything else” by reading, passing notes or just looking elsewhere, they&#39;re punished. For learning. Framing a further restriction as &#39;giving them time off&#39; doesn&#39;t make it so.</p></blockquote><p> You want to take the phones away from kids, to free them from constant interruptions? Great, but you also have to allow them things worth not interrupting.</p><h4> Kids Respond To Incentives</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.thefp.com/p/what-happened-when-one-illinois-town">In this piece</a> that mostly focuses on reparations, a black former student notes:</p><blockquote><p> In the early 1950s, Weathers was the first black kid to go to the local public high school. The teacher picked on him; so did the white kids.</p><p> “If I raised my hand, she wouldn&#39;t call on me, because she didn&#39;t want the white kids to see I knew the answer,” Weathers told me. “She called on me when I kept my hand down to make me look stupid.”</p></blockquote><p> I wonder how long it would take such a child to use a mixed or reversed strategy. Do this to me three times and I&#39;m going to start raising my hand only when I don&#39;t know the answer. The primary lessons of school are often different than the ones we think.</p><h4> Let Them Eat Lunch</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/TheStalwart/status/1684117314705461248">Transaction costs rule everything around you, and they are not always financial</a> . It makes no sense to be charging for school lunches in public schools, it makes even less sense than it would to charge tuition.</p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: “Imagine: Children just walking into the cafeteria and getting fed. No accounts that parents have to keep up, no time spent assessing families&#39; incomes or processing payments or running down parents who haven&#39;t paid — no &#39;lunch shaming&#39; — none of that.”</p><p> Joe Weisenthal: At my elementary school, on the first day, they made kids raise their hands in class to ask for a paper application for free or discounted lunch for the rest of the school year. Even as like a 9 year old, without much broader awareness, remember thinking how messed up that was.</p></blockquote><p> The regulations can always be stupider and more expensive, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/AlecStapp/status/1664947189653688322">UK childminder requirements to provide food to children edition</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Childcare is another case – the number of registered childminders in the UK has fallen by 80% since the 1990s (and is still falling), probably driven by increasing requirements for qualifications and “death by a thousand cuts” mini-regulations, like the fact that a childminder today has to register with the Food Standards Agency and <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.food.gov.uk/sites/default/files/media/document/sfbb-childminders-pack_0.pdf">keep a legally-required “food diary”</a> recording what food products you have bought, who you bought them from, the quantity and date, and log incidents like having “found a pack of sliced ham out of date in the fridge”.</p></blockquote><h4> No Child Left Behind</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0927537123000301">Paper claims that graduate rate rise in wake of No Child Left Behind is &#39;real&#39; and represents a substantially increased stock of human capital</a> . A few different things jumped out right away.</p><p> The first was to simply defy the data on strategic behavior, and presume that various forms of cheating and adjustment were going unmeasured. Graduation is largely about negative selection. Did you fail anything? It is easy to send the message to teachers not to fail their students. It is easy to, on the margin, disregard a few extra unexcused absences, or not expel a student. None of that would be measured here as &#39;strategic behavior,&#39; which was categorized as changing graduation requirements or cheating on tests. One does not need to formallyalter requirements to radically alter them in practice. As for the tests, yeah, I&#39;m willing to guess some of them got easier. I know for sure there was a lot more teaching to the tests.</p><blockquote><p> Second, we provide descriptive analysis of the trends in state graduation rates by whether states have graduation exams (or experienced changes in graduation exam policies during the panel period). If the rise in graduation rates was entirely due to strategic behavior, we would expect that the states without graduation exams experienced larger increases in graduation rates. But we see the opposite, suggesting that the upward trend in high school graduation is not because schools lowered their academic standards to make graduation easier.</p></blockquote><p> I see the theory here, that tests are the hardest thing to cheat. Except that when the tests are what is gating graduation, it seems plausible schools can find ways to pass those tests without building human capital, or even by sacrificing it. Worst case, state can respond to pressure by issuing a weaker test, or teaching directly to it. One can also see this as, places with gating tests had slack in the form of students who could plausibly graduate otherwise, if only some right answers can be made to appear in the right places.</p><p> It is also very easy to see how NCLB can harm human capital development. If you are focusing on children not failing, and on them passing tests, you are going to invest less in building their actually valuable human capital. You are going to alienate your best students, waste their time, get them out of good habits and teach them the wrong lessons.</p><p> So it&#39;s hard to presume that all of this largely lines up with human capital. It lines up with the capital of saying you graduated, but to what extent is that an absolute good versus a positional good? Similarly, one could presume that NCLB need not be all that causal here, as the economic cost of non-graduation has been rising, which also should lead to higher graduation rates, and also schools being more hesitant to fail a student since it would ruin their lives more.</p><p> In conclusion, I am not convinced here.</p><p> Then there are the schools where no children are left behind, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Austen/status/1704698874697486692">because no child is going anywhere at all.</a></p><blockquote><p> Fox Baltimore: The Maryland State Department of Education&#39;s 2022 state test results report Baltimore City&#39;s math scores were the lowest in Maryland. Just 7 percent of third through eighth graders testing proficient in math, meaning 93 percent do not read at grade level.</p><p> ……</p><p> In 23 Baltimore City schools, there were zero students who tested proficient in math. Not a single student.</p></blockquote><h4> School Reinvented</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/education/interactive/2023/homeschooling-microschools-pods-esa-vouchers/?itid=hp-more-top-stories_p004_f002">The latest trend in home schooling is… school?</a> They&#39;ve reinvented a school? It sure sounds like they have. You take a few kids, you hire a &#39;guide&#39; to help them and work through learning exercises and enrichment activities while the parents work. Almost as if education were a product, and you could form a market for it, and provide it vastly better (via vastly smaller student-teacher ratios, and being in a nice home rather than in a dystopian hellhole building, and customizing the content, and so on) and cheaper.</p><blockquote><p> Families pay Prenda $2,199 per year, plus additional fees set by the guides, which can range from $2,800 to $8,000, Smith said.</p></blockquote><p> For comparison, the average public school student costs the state roughly $13k/year. State funding for these micro schools seems much lower than that.</p><p> Another data point is that NYC schools <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/Duderichy/status/1705345080209355161">have been “defunded” to the tune of $38k per student</a> . I realize that space is not free exactly and there is a lot of paperwork, and costs in NYC are higher, but one has to notice this is utterly absurd.</p><p> Even at $13k, one has to wonder about the &#39;get a few kids and hire a teacher&#39; option.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1706757195864367422">Matt Yglesias says it is wild American schools get so many tax breaks</a> . The obvious response is to point to the full public funding of the public schools and the need to compete with them. You pay your property taxes either way. It does seem wild if and when they get vouchers similar to the amount public schools are funded and then also keep a lot of tax breaks on top of that.</p><p> Whereas <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1706757195864367422">Labour is saying in the UK they will add a 20% VAT to private school fees</a> via removing their exemption, which they then say they will use to &#39;raise educational standards&#39; since money is not fungible.</p><p> Did you know that letting kids learn what they are curious about helps them learn?</p><blockquote><p> She picks and chooses topics for study based on student interests, not a set of state standards.</p><p> She pointed to one of her students who wants to be a judge. “She wants to learn about the Constitution and government. So why should I say, &#39;No, you should learn about ancient Egypt.&#39;”</p></blockquote><p> The two obvious concerns are socialization and situational tail risk. For socialization, I would continue to make the case that most socialization in schools is not the kind you want, and that a few close friends from a micro school or otherwise is vastly superior, and you can find friends in much better and cheaper ways and situations. The real issue is that while most micro school situations with attentive parents are going to go quite well, some parents are not so attentive or caring, and some children could end up in bad spots in ways that are highly blameworthy, as opposed to it happening in a public school where if it happens everyone followed procedure, and admittedly things could go farther south this way.</p><p> Presumably the solution for that is some form of periodic check-in, a test if you will, to ensure that things are going all right. If you are doing very well, warping things to pass the test will be unnecessary, provided it is not too particular (eg the student can demonstrate mastery of the Constitution or Egypt, and either counts for history).</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.richardhanania.com/p/the-old-school-reformers-case-for?utm_source=post-email-title&amp;publication_id=98102&amp;post_id=116966416&amp;isFreemail=true&amp;utm_medium=email">Richard Hanania makes &#39;The Old School Reformer&#39;s Case for Privatizing Education.&#39;</a> It is the standard set of true observations about what schools are and what it means to force children to spend thousands and thousands of hours in the place the government decides, when they decide it, doing what the government decides, without the right to go to the bathroom without asking first. And that public schools are a pretty non-optimal set of answers to those questions, so perhaps we should let families decide what is best for their children. I mostly don&#39;t disagree yet found it inessential.</p><p> Everyone tells me the lives of kids must be structured around having them &#39;socialize&#39; with others exactly their age, a &#39;peer group.&#39; <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/krishnanrohit/status/1663296837455888385">I agree with Rohit that this is dumb</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Rohit: One of my more controversial hypotheses on education is that having kids primarily be surrounded by other kids, especially of the same age, is bad actually, both for educational and socialising purposes</p><p> Mat Bateman (Quoting Montessori): “The education of today is humiliating. It produces an inferiority complex and artificially lowers the powers of man. Its very organization sets a limit to knowledge well below the natural level. It supplies men with crutches when they could run on swift feet.”</p></blockquote><h4> School Choice</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.vox.com/politics/23689496/school-choice-education-savings-accounts-american-federation-children">School choice is on the march</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Andrew Prokop at Vox: Very suddenly, that has changed. It started with West Virginia in 2021 and Arizona in 2022, and then continued with a flood this year — Iowa, Utah, Arkansas, Florida, Oklahoma, Ohio, and Indiana. More may follow. “It&#39;s happening!” Corey DeAngelis, a conservative activist who describes himself as a “school choice evangelist,” regularly tweets, joyfully chronicling each new victory.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/DeAngelisCorey/status/1660736473988050947">Governor of North Carolina declares state of emergency</a> because school vouchers are about to come online, and he wants to raise awareness. That is quite the mockery of the term &#39;state of emergency.&#39; On so many levels.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.nber.org/papers/w31553#fromrss">A new NBER working paper</a> by Christopher Campos and Caitlin Kearns finds that LA&#39;s zones of school choice, where families could choose where to send their kids, resulted in marked improvements in educational outcomes versus areas outside such zones. Some form of competition and choice between schools seems clearly necessary if you want good outcomes. In sufficiently wealthy places you can get that competitive effect in other ways, in less well-off places you need families to be able to choose.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.thefp.com/p/three-biggest-myths-of-american-public-schools">Magnet schools mostly aren&#39;t real</a> . They don&#39;t use objective tests. Instead, the principal mostly decides who gets in and mostly that means whoever is local. Then they sit back and collect the extra funding. Whereas the few real magnet schools, the ones that use real tests and provide differentiated high-quality experiences like Stuyvesant High School in New York and Thomas Jefferson in Virginia, are largely in the process of being dismantled so preferred groups can be preferred.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1706730741437284603">Here are some survey results on homeschooling</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Matt Bateman: Only 34% of homeschooling parents are motivated by religious instruction, but 68% are motivated by moral instruction.</p><p> Mason: – majority concerned with violence, bullying, academics, and moral (but not religious) instruction</p><p> – only slightly more religious than non-homeschoolers</p><p> – more likely to identify as independent, less likely as D (R about the same)</p></blockquote><p> I would caution that providing religious instruction is distinct from shielding a child from outside influences, so perhaps that number is too low, or is better expressed as &#39;moral instruction&#39; that is largely about religion. Also noteworthy is that parents robustly say there is too much school focus on gender identity, 31-16 among those with kids in school and 53-16 among home schoolers.</p><h4> School Hidden</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RyanRadia/status/1651379732288614406">Heritage Foundation proposes banning considering college degrees in not only public hiring, but also private hiring</a> , including any algorithmic screenings. This fits the pattern of our hiring laws where we tell people to ignore Bayes&#39; Rule and not care about their own preferences, because we don&#39;t like the implications, and we think that if we tell people to disregard Bayes&#39; Rule and their own preferences then they will go away.</p><p> Except, they don&#39;t go away. Which means everyone who ever hires anyone is breaking employment law constantly. It&#39;s not like you can look at resumes, or talk to people, and avoid learning who has a college degree.</p><p> You can try toban algorithms from considering college or various other things, and perhaps with some bespoke work you could even kind of do it, which would then mean you&#39;d want humans in the loop to fix that, I guess, if you did in fact care about such things in either direction. It&#39;s hard not to do that when everyone else is doing it, various signaling game dynamics, and so on.</p><p> What you can partially do is ban using college degrees as a requirement, so that anyone with statistically observable size has to give those without one a chance. However this risks making things even worse for those without degrees when such discrimination can go undetected, because they will now have no sign of where they can and cannot usefully apply. Then again, right now the requirements at such places are often only suggestions, so it is not obvious much would change.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RyanRadia/status/1651379732288614406">Ryan Radia, ultimate reply guy</a> , notices that one of those requiring college degrees would be the Heritage Foundation. Except that&#39;s exactly the point. If you have the option to use college degrees as a filter, it is in your interest in such situations to use it, which helps you at the expense of forcing lots of people to waste years of their lives. It&#39;s the opposite of a gotcha.</p><h4> School Evaluation Hard</h4><p> I intended for this section to be longer: <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.mathematica.org/publications/long-term-impacts-of-kipp-middle-and-high-schools-on-college-enrollment-persistence-and-attainment">New study of 2k children</a> allocated via lottery to attend or not attend one of 280 charter schools shows <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JohnArnoldFndtn/status/1701645859291558214">dramatic long term impact from KIPP (Knowledge is Power Program) charter schools</a> if and only if the kids stay from middle through high school.</p><p> I did some back and forth exchanges with the author of the paper, attempting to reconcile the claims that KIPP was effective with statistics that said that giving students access to KIPP middle schools did not make them substantially more likely to graduate from college, which seems like the best endpoint measured here. I haven&#39;t had time to get sufficient confidence in my understanding here, so I&#39;m pushing that for later, while asking if any of you have a reading here.</p><h4> A Metaphor</h4><p> There has been a bunch of recent discussion of the concept of Two-Parent Privilege, as described in the book of that name by Melissa Kearney. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.ft.com/content/14b0873e-c7cf-4927-aebe-71d562645bd4">Here is a Financial Times piece on the book</a> . A common response is to claim that everyone agrees that two married parents are better than the alternatives, and two parents of any kind are better than one, of course we (or the elites or liberal elites) know this and profess it. Yet we do not often say this, or emphasize it, or put force behind the message.</p><blockquote><p> Matthew Yglesias: One of the weirdest sentiments I read on here is the idea that the “elites” won&#39;t tell you about the value of marriage, physical fitness, friendship, healthy eating, etc — look up the stats and it&#39;s college grads doing way better on all those measures.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robkhenderson/status/1701250176931725552">Rob Henderson</a> : Scenario: Rich right-wing anchors say getting a vaccine is just as good as not getting one, implies vaccines might be harmful, promotes broad skepticism about them. And then personally ensures they and their families are vaccinated.</p><p> Very smart cultural critic: Why are people saying rich right-wing anchors won&#39;t tell you about the value of vaccines? Look it up, they&#39;re all vaccinated.</p></blockquote><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/09/the-shaming-of-one-parent-families.html">Tyler Cowen views this in terms of shame</a> . We used to shame one-parent families, and also some other things such as suicide. Now we instead shame other things.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/BradWilcoxIFS/status/1702138878507811011">Brad Wilcox challenges that this is merely about failure to be loud or to shame</a> .</p><blockquote><p> Brad Wilcox: Plenty of folks, including @mattyglesias, have asked: Where is the evidence that left-leaning elites don&#39;t support marriage?</p><p> Here is some polling evidence from the American Family Survey (2022).</p><p> “while 91 percent of college-educated conservatives agree that “children are better off if they have married parents,” only 30 percent of college-educated liberals agree, according to a report to be released next week by @FamStudies.</p></blockquote><p> Children are better off if they have married parents. That does not mean that every child&#39;s parents should get or remain married. It does not mean that you should not have children in other circumstances.</p><p> What it does mean is: Children are better off if they have married parents. If you fail to agree with this, presumably it is because you do not care for the implications.</p><p> I would also add: Children are better off being raised by two parents than being raised by one parent, even if marriage is not strictly involved.</p><p> One problem is that those who would traditionally ever be willing to apply any pressure to anyone can&#39;t <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias/status/1703525334472085918">keep their eye on the ball</a> , instead worrying more about the genders of everyone involved. Those in the red faction really, really do not want gay or lesbian or unmarried couples having children.</p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F62c7c42d-931c-4296-8386-ad853541befd_840x1196.jpeg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/xpydosgmjoqy5oc5xnx2" alt="图像"></a></figure><p> The sleeper thing to notice is that only 76% of conservatives think it is acceptable for a married couple to decide not to have children.</p><p> The weirdest one of all is an unmarried man and woman raising a child only get 58% approval, versus 70% for a single parent. Presumably this is because the unmarried couple could choose to get married whereas the single parent cannot not have a kid. It still seems like this is actively going to point incentives in the wrong direction, when most of the approval benefit of getting married is also available if the father leaves.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://mattbruenig.com/2023/09/30/response-to-douthat-on-two-parent-families/">Matt Bruenig responds</a> (directly to Ross Douthat, but mostly to the broader claim) with the counterargument that we are asking the wrong question:</p><blockquote><p> Matt Bruenig: I responded to this argument by rehashing what I take to be the common view on this topic, which is that parent cohabitation is sometimes good and sometimes bad, depending on the characteristics of each parent and how those parents get along. Based on this view, the relevant inquiry is how many of the 22 percent of kids who live in single-parent households would actually be better off if <strong><em>their specific parents</em></strong> lived together.</p><p> ……</p><ol><li> One of the parents may be dead, in prison, or living remotely for job reasons. This is not a huge slice of people, but it probably does shave a couple of percentage points off the total.</li><li> Dad might be a bad guy.</li><li> Mom might be a bad lady.</li><li> Dad and mom might be alright but don&#39;t mix well.</li></ol></blockquote><p> That is the question of what to do about a particular child, in isolation, already faced with a non-ideal situation. And yes, sometimes given who the parents are, their circumstances or their relationship to each other, it will sometimes be impossible or unwise to retroactively &#39;fix&#39; the situation in this way. The best time to intervene and change the situation is before it gets to that point, including on a broader scale. The second best time will in a particular case sometimes be right now, sometimes not.</p><p> Matt then makes the claim that since upper class people marry upper class people but mostly don&#39;t marry lower class people, they are only providing evidence that marriage is good when you marry someone upper class. There is certainly a coherent position that says something like &#39;if you have a good enough situation lock it down, otherwise don&#39;t until you get one.&#39; I would argue that if anything this throws shade on arguments of the form &#39;lower class people should be able to get the message from the actions upper class people take.&#39; Instead, they often take to heart that they need similarly secure circumstances first, which they rarely will get. So all the more reason one must say the full arguments out loud.</p><p> This all follows the common pattern where we used to get good thing X via method Y, then we realized (usually correctly) that Y is terrible and stopped doing Y (or we got it via mechanism Z that went away or changed for other reasons), except now we are getting steadily less X and we don&#39;t have a solution. We need more X, so we need alternative methods for getting more X.</p><p> The most obvious X is fertility, which makes this particular situation even trickier.</p><p> The obvious thing to do is some combination of financial support for X or some alternative mechanism Z that causes X, or financial punishment for ~X or ~Z, or supporting helpful norms and other cultural features. In general, people say &#39;it is impossible to get more X&#39; or &#39;X is outdated&#39; or &#39;we cannot afford X&#39; or some such, before trying much.</p><p> More than that, they refuse to say X is good, or that we need more X, because they associate that with support of nasty, no-good method Y or outdated mechanism Z, or otherwise the use of force or shame or pressure. We are against shame, but we also don&#39;t see any way to offer praise or honor for X without considering that shame of ~X.</p><p> Meanwhile, more and more forms of punishment are being considered Ys.</p><p> Every parent knows this dilemma well.</p><p> We need some knob, somewhere, that we can turn to reward the good and discourage the bad. What to do?</p><h4> Lies</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/robinhanson/status/1648789845701976064">Liars, liars, pants on fires.</a></p><figure class="wp-block-image"> <a href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fcd9ea6ca-b4c1-45f4-9208-57d705923304_907x963.png" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/gkme2dijqigetufg03lt" alt=""></a></figure><blockquote><p> Eucaliculia: This poll is likely biased by lots of parents only having kids who are &lt;10 years old. I can definitely tell when my 2 year old lies to me more reliably than I could a 16 year old.</p></blockquote><p> I am with Eucaliculia here. At first, children can&#39;t lie without giving the game away. Then, slowly, they skill up, until finally they can mostly lie with impunity absent evidence, and they get good at knowing when their story can get double checked. By the end, I was <em>very</em> confident that most of my lies were getting through, and was willing to rather aggressively lie to my parents despite a strict honesty policy for everyone else.</p><p> Whereas with my kids right now, they&#39;re young enough that I&#39;m very confident they almost never successfully fool me. I do expect that to change, but as we say to the God of Death: Not today.</p><p> I do, however, think that parents likely systematically overestimate how often they can detect kids&#39; lies, and kids overestimate how often they can get away undetected, because parents don&#39;t always tell you that they know you&#39;re lying.</p><p> Rick from Baltimore asks Tyler Cowen, given he does believe in the value of two-parent families, <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/09/from-my-email-on-single-parent-families.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=from-my-email-on-single-parent-families">what would his pro-parent plan look like?</a></p><p> Rick&#39;s suggestions mostly involve a variety of proposed cultural shifts towards favoring marriages by moving back towards some older cultural norms, including better tax incentives and perhaps job programs and otherwise helping create more eligible men. Tyler responds that he does not know what would work, but that it could not hurt to indeed get buy-in that this problem really matters and is not a hopeless one, and asks who is on board.</p><p> I am definitely on board. I also notice this kicks the can down the road and dodges the question, and that Tyler would point this out in other contexts. If you want to get buy-in for the importance and tractability of X, you need to help move towards or at least affirm some method Y of getting more X, or it&#39;s all talk and also people won&#39;t know what they are getting behind.</p><p> The answer necessarily involves a combination of financial incentives, lifestyle changes, cultural and norm shifts and attributions of status and honor. Which is dodging the question again, although less so. Concretely, where should we start?</p><p> I would say there are three distinct fronts here – pro-fertility pro-child actions in general, direct pro-marriage incentives and cultural factors.</p><p> We should do the pro-fertility and pro-child actions anyway. Doing this has other benefits that justify doing so, it would make marriage and raising a family more attractive and help move the needle here as well. So much higher subsidies for those who have children, and even more than that get rid of the various albatrosses we tie around parents&#39; necks, that are doubtless driving potential fathers away.</p><p> We can and should combine that by tying some of those financial incentives to marriage, and ensuring that the tax code, including various virtual taxes (such as the taxes imposed by schools in the form of usually-discounted tuition) essentially never penalizes marriage.</p><p> The obvious way to start on this is to offer a universal option – couples can be given the option to file as individuals if filing jointly would be more expensive. And we should make it illegal to consider spousal income or wealth in need-based educational or other similar assessments. Yes, there are obvious concerns and details that need to be worked out there, and it won&#39;t be cheap, but the alternative is forcing people to choose.</p><p> Cultural shifts are harder to mandate. Financial incentives help, but culture also has a life of its own. That part is less my area. I would start with a bigger fight, where we have developed a norm that when a choice has superior outcomes, we are afraid to point this out and reward those who make that choice or say things that look down upon those who do not make that choice, even in relatively mild form. We are going to have to walk some of that back.</p><h4> Don&#39;t Worry, Be Happy</h4><p> Another kind of lie is that unhappy childhoods are good, actually. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1703108053913002219">They&#39;re not.</a></p><blockquote><p> Paul Graham: It&#39;s bullshit that you have to have an unhappy childhood to do great things. You *can* do great things despite having an unhappy childhood, and that misleads people into thinking that it has a positive benefit.</p><p> I want my kids to do great things, and I&#39;m not trying to give them unhappy childhoods so that they can. Exactly the opposite. I know from talking to thousands of YC founders that the best way to make people ambitious is to encourage them.</p><p> It&#39;s certainly a powerful motivation to want to prove people wrong. But if you&#39;re at all independent-minded, you&#39;ll encounter enough resistance to give you plenty of this motivation whether your childhood was unhappy or not.&#39;</p><p> Yheushen.eth: @WalterIsaacson has a slightly different opinion on this.</p><p> Paul Graham: That was what made me write this. It&#39;s not just bullshit, but very dangerous bullshit, because it will allow abusive parents to rationalize and thus continue doing the bad things they&#39;re doing to their kids.</p></blockquote><p> There is indeed a failure mode where you prioritize your child&#39;s present happiness so much that you do not prepare them for the future. What is good for them will not always be what makes them happy. So sometimes you shouldn&#39;t do what makes your kid most happy. Tradeoffs are a thing. That is very different from happiness being an active detriment to ambition or success.</p><h4> You Might Learn Something</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://economistwritingeveryday.com/2023/05/27/the-value-of-student-organizations-and-on-campus-education-anecdotal-evidence-from-tim-keller/">Argument that on-campus education is valuable</a> because being a club officer position is valuable, and generally thousands of students get to &#39;practice working&#39; together, giving practical leadership and other experience in a low-stakes environment. That&#39;s not an argument for education. That&#39;s an argument for work. For doing real things. It&#39;s also saying that on-campus education right now is <em>less fake</em> than online-only education, because the things students do among themselves are real while the core educational experience is fake. Got it.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/RomeoStevens76/status/1656846941337305088">An all too common form of RLHF</a> :</p><blockquote><p> Romeo Stevens: Hypothesis: people with inaction bias were &#39;Copenhagen punished&#39; as children ie they were punished under the Copenhagen interpretation of ethics whereby they were held accountable if they did something poorly instead of rewarded for trying something at all.</p></blockquote><p> This is standard procedure. Constantly, as children and as adults, we are taught that if something is going to go badly, we should avoid interacting with it. If we are going to mess something up, better to not try, we will only get blamed. Parents who understand this problem will go to extraordinary lengths to do the opposite.</p><h4> Restorative Justice Does Not Scale</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/ArmandDoma/status/1685536579803115520">What is up with schools and restorative justice?</a></p><blockquote><p> Armand Domalewski: A recurring pattern I have noticed in education is that it seems particularly prone to fads. New ideas that show initial promise become rapidly adopted at scale without a lot of <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://hechingerreport.org/the-promise-of-restorative-justice-starts-to-falter-under-rigorous-research/">rigorous evaluation</a> or evidence of success.</p><p> Pittsburgh study found that academic performance actually got worse at schools that tried restorative justice, with math test scores for Black students being the hardest hit. But it&#39;s unclear if this is because of bad policy or bad implementation.</p><p> Hechinger Report: In surveys, teachers at the schools that tried restorative justice said that their school climate improved. But students reported that teachers struggled more to manage classroom behavior. I wondered if disruptive behavior in the classroom might have detracted from learning time, or perhaps even worthwhile and productive restorative justice conversations ate away at precious instructional minutes. Either way, it could potentially explain why some kids&#39; performance suffered.</p><p> The <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10964-019-01013-2">Maine study</a> , published online in March 2019 by the Journal of Youth and Adolescence, found no difference in school climate between middle schools that tried restorative justice and those that didn&#39;t. It didn&#39;t look at suspension rates or academic outcomes. But the fact that bullying and other school climate measures didn&#39;t budge is another sign that restorative justice programs aren&#39;t a slam dunk solution to addressing student misbehavior.</p><p> ……</p><p> “Conceptually and theoretically, restorative practices should work,” said Francis Huang, an associate professor at the University of Missouri&#39;s College of Education who is conducting another study of restorative justice in schools in Brooklyn. “But it&#39;s harder.”</p><p> ……</p><p> One bright side for restorative justice was that the more that Maine students reported that they personally experienced elements of restorative justice, such as discussing problems in circles, the more that student felt connected to his or her peers and the less cyber-bullying he or she experienced.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.rand.org/pubs/research_reports/RR2840.html">Rand report</a> key findings:</p><ul><li> Implementation of restorative practices through PERC improved overall school climates, as rated by teachers.</li><li> Implementation of restorative practices reduced the average suspension rate: During the study period, average suspension rates decreased in both PERC and non-PERC schools, but rates decreased more in PERC schools.</li><li> Suspension rates of African American students and of those from low-income families also went down in PERC schools, shrinking the disparities in suspension rates between African American and white students and between low- and higher-income students.</li><li> Academic outcomes did not improve in PERC schools, and actually worsened for grades 6–8.</li><li> Arrest rates among PERC schools did not decrease.</li></ul></blockquote><p> The core problem with restorative justice is that it is not justice.</p><p> That is not a claim that it is a bad thing. Most useful policies are not justice.</p><p> Instead, it is a claim that:</p><ol><li> This is poorly named. This should be called conflict mediation or something.</li><li> This aims to address root causes of individual conflicts, which can be great.</li><li> But which is not incentive compatible with preventing future conflicts.</li><li> Nor does it provide an actual sense of individual justice.</li><li> Thus, it needs careful implementation and a mixed strategy, or will backfire.</li></ol><p> If you have a system that is mostly working well, where people are mostly cooperating, then such initiatives have the necessary groundwork and can succeed. If you do not have that, then you are giving the green light to bad actors and such policies seem doomed unless you also fix the other problems. Thus it is an especially strong candidate for working in a pilot program and then failing when scaled up.</p><h4> Other Things In Brief</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/oscredwin/status/1673475939227901953">Studies keep showing sugar does not cause hyperactivity in children</a> .</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2023/08/the-wv-canary-in-the-coal-mine.html?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-wv-canary-in-the-coal-mine">West Virginia University cuts 7% of faculty and 9% of its majors</a> , including moving its foreign language instruction online. The reduction reflects a larger reduction in enrollment. It also seems like they made highly reasonable cuts, to the extent one cannot trim the administrative staff instead.</p><p> Daycare is often thought to be an inadequate substitute for individualized (maternal or otherwise) child care. <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/wesyang/status/1690708622949367809">The results from Quebec&#39;s universal daycare, including for infants under the age of 1, do not seem great</a> . I look at what went into our children, especially at young ages, and even if you discard all other considerations I have no idea how to duplicate anything like it at a 5-to-1 caregiver ratio. Someone needs to give direct attention to that kid more than 20% of the time. Do the math. The efficiency gains available are limited. There are also huge issues with continuity of care, which definitely matters.</p><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/webdevMason/status/1707123181205815365">Most homework is truly evil</a> . It is work justified in the name of training children that their time is not their own and they will later be forced to do endless piles of pointless busywork, so they&#39;d better do pointless busywork now.</p><blockquote><p> Katharine Birbalsingh: Out of 6.5 hours, you can&#39;t find the time for an hour&#39;s homework?</p><p> Mike Solana: before middle school, homework serves no purpose but to traumatize children. do your job and teach them in the classroom. when they&#39;re home, let them play.</p><p> Mason: A really sad trend I&#39;ve noticed is parents who appreciate homework because it gives them a prescribed, unambiguous way to be an “involved” parent and because they don&#39;t respect the ways their children choose to use their time when they&#39;re not forced.</p></blockquote><p> Imagine if I said the same thing to a worker, you have 6.5 hours at home and you can&#39;t find time for this hour of extra paperwork that we don&#39;t even use? People somehow don&#39;t think children&#39;s time has value if it isn&#39;t being used on school. Let your children play.</p><p> I would go so far as to say that it&#39;s fine to ask children to do some amount of homework-style work, but if it&#39;s so valuable then set aside school time for that. When the work is done, the work is done.</p><h4> The Lighter Side</h4><p> <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://twitter.com/patio11/status/1702084458185167165">At least someone&#39;s password is not so easy to guess.</a></p><p> Patrick McKenzie: Lillian is having trouble playing Guess the Password in math class because the material assumes the kids can&#39;t do the math, and because she hasn&#39;t yet learned how to play Guess the Password with an American teacher.</p><p> Humorous example:</p><blockquote><p> Diego&#39;s homework had a page torn off. He was trying to add 243 and 100. The two remaining digits were 54. How can his teacher know he is incorrect without seeing the digit in the hundreds place?</p><p> Justify your answer. This was in a lesson about odd plus even equals odd, etc.</p><p> The answer the question “wants” is “Because an odd number plus an even number is an odd number, an even answer is always wrong.”</p><p> The answer Lillian wanted to give: “She can add, because she is a teacher.”</p><p> Me: Let&#39;s pretend she can&#39;t do that in her head.</p><p> Lillian: ARE YOU JOKING?</p></blockquote><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/childhood-roundup-3#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j/childhood-roundup-3<guid ispermalink="false"> M3x2bGyJayxi52z3j</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Zvi]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:30:09 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[My simple model for Alignment vs Capability]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 12:07 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> I have a simple model of the alignment vs. capabilities question. I am writing it down because after chewing on Michael Nielson&#39;s post about <a href="https://michaelnotebook.com/xrisk/index.html">existential risk from AI</a> , I thought it was great but was unsatisfied with with the idea an alignment dilemma. I wasn&#39;t the only person to <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/8Q7JwFyC8hqYYmCkC/link-post-michael-nielsen-s-notes-on-existential-risk-from?commentId=uuqrjTaf5dZ6HtTmy">feel that way</a> , but neither was I able to find any satisfactory source describing the (tension? dichotomy? tradeoff?). The real rub of Nielsen&#39;s dilemma for me is that it was expressed in terms of accelerationism, which is a form of one-dialism, and <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Zzar6BWML555xSt6Z/the-dial-of-progress">one-dialism is wrong</a> .</p><p> I note there is nothing actually new here; I am quite sure these considerations were all covered, and more besides, back when MIRI getting started. Yet we weren&#39;t speaking in terms of alignment vs capability then, and capabilities were a less urgent concern, and regardless of what we have said before <i>here,</i> people aren&#39;t talking about models in public <i>now</i> . So a simple model it is.</p><p><strong>背景</strong></p><p>The way I understand the alignment vs capabilities question is that capabilities research eventually cashes out as AGI, and alignment research cashes out as aligned AGI, so in this context alignment research is effectively a subset of capabilities research. I expect this to apply more or less continuously, where increasingly-capable-but-not-AGIs will still need to be aligned.</p><p> What I want to accomplish with the model is to have something we can use to make heuristic judgments about research: in particular things like whether to support, fund, or pursue it, and how to make comparisons between different research agendas. This is <i>not</i> for doing things like predicting timelines directly, or the course of AI research overall, or the future of a given research org.</p><p> <strong>Reject Acceleration</strong></p><p> My chief objection to thinking and speaking in terms of acceleration is that it is causally useless. I make analogy to GDP as an economic metric: if a particular industry is growing very fast, and we want that industry to succeed but also to avoid catastrophic industrial accidents, one scalar number that refers to a big pile of all the activity adds nothing. We cannot build safer industrial facilities by saying &quot;but GDP should go up <i>less.</i> &quot; Likewise for talking to investors, and also to regulators. Acceleration is purely a rhetorical device, which is why we should be unsurprised to see it appear in the public conversation, and also why it should be treated with caution.</p><p> <strong>Think Paths to Success Instead</strong></p><p> I prefer to think in terms of paths to success, in the sense (but not rigorous definition) of paths through phase space. Here we are thinking about paths through the phase space of the world, specifically those which lead to AGI and the smaller subspace of aligned AGI. Further, we are just thinking about the research, as distinct from thinking about orgs, number of researchers, funding, etc.</p><p> I frequently recall ET Jaynes&#39;s paper <a href="https://bayes.wustl.edu/etj/articles/macroscopic.prediction.pdf">Macroscopic Prediction</a> , and in particular this bit:</p><blockquote><p> Gibbs&#39; variational principle is, therefore, so simple in rationale that one almost hesitates to utter such a triviality; it says &quot;predict that final state that can be realized by Nature in the greatest number of ways, while agreeing with your macroscopic information.&quot;</p></blockquote><p> In our context, something becomes more likely the more paths there are to accomplishing it.</p><p> So how do we count the paths?</p><p> <strong>Count the Paths</strong></p><p> We want to identify the actionable parts of research. For our purposes, &quot;leads to future research&quot; and &quot;applicable to real systems&quot; both count as actionable. I think directly about angles of attack in the sense of Hamming&#39;s <a href="https://gwern.net/doc/science/1986-hamming#problems-with-attacks">important research problem criterion</a> , where what Hamming is talking about is &quot;a way to make progress on the problem.&quot;</p><p> What Hamming calls angles of attack are what I think an alignment research agenda produces: ways to make progress on the problem of alignment (likewise for major AI labs: ways to make progress on the problem of capability). Mechanistic Interpretability is a research agenda. Suppose they discover a new behavior they call <i>schlokking</i> .</p><p> Example 1: Another paper expands on the <i>schlokking</i> behavior. This counts as a path because it lead to future research.</p><p> Example 2: Another paper reports successfully predicting the outputs of an LLM, based on the <i>schlokking</i> behavior. This counts as a path because it was applied to a real system.</p><p> Example 3: Before either 1 or 2, a researcher had an idea and poked around some weights. They thought to themselves &quot;I&#39;m pretty sure I found something weird. Why does it look so <i>schlokky</i> ?&quot; This does <i>not</i> count as a path by itself, because it hadn&#39;t gone anywhere yet.</p><p> This gives us a simple <strong>path heuristic</strong> : something good enough to get a name, that later research refers to or gets applied to real systems.</p><p> <strong>Dual Use Accounting</strong></p><p> The same rules apply for capability paths, and we count paths on the capability side the same way. Continuing with <i>schlokking</i> :</p><p> Example 4: A paper explains how they optimized their training procedure to exploit the <i>schlokking</i> behavior to reduce training time. This counts as a capability path, as applied to a real system.</p><p> Example 5: A paper explains how <i>schlokking</i> is <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcVfceTsD0A&amp;t=2220s">actually pretty suboptimal</a> , and through deliberate design they can get the same behavior faster. This counts as a capability path, as lead to future research.</p><p> <strong>Consider the Ratio</strong></p><p> Since each agenda is likely to produce paths to both alignment and capability, we can look at the ratio of alignment paths to capability paths, which I simply label the <strong>path ratio</strong> .</p><p> Example 6: In the previous examples we count two alignment paths, and also two capabilities paths. Therefore the <strong>path ratio</strong> of alignment:capability is 2:2, or simplified 1:1.</p><p> Between counting the paths and looking at the path ratio, we have a few ways to sort research output:</p><ul><li> The highest ratio of alignment:capability is the lowest-risk</li><li> The highest number of alignment paths generated is the most productive (likewise for capability)</li><li> The highest number of total paths is probably the most insightful</li><li> Etc.</li></ul><p> At this point is when we can actually use the model to engage with the alignment vs capability question. The intuitive answer is naturally to favor the lowest-risk research, which is to say the highest path ratio of alignment:capability; if I read the public conversation right this even extends to <i>forsaking</i> any research agenda that adds any capability paths at all, which is to say the alignment:capability path ratio must be infinite for some people. I think this is wrong.</p><p> <strong>The Total and the Threshold</strong></p><p> I think the strong position against adding capability paths is wrong for two reasons based on this model.</p><p> The first reason is that I claim we should be concerned with how many ways there are to make progress on alignment vs ways to make progress on capability overall. In the model that is the <strong>total ratio</strong> of paths over all the research that has been done to date. This is a comparative measure that is proportional to how much of an advantage capability has currently. While this could plausibly be made fully quantitative with a sufficiently broad literature review, I lack a broad base in the literature and so I have been using a gut-level fermi estimate instead.</p><p> Example 7: An alignment:capability ratio of 1:1 suggests progress is about equal, which feels patently absurd. So the real question is whether we are looking more like:</p><ul><li> 1:10, which is to say capability has a 10x advantage.</li><li> 1:100, which is to say capability has a 100x advantage.</li><li> 1:1000, which is to say capability has a 1000x advantage.</li></ul><p> Of these, 1:100 feels the most right to me. That being said, I will lean on the the simplicity of the optimistic estimate of 1:10 for examples.</p><p> The second reason is that we have so few paths to success with alignment, in absolute terms. In the trivial case, if the path ratio alignment:capability is 0, which is to say that there are no viable alignment paths at all, then we are simply doomed unless we are completely wrong about the risk from AI in the first place. If the aggregate number of alignment paths is still very small, then the question of whether we are doomed is reduced to the question of whether these few paths succeed or fail, which is the in-model way of saying we still need more alignment research.</p><p> These two things interact to let us look at a question like &quot;Should I go into alignment research?&quot; or &quot;Should I pursue my idea for a research agenda?&quot;. If the total number of alignment paths is zero or very small, the answer is trivially <i>yes</i> , because otherwise there is no hope, capabilities be damned. If the total number of alignment paths is high enough that we care about controlling risk, then I claim the <strong>heuristic threshold</strong> for <i>yes</i> is whether it makes the <strong>total ratio</strong> better.</p><p> Example 8: If your total ratio is 1:10, then your answer should be <i>yes</i> if you can be confident you will not accidentally produce more than <i>10x</i> paths to capability as paths to alignment. If the path ratio you wind up with from your research agenda is 1:9, that is still a net gain.</p><p> I notice this is <i>extremely</i> permissive relative to people who express concern about enhancing capabilities. I have not seen a single proposal for an approach to alignment that I thought would provide 10x more ways to help capability. As it stands, my model does not predict that alignment research can&#39;t accidentally cause AGI, so much as predict it is almost always worth the gamble.</p><p> <strong>Refinements</strong></p><p> The model is simple unto brutality. I can anticipate several concerns, most of which could probably be addressed.</p><ul><li> <strong>Doesn&#39;t talk about probability.</strong> That is deliberate - there needs to be a way of answering &quot;The probability of <i>what</i> , exactly?&quot; and in the current state of conversation about capability vs alignment there doesn&#39;t seem to be an answer. This model isn&#39;t even really quantitative; all I&#39;m actually doing is using a few numbers to get some rank ordering.</li><li> <strong>Probability aside, does not address uncertainty.</strong> I have mostly been thinking about this in terms of determining results from other agendas before launching your own, which should be answerable. That being said, I have been treating uncertainty as mostly being a range of values in the path ratio, something like [0-3]:[0-5] or similar for simplicity. A distribution of possible outcomes would be better, but I don&#39;t have enough information to tell what those would look like other than to just guess gaussian.</li><li> <strong>Doesn&#39;t talk about time.</strong> Time is another thing that I believe needs a model to work on. I have been considering a unit of time in the form of one research cycle, which I feel like lasts approximately from the time a research agenda coalesces to the time that the rest of the community digests its outputs well enough to start trying to use them. This is still just comparative at best - for example, I think it would be a reasonable claim that the research cycle for capabilities is faster than for alignment for various reasons. Conceiving of it this way would effectively count as some multiplier for the number of capability paths generated (which is the converse of how I usually see this kind of thing tracked, where each research path is treated as a small speed multiplier). My suspicion is that the real difference would be between concrete vs theoretical, because running experiments gives you more information, and it also seems like a bigger fraction of capabilities research is concrete. But how much would that change if people weren&#39;t avoiding concrete alignment research on the grounds that capability might also benefit?</li><li> <strong>All paths are not created equal - doesn&#39;t talk about quality or impact</strong> . This is mostly because I have very little sense of how we would compare them in terms of whatever qualities they might have. A way to increase the granularity one level would be to use a comparative measure again; we could have a path <i>size</i> , which is to say regular paths are worth one path, but especially good ones might be worth two or three regular paths, up to some crucial or paradigm-defining breakthrough value. I slightly prefer a size implementation to a multiple implementation because of how it feels like it would effect transmission. As a practical example, we might consider research picked up by two major AI labs as having twice the path size as a different path picked up by only one.</li></ul><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8/my-simple-model-for-alignment-vs-capability#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8/my-simple-model-for-alignment-vs-capability<guid ispermalink="false"> hmJHbSHnbfC4CZmh8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[ryan_b]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:07:42 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Next year in Jerusalem: The brilliant ideas and radiant legacy of Miriam Lipschutz Yevick [in relation to current AI debates]]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 9:06 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> This is a link post for <a href="https://3quarksdaily.com/3quarksdaily/2023/10/next-year-in-jerusalem-the-brilliant-ideas-and-radiant-legacy-of-miriam-lipschutz-yevick-in-relation-to-current-ai-debates.html">an article I just published in <i>3 Quarks Daily</i></a> . No one has conceptualized the phenomenon of human thought in technical terms more deeply than Yevick did in her 1975 article, <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/0031-3203(75)90005-9">Holographic or Fourier Logic</a> . Her conception was certainly incomplete – she knew that. It may also be wrong, but that&#39;s something that has yet to be determined. That requires analysis and discussion.</p><p> I&#39;ve quoted Yevick at some length in an earlier post at LessWrong: <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/nupJLBe2xxbB8KJxc/miriam-yevick-on-why-both-symbols-and-networks-are-necessary">Miriam Yevick on why both symbols and networks are necessary for artificial minds</a> .</p><p> Here is the introduction to the article:</p><p></p><p> <i>Oh, Ariela, daughter of the People of the Book, the work of the mind is our game!</i><br> <i>– Miriam Yevick</i></p><p> I first became aware of Miriam Lipschutz Yevick through my interest in human perception and thought. I believed that her 1975 paper, <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/0031320375900059">Holographic or Fourier Logic</a> , was quite important. David Hays and I gave it a prominent place in our 1988 paper, <a href="https://www.academia.edu/235116/Principles_and_Development_of_Natural_Intelligence">Principles and Development of Natural Intelligence</a> , and in <a href="https://www.academia.edu/238608/Metaphor_Recognition_and_Neural_Process">a related paper on metaphor</a> .</p><p> Since Yevick&#39;s work shares a mathematics with some work in machine vision and image recognition, I wondered whether or not that paper had been cited. Moreover, that work is relevant to current debates about the need for symbolic processing in artificial intelligence (AI). <a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF02985683">As recently as 2007 Yevick was arguing</a> , albeit informally, that human thought requires both poetic, Gestalt, or holographic processing, on the one hand, and analytic, propositional, or logical on the other.</p><p> As far as I can tell, her work has been forgotten.</p><p> That is one thing. But there is more. I become curious about her, this woman, Miriam Lipschutz Yevick.</p><p> What about <i>her</i> ? And so I began reading her 2012 memoire, <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Testament-Ariela-Miriam-Lipschutz-Yevick-ebook/dp/B00BEZVTX2/ref=tmm_kin_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;qid=&amp;sr="><i>A Testament for Ariela</i></a> , which takes the form of letters she had written to her grand-daughter in a three-year period in the mid-1980s. The memoire says nothing about her mathematical ideas, though it does mention that in 1947 she became the fifth woman to get a mathematics Ph.D. from MIT. She also talks of her friendship and correspondence with <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_Bohm">David Bohm</a> , who became a noted quantum theorist. It quickly became clear that she had not had an academic career worthy of her intellectual gifts. Yet she did not seem bitter about that. She had a rich and fulfilling life.</p><p> This essay is about both her life and her holographic logic. The work on holographic logic leads me to a harsh assessment of the current debate about artificial intelligence. Thinking about her life leads me to conclude with an optimistic look at the future: <i>next year in Jerusalem</i> .</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/jweG3Y9hn68ePLbv6/next-year-in-jerusalem-the-brilliant-ideas-and-radiant#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/jweG3Y9hn68ePLbv6/next-year-in-jerusalem-the-brilliant-ideas-and-radiant<guid ispermalink="false"> jweG3Y9hn68ePLbv6</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Bill Benzon]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm a Former Israeli Officer. AMA]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 8:33 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> Hey everyone! Long time lurker, first time poster.</p><p> My name is Yovel Rom. I&#39;m an Israeli data scientist. I served in the IDF in an elite program called Talpiot, which consists of a physics udergrad and broad military education (basically West Point for technology people, but more elitist), then as a data scientist, and finished my service as a captain. I&#39;m currently at home, since I finished my service two years ago and they don&#39;t need many data scientists right now.</p><p> Ask me anything. I&#39;m as updated on the situation as a person with no formal position can be (which might be less than you expect).</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi/i-m-a-former-israeli-officer-ama#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi/ima-former-israeli-officer-ama<guid ispermalink="false"> zJCKn4TSXcCXzc6fi</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Yovel Rom]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:36:28 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Become a PIBBSS Research Affiliate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 7:41 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> <i>TL;DR：</i> <a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/affiliate"><i><strong>PIBBSS 正在招聘研究附属人员！</strong></i></a> <i><strong>&nbsp;</strong></i></p><p> <i>PIBBSS 是一项研究计划，旨在促进利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似性开展工作，并利用这些见解来使人工智能系统安全、有益和一致。</i></p><p> <i>We want to support excellent researchers pursuing “PIBBSS-style” AI alignment research by providing them with tailored longer-term support: a full-time salary, a lively research community, operational support and more.最初承诺期限为 6 个月，有可能延长至 12 个月或更长。</i></p><p><i><strong>如需申请，请点击</strong></i><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwMZBTMErBhuXNGNfY_dubgcV8FT3eqYOioxluV82v1V766Q/viewform?usp=sf_link"><i><strong><u>此处</u></strong></i></a><i><strong>。</strong> To be considered as part of the next iteration of affiliates, apply by <strong>November 5th</strong> .</i></p><hr><p>在<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/"><u>PIBBSS</u></a> （“生物和社会系统中智能行为的原理”），我们的使命是利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似之处，促进人工智能对齐研究。 （有关更多详细信息，请参阅下面的“关于 PIBBSS 和我们的研究重点”部分。）</p><p>自 PIBBSS 于 2022 年成立以来，我们已经开展了两次为期<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/fellowship"><u>3 个月的研究奖学金</u></a>，以及<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/mqvxR9nrXAzRr3ow9/announcing-key-phenomena-in-ai-risk-facilitated-reading"><u>一个阅读小组</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMo5Ei9xLHbk9sqNMSH3mdQ"><u>一个持续的演讲者系列</u></a>以及一系列研究静修活动，探索符合 PIBBSS 研究兴趣的主题。我们的校友继续在 OpenAI、Anthropic、复杂系统对齐研究小组和学术界等机构以及通过独立资助进行人工智能对齐研究。</p><p>虽然我们继续对这些活动的价值感到兴奋，但我们也相信还有更多价值！特别是，我们看到了一项旨在<strong>支持与 PIBBSS 的研究赌注一致的长期、更持续的研究工作的</strong>计划的潜力。</p><p>因此，我们很高兴推出新的<a href="https://www.pibbss.ai/affiliate"><strong>PIBBSS 联盟计划</strong></a>。</p><h2><strong>联盟计划的目标和主要特点</strong></h2><p>我们运行该计划的核心<strong>目标</strong>是反事实地帮助就人工智能风险、协调和治理问题取得实质性、高质量和清晰的研究进展。该附属计划旨在通过以高度定制的方式支持有前途的个人研究人员来确定、发展和推进他们的个人研究议程，从而实现这一目标。</p><p>具体的<strong>成功场景</strong>可能看起来像（但不限于）附属机构发布有洞察力的研究成果；加入现有研究小组的努力或建立新的研究小组；识别、确定范围、测试并吸引新的或被忽视的研究途径；完善他们的个人研究议程并获得独立资金； ETC。</p><p> PIBBSS 联盟计划具有以下<strong>主要特点</strong>：</p><ul><li>附属公司的<strong>工资</strong>为 5,000 美元/月/FTE。我们愿意向优秀的候选人支付更高的薪水。<ul><li>默认情况下，我们正在寻找将全职加入该计划的附属机构。也就是说，我们愿意在适当的情况下适应附属公司的情况，例如以兼职方式加入该计划。我们还有能力为那些不想离开当前研究职位的人提供支持。</li></ul></li><li>附属机构受益于一系列旨在帮助他们专注于并推进研究工作的<strong>支持结构</strong>，例如：<ul><li><strong>季度研究静修</strong>会将附属机构以及其他联盟研究人员聚集在一起，形成我们的扩展网络</li><li><strong>个性化研究和战略支持</strong>，通常以每两周一次与您的负责人通话的形式（可以选择根据附属机构的需求和偏好调整支持频率）</li><li><strong>访问 PIBBSS 研究社区</strong>和扩展网络，包括加入我们的 Slack 空间、量身定制的介绍、参加研讨会的机会等。</li><li><strong>财务和行政支持</strong>，例如访问相关研究会议、访问基础模型并在研究需要时进行计算等。</li><li><strong>根据附属公司的需求/偏好使用办公空间。</strong></li><li>注意：该计划的一个关键特点是根据最能帮助我们的附属机构在研究方面取得进展的反事实因素，为他们提供高度定制的支持。因此，上述列表虽然具有代表性，但不一定完全准确或全面。</li></ul></li><li><strong>联属关系的初始期限为 6 个月</strong>，届时我们将审查联属关系是否可以<strong>延长至 12 个月</strong>。在特殊情况下，我们将提供 12 个月的初始报价。<ul><li>我们的愿景是，附属计划为有前途的研究人员提供一个严肃的长期家园，这些研究人员在 1 年或更长时间的时间尺度上从事 PIBBSS 式的人工智能对齐研究，包括永久职位的可能性。</li></ul></li><li>我们希望巩固并加强 PIBBSS 在过去两年中建立的<strong>支持性、好奇心和奉献精神的文化</strong>。我们关心良好的认知实践，同时探索理解复杂世界的复杂性，并特别强调<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/wi3upQibefMcFs5to/levels-of-pluralism"><u>认知多元化</u></a>在此过程中的价值。</li></ul><p><br>目前，我们以<strong>实验性的</strong>视角来看待联属网络营销计划 - 测试该计划可以提供重大价值的假设，并了解我们究竟如何才能最有效地支持我们的联属网络营销商。根据我们了解到的情况，我们可能会扩大或缩小规模，简化计划或使其更适合各个附属机构，旨在建立有时间限制或开放期限的附属机构，或者采取其他措施来增加影响力该程序。</p><h2><strong>联盟计划的要求</strong></h2><p>联盟计划是一个非常开放的计划，要求有限。以下是我们向附属公司提出的要求：</p><ul><li>提交反映您的研究进展和前瞻性研究计划的<strong>季度</strong><strong>报告</strong>。<ul><li>这些报告旨在通过提供问责结构并鼓励他们定期进行缩小和反思来帮助附属机构。它们还帮助我们了解附属机构一直在做什么，以及我们是否可以做些什么来支持他们更好地前进。</li></ul></li><li>参加我们的~季度<strong>研究静修活动</strong></li><li><strong>真诚致力于</strong>在人工智能安全、协调和治理相关问题上取得进展，并建设性地、求实地和善意地参与我们共同的认知文化</li></ul><h2><strong>我们在理想的联营公司中寻找什么？</strong></h2><p>选择附属机构是因为他们能够以高度自主的方式在人工智能领域追求有前途的 PIBBSS 一致研究方向。因此，我们正在寻找以下特征（的组合）：</p><ul><li>您的专业领域的学术能力/才干</li><li>对人工智能风险和协调有深入的了解</li><li>良好研究判断/品味的证据</li><li>良好研究生产力的证据，包括强大的自我管理技能</li><li>您提议的研究方向的前景</li><li>能够从 PIBBSS 提供的功能中反事实地受益</li></ul><p>请注意，根据我们的经验，优秀的 PIBBSS 风格的研究人员往往具有非标准背景。因此，我们希望鼓励具有不同背景和观点的个人申请。</p><h2><strong>关于 PIBBSS 和我们的研究重点</strong></h2><p>PIBBSS 是一项研究计划，旨在促进利用自然系统和人工系统中智能行为之间的相似性开展工作，并利用这些见解来使人工智能系统安全、有益和一致。</p><p>从本质上讲，我们相信，对复杂自然和社会系统的研究可以帮助我们更好地了解在人造基质中实施此类行为所涉及的风险，并提高我们开发人工智能系统的能力，使其可靠地显示所需的安全性和可治理性相关属性。 （我们在<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/FuToH2KHxKmJLGk2B/ai-alignment-as-navigating-the-space-of-intelligent"><u>这篇文章</u></a>以及<a href="https://youtu.be/2UabDJKVQcI?si=abcbqyDX6xPvcgmK"><u>这次演讲</u></a>中更详细地描述了我们的认知赌注的性质和一些背景假设）。</p><p>为了对我们感兴趣的研究类型提供更具体的指导，以下是我们过去支持的工作示例：</p><ul><li>旨在<strong>对人工智能系统之间的多智能体交互</strong>产生的动态有原则性的理解， <strong>&nbsp;</strong>例如通过对<a href="https://youtu.be/h8ZbjKS9OTA"><u>行军蚂蚁集体行为的研究</u></a>或进化生物学和生态学的模型</li><li>探索如何在开发<strong>模型评估</strong>中纳入对多智能体人工智能动力学的理解[即将发布]</li><li>探索<strong>可解释性的新途径</strong>，例如<a href="https://youtu.be/cvA3C68Hzqg"><u>可解释性的几何方法</u></a>和<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2dx_VRZtoCs&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>奇异学习理论</u></a></li><li>建立<strong>自然化的能动性理论</strong>，例如探索<a href="https://youtu.be/vx9iHJLd9xI"><u>抽象概念在生活现象中的作用</u></a>；检验<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/BzYmJYECAc3xyCTt6/the-plan-2022-update#What_high_level_progress_have_you_personally_made_in_the_past_year__Any_mistakes_made_or_things_to_change_going_forward_"><u>生命游戏中的自然抽象假设</u></a>；思考对自己应用意向立场的主体的特征<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bFGcBrnrdmk&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>（“自动意向主体”）</u></a> ；或应用动力系统视角来看待目标导向的行为</li><li>解决<strong>决策理论</strong>中的问题，例如<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uNv1Cq-aVKY&amp;t=46s&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>形式化无更新决策理论</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ivqSoZJEiBc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>自我修改的鲁棒性</u></a>，或者尝试连接<a href="https://www.alignmentforum.org/posts/rQDYQrDjPGqjrf8Mk/bridging-expected-utility-maximization-and-optimization"><u>期望效用最大化和优化。</u></a></li><li>对<strong>价值观和实践推理进行更现实的解释</strong>，并探索它们对我们理解人工智能对齐问题的影响[即将发布]</li><li>评估<strong>现有</strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=05iQTypREPc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><strong><u>法律工具</u></strong></a>在减少人工智能灾难性风险方面的潜力和局限性</li><li>测试人工智能对齐与其他领域/主题之间<strong>富有成效的认知交换</strong>的潜力，例如<a href="https://humanvaluesandartificialagency.com/"><u>人工生命</u></a>、 <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RwEKg5cjkKQ&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowshiphttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RwEKg5cjkKQ&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>基础认知</u></a>、<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7-wvArSvHsc&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>形态计算</u></a>、主动推理、批判社会理论等。</li><li>着眼于<strong>科学哲学（以及特殊科学），</strong>寻找使<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/FuToH2KHxKmJLGk2B/ai-alignment-as-navigating-the-space-of-intelligent"><u>我们的哲学成为现实的方法。</u></a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=itvIBZ8a5BU&amp;t=947s&amp;pp=ygURcGliYnNzIGZlbGxvd3NoaXA%3D"><u>研究</u></a>。<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUxTiHUazCo&amp;ab_channel=PIBBSSFellowship"><u>努力</u></a>。 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/CewHdaAjEvG3bpc6C/epistemic-artefacts-of-conceptual-ai-alignment-research"><u>更多</u></a>。 <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/b9sGz74ayftqPBDYv/the-space-of-systems-and-the-space-of-maps"><u>富有成效的</u></a>。</li></ul><p>我们的研究员和合作者带来了许多领域的专业知识来解决人工智能一致性问题，包括但不限于：</p><ul><li>生态</li><li>进化和发育生物学</li><li>系统生物学</li><li>生物物理学</li><li>神经科学</li><li>认知科学</li><li>语言学</li><li>法律理论</li><li>政治理论</li><li>经济理论</li><li>社会理论</li><li>复杂系统研究</li><li>控制论</li><li>网络科学</li><li>物理</li><li>科学哲学</li></ul><h2><strong>如何申请</strong></h2><p>申请现已开放。您可以通过<a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScwMZBTMErBhuXNGNfY_dubgcV8FT3eqYOioxluV82v1V766Q/viewform?usp=sf_link"><u>此链接</u></a>进行申请。</p><p>我们每季度接受新的附属机构。 To be considered as part of the next iteration, apply by <strong>November 5th</strong> .</p><p>我们预计在未来 6 个月内雇用 2-6 家（中位数 4 家）附属机构。</p><p><strong><u>关于申请流程：</u></strong>申请流程的细节可能因候选人而异，我们认为哪些信息最能帮助我们做出明智的决定。在大多数情况下，初始阶段（申请表）之后是一次或多次采访，以更深入地讨论您的研究。我们也可能会联系您的推荐人，或者在某些情况下，要求您提交约 2-5 小时的工作任务。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad/become-a-pibbss-research-affiliate-1#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad/become-a-pibbss-research-affiliate-1<guid ispermalink="false"> JvL3SC6tPjFyCiHad</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Nora_Ammann]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:41:03 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Epistemic Motif of Abstract-Concrete Cycles & Domain Expansion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 3:28 AM GMT<br/><br/><p> <i>(crossposted from</i> <a href="https://dalcybremin.github.io/posts/2023-10-09-epistemic-motif.html"><i>here</i></a> <i>)</i></p><p>我注意到在数学和哲学的相当广泛的环境中出现了某些认知主题（即清晰且一致的知识生产模式）。这是我认为相当强大的一个：</p><h2> Abstract-Concrete Cycles and Domain Expansion</h2><p>给定一个模拟某些概念的特定对象[结构/定义]，我们可以通过[抽象出它的一些特征]或[实例化它的更具体版本]来修改它，因为我们[<a href="https://tsvibt.blogspot.com/2022/05/expanding-domain-of-discourse-reveals.html">修改讨论的领域</a>]该对象伴随着[来自现实世界的直觉果汁指导我们的搜索]继续运作。在各种抽象级别上重复此操作，您最终会得到一组更丰富的对象。</p><h3>其如何发挥作用的示例</h3><p><i><strong>空间</strong></i></p><p>Here&#39;s an example from mathematics <i>(inspired from</i> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xun4c-NXgW8"><i>here</i></a> <i>)</i> .你对想要捕捉的<i>事物</i>有一些具体的概念，比如空间。因此，您可以使用一些立即显而易见的定义（例如<span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\mathbb{R}^n"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-msubsup"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-texatom"><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-ams-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">R</span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sup" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: 0.615em; padding-left: 0px; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">n</span></span></span> ）</span></span></span></span></span></span>来操作它<style>.mjx-chtml {display: inline-block; line-height: 0; text-indent: 0; text-align: left; text-transform: none; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 100%; font-size-adjust: none; letter-spacing: normal; word-wrap: normal; word-spacing: normal; white-space: nowrap; float: none; direction: ltr; max-width: none; max-height: none; min-width: 0; min-height: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; padding: 1px 0}
.MJXc-display {display: block; text-align: center; margin: 1em 0; padding: 0}
.mjx-chtml[tabindex]:focus, body :focus .mjx-chtml[tabindex] {display: inline-table}
.mjx-full-width {text-align: center; display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em}
.mjx-math {display: inline-block; border-collapse: separate; border-spacing: 0}
.mjx-math * {display: inline-block; -webkit-box-sizing: content-box!important; -moz-box-sizing: content-box!important; box-sizing: content-box!important; text-align: left}
.mjx-numerator {display: block; text-align: center}
.mjx-denominator {display: block; text-align: center}
.MJXc-stacked {height: 0; position: relative}
.MJXc-stacked > * {position: absolute}
.MJXc-bevelled > * {display: inline-block}
.mjx-stack {display: inline-block}
.mjx-op {display: block}
.mjx-under {display: table-cell}
.mjx-over {display: block}
.mjx-over > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-under > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sup {display: block}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sub {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presup {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presub {display: block}
.mjx-delim-h > .mjx-char {display: inline-block}
.mjx-surd {vertical-align: top}
.mjx-surd + .mjx-box {display: inline-flex}
.mjx-mphantom * {visibility: hidden}
.mjx-merror {background-color: #FFFF88; color: #CC0000; border: 1px solid #CC0000; padding: 2px 3px; font-style: normal; font-size: 90%}
.mjx-annotation-xml {line-height: normal}
.mjx-menclose > svg {fill: none; stroke: currentColor; overflow: visible}
.mjx-mtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mlabeledtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mtd {display: table-cell; text-align: center}
.mjx-label {display: table-row}
.mjx-box {display: inline-block}
.mjx-block {display: block}
.mjx-span {display: inline}
.mjx-char {display: block; white-space: pre}
.mjx-itable {display: inline-table; width: auto}
.mjx-row {display: table-row}
.mjx-cell {display: table-cell}
.mjx-table {display: table; width: 100%}
.mjx-line {display: block; height: 0}
.mjx-strut {width: 0; padding-top: 1em}
.mjx-vsize {width: 0}
.MJXc-space1 {margin-left: .167em}
.MJXc-space2 {margin-left: .222em}
.MJXc-space3 {margin-left: .278em}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-display {display: table!important}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-inline {display: inline!important; margin-right: -1px}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-default {display: block!important; clear: both}
.mjx-ex-box {display: inline-block!important; position: absolute; overflow: hidden; min-height: 0; max-height: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; width: 1px; height: 60ex}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-left-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: left}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-right-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: right}
.mjx-test-display .mjx-right-box {display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em!important; min-width: 0; max-width: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-R {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-I {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-B {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-BI {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-ams-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R,MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R,MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-BI {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI,MJXc-TeX-math-BIx,MJXc-TeX-math-BIw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R,MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I,MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix,MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-script-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R,MJXc-TeX-script-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-type-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R,MJXc-TeX-type-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R,MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B,MJXc-TeX-main-Bx,MJXc-TeX-main-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I,MJXc-TeX-main-Ix,MJXc-TeX-main-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R,MJXc-TeX-main-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I,MJXc-TeX-math-Ix,MJXc-TeX-math-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-size1-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R,MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size2-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R,MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size3-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R,MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size4-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R,MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R,MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R; src: local('MathJax_AMS'), local('MathJax_AMS-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_AMS-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_AMS-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_AMS-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic Bold'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur Bold'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI; src: local('MathJax_Math BoldItalic'), local('MathJax_Math-BoldItalic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIx; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-weight: bold; font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Bold'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Italic'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R; src: local('MathJax_Script'), local('MathJax_Script-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Script-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Script-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Script-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R; src: local('MathJax_Typewriter'), local('MathJax_Typewriter-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B; src: local('MathJax_Main Bold'), local('MathJax_Main-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I; src: local('MathJax_Main Italic'), local('MathJax_Main-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R; src: local('MathJax_Main'), local('MathJax_Main-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I; src: local('MathJax_Math Italic'), local('MathJax_Math-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R; src: local('MathJax_Size1'), local('MathJax_Size1-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size1-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size1-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size1-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R; src: local('MathJax_Size2'), local('MathJax_Size2-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size2-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size2-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size2-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R; src: local('MathJax_Size3'), local('MathJax_Size3-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size3-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size3-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size3-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R; src: local('MathJax_Size4'), local('MathJax_Size4-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size4-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size4-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size4-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R; src: local('MathJax_Vector'), local('MathJax_Vector-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B; src: local('MathJax_Vector Bold'), local('MathJax_Vector-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Vector'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
</style>它非常具体，配备了一堆隐式结构（公制、角度、显式坐标等）——其中许多结构您可能没有明确意图，甚至对您的目标来说是多余的。</p><p>然后你将结构一一抽象出来，例如，</p><ul><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metric_space">度量空间</a>使用度量抽象出“距离”的概念。</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inner_product_space">内积空间</a>抽象出“相似性”的概念，从而抽象出“大小”和“角度”的概念。</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Topological_space">拓扑空间</a>使用开集抽象出“局部性”的概念。</li></ul><p>有了这个更抽象的<i>空间</i>概念，您可以将其投射到与最初考虑的领域不同的领域中更具体的结构，有效地将其用作生成器。例如，</p><ul><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Function_space">函数空间</a>：“<i>现在我对空间的限制有了更宽松的概念，如果我将其讨论范围扩展到诸如函数之类的无限维对象，会发生什么？”</i></li></ul><p>从这里开始，循环继续。手头有一个可以捕获您想要的内容的具体结构，但现在有了在不同领域中操作的风格，这可能会深入了解最初不在您考虑范围内的某些结构可能会如何进一步抽象出来。</p><ul><li>当然，这个过程是由我们的[对现实世界事物/美学/实用性/简单性的直觉]指导的，而不是在概念空间中盲目搜索。</li></ul><p>当你继续在许多不同的抽象层次上抽象/具体化你的结构的过程之后（每个层次都有利于描述不同类型的论域），你最终会得到一个极其丰富的<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_(mathematics)">空间</a>概念，其中一些概念与你最初的<span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\mathbb{R}^n"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-msubsup"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-texatom"><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-ams-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">R</span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sup" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: 0.615em; padding-left: 0px; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">n</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span>截然不同。</p><p> <i><strong>b) “优化”的概念</strong></i></p><p>在哲学中，我认为情况更加明显。例如，Alex Flint 的<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/znfkdCoHMANwqc2WE/the-ground-of-optimization-1">优化基础</a>，主要通过语域扩展来比较不同的优化定义，即对“奇怪”场景中的定义进行案例分析，看看哪些概念更好地概括并符合我们对这个词的直观概念。优化”应该是这个意思。</p><p> <i><strong>c) “作为定义的定理”的认知母题</strong></i></p><p>一种结构中的定理现在可以成为另一种结构中的定义。这与前面的主题高度相关：我们可以将某些定理视为原始结构的具体[特征/公理]的结果，并以更[轻松/一般的方式将定理转变为定义的行为] ]结构]作为抽象出[定理在原始结构中捕获的特定概念]。例如，</p><ul><li><strong>求幂</strong>：从重复乘法的概念开始。发现幂运算具有泰勒级数近似值。请注意，后者具有更通用的讨论领域，并用它来概括复数、运算符等上下文中的概念。</li><li><strong>分形维度：</strong>首先观察空间的维度对应于缩放指数，并用它来定义“分形性”的度量。</li></ul><p>这是<a href="https://ncatlab.org/nlab/show/The+Rising+Sea">海平面上升</a>！</p><h2>为什么它有效？</h2><p>我可以想到这个过程起作用的几个原因（受到<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/GhFoAxG49RXFzze5Y/what-s-so-bad-about-ad-hoc-mathematical-definitions">这里</a>的启发），“为什么”是指它作为人类认识论过程的有效性的原因。</p><p>仅通过选择，我们最终建模的概念（以及科学家对首先<i>可以</i>建模的内容建立的直觉）往往是可以由少数需求捕获的概念。</p><p>如果需求排除了所有可能性或规定了太多，我们可以纠正我们的直觉/需求，例如发现以我们没有注意到的方式巧妙地限制我们结构形式的假设。</p><p>通过找到我们的结构必须满足的这种“最低条件”，它变得更有利于添加新的结构，这样它就可以更加具体地应用于新的讨论领域。从那里，我们可以列出例子并找到新的定理，从而丰富我们反馈到这个循环中的直觉。</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW/epistemic-motif-of-abstract-concrete-cycles-and-domain#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW/epistemic-motif-of-abstract-concrete-cycles-and-domain<guid ispermalink="false"> x6xfX7nwf53uM8hBW</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalcy Bremin]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:28:45 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Simple Terminal Colors]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 12:40 AM GMT<br/><br/><p><span>我经常在终端上工作，并且经常想编写一些程序来对输出进行一些着色。例如，也许我正在查看</span><a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/sequencing-intro">测序读数</a>，我想知道它的哪一部分是其被标记的原因。我可以使用<a href="https://pypi.org/project/colorama/">colorama</a> 、 <a href="https://pypi.org/project/termcolor/">termcolor</a>或其他库，但<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/designing-low-upkeep-software">包含这么简单的东西的依赖项</a>并不值得。相反，打印彩色文本非常简单：</p><p></p><pre> COLOR_RED_BOLD = &#39;\x1b[1;31m&#39;
COLOR_BLUE_BOLD = &#39;\x1b[1;34m&#39;
COLOR_END = &#39;\x1b[0m&#39;
打印（
  “一条鱼，两条鱼，” +
  COLOR_RED_BOLD +“红色”+
  COLOR_END +“鱼，”+
  COLOR_BLUE_BOLD +“蓝色”+
  COLOR_END +“鱼。”）
</pre><p><a href="https://www.jefftk.com/terminal-one-fish-two-fish-red-fish-blue-fish-big.png"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/yb6yjheuv5hy5j3kdm6t" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/yb6yjheuv5hy5j3kdm6t 550w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/af02tlyznphgzazdh0qz 1100w"></a></p><div></div><p></p><p>我通常只需要一种或两种突出显示颜色，通常为粗体，并且很少发现六种标准颜色有限制。如果您想将注意力吸引到特定的事物上，同时在需要进一步观察时保持其周围的背景，那么这会特别有用。</p><p>这有多兼容？有一天，使用非 ANSI 终端的人会运行我的代码并抱怨吗？一个数据点是我在<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/introducing-icdiff">2009 年</a>用这种方法编写了<a href="https://www.jefftk.com/icdiff">icdiff</a> ，并且它相当流行。虽然我收到了<a href="https://github.com/jeffkaufman/icdiff/issues?q=is%3Aissue">数百份</a>错误报告，但这从来没有人抱怨过。</p><p><i>评论通过： <a href="https://www.facebook.com/jefftk/posts/pfbid0yNYkCYNaKotC3ZKBJZ2sCMiAogXFgBcjyfS9qW7JHduMXkUEBNxW5ywpcphoGJQel">facebook</a> , <a href="https://mastodon.mit.edu/@jefftk/111207929256178296">mastodon</a></i></p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/simple-terminal-colors#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oLK5J7xazS8L3p6fy/simple-terminal-colors<guid ispermalink="false"> olK5J7xazS8L3p6fy</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jefftk]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:40:08 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[The Handbook of Rationality (2021, MIT press) is now open access]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on October 10, 2023 12:30 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>这里特别令人感兴趣的是关于概率的主观解释的第 4.1 节和第 8.4 节，其中明确讨论了奈特不确定性及其对贝叶斯解释的挑战。</p><p> <a href="https://direct.mit.edu/books/oa-edited-volume/5525/The-Handbook-of-Rationality">https://direct.mit.edu/books/oa-edited-volume/5525/The-Handbook-of-Rationality</a></p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zcigMWSr5uKs2cPCv/the-handbook-of-rationality-2021-mit-press-is-now-open#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/zcigMWSr5uKs2cPCv/the-handbook-of-rationality-2021-mit-press-is-now-open<guid ispermalink="false"> zcigMWSr5uKs2cPCv</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[romeostevensit]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>