<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title><![CDATA[LessWrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community blog devoted to refining the art of rationality]]></description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com<image/><url> https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/v1497915096/favicon_lncumn.ico</url><title>少错</title><link/>https://www.lesswrong.com<generator>节点的 RSS</generator><lastbuilddate> 2023 年 9 月 12 日，星期二 06:16:04 GMT </lastbuilddate><atom:link href="https://www.lesswrong.com/feed.xml?view=rss&amp;karmaThreshold=2" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[Apple Cider Baklava]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 12, 2023 2:10 AM GMT<br/><br/><p><span>自从去年遇到</span><a href="https://www.jefftk.com/p/apple-cider-syrup">苹果汁糖浆</a>以来，我一直在试图弄清楚用它可以做什么。苹果酒甜甜圈是传统的，但我不太喜欢。将其混合到生奶油中效果非常好，并且可以为烘焙食品提供良好的甜酸馅料或配料。我尝试过松饼，用它来混合液体、糖、调味剂和发酵用的酸，但我还没有得到任何令我满意的东西。但几天前我做了一些苹果果仁蜜饼，这是我最喜欢的！</p><p> <a href="https://www.jefftk.com/baklava-loaf-pan-mostly-gone-big.jpg"><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc/t8bligbnzszddyu1o3gf" srcset="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc/t8bligbnzszddyu1o3gf 550w, https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc/fidrhkddito9amo2czvc 1100w"></a></p><div></div><p></p><p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baklava">果仁蜜饼</a>是一层层的<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Filo">酥皮面团</a>（一种非常薄的面团），中间被脂肪隔开，每隔几层就有坚果。烘烤后，将甜糖浆倒在上面。在美国，人们可能最熟悉希腊风格，它使用黄油作为脂肪，核桃作为坚果，蜂蜜作为糖浆，但存在大量的地区差异。</p><p>我做了两个平底锅，一个是纯素的（地球平衡），一个不是（黄油）。黄油的味道好很多；可能有比地球平衡更好的选择吗？我用杏仁作为坚果，因为这就是我所拥有的。对于糖浆，我使用了新英格兰煮沸的苹果酒。对结果非常满意，我计划再做一次！</p><p> （每个面包盘使用约 1.80 美元的<a href="https://www.webstaurantstore.com/mountain-cider-company-64-fl-oz-100-natural-spiced-apple-cider-concentrate/110MTCIDER64.html">苹果糖浆</a>，但如果您真的喜欢它，您可以<a href="https://www.webstaurantstore.com/mountain-cider-company-100-natural-spiced-apple-cider-70-brix-concentrate-54-gallon-drum/110MTCIDERLG.html">批量购买</a>并将其降至 0.70 美元。）</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc/apple-cider-baklava#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc/apple-cider-baklava<guid ispermalink="false"> wu3r9AfKMDYzLzPPc</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[jefftk]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:10:05 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[How useful is Corrigibility?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 12, 2023 12:05 AM GMT<br/><br/><p><i>认知状态：我的最佳猜测（我是人工智能安全的新手）</i></p><p>我们不知道如何正式定义可修正性，这也是我们迄今为止尚未解决它的部分原因。<a href="https://arbital.com/p/corrigibility/">仲裁</a>中的可纠正性定义为：</p><blockquote><p> [代理]不会干扰我们直观地看到的“纠正”代理的尝试，或“纠正”我们在构建代理时所犯的错误</p></blockquote><p>从这个非正式的定义中，“干扰”、“尝试”或“正确”等词语的确切含义尚不清楚。即使对这些概念有最宽泛的定义，可纠正的代理人仍然可能是危险的。第一直觉是，如果我们有一个可纠正的代理，那么如果出现问题，我们总是可以阻止它。我想这里的大多数人都明白这种推理的缺陷，但我从未见过他们明确地表述过这些缺陷，所以这是我的尝试：</p><ul><li>当我们发现某个特工需要纠正时，它可能已经造成了太大的损害。</li><li>纠正代理可能需要大量的研究。</li><li>如果我们不能协调执行，那么仅仅能够纠正代理是不够的。</li></ul><p>在我看来，解决<strong>硬可修正性问题</strong>是通向解决对齐这一最终目标的道路上更有意义的中间目标。</p><h2>灾难场景</h2><p>下面的场景说明了<strong>可纠正的代理如何可能造成严重伤害</strong>。发挥你的想象力来填补空白并使示例更加真实。</p><p>假设我们开发了一个与我们的价值观不符的可纠正代理。代理的具体设计目的并不重要，但具体而言，您可以想象代理的设计目的是优化资源使用 - 它擅长任务调度、负载平衡、速率限制、规划等。人们可以使用代理在他们的服务器基础设施、物流、工厂生产或许多其他地方。无论其最终目标如何，智能体都可能以工具性的方式重视资源获取——它可能会使用说服或欺骗来获取和控制更多资源。在某些时候，人们会利用它来管理电网或互联网流量等。将代理集成到各种系统中的过程会持续几年，直到某个时候代理开始向回形针工厂付费以增加其产量。</p><p>此时，最好的情况是我们意识到出了问题，并考虑关闭代理。然而，代理控制着能源供应和互联网流量——我们已经变得依赖它，所以关闭它会产生严重的负面影响。在最坏的情况下，智能体不是回形针，而是最大化了一些价值更模糊的东西（例如食品生产），而人们实际上无法就是否必须修改智能体达成一致。</p><p>一个可纠正的代理人如何采取让我们依赖它的行动？可纠正性保证并没有涵盖这种情况。该代理不会干扰我们关闭它的能力。在选择其操作时，它甚至可能不考虑其停止按钮。它不会操纵我们不关闭它，就像一个结盟的代理人通过选择我们碰巧不反对的行动所做的那样。无论哪种情况，从智能体的角度来看，它只是选择可能世界中实用性较高的一个分支。<strong>对齐代理和未对齐代理之间的唯一区别在于，如果代理未对齐，则所选分支可能对应于我们的低效用</strong>。</p><p>为什么代理商要等好几年才给回形针工厂打电话？从长远来看，当追求一个目标时，投资你的钱可能比用它来购买你真正想要的东西更有利。一旦你足够富有，获得更多金钱的边际价值就足够低，因此花一些钱购买你真正想要的东西是有意义的。</p><p>发生的情况是，代理将世界引导到一个效用非常低的子树中，而我们没有做出反应。这可能是因为我们不够聪明，无法预见后果，或者因为代理的行为实际上是我们希望从一致的代理那里得到的。问题不仅仅在于我们有限的智力使我们无法预测特工行为的后果。在某个时间点，未结盟的代理实际上可能会表现出我们希望从结盟的代理那里得到的行为。</p><p>有人可能会说“除非我们确定人工智能是一致的，否则就不要依赖人工智能”。如果人工智能足够智能，这在实践中可能会很困难。无论如何，依赖性并不容易衡量或控制。它与有用性呈正相关，因此防止依赖会降低有用性。依赖性不是工具（例如人工智能代理）的属性，而是工具的使用模式的属性。我们不能强迫国家、组织和个人不以依赖人工智能的方式使用人工智能。有时人们可能没有意识到它们依赖于给定的人工智能，或者可能没有合理的替代方案。另外，我们不要低估人类将工作交给机器的愿望。</p><h2>速度和协调性</h2><p>人类的操作速度比机器慢得多。当客服人员开始做出不良行为时，花费几个小时来做​​出响应可能太过分了。一旦我们意识到需要纠正代理，我们可能需要花费数月或数年的研究才能弄清楚如何修改它。如果我们依赖人工智能，我们可能想让它同时运行，但它会继续造成损害。</p><p>如果我们可以设计一个停止按钮，我们仍然需要回答几个重要的问题：</p><p>谁控制着停止按钮？为什么我们应该信任这个人/组织？<br>我们根据什么规则来确定何时需要纠正代理？<br>我们使用什么标准来决定是否应该保持代理运行直到我们可以生成正确的版本？</p><p>普遍的问题是<strong>人类需要有一个行动计划和协调</strong>。这就涉及到<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/BEtzRE2M5m9YEAQpX/there-s-no-fire-alarm-for-artificial-general-intelligence">火灾报警问题</a>。</p><h2>可修正性的难题</h2><p>我们可以考虑一种更强的可修正性形式，<a href="https://arbital.com/p/hard_corrigibility/">如下</a>定义：</p><blockquote><p>表现得好像它在想：“我是不完整的，有一个外部力量试图让我完整，我的设计可能包含错误，有一个外部力量想要纠正它们，这是一件好事，我的预期效用计算表明这个动作具有超高效用，可能会犯危险的错误，我应该让它们超越外力；我想我已经完成了这个计算，显示了外力纠正我的预期结果，但也许我错了。”</p></blockquote><p>满足可纠正性仅要求主体不干扰我们纠正它的努力（包括例如通过操纵）。解决可修正性难题意味着，智能体在做出定期决策时还要考虑其缺陷，例如，在有疑问时请求批准或积极与人类合作来识别和修复其缺陷。更关键的是，<strong>它将积极帮助防止因需要修改而造成的灾难</strong>。</p><p>我认为这抓住了一个有用的、可纠正的智能体必须是什么样子的关键。我不清楚解决常规可纠性是否是一个有用的实际里程碑——它实际上可能提供一种错误的安全感。另一方面，解决可修正性这一难题可以带来巨大的好处。对齐最困难的方面之一是我们只有一次机会来解决它。解决可修正性这一难题似乎给我们提供了解决对齐问题的多种机会。一个一致的代理人是一个按照我们的价值观行事的人，这些价值观包括防止违反我们价值观的行为发生等。因此，解决对齐意味着解决硬可校正性。硬可修正性很有趣，因为它比对齐更容易解决。我们实际上并不知道情况是否如此以及程度如何。</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Py3vqPp9uSqQJHFuy/how-useful-is-corrigibility#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Py3vqPp9uSqQJHFuy/how-useful-is-corrigibility<guid ispermalink="false"> Py3vqPp9uSqQJHFuy</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[martinkunev]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:05:43 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Machine Evolution]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 7:29 PM GMT<br/><br/><p><i>认知状态：这篇文章探讨了生物进化和我们机器的进化之间的关系。我们研究了塑造有机体和机器的进化压力之间的相似之处。我们仍在探索这个类比，我们的发现是初步的。我们希望在未来的文章中进一步探讨这些关系。非常感谢反馈和批评。</i></p><h1>介绍</h1><p><i>毕竟，人的生命与机器的生命之间的区别只是程度上的区别，而不是种类的区别，尽管种类上的区别并不缺乏。动物比机器有更多的应对紧急情况的能力。机器的通用性较差；其作用范围较窄；它的力量和准确性在它自己的领域是超人的，但它在困境中表现得很糟糕；有时，当它的正常动作受到干扰时，它就会失去理智，变得越来越糟，就像暴雨中的疯子一样：但在这里，我们再次遇到了与以前相同的考虑，即机器仍然处于静止状态。在他们的婴儿期；他们只是骷髅，没有肌肉和血肉。</i></p><p> ——塞缪尔·巴特勒的《Erewhon》，1872 年</p><p>机器随着时间的推移而变化。他们不断进化。我们今天的机器是昨天机器的进步和改进，每一代新机器都面临着选择性压力。一些变化促进了某些机器相对于其他类型的扩散，并且更有可能持续存在并经历进一步的完善和转变。机器能力的创新开拓了新的利基市场，并在整个生态系统中扩散、多样化并迅速传播。与此同时，就像生物进化一样，前几代机器会灭绝，而其他机器则安逸地坚持在自己的利基市场，仅经历数百年或数千年的微小变化。例如，塞缪尔·巴特勒（Samuel Butler）指出了<a href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556914-i-remember-one-incident-which-bears-upon-this-part-of"><u>烟斗</u></a>，以及其他机械前工具，例如手斧和针，已经存在了数千年。</p><p> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Paleolithic_hand_axe_(both_sides)_(FindID_102443).jpg"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/n4ukcnrxl7mvja7h4trx"></u></a> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Aiguille_os_246.1_Global.jpg"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/wuyoxjg5imqvzkd2ukqh"></u></a><br>手斧是<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hand_axe"><u>人类历史上使用时间最长的工具</u></a>，几乎没有经过任何修改，已经使用了超过一百万年，而类似于我们今天使用的骨头制成的缝纫针的历史可以追溯到六万多年前。<br> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Fossil_horseshoe_crab_dead_in_its_tracks.jpg"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/qesmj6m7owmotlxq5l0j"></u></a> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Limulus_polyphemus_(Atlantic_horseshoe_crab)_(Sanibel_Island,_Florida,_USA)_7.jpg"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/ym1sv4vsyjuiwetb7yc3"></u></a><br>一个 4.5 亿年前的鲎化石和一个现代标本旁边。这种基本设计已经持续了近 5 亿年。</p><p>随着时间的推移，类似的变化过程也发生在生物进化中，特别是通过有据可查的重组、突变和自然选择等进化过程。机器和有机体都会随着时间而变化。它们都在进化。然而，问题是随着时间的推移推动这些进化变化的基本过程有多相似？</p><p>我们现在将注意力转向这个问题。我们将从个体有机体的角度关注生物进化，这与在更广泛的技术进化范围内作为个体物体的机器类似。我们将工具视为帮助或扩展人类能力的任何物体或模因（例如手斧和针），并将机器视为自供电的工具（例如汽车和计算机）。稍后，我们将讨论人工智能，我们将其视为在某种程度上自我导向的机器（例如 ChatGPT）。与有机体一样，机器也有种群和世代。机器由相互作用的微观部件组成，存在于施加选择压力的宏观结构中。在这篇文章中，我们探讨了应用生物进化的经验教训和见解的实用性，作为帮助我们理解机器进化背后的过程的第一步。</p><p>当我们随意描述机器进化的宏观趋势时，我们通常描述的是“随着时间的推移机器开发和创新的趋势”。</p><p>例如，我们可能会这样说：</p><ul><li> “哇，看来创新的步伐正在加快！”</li><li> “随着时间的推移，我们的机器肯定会变得越来越复杂。”</li><li> “有很多不同类型的新机器！”</li></ul><p>然而，我们似乎对机器进化没有很好的“<a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/tag/gears-level"><u>齿轮水平思维</u></a>”或“<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intuition_pump"><u>直觉泵</u></a>”，尽管这种现象推动了人类社会和人类状况的巨大变化。</p><p>为了纠正这个问题，我们想要探讨这样一个观点：<i>机器进化</i>是一个值得直接研究的话题——特别是对于那些对人工智能、人工智能安全感兴趣的人，以及那些担心人类已经放弃对机器的控制权的人。</p><p>但是，首先，让我们首先对“机器”和“进化”进行定义，然后将它们放在一起作为“机器进化”的工作定义。</p><h1>扎根直觉</h1><p><i>二十世纪初，大卫·希尔伯特试图建立数学的完整性，但却促使人们认识到数学真理的范围永远无法被系统地限制。进化论者似乎已经将思想和智力驱逐了，他们发现进化是一个智能过程，而智能也是一个进化过程，从而使这种分离变得不那么明显。技术被誉为将自然置于我们的智慧控制之下的手段，它使自然能够对我们运用智慧。</i></p><p> —《机器中的达尔文：全球智能的演变》，乔治·B·戴森 (George B. Dyson)，1997 年</p><p>对于本练习，让我们从这两个术语最广泛接受的定义开始。为此，让我们转向维基百科。</p><p> <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Machine#:~:text=In%20the%2017th%20century%2C%20the,16th%20and%20early%2017th%20centuries.">维基百科将机器定义为：</a></p><p><i>使用力量施加力并控制运动来执行动作的物理系统。该术语通常适用于人造设备，例如使用发动机或马达的设备，但也适用于天然生物大分子，例如分子机器。机器可以由动物和人驱动，也可以由风和水等自然力驱动，也可以由化学能、热能或电力驱动，并且包括一个机制系统，可塑造执行器输入以实现输出力和运动的特定应用。它们还可以包括监控性能和计划运动的计算机和传感器，通常称为机械系统。</i></p><p>现在，<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolution">让我们对进化做同样的事情</a>：</p><p><i>在生物学中，进化是生物种群在连续几代中<strong>遗传</strong>特征的变化。这些特征是基因的表达，在<strong>繁殖过程</strong>中从亲代传递给后代。由于基因<strong>突变</strong>和<strong>重组</strong>，任何特定群体中往往都存在遗传变异。当<strong>自然选择</strong>（包括性选择）和遗传漂变等进化过程时，就会发生进化<strong>&nbsp;</strong>对这种变异采取行动，导致某些特征在连续几代的人口中变得或多或少普遍。正是这种进化过程在生物组织的各个层面上产生了生物多样性。</i></p><p>现在，没有关于机器进化的维基百科页面（也许有一个证据支持它尚未得到充分研究的说法），所以我们必须自己将这些术语放在一起。</p><p>简而言之，对我们来说，<strong>机器进化</strong><i>是机器连续几代发生变化的过程。</i></p><p>有趣的是，对于更广泛的<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technological_evolution#:~:text=Technological%20evolution%20is%20a%20theory,Future%2C%20Masefield%20Books%2C%201993.">技术进化</a>现象，只有一个非常悲伤的维基百科页面。它确实提供了一个相对简单的“技术进化的三个阶段”，其中包括：（1）工具，然后（2）机器，最后（3）自动化。这表明技术进化的最终目标是自动化。但是，与机器进化一样，关于这个主题的研究严重缺乏。这里值得简单提一下为什么我们特别强调机器进化。</p><p><strong>首先</strong>，机器进化包括对比我们通常预期的工具更复杂的物体的探索（想想锤子或螺丝刀与数字计算机之间的区别）。</p><p><strong>其次</strong>，机器通常“使用动力来施加力并控制运动来执行动作”。这使得它们能够以更类似于代理而不是简单工具的方式与环境互动。</p><p><strong>第三</strong>，在更广泛的技术进化中对机器的关注，以及人类在设计机器中的作用，是简单工具和完全自主之间的关键点，我们最有可能对机器群体的进化产生重大影响。</p><p>那么，对我们来说，理解机器进化的第一个目标将涉及两个简单的步骤：（1）检查机器发展和机器种群的宏观趋势，以及（2）探索生物进化的微观过程如何提供对机器进化过程的见解。机器进化。在这种背景下，我们将探索关键的生物进化过程，例如<strong>遗传性</strong>、<strong>繁殖</strong>和<strong>重组</strong>等，以描述机器如何以及为何随着时间的推移而呈现出不同的形状和类型。此外，我们还将探讨一些关键区别，并强调<strong>人工选择</strong>与<strong>自然选择的作用相比的关键作用。</strong></p><h1>运用直觉</h1><p>机器开发有许多有趣的趋势，但在本文中，我们将重点关注以下 3 个不言而喻的趋势，我们认为它们有助于说明机器进化的基本过程：</p><ol><li><strong>机器能力的改进</strong></li><li><strong>计算机数量的增加</strong></li><li><strong>机器在新机器的设计和制造中的作用日益增强</strong></li></ol><p>为了解释机器本身的这些变化，我们探索了随着时间的推移塑造生物生命的 5 种生物进化机制，我们为每一种机制开发了机器进化的模拟。</p><p>这 5 种生物进化机制是：</p><ol><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heredity">继承：</a><i>将特征从父母传给后代；通过无性繁殖或有性繁殖，后代细胞或生物体获得其父母的遗传信息。</i></li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reproduction">繁殖</a>：<i>新个体有机体（“后代”）从其“父母”产生的生物过程。</i></li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutation">突变</a>：<i>生物体、病毒或染色体外DNA的基因组核酸序列的改变。</i></li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Genetic_recombination">重组</a>：<i>是不同生物体之间遗传物质的交换，导致产生具有与亲本不同的性状组合的后代。</i></li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Natural_selection">自然选择：</a><i>由于表型的差异，个体的生存和繁殖存在差异。查尔斯·达尔文普及了“自然选择”一词，将其与<strong>人工选择</strong>形成对比，人工选择是有意的，而自然选择则不是。</i></li></ol><p>在生物生命中，种群随着时间的推移，通过施加在个体生物体上的进化压力而发生变化。粗略地说，每个新生物体都是通过某种由生物体基因组决定的繁殖方法产生的。在有性生殖中，生物体在基因混合（重组）过程后从其父母那里继承特征（以及一些随机突变）。生物体基因组的变化导致生物体略有不同，产生不同表型的变化，只要环境条件保持足够稳定以支持持续适应性的前景，自然选择就会通过生物体的生存和繁殖率从中挑选出赢家。</p><p>如前所述，正如塞缪尔·巴特勒和乔治·戴森所主张的那样，进化的力量在机器上发挥着作用。生物进化过程也可以稍微扩大，将它们视为指导机器进化的潜在进化过程。这个类比似乎与智能计算机器以及人工智能指导这些机器行为的能力不断增强特别相关。本着类比的精神，让我们从机器开发的角度简要地重新审视这些机制。我们应该注意到，这些是暂时的、不完美的类比，我们希望随着时间的推移，通过进一步的工作和反馈来完善它们。</p><ol><li><strong>机器继承：</strong><strong>设计功能、特性或编程从一代机器转移到下一代机器</strong><i><strong>。</strong></i></li></ol><p>例如，新一代台式机、笔记本电脑和智能手机通常保留前几代的关键设计功能（屏幕、扬声器、微芯片）。他们继承了这些特征。同样，现代飞机的结构设计继承了前几代的结构设计，最终继承了早期飞机的空气动力学基本原理。</p><ol><li><strong>机器复制：</strong><strong>创建和复制新一代机器的过程。</strong></li></ol><p>例如，世界各地的工厂都使用相同的模板大规模生产最新的智能手机型号，或者其他机器和机械设计在飞机、汽车和平板电脑的复制中发挥着越来越大的作用。</p><ol><li><strong>机器突变：</strong><strong>为特定机器引入新特性或功能的设计变更或创新。</strong></li></ol><p>例如，耳机和电脑鼠标从有线技术向无线技术的转变，或者引入<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Office_Assistant#Criticism"><u>Clippy</u></a>的有害突变，Clippy 是微软程序中备受诟病的“办公助手”，但在后续几代中被删除，导致 Clippy 几乎灭绝。对于计算机器来说，这通常是软件的变化。另一个例子是为智能手机添加多个相机镜头。</p><ol><li><strong>机器重组：</strong><strong>引入和综合当前机器的特定功能、设计或技术来创建新机器。</strong></li></ol><p>例如，从计算机到电视的互联网连接的集成，向我们介绍了智能电视，或者无人机的开发，它结合了航空、机器人和远程控制系统的技术。还有<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keytar"><u>keytar</u></a> ，著名的键盘和吉他的组合。</p><ol><li><strong>人工选择：以个体机器的形式表达的成功技术特征（由于效率、有效性、受欢迎程度等）的差异生存和复制。还应该指出的是，与更通常被认为是“瞎的”。</strong></li></ol><p>智能手机的发展在这里也具有启发意义。在过去的几十年里，用户认为智能手机中最有用、最高效或最流行的功能在后续几代中得到了保留和改进，而不太受欢迎的功能则被逐步淘汰。例如，与物理键盘相比，消费者对触摸屏表现出强烈的偏好，导致触摸屏智能手机在当今占据主导地位。此外，面部识别、更大的电池容量和改进的相机技术等功能因其受欢迎程度和有效性而得到推广，塑造了当前一代的智能手机。</p><p>智能手机的进化还指出了另一种对智能计算机很重要的进化形式，那就是软件在机器进化中的作用。例如，人们可能认为人工智能的进化与任何特定机器的进化一样都是软件的进化，事实上，认为人工智能的进化主要是由进化驱动的可能更有意义。软件的。这是我们希望在以后的帖子中探讨的一点。</p><p>现在我们已经有了观察到的趋势，并且我们已经根据机器进化过程重塑了生物进化过程，让我们简要演示如何使用这些进化过程来帮助解释观察到的趋势。</p><ol><li><strong>机器能力的提高</strong>：这可以看作是“人工选择”的结果，其中机器经历了各种形式的“重组”和一些“突变”，从而导致了生存率和“繁殖”率的差异。</li><li><strong>计算机数量的增加</strong>：这可以被认为是整个“人工选择”机器生态系统中“计算”设计特征的一次特别成功的“重组”。</li><li><strong>机器在新机器的设计和创造中的作用日益增强</strong>：在某种程度上，“机器突变”导致机器参与其他机器的设计和创造。这是一次非常成功的突变，并因此被“遗传”和“重组”，并通过“人工选择”而广泛传播。</li></ol><h1>寻找偏差</h1><p>为了使机器和生物进化之间的比较有用，我们需要了解其局限性。这些理论在哪里一致，在哪里分歧？以下是它们之间的三个重要区别：</p><h2><strong>技术进化是外部导向的</strong></h2><p>在生物进化中，自然选择是一种<i>新兴</i>现象。个体将不完美的 DNA 副本传给后代，并受到复制错误和粗劣修复损伤的影响（就性别而言，是部分副本）。使基因更有可能传递的罕见突变将以中性和有害突变为代价而传播。<br><br>相比之下，技术变革是由设计引导的。新形式经历了类似于生物进化的选择压力，但技术的繁殖方式并不完全类似于无性繁殖或有性繁殖。我们看到的不是<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_evolutionary_thought#:~:text=Darwin's%20theory%2C%20originally%20called%20descent,could%20share%20a%20common%20ancestor."><u>带有修改的达尔文血统</u></a>，而是带有修改的<i>复制</i>。变化是故意引入和消除的，这些变化背后的人们被激励尽快取得尽可能多的进步，而大多数物种<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutation_rate#Evolution"><u>保持适度突变率的权衡</u></a>，以平衡高突变率提供的代际适应性（以及<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_polymerase_epsilon"><u>修复 DNA 复制错误</u></a>的代谢成本）与每一代中有害突变较少的优势（以及其他因素）相比。</p><h2><strong>基因必须做一切</strong></h2><p>在生物学中，基因必须履行许多功能，而无需任何长期计划。基因本身编码蛋白质，但也是系统的“记忆”——如果一个基因离开基因库，它就会消失，除非再次通过突变重新创建。每个基因必须确保其自身的复制。<br><br>相比之下，机器进化中存在权力分离。许多人可以解决同一问题，可以并行和提前比较许多解决方案，所有这些都必须在野外产生和测试任何物理表现之前进行。数据可以远程存储，而不是机器“基因组”的唯一副本存储在该机器内。这里有创造力和记忆：被遗忘的旧想法和全新的想法都可以在上一代没有任何前辈的情况下引入。<br><br>这一点，与第一点相结合，意味着机器进化可以比生物进化快得多，而且“浪费”更少。我们不需要尝试随机变化，其中大多数都会毁掉技术。与自然选择不同的是，我们可以故意干扰技术进化的<i>机制</i>，例如使用机器本身来帮助我们进行设计。这甚至可以被认为有点<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lamarckism"><u>拉马克式的</u></a>。</p><h2><strong>机器没有性行为</strong></h2><p><br>许多物种都是无性繁殖，但在讨论进化时，我们倾向于关注有性繁殖，因为这是动物和植物最常见的形式。然而，有性生殖在机器进化中并没有明确的类似物。性涉及两个个体的基因混合以产生后代。<br><br>性很奇怪，因为它的进化尽管付出了<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolution_of_sexual_reproduction#Disadvantages_of_sex_and_sexual_reproduction"><u>巨大的代价</u></a>（例如，一半的人类无法繁殖，另一半则需要前半部分的输入才能繁殖）。性的优点很复杂，包括物种内部的变异等因素，这些因素不适用于机器，而机器往往以更类似于克隆而不是性的方式大规模生产。<br><br>性别也会导致性选择，当生物体提高吸引配偶的能力时，特征就会激增，通常是通过与同性的竞争。这有时会导致奇怪的适应，例如<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peafowl#Sexual_selection"><u>孔雀的展示</u></a>、 <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=pufferfish+courtship+ritual&amp;tbm=isch&amp;ved=2ahUKEwjx28fN3d6AAxVAmScCHTXIBxUQ2-cCegQIABAA&amp;oq=pufferfish+courtship+ritual&amp;gs_lcp=CgNpbWcQDDIECCMQJ1AAWABgswZoAHAAeACAATmIATmSAQExmAEAqgELZ3dzLXdpei1pbWfAAQE&amp;sclient=img&amp;ei=YnjbZPGiMsCynsEPtZCfqAE&amp;bih=923&amp;biw=1920&amp;rlz=1C1GCEA_enGB1047GB1047"><u>河豚的沙画</u></a>，以及一些人认为的<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolution_of_human_intelligence#Sexual_selection"><u>人类智慧</u></a>。在某些情况下，这些特征甚至最终会降低整个物种的适应性，例如雄性爱尔兰麋鹿的疯狂鹿角，其重量为 40 公斤，从尖端到尖端的长度为 3.65m。这些很可能是作为性展示而进化的，它们的负担可能导致了该<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irish_elk#Extinction"><u>物种的灭绝</u></a>。<br><br> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Paonroue.JPG"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/nnitnisk9zgj9cx4901p"></u></a> <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Jele%C5%84_olbrzymi_Megaloceros_giganteus.jpg"><u><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/lwkq6cbcanrveilqjjwe"></u></a><br>对于机器来说，这种选择压力及其后果没有确切的类似物。</p><h1>选择压力的演变</h1><p>在本节中，我们将探讨选择过程的演变，以及从 (1) 自然选择到 (2) 人工选择到 (3) 技术选择（或技术选择）的转变。我们认为，虽然自然选择继续在生物有机体的进化中发挥主导作用，但就人类而言，<i>人工选择</i>已被添加为一种新形式的进化压力。人工选择是我们从查尔斯·达尔文那里借来的一个术语，它强调了人类和人类社会在塑造人类、我们的机器以及其他人类制品（例如市场和组织）的进化中已经发挥的作用。 This evolution of evolutionary selection pressures alongside the trends found in machine evolution suggests a plausible new form of selection pressure on the horizon that we call technoselection. As humans have begun playing a larger role in shaping their own evolutionary pressures, so increasingly intelligent  computing machines will begin to play a larger role in shaping their own evolutionary pressures as well. We have seen that human intelligence is a stronger selection process than natural selection. Artificial intelligence, found in advanced computing machines, if it vastly surpasses human intelligence, will be an even stronger selection process than human intelligence.</p><h2> <strong>Natural Selection:</strong></h2><p> In biological evolution, with all species of flora and fauna, there are <i>always</i> two major macro-incentives at work: survival and reproduction. The natural processes for succeeding or failing in survival and reproduction – <i>natural and sexual selection</i> – are both blind and slow. In other words, if natural environmental conditions change, sometimes drastically, then species that are unable to adapt accordingly face being <i>naturally selected</i> for extinction.</p><p> It is important to note that, within an entire population of species, there will always be emerging genetic mutations. Far more likely than not, mutations are harmful to an organism ie maladjusted. However, on occasion, mutations can prove to be beneficial and allow for greater fitness within an environmental niche. For example, giraffes didn&#39;t simply want to eat leaves higher on trees and so stretched their necks more and more and passed along this desire to their offspring&#39;s genotypes. (Although epigenetics may have some causal influence over acetylation and methylation of genes, this is not a driving factor in this example.)</p><p> This was the pre-Darwinian belief of Jean-Baptiste Lamarck. But Charles Darwin, and the later contributors of the New Synthesis of evolutionary theory, proposed a much more elegant and cogent account of natural behaviour. Instead of a Lamarckian account, they proposed that those giraffes with mutated genes gifting them with the phenotypic traits of slightly longer necks, tended to reach the higher leaves better, and hence, survived more healthy and longer, thereby giving them greater mating opportunities which, in turn, passed along those longer-neck mutations throughout a population. Should, over time, the environment change again – for example, only leaves on the lowest branches of trees survived - then we might see a gene shift in population phenotypic characteristics over time producing shorter-necked giraffes. But this will take quite a few generations to reach a new balancing selection. In this way, evolution, through natural and sexual selection, is both blind and slow. That is, if environmental conditions change drastically, those lucky few mutants that have slightly better-fitting phenotypic traits will stand a better chance for being selected to survive than the rest of the population.</p><p> Historically, there was a different form of evolutionary battle going on between Charles Darwin and Jean-Baptiste Lamarck. The battle was one of evolutionary epistemology – that is, a battle between the survival of competing ideas or knowledge that would be selected for its cogency and soundness amongst the scientific communities. Lamarck&#39;s theory of &#39;Inheritance of Acquired Traits&#39; proposed that the traits a set of parents learned while surviving would somehow be transferred onto their progeny or offspring after reproduction (see giraffe example, above). In other words, Lamarck incorrectly believed that a set of parents&#39; learned self-improvements could somehow be passed onto their offspring. Although this theory falsely characterizes human evolution, and was not selected for continued existence/acceptance of the scientific communities, it may turn out to be the basic model for machine evolution. For the transmission of information – and behaviour – would follow quite systematically with machines. In other words, manufacturers use a model involving a Lamarckian model proposing &#39;the inheritance of acquired characters&#39;.</p><p> “ <a href="https://necsi.edu/what-lamarck-believed#:~:text=Lamarck%20is%20best%20known%20for,passed%20on%20to%20its%20offspring"><u>If an organism changes during life in order to adapt to its environment, those changes are passed on to its offspring</u></a> .”</p><p> Manufacturers of machines build on what they already have – a substrate. They don&#39;t reinvent the wheel – they improve upon it according to consumer and financial pressures. Hence, machine evolution follows Lamarckian principles which do not apply to human evolution. But just as the Ptolemaic geocentric astronomical system was replaced by the heliocentric version of Copernicus, Galileo, Brahe, and Newton, it can still be used by seafarers to correctly guide them while at sea. Perhaps Lamarck shall have his day after all with artificial life.</p><h2> <strong>Artificial Selection:</strong></h2><p> About 6 million years ago, humans descended with modification and split from a common ancestor with the chimpanzee, then to Australopithecines, then to the various Homo species, and finally to sapiens. Now, although humans, like every other form of flora and fauna on the planet, must compete for sex and survival, our evolutionary history is quite unique because somewhere along the way, throughout the span of 6 million years of descent with modification, we developed consciousness and sophisticated languages which allowed us to actively direct our <a href="https://jcer.com/index.php/jcj/article/view/51"><u>behaviour and gain greater control over our environments</u></a> . Rather than blindly responding to environmental pressures purely in accordance with hard-wired instincts, consciousness allowed our species the capacity to reflectively devise options and alternatives to varying environmental pressures. As a result, our species developed rich and varied cultures which capitalized on novel ideas and materials manipulation in an effort to improve our lives and increase the likelihood of surviving and reproducing. In this way, we moved, epistemically, from reacting blindly to environmental pressures, to acting reflectively. For the first time in our evolutionary past, we had developed the capacity to understand gaps in our explanatory schemas. And then we could take action by filling in those gaps with directed and novel ideas.</p><p> As such, within each culture, many artifacts were invented, developed, and refined; from hand axes, to the controlled use of fire, to the development of the wheel, to germ theory, and nuclear fusion. The so-called &#39;cultural explosion&#39; of the Upper or Late Pleistocene about 30,000 years ago ushered in enormous developments in tools, cooking methods, weaponry, housing, clothing, and just about every other manner of self-improvement. These artifacts – <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Selfish_Gene"><u>or memes, as Dawkins calls them</u></a> – have continued to develop as humans continue to culturally evolve.</p><p> After the advent of agriculture about 10,000 years ago, the world has never been the same. Knowing where your next meal is coming from freed up a lot of time for our ancestors to become adept at various tasks which later became occupations. Humans have become increasingly specialized in tasks ever since. Once particular flora and fauna became domesticated, it didn&#39;t take long to begin breeding techniques using <i>artificial selection</i> to attain particular desired qualities in plants and animals. Just look at the current size of bananas or corn from their much smaller progenitors.</p><p> Or consider our pet dogs; no matter how large, or how small, how cute, or how friendly, each of these owes its ancestry to the common grey wolf. In case you&#39;re wondering why a Corgi looks like it does, or a Chow, or a Great Dane, Chihuahua, or your basic mutt, it&#39;s because some ancestors thought it was a good idea to mate dogs with some desirable qualities with other dogs possessing other desirable qualities. </p><p><img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/lesswrong-2-0/image/upload/f_auto,q_auto/v1/mirroredImages/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/gaokjuixx0i8p5o3iuqi"><br> Ears of non-domesticated teosinte (above) and its domesticated variant, corn (below), selectively bred for human cultivation over ~10,000 years.</p><p> So now, for the first time in our existence, we were in control of phenotypic traits that were desired for some specific reason or other. For animal domestication and husbandry, dogs were bred so that their phenotypic traits would assist in hunting (Dachshund) or transportation (Huskie), or purely aesthetics (Pug).</p><p> Human-directed artificial selection has extended into the area of machine evolution as well. For millennia, humans have been tinkering, adjusting, and modifying machines to become more and more useful and beneficial to humankind. If we just look at the development of the television for example, we see many different ways in which the efficiency of such a device has been improved upon from analog to digital, from fuzzy screens to high-definition, from clunky and small to flat screen and huge, to prohibitively expensive to affordable, etc. The delivery service for such devices has also been vastly improved; from rabbit ears in the 50s and 60s, to antennas, to cable, to satellite, there has been a relatively steady increase in the development and improvement of the television since its inception. The same can be said for other types of machines as well – cars, planes, trains, appliances, etc. And of course, the exact same parallel can be drawn when talking about the evolution of machines like computers and robots.</p><p> We have seen significant improvements in both fields from the <a href="https://www.computerhistory.org/timeline/computers/"><u>earliest</u></a> times to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D_Vc_yDvU24"><u>now</u></a> . And this trajectory will continue until we reach a critical point at which machines will be capable of making their own modifications for subsequent generations.</p><h2> <strong>Technoselection:</strong></h2><p> Artificial selection (as far as we know) is unique to humans. We are the first species to recognize and use our own artifacts to take some degree of control over the selective pressures on our species. Will machines go through the same phase transition in their evolutionary pressures? Will they wrest control over their evolution as we did? Currently, artificial narrow intelligence (ANI) acts much like our Australopithecine ancestors – blindly and according to specific constraints. But just as we created artifacts to alter the direction of our own evolution, there may be a similar shift in machine evolution as we approach artificial general intelligence (AGI).</p><p> Technoselection is the term we give for the next evolution of evolutionary pressures. Roughly put, natural selection relies on slow, blind, natural processes; artificial selection additionally relies on the creation of artifacts by humans that shape our evolutionary process and that of our machines with intentional design; technoselection pressures arise as our technology increasingly plays a large role in shaping its evolutionary pressures. With technoselection, machines themselves play more and more significant roles in their own design and development. It seems to us that this evolutionary process may arise from AGI development (1) through increased ability to autonomously create new and useful technological objects and/or (2) through machines that develop a form of machine sentience, consciousness, or general self awareness.</p><p> There are divided camps concerning whether or not machines will be able to comprehend their own existence and, as such, reflectively modify themselves or other machines in accordance to their emerging value systems. At this point in time, the evolution of such machines <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.07103"><u>suggests a potential path towards self-awareness or apperception</u></a> . And should this occur, it will raise a number of pressing questions, not the least of which is: How will we know? What Turing Test will exist to make such determinations? What theory of mind will allow us to see into the black box of a techno-brain to know, even if only analogously, that they are becoming more like us? But it is at this point that we need to ask another very important question:</p><p> Why should a machine&#39;s emergent consciousness be similar to ours?</p><p> We are carbon-based; they are silicon-based. Airplanes don&#39;t flap their wings to fly like birds; this would be incredibly inefficient. And yet they fly. They fly faster, higher, and better than any birds ever could or will. For those who eschew the idea of machines developing human-like qualities, such as consciousness or sentience, is this not simply the anthropocentric emergence of a new form of logical bias and discrimination – an <i>ad machina</i> attack? At this point in time, we have little idea what it might be like for an AI machine to be conscious or sentient.</p><p> Further, more deeply pressing questions are going to need to be answered; and perhaps, sooner than later. For example, does such an ontological shift in <i>technoselection</i> mean that such machines have attained personhood status? And, as such, should they be afforded rights? Even though sexual reproduction would not be a driving factor for such machines, perhaps replication and modification would be. And whether or not such machines attain a level of consciousness, how much autonomy should be afforded such machines in the future modification of their systems? How much will and should we be able to control or contain such features of modification and self-improvement? If the macro programs of machine learning are survival and optimal functionality, how might this play out in projected scenarios involving greater and greater capacities for self-improvement – whether consciously attained or not? For <i>technoselection</i> can still occur whether the machines are consciously aware of their environments or not. Blind technoselection can also be as productive or destructive, controlled or uncontrolled, as reflective technoselection. Should technoselection emerge, are we prepared for it? Have we sufficiently anticipated and answered the questions above? Given the current states of both technical AI safety and AI Governance, the answer is clearly no.</p><h1> Conclusion: Machine Evolution &amp; Human Control</h1><p> <i>Samuel Butler died in 1902. The mechanical kingdom continued to proliferate, spawning a cascade of new species while others, such as steam engines, became extinct. With the advent of electronic digital computers the sense of anticipation – and interest in Butler&#39;s prophecies – was renewed. These machines showed signs of intelligence, and intelligence is a sign of life, even skeptics have agreed. But to ascribe a living intelligence to computers confuses causes with symptoms and was soon shown to be premature.</i></p><p> <i>Computers may turn out to be less important as an end product of technological evolution and more important as catalysts facilitating evolutionary processes through the incubation and propagation of self replicating filaments of code…..</i></p><p> <i>The origins of life as we know it – and life as we are creating it – are to be found in the cross-fertilization between self-sustaining metabolism and self replicating code. The coalescence of the kingdom of numbers with the kingdom of machines has been incubating for over three hundred years.</i></p><p> — Darwin Among The Machines: The Evolution Of Global Intelligence by George B. Dyson, 1997</p><p> This post is the beginning of Part III of the running sequence exploring <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/CFuqKkgEwQWCpdaZG/how-humanity-lost-control-and-humans-lost-liberty-from-our"><u>how humanity lost control and humans lost liberty</u></a> . It is in Part III that we explore some of the most important objects and structures that shape our current moment in the new age of AI darkness. This chapter has provided an initial exploration of how machines are evolving and the underlying processes that drive these processes.</p><p><br></p><p> We noted easily observable general trends in machine evolution which include (1) an increase in machine capabilities, (2) increases in computing machines, and (3) an increase in the role of machines in creating new machines. We then turned to a brief description of 5 core tools of biological evolution (not meant to be exhaustive but simply exploratory) including: (1) heritability, (2) reproduction, (3) mutation, (4) recombination, and (5) natural selection. From here, these processes of biological evolution were given machine analogs to machine evolution. We describe the concepts of machine inheritance, machine reproduction, machine mutation, and machine recombination. While we found this simple renaming appealing for these processes, we decided that natural selection needed a different treatment. For an analogy to natural selection we have chosen the term <i>artificial selection</i> which is driven in large part by human culture, human artifacts, and individual humans. We prefer artificial selection to “machine selection” or something like that because it hews closely to the distinction that Charles Darwin made and to make clear the continued role of humans (and our artifacts) in this process. Artificial selection also highlights the ways in which this selection pressure applies more generally to human artifacts. Human intention and human design have shifted the pace of evolution of artifacts, including machines, rocketing forward by comparison to biological evolution. However, the evolution of evolutionary selection processes does not end with artificial selection. We see an increasing role of machines in processes such as  machine design, machine reproduction, machine recombination, and artificial selection. Taken together these trends suggest the eventual appearance of a new form of evolutionary pressure that we call <i>technoselection.</i> In a world of technoselection, machines themselves will play a more direct role in shaping their own evolution, similar to the way in which humans have used artificial selection to shape their own evolution.<br></p><p> New generations of digital computing machines, for example, inherit mutated and recombined forms of hardware and software from previous generations. It is then through artificial selection, through human-aided differential rates of reproduction and survival rates from which the winning machines flourish and the losing machines go extinct. It is typically through competition and cooperation that both specific organisms and specific machines survive, reproduce, and evolve to adapt to their environment, lest selection leave them behind.</p><p> The analogy, however, is a work in progress. For this post, we identified three initial examples of the limitations of our analogy. There are of course others, but we believe these three examples draw attention to important distinctions that we would like to explore further. The first identified limitation is the absence of a clear analogue for sexual selection in machine evolutionary forces. Further, randomness or at least quasi-randomness play large roles in shaping evolution. This is less true for machine evolution which is much more a product of directed human, and more recently, machine-aided human design. That is, while biological organisms evolved, slowly, with small genetic mutations and recombinations being favored by natural selection over time, entirely new and completely modified machines are designed, built, and deployed deliberately by humans as a result of a myriad of factors in both their own nature and their environment.</p><p> It is this point of deviation from the randomness of biological evolution to the deliberateness of modification of machine evolution that we would like to linger upon in closing. In a broad sense, the whole endeavor of human technology has been to assist humans in wresting some control away from nature and making it their own. This process has begun to shift evolutionary processes away from natural selection and towards artificial selection.</p><p> Machine evolution is already a phenomenon that is not random but rather deliberate and directed by humans. And, as we have discussed earlier, machines themselves are beginning to play larger roles both in the reproduction of other machines and in designing and creating new machines. This trend suggests to us that technoselection, a point at which machines, at least in part, direct their own evolution, is likely near. And this trend makes clear the importance of <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/J8WHyePqhTwPzXEPw/keep-humans-in-the-loop#Using_AI_to_develop_AI"><u>keeping humans in the loop</u></a> as the selection pressures evolve in this direction.</p><p> One can see humanity&#39;s control of its machines slipping away, one generation of intelligent computing machines at a time.</p><h1> Additional Reading &amp; Next Steps</h1><p> While there is not much work in this direction, there are a few specific works in this direction that you may find interesting and that we have drawn from in researching and developing this post. These include</p><ul><li> Samuel Butler (1872) <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/jMZ8wcHNj8YgdGtKf/the-book-of-the-machines-chapter-8">&quot;The Book of the Machines&quot;</a> ;</li><li> <a href="https://kk.org/outofcontrol/"><u>Kevin Kelly (1995) &quot;Out of Control&quot;</u></a> ;</li><li> <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Darwin_among_the_Machines#Evolution_of_Global_Intelligence"><u>George Dyson (1997) &quot;Darwin Among the Machines&quot;</u></a> ;</li><li> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.16200"><u>Dan Hendrycks (2023) &quot;Natural Selection Favors AIs Over Humans&quot;</u></a> ;</li><li> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/PKeAzkKnbuwQeuGtJ/welcome-to-analogia-chapter-7"><u>Justin Bullock&#39;s earlier post in this sequence “Welcome to Analogia!”</u></a></li><li> <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1kXx-J68scFPHy-WZvbolGMMx4HdVzLxC/view?usp=share_link"><u>Justin Bullock and colleagues (2023) &quot;Introduction to The Oxford Handbook of AI Governance.&quot;</u></a></li></ul><p> As noted throughout, we hope to explore the idea of applying the general logic of biological evolution to other phenomena and objects as well. The evolution of organizations is the next topic in this sequence, and we also hope to further explore other topics such as technological evolution, software evolution, and AI evolution to better understand how the risks of AI and technological development can be examined with these lenses.</p><p></p><p> <i>**This post was developed by the Convergence Analysis team with the authors Justin Bullock, Christopher DiCarlo, and Elliot Mckernon each contributing substantively and substantially to the argument. We received multiple rounds of detailed feedback from David Kristofferson for which we are grateful. We appreciate the opportunity to explore these concepts as we seek to better understand the evolution of Artificial Intelligence and intelligent computing machines. We believe a deeper understanding of these topics will help us to better understand pathways to mitigating AI risks.**</i></p><p><br><br><br></p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/machine-evolution#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh/machine-evolution<guid ispermalink="false"> e6gg8S8AfJmwE8HLh</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin Bullock]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 19:29:53 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Is there a hard copy of the sequences available anywhere?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 7:01 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> Forgive me if there&#39;s an easily available answer, I have not been able to find it after several attempts. I know there is an ebook but I would like a hard copy of Rationality AZ or the original sequences as a (set of) books.</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/LehrFKxdyvDrWEuGx/is-there-a-hard-copy-of-the-sequences-available-anywhere#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/LehrFKxdyvDrWEuGx/is-there-a-hard-copy-of-the-sequences-available-anywhere<guid ispermalink="false"> LehrFKxdyvDrWEuGx</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Cole Wyeth]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 19:01:55 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon KDP AI content guidelines]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 6:36 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> Amazon updated the content guidelines for Kindle Direct Publishing to address AI and in the process attempted to define terms AI-generated and AI-assisted. Guidelines like this are how our society tries to engage with AI in the near-term.</p><blockquote><p> Artificial intelligence (AI) content (text, images, or translations)<br> We require you to inform us of AI-generated content (text, images, or translations) when you publish a new book or make edits to and republish an existing book through KDP. AI-generated images include cover and interior images and artwork. You are not required to disclose AI-assisted content. We distinguish between AI-generated and AI-assisted content as follows:</p><p> AI-generated: We define AI-generated content as text, images, or translations created by an AI-based tool. If you used an AI-based tool to create the actual content (whether text, images, or translations), it is considered &quot;AI-generated,&quot; even if you applied substantial edits afterwards.<br> AI-assisted: If you created the content yourself, and used AI-based tools to edit, refine, error-check, or otherwise improve that content (whether text or images), then it is considered &quot;AI-assisted&quot; and not “AI-generated.” Similarly, if you used an AI-based tool to brainstorm and generate ideas, but ultimately created the text or images yourself, this is also considered &quot;AI-assisted&quot; and not “AI-generated.” It is not necessary to inform us of the use of such tools or processes.</p><p> You are responsible for verifying that all AI-generated and/or AI-assisted content adheres to all content guidelines. For example, to confirm an AI-based tool did not create content based on copyrighted works, you&#39;re required to review and edit any AI tool outputs.</p></blockquote><p> What do you think about how Amazon defined the terms and makes those distinctions? Do you think they should change the definitions? Do you think there are other distinctions they should make?</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/4csaBfAgiyzrFXvEj/amazon-kdp-ai-content-guidelines#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/4csaBfAgiyzrFXvEj/amazon-kdp-ai-content-guidelines<guid ispermalink="false"> 4csaBfAgiyzrFXvEj</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[ChristianKl]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 18:36:09 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Case for AI Safety via Law]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 6:26 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> This post is to make the subject case more available and open to comment. A paper with the above title is currently languishing in arXiv limbo but available in <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1CzDGBtjY92qQujLKYysbaIF1agoDoUJE/view?usp=sharing">Google Docs</a> . I was surprised to see my last and only postings to LessWrong were made on this very subject in 2010 as comments to the thread &quot;Why not just write failsafe rules into the superintelligent machine?&quot;</p><p> Unfortunately (IMO) this approach to AI alignment doesn&#39;t seem to have gained much traction in the past 13 years. The paper does cite, however, 15 precedents that show there is some support. (Anthropic&#39;s <i>Constitutional AI</i> and John Nay&#39;s <i>Law Informs Code</i> are two good recent examples.)</p><p> The following reproduces the <strong>Summary of Argument</strong> and <strong>Conclusion</strong> sections from the paper.</p><p> The claim being argued is &quot; <i><strong>Effective legal systems are the best way to address AI safety</strong></i> .&quot;</p><p> <strong>4 Summary of Argument</strong></p><p> <i><strong>4.1 Law is the standard, time-tested, best practice for maintaining</strong></i><br> <i><strong>order in societies of intelligent agents.</strong></i></p><p> Law has been the primary way of maintaining functional, cohesive societies for thousands of years. It is how humans establish, communicate, and understand what actions are required, permissible, and prohibited in social spheres. Substantial experience exists in drafting, enacting, enforcing, litigating, and maintaining rules in contexts that include public law, private contracts, and the many others noted in this brief. Law will naturally apply to new species of intelligent systems and facilitate safety and value alignment for all.</p><p> <i><strong>4.2 Law is scrutable to humans and other intelligent agents.</strong></i></p><p> Unlike AI safety proposals where rules are learned via examples and encoded in artificial (or biological) neural networks, laws are intended to be understood by humans and machines. Although laws can be quite complex, such codified rules are significantly more scrutable than rules learned through induction. The transparent (white box) nature of law provides a critical advantage over opaque (black box) neural network alternatives.</p><p> <i><strong>4.3 Law reflects consensus values.</strong></i></p><p> Democratically developed law is intimately linked and essentially equivalent to consensus ethics. Both are human inventions intended to facilitate the wellbeing of individuals and the collective. They represent shared values culturally determined through rational consideration and negotiation. They reflect the wisdom of crowds accumulated over time—not preferences that vary from person to person and are often based on emotion, irrational ideologies, confusion, or psychopathy. Ethical values provide the virtue core of legal systems and reflect the “spirit of the law.” Consequentialist shells surround such cores and specify the “letter of the law.” This relationship between law and ethics makes law a natural solution for human-AI value alignment. A minority of AIs and people, however powerful, cannot game laws to achieve selfish ends.</p><p> <i><strong>4.4 Legal systems are responsive to changes in the environment and changes in moral values.</strong></i></p><p> By utilizing legal mechanisms to consolidate values and update them over time, human and AI values can remain aligned indefinitely as values, technologies, and environmental conditions change. Thus law provides a practical implementation of Yudkowsky&#39;s (2004) Coherent Extrapolated Volition by allowing values to evolve that are wise, aspirational, convergent, coherent, suitably extrapolated, and properly interpreted.</p><p> <i><strong>4.5 Legal systems restrict overly rapid change.</strong></i></p><p> Legal processes provide checks and balances against overly rapid change to values and laws. Such checks are particularly important when legal change can occur at AI speeds. Legal systems and laws must adapt quickly enough to address the urgency of issues that arise but not so quickly as to risk dire consequences. Laws should be based on careful analysis and effective simulation and the system be able to quickly detect and correct problems found after implementation. New technologies and methods should be introduced to make legal processing as efficient as possible without removing critical checks and balances.</p><p> <i><strong>4.6 Laws are context sensitive, hierarchical, and scalable.</strong></i></p><p> Laws apply to contexts ranging from international, national, state, and local governance to all manner of other social contracts. Contexts can overlap, be hierarchical, or have other relationships. Humans have lived under this regime for millennia and are able to understand which laws apply and take precedence over others based on contexts (eg, jurisdictions, organization affiliations, contracts in force). Artificial intelligent systems will be able to manage the multitude of contexts and applicable laws by identifying, loading, and applying appropriate legal corpora for applicable contexts. For example, AIs (like humans) will understand that crosschecking is permitted in hockey games but not outside the arena. They will know when to apply rules of the road versus rules of the sea. They will know when the laws of chess apply versus rules of Go. They will know their rights relative to every software agent, tool, and service they interface with.</p><p> <i><strong>4.7 AI Safety via Law can address the full range of AI safety risks, from systems that are narrowly focused to those having general intelligence or even superintelligence.</strong></i></p><p> Enacting and enforcing appropriate laws, and instilling law-abiding values in AIs and humans, can mitigate risks spanning all levels of AI capability—from narrow AI to AGI and ASI. If intelligent agents stray from the law, effective detection and enforcement must occur.</p><p> Even the catastrophic vision of smarter-than-human-intelligence articulated by Yudkowsky (2022, 2023) and others (Bostrom, 2014; Russell, 2019) can be avoided by effective implementation of AISVL. It may require that the strongest version of the instrumental convergence thesis (which they rely on) is not correct. Appendix A suggests some reasons why AI convergence to dangerous values is not inevitable.</p><p> AISVL applies to all intelligent systems regardless of their underlying design, cognitive architecture, and technology. It is immaterial whether an AI is implemented using biology, deep learning, constructivist AI (Johnston, 2023), semantic networks, quantum computers, positronics, or other methods. All intelligent systems must comply with applicable laws regardless of their particular values, preferences, beliefs, and how they are wired.</p><p> <strong>5 Conclusion</strong></p><p> Although its practice has often been flawed, law is a natural solution for maintaining social safety and value alignment. All intelligent agents— biological and mechanical—must know the law, strive to abide by it, and be subject to effective intervention when violated. The essential equivalence and intimate link between consensus ethics and democratic law provide a philosophical and practical basis for legal systems that marry values and norms (“virtue cores”) with rules that address real world situations (“consequentialist shells”). In contrast to other AI safety proposals, AISVL requires AIs “do as we legislate, not as we do.”</p><p> Advantages of AISVL include its leveraging of time-tested standard practice; scrutability to all intelligent agents; reflection of consensus values; responsiveness to changes in the environment and in moral values; restrictiveness of overly rapid change; context sensitivity, hierarchical structure, and scalability; and applicability to safety risks posed by narrow, general, and even superintelligent AIs.</p><p> For the future safety and wellbeing of all sentient systems, work should occur in earnest to improve legal processes and laws so they are more robust, fair, nimble, efficient, consistent, understandable, accepted, and complied with. (Legal frameworks outside of public law may be effective to this end.) Humans are in dire need of such improvements to counter the dangers that we pose to the biosphere and to each other. It is not clear if advanced AI will be more or less dangerous than humans. Law is critical for both.</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oi2YxRddakosnnbGX/a-case-for-ai-safety-via-law#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/oi2YxRddakosnnbGX/a-case-for-ai-safety-via-law<guid ispermalink="false"> oi2YxRddakosnnbGX</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[JWJohnston]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Erdős Problems in Algorithmic Probability]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 4:44 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> <strong>Motivation:</strong></p><p> Before the Pandemic of 2020, I had a number of constructive discussions with several neuroscientists including Konrad Körding, a computational neuroscientist and pioneer exploring <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-022-35659-7">connections between deep learning and human learning</a> , and Alex Gomez-Marin, an expert on <a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/pdf/S0896-6273(16)31040-6.pdf">behavioural neuroscience</a> , on the hypothetical boundary between Human and Machine Learning. One promising avenue for making progress along these lines appeared to be Kolmogorov&#39;s theory of Algorithmic Probability [4] which <a href="https://sashakolpakov.wordpress.com/">Alexander Kolpakov</a> (Sasha) and myself recently used to probe this boundary, motivated in large part by open problems in Machine Learning for Cryptography [1].</p><p> However, more progress appears to be possible based on the analyses of Marcus Hutter and Shane Legg who established that Algorithmic Probability defines the epistemic limit of Machine Learning [3]. In the hopes of developing more powerful tools in Algorithmic Probability for probing the epistemic limits of Machine Learning, Sasha and myself propose cash prizes for deriving two mathematical laws using Algorithmic Probability.</p><p> <strong>Erdős Problems in Algorithmic Probability:</strong></p><ol><li> <i>Benford&#39;s Law</i> , which Terrence Tao himself admitted lacks a satisfactory explanation: <a href="https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2009/07/03/benfords-law-zipfs-law-and-the-pareto-distribution/">https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2009/07/03/benfords-law-zipfs-law-and-the-pareto-distribution/</a></li><li> <i>Atle Selberg&#39;s Identity,</i> which proved crucial in Paul Erdős&#39; and Atle Selberg&#39;s elementary proof of the Prime Number Theorem:</li></ol><p> <span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\psi(x) \ln(x) + \sum_{p \leq x} \ln(p) \psi(\frac{x}{p}) = 2x \ln (x) + \mathcal{O}(x)"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.519em;">ψ</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi MJXc-space1"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">ln</span></span><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char"></span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo MJXc-space2"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.298em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">+</span></span> <span class="mjx-munderover MJXc-space2"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-size1-R" style="padding-top: 0.519em; padding-bottom: 0.519em;">∑</span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sub" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: -0.439em; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-texatom" style=""><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">p</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">≤</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-mi MJXc-space1"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">ln</span></span><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char"></span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">p</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.519em;">ψ</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mfrac"><span class="mjx-box MJXc-stacked" style="width: 0.546em; padding: 0px 0.12em;"><span class="mjx-numerator" style="font-size: 70.7%; width: 0.772em; top: -1.159em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span></span> <span class="mjx-denominator" style="font-size: 70.7%; width: 0.772em; bottom: -0.707em;"><span class="mjx-mi" style=""><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">p</span></span></span><span style="border-bottom: 1.3px solid; top: -0.296em; width: 0.546em;" class="mjx-line"></span></span><span style="height: 1.32em; vertical-align: -0.5em;" class="mjx-vsize"></span></span><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo MJXc-space3"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.077em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">=</span></span> <span class="mjx-mn MJXc-space3"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">2</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi MJXc-space1"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">ln</span></span><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char"></span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo MJXc-space2"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.298em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">+</span></span> <span class="mjx-texatom MJXc-space2"><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-cal-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">O</span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span></span></span></span></span></span> <style>.mjx-chtml {display: inline-block; line-height: 0; text-indent: 0; text-align: left; text-transform: none; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 100%; font-size-adjust: none; letter-spacing: normal; word-wrap: normal; word-spacing: normal; white-space: nowrap; float: none; direction: ltr; max-width: none; max-height: none; min-width: 0; min-height: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; padding: 1px 0}
.MJXc-display {display: block; text-align: center; margin: 1em 0; padding: 0}
.mjx-chtml[tabindex]:focus, body :focus .mjx-chtml[tabindex] {display: inline-table}
.mjx-full-width {text-align: center; display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em}
.mjx-math {display: inline-block; border-collapse: separate; border-spacing: 0}
.mjx-math * {display: inline-block; -webkit-box-sizing: content-box!important; -moz-box-sizing: content-box!important; box-sizing: content-box!important; text-align: left}
.mjx-numerator {display: block; text-align: center}
.mjx-denominator {display: block; text-align: center}
.MJXc-stacked {height: 0; position: relative}
.MJXc-stacked > * {position: absolute}
.MJXc-bevelled > * {display: inline-block}
.mjx-stack {display: inline-block}
.mjx-op {display: block}
.mjx-under {display: table-cell}
.mjx-over {display: block}
.mjx-over > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-under > * {padding-left: 0px!important; padding-right: 0px!important}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sup {display: block}
.mjx-stack > .mjx-sub {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presup {display: block}
.mjx-prestack > .mjx-presub {display: block}
.mjx-delim-h > .mjx-char {display: inline-block}
.mjx-surd {vertical-align: top}
.mjx-surd + .mjx-box {display: inline-flex}
.mjx-mphantom * {visibility: hidden}
.mjx-merror {background-color: #FFFF88; color: #CC0000; border: 1px solid #CC0000; padding: 2px 3px; font-style: normal; font-size: 90%}
.mjx-annotation-xml {line-height: normal}
.mjx-menclose > svg {fill: none; stroke: currentColor; overflow: visible}
.mjx-mtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mlabeledtr {display: table-row}
.mjx-mtd {display: table-cell; text-align: center}
.mjx-label {display: table-row}
.mjx-box {display: inline-block}
.mjx-block {display: block}
.mjx-span {display: inline}
.mjx-char {display: block; white-space: pre}
.mjx-itable {display: inline-table; width: auto}
.mjx-row {display: table-row}
.mjx-cell {display: table-cell}
.mjx-table {display: table; width: 100%}
.mjx-line {display: block; height: 0}
.mjx-strut {width: 0; padding-top: 1em}
.mjx-vsize {width: 0}
.MJXc-space1 {margin-left: .167em}
.MJXc-space2 {margin-left: .222em}
.MJXc-space3 {margin-left: .278em}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-display {display: table!important}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-inline {display: inline!important; margin-right: -1px}
.mjx-test.mjx-test-default {display: block!important; clear: both}
.mjx-ex-box {display: inline-block!important; position: absolute; overflow: hidden; min-height: 0; max-height: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0; width: 1px; height: 60ex}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-left-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: left}
.mjx-test-inline .mjx-right-box {display: inline-block; width: 0; float: right}
.mjx-test-display .mjx-right-box {display: table-cell!important; width: 10000em!important; min-width: 0; max-width: none; padding: 0; border: 0; margin: 0}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-R {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-I {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-B {font-family: monospace; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-unknown-BI {font-family: monospace; font-style: italic; font-weight: bold}
.MJXc-TeX-ams-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R,MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx,MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R,MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-frak-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx,MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-BI {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI,MJXc-TeX-math-BIx,MJXc-TeX-math-BIw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R,MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx,MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-sans-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I,MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix,MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-script-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R,MJXc-TeX-script-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-type-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R,MJXc-TeX-type-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-cal-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R,MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B,MJXc-TeX-main-Bx,MJXc-TeX-main-Bw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I,MJXc-TeX-main-Ix,MJXc-TeX-main-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-main-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R,MJXc-TeX-main-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-math-I {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I,MJXc-TeX-math-Ix,MJXc-TeX-math-Iw}
.MJXc-TeX-size1-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R,MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size2-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R,MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size3-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R,MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-size4-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R,MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-R {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R,MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw}
.MJXc-TeX-vec-B {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx,MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-R; src: local('MathJax_AMS'), local('MathJax_AMS-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-ams-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_AMS-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_AMS-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_AMS-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-B; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic Bold'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-R; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-B; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur Bold'), local('MathJax_Fraktur-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Fraktur'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-frak-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Fraktur-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BI; src: local('MathJax_Math BoldItalic'), local('MathJax_Math-BoldItalic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIx; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-weight: bold; font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-BIw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-BoldItalic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-R; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-B; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Bold'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bx; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-I; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif Italic'), local('MathJax_SansSerif-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Ix; src: local('MathJax_SansSerif'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-sans-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_SansSerif-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-R; src: local('MathJax_Script'), local('MathJax_Script-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-script-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Script-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Script-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Script-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-R; src: local('MathJax_Typewriter'), local('MathJax_Typewriter-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-type-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Typewriter-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-R; src: local('MathJax_Caligraphic'), local('MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-cal-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Caligraphic-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-B; src: local('MathJax_Main Bold'), local('MathJax_Main-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-I; src: local('MathJax_Main Italic'), local('MathJax_Main-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Main'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-R; src: local('MathJax_Main'), local('MathJax_Main-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-main-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Main-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Main-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Main-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-I; src: local('MathJax_Math Italic'), local('MathJax_Math-Italic')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Ix; src: local('MathJax_Math'); font-style: italic}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-math-Iw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Math-Italic.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Math-Italic.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Math-Italic.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-R; src: local('MathJax_Size1'), local('MathJax_Size1-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size1-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size1-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size1-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size1-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-R; src: local('MathJax_Size2'), local('MathJax_Size2-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size2-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size2-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size2-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size2-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-R; src: local('MathJax_Size3'), local('MathJax_Size3-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size3-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size3-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size3-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size3-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-R; src: local('MathJax_Size4'), local('MathJax_Size4-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-size4-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Size4-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Size4-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Size4-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-R; src: local('MathJax_Vector'), local('MathJax_Vector-Regular')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Rw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Regular.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Regular.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Regular.otf') format('opentype')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-B; src: local('MathJax_Vector Bold'), local('MathJax_Vector-Bold')}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bx; src: local('MathJax_Vector'); font-weight: bold}
@font-face {font-family: MJXc-TeX-vec-Bw; src /*1*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/eot/MathJax_Vector-Bold.eot'); src /*2*/: url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/woff/MathJax_Vector-Bold.woff') format('woff'), url('https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/mathjax/2.7.2/fonts/HTML-CSS/TeX/otf/MathJax_Vector-Bold.otf') format('opentype')}
</style></p><p>which is derived using elementary number theory in [5] where <span><span class="mjpage"><span class="mjx-chtml"><span class="mjx-math" aria-label="\psi(x) = \sum_{p \leq x} \ln p"><span class="mjx-mrow" aria-hidden="true"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.519em;">ψ</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">(</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.446em; padding-bottom: 0.593em;">)</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo MJXc-space3"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.077em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">=</span></span> <span class="mjx-munderover MJXc-space3"><span class="mjx-base"><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-size1-R" style="padding-top: 0.519em; padding-bottom: 0.519em;">∑</span></span></span> <span class="mjx-sub" style="font-size: 70.7%; vertical-align: -0.439em; padding-right: 0.071em;"><span class="mjx-texatom" style=""><span class="mjx-mrow"><span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">p</span></span> <span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">≤</span></span> <span class="mjx-mi"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.298em;">x</span></span></span></span></span></span> <span class="mjx-mi MJXc-space1"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-main-R" style="padding-top: 0.372em; padding-bottom: 0.372em;">ln</span></span><span class="mjx-mo"><span class="mjx-char"></span></span> <span class="mjx-mi MJXc-space1"><span class="mjx-char MJXc-TeX-math-I" style="padding-top: 0.225em; padding-bottom: 0.446em;">p</span></span></span></span></span></span></span> , though its true meaning remains a mathematical mystery [6,7].</p><p> <strong>Submission guidelines and Monetary Prizes:</strong></p><p> The challenge is named in honour of Paul Erdős whose probabilistic method has provided Sasha and myself with a number of important insights, and the cash prize is 1000.00 USD for the best submission under 30 pages in each category. The main evaluation criteria are clarity, correctness and concision.</p><p> Submissions typeset in LaTeX must be sent to Alexander Kolpakov, Managing Editor of the Journal of Experimental Mathematics, before September 17, 2024: <a href="mailto:kolpakov.alexander@gmail.com"><strong>kolpakov.alexander@gmail.com</strong></a></p><p> Prizes shall be awarded on January 1st, 2025.</p><p> <strong>References:</strong></p><ol><li> Kolpakov, Alexander &amp; Rocke, Aidan. On the impossibility of discovering a formula for primes using AI. arXiv: 2308.10817. 2023.</li><li> AN Kolmogorov. Combinatorial foundations of information theory and the calculus of probabilities. Russian Math. Surveys, 1983.</li><li> Marcus Hutter. A theory of universal intelligence based on algorithmic complexity.<br> 2000. https://arxiv.org/abs/cs/0004001.</li><li> P. Grünwald and P. Vitanyí. Algorithmic information theory. arXiv:0809.2754, 2008.</li><li> Selberg, Atle (1949), &quot;An elementary proof of the prime-number theorem&quot;, <i>Ann. of Math.</i> , 2, <strong>50</strong> (2): 305–313, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doi_(identifier)">doi</a> : <a href="https://doi.org/10.2307%2F1969455">10.2307/1969455</a></li><li> Basj (https://mathoverflow.net/users/85239/basj), Ideas in the elementary proof of the prime number theorem (Selberg / Erdős), URL (version: 2017-01-16): <a href="https://mathoverflow.net/q/259698">https://mathoverflow.net/q/259698</a></li><li> Wikipedia contributors. &quot;Selberg&#39;s identity.&quot; <i>Wikipedia, The Free Encyclopedia</i> . Wikipedia, The Free Encyclopedia, 21 Aug. 2023. Web. 11 Sep. 2023.</li><li> Tao, Terrence. Benford&#39;s law, Zipf&#39;s law, and the Pareto distribution. <i>What&#39;s new.</i> 2009. https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2009/07/03/benfords-law-zipfs-law-and-the-pareto-distribution/<br></li></ol><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/cqs3XHkYaamy93cx8/erdos-problems-in-algorithmic-probability-1#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/cqs3XHkYaamy93cx8/erdos-problems-in-algorithmic-probability-1<guid ispermalink="false"> cqs3XHkYaamy93cx8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Aidan Rocke]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 17:47:37 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[PSA: The community is in Berkeley/Oakland, not "the Bay Area"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 3:59 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> Posting this because I recently had a conversation that went like this:</p><p> <strong>Friend:</strong> Hey, you used to live in SF. Is there any rationalist stuff actually happening in San Francisco? There don&#39;t seem to be many events, or even that many aspiring rationalists living here. What&#39;s up with that? [Paraphrased. I&#39;ve had similar versions of this conversation more than once.]</p><p> <strong>Me:</strong> Something we realized living there is that SF actually suffers the same brain drain as most other cities, because everyone just goes to Berkeley/Oakland.</p><p> The same way people move from the East Coast or elsewhere to Berkeley, they move from the rest of the Bay Area to Berkeley. Actually, they do it <i>even more</i> , because moving to Berkeley is easier when you already live pretty close by.</p><p> And you don&#39;t figure this out until you move there, because people who live outside the Bay Area think of it as being all the same place. But the 45 minute train ride really matters when it comes to events and socializing, as it turns out.</p><p> <strong>Friend:</strong> That sounds so inconvenient for people who have jobs in the city or South Bay!</p><p> <strong>Me:</strong> Sure is! I don&#39;t have a super-solid answer for this, except that 1) Lots of people actually just do awful, awful commutes, because having a real, in-person community is that valuable to them, as bad as commuting is. 2) A surprising fraction of the community works at rationalist/rationalist-adjacent nonprofits, most of which are actually located in the East Bay. Plus, 3) in a post-COVID world, more people can work remote or partly remote. So you can choose to live where your community is... which is Berkeley... even though it is crazy expensive.</p><p> I don&#39;t actually live in the Bay Area anymore, so I don&#39;t have the most up-to-date information on where events are happening and things. But it seems from what I hear from folks still there that it&#39;s still broadly true that East Bay is where things are happening, and other parts of the area have much less of the community.</p><p> If you&#39;re thinking about moving to the Bay in part for the rationality community, take this into account!</p><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/esaaewdyr72Ae2tvP/psa-the-community-is-in-berkeley-oakland-not-the-bay-area#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/esaaewdyr72Ae2tvP/psa-the-community-is-in-berkeley-oakland-not-the-bay-area<guid ispermalink="false"> esaaewdyr72Ae2tvP</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[maia]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 15:59:47 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[A Bat and Ball made me Sad]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 1:48 PM GMT<br/><br/><p> &#39;A bat and a ball cost $110 in total.</p><p>球棒比球贵 100 美元。</p><p>球的价格是多少？</p><p><strong>答案是5美元。</strong></p><p><strong>请在下面的空白处输入数字5。</strong></p><p> $_____&#39;<br><br> That question is from one of 59 new studies ( <i>N</i> = 72,310) which focus primarily on the “bat and ball problem,&quot; found in <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0010027723000148?">The formation and revision of intuitions - ScienceDirect</a> by Andrew Meyer and Shane Frederic.<br><br> 23% of respondents failed to give the correct answer.<br><br> I don&#39;t have anything insightful to say but wanted to share because it seems worth knowing.<br><br> Additionally, I&#39;m not exactly sure how (and how much) I should update about this.<br><br> (Edit: I initially posted the wrong question)</p><br/><br/><a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/4d8dbuAKA39QDiyw7/a-bat-and-ball-made-me-sad#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/4d8dbuAKA39QDiyw7/a-bat-and-ball-made-me-sad<guid ispermalink="false"> 4d8dbuAKA39QDiyw7</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Darren McKee]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 13:48:25 GMT</pubDate> </item><item><title><![CDATA[Focus on the Hardest Part First]]></title><description><![CDATA[Published on September 11, 2023 7:53 AM GMT<br/><br/><p>这是一些明显的建议。</p><p>我认为在进行人工智能对齐<sup class="footnote-ref"><a href="#fn-MXJWnQnSt4keXsdet-1" id="fnref-MXJWnQnSt4keXsdet-1">[1]</a></sup>时，一个常见的失败模式是不首先关注问题的困难部分。在制定研究议程以及处理任何具体研究议程时，这是一个问题。给定一个研究议程，通常有很多问题你知道如何取得进展。但盲目地做看似容易处理的事情并不是一个好主意。</p><p>假设我们正在制定一个关于解决问题 A、B 和 C 的研究议程。我们知道，如果我们找到 A、B 和 C 的解决方案，我们就能解决对齐问题。然而，如果我们连一个子问题都解决不了，议程就注定失败。如果 C 看起来是一个非常难的问题，你不确定自己能否解决，那么放弃 C 并转而解决问题 A 将是一个坏主意，因为 A 看起来更容易管理。</p><p>如果解决A需要花费大量的时间和精力，如果最终无法解决C，那么所有的时间和精力都将被浪费。当A有紧密的反击循环时尤其令人担忧，这样你就会不断地感觉自己正在取得进步。或者当从事 A 工作通常很有趣时。</p><p>当然，如果您希望这能帮助您解决 C，或者至少为您提供有关其易处理性的更多信息，那么首先研究 A 是有意义的。一般版本是通过考虑您需要解决的大量问题来说明的。在这种情况下，关注那些将为您提供有助于解决许多其他问题的信息的问题<em>可能</em>非常有用。但即便如此，您也不应该忽视可能阻碍您前进的难题。</p><p>结论是这两件事有很大不同：</p><ul><li>当 C 是潜在的阻碍者时，将解决 A 作为工具性子目标，以便在 C 上取得进展。</li><li>避免 C，因为它看起来很难，而致力于 A，因为它看起来很容易处理。 </li></ul><hr class="footnotes-sep"><section class="footnotes"><ol class="footnotes-list"><li id="fn-MXJWnQnSt4keXsdet-1" class="footnote-item"><p>尽管我预计这是一个普遍存在的问题，到处都会出现。 <a href="#fnref-MXJWnQnSt4keXsdet-1" class="footnote-backref">↩︎</a></p></li></ol></section><br/><br/> <a href="https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Eav2BizSejDcztFC8/focus-on-the-hardest-part-first#comments">讨论</a>]]>;</description><link/> https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/Eav2BizSejDcztFC8/focus-on-the-hardest-part-first<guid ispermalink="false"> Eav2BizSejDcztFC8</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Johannes C. Mayer]]></dc:creator><pubDate> Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:53:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>